I feel hungry now.
Let's go.
Joon can order one jjajangmyeon...
and four bowls of rice,
and we can take the extra sauce.
- That's how it works?
- That's perfect.
(Laughing)
(He just laughs.)
Our dear Joon.
- One is one
- It's not two
(Everyone but Joon is in agreement.)
(Looking carefully)
Those flowers are really pretty.
What flower is this?
- A pretty flower.
- They're pretty.
(Flanders poppy flowers
brighten the quiet roadside.)
This is what I like
about the countryside. Its nature.
(Brisket Jjamppong)
- This is it.
- It's brisket jjamppong.
- Gosh.
- What's this?
- My word.
- It's insane.
There's brisket.
Brisket jjamppong?
Brisket jjamppong. That's crazy.
You're the best of all jjamppong
Places like this
don't scrimp on ingredients.
The best of all jjamppong
They don't scrimp.
The jjamppong must be really good...
- because...
- I'll sit here.
it costs ten dollars...
while the tangsuyuk
costs 13 dollars.
- That's the small serving.
- Yes.
That's impossible.
Joon could order a bowl for himself.
(Only Joon will have a full belly.)
Right now,
you have just ten dollars.
- Joon.
- Yes.
Don't be too discouraged.
- Okay.
We came to a famous restaurant,
- so you deserve a taste.
- That's right.
- We should taste it.
- Yes.
That's right.
This mission is...
Guess the Song.
- What?
- "Guess the Song?"
What's the title?
Who sang the song?
Is that it? Okay.
"Guess the Song?"
We'll play a song backward.
- Name the song and singer.
- We can't do that.
We'll give you
2.5 dollars per correct answer.
- Do you have like ten songs?
- Yes.
Do we fend for ourselves?
- You're in it alone.
- I see.
If you get two right,
you can only afford makgeolli.
You can have jjajangmyeon too.
Just so you know, the team...
that test-tasted the food here...
"Test-tasted."
- "Test-tasted."
You test-tasted the food.
Good for you.
(He mastered mocking Jong Min.)
(Now he's mocking the director.)
You're an expert at mocking others.
I am. That short nap...
maximized my energy!
(They're hyped because of
their relatively relaxed schedule.)
- "Guess the Song."
- This is fun.
- All right.
- If I were you, I'd drop him.
Seriously. I really would.
(Drop him from the show, Jong Hyun.)
Why are you putting up
with this kind of treatment?
Hey. It's like...
No!
Don't drop me.
(I don't want to drop out
of the show.)
- Gosh, he's no joke.
- Well...
(Director Joo,
leave Se Yoon's body.)
A while ago, Se Yoon sang...
- Yes.
- IU's song backward.
- He made it entertaining.
- Yes.
- Which song was it?
- It was "Marshmallow."
How did you sing it?
(Mallow marsh)
Is that how it will go?
(The marshmallow might melt
from the pressure.)
Mallow marsh
(Getting a reality check)
- He's full of energy today
- It love I
(He finishes it
with the perfect ending.)
- Do you want to do a practice run?
- My gosh. "Mallow marsh."
Here's a practice round.
This is a practice round.
Quiet down.
We have songs
from the 1990s, 2000s, 2010s,
and 2020s.
- That's neat.
- Okay.
Whoever wins the practice round...
- will get to choose the era.
- From that era?
- Okay.
- From the 1990s?
How about a dollar for this round?
To get us in good spirits.
- Yes.
- It will keep us in good spirits.
- Yes. We can't use it anyway.
- Yes, you should.
We can't order any food with that.
- We'll give you two dollars.
- Okay.
- Gosh, two dollars.
- Oh, my.
Then Joon will probably know better
and not participate.
- Right. Don't play.
- I'll donate it.
- You can go for it.
- Yes.
- All right.
Play the song.
(The practice round starts.)
(The song sounds a bit strange.)
- I...
- I got it.
- DinDin.
- "Lucifer."
- That's it.
- Whose song is it?
- I got it.
- SHINee.
That's correct.
Correct.
- Okay.
- That was amazing.
(They were listening to the song
in reverse from the end.)
(What if the song was played
the right way?)
(It's the song we recognize.)
(As DinDin won the practice round,)
(he will pick the era
for the next song.)
- Hey, but...
- I picked up on the synthesizer.
- You recognized the synthesizer.
- Gosh.
- I picked up on that.
- He's a musician, indeed.
Okay. I won two dollars.
- Yes, two dollars.
- That was amazing.
- Okay.
- Gosh, if I win one more dollar,
I can buy makgeolli.
By the way,
it didn't sound completely off.
- It had a similar vibe.
- Yes, it did.
- The melody sounded similar.
- Yes. I got the vibe.
- I just didn't know this song.
- I...
- I can follow my gut.
- All right.
- Which era?
- DinDin, which era will you pick?
- You have 2 dollars now?
- Pick the 2000s.
- I'll pick 2020s.
- You'll pick 2020s?
The 2020s.
- I don't know songs from this era.
- I guess this is my break.
I don't think
I can recognize them in reverse.
All right. Play the song.
(Here's the first question.)
(He doesn't know the song,
but he's getting excited.)
- I got it.
- DinDin.
What song is it?
- I have no idea.
- I doubt I even know this song.
Three, two,
- I won't say it.
- one.
- Out of time.
- Let's keep listening to it.
- We'll keep playing it.
(Humming)
- I got it.
Darn it.
"Dynamite" by BTS.
- Gosh, that's not it.
- That's it.
- Really? That's...
- Correct.
Yes. I wasn't sure...
(As the lyrics are the same
forward and backward,)
(he figured out the title
right away from this part.)
Yes. I wasn't sure whether or not
this was "Butter" or "Dynamite."
(I got confused with "Butter.")
Gosh,
that was "Dynamite" in reverse?
- Look at him swaying his hips.
- Wasn't that too fast?
Look at his hips.
(His movements are robust
given his medical condition.)
It's the lymph node dance.
- My gosh.
- Check out his lymph node dance.
- There it is.
- Ta-da.
- Great. "Dynamite."
- My gosh.
I won 2.5 dollars. Let's go.
- I can pick the era I want.
- Gosh, I knew it.
Yes.
- Gosh.
- Gosh, I knew it.
- I could've gotten this right.
- Yes.
The era I want is the 1990s.
- Okay.
- The 1990s.
- Okay. Let's go.
I have to get this right for sure.
(This is the perfect era
for the older members)
- Gosh, this is hard.
- This is it for me.
- It's the 1990s.
- This is fun.
- Ballad songs will be harder.
- All right.
- Right?
- Yes.
Play the song.
(The second question)
(Flinching)
- I got it.
- Se Yoon.
- He recognized the song?
- I got it.
Clon's song.
- Two...
"First Love."
("First Love" by Clon)
- Wrong.
- He's fixated on Clon.
- No. I'll keep listening to it.
- Wrong.
What?
- I got it.
- Joon.
- What?
- "Pure Love" by KOYOTE.
Wrong.
- I got it.
- Seon Ho.
"Change" by Lee Jung Hyun.
- Wrong.
- "Change" by Lee Jung Hyun.
- I got it.
- Sae Ho.
- "Come" by Lee Jung Hyun.
That's the one.
("Come" by Lee Jung Hyun)
(That's the one.)
- That's it.
- Correct.
(A timid way
of expressing his anger)
- So...
- Hold on. Mister.
- Mister.
- You know what?
- You gave a hint with your face.
- Mister!
"Lee Jung Hyun's..." What was that?
"Change." "Oh, no."
(Director Joo gave a hint
with his facial expression?)
(When Seon Ho's answer was close
to the correct answer,)
(he failed to control
his facial expression.)
(He practically gave away
the answer.)
Are you seriously going to do that?
(He doesn't care.)
Why did you do that, seriously?
- What was that?
- Mister.
That was so obvious.
- You gave away the answer.
- We just had to read his face.
This game is
about reading your face then.
This game becomes...
- Read Jong Hyun's Face.
- I knew the answer.
(He has no excuse to offer.)
- My gosh. I'll be careful.
- This is...
- Gosh, I was close.
- You know what?
I have enough money
for jjajangmyeon.
- All right.
- That's amazing.
Let me pick the era again.
I'll pick the 2000s.
- You picked the 2000s.
- Okay, the 2000s.
- That's good.
- I'll play a song from the 2000s.
My lips are getting dry now.
- I hope it's from 2001.
- Gosh.
Play the song.
(Here's the third question.)
(What song is this?)
(This isn't on pause.)
- I got it.
- Sae Ho.
- It's Fin.K.L's song.
- Gosh.
- I got it.
(He can't remember the title.)
- Three, two, one.
- I got it.
(The runaway engine has returned.)
- Get out of my way.
- I got it.
(Taking over Seon Ho's camera)
(As he was born in 2002,
he has no idea.)
- I was faster.
- Jong Min said it first.
(Jong Min gets to answer it.)
- I...
- You answer it quickly then.
- This is the only thing I can get.
- He's buying time to think.
- I got it.
- What's the correct answer?
"Now."
- Whose song is it?
- Fin.K.L's song.
- I guess he's wrong.
- Correct.
- It was "Now."
(Disappointed)
One, two, three, four.
My gosh.
(Bumping)
Stop the song.
My gosh. Great.
Are you okay, Jong Min?
- Are you okay?
- Stop the song.
- Hey, it's made of steel.
- Where?
- I'm serious, though.
- Hey, it's made of steel.
There was a loud thud.
- Jong Min, you won 2.5 dollars.
- Just like how I imagined
Which era will you pick?
- I'll pick the 1990s.
- The 1990s.
- We can only pick those two.
- He went back.
- Right. The 1990s and 2000s.
- We must answer as many as we can.
All right. Play the song.
(Here's the fourth question.)
(Viewers,
try guessing the song with them.)
(What's the correct answer?)
- I got it.
- Joon.
- Three, two,
- It's Baby V.O.X's song.
- one.
- "Get Up."
- I got it.
- Gosh, that's correct.
- Correct.
- That's it.
- He got that right?
- "Get Up."
Gosh, I was going to answer that.
Let's go, Kan Mi Youn.
- Tell me
- Kan Mi Youn.
(Things are getting heated now.)
(Their reaction differs
based on their age groups.)
(They're not excited
as they don't know the song.)
Get up
What did you say? "Giddy up?"
(Giddy up?)
Gosh, I'm in trouble.
- I can't seem to recognize any.
- Paparazzi
Gosh, how did he figure it out?
(He'll pick recent eras now.)
- What's the era you want, Joon?
- It's the 2000s.
- Okay.
- The 2000s.
Wouldn't the 2010s
be better for you?
- You performed as a singer then.
- No.
- He still listened to songs.
- I want the 2000s.
(It looks like we won't be able
to answer it again.)
Se Yoon and Seon Ho are...
the only ones who haven't gotten
any correct answer.
Play...
- I'm clueless.
- the next song.
(What is it?
I think I might know this one.)
I got it.
- I got it.
- Sae Ho.
"Pyo Pyo" by UP.
- Wrong.
- That's not it.
- That's totally wrong.
- I got it.
- Joon.
- "Give to You" by Lee Jung Hyun.
Wrong.
- Wrong.
- I got it.
- Sae Ho.
- "Mallow Marsh." "Marshmallow."
("Marshmallow")
- Whose song is it?
- IU.
Correct.
Mallow marsh
("Marshmallow" sounds
like a traditional folk song.)
(Unlike the melody,
his dance moves are cute.)
(That's cute.)
(Se Yoon puts on a concert
at a Chinese restaurant.)
(Laughing)
- Mallow marsh
- That was crazy.
- How did he get that?
- Mallow marsh
- He helped me.
- You just guessed it, right?
- Singing it earlier...
- That was crazy.
because of DinDin helped me.
(Sae Ho got him to sing it.)
- He must feel great.
- It's a dopamine rush.
- Do you have 2.5 dollars now?
- Yes, I do.
I'm doomed.
(Seon Ho is ranked last.)
All right. Pick the era.
- Okay.
- Let's go with the 2000s.
- Okay. The 2000s.
- The 2000s.
- My gosh.
- I must secure jjajangmyeon.
I must at least secure that.
You need to get things going
for you. Get one song first.
- Yes. I must go over to the 2020s.
- Yes.
You must.
Even Seon Ho might know this song...
- from the 2000s.
- Okay.
All right. Play the song.
(Here's the sixth question.)
- I got it.
- Seon Ho.
(Seon Ho finally goes for it.)
"Sweet Little Kitty"
by Cherry Filter.
That's not it.
"Travel to Me" by Buzz.
- That's the one.
- That's it.
Correct.
- How did you get that?
- My gosh.
You have to put on a performance
with the song.
- Far away
- Use your front teeth.
- You're my sunshine
(Min Kyung Hoon can sing
with his head voice.)
(I can sing with my teeth.)
- Go for it.
- He's playing it with his teeth.
He's playing the guitar
with his front teeth.
(2 Days and 1 Night Band
has been formed.)
One, two. One, two, three, four.
This is it.
(Satisfied)
This is great. I've got 4.5 dollars.
(The band will be back someday.)
- Tell him the era.
- Yes.
- It's the 2010s.
- The 2010s.
My gosh, it's the 2010s.
- That's not a bad era.
- Yes.
Play...
(Here's the seventh question.)
the song.
This is from the 2010s?
(Is it a ballad song?)
What? It's an English song!
- I got it.
(Sae Ho beats Seon Ho
by a very close call.)
"Red Flavor" by Red Velvet.
- Right.
- I'm curious, honey
- That's it?
- I bet Sae Ho...
- lied about his medical condition.
- Correct.
- Okay.
- He's so good at dancing.
Do the dance by Red Velvet.
(If it means
he can get jjamppong...)
Could you move to the side?
He's putting on a performance.
What's he doing?
- I should've gone for it sooner.
- It goes like this.
How does the song start?
- I knew this one.
- Red flavor
- How does it start?
- I had a feeling. Seriously.
- I'm curious, honey
(My favorite thing)
(In the world is red)
All right.
Really?
- No?
- You should say, "Brick Flavor."
(He plays along.)
All right.
(It's dry, honey)
(Laughing)
(Feeling proud)
- Which era would you like?
- Oh, the era? The era...
- Can you pick the 2020s?
- I'll pick this for Seon Ho.
I'll pick the 2010s for Seon Ho.
- I'll go with that again.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- Or do you want the 2020s?
- The 2020s then.
- I'll go with the 2020s.
- The 2020s?
- Yes, the 2020s.
- For Seon Ho.
- My gosh.
Jong Min and I will have to
take a break.
- This...
- I'm sure you all know this song.
- Okay.
- All right.
Play the song.
(Please let me get this one.)
I got it.
- Gosh, he knows.
- He got it.
- DinDin.
- ZICO's song.
"Any Song."
("Any Song" by ZICO)
Correct.
(Playing the piano with his teeth)
(Why do you guys look so down?)
(What's the problem? Say something)
(I know this song too.)
How did you figure it out?
- It's "Any Tooth" by DinDin.
- Yes.
DinDin can order jjajangmyeon too.
I can order jjajangmyeon.
- I'm envious.
- The road to jjamppong...
is quite far.
- Seon Ho.
- Yes?
- I'll go with the 2020s again.
- Thank you.
It's the 2020s.
How about doubling the money
for the last two questions?
Doubling the money.
What do you think
doubling the money?
- Director Joo, we can hear it.
- Really?
We can double it, right?
It means we'll get twice the money.
If you get this one right,
we'll double the money.
- Okay.
- So we can earn five dollars?
- All right, the 2020s.
- The 2020s.
I'm sorry.
We ran out of songs from the 2020s.
- Let's go with the 2010s.
- Gosh.
The 2010s? Okay.
I'll play a song from the 2010s.
- Please.
- Let me just get one right.
- I can double the money.
- This one...
- Let me get jjajangmyeon.
- Play...
- Please let it be a song I know.
the song.
(Viewers, did you figure it out?)
(Viewers,
try guessing the song with them.)
- I got it.
- Seon Ho.
"I Am the Best" by 2NE1.
- I think that's it.
- Correct.
("I Am the Best" by 2NE1)
(Seon Ho wins the doubled reward.)
- Gosh, how did you know that?
- That was good.
- Gosh, I did it.
- Seon Ho did a good job with it.
(Feeling proud)
(The brightest smile)
- I did it.
- Better than you!
- I'm the best
Let me go over the amounts
of money you have now.
Jong Min, you have 2.5 dollars.
- Gosh.
- Se Yoon.
- Do I have 2.5 dollars?
- I can only order rice.
You have 2.5 dollars.
- That's...
- Sae Ho.
- You have 7.5 dollars.
- Okay.
- I have 7.5 dollars.
- Let's pool our money together.
- Gosh.
- Joon.
Excluding the 10 dollars,
you earned 2.5 dollars.
- DinDin, you have 7 dollars.
- Can you give me 2.5 dollars?
- Seon Ho, you have five dollars.
- Gosh.
- With just one question.
I only got one question right.
But why do I feel like
I got many questions right?
- Because you're having fun.
- Because I'm having fun?
(That's odd.)
It feels like I answered them all.
- All right.
- Sorry. I'll go with the 2010s.
- The 2010s?
- Yes. Sorry.
- Okay.
- I need to have jjamppong.
Okay.
Play...
(Here's the last question.)
the song.
- What?
- I got it.
- DinDin.
- It said something about the feet.
Three, two,
- one.
Out of time!
(He runs out of time.)
- I got it.
- Hold on.
I was first. I got it.
- "Growl" by EXO.
- That's it.
- I couldn't remember the title.
- That's correct.
("Growl" by EXO)
That's it.
- I couldn't remember the title.
- That's correct.
(Is he trying to provoke them?)
Sae Ho...
(Laughing)
Sae Ho is so hyper.
His lymph nodes are swelling
(I'll play along, my friend.)
- Inflammation is building up
- Building up
Gosh, I knew it.
- All right, everyone.
- His lymph nodes are swelling
Let me go over the final results.
- It's ten dollars?
- Gosh.
(Joon: 12.5 dollars,
Seon Ho: 5 dollars,)
(Sae Ho: 12. 5 dollars,
Jong Min: 2.5 dollars,)
(DinDin: 7 dollars,
Se Yoon: 2.5 dollars)
If we combine all of our money,
we have a lot.
- If we pool all of our money...
- How much do we have then?
- Let's add up our money.
- If we do... I have 12.5 dollars.
- I have...
- Joon has 12.5 dollars.
That's 25 dollars.
- We have 42 dollars.
- Forty-two dollars? Gosh.
- Forty-two dollars.
Let's order tangsuyuk...
We can increase the size.
We can double our noodles.
Hold on.
How much do we have
if only the rich pooled the money?
(Oh, no.
He's trying to outsmart us again.)
How much do you have? Seven dollars?
- You're going down the evil path.
- Seven dollars.
- I have 7 dollars.
- We have 12.5 dollars each.
We have 32 dollars then.
- With Seon Ho, we have 37 dollars.
- We have 37 dollars.
Isn't it better to share 37 dollars
with just the 4 of us?
- It's better to have 37 dollars...
- Hey.
- with the four of us instead of...
- Yes.
- sharing 42 dollars with 6 people.
(It's better to pool money
with the rich.)
Don't you agree? Let's be realistic.
They have five dollars together.
- They'll share jjajangmyeon.
- Hey.
You want us to share jjajangmyeon?
- Right?
- We can order small tangsuyuk.
- My gosh.
(Are you seriously going to
do this?)
We can do that, right?
It doesn't matter.
(Yes, we will.)
Come on. Let's share the food.
Come on, you brat.
(Apologizing to the viewers)
- That's enough.
- Gosh.
Hey. Do you want me
to bury you in the countryside?
I saw an empty spot
next to the chili peppers.
- Great.
- We sorted it out.
- Here's our revised plan.
- Yes.
So what are we going to do?
So the four of us...
will order
large seafood tray jjajangmyeon...
and large brisket jjamppong.
- Then it'd cost 22 dollars.
- Okay.
- We'll order small tangsuyuk.
- You didn't hear me.
- No, wait.
- Okay. Go ahead.
- Come on. Let's share the food.
- Jong Min.
You should try to convince us.
We earned the money by working hard
and winning the game.
But why should we share the food
with you?
You should convince us
why it's better for us.
Jong Min. Are you going to cry?
(Is he tearing up?)
If you can convince us,
we'll let you join us.
- Jong Min. Could you...
- I'm hungry.
- You're just hungry?
- Let's share the food.
(I'm doomed.)
- All right.
- Seriously?
(He fails to convince them.)
(The 2 of them will share
1 bowl of jjajangmyeon.)
- You guys should...
- You two should...
- order jjajangmyeon.
- Okay. I'll tell you what.
- We...
- The reward is the jjajangmyeon.
- Okay.
The winner takes it all.
- I'm in!
- Give us a song or something.
- Okay.
- Yes?
- Darn it.
- Nice.
The winner takes jjajangmyeon.
That's it.
- This will be fun.
- This is good.
It's our money.
So let's do whatever we want.
We'll play it when our food is here,
so it's more nerve-racking.
- Okay.
- As soon as it's served.
Our tangsuyuk is ready.
That's a lot of tangsuyuk.
- That way.
- This way, please.
That's the normal portion.
Pour the sauce
or keep it on the side?
No. I want to dip it
in the sauce separately.
- You want to dip it separately?
- Yes.
You keep the sauce on the side?
(But I like to pour the sauce.)
- I'll pour it on just half of it.
- Okay.
(We can go half and half.)
- All good?
- That's great.
(Combining the crispy tangsuyuk
with the sweet and sour sauce)
- Joon, have some food.
- Dig in.
That looks so good.
(I'm so envious.)
Gosh, this is good.
It's so good.
Ma'am, this is so good.
My gosh. I love this.
- Yes. It's so good.
- My gosh. I love this.
- It's so crispy and tasty.
- Yes, it's good.
(We'd love to have a bite too.)
- You guys should at least enjoy it.
- It's so good.
Gosh,
it's much better than I thought.
You disloyal members.
- Jong Min.
- Did you get that?
Gosh, this is so good.
- Really?
- It's so good.
Really?
(Smacking his lips)
(He keeps on eating pickled radish
while waiting for the food.)
Gosh, jjamppong looks legit.
(The jjamppong's portion is big
just like the owner's generosity.)
- Enjoy.
- Oh, my.
- This looks amazing.
That looks amazing.
The fat from the brisket
is infused in the broth.
- Right. The fat...
- It's the meaty broth.
- I bet it's thick.
- Look at the noodles.
The noodles look great.
The noodles are cooked nicely.
- Thank you for the food.
- Enjoy the food.
Enjoy.
(We'll enjoy the food
on your behalf.)
(Inhaling)
I don't eat a lot.
(Loving the noodles)
Is it good?
This jjamppong
tastes like meat soup.
It tastes like meat soup
because it has a lot of brisket.
- This jjamppong is to die for.
- Really?
(Even the light eater, Cheol,
can't help but slurp the noodles.)
It's the best jjamppong
I had recently.
The broth is really rich.
(As the broth is so rich...)
We have to mix rice in this.
(not mixing rice in it
will be a crime.)
(When they have a big bite
of the rice with the beef brisket,)
(the frown of the truth appears.)
- Is it good?
- Yes.
The jjamppong rice
tastes like beef radish soup.
- Totally.
- Yes.
It tastes like spicy gukbap.
- Totally. That's it.
- It's so good.
I'm getting sweaty
because it's spicy.
It's good.
(The two of them
can only have jjajangmyeon.)
- You're open tomorrow, right?
- What is this?
- Let's come here tomorrow and eat.
- Okay.
- We'll eat all of these.
If we just wait today,
it will be tastier.
Exactly. Let's hang in there.
We're luckier than them.
- It'll be very delicious tomorrow.
- Right.
Jjajangmyeon is here.
We'll eat some jjajangmyeon.
- Se Yoon.
- I'll flip the coin.
- Where's the coin? Heads or tails.
- I'll flip it.
- Hurry.
- I pick heads.
- Is heads the number?
- No, the crane.
- The crane?
- Yes.
- Okay, I pick tails.
- To Se Yoon.
- All right.
- Here I go.
Hold this side.
If it's the number, I'll eat.
- If it's the crane...
- I'll eat.
- Here I go.
- I win if it's the number.
- Yes.
- Okay.
All right.
(The coin has been tossed.)
It's done. Let's see.
- Wait.
- Please, let it be the number.
- If it's the number,
- will Se Yoon get to eat?
- Yes.
One, two, three.
What is it?
- What is it?
- It's the crane.
(Heads)
(All the jjajangmyeon
goes to Jong Min.)
(How could you, Director Joo?)
(Darn it!)
(I'm sorry.)
Joo Jong Hyun, darn it!
(While Se Yoon is resenting him)
Goodness.
The serving is very generous.
(I can't wait to eat
some jjajangmyeon.)
The serving is huge.
Look at the color.
It looks like
Jong Min will be eating the most.
Guys, look at this.
The noodles are firm and bouncy.
(Slurping noodles violently
right in front of him)
It looks delicious
The jjajangmyeon looks delicious
(I could've eaten
that jjajangmyeon.)
(Groaning)
Let me borrow a dollar!
(No borrowing is allowed.)
I don't mind even if
it splashes on my clothes.
Shouldn't we give
this to Se Yoon, at least?
- The condiment dish?
- This.
- What's that?
- Serve yourself some food on this.
How many times can I serve myself?
- Let's make it clear.
- The black one.
The white one could be pretty.
- What do you think?
- You can get three servings.
(Se Yoon gets his last chance.)
(His hands are moving...)
(faster than the eyes.)
(Possessed by the hungry spirit,
he starts to analyze.)
(He's done shuffling.)
Cho Sae Ho.
You're right-handed.
You're likely to hold heavy things
in your right hand.
(The soy sauce dish
in his right hand)
Since you're right-handed,
you mixed with your right hand.
You're likely to use the muscles.
You might be holding the black dish
in your right hand,
but I can't bet everything on it.
It's on the left.
- Left?
- Left.
(He picks left.)
- Congratulations.
- Seriously?
(Congratulations)
Thank you.
I switched hands at the last moment.
Thank you. Can I get some of this?
Why are you eating my food?
You have the sauce all over you.
You're covered with greed.
Let's see.
Can't I pile some food
including the tangsuyuk?
Go ahead. Take some rice too.
Wait, Jong Min.
I'll bring us some tangsuyuk.
- Okay.
- Just now,
Sae Ho made a huge mistake.
- Why?
- You have no idea...
how much food Se Yoon can pile up.
Is that so? Wait.
(Running away with the entire plate)
This is creative.
You can't do that.
It's creative.
- I've been observing many things.
- It's creative.
- I put it on my plate.
- You can't deny it.
- This isn't allowed.
- His creativity was good.
- Why not?
This isn't allowed.
I put it on my plate.
- It was nice and creative.
- You can't take the entire plate.
- Only food is allowed.
- I know.
Thank you anyway, my friend.
I'm going to take this. Thank you.
(The familiar taste of jjajangmyeon
that spreads in the mouth)
- It's tasty.
- Se Yoon,
make sure to try some jjamppong.
- What?
- Try some jjamppong.
The jjamppong is excellent here.
When can I eat it?
(I almost forgot.)
- Do you mean tomorrow?
- No, right now...
Really? This is so delicious.
How can it only cost five dollars?
The jjajangmyeon is good,
- but the jjamppong is to die for.
- The jjamppong is excellent.
I'll eat it tomorrow.
Let's eat some tomorrow. It's good.
It's really delicious.
(He's satisfied with jjajangmyeon
and tangsuyuk for today.)
- It's delicious.
- It's really delicious.
Everyone.
After eating Chinese food,
do you crave beverages like Coke?
Definitely. I'm craving some now.
It leaves a heavy aftertaste.
This is called tangsuyuk game.
Yes?
If your team's representative wins...
Our team's representative?
Whom will he play against?
Me.
(Oh, come on.)
Against you, anyone would win.
- Jong Min, you should play.
- Goodness.
I'm sorry, Director Joo.
I laughed at you too much.
I laughed at him too much.
(Director Joo is known
as the worst player.)
Jong Hyun, you must be
quite narcissistic.
Is it because you want to give us
some Coke for free?
It'd be unfair to play
against one of us.
You should play against Jong Min.
I'd like you to drink some Coke.
If I play against Jong Min...
(My goodness)
He's looking down on you.
It's funny to be scorned by you.
(They scorn each other.)
I bet he studied something.
- No, I didn't study.
- Why don't you do it...
- with "jjamjamyeon?"
- How about "fried dumplings?"
Do it with "jjamjamyeon."
- Jjamjamyeon is difficult.
- Jjamjamyeon?
Let's play.
- Here we go.
- Yes.
You start.
- Here we go.
- Let's go.
(The weakest player
versus the weakest player)
- Here we go.
- Yes.
(Who will be the winner?)
- Jjam.
- Ja.
- Myeon.
- Jjam.
- Ja.
- Myeon.
- Jjam.
- You lost.
- You won.
- He's the champion.
- Jjam.
(They figured out who was weaker.)
He lost to Jong Min.
It can be confusing.
- It was very confusing.
- You must've been confused...
because we did it slowly.
(An unexpected win thrills him.)
I still thought that
Jong Hyun would win.
When you go out,
I'll give you ten dollars.
- All right.
- You won.
(They won ten dollars
thanks to Jong Min's performance.)
I should watch the video again.
I couldn't concentrate.
(The rising fairy of defeat)
Thank you for the food.
- Let's go to the supermarket.
- I want chestnut ice cream.
We have nothing in the fridge
except for water.
Right.
It's starting to rain.
It's raining heavily
all of a sudden.
I can smell the asphalt
because of the rain.
Shouldn't we fish
under an umbrella when it's raining?
- Right.
- We said that we'd go fishing.
If we fish when it's raining...
Some days, you catch a lot of fish.
Other days, you catch none.
Jong Min,
you're stating the obvious.
(The raindrops slowly start
to wet the rural village.)
(Taking a break in their lodging)
("Meeting" by KOYOTE,
the acoustic guitar version)
Who's singing
with such a sweet voice?
Which song is this?
(It's my song.)
Come here.
(It sounds different
with the acoustic guitar.)
Is this a song by Jong Min?
- Right?
- The original is a ballad song.
- Is it?
- It's a cover song.
The original is by Im Ki Hoon.
- Is this a cover song?
- The original sounds like this.
- Jong Min, is this a cover song?
- Yes.
(Genuinely shocked)
Is the original song
also called "Meeting?"
No, I think
it's "The Day I Met You."
(The original song of "Meeting")
("The Day I Met You" by Im Ki Hoon)
("Meeting" is its cover song
turned into a dance song.)
It's raining again today.
(Full of romance)
Jong Min, now that we took a break,
let's enjoy a leisure sport.
- Shall we go fishing?
- It's not raining anymore.
- Sae Ho, do you want to go fishing?
- Yes, let's go fishing.
- I'm going fishing.
- What?
- Then I'm going to run.
- Se Yoon, let's run together.
- Yes, take all of those.
I didn't hear you.
Let's run together. I'll teach you.
Go and learn how to run.
- You can't teach me how to run.
- Let's go.
You can learn how to run.
(Suddenly, his face turns grim.)
I'll get changed.
Get changed into what?
I don't want to run.
(Cheol, I'm scared.)
- I don't want to run.
- No. You have to.
Where are you guys going?
(Feeling pressed)
- I'm going fishing.
- Who's going?
- Me.
- What about you?
- I'll just work out here.
- By doing what?
- Muscle training.
- Where should I go?
- You have to run with me.
(Pretending not to hear him)
Joon, what is this part called?
- This is no joke.
- This part.
- By the way...
- It's a workout.
That's insane.
He looks like a man...
in his 80s on "Incredible Moment"
who does bodybuilding.
(His tank top marked by age
and experience)
He'd say, "There's nothing special
about working out."
"You just need to eat and sleep well."
He looks just like him.
What are you doing?
That's funny.
(Coming out)
(The country vacation vest
to show off his muscles)
- What?
- Come out and learn from him.
- Let's just go.
He's here to inflate his muscles.
Which parts will you work out?
Let's try it.
- Over here?
- Yes.
While standing here...
(1. Lift up the weights.)
(2. Do push-ups with the weights.)
(The student only observes him.)
(3. On all fours,
lift the weight on each side.)
Is that how it's done?
(1 set of Lee Joon's weight workout)
This is one set.
Se Yoon, save your energy...
- for the run.
- Why would I run?
Why would I...
- What's that?
- What?
What an unpleasant sight.
- I mean...
- Get ready.
(The running instructor appears.)
- What is it?
- What are you doing?
- We need to run.
Your skin is too pale.
- You're too pale.
- What's wrong?
- What is this?
- Hey.
- What's wrong with your shorts?
- This is normal.
- They look like your underwear.
That's hilarious.
You're not supposed
to wear underwear.
Jong Min's reaction is hilarious.
That looks nice.
Hurry and get ready.
The more I look at him,
the more annoying he looks.
(Just trust and follow me.)
What's wrong?
(Strangely, his outfit is
infuriating to look at.)
- It's infuriating.
- Why?
Can you show us...
how you run while standing still?
When I run for a long time...
(His infuriating walk)
His legs are so pale.
- It's so...
- Usually, I also wear a hat.
Se Yoon, go and run 3km.
I don't know how to run 3km.
You can run 3km without thinking.
After your run,
come to the fishing area.
Come to the fishing area.
Does it not have wheels?
Do I have to carry it?
You have to carry it.
By the way, where's the reservoir?
It takes five minutes by foot.
Fishing is about waiting,
and it's a fight with carp.
Jong Min and I
promised to go fishing...
outside the shoot
when the weather gets warmer.
We get to go today.
I'm a master of freshwater fishing.
- I'm a master.
- Really?
It's over. I'm too good
for a place like this.
- You can find many types of fish.
- It's beautiful.
It's big and beautiful.
(Goryeo Reservoir on Ganghwa Island)
Fishing will be fun.
The carp at this place
will be beautiful.
- Really?
- Of course.
- I saw fish jumping up.
- Did you see that?
(Dreaming of catching a big fish,
they're both excited.)
- It's over there.
- There's a lot of fish.
That's where fish find
things to eat.
(They get on the same pedestal.)
You haven't seen me fish, have you?
I only talked about it.
You guys are in big trouble.
You just need to pull. Keep pulling.
All you have to do is
lift it lightly.
Just yank it when the float moves.
(The endless waiting starts.)
Hurry up.
We have to run now.
- He wants it badly.
- We don't have much time.
Hang a piece of sausage
on a wooden stick.
You'll make him run that way.
I can't run.
Warming up is important for you.
Turn your ankles first.
(Carelessly turning)
You shouldn't turn them
so carelessly.
Let's do this first.
Keep your shoulders down.
After that...
- Grab your foot.
- That's it for my workout.
- Do this.
- Seriously.
- It says that I walked 200m.
- Do this.
- That hurts my leg.
- You need to breathe.
(He's forced to warm up.)
(Groaning)
It will start as soon as we run.
- Let's go.
- You can do it, Se Yoon.
We will start the run from here.
Get ready.
(Se Yoon challenges himself
to run for the first time.)
Get ready.
(He is running!)
Keep your arms close to your chest.
Instead of running,
think of it as walking fast.
I can't stop burping.
We only ran 200m so far.
Have you run while weighing 120kg?
- No.
- Then be quiet.
We can run along the reservoir.
(They arrive at the reservoir
where the fishing team is.)
I must be out of my mind
to be doing this.
It's your first run. Isn't it great?
- How is it? Is it good?
- Isn't it good?
Did you get the runner's high yet?
If you continue running
in the future,
you'll want to thank me.
That's why I won't.
I don't want to thank you.
- Let's get started.
- Okay.
Which parts shall we work out?
Let's work out the upper body.
- The upper body?
- Yes, my legs aren't in shape.
I have weak biceps,
so I need to work them out.
Do you want to know an exercise
that burns your biceps?
- It burns your biceps?
- It's extremely painful.
(Lee Joon runs a gym.)
(He exposed his upper body 8 times.)
It's called 777.
(777 exercise to train the biceps)
First, lift the weights halfway
and bend at 90 degrees.
(1. 7 times from the lowest point
up to the chest)
Next, from the middle.
(2. 7 times from the chest
to the highest point)
After that, it's full-out. One...
(3. 7 times from the lowest
to the highest point)
Two.
Three.
Gosh, good shot.
- This will be hard.
- One.
Two, three,
four. More.
Slow down a bit. Five.
Six. Make it firmer.
- Seven. Do it full out.
- This time...
- One.
- It's hard.
(Inhaling)
(His biceps are dominated
by 10kg dumbbells.)
(Screaming)
Two.
Three.
Make it firm. Four.
(Moaning)
Hold them there and lift halfway.
(He can't move the way he wants.)
(Shaking)
All right.
Six. It's the last one.
(Mr. Joon doesn't go easy on him.)
(He barely made it.)
Ten kilograms is heavy.
Let's take a short break.
We can take a break.
Let's see.
It pumped up my muscles.
(The surprising pump effect)
You're a good instructor.
(Mr. Joon is very competent.)
Do you know an exercise
for the chest?
I do. It's something we can do here.
- How about on the mat?
- You can do it on the mat.
Let's do it on the mat.
Touch the ground.
One.
(Chest fly)
(Concentrating)
Can I watch you do it
without the top?
I can't see the muscles right now.
(Sae Ho asks him to undress
during the demonstration.)
- Unbutton my vest.
- It's because I can't see them.
(Fidgeting)
It's because I can't see them.
Like this?
I see.
I can't see them.
Straighten.
- These muscles are rising.
- Straighten.
(The stimulated muscles are
clearly visible.)
Straighten like this.
All right, I'll try.
(It's the trainee's turn.)
By the way,
I have to look at your muscles too.
- Can I unbutton it?
- Go ahead.
- But I...
- Just in case.
This is how workout YouTubers do it.
(Exposed)
Straighten.
Don't make ring sounds
with the dumbbells.
That's it.
- My chest is getting torn.
- That's good.
- All right.
Aren't you getting too close?
- That's good.
(In search
for his lost chest muscles)
Raise your hands.
Grab them.
- Start right away.
- Okay.
Let's go.
No, you have to lower them more.
Lower them more.
Touch the ground with your elbows.
Touch the ground
before coming back up.
(What am I doing right now?)
- Is this correct?
- It's correct.
(Happy)
That was great.
It looks better now.
In that short time...
- Please take a photo of me.
- A photo?
You look very nice. You look good.
You look great.
My goodness. I look great.
(Mr. Joon's chest workout
is awesome.)
- How about this?
- Yes?
Why don't you unbutton
a little more?
Isn't it better to take it off?
I might as well...
- I'll just take it off.
- Did you take it off?
(He took it off.)
Sae Ho, let's do something fun.
(Mr. Joon's secret past
that no one knows at the gym)
Let's do something fun.
(When he takes off his top,)
(he gets excited.)
It will be difficult.
(Tough)
(Sae Ho also gets undressed.)
- Let's start.
- Okay.
I'm going to stop.
(The inferno of endless intervals)
I want to stop.
(Mr. Joon who's bulking up)
(And his new member
who's running endlessly)
What is this?
Normally, we have to run.
(High on adrenaline)
(Trying to run away)
Where are you going?
(Sir?)
- Where are you going?
- I'm right here.
(He fails to run away.)
(You're free to come in,
but you aren't free to leave.)
Why am I doing this?
(How will
the infernal bulking up end?)
- My heart is in pain.
- When you breathe...
My heart is in pain.
Do you see that over there?
We'll turn around over there
and go back.
Shall we run a little faster?
We're running
at our walking pace now.
My calves are hurting.
- My shins hurt.
- That's normal.
- I can't stand it. My back hurts.
- It's okay.
You can endure it.
- It's been seven minutes.
- I know.
- This is crazy.
- Instead of lying down at home,
you can move for seven minutes
without a break.
You can do it.
One. Keep up with this pace.
(Running step by step
with the instructor's chant)
We passed 900m.
The first 1km
in Moon Se Yoon's life.
You only have 10m left.
Go up here.
(Using every ounce of his strength
while gasping for breath)
Moon Se Yoon finished his 1km.
You took 9 minutes 33 seconds.
(I made it!)
Nice.
Well done. Get ready.
We have to go this way.
We'll walk this way.
(Pretending not to hear him)
Carry me on your back.
No. Then let's go back.
I run at this speed.
(The instructor
with sunglasses is merciless.)
Come. Run.
(Running with his face)
Your posture looks good.
- You have to keep running.
- I'm sorry.
Keep running.
The smell of jjajangmyeon.
- I can't stop burping.
- We're almost there.
You can run
when you run with someone.
- My muscles.
- We're almost there.
Do you see the house?
We're almost there.
You're the head of the family.
You can endure this much, can't you?
What does that have to do with this?
Seon Ho, please cheer for him.
Here's the finish line.
How many kilometers did you run?
- We ran 1.6km without a break.
- Yes!
(Not interested)
We ran 1.6km without a break.
- I'm going to run a little more.
- Go ahead.
Look how drenched he is in sweat.
Look how wet his headband is.
- Go ahead.
- Here I go.
What's going on?
(His instructor goes
to enjoy himself.)
Running 1.6km felt...
as painful as running 160km.
Everyone, please run.
After the run, you'll get to rest
for so long that you'll be bored.
(Moon Se Yoon's Run, the end)
(Groaning)
(He got cramps in his calves
as an aftereffect from running.)
Joo Jong Hyun! Darn you.
(Giggling)
You said we could just rest. Gosh.
Se Yoon, I'm sure
you've become healthier.
Oh, my. He's really fast.
Catch some fish
so we can have some sashimi later.
- Okay.
- I'm off.
Take your time. Don't rush it.
(They're catching time
instead of fish.)
It's raining quite heavily.
Why does it rain
when we just got here?
We should put on a raincoat.
All right. Now...
I see a fish jumping up.
There are some carp here.
Why won't any fish bite the bait?
(No fish have the intention
of getting caught.)
A fish always bites bait
at an unexpected moment.
(They've been fishing for 1 hour
and had no bites.)
Why aren't any fish biting?
- There it comes.
- Wait.
- It's biting.
- Should I keep waiting?
- Yes, you should wait a bit longer.
Oh, my.
It went down deeply and quickly.
- I can see it now.
- That's good. You got it.
(What did Seon Ho catch?)
- I'm tired.
- Good job. Yes.
- But I'm not joking.
- Okay.
- I feel great.
- Right?
- My arms look great now.
- Indeed.
- Do you want to try anything else?
- No, I want to take a break.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Why don't you put your vests back on
while taking a break?
All right.
- I feel good after working out.
- Yes.
- Right. You feel good after that.
(He's not satisfied
for some reason.)
I can also teach you
how to do squats in a fun way.
I have to burn the calories
of the jjamppong.
Just show me how to do it
since I can't do it.
- Shall I show you?
- Yes.
I'll show you a simple squat workout
you can do easily at home.
He'll teach you, viewers.
- It's Lee Joon's Squat Class.
- You see...
When I work out by myself at home,
I do squats for ten minutes
before showering...
to work up a sweat.
Here's how I do squats.
Just squat down like you do
when you sit on a toilet.
(Sitting on a toilet)
It's simple. You just have to...
(Panting)
What's this sound?
(The breathing sound disturbs
the squat lesson.)
The next gym member is here.
Sir, listen to me.
You did a good job running.
Usually,
when people do squats at home,
they set the goal number of squats.
"I'll just do ten squats."
But the number of squats you do
doesn't matter at all.
You must maximize the intensity
while doing each of the squats.
And repeat doing squats
until you can't do it anymore.
Even seven squats would do.
The number of squats doesn't matter.
When you've reached your limit,
don't stop.
When you think you can't stand up...
This could seem a little funny.
Put your hands on the floor.
- One, two, three...
- I see.
I'm not joking.
I'm serious. Try this just once.
You'll be exhausted.
When you feel like
you can't do any more squats,
push your hips upward.
One, two, three, four,
- five, six, seven,
- What is he doing?
- eight.
- What's with him?
It's a lower body workout. Nine.
If regular squats
are regular coffee,
this kind of squat is
a strong type of coffee.
(I don't care. I'm tired.)
(Farting)
What are you doing right now?
You must've lost your mind.
(What are you doing right now?
You must've lost your mind.)
- Why?
- He just farted. Unbelievable.
(Angry)
He must've lost his mind.
Why would he do that?
I can't help it. I'm sorry.
- How about you try to do squats?
- Sorry?
Why don't you try to do squats?
- No, I don't want to do it.
- Just one set.
One set? Then show me how to do it.
Just squat down
as you do when you sit on a toilet.
It'll come out if I do that now.
I'm sorry. I'll try it later.
You heard that one just now, right?
- Until you can't lift them up.
- Try it, Se Yoon.
We even took off our vests earlier
to do this workout.
We worked out really hard earlier.
If I take my shirt off,
some piglets might come
and try to latch onto my nipples.
(Mommy)
Calling me "Mommy."
I can breastfeed only two of them.
- Have you finished your workout?
- Yes.
In any case... Yes, we have.
(The gym is closed as the members
are not feeling well.)
They're exhausted, apparently.
Did you run far?
- I ran 3km more.
- Really?
(DinDin, who went for a run alone,
is back too.)
Can you play this song?
(Singing gibberish)
What song is that?
(You mean, a song like this?)
("Rainy Street" by Lee Seung Hoon)
(We enjoy ourselves with no worries
on Our Own Country Vacation.)
(Happy)
(The best song choice
for a rainy day)
(Listening to the song comfortably
while lying down)
Hey, guys!
What... Did you catch a fish?
Did you see what we caught?
- We caught a fish for dinner.
- Really?
- You'll be surprised.
- Stop lying.
(He shows them the bucket
with confidence.)
- I bet there's no fish in there.
- All I can hear is a rock rattling.
- Gosh. Come on.
- Did you catch no fish?
(Empty)
I feel bad for them, though.
Jong Min has never caught a fish
on 2 Days and 1 Night.
- Why is there so much water plants?
- There's much of it here.
- What are you doing?
- Spit it out!
(He suffers
from a severe aftereffect.)
(He looks as if he were getting
an electric shock.)
(Be sure to do warm-ups
before going for a run.)
It hurts. What's the point
of doing this after running?
That's enough.
(While they are
having fun together...)
Everyone, please come out.
(Come out?)
- Jong Min, let's go.
- Okay.
- They want us to be out.
- I'm sleepy now.
It's really fun to fish in summer.
(They go out of the house for now.)
- Gosh, it's hot.
- Oh, what?
What's going on?
What's with the table tennis table?
Why? What are we going to do now?
(He senses that something's wrong.)
- My gosh. What's this?
- What?
- Table tennis?
- There must be something wrong.
- What's this?
- So it has begun finally.
- Are we going to play a game?
I knew it.
This was never an easy one.
It has just begun, right?
Are you enjoying
your country vacation?
- Yes, this is nice.
- Yes. I'm so excited.
We can have fun and take a nap.
Today, you must prepare dinner,
tidy up the place,
- and make a bed by yourselves.
- My goodness.
But it's not that
all of you have to do the work.
- Absolutely.
- That's right.
- Three of us could do all that.
- Okay.
Sae Ho shared
an idea for a new game with us,
which we're grateful for.
- A game?
- Oh, you're talking about that.
- What is it?
- I see that Sae Ho works hard.
- What's that idea?
- What is it?
Sae Ho can't move his legs,
but he can use his arms. So...
- Hey, what are you talking about?
- He can move his legs.
- His legs are fine.
- That's not what I meant.
- A game involving leg movements...
- could be challenging for him.
- He has a problem with his leg.
- In this part of my leg.
- Yes.
So you're going to play the game
that Sae Ho suggested...
to select two workers...
who will be
your hands and feet today.
Two out of the six members?
I'll explain about the game first.
Hit as many cups and bottles
as you can...
with table tennis balls
within 30 seconds.
- The ones with higher scores win.
- Okay.
The two with the lowest scores
will be the workers, naturally.
What should the two workers do?
If you're chosen as a worker,
you should run small errands
for the other members,
prepare dinner,
and make bed for all members.
- The two workers should do those?
- Yes.
The workers should even
lay out beddings?
If someone asks for water,
the workers should fetch water?
- That can be an example.
- This is the worst.
They'll be slaves for the others.
"I'm going to fart.
Put your face close to my butt."
What kind of life are you leading?
What do you do for fun
alone at home?
Who would make such a demand?
(I was joking.)
You can decide the order
just as you want.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Joon, when do you want to do it?
- I'll go last.
I'll go fifth.
- Then I'll go 3rd.
- I'll go 2nd.
Se Yoon will go first.
We'll start with Se Yoon.
- "You punk."
- That must be his strategy.
- I'll go with the You Punk Method.
- Get ready.
- This is nerve-racking.
- Okay. Good.
- Are you ready?
- "You punk."
- You've got this!
- Let's go!
- Ready.
- Set.
- Se Yoon!
Se Yoon, hit the third one!
That's good. You're doing great.
You're doing an excellent job.
You're amazing.
Wait. What?
Oh, my. He's really good at it.
(After hitting
two 5-point targets...)
(He only hits 5-point targets.)
(He gains another 5 points.)
How many five-point targets
has he hit so far?
Hey, he hit 10 5-point targets.
He can't hit any of the big ones.
Hey, you're doing well.
You're doing just great.
(He gains 50 points!)
(Awesome)
(He hit the 100-point target,
but he failed to make it fall off.)
- What are you doing?
- Se Yoon, keep going.
(Disappointed)
- Five, four, three...
- That's good.
- Nice!
- Se Yoon, what are you doing?
- One.
- It's over!
- He did a great job.
- It was harder than I thought.
It seems fun.
- Se Yoon.
- You hit this one.
- Oh, good.
- It's a 50-point target.
- Really?
- I hit a 50-point target, at least.
- You did a very good job.
- Se Yoon's score is 70 points.
- Okay. That was good.
- That's a high score.
I think I did well.
He did better than I expected.
Had I not gone for a run...
(He ran out of energy.)
- Jong Min, are you ready?
- Yes.
- Hold on. Just in case.
- Ready.
I'll put this here.
It might be flown away.
(A spare racket to be used
in case his racket is flown away)
- You should use just one racket.
- No. You never know.
- That's not allowed.
- You should use just one racket.
- I'll cherish it.
- Jong Min, are you ready?
- Yes.
- Here we go. Ready.
Please.
Set.
Hey, throw it lightly.
(He missed the targets.)
(He gains 15 points,
and then he gets another 15 points.)
(He gains 5 points.)
(After hitting
three 5-point targets...)
(Just like Se Yoon,
he only hits 5-point targets.)
They're all 5-point targets.
That's 5 points too.
They're all 5-point targets...
Oh, my.
(He gains 50 points!)
(No...)
(Remaining time: 10 seconds)
- He doesn't know how to hit it.
- You have ten seconds left.
(Maybe he got tired.
He keeps groaning.)
- No. Please.
- Gosh.
(Laughing)
(He feels pity for Jong Min
for some reason.)
- Three, two, one.
- Aim at Director Joo.
- Okay.
- It's over.
- Let's check.
- What's his score?
- He did well.
- That's 55 points.
- He hit many targets.
- His score must be high.
Jong Min's score is 105 points.
(Jong Min gained 105 points.)
- I did better than Se Yoon.
- That's 20 points.
- Fifty points.
- I beat him.
- He did very well.
- I beat Se Yoon.
- I've got this!
- Here goes the third player.
- Ready.
- Sae Ho, you can do this!
Sae Ho, you can... Oh, my.
(Sae Ho hit a 50-point target
as soon as he started.)
- He hit no five-point ones.
- What?
(He gains 15 and 80 points
at the same time.)
- Only five seconds have passed.
- He already got many points.
You were too hasty.
That's a 100-point target.
(He hit the 100-point target,
but it didn't fall off.)
(Sae Ho hit the 100-point target.)
Stop it now.
(He lost the will to play.)
Five, four,
three, two, one.
I'm sure he practiced this
with his wife.
No! How could I have practiced this?
- He practiced it with his wife.
- I'm sure he practiced.
- He practiced for sure.
- I know.
- Where would I practice this?
- At your place!
How can you practice this at home?
Please check his shopping history.
I'm sure he got the ping-pong table.
Sae Ho earned 275 points.
(Sae Ho earned 275 points.)
I think it will be Se Yoon and Joon.
(Se Yoon and Joon
will be the workers.)
You are in last place as well.
But Joon can't score at all.
So it's Joon then.
- You still have chances.
- Right.
- It makes me nervous.
- Right, I'm nervous.
- It's fun.
- Director, be careful.
(Bluffing)
(What is he saying?)
You will get 1,000 points
if you make the director fall.
I should play as I usually do.
You'll only hit the ball
when you play as you usually do.
All right, let's start. Ready?
Making it fall off must be hard.
He hit the 100-point target.
(DinDin hits the 100-point target.)
(He couldn't make it fall off,
although he hit it right.)
(Shocked, thinking
DinDin got 100 points)
- He only hits the 100-point target.
- That's fast. What?
- Great! You're doing amazing.
- He's good.
Okay, that's great.
- Okay, you're doing great.
- You're doing great.
- All right, hit it again.
- Keep going.
- Look at how he smashes.
- He's really good.
(He still has only 25 points.)
(Se Yoon won't be in last place
if DinDin keeps up this way.)
Oh, what's going on? No!
(DinDin hits the 100-point target.)
(Then he hits the 50-point target
right after.)
(He saves his life 10 seconds
before the game ends.)
Ten seconds!
(10 points earned, 5 points earned)
(Why is he good at it
all of a sudden?)
What? Why is he good?
Two, one.
That's it.
He got the 100-point target.
Hey, Sae Ho.
- Suggest such games more. It's fun.
- Great.
I mean he was leading...
(Se Yoon remains
in last place again.)
But DinDin
could have been in big trouble.
I know. It could've been bad.
You would have lost if it weren't
for the 100-point target.
- You were flustered, right?
- Yes.
Let me announce the scores.
Sae Ho earned 275 points.
- That's a lot.
- Goodness.
- DinDin earned 190 points.
- Okay.
Jong Min earned 105 points.
That's not bad.
Se Yoon earned 70 points.
(Another worker candidate)
I want to play this again.
I should make Se Yoon run
if he becomes our slave.
(Laughing)
We can make him get meat
from a store that's 3km away.
- Don't call me a slave.
- No, a worker.
- A slave.
- Okay, a worker sounds fine.
We don't know yet.
Their play might be bad.
All right, it's Seon Ho's turn.
As long as I get 100 points...
- I think he won't get it.
- I know.
- Look at the skinny boy.
- Goodness.
- He's as thin as a toothpick.
- Gosh, his arm.
(His smash looks somewhat weak.)
- Gosh, that Paper Doll.
- He isn't the important one here.
(Trying to bribe the helper)
We don't want to get uncomfortable,
you got that?
Throw it like this.
(Throwing)
Nobody is going to say anything.
Make yourself at home.
Hey, come on now. Mister.
- Let's start now.
- I'll step away a little.
Start.
- There you go.
- Great.
(Missing the ball)
- There you go.
- Great.
- You're doing great, Seon Ho.
- There you go.
(His swing looks unstable
from the start.)
- What if he hits the 100-point...
- All right! We got this!
- We got this.
(The ball won't even reach
the target.)
(Great, I won't be a worker.)
- We got this! Yes.
- We got this.
(He finally earned 15 points.)
(50 points earned, 15 points earned)
- He beat Se Yoon.
- He will never make it.
(15 points earned)
(Seon Ho earned 80 points
in no time.)
(Se Yoon failed to escape
from being the worker.)
Oh, no. He's getting it.
Gosh, he's getting it.
(Seon Ho beats Jong Min
as he scores another 50 points.)
- That's more than 100 points...
- One more shot.
(10 points earned)
- Hit the 100-point target again.
- Five,
four,
three, two, one.
He earned more than 100 points.
Seon Ho earned 140 points.
(Seon Ho earned 140 points.)
- Se Yoon's the worker for sure.
- He is the worker for sure.
- I am.
- You're the worker now.
I don't want to do this with him.
It makes me even angrier
when he teases me.
All right, I'll start.
Joon, are you ready?
(Screaming)
Let's go!
Joon, please!
Joon can never get this.
I feel like I'm playing
for the Summer Games.
Please!
Joon, please.
You can do this. You're strong.
- Your muscles aren't for fashion.
- Please.
Please.
I can't stand him teasing me.
Please let me get a break.
It's Jong Min versus Joon.
All right, let's start. Ready?
- Start.
- Hit it toward the sky.
- The snap.
- Hit it toward the sky!
- You're doing great.
- Oh, great.
- No!
(His play is different this time.)
(He hits the 50-point target
as soon as he starts.)
(Flustered at the high score
from the start)
- Great. One more time. That's it.
- No!
(Gym Lover's leading a good start.)
- There you go.
- He's good.
- You're doing great.
- Hit it hard.
- You're doing just fine.
- It has been ten seconds.
- Joon, you're doing just fine.
- Joon, make the target fall off.
- Hit it harder.
(Screaming)
- Hit it to the ground.
- Die!
- There you go. To the ground.
- To the ground!
- What's happening?
(He won't be the worker
if he scores another 45 points.)
- There you go. Good.
- Here!
Hit it to the ground.
(Missing)
The ball only goes through the gaps.
(Interestingly enough, the ball
only goes through the gaps.)
(This surely is a talent.)
- Gosh, what's going on?
- No.
- Great.
- Four, three,
- two, one.
- Great.
- You...
- You idiot.
Joon is the worker.
(He is the worker.)
- He's so bad at this.
- But his ball was precise...
He hit it toward the gaps only.
That means he's a good player.
He's good at this.
- He hit it toward the gaps only.
- This is hard.
I'll tell you the final scores.
Se Yoon earned 70 points.
- Joon scored 65 points.
- No.
You're both workers now.
(Joon and Se Yoon
are the workers for tonight.)
You will see an ice box up there.
- Please get me cold water.
- Yes, do that.
- Joon.
- Will you be going?
- Clothes for the workers?
- That's right.
Clothes for the workers.
(You have clothes for the workers?)
Give me Se Yoon's too.
Please take off your shirts now.
I'm glad, though.
They might have to cook.
- Se Yoon is good at cooking.
- He is.
Here you go.
(Getting changed
into workers' outfits)
- Joon.
- Yes?
Please push back your hair.
- We have to wear this too.
- Right.
- What's that?
- You have to work...
whatever is needed
for the country vacation.
Workers, please make sure...
to prepare dinner for them.
Today's dinner menu is barbeque...
that goes well
with the country vacation.
- That'd be nice.
- Barbeque?
He's good at this.
(A barbecue is a must
on the country vacation.)
I'll be providing 200 dollars...
for you to go grocery shopping.
Is this your last day?
What's wrong with you?
- It's like you're being rebellious.
- Are you going somewhere?
There is a supermarket around here.
There's a seafood market,
as well as many restaurants.
Should we grill some clams?
Seafood?
- Shrimps?
- How about...
- Get us pen shells and scallops.
- Then...
Let's get scallops and beef brisket
for a combo meal.
- Mushrooms.
- Make a good meal.
Can we have scallops with cheese?
- Of course.
- Nice.
Joon, get us water...
from the ice box.
Four bottles.
- Four bottles.
- But this is...
- Sure.
- Sing for us now.
(Singing right away)
(We surely have good workers.)
(We can see the future
of the workers.)
Great.
- Okay, that was amazing.
- All right.
He's good.
- Thank you.
- You can go shopping now.
Do we take a break
until they come back?
Yes.
I should take a nap.
Just because
I wasn't good at table tennis,
I ended up as a worker.
That's life.
They don't know how much
it would cost. We have 200 dollars.
Do you think we should eat
and go back?
Of course, I thought about that.
- You did? Are you sure?
- Yes.
Let's check if we can eat something
before we go back.
(The two workers dream
of committing a crime in secret.)
We can get a glass of slushy
or something.
Let's just pass out
after we have slushies.
- We'll pass out after having it.
- Sure.
We're here at the seafood market.
Let's get out.
It looks like we're shooting
"My Hometown at 6pm."
I know.
"We're here at a seafood market..."
"in Oepo-ri, Ganghwa-gun."
- We can find direct sellers here.
- Right, Oepo Port.
We're here to get seafood
directly from the sellers.
(Fresh)
I love seafood smells like this.
(Going inside the market
feeling excited)
- Goodness.
- Hello.
- I see crabs.
(They reached a stall where they
sell different types of seafood.)
- Hello.
- Do you have scallops?
- We have pen shells.
- How much is it?
Please give me five pieces.
She'll steam the scallops for us.
That would be 40 dollars
for 5 pieces.
Yes, give us 1kg of it.
That's all we want.
Do you happen to have
salted oysters with hot pepper?
- It surely tastes great.
- Taste it.
- Does it smell good?
- Goodness.
We have to get this.
Can we taste it? Thank you.
It's so delicious.
I've never heard of this.
Should we try it as well?
The salted oysters with hot pepper
taste really good.
(They purchase the salted oysters
with hot pepper perfect with rice.)
We can eat rice with just this.
This is crazy.
If we grill meat and eat it
with scallops, it's amazing.
- Right.
- Yes.
(Meanwhile, she's preparing
the pen shells.)
(Attracting his attention)
(Only the flesh of the thick pen shells
are packed.)
That looks good.
(Feeling dizzy)
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
I'll carry one.
- It's okay.
- We have to go this way.
We should hurry back to cook.
Thank you.
- Bye.
Let's go to the supermarket now.
Are they really relaxing?
- This is fun.
- It's really healing.
Has it ever been like this before?
Lightly. That's right!
Nice.
(A recovery massage after a run
is a must.)
(They had all the fun,
and now it's nap time again.)
Should we take a cart?
- Let's do that.
- Yes.
This is barley.
It's 12 dollars for 2.5kg.
This is 5 dollars for 4kg.
- Let's get these two.
- Okay.
- These two should be enough.
We have to get kimchi.
Common kimchi.
That's enough.
This one? Wait. It's packed.
Let's get meat first.
We're five. Okay.
- This is enough.
- Wait.
It's more than enough.
Get some pork jowl if there is any.
Pork jowl.
Pork jowl is expensive. Gosh.
I don't like pork neck.
(But he'd make a fuss.)
Okay. Let's get pork belly
and pork jowl.
Really? But the money...
Do we have enough money?
I think it would be fine.
Let's see how much it is.
- Hello.
- We're curious how much this is.
- Could we...
- Okay.
- We don't have so much money.
- Take out what you don't need.
- Okay.
- We'll do that.
- I'm sorry.
Just put what we really need.
And...
(Will they have enough money
for the slushy?)
(Purchased Items)
Yes.
Take a look at the price.
It's okay.
It's 87 dollars. It's 88 dollars.
It's 117 dollars. It's 122 dollars.
- How much do we have?
- We have 130 dollars.
No!
(The amount goes over 130 dollars.)
It's more than 130 dollars.
We can't get slushies.
We'll remove the pork jowl.
We'll remove the broth too.
(They take out
the budae stew broth.)
We can't get slushies.
It's 121.7 dollars. It's good.
- Hold on.
- What?
We should have 5 dollars each.
We'll take this out too.
We'll be able to eat a lot.
We'll take these.
(Final price: 117 dollars)
I'm sorry.
Do you have Nonghyup points?
- Points?
- Yes.
It's 117.19 dollars.
(They really need the points now!)
Are there points under my name?
(How many points does Se Yoon have?)
- How much is there?
- Zero points.
Okay. Darn it.
Really?
But you got a 50-cent discount.
How?
Because you're a member.
I'm a member? All right.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- Sure.
(Current balance: 13 dollars)
Let's...
have some snacks before we go back.
We should get something
to be motivated to work.
We should eat something sweet.
There must be something around here.
What about twisted donuts?
- There...
- There are twisted donuts.
- Should we go in there?
- Do you want twisted donuts?
- Let's eat twisted donuts.
- It's for the sake of fun.
- It's for fun.
- Yes.
If we get nine twisted donuts...
So 3 times 5 is 15, 3 times 6...
It's 7.5 dollars.
It would be just the right amount.
Okay.
Hello.
- What's this?
- You startled me.
- It's here.
- This looks good.
Slushies are two dollars.
- Let's get one each.
- We could eat this.
- They had slushies here.
- Let's get them.
It's...
It's fascinating that they have
what we so wanted.
We really wanted slushies,
and they were right here.
Should we eat some here?
Let's eat. Can we eat it?
(Joon takes a sip of the slushy,
his soul food.)
(The refreshing taste of the slushy)
Where is the donut?
Let's eat.
(Se Yoon quickly joins
with the twisted donuts.)
(Freshly fried twisted donuts
can't taste bad.)
Twisted donuts
should be eaten fresh.
(This is the taste of freedom.)
This is great.
(Se Yoon gets a sip
of the slushy too.)
Hold on. Gosh, my head.
Have you ever fainted
after drinking a slushy?
- No. You fainted?
- I did when I was in high school.
- You actually fainted?
- Yes.
The machine used to be outside,
so I could pour myself a cup.
When it gets full,
you just close the lid and go.
What I did was...
I suck on the straw
while pulling the lever.
(He wanted to drink more,)
(and he fainted.)
When I woke up,
my friends were stepping on me.
"What are you doing?"
They thought I was joking.
My head hurt.
(Do not try this.)
Seriously.
That never happened to me.
(There are still
10 twisted donuts left.)
Raise your hand
if you want a twisted donut.
Okay. First letter.
Quack.
- Second letter.
- I'm hungry.
- Third letter.
- Let's energize.
Amazing.
I knew it.
Why are you so good?
- Why are you so good?
- You did great.
He really...
What was that?
Who else wants a twisted donut?
- Thank you.
- Take a bite from here.
Tell us how it tastes.
- Please describe the taste.
- ASMR.
(Teary-eyed)
Thank you.
(Laughing)
It's the raw reaction of an amateur.
- It's raw.
- He's good.
Do you have a girlfriend?
- I have someone I like.
- Someone you like?
- Hold on.
- Don't say her name.
(A message for his crush)
Say something to her
while eating the twisted donut.
How are you?
(He spurts out the slushy.)
(Choking)
(He's confused.)
Did she go to jail or something?
Why did you ask her
if she's doing well?
(It looks like
she's quite far away.)
Wait.
Please continue.
Look at this camera.
- Jail...
- I don't know if you're listening,
but I like you so much.
(I like you so much.)
I wish you good luck.
- It will turn out well.
- Okay.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
This is nice.
It was funny
when he asked how she was.
It's 7:20 p.m.
Should we go back at 8:20 p.m.?
- No. Let's get going now.
- Now?
You slack off hard, don't you?
I'll keep an eye on you
when you go on chores.
- Thank you.
(After eating and having fun,
evening came upon Ganghwa Island.)
Have you been having fun, friend?
- You're back.
- Hello.
Go to the left. To the kitchen.
You can put the ingredients
in the fridge.
- We should.
- You're already here?
Goodness.
Don't take this wrong,
but show me the receipt.
(He pretends not to hear.)
Do you have a receipt?
Let's not do that. We're so tired.
(He takes a bite
of the twisted donut first.)
- They bought snacks.
- What?
I think they ate something.
- They must have.
- It's for sure.
I smell something.
What smell?
We even bought twisted donuts.
Why are you lying down?
- Why did you take so long?
- Why can't I?
But...
- Go work.
- I'm so tired.
You should work.
(Se Yoon escapes to the yard
away from the nagging.)
The pork cutlet looked good.
We should eat that.
People always want to grill meat
when they're out.
(Workers need rest too.)
(Should I lie down and rest
for a second?)
Okay.
What are you doing here?
(The first son says a word.)
Why aren't you working?
What should I do for you?
They will keep making us work there.
(This was why Joon
didn't want to go back.)
Let me know if you need anything.
- Se Yoon.
- Yes?
Please give me a massage.
A massage?
Which bone do you want broken?
Which one?
Where do you want to feel pain?
Just the shoulders.
- You don't mind it being broken?
- Yes. The shoulders.
(A K-massage shop is open.)
I'm next.
(Annoying)
(Screaming)
(A 0.1ton pressure massage)
Se Yoon.
Yes?
I'd like a pineapple slushy.
That's crazy.
(Lee Joon, you punk...)
(He sticks next to the master.)
(It was 5 minutes ago.)
I'll let you rest
if you tell me what you ate.
We had one slushy.
One slushy?
A two-dollar slushy.
(He confessed in the end
because of the offer.)
(He told him about the taste
and the price.)
It looked like they sold it
at a nearby store.
(He's shocked
by his best friend Joon's betrayal.)
(He can't say anything.)
You'd know.
You had a brain freeze
after drinking a pineapple slushy.
(He punishes the betrayer.)
Really? You...
(There are lots of screams tonight
at the country vacation.)
Who suddenly said that?
Bring some of your poop later.
I should check.
(He needs his poop examined now.)
This is really bad,
but I really want to check...
what they ate.
- Se Yoon.
- Yes?
Please sing us a song
while playing the guitar.
It was really nice.
Okay.
(He has given up.)
Music on!
(The worker's dinner show is on.)
(Instrument: Se Yoon,
Dance: Lee Joon)
(A work that expresses
the sorrow of workers)
It's a sad song.
He's pretty good.
He must've been
a great dancer in the past.
(A great talent that has
experience with dancing)
(The guitar rhythm
suddenly gets faster.)
Great! Make it intense!
(The past sorrow gets expressed
through this performance.)
- Gosh!
Se Yoon,
sing "Meeting" by KOYOTE for us.
I'm sorry. I need to sleep.
- I'm sorry.
- Just this once.
- Sorry?
- I'm really tired.
- Just this once.
KOYOTE's "Meeting"
A new "Meeting"
Gosh.
(Was that a PSY song
or a KOYOTE song?)
- That was good enough, right?
- Yes.
That was "Meeting" by KOYOTE.
- Okay.
- That was entertaining.
(Everyone is satisfied
by the worker's talent show.)
- Let's get some rest.
- Right.
- Get some rest.
- Okay.
(Se Yoon finally gets to lie down
for the first time.)
- Everyone.
- What?
Let's head out now.
I just got to lie down.
Where do you want us to go?
- Let's head out now.
- I just got to lie down.
We have to move onto our next event.
It seems like
you have rested up quite a bit.
- Where are we going?
- Just out there.
- We're leaving again?
- Yes.
(Letting out a sigh)
My gosh. This is...
Why does it feel like
I'm doing things nonstop?
(It feels like there's no end
to his work.)
He wants us to head out.
- Sae Ho.
- Head out? Let's go then.
All right. I won.
- Let's head out.
- Are you all here?
- Be careful.
- Okay.
Please stand together again.
Can't we eat now?
Se Yoon and Joon,
you two have gone through a lot
as workers.
- Right.
From now on,
rank your own appearances.
- What?
- Rank our own appearances?
Get into a discussion...
and decide on the ranks
of your appearances...
- from 1st to 6th.
- Will this be okay?
There's an obvious contender
for 6th place.
What?
(They all look the same way.)
Including the workers?
- All six including the workers.
- We're people too.
Then let's decide on...
the top ranks starting with
the person in first place.
There are 2 at the top,
3 in the middle,
and one at the bottom.
This is what I honestly think.
- There are two at the top,
- Right.
one in the middle,
and three at the bottom.
Will you name the three
that are at the bottom?
The three at the bottom?
I'm one of them.
- Right.
- There's another one.
- There's another one after him.
That other person is...
The person who had
some good news recently.
(Part of the 3 at the bottom)
Joon looks handsome.
Joon was at the center...
- even when he was in MBLAQ.
- Right.
- Joon has great looks.
- Okay.
Seon Ho has a face
that is liked by...
- the younger generation.
- Really?
- Can I share my opinion?
- Sure.
- These two are neck and neck.
- Right.
These two are neck and neck.
Let's think about these two later.
Right. But I also think that...
Jong Min's face
has melted down a lot.
Why would you say that?
- Gosh.
- How could my face melt down?
- Take a look at us.
- Hey!
- Stand together.
- Move away.
- Gosh.
- Don't laugh!
I just like making others laugh.
I don't have an ugly face.
Why does Se Yoon
look really handsome to me today?
- Come on.
- But...
when Se Yoon
played the guitar earlier,
- He's charming.
- I thought that...
- he looked great.
- He's someone that's likable.
I have a camera with me.
- Let's take ID pictures.
- Right.
- Let's compare them.
- Let's do that.
(Comparing their faces
with ID pictures)
I joined KOYOTE with my appearance.
His face has melted down.
Take it like a pictorial.
- I decided on the one that's last.
- What's with his eyes?
(Candidate 3, Moon Se Yoon)
All right.
Let's take a look at them now.
- Right.
- Se Yoon.
Se Yoon looks handsome.
- This is Se Yoon.
- What are you saying?
Let's take a look at Jong Min next.
Come on. I look different, don't I?
- This is driving me crazy.
- He does look different.
- Come on.
- There was one with me smiling.
He's a comedian.
I'm the face of my group.
(They check Sae Ho's picture
this time.)
I told you!
- What is it?
- Gosh!
Sae Ho is really ugly.
(His magazine face
has appeared again.)
The person in last place
has been decided.
It's neck and neck between
4th and 5th place.
I'm in last place?
- What? I didn't say anything.
- He's just...
(Feeling bitter)
- But...
- Things have gone completely wrong.
- Joon should just step away.
- Okay.
- Step away.
- I'm in first place?
- First place, stay right there.
- Gosh.
- Are you serious?
- Be honest...
and raise your hand if you think
you are in second place.
I'll be honest.
Raise your hand if you think
you are in second place.
Your face? What's wrong with him?
- Raise your hand for second place.
- Gosh!
- Gosh.
- You can step away...
- if you get a majority vote.
- I can't believe this.
Raise your hand if you think
Seon Ho is in second place.
One, two, three.
He looks better than DinDin.
- Step away with second place.
- Right.
- We will vote too.
- All right.
Raise your hand
if you think you are in third place.
- All right.
- Just stop.
- Get back here.
- Just stop!
- Look at his mouth!
- Get back here.
I look amazing in person.
- I'm serious.
- Who said that?
This is the response I get
from people when I walk around.
- "What?"
- Show us your most confident look.
But that's true about DinDin.
He doesn't look bad.
People get surprised
to see him with his great looks.
When they ask if he's DinDin,
he goes, "Hello!"
(Feeling annoyed)
There's one part about you
that's disappointing.
Where?
Your nose looks really entertaining.
Gosh! I admit it.
I heard that a lot.
They said I had a nose
that looked like a frog.
They said it looked like a frog
that was about to jump.
- Right.
- He looked handsome in the past.
- A frog?
- He looked handsome.
- A frog that was about to jump?
- Right.
Step away as third place.
That's hilarious.
It's raining so let's hurry up
with the votes.
Raise your hand if you think
you are in fourth place.
- One, two, three.
- Let's be serious now.
Raise your hand for Jong Min.
One, two, three.
Se Yoon, show us your handsome face.
(Irregular faces will be seen
on the screen for a while.)
(Please be understanding.)
Why do you keep doing this?
I'm trying to cover my nose.
Raise your hand for Jong Min.
One, two, three.
I still think Jong Min
looks better than them.
- He only got two votes.
- Yes.
I vote for myself too!
What are you talking about?
- So that's 3 votes. All right.
- That's 3 votes.
- It'll be the same.
- Sae Ho in fourth place.
One, two, three.
(He just gets his own vote.)
Se Yoon in fourth place.
One, two, three.
- I vote for Se Yoon.
- It's over anyway.
- Fine.
- You saw when I raised my hand, no?
- All right.
- You were just a bit unlucky.
- I'm fine.
- All right then.
These are the ranks
of your own appearances.
- All right.
- What?
The most good-looking member
will go inside now.
- What?
- Am I free from being a worker?
Really?
You can go inside.
It's raining a little right now,
- so you should move back.
- What?
Being in sixth place
is upsetting enough. What is this?
(Joon enters the front yard
of the base camp.)
I won't be a worker anymore!
(He gets invited to the kitchen.)
Hello, Joon.
We will now begin the Dinner Game.
Today's Dinner Game is called...
Read the Room and Set the Table.
Did you figure out
how the game works?
No.
Out of the ingredients
that are in front of you,
you can leave after selecting one.
When more than two people
choose the same ingredient,
that ingredient will be taken back.
Think about one ingredient...
(The same ingredient
cannot be chosen between them.)
you wish to choose.
You may leave after that.
This is tough.
We worked hard to buy these.
(Feeling anxious)
Did you make your decision?
I don't think anyone
will choose this one.
- I'll go with this one.
- Okay.
- You have chosen seafood.
- Right.
Head outside through this way...
- and wait. Yes.
- Do I bring it with me?
(The members that have chosen
get moved inside.)
Please close the door.
(Sniffing)
(These people are quite hungry.)
I tasted it, and it was really good.
I think going in first could be bad.
- Right.
- That could be true.
To be honest, Jong Min
would place first if he were young.
It would be hard to beat Jong Min
if he were young.
- Jong Min was really handsome.
- Jong Min would've placed first.
- Right.
- This shows...
how much you can drop down
if you don't take care of yourself.
What do you mean I've dropped down?
He was really handsome
when he was young.
The nose that looks like a frog
about to jump is really funny.
- Let's see it.
- A frog about to jump.
Here.
Who came up with that one?
- Tae Hyun kept saying that.
- Really?
I think it will jump
if I press it like this.
It looks exactly like a frog.
- Seon Ho, please head inside,
- What?
I'll scream inside...
- if it's something weird.
- Okay.
- Check how it is inside.
Something feels off.
(Seon Ho heads into the kitchen
as well.)
So I have to choose something...
- that Joon hasn't chosen.
- Right.
All right. Is Joon over there?
Let's think about Joon...
from what I know about him.
He is someone who finds protein
to be very important.
I think Joon
would have chosen pork belly.
But he might've
made a drastic change...
and went with budae stew.
That thought fills up my head.
I don't think anyone
will choose this one.
(I don't think anyone
will choose the seafood.)
(He will end up choosing
the same one as Joon at this rate!)
I like this one better
than these two.
(Seon Ho went with seafood.)
Why didn't you go
with what you would've chosen?
You should've chosen pork belly.
Why must I choose pork belly?
Why did you choose that one?
I've never made it obvious
about pork belly.
You always talked about
the importance of protein.
- I was talking about carbs!
- Please keep your voices down.
We can't even fight?
You should've chosen pork belly!
Why did you choose this?
- Why did you choose this?
- What about you?
- Because I like this.
- I like it too.
- All right. From now on...
- Pork belly...
Please be quiet, Seon Ho and Joon.
- This is much better!
- I love this.
I love this more too.
Do not say a word from now on.
Fight without making any sounds
with your mouths.
We need to fight right now.
Really? I think this will be
a good scene for the show.
They can hear you from inside.
DinDin is in third place, right?
Yes.
The good-looking ones
will head inside first.
Sure. See what it's like inside.
Why is he being so annoying?
- Gosh.
- He thinks he's good-looking?
What is this?
Did you figure it out?
(This has nothing to do with looks.)
Choose an ingredient
and head outside.
(He must not choose
what the other members have chosen.)
Gosh, this is hard.
(Opening)
(Is it seafood again?)
No way. Don't be like that.
What did you choose?
Thank goodness.
(DinDin chose rice.)
DinDin.
- I thought he'd choose pork belly.
- I don't have any thoughts.
- Everyone.
- Yes.
Do you know what this is about?
- Not at all.
- No. What are we doing?
You guys are...
playing Dinner Game now.
What are we doing?
Then why...
We don't get to eat?
(Laughing)
- What?
- I won't be eating?
I...
I bought pen shells.
And I got scallops.
I had to rack my head at the market.
I bought them
while imagining delicious food.
- What is this?
I'm hungry.
I have no idea what this is about.
Try to guess what you are doing now.
- Guess?
- I believe it will help.
So, is this a team game?
(He remains silent
when he's asked questions.)
I guess not.
I have no idea.
(I have no idea.)
Jong Min, you should go.
- Okay.
- What's going on?
I guess I get to eat.
(He understood the mission.)
(Surprisingly, he goes
through the bag of vegetables.)
The vegetables... Hang on.
I don't think they will eat this
even if I take it.
I will make a bold choice.
If we keep going like this,
- we won't get pork belly.
- I know.
(Kim Frog Nose makes
a creaking entrance.)
I'm sure Jong Min picked ramyeon.
- I was right.
- Jong Min always picks ramyeon.
That's the rule.
- Jong Min picks ramyeon.
- Right.
- I knew he'd pick this.
- And Se Yoon will pick kimchi.
- Se Yoon will get kimchi for sure.
- Listen.
Hang on. If...
(Hang on a second.)
If Sae Ho picks rice...
and Se Yoon picks this,
- we won't get to eat anything?
- You can't eat.
What kind of game is that?
Do we have to starve?
We should've eaten
200 dollars worth of twisted donuts.
You're right.
(They reflect on themselves
right away.)
We should've bought
200 dollars worth of twisted donuts.
If they pick the wrong one...
We have an ax here.
(We have an ax here!)
- Is this the Dinner Game?
- Yes.
- Director Joo.
In a situation like this,
when you say, "Can you guess,"
is there anyone who says yes?
I'm really curious. What about you?
- Let's say if there's...
- We were just sitting still.
(He finally realizes
how Director Joo makes a fool of them.)
He looks at us
as if we are really stupid.
"Can't you still guess what it is?"
That makes me lose my self-esteem.
- This is...
- Why are you doing this?
You just let us
rank our appearances...
and told us to go in.
Then you ask us if we can guess.
How would we even guess?
Does it have to be like a gamble?
He just looked at us
as if we were pathetic.
How would we even make a guess?
If there is a disadvantage
depending on the ranking,
- that's just wrong.
- It's bad. It's horrible.
Please go in.
Good luck.
Among the ingredients
in front of you,
choose one and head outside.
I can't think of anything.
This is driving me crazy.
If the ingredients overlap,
do we have to return them?
Do I have to choose what I want?
(He touches the kimchi right away.)
By the way, why is it deflated?
What's this? Who touched my kimchi?
- It's deflated.
- We didn't touch it.
- I know you did.
- We didn't.
It's supposed to be full of air.
Who touched it?
Be honest. You saw it, right?
Did you take some?
This is...
This looks totally different.
Are you messing with me?
What are you doing?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
Hang on.
(Se Yoon's eyes change.)
If my guess is right,
the 1st person
would've taken number 1.
The 2nd person took number 2.
And the 3rd person took number 3.
If they took things
in order like that,
we would get to eat the whole thing.
(Taking the ingredients
in the order of entry)
(The same number of members
has to come out.)
One, two, three.
(During the Read the Room and Escape
in Uljin)
It's easy. Those on the second floor
should stay inside.
(They came up with the strategy
where they went out in order.)
(Only those
in Rooms 1, 2, and 3 went out.)
- Why did you come out?
- You shouldn't come out.
- Is everyone out?
- This is... My gosh.
(Se Yoon was the only one
who didn't figure it out...)
(and got scolded severely.)
(Read the room.)
I'm also a member.
(Laughing)
During Read the Room and Escape,
I didn't understand the rules.
I believe them.
We have been trained.
I should trust them
and do as we were trained.
That's what I should do.
Should I go out now?
Please, my members... Please.
We had to calculate everything...
to buy all this.
(Guys, I did it!)
(He spots the rice
in DinDin's hands.)
- Really?
- We know what you chose.
He's holding it with one hand.
- That means it's rice or...
- It's kimchi.
- Pork belly.
- It must be 1 of the 3.
Is he holding pork belly vertically?
- Is he holding it vertically?
- Hey! You fools.
The 1st person should pick number 1.
- My goodness.
- I picked number five.
We have to return the rice?
What are we going to eat?
Hey, this is
what we practiced all the time.
You're right.
You fool.
We should've taken things
in order... What's this?
We should've picked them
in order. You fools.
- My goodness.
- What did you do?
This is crazy.
(They scolded me
so harshly the other day.)
Numbers 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, and 6!
You scolded me on the balcony.
- My goodness.
- We will just eat budae stew.
Unbelievable.
- If Sae Ho picks this...
- If he does, it will be over.
My gosh. What do we do?
We will have to skip dinner.
But Sae Ho is now...
If he's the ugliest one
and doesn't get to eat,
he will be really upset.
Why did we take a vote?
- I know. To begin with...
- We could've done it randomly.
Please.
If Sae Ho picks pork belly here,
- we can eat this with pork belly.
- That would be nice.
(Will Sae Ho be able
to become a hero?)
(He understood the mission.)
I'll rule a few things out first.
- Okay.
- The thing...
I don't have to eat tonight is...
- This would be it.
- You will leave it out.
I'll leave this out.
And this too.
- Rice too?
- Yes.
It's hard to tell what Joon chose.
Joon could've been simple
and picked pork belly.
Seon Ho would never choose seafood.
He recently caught norovirus,
so he can't eat seafood.
They said they wanted to eat this.
(All his guesses are wrong.)
(What's his final choice?)
Sae Ho is coming. He's out.
Don't look.
- Sae Ho.
- Yes.
- Did you choose one?
Just tell us this.
Is it 1 of numbers 1, 2, and 3?
Or is it 1 of numbers 4, 5, and 6?
- It's 1 of numbers 1, 2, and 3.
- What?
(It's either pork belly,
budae stew, or kimchi.)
Walk over here.
This is bad.
You can be a star here.
Please.
(It's a chance for him
to become our star!)
I wish my guess was right.
Please.
One, two, three.
Pork belly!
Three. Pork belly!
(Sae Ho chose pork belly.)
(Sae Ho did it.)
- Sae Ho! You did it!
- My goodness.
You're Cha Eun Woo.
- Cho Eun Woo.
- I did a great job.
Is it a good one?
- You did well.
- I see.
My goodness.
This is the best.
- It's perfect.
- It's amazing.
I made a guess.
- How?
With telepathy,
I thought you let the last member
to pick pork belly.
- I see.
- So I chose pork belly.
- Good job.
- I thought it would work.
- You did a great job.
- Well done.
- Really?
- It's good. It's all thanks to you.
- You did a great job.
- Is this a joke?
- No, we get to eat thanks to you.
- Really?
This feels strange.
(It feels strange
that you guys are praising me.)
- Okay.
- All right, everyone.
- I'm so relieved.
- You will eat...
- pork belly and budae stew.
- Thank goodness.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- We got the good ones.
- They are the main dishes.
- We are eating two main dishes.
- Right.
We will clean the kitchen now.
- Please wait a moment.
- Okay.
Sae Ho saved us.
- This feels good.
- You did a good job.
Guys, let's eat.
The budae stew doesn't have
vegetables in it.
Anyway, we can make it
salty and spicy.
And grill the meat...
Why are we grilling the meat?
- I'll do it.
- Joon will do it.
We have workers here.
- I saw a big pot in there.
- Okay.
Bring it. We will use it
to cook ramyeon.
Then we can grill meat.
Don't tell us what you'll do.
Just do it.
- Have a seat and wait.
- I was like,
"Why is he telling us what to do?"
- I know.
- This is nice.
Come to think of it...
Have some chat while you wait.
- My gosh.
- Why did you bring seafood?
- The workers... Gosh.
- Okay.
All right. Shall we begin?
(The workers start cooking.)
For the past four years,
I've never been so relaxed
during our trips.
- Is it your first time?
- Yes.
- It's strange because I'm relaxed.
- I know.
Even when things were easy,
we always had at least one issue.
- But we don't have any now.
- I bet there will be one tomorrow.
This is just nice.
Sae Ho hurt his leg.
Right.
Things should be easy
until Sae Ho is fully recovered.
Sae Ho, you said
it would take about two years.
- Three years.
- Right.
- Including rehabilitation...
- It takes a long time.
It will take three years until
I can do the One-legged Fight again.
- One-legged Fight?
- And two years until jegichagi.
If it's that bad,
you should quit this show.
(He should quit the show then.)
Let's wait and see.
- If it turns out...
- Wait and see?
that I can't do it,
I'll write a letter...
and leave the show.
Should we go and take a look?
I'll just go and check things.
I want to see.
I'll see
if there's anything I can eat.
- We will grill the pork belly.
- Let me help.
I think it will take a long time.
- No.
- You can cook the meat there.
Where?
What? No, you can't eat it.
I need to taste it.
- No.
- Why not?
- I can grill meat well.
- It's raw.
- Is it okay to eat it raw?
- Yes.
(DinDin also achieved his goal.)
Do you want me to cook pork belly?
- I'll do it. We can do it together.
- Okay.
I'm good at this.
The color looks nice.
- Turn on the stove.
- Turn it on?
You do it.
- Why? Because it's dangerous?
- Yes.
(Kim Scaredy-cat is scared.)
If it's dangerous, we all will
die together when it bursts.
- Really?
- Yes.
- But I'm right in front of it.
- I'll do it.
Right. It's more dangerous.
Isn't this how you turn it on?
No. Hang on.
- Is it open?
- You should open it.
Let me do it. I'll do it for you.
It says "open."
(Keeping his distance)
You must open it some more.
This is so annoying.
(DinDin has to finish up.)
That's it.
- It's hot.
- What are you doing?
(These two aren't much help.)
Did you clean this?
(Cooking begins in earnest.)
Wipe it with some grease.
(They grease the pan first.)
(Sizzling)
- What nice pork belly.
- Sae Ho.
How many does this serve?
- This is enough for nine.
- Sounds good.
One strip is one portion.
Shall I sprinkle some black pepper?
- Yes.
- Salt and pepper.
That's it. Lovely.
It looks great.
I think that's about enough.
- Yes.
- Black pepper is nice.
- Leave some for the other side.
- It looks so good.
- My gosh.
- Look at this.
Just look at the color.
- Gosh.
- It's amazing.
- Sae Ho did us good today.
- Yes.
We wouldn't have this
if not for him.
Sae Ho did great.
I think we chose well.
Keep it rough and simple.
There's no need to make it fancy.
This is just...
(He starts with ham,
the main ingredient.)
(Shaking it out expertly)
(Meticulous slicing)
(Chef Moon doesn't disappoint.)
What do you need me to do?
- Shall we make the base?
- Shall we?
That's done.
(Estimating the amount of soy sauce)
(Estimating the amount of gochujang)
We don't have kimchi,
so we need the secret sauce.
(MSG is added.)
(And some ramyeon powder too.)
(Mix it well.)
(Mix the sauce base
into beef bone broth.)
It looks good.
- You think so?
- It'll be good enough.
We have only a few ingredients.
It'll taste good
with what little we have.
Let's slice it and fry it.
- We have to cut it.
- Cut it up.
(They cut it to cook it thoroughly.)
It sounds fantastic.
(Full of juice)
Can I taste this piece?
- Yes.
- Go ahead.
It's incredible. This is great.
- Let's all have a piece.
- Yes.
- Me too. I want a taste.
- Have this piece.
- Eat one.
- The oil is splashing.
Can I eat it as is?
My gosh.
(What's this noise?)
Are you starting first?
(Next episode)
(A romantic countryside barbecue)
(Are you starting first?)
(Explosive nagging)
(It's not easy being a worker.)
(Whining)
(At last, it's time...)
(to change their status.)
- Hurry up.
- It's close.
(Let your guard down,)
(and you become a worker.)
Now it's dangerous.
(Please!)
(Anyone but me!)
(The surface wobbles.)
(Who will be the new worker?)