I'm glad we found each other.
- We did well.
- We did.
How do we all sleep indoors?
How long has it been
since we all slept together?
The lodging. Why is it so nice?
- What's this?
- This is insane.
- It's madness.
- It's so nice.
We're sleeping in a nice place.
(Pretty vines welcome them
to the lodging.)
- Hey, meringue...
- Isn't this the meringue place?
Isn't this the meringue place?
Yes, we were here before.
- Jong Min was...
- We were here before.
I remember this place.
(3 years ago, a meringue mission
decided where they would sleep.)
Go on.
(Jong Min suddenly attacked,)
(but he suffered greatly
when DinDin got back at him.)
(This place holds
scary memories of meringue.)
This place is amazing.
Let's go. It's nice here.
I'll show you around.
- This place is awesome.
- We came here often.
- Show me around.
- Okay. Come along.
We're sleeping in a nice place.
- This is an incredible place.
- It's insane.
(They love their base camp,
and they're feeling great.)
We can drink this.
- For real?
- We can drink this.
- We can?
- It's to welcome us.
- Can we really drink it?
- I don't know.
(Smiling)
- We can't drink it.
- They're here.
We came back.
- It's so...
- There's a room with beds.
Can we eat something?
This place is insane.
Jong Min's
going to drink the coffee.
There's a room with beds.
My gosh, this is...
- It was nice here.
- There's a bidet too.
- Of course.
(Eating)
- What are you eating so much of?
- What?
- What are you eating?
What are you eating?
- What's that?
- What...
- What are you doing?
- What's this?
- In the open?
- It won't kill you. It's a coin.
(Jong Min had been
secretly eating...)
(the gold coin chocolate.)
(Glancing)
- You're so thick-faced.
- What the heck?
(What is with him?)
- I thought the coin...
- The gold coin...
- How many are there?
- You're unbelievable.
My gosh.
- How many did you eat?
- What are you doing?
Two?
If you had this many,
you should've asked
if we wanted any.
- He just...
- You kept eating.
He sat here and ate
as if it were no big deal.
We still have a lot.
- Director Joo is entering.
- What's going on?
- Aren't you hungry?
- Yes.
- Let's get going then.
- Okay.
- Great.
- Let's go and eat.
Let's go and eat, guys.
(As the cloudy sky clears up,
the moon shines brightly today.)
We're lucky that it stopped raining.
- Right. My gosh, it's so humid.
- Yes.
Where are we going to eat?
(Director Joo, give us our food.)
You must be getting hungry now.
- I'm hungry.
- I'm starving.
- It's getting pretty late.
- "Now?"
- It's 10 p.m. now.
- It's past 10 p.m. now.
You've been on an adventure today.
- Is it still ongoing?
- Yes.
Actually,
the biggest firefly habitat is
on a nearby mountain, Mount Unmun.
And it's the first place where
fireflies are spotted in Korea.
- I want to see some fireflies.
- Fireflies are beautiful.
This natural greenhouse is called
Cheongsuri Gotjawal.
- Cheongsuri Gotjawal.
- We prepared to go there today.
- But we got here late today.
- We can't see the fireflies then?
- So...
- And it's raining too.
Fireflies are spotted
only in clean areas.
- Really?
- I see.
- They're spotted only for a month.
- Right. In June.
- They're spotted from June to July.
- But we won't get to see them?
(They're much more beautiful
in person.)
(The fireflies shine brightly
as they greet summer.)
(They radiate brightly and disappear
like the stars in the night sky.)
- Gosh, that's amazing.
- What?
That's what we prepared.
- Let's check it out next year.
- We ought to do that.
Let's do that then.
- All right then.
- What about our dinner?
You must embark on a journey
for your dinner.
- A journey?
- By the way,
- Yes?
- when will today's journey end?
I'm so hungry that
my stomach is hurting.
- You must be quite hungry.
- Yes.
Today's dinner is
about the pride of Jeju.
Is it black pork?
It's a black pork meal
with an assortment of special cuts.
- Let's get this.
- We ought to eat this.
- It's not Jeju without black pork.
- This is great.
(The staff picked up
special cuts of black pork...)
(from a famous local restaurant.)
(Pork neck, thin skirt, gabrisal,
pork jowl, collar butt, pork temple)
You can't see it from here.
But there's a mountain
called Mount Sanbang.
- Yes, I know that mountain.
- It's a famous mountain.
- Mount Sanbang.
Legend has it that
the Great Jade Emperor tore...
the peak of Mount Halla
and threw it.
And that became Mount Sanbang.
So this mystical mountain comes
with a legend of its own.
- He threw it?
- Yes.
We prepared the Dinner Game
with the mystical energy...
of Mount Sanbang.
It's Jeju Makeover Challenge.
- "Jeju Makeover Challenge?"
- Yes.
Just like the title,
you must undergo a makeover...
for this mission.
It will be a 3-on-3 team match.
It will be a best-of-three match.
Then only 3 of us can eat.
And the other 3 can't eat.
This is the worst.
We can't let them have black pork.
(Whom should I team up with?)
Who had hairtails earlier?
What? Did all of you eat them?
Is that
how you want to divide up the teams?
- You want your revenge? Is that it?
- Yes, it's a revenge match.
- If we do that, it's likely...
- We can...
- that we might lose.
- Joon can't eat then.
- Do you not want me on your team?
- Yes.
- You're looking down on me.
- No.
- He's totally looking down on you.
- I'm good at makeovers.
- No. That's not the problem.
- Come on. Believe in him.
But everyone is trying to avoid
teaming up with you.
- No.
- Why are you avoiding me?
- Are you trying to avoid me?
- That's not it.
- You should ask Sae Ho too.
- Hey.
- His opinion is important too.
- What do you think, Sae Ho?
Won't it be fun
if we mix up the teams?
- Right. Well...
- The thing is...
- How did I end up as the weakest?
- No.
- Okay. Are you really confident?
- I'm really confident.
- Okay. I'll team up with you.
- No. You can't believe that.
This is how we lost earlier.
- My hands are tied.
- Hey, join them.
- He and I were the new recruits.
- Who knows?
- Hey, you have no confidence in me?
- Join them.
- But I'm really hungry.
- Is that all you amount to?
- Hey, I'll get you dinner.
- You can win dinner then.
- Why...
- I'm sure he'll carry your team.
- Why are you so scared?
- Promise me one thing.
What promise?
- Let's do our best.
- Right.
I've always done my best.
It's not about doing our best.
Let's do well.
- We'll have a feast. Let's do this.
- Promise me one thing.
(Satisfied)
Hey,
check out the color of my shirt.
- Black.
- It means I'm getting black pork.
- You're a black pig today.
- Right.
- You're dressed like a black pig.
- You're dressed in black.
(His outfit is time, place,
and occasion appropriate.)
Why do you think
I'm wearing a black shirt?
- Really?
- It's for black pork.
He suddenly changed his outfit
and dressed like a black pig.
- A black shirt for Jeju.
- You bet.
We have the game in the bag.
- Here's the name of our team.
- Yes?
- We are...
- What is this?
- Team Along with Joon.
We're Team Along with Joon.
- I see. That's great.
- Believe in me.
- Team Along with Joon.
- I'll get you dinner.
We don't need to come up
with names like that.
- We're Team Original.
- Okay.
- Team Pure-Blooded.
- Team Pure-Blooded?
- Yes. We're Team Pure-Blooded.
If you're ready,
let's start the first round.
(Darn it.
I think we're going to lose.)
Hey, don't be scared.
- I know what we're doing.
- Come on.
- We have to put on the outfit.
- Gosh.
Okay.
Gosh, Team Along with Joon.
For the first round
of the Jeju Makeover Challenge,
you must transform into...
- a haenyeo.
- Transform into a haenyeo.
The team that finishes putting on
the haenyeo diver suits first...
- in the relay will win the round.
- This?
Only those
who finish putting on the suit...
- can help the next person.
- Okay.
Everyone on the team must put on
the haenyeo diver suits.
Then the team
that rings the bell first will win.
Then we have to take off our pants.
I think you can wear the suit
on top of your clothes.
- Take it easy.
- But my pants are wide.
- I have a disadvantage.
- Right. Yours are too wide.
- Hey. I should take them off.
- Come on.
- You'll take them off again?
- If...
If we take off our clothes,
can you blur us?
I want to stop taking off
my clothes on the show. Please.
We can blur you out.
I took off my clothes too many times
on the show. I hate it too.
- You did take them off quite often.
- I hate it too.
You're taking off your clothes
once every month.
- Do you want to go and change?
- All together. Okay.
- Can I?
- Yes.
- You'll change your pants?
- No.
- You can't do that.
- We don't have time.
This is why
no one wanted to team up with you.
Hey. Watch me.
- I'll take off my pants.
- Sure.
- Take them off. We can, right?
- Hey.
- Whatever.
- He's always stripping on our show.
- No.
- This should be the order.
This should be the order.
- I'm going to need help.
- No. He must go second.
I'll be honest. I've done
this game before on the show.
But I wasn't good at it.
I shouldn't go first.
- This guy...
- Then...
- I should go 2nd.
- I'll go 1st.
- I'm good at this.
- Yes, I think you'll be good at it.
- Great. We're ready.
- Let's go for it.
- We're ready.
- Let's go. Let's do this.
- Did you decide on the order?
- Jong Hyun.
Make sure to blur out my body.
- I'm serious.
- Okay.
Writers, don't be so shocked.
(Warning them in advance)
Let's begin.
Get ready.
(1st, 2nd, and 3rd)
Sae Ho. Zip up your pants.
And then we'll begin.
- Hey. Come on.
- My gosh.
- Come on.
- Hey!
I'm sorry.
- Our show is classy.
- I...
Let me formally apologize.
How dare you expose your underwear?
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
You can't play it like that.
- Get ready.
- What's up with the socks?
Set.
- Let's go.
- Let's do this.
Let's go.
- He's exposing his underwear.
- Come on.
- What is this? Come on.
- What is this?
This is just disgusting.
- Let's do this.
- You're fast.
- My gosh.
- Show them.
- Calm down.
(Jong Min quickly puts in
one of his legs.)
- You're fast.
- Show them.
- Calm down.
- Take your time.
- Okay. Don't worry.
- Show them.
- You're fast.
- This is so tight.
- We're faster.
- This is it.
- We're ahead.
- We're winning.
- Hey.
- There you go!
- Yes, that's it.
- Square your shoulders.
- That's it.
- My gosh.
- You won.
- You got this.
- There you go.
- My gosh.
- It has to cover up more.
- Let it cover up.
- It must cover up more.
- That's it.
It must cover up more.
- Okay.
- Hey, go.
- Right here. Put it on.
- You got this, Jong Min.
(A fully dressed member
can help other members.)
No.
You got this, Jong Min.
(They're frustrated
as they can't help him.)
(He just needs to zip it up.)
Hurry up. Come on.
- You got it.
- That's it.
- Okay.
- Put it on.
He must put on the cap.
- Hurry up.
- Put it on.
- Okay.
- Help him.
(They must pick up the speed,
but Se Yoon is up next.)
(He puts on the cap first
as it's easy to put on.)
Stop laughing. Don't laugh.
- Put it in.
Go ahead.
(Se Yoon is doing better
than anticipated.)
(He's not helping.
He just has his hand on Se Yoon.)
(Seon Ho will be done
once he puts on the cap?)
- Seon Ho.
- Get your arms.
No, Seon Ho isn't done. Wait.
- His zipper is open. Stop, Joon.
- Seon Ho isn't ready.
- Seon Ho.
- The zipper...
The zipper is broken.
- Okay. Go ahead.
- Okay.
(Meanwhile, Se Yoon finishes
putting on the suit super quickly.)
- I'm done.
- Go.
The last members are up!
(They start putting on the suit
at the same time.)
Here.
- Put in your legs.
- They're neck-and-neck.
Put it on.
(I had to take off my clothes again.
I can't lose now.)
- Your arms.
- Put in your arms.
- Just put in your arms.
- I got it.
- One, two.
- Okay.
- Right away...
(Popping into the suit)
(He perfectly puts on the suit
without any difficulty.)
- Go.
- My gosh.
(They try to catch up
instead of giving up.)
(The game is already over.)
- Ring the bell. Okay.
- The bell!
(Team Pure-Blooded wins.)
- Team Pure-Blooded!
(This is the know-how
of the original members.)
We couldn't get past this.
(Feeling dejected)
(Why did we even bother
taking off our clothes?)
- Hey, he put it on in one go.
- We had a great strategy.
(Good job on your wasted effort.)
Let's continue
with the second round.
The second round
of the Jeju Makeover Challenge is...
Transform into Dol Hareubang.
- What?
- All right.
Bring it in now.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Let's begin.
For this round, you must put on
the cap like Se Yoon.
- Your hair can't...
- It can't stick out?
- Right. Cover up your hair.
- Like this?
Wait. Aren't you Pong Pong Man?
(Dancing his signature move
right away)
- Show us your act.
- I haven't seen that in a while.
But I'm shy.
- It's fine.
- I'm good.
Everyone.
Here's the guest of today's episode.
- Help me, Pong Pong Man!
- Go.
(Back in the day, he was the fatty,
beloved by everyone.)
(His movements are sharp
despite his big build.)
(This dance was a sensation
in 2007.)
(The original performer shows us
the 2025 version of the dance.)
(His facial expression
has become more authentic.)
(Fascinated)
Let's win!
I haven't seen that in a while.
- It's been so long.
- It's been a while since I saw it.
- It's been a while, hasn't it?
- Everyone.
This time, you'll transform...
into dol hareubang,
the local symbol.
Your goal is to apply
the black cream on your face.
To win,
you must beat the other team...
at painting your faces black
like dol hareubang.
- All three of us must do it?
- Yes.
All of your faces
must be painted black.
Then wear the hats
on top of the judgment table.
You know the dol hareubang pose,
right?
- What pose?
- What is it?
This is the pose.
Your right hand is higher.
The right hand goes higher.
This is the perfect example.
All of your skin must be covered.
Once you do that pose...
With that pose, your team will win.
Hold on.
- We can wash it off, right?
- Of course.
My face won't look black
on my way to Seoul tomorrow, right?
- All right.
- Try to push up the cap.
But you can't touch your own face.
Teammates must apply it
on each other's faces.
I'll start in this pose.
(Let's begin in this pose too.)
- Team Pure-Blooded.
- All right.
(They're ready.)
Get ready.
Set.
(Transform into Dol Hareubang
starts!)
(Team Pure-Blooded's strategy is...)
(to paint two of their faces
simultaneously.)
Close your eyes.
(Se Yoon with big hands applies
the cream with delicate touches.)
(Their strategy is that 2 members
will work on 1 member together.)
- This is good.
- That's good.
Great.
- Okay. Good. Don't open your eyes.
- Don't open your eyes.
- That's good. Come here, Joon.
- Good.
(He kind of looks funny.)
I need to apply a bit more.
- Close your eyes.
- It's working.
(His touches on Joon
are even more aggressive.)
We can't miss a spot.
- We must cover everything.
- Joon's cheeks.
- We got it.
- Good.
(They're done with another one?)
- I'll close my eyes.
- Okay.
(Forget about being gentle.
They start applying it haphazardly.)
- I think we're good.
- We're good.
- We got it. Let me see.
- Let's see.
(We're good.)
(What do they need right now?)
(Speed!)
(Which team had the perfect makeover
to become dol hareubang?)
The right hand and then the left.
(We rang the bell first.)
My gosh. This is crazy.
(What's the result?)
(The perfect transformation
into dol hareubang)
Oh, my.
(Why won't you tell us the result?)
This round...
Guys, this round...
- Guys.
- Check the details.
Look at the middle
of DinDin's forehead.
(What about the middle
of his forehead?)
What is it?
- Look.
- Jong Min.
Let me see. They missed these spots.
- Really?
- These spots aren't covered.
- But our faces are fully covered.
- You can't fix it now.
Do you know what they remind me of?
They look like the white eyebrows...
- on those cute Shibas.
- What is this?
- I don't know what happened.
- I don't know how I look now.
- How did we miss those spots?
- What about you guys?
- We're fully covered.
(Then did you
fully paint your faces?)
- We're perfect.
- Yes.
We didn't miss any spots.
- All right.
- They did it perfectly, indeed.
Joon. You...
(Me?)
Hey, did you use a special product
or something?
Hold on. I saw him in New York!
I saw him in New York.
(Is that the kind of robot
spotted on the streets of New York?)
(A New Yorker shows up in Jeju.)
- I saw you in New York.
- Seriously.
- That's perfect.
- My gosh.
(Amazed)
- You get the vibe, right?
- This is amazing.
The second round
of Jeju Makeover Challenge...
- goes to Team Along with Joon.
- Okay.
We're not going to eat,
looking like this, right?
(Seon Ho's camera)
- That would be too mean.
- Do we have to eat in this state?
That would be too mean.
(You'll find out
once you get there.)
- Let's take a group picture.
- Yes.
- Yes. Let's take one.
- Take a picture of us.
- In this pose?
- Yes.
- We won't get a chance like this.
- Like statues.
- You should...
- Okay.
- We're dol hareubang.
- Look over there.
One, two, three.
(We're dol hareubang.)
- But this is funny, indeed.
- Yes.
Guys, we'll proceed
with the third round right away.
Great.
- We'll play in this condition?
- Yes.
The third round
of Jeju Makeover Challenge is...
Transform Back into Celebrities.
- Come on.
(Growling)
- Come on. Seriously?
- Come on.
- Why are you torturing us?
- This... My gosh.
- Why are you doing this to us?
- Come on.
- How...
- Is this fun for you?
Does it give you a thrill?
He was so happy when we were
playing the second round.
How can we transform back?
- All right. Set it up, please.
- We have to remove this.
I know this.
It's that humiliating game again.
(That day, his face was
painted black just like today.)
(It was a humiliating memory...)
(as he could only wash his face
with water from Se Yoon's back.)
(Joon's camera)
Guys, you need to come back
to your original condition, right?
Just like in the second round,
you can't touch your own face.
- What?
- The team that removes...
- You must tell me.
- more of the black cream will win.
- Okay.
Let me start without my hat.
(They remove the cap.)
(Laughing)
- You know what...
- He took it off nicely.
- It looks like Joon has a mask on.
- he looks like?
He looks like an actor in a movie
or something.
(I look like an actor?)
- You know?
- All right. Guys.
(I, Lee Joon,
will show you my superb acting.)
- Did you understand the rules?
- Yes.
This time, you can...
(It's shocking
how no one pays any attention.)
Two of you can only work
on one member.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Here's what we'll do.
- You'll start with your hands...
- at your sides.
- My hands won't reach.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Okay. You...
- Can you squeeze that?
- Okay.
Let's say you're washing my face.
But when I'm almost done,
- we must switch first.
- Okay.
Here's what you'll do.
The moment we begin,
- Splash my face with it.
- dip your face in the bucket.
- Should I dip it in the water?
- Yes, do that.
Let's begin. Get ready. Set.
Dip your face in.
(Both of them dip their faces
in the water first.)
Okay.
(Team Pure-Blooded's strategy is
to wash his face in the water.)
Come out for a second. Breathe.
Gosh, it's not coming off.
- You need to use something for it.
- Get the foaming cleanser.
Wait.
- Hold on.
- Wait.
(He rubs soap on Jong Min's face.)
This is what we have to do.
This is the best method.
- It won't come off.
But we tried it out.
(Team Along with Joon is struggling
with the same problem.)
(Not much has changed
with Seon Ho's face.)
Is it not working?
Then try it on me. Work on me.
You have to wash off
the soap first. Wait.
(You have to wash off
the soap first.)
Hold on. You can't touch your face.
- I can't see. Wait.
- Give that to me.
Why...
(It's a mess.)
You...
- It's not coming off at all.
- Hold on.
(He uses both hands,
but nothing is working.)
- Hey, this isn't working.
- Let's take our time.
- Let us work on you too.
- It's not coming off.
- It's not coming off at all.
Something has gone wrong.
- Who's next?
This isn't right.
We're having a mental breakdown.
Jong Min.
But yesterday...
(He's the most flustered one
of them all.)
(Resting his forehead on his hand)
Hold on, everyone.
(They bring in a new tool,
the cleansing tissue.)
- Hold on. Let's continue.
- What's that? Give that to me.
- Come on.
- Use that to wipe.
(Will the black cream come off
with the cleansing tissue?)
Wipe it off.
- It's working.
- What a relief.
- It's coming off.
Go easy on his face.
- I'll pull it out.
- Okay.
- Hold on.
- Hey. Wait.
(They're no longer
black dol hareubang.)
Gosh, it's coming off really well.
What a relief.
Step back.
- Hurry up.
- Are you up next?
Grab that.
(They're slowly transforming
into celebrities.)
- We must check for details.
- Fifteen seconds!
- Wipe that part.
- More.
- Open your eyes.
- That's good.
(Both teams give it their all
as they're nearing the end.)
- We must wipe each other's face.
- Ten,
- We can only work on one person.
- nine,
- eight, seven,
- Sae Ho. Let me.
six, five, four,
- three,
- Rinse it.
- two, one.
- Okay.
(The 3rd round is over.)
Okay!
He looks like himself.
- Can I ask you something?
- Sure.
Is this good?
My gosh. We're doomed.
You have a scary face.
- Yes.
- Hey, your forehead...
My gosh. That's...
Yes. We have to check everything.
My gosh.
(Team Pure-Blooded
versus Team Along with Joon)
- Many staff members...
- Yes?
evaluated your performance.
- Gosh. The foaming cleanser...
- All right.
- The Dinner Game...
- What?
(Which team is the final winner
of the Jeju Makeover Challenge?)
Team Pure-Blooded
is the final winner.
(Team Pure-Blooded wins!)
By the way...
(They fail to acquire dinner.)
By the way,
you haven't seen your faces yet.
- But your faces...
- Really?
(They look in the mirror to check.)
I told you
we had to be more thorough.
I have a lot of stains on my face.
I wouldn't have taken off my pants
had I known we would lose.
You know?
But given how we lost this game,
I'm not in the mood...
to eat dinner.
Right?
I lost my appetite for any food.
Give me whatever food you have.
I just need to quell my hunger
and go to sleep.
I'll just play a game
for the mission tomorrow morning...
and then go home.
- Don't you agree?
- Yes.
- Do you want to eat?
- I don't.
Right?
I'm not hungry.
(Even Joon has no appetite.)
- I have no appetite.
- Don't you feel the same way?
- Great job, everyone.
- Of course, we did a great job.
Did I say otherwise?
You know? I mean,
he's pointing out the obvious.
All right.
Let's go inside for your dinner.
- Where are you going?
- This way?
It's in the next building.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Everyone shows up,
freshly cleaned up.)
- All right. This is our table.
- What?
This is nice.
- Let's eat since we worked hard.
- My gosh. Yes. Jong Min.
- You sit in the middle.
- What's this?
Let's eat a lot
since we worked hard.
Gosh, these are the special cuts.
The special cuts.
(Their hard work is rewarded
with special cuts.)
What do you think about this meal
with special cuts?
- This looks great.
- Gosh, it looks great.
The meat has a great color.
The black pork looks beautiful.
(It has a brilliant color.)
(Pork neck, thin skirt, gabrisal,
pork jowl, collar butt, pork temple)
(An assembly of texture masters)
You may grill the meat and enjoy it.
- Really?
- Thank you for the food.
Thank you.
Se Yoon, can you add some garlic
to the salted anchovies?
- It should be added.
- That's a good idea.
You have to add it
to the salted anchovies.
I'll add it.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
I'll grill the meat now.
So it can be cooked right away.
- Which cut is it?
- I don't know.
That's called collar butt.
- This?
- It's the back of the pig's neck.
It's very chewy.
(It has an outstanding
chewy texture.)
Can you film this? This part.
- Will you film it?
- Can you lower your head?
It's collar butt.
Press the back.
Behind the neck.
(A real-life image
of different cuts)
Take a look.
- Oh, my.
- I can't look at this.
It's really delicious.
The meat is very firm.
(As the taste is familiar,
collar butt is harder to resist.)
Since we're in Jeju,
bracken is served.
Bracken is very delicious
on Jeju Island.
It's plump.
We need to discuss.
What should we do from now on?
(Analyzing the reason
for their defeat)
The three of us don't make
a bad team.
- We did well.
- We aren't a bad team,
- but we're missing something.
- It wasn't Joon's fault.
It wasn't Joon's fault this time.
- I did well today.
- Team Pure-Blooded was too good.
What are you doing this Sunday?
If you're free,
let's get together for a meeting.
I'm serious. Let's discuss.
Notify your musical team
that you won't be able to make it.
(Ask the musical team
for their understanding.)
Actually, you should perform.
We'll wait
until your performance ends.
- Outside the theater?
- We need to practice playing games.
It's near my house,
so I'll come and pick you up.
Right.
(With Joon forever)
- I should get ready.
- The meat is almost cooked.
- Really?
- The thin pieces.
I'll eat it with this.
You can eat the thin pieces.
It looks delicious.
(Golden)
(Spacing out)
Can we eat two pieces at a time?
Of course.
- There's a lot of meat.
- Thank you.
(They can even eat
three pieces at a time.)
I'll eat two pieces at a time.
(Aren't you jealous?)
The meat looks very delicious
as it's being grilled.
(2 pieces of meat
with 1 garlic clove)
Let's go, Team Pure-Blooded.
- Let's go!
- Eat two pieces at the same time.
All right.
(Taking a big bite)
It's really good.
It's so good.
It's nice and firm.
The meat is nice and firm.
It's really delicious.
It's nice and firm.
- What's this?
- It's excellent.
- Is it good?
- The black pork is very good.
(Drooling...)
(a lot)
- How is it so good?
- The texture is amazing.
(They love the firm texture.)
- The special cuts are...
- Yes.
- The meat is very good.
- It's delicious.
(The special cuts
are especially good.)
It also tastes outstanding
with some bracken.
Yes.
(Eating)
(He also takes a bite.)
(Black pork and bracken
make a perfect match.)
These cuts are unbelievable.
They're unbelievably good.
Right.
(Gosh, it looks delicious.)
Can we have a little?
(Begging)
Since everyone worked hard,
you deserve to eat.
- We'll bring you food right away.
- Right away?
- They didn't even win.
- I know.
It looks like rice.
Is it rice with a stew?
Rice. You got some food.
- Gosh, that's nice.
- It looks quite good.
- That's not bad at all.
- Of course not.
It looks okay.
There isn't enough broth.
This is fine.
- Give me some vegetables.
- The cabbage is delicious.
- Thank you for the food.
- Please enjoy.
It's hard to remove dirt
from my nails.
(Delicious)
This cheonggukjang is good.
(Savory cheonggukjang is also good,
but...)
(Glancing)
Isn't the meat flavor amazing?
The meat flavor is great.
- Isn't it as good as beef?
- Yes.
The pork flavor is excellent
once you fall in love with it.
Honestly,
I'd be satisfied with this meal,
but looking at them makes it hard.
I agree.
(A fantastic combination of
the smell and the sizzling sound)
I can't stop eating it.
(A fantastic combination of
the smell and the sizzling sound)
- It doesn't look cooked.
- Can you give me some earplugs?
To block that sound.
Isn't the sizzling sound insane?
Honestly,
what we're eating is good,
but having the meat next to us...
Team Along with Joon,
aren't you curious...
about how the special cuts taste?
Yes, I'd like to know.
I'll give you
a very simple mission...
to allow just one person...
to taste the cut of your choice.
(A chance to taste a special cut)
If Team Pure-Blooded is okay
with it,
we'll give a generous amount
in a small dish for soy sauce.
Okay.
- About that much...
- That's fine.
- Are you okay with it?
- Yes.
That should be okay.
We're on Jeju Island.
They deserve to taste some.
(Today's relief mission)
From the bundle of bracken,
the member who picks
the longest bracken will get...
to taste a special cut.
Okay.
- You're out if it breaks.
- Can I pick with my hand?
- You can pick it with your hand.
- Okay.
You must pick whatever you touch.
(After observing
the bracken carefully)
Okay, here I go.
(He picked one.)
(Its disadvantageous
if the first one is long.)
(What will be the result?)
What?
Why is it so short?
(Why did it snap already?)
Is it over already?
- Here I go.
- Go.
Please put it down.
Joon is really...
(Joon is so unlucky.)
No matter how hard Joon tries,
nothing is working out
for him today.
- This could be the longest.
- Right.
I'll go ahead.
Look how short mine is.
It's over once it snaps.
Pull it out at once.
It's done.
- Did Joon survive?
- Joon won.
- Okay.
I have to pick a good one.
- Let's go!
- Who?
Cho Sae Ho can do it.
(He cheers for himself.)
It's shorter than you think.
- I picked one.
- Okay.
It's over once it snaps.
- It will snap.
- It might be long.
(All three of them have
about the same length.)
(Did I win 1st place?)
- Joon.
- Mine is the shortest.
(Sae Ho, Seon Ho, Joon)
- Joon.
- Gosh, Joon.
- Oh, my.
- Your small plate.
- Joon, bring it.
What's going on?
- I'm fine.
- There was this one.
- Did you win?
- Joon got lucky this time.
Pork neck is ready.
- Mine wasn't very long.
- Try some pork neck.
Take some pork neck.
Okay.
- Mine wasn't very long.
- Take this.
My teammates.
He asked us to join his team.
Honestly, I didn't want to join him.
- Hey, he kept...
- I'll be honest.
I didn't want to join his team.
I wanted to join the other team.
- Have some bracken.
- No.
He only took meat.
(Only meat)
(Anticipating the first bite
of the special cut)
How does it taste?
(His eyes widen.)
Is there any salt?
- My teammates.
- Can I try a piece?
What?
- Well done.
- Okay.
- I will...
- Thank you.
- share it with you.
- Please eat.
(Let's comfort ourselves
with savory meat.)
Can I get some salt?
- What?
- Over there...
- I can sprinkle some on your face.
- Go ahead.
- Which salt?
- The pink salt.
Sprinkle a lot on it.
- That's great.
- Yes.
Can you sprinkle more
like Chef Choi Hyun Seok?
(One more time
like Chef Choi Hyun Seok)
That's nice.
(Clinking with salt)
Is it good?
This is good.
(In awe)
(The more you chew,
the more the special cut tastes savory.)
It's so good that it's annoying.
- We can win next time.
- Let's win.
I wish I could have
one more bite of the meat.
- You want 1 more bite of the meat?
- Just 1 more bite.
Don't you agree?
Yes.
He should have some more
to be happy.
- Let's give him a piece.
- Thank you.
Take this greasy piece of pork neck.
- Gosh.
- Take it.
This is for Seon Ho.
- However,
- Pork neck.
to enjoy this piece completely,
- eat it with anything you want.
- Anything.
- Make the perfect wrap.
- Thank you.
You'll be eating everything
Jeju has to offer.
(Jeju in one bite)
That sounds good.
Let me know if you want more.
(Stacking up food neatly
to make a wrap)
Thanks to you, I get to
take a bite as big as I want.
- Wrap it with dried laver.
- Thank you.
I'm happy today.
(Eating)
(It doesn't take much to be happy.)
- That was nice.
- It's really good.
(Happiness is sharing delicious food
with good people.)
What?
It was a good day today.
- We finished it all.
- It was delicious.
(Everyone is happy
at the end of dinner.)
You worked very hard...
during the expedition today.
For tomorrow, on Jeju Island...
- Expedition?
- We will decide...
your last expedition.
Are we deciding it now?
Is this really happening?
- It's starting now.
- Deciding it now means...
that it will take place
tomorrow morning.
- Wait.
- It must be hiking.
I have a question.
Would you be willing...
to play a team game?
A team game?
- They're thinking.
- No.
You're thinking hard about it.
Even as a beginner,
I can easily tell...
what it will be.
All of us expect it to be...
- hiking Mount Halla.
- Everyone.
"Life is C between B and D."
"Life is C..."
"between B and D."
- Isn't that right?
- What does it mean?
It's about the choice
between birth and death.
(Life is a choice
between birth and death.)
For your last expedition tomorrow,
there are two types.
What?
This is so nerve-racking.
- My goodness.
- It must be Mount Halla.
It's up to luck. It can't be helped.
You'll find out what type
of expedition it is...
once you get there.
Will we go there without knowing?
Each of you will be going there now.
- Each of us?
- You'll know when you get there.
Let's say our two choices are...
- A and B.
- What if everyone picks A?
- It could be 4 to 2 or 5 to 1.
- Yes.
Will that not matter?
Each room can accommodate
three people.
(Inside the members' lodging)
(There are 2 rooms,
and each accommodates 3 people.)
(Room D for 3 people)
(Choose 1 of the 2 rooms)
(Expedition sites will be revealed
once they make their choice.)
Let's say that there's a room
for Mount Halla.
Three people chose that room.
Then...
- In that case,
- The others can't go there?
the remaining members
can't go there?
Then it's better to choose later.
You never know.
If the other room is full,
you have to go to Mount Halla.
Are we going to Mount Halla?
Why are we assuming that?
Why aren't you negating it?
Tell us where we're going.
So we can prepare ourselves
before going to sleep.
Why do you look so sad?
(Viewers, we will tell you first.)
(One of them is
going to Mount Halla.)
Since the maximum number
of people is three,
the order of choosing
is also important.
Please decide
in which order you'll choose.
Shall we pick bracken again?
- Let's do that.
- What bracken?
- Bracken is over there.
- Okay.
- With the remaining bracken.
- Let's go with luck.
- Let's pick bracken.
- In the order of who picks...
- the longest bracken?
- Yes.
Let's see.
That doesn't look bad.
It doesn't look bad.
That looks good.
(Jong Min is the second person
to pick.)
- Gosh.
- It's not that long.
It's long.
Pull it out quickly.
(Se Yoon picks one
with his thick hand.)
(Sighing)
- It's very short.
- I'm going next.
- The longest one is mine.
- Okay.
- Here I go.
- DinDin is in second place.
- I'll go right away.
Didn't it snap?
(Sae Ho and Joon also picked
their bracken.)
Joon is in last place.
- Joon is in last place.
All right, tell me
in which order you'll choose.
- I'm number one.
- This is insane.
I'm number two.
(The order of choosing the room)
(Numbers 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6)
My goodness. Look.
(More vivid and thrilling
than any other expedition so far)
(The last game
for their last expedition)
(What will be the members' fate?)
This is the last one.
- All right.
- My goodness.
- Sae Ho.
- Number one.
- Okay.
- Good luck.
- Go.
- We'll meet somewhere.
I bet Se Yoon...
- and I'll go to Mount Halla.
- I can do it.
- It's because...
- Me?
- What?
- Why me?
That's just how I feel.
Fortunately, you were wrong
about everything today.
(Sae Ho heads to pick
one of the rooms.)
(Watch me.)
(He faces two rooms with a sigh.)
(Glancing)
It's driving me crazy.
(Which room will be Mount Halla?)
I think these members
will go to Mount Halla.
You, you, and me.
- Who?
- That's good.
- You, me, and Joon.
I don't think so.
- That wouldn't be good.
- We'll find out.
Next up is Jong Min.
- Jong Min.
- That's me.
- Okay.
- Be careful. It's slippery.
Jong Min.
(Good luck, Jong Min.)
(Jong Min moves
while looking around in doubt.)
What is it?
Sae Ho.
What's this?
Between B and D.
Choice.
Sae Ho!
(Sae Ho has already picked a room.)
How can I make a choice
without knowing anything?
I can't base my deduction
on anything.
(Scratching)
I will choose in a direct way.
(Jong Min opens a door and enters.)
(No one is here?)
Gosh, you startled me.
(Welcome, it's good to see you.)
(Sae Ho picked Room D
after thinking hard.)
I picked death on purpose,
hoping that it's the opposite.
I picked this because...
Here's what I think.
Inside the room for Mount Halla,
there might be some kind of gear.
(Are there hiking gear
in the room next door?)
(Seon Ho is the third one to enter.)
I've worked hard in my life.
I've been good.
(As they hear someone approaching,
they switch to hide-and-seek mode.)
The first thing
B reminds me of is...
birds.
B, I, R, D.
D reminds me of dive.
We will have to dive.
Pain.
(What will be Seon Ho's choice?)
(Knocking)
(If Seon Ho comes into Room D)
I have no choice,
but miraculously, I was wrong
in every O-X quiz today.
(Will Seon Ho pick Room D?)
My goodness.
(The tension makes him
take another breath.)
Seon Ho, hurry up!
Why is he taking so long?
He's being funny.
It's based on luck anyway.
What is there to think about?
Joon reminds me of Park Young Gyu...
in "Soonpoong Clinic" in his prime.
(Scolding angrily just like him)
Aren't I right? It's based on luck.
(Frustrated)
(Getting up)
Why... What is he doing?
Next.
- Cheol, let's do it fast.
- DinDin.
- Hey.
- Let's do it fast.
Why do I feel like
you and I went through this before?
- Please.
- DinDin.
- Make your choice fast.
- It's based on luck anyway.
- Let me choose as well.
- Okay.
- It's all about luck. Just do it.
- I want to make a choice.
- Don't think about it.
Don't leave me with him.
It's 1 a.m. already.
Don't say that.
It's 7 p.m. for the viewers.
Who cares?
I have to get up early tomorrow
to go to Mount Halla.
It's 7 p.m. for the viewers.
- That's true.
- For you, it's 1 a.m.
(Sighing)
Please!
B and D.
D and D.
Since I'm DinDin, I pick D.
I pick D.
- Where are we going?
- What?
- I don't know.
- You don't know yet?
- No.
- You don't know?
Can you take out the blanket?
Blanket?
(Screaming)
What?
(Sae Ho jumps out of the closet.)
- Why are you here?
- What?
Birth.
It means that you're being born.
Being born anew.
It must be Mount Halla.
I'm going to Room D.
(Surprisingly,
all three went to Room D.)
- What? It's over.
(Jong Min, Sae Ho,
and Seon Ho picked Room D.)
- There are three of us.
- This is crazy.
Seriously?
- We all picked the same room.
- All of us?
- Why are you here?
- What?
DinDin, please go to Room B.
All three of us picked this room.
Everyone came here so far.
He's shocked.
(DinDin is sent to Room B.)
Why does it feel so tense here?
(It seems ominous.)
- Please.
- Things like this...
Don't let me be
in the same room as Joon.
This is driving me crazy.
Okay, Se Yoon. Please go.
Here's what I think.
You won't have any choice,
but I won't either.
That's also how I feel.
Se Yoon, can you choose quickly?
We won't get to sleep much.
We'll go to Mount Hall anyway.
We'll be going there anyway.
(Hopeless)
Obese.
Diet?
Obese and diet?
(Sighing)
Please, or I'll die.
(Please save me.)
(Will Se Yoon pick B or D?)
(Peekaboo)
(What?)
- What's going on?
- This is so fascinating.
Psychologically...
Isn't the way we think
so fascinating?
The elders are here.
There are gear inside the closet.
- What?
- There are gear in here.
- In here? What gear?
- Yes.
(Gosh)
(Here's the youngest.)
(He took a big hit.)
(Laughing)
Se Yoon flew.
(He almost flew.)
You startled me.
- Is it the three of you?
- Yes.
I don't think this one is good.
Joon will be coming here.
We're doomed.
I don't want to be
in the same room as Joon.
Me neither.
(Where is it?)
What is there to think about?
You just need to pick any room.
(Going straight energetically)
(He chose "D" as expected.)
What?
(He got surprised
just as the other two did.)
(And he was moved to Room B
as he was supposed to.)
You're not surprised. Why?
I already went into the other room
and came here.
- We're done for as Joon is here.
- Hey.
- Hey, leave the room.
- Sorry?
Get out of here.
Apparently, the 1st 3 members
chose the other room.
All of us chose this room,
which makes me anxious.
- I have a bad feeling about this.
- Right?
We were all drawn to this room
for some reason.
(The room selection is finalized.)
(Which of the rooms could be
for the Mount Halla adventure?)
- Really?
- But we don't know the result.
That's true, but...
See? We don't know yet.
Why the long face?
You came here. That's why.
(Am I the result?)
- Do you really not know?
- Why are you being like this to me?
Finding out the result
is not important.
You coming here...
tells us the result.
Isn't it hard to believe
that all six of us chose this room?
- It is, indeed.
- It had no chance of happening.
It doesn't make sense.
But this room may be the lucky room.
- Right.
- It'd be nice if that's the case.
- This room may be the lucky room.
- Let's think that way for now.
Why would you think
we'll definitely go there?
Everyone, please come out now.
Let's go for it with confidence!
- Please.
- It's really hard to believe.
- All six of us chose the same room.
- How did we all go to that room?
- We all chose the same room.
It's unbelievable that
all six of us chose Room D.
Now...
Has it been decided?
Do you have a hunch
about where you'll go tomorrow?
We don't need a hunch.
Joon came to the same room as us.
(Sad premonition)
- Maybe Joon brought good luck.
- Joon came to our room.
Now that it's past midnight,
- his daily fate has changed.
- His fate has changed.
- Okay.
- You chose one of these, right?
His hands are shaking.
Is it written on the back of those?
- Which one shall I reveal first?
- That's right.
- That makes sense too.
- For the show to be fun...
Yes?
- "D" should be the bad one.
- Right.
- We didn't have a choice. Right?
- Exactly.
I find it so hard to believe.
Please reveal "D" first.
I will reveal "D."
The energy of Joon...
Wait. Should I just listen?
What should I do?
Here we go.
- The look on his face isn't good.
- I think we'll go to Mount Halla.
Please take it off slowly.
No.
- Slowly.
- He seems quite bitter.
Just take it off already.
- Darn it.
- What is it? Show us.
- All right.
- Those are dolphins.
- You will go on an adventure...
- Dolphins.
- They're dolphins.
- of the discovery...
of the Jeju sea treasure,
- Indo-Pacific bottlenose dolphins.
- Oh, yes.
(3 members)
(Dolphin, 3 members)
(Jong Min, Sae Ho, and Seon Ho
will go on a search for dolphins.)
- Isn't this the harder one?
- No.
- We have to go to the sea.
- That's not a problem.
- But dolphins rarely appear.
- It happens rarely.
You must find a dolphin...
- to get off work tomorrow.
- What?
- But... I mean, I know this.
- We can't go home if we don't?
If we go out to the sea
around Jeju Island,
we can see many dolphins.
- I know. Of course, I know that.
- I guess we have to film them.
But they might not appear
due to the bad weather.
Listen to me.
Tae Hyun once went out to the sea
to see dolphins,
but he failed to find them.
So he had to go back there later.
(He keeps throwing a wet blanket.)
Come on. Stop saying such a thing.
I can't believe you.
It's a true story.
You know... I can guarantee you.
I saw dolphins
every time I came to Jeju Island.
(If one is the sea,)
(the other must be the mountain.)
- I don't know.
- Seriously, what's your problem?
(Sighing)
You should check it.
You don't know yet.
Earlier, Joon said he thought...
- that these three of them would go.
- The members who chose Room D.
- This is really important.
- Yes.
Se Yoon, Joon, and DinDin...
(The three of them were kicked out
and moved to Room B.)
- Maybe they'll just go home.
- They'll go home?
They'll go home without a mission?
Please.
(Please.)
- Get off work?
- Please.
Yes. Take it off.
What?
- All right.
- It's almost touching the sky.
You will go and explore the treasure
of Mount Halla,
which is one of the best mountains
in Korea.
It is situated
1,660m above the sea level.
(The treasure of Mount Halla
situated 1,660m above the sea level)
You will explore Baekrok Spring.
- Baekrok Spring?
- Yes!
(They'll go hiking after all!)
We can relax now.
What's Baekrok Spring?
(Baekrok Spring?)
(Located south of Lake Baengnok)
It's a spring.
It used to be...
a restricted area.
(Baekrok Spring will be revealed
on TV for the first time.)
- This is a benefit.
- They should be grateful.
This is a benefit.
You can't get a chance to see it,
even if you're willing to pay.
- Should I stop teasing them?
- Just be quiet.
Okay. I'll do that.
(6 hours later)
(My gosh. The wind is so strong.)
(The worst condition
in the history of 2 Days and 1 Night)
(Please look forward to seeing
the legendary hike.)
Right. We'll probably be knocked out
on the plane going home.
Joon lost in every game we played.
- It's unbelievable.
- Joon lost in every game.
Joon lost in every game.
You'll go on an adventure tomorrow,
so sleep tight.
What time should we wake up
tomorrow morning?
As for Team Baekrok Spring,
we'll wake you up...
- What are you talking about?
- at 6 a.m.
(Team Baekrok Spring
has to wake up at 6 a.m.)
(Finding inner peace)
You're doing great.
- It's 1 a.m. now.
- At 6 a.m.,
- Yes.
- I'll come to wake you up.
- Seon Ho.
- What about us?
- What about Team Dolphin?
- Come here. Let's go together.
- As for Team Dolphin,
you have to wake up at 8:30 a.m.
- That's so early.
- I'm jealous.
(Read the room, will you?)
(Whispering)
Excuse me. We have to go to bed,
so let's stop chatting.
Okay.
I'll stop chatting with the others.
- Right.
- You have things to do tomorrow,
- so please go to bed now.
- Okay.
- Got it.
- Good job, everyone.
Thank you.
I won't see you off.
See you tomorrow.
(Se Yoon and Sae Ho
got ready for bed first.)
Jong Hyun will come and wake us up,
right?
Yes, he will.
(Se Yoon is worried a lot
about hiking.)
Goodness.
I wish
I could go up there with my friend.
- I know.
- It's a shame.
(The same age friends are sad
as they can't go together.)
Exactly.
You chose Room D.
I can't believe
all six of us went to Room D.
Exactly.
I'm going to get some rest now.
I thought we might go to Mount Halla
since we were coming to Jeju Island.
I knew it when I heard
we were going to come here.
(They thought of Mount Halla
when they heard about the shoot.)
I was 100 percent sure
some of us would go to Mount Halla.
But I didn't know
if I would be chosen.
I knew I would be chosen.
(Joon had predicted
his fate already.)
I didn't know I'd be chosen.
(They only share sighs and regret.)
I should've done better
at picking bracken.
It's okay. It might be fun.
But it won't be, though. Right?
It will be simply exhausting.
(DinDin is sullen.)
I guess you guys will ride a boat,
right?
Probably.
Is it true that you saw a dolphin
from a tent bar?
Yes.
Come on. Stop lying.
It's true. Why would I lie?
While drinking at a tent bar,
he saw a dolphin swimming by.
I think I have a photo too.
But Jeju Island... I mean...
Don't dolphins live in the deep sea?
No, they don't.
They often appear
in the shallow parts...
- near a beach.
- Really?
I know I have it somewhere here.
(He wants to prove it's true
by showing Seon Ho the photo.)
(Scrolling like crazy)
I found it.
(He finally found the photo
of the dolphin he saw.)
Oh, my. I see that it's true.
(The video of the dolphin
recorded by Jong Min)
Wait. What is this?
(But the more they see it,
the harder it is to tell.)
- Is it a seal?
- Is that really a dolphin?
I think it's a seal.
(Now, even Jong Min is confused.)
- This is driving me nuts.
- So it's not a dolphin?
(The dolphin that Jong Min saw
becomes a mystery again.)
- Good night, Jong Min.
- You too. Sleep well.
(Seon Ho got tired while waiting
and went to sleep first.)
(Jong Min, who kept searching
for a long while,)
(fell asleep
after everyone else did.)
(The pitch-dark night...)
(is filled with bright light.)
(The second day on Jeju Island
has come.)
(It's bright outside already.)
(But Team Baekrok Spring
is still sleeping soundly.)
(Today's morning fairy,
Director Joo, appears.)
(Tapping)
It's time to hike, Se Yoon.
(Talking quietly)
(Dazed)
Wake up.
(After that,
he wakes Joon and DinDin up too.)
Let's go hiking.
(Then he leaves the room relaxedly.)
(Sae Ho wakes up briefly
at the noise.)
Have a good time.
(Sweet)
- Be careful not to hurt your legs.
- Go back to sleep.
(He's always worried
about his friend.)
- Jong Hyun, you be safe too.
- Got it.
I'm going back to sleep.
(The members of 2 Days and 1 Night
take care of each other.)
(He covers Sae Ho
with the blanket thoroughly.)
(Se Yoon comes out first.)
(DinDin and Joon come out too.)
I heard
we should have a hearty breakfast.
So let's have breakfast first.
Oh, it's nice.
Tofu. Nice.
(The food truck is waiting
for the members.)
It's very windy.
- "Keep out of the mountain."
- I don't think you can go.
I don't have much of an appetite.
(A lot of food)
Thank you for the food.
We should eat for six hours.
What's happening after six hours?
It's going to rain in six hours.
So we should eat for six hours.
(Joon has no thoughts or ideas.)
Did you look up articles
about Baekrok Spring?
It's open to the public
for the first time.
- We've only heard about it.
- Really?
It never gets dry.
The spring is full of water.
It's the highest spring water
in South Korea.
It's that legendary spring water.
We are lucky boys.
That makes us really lucky.
We can't even find...
pictures of Baekrok Spring
on the Internet.
- People can't visit there.
- Right.
(We are the first ones to visit.)
It's a new way up to Mount Halla.
That's great.
(I think it's worth hiking.)
We are going somewhere
that hasn't been open to the public.
I will see you here at 7:50 a.m.
I'll meet you at 7:53 a.m.
(Get ready to go to Baekrok Spring
and see you all later.)
Now that we're here already,
we should all go up.
- Everyone.
- Yes?
You have to climb up Mount Halla.
(Let's go to Mount Halla.)
Get ready with your backpacks.
You see the backpacks
in front of you?
Please don't touch them yet.
What? Are we playing a game or what?
You can pick one of those.
Only 1 bag out of these 3...
has all the snacks and water.
Please take note...
- and choose one.
- So it must be heavier.
That's right.
Seon Ho was worried about me.
So he gave me this.
- It's an energy gel.
- He was worried.
He told me to have it
if I got exhausted.
Okay.
(We approve of Seon Ho's love
toward Se Yoon.)
All right.
Which one do you want to choose?
Let's pick this one right here.
It's light.
(What? This is light.)
Did you mark it as red and blue?
And black?
I'm MBLAQ, so...
Why is this so heavy?
(Is it Joon again?)
He just gets all the bad luck.
- Come on.
- You're so unlucky.
- Joon's so unlucky.
- MBLAQ.
Are you all ready? Let's get going.
(Celebrating
Visit Jeju Heritage Year,)
(they're headed to find
hidden treasures in Mount Halla.)
(However)
(A few raindrops started to fall.)
(It became really foggy.)
(It started to rain even harder.)
It's raining, but we are still...
We have to go up
since we're here already.
Right, let's show the spirit
of 2 Days and 1 Night.
We'll come down
if things get too hard.
But we'll still go up.
Along with Joon.
(With unlucky Joon)
The staff from Mount Halla are here.
We have to go with them. Hello.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- How do you do?
- The weather is...
- Yes.
- The weather is bad.
- Right.
- It's bad.
- Right?
We can still go up, right?
- Yes.
- So we can go up.
I heard that you're going
to Baekrok Spring. Am I right?
That's right. Baekrok Spring.
I can't wait to get there.
I'm so excited.
Baekrok Spring is...
- the highest spring in Korea.
- Right.
It's right below Lake Baengnok.
It's at an altitude of about 1,660m.
It's located in an area
that's prohibited from visiting.
- So people can't visit there.
- Right.
But we're celebrating
Visit Jeju Heritage Year.
So we take reservations
for the month of July.
For one month.
Right. We open it to the public.
And we're the first ones to visit.
- Your team...
- It's the first time ever.
is lucky to visit there.
But it's raining hard today.
What a lucky day.
Are you going up with us?
I have to be in charge
of safety management.
So I have to stay behind.
That's why you look happy.
Is the man behind you
going up with us?
- That's right.
- He's wearing something dark.
And you're wearing something bright.
(Kim Jong Gab, a researcher
at Jeju World Heritage Headquarters)
I'm sure the audience
wants to take a look at Mount Halla.
- So please enjoy.
- Of course, they're curious.
I hope you enjoy your time there.
It would have been even better
if the weather were good.
- It's all because of you.
- I like it better this way.
I like this better.
- See you.
- Have a safe trip.
- Good luck.
- Thank you. Baekrok Spring.
(Let's all get hyped and go!)
(Today's course: Yeongsil Trail)
(Yeongsil)
(A valley where deities stay)
(The most beautiful trail
up to Mount Halla)
(Follow me.)
(Rocks of fantastic shape
created by deities)
(Byeongpung Rocks
where deities live)
(Seonjakjiwat, Garden of deities)
(You can see all of these
on Yeongsil Trail.)
(On their way to the final destination,
Baekrok Spring)
I heard that the beginning
of this train is quite tough.
(They say the beginning
of this course is tough.)
When you go up from there,
- it will get easier.
- Okay.
It's the shortest course
to reach Witse Oreum.
The view here is amazing.
You can see the running water
of the valley.
- It's cool.
- It's the only place with water.
(The only course with running water
on Mount Halla)
Is everyone coming up?
You can take steps here.
(DinDin and the staff
are all going up well.)
(Controlling his pace)
Joon, take care of DinDin.
I think DinDin is the ace here.
He's good.
This was one of my dreams.
- What was?
- Here?
When I watched,
"My Lovely Sam Soon,"
(When I watched "My Lovely Sam Soon"
20 years ago...)
Sam Soon climbs up this mountain
on a rainy day.
Really?
I'm doing what she did.
- On a rainy day...
- That's romantic.
Sam Soon was also wearing
a raincoat.
(One of DinDin's bucket list
was climbing up Mount Halla.)
I think she broke up with Hyun Bin
in the series.
She climbed up here on a rainy day
to forget him.
- By herself?
- Yes.
I think Hyun Bin came to follow her.
Did he put a GPS on her?
How did he know?
I'm not sure.
(We met without any GPS.)
It's so clean.
- Isn't the water refreshing?
- Yes.
It's amazing.
The sound is very refreshing.
- I know.
- It would be nice...
to sit in the middle right there.
Why don't you get
in the water for us?
If we get in the water...
- It's not allowed.
- You will be in trouble.
It would be nice
to sit in the middle, right?
- Right.
- It's incredible.
(Let's climb up again
if you're done enjoying the view.)
- Let's go up.
- I think you're going up too fast.
- Right.
- Is he fast, or...
You think I'm the fast one?
This is the normal speed.
- Really?
- Yes.
It's DinDin's first time climbing up
a proper mountain.
(It's his first time climbing up
on a rainy day.)
(First time climbing up is so hard)
(I never had climbing in my plan.)
(It's not too tiring because they're
still in the beginning course.)
I think we just passed
the first hill.
(They're about to enter
the tough course.)
Shall we take a big breath here?
- Here?
- Yes.
From here...
The place is called Kkalddak Hill.
So we won't get to smile from here.
Right. You will neither smile
nor talk from this point.
- We have stairs all the way up?
- That's right.
(Nonstop stairs that stop you
from laughing and talking unfold.)
Can you take that one out of my bag?
(They must hydrate themselves.)
(Walking)
(Some more walking)
(The only sound we hear
is them out of breath.)
What we did earlier
wasn't even climbing.
(The earlier course is more like
a walking course.)
This is climbing.
(This is true climbing.)
It's like a StairMaster.
(Exhausted)
My goodness.
(Out of breath)
- Goodness.
- Let's keep going.
This is exhausting.
(When everybody is about
to get exhausted...)
You can take a break here. Hurry up.
We're taking a break here.
(It's time for a short break.)
Goodness, it's so nice here.
The view is amazing.
(The view is fantastic.)
I think the view here is so good
with this weather.
You ended up here
because I'm a lucky man.
Thanks to me.
That view is incredible.
(I love it.)
What is this? Fog?
Yes, it's fog.
(The spectacular view of the fog
that rewards the climb)
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- We took a good break.
(On their way to Baekrok Spring again
after taking a break)
The view from here is spectacular.
It's amazing. Goodness.
It's unbelievable.
I can't see it properly,
but it still is cool.
The vibe is amazing.
(The vibe is rather dreamy
thanks to the fog.)
(But it suddenly starts to rain hard
after their break.)
(They can't even open their eyes
due to heavy wind.)
My hat will fly away.
(The wind is so heavy
that his hat almost got flown away.)
I want to go back!
(Flopping down)
(Where is this place? Who am I?)
- Mr. Kim.
- Yes?
Please say something hopeful.
Maybe, "We are almost there."
Let's go!
He surely is a Type T.
(Mr. Kim is Type T for sure.)
He is a Type T.
(They're still at Byeongpung Rocks.)
(They're almost done climbing up
the tough course.)
My goodness, the wind.
(But the storm gets even heavier
as they go up.)
(Swaying)
(He can't even open his eyes.)
My face is burning.
(The storm is so heavy
that even his face is burning.)
Goodness, what is this?
(Se Yoon's cameraman swaying)
- I think I'll get blown away.
- I know.
- Me too.
(It's so hard to see
Baekrok Spring.)
(Se Yoon stops for a moment.)
Hello.
(Suddenly?)
I'm the entertainer
with the spirit of a bear,
Moon Grylls, not Bear Grylls.
I think we're at an altitude
of about 1,500m.
There's a promise
I made with Seon Ho yesterday.
I'm really tired, Seon Ho.
I'll eat this now. Thanks.
It's warm since I just caught it.
(Moon Grylls toughly tears it
and eats it.)
I won't give up.
My body may be fat,
but in my heart, I'm muscular.
Let's walk.
Goodness.
(Moon Grylls stops
after about 5 seconds.)
The medicine isn't working.
It's not working at all.
I'm so tired.
I just hope it starts working later.
(Moon Grylls, the end)
(Meanwhile, at the base camp)
(It's not rainy or windy.)
(They're going in
to wake up Team Dolphin.)
Good morning.
(He's startled.)
(Forced wake-up)
Wake up.
What is it?
(Is this a dream?)
It's time for the adventure.
(He attacks
by turning on the lights.)
What?
It's 8:30 a.m. now.
We'll go and have breakfast.
Let's eat.
Let's go.
It's a proper meal.
Right.
We're having a proper meal
after two days.
I found the picture
I talked about yesterday.
- Did you find it?
- Yes, I found it.
I went to a tent bar,
and I found dolphins.
- It's true.
- It's amazing, right?
I think the name was
Indo-Pacific dolly.
Indo-Pacific dolly?
It's called
the Indo-Pacific bottlenose dolphin.
Do you think the other team
had breakfast?
They were telling them to go eat
when I woke up at 6:30 a.m.
- I heard that too.
- Right.
They'd have mixed feelings.
(They'd be struggling.)
You'll be telling us
what we'll ride...
to see the dolphins in a while.
We'll probably take a boat.
- A boat.
- I think so too.
We'll ride motorcycles
to see the dolphins?
To see the dolphins?
(We'll take the scooter today.)
We'll get on the scooters...
and head out
for a dolphin adventure.
The Indo-Pacific bottleneck dolphins
of the sea in Jeju...
mainly live in the sea...
off Noeulhaean-ro in Daejeong-eup.
When you meet
the lucky dolphins today,
you should take a picture
and send it to us.
When we get the pictures,
your Jeju adventure will end
immediately.
(The older members
are already excited.)
- Let's do well.
- We'll ride motorcycles...
We'll ride motorcycles and see them?
We'll ride motorcycles
along the beach.
They move in packs.
- We'll be able to see them.
- Let's go.
- Dolphin, dolphin, yes!
Isn't it childish?
- "Dolphin, dolphin, yes?"
- Right.
(The last Jeju expedition)
(Find the Indo-Pacific
bottleneck dolphins!)
Shall we all set off
to find the dolphins?
Let's go!
We'll let you go home quickly.
- Let's go.
(Heading out to find the dolphins)
Let's go!
Keep a safe distance.
Let's be careful.
We shouldn't get hurt.
We should keep going
at the speed of 40km per hour.
- Yes.
- Let's go to their home.
Okay.
You have to lead well, Sae Ho.
We're on a Jeju trip together
while feeling the breeze.
We turn right here.
(They follow navigator Sae Ho.)
I think we'll see them here.
Gosh.
This is amazing.
It's awesome. It's so beautiful.
(They're on a beachside road
with an open view.)
The dolphins swim...
near the beach.
- Right.
- They don't swim far.
The sea on the left is so pretty.
- It's amazing.
- This is nice.
It's beautiful.
This is the charm of Jeju.
This is Jeju.
(It was Jeju.)
You can look at the sea
while riding along the coast.
You can see the Indo-Pacific dolly.
Should we watch them
from the left...
- with a wider view?
- The left.
The left.
This side is good.
It's easy to park too.
Okay.
Gosh. This is it.
(There are dolphins
somewhere in the vast ocean.)
It's so nice.
(There are dolphins
somewhere in the vast ocean.)
We have to hold our phones.
We never know when they'll come.
Look through the binoculars.
You can see so clearly.
(They use an item to search.)
- You can see it well.
- Right?
I think they'd be there.
Somewhere, right?
(Glancing)
You startled me.
(He saw something else
instead of the dolphins.)
(They keep searching
for the dolphins.)
Do you not see them?
I don't think they're around.
It's not easy to find them.
I think we'll have to
travel some more.
They're not here?
(The view is great,
but there are no dolphins.)
Let's move after taking a picture.
Let's do that.
Let's go to their house.
If they're not home,
- we can go to their friend's house.
- Right.
They should meet their friends
since it's a weekend.
(The dolphins should also
meet their friends.)
One, two, three.
- Yes!
- Let's go!
- Let's go.
- Yes!
(You must take pictures
on an expedition.)
Let's go!
You have to look to the left at times.
The dolphins may come out.
Dolphins! On the left.
(Did he find one right away?)
A statue.
How are you doing, statue?
Left!
The view on the left is great.
That spot is nice.
Let's pull over on the left.
We'll see the dolphins
if we look closely.
Let's go down to the left.
(Please!)
Go to the front.
Right.
We'll find the dolphins here.
I think we'll see them here.
I have a good feeling.
Come out!
Dolphins!
(Did he find something?)
What?
No.
(It's a water bird.)
(They start getting worried.)
Talk to them in a high tone.
I see them!
They're there!
Let me see.
- They're right there.
- Where? Let me have it.
There.
Where?
- Hold on.
- The buoy?
No. Where did it go?
The fin went up and down.
- I think that was a buoy.
- No.
It looked so much like a fin.
I don't think they're here now.
Let's go.
Seon Ho might have seen them.
(Seon Ho can't leave
the breakwater so easily.)
(What did Seon Ho see?)
We're in trouble.
(Will they be able to see
the dolphins at the next spot?)
We have very poor visibility.
It's very foggy.
We can't find the dolphins.
They also wouldn't come so close.
(They can't see the road
so clearly.)
(The production crew makes
an urgent decision...)
(to find the dolphins.)
(They distributed cameras...)
(at the locations
where they saw the dolphins...)
(during their previous search.)
(Location 1: Bbulsora Park)
(It's a famous location
for seeing dolphins.)
(Travelers visiting Jeju
often wait here.)
The wind...
(The weather condition
is bad today.)
(Hint them if there are dolphins.
It'll be hard to see anything.)
(A text that
the production crew sent.)
(Team Bbulsora arrived,
and we can see only 50m ahead...)
(because of the fog.)
(Location 2: Ilgwa 2-ri
Fishing Village Association)
The weather is bad.
(They're struggling
with the wind here as well.)
(Location 3: Yeongnak-ri Breakwater
that the members dropped by)
The weather...
(No one took pictures yet, right?
I don't think we'll be going home!)
(All they see are the strong waves.)
(They're not at the breakwater.)
Will we really not go home?
- I think we should move.
- They're not here?
Let's take a picture and move.
Okay.
I think we'll have to go further.
The visibility is really bad.
I can't see.
This...
Today...
(Will they fail the mission today?)
Will we be able to see them?
We can't see far ahead.
(The scooters of the three
pace through the frustration.)
(At these times...)
Should we go to a cafe
and try spotting them...
with a cup of coffee?
Okay. Let's do that.
(Haste makes waste.)
If there's a nice cafe,
we should have
a cup of coffee, latte, or tea.
- Sounds good.
There's a cafe here.
I think it'll be nice.
It's open.
- Let's go.
We'll just go to any place
we see like this.
This is what
free traveling is about.
Let's go for the vibes.
(How is Team Baekrok Spring doing?)
(The rainstorm seems to
know no end,)
(and the journey to
Baekrok Spring continues.)
(His cheeks get pushed in.)
Gosh, that stings.
(The rain slams down
against their faces.)
(The members are getting exhausted.)
- Enjoy.
- Cheers!
- Thank you.
Gosh, the coffee is good.
The coffee is so good.
(Team Baekrok Spring is hiking
in extreme conditions.)
(They have passed
the Byeongpung Rocks.)
(The decide to take a break
at the end of the difficult course.)
Gosh, the wind...
I've never felt a wind this strong.
Gosh.
My eardrums hurt.
Right.
(Getting energized with sugar
during the break)
(Moon Grylls arrives
after going through the rainstorm.)
(In tatters)
Gosh, it's the cool guy.
(You've gone through so much.)
Have a chocolate bar.
Have some. No?
(He lost his appetite
with the arduous hike.)
Let's go.
- Let's go. It's cold.
- Let's go.
- Do you want to take the lead?
- Okay.
(Current location)
(The path is flat
starting from now.)
It's much easier now.
There are trees too.
That part was really tough.
Right. It was really tough.
- Gosh, the wind...
- Now,
you can enjoy the view, right?
- Gosh.
- Will you take a look at this?
This tree.
- Gosh.
- It's pretty.
This is the Korean fir,
which is used as a Christmas tree.
I can tell right away.
(The original Christmas tree,
Korean fir)
(It's an endemic species
in Korea...)
(that grows in alpine regions...)
(and blossoms flowers of
several colors in May and June.)
(The Korean fir grove
unfolds from this point.)
Gosh, it's so pretty.
The trees are precious.
They block the rain and wind for us.
Right.
(They take in the view
of Mount Halla thanks to the trees.)
- Gosh, there are young ones here.
- Hello.
- They're celebrities!
- Move down safely.
- Gosh.
- It's 2 Days and 1 Night!
Move down safely, ma'am!
You're amazing!
- She's amazing.
- I'm dying right now!
You're amazing!
2 Days!
- 2 Days!
- And 1 Night!
It became 2 Days 2 Days and 1 Night.
Thank you!
(A vast grassland unfolds
after passing the Korean fir grove.)
(This place is Seonjakjiwat.)
Why are we stopping here?
- This is Nolu Spring.
- Nolu Spring?
This place has drinking water
at the highest altitude...
- in our country.
- Really?
This is the source...
of Jeju's famous water brand.
- Let's have some!
- Really? It's from this place?
- Gosh!
- Let's have some!
Give it a try.
(Drinking)
Does it taste good?
Gosh.
How is it?
It tastes a bit different.
It's a bit different
from regular water.
These must be fine against the wind.
Gosh!
- It's a bit sweet.
- Gosh, it's refreshing!
Is it good?
- It's so nice.
- Thank you.
It tastes a bit like acacia.
It's so clean.
- It's a very clean taste.
- Right.
It has the sweetness of acacia.
So this is Jeju water.
(The true taste of Jeju water)
Gosh, that's refreshing.
It can't be collected, though.
We drank the spring water
of Mount Halla.
- Gosh.
- This is amazing.
We drank water that's 1,650m high.
- Gosh.
- This is amazing.
I'll see you in my next life,
Nolu Spring.
(Current location)
(They are around 10 minutes away
from the shelter.)
Gosh, the winds are so harsh.
(The winds are still strong.)
I think we should hurry
as it's cold.
(Even the camera lens gets fogged up
and wet with rainwater.)
It should die down a bit.
(After walking
for around 10 minutes...)
Is that the shelter?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
(They spot a place with a roof
after hiking for 2 hours.)
I feel so happy to see it.
What is this place?
(The Witse Oreum shelter is placed
1,700m above ground.)
Let's rest up.
Gosh, it's cold.
(Let's take a break
in the warm shelter.)
Gosh, hiking is fun!
(Touched)
Gosh, it's so cold.
My goodness.
Gosh, it's so cozy.
Gosh, it's cold.
Come here. The heater is here.
(Happy)
(Joon shakes the water
off of his hair.)
(DinDin shakes the water
off of his pants.)
(Se Yoon has just been shaken up.)
I thought just the first hour
was going to be tough.
How could you say that?
I was told just the first hour
was going to be tough.
(We'll take a break
as we're too exhausted.)
Is my phone safe with me?
(Joon has more chocolate.)
Gosh.
(He checks how he looks right now.)
I think I've lost
all of my chubbiness.
Aren't I like Joon?
- Gosh.
- You really lost weight!
To me, it feels like
I'm just like you right now.
Gosh, Mount Halla
is the best plastic surgery clinic.
(We'll let the viewers decide.)
(He makes a video call
to Team Dolphin.)
- What?
What's wrong with your eyes?
(Sae Ho gets flustered for real
after seeing Se Yoon.)
What's wrong?
(The shocking face appears.)
What are you saying? I look great
after losing weight right now.
What happened to you?
Why are your dark circles so big?
I almost died.
- How was it, Joon?
- Are you done?
We came up 1,600m.
- Pass the phone to DinDin.
- That must've been tough.
- We came up 1,600m.
- Right.
We came up 1,600m.
Gosh, that's impressive.
- How high up are you?
- That was fairly quick.
We came up 1,600m.
Did it take around two hours?
Longer than that.
The winds were so strong.
They're strong enough
to make people waver around.
- Really?
- That was the tough part.
You and Joon look fine.
What's wrong with Se Yoon?
- Se Yoon looks better.
- His face melted.
(Se Yoon's face seems like
it got melted.)
- He lost weight.
- Did someone punch you in the eye?
Did he get stung by a bee?
No. Everyone is going wild
as I look much better.
Nobody is going wild.
That must've been tough.
- You guys will become healthier.
- Right.
If you don't believe us,
watch this week's episode
to see what we went through.
Okay.
Gosh, Se Yoon looks like
he's really struggling.
But he said
he looks better like that.
(But he said
he looks better like that.)
Everyone,
there's delicious food in the bag.
- What?
- You can have it.
- In our bags?
- Yes.
I didn't see anything in my bag.
Joon's bag.
There.
(Food is found in Joon's bag.)
This is kimchi stew.
- What is that?
- It's a combat ration.
- Really?
- It's made the same way.
(Drinking water just needs
to be added.)
What next after that?
- It's boiling.
- Really?
It's hot.
(The combat ration boils up
with the heating pack.)
(Ramyeon is made easily
in just 10 minutes.)
It has cooked well.
Ramyeon after a hike? This is great.
(Slurping)
It tastes great.
(Baekrok Spring must be enjoyed
after a good meal.)
In the future,
we should put together
a special episode.
We should climb up K2
or Mount Everest.
(Joon dreams about K2
and Mount Everest after today.)
Just start your own channel!
Just do it on your own.
You had to see your face
when you hid behind the tree.
I thought that you were going to
step down from our show.
(Mount Everest
with a face like this?)
Really?
Wasn't Mount Halla okay?
It's fine now as we're inside.
Right.
I think it'll be meaningful
to climb up a significant mountain.
(Will they be able to maintain
this energy to Baekrok Spring?)
Let's go! Let's head out to a place
with a good view.
We have to see them.
We'll see them now.
(Peeking)
The dolphins might appear
all of a sudden!
Okay.
(Always be alert.)
(Peeking)
I think we'll see them around here
if we stand and watch.
Definitely.
We did stop to see them here.
Should we go further?
Hold on.
I'm getting a feeling.
- Okay. Let's keep going.
- Let's keep going.
I have a feeling it'd appear here.
Okay.
(Staring)
Wait.
- Wait.
- What is it?
I see it.
(Did he find a dolphin?)
(Is there a dolphin?)
Where?
Pull over. Let's check.
What? Is it here? What?
Where?
(They went around for 2 hours
to find dolphins.)
Where?
(Looking around)
(I swear I saw it.)
(Will they get to see it today?)
There it is.
(Seon Ho found the dolphin.)
Where?
I see it.
Take a picture first.
(Yelling)
(Let me see.)
Hey. I see it.
(Did they finally succeed
in finding the dolphin?)
- Where is it?
- Where did it go?
I saw it coming up to the surface.
Where did it go?
- Does it dive for a long time?
- Do you want to keep going?
There it is. I see it.
- Where?
- It's moving. Do you see it?
There it is.
Where? Where is it?
Over there. It's moving down.
Let's go. Let's keep going.
Let's keep going.
- Let's get closer to it and see it.
- Let's go.
- Where are you going?
- It's here. Where are you going?
If I go further,
I'll get to see it moving.
- Right. Let's go.
- Let's go.
Okay.
It's moving this way.
I think it's moving up.
If we stand by up there,
we'll be able to see them.
- Right?
- We can take a picture there.
Okay. I'll pull over there.
We'll get a good view from here.
- Over here. This is nice.
- Here?
- Stop here?
- This is a good spot.
If I miss it because of you, Sae Ho,
- I'm going to get mad at you.
- No.
(They must find it.)
There it is.
There.
See? I told you. They didn't leave.
Over there.
I see it.
I can see it clearly.
Where? I see it.
Gosh.
It's out. There it is.
- Where?
- Over there.
I can see it clearly.
(Peekaboo)
I see it.
This is crazy.
I saw them real good. There it is.
It's huge.
- I can see them well.
- And there are many.
There are many.
You can see them with the naked eye.
(A school of dolphins
swimming across the Jeju sea)
There are so many.
- Amazing.
- It's terrific.
They're pretty close, right?
(And...)
(News of dolphin spottings
here and there)
- I caught them.
- I see them.
- Here.
- Where?
- Oh, sorry.
- Sorry.
There.
(The fin fighting against the waves)
- There.
- I see it.
The fin.
- Oh, my gosh. I found the dolphin.
- That's awesome.
I found it.
Is it coming this way?
(If you wait...)
Where did it go?
It's moving this way.
This is awesome.
Aren't you amazed
to see the dolphin?
What? Yes.
(A total of 25 years of experience
behind the camera)
(A strong jump)
They're jumping.
I filmed like ten.
I'm getting more. There are more.
(Interacting with nature)
There are so many.
This is crazy.
I can see them so clearly.
This is the spot.
This place is perfect
for seeing dolphins.
Gosh.
(People gathered.)
It jumped.
Isn't it amazing?
(Watching the piece of art together)
- This is a rare sight.
- Yes.
Gosh. I can see their bodies too.
This is art.
Gosh.
(As if they knew
we were waiting for them...)
- There are so many.
- Gosh.
This is perfect. It was a good idea
to listen to Sae Ho.
We can get a better view here.
What are they doing?
This is so exciting.
This is unbelievable.
This is perfect.
I can see them clearly.
(You should check them out
when you visit Jeju.)
This place is perfect.
(Exclaiming)
I caught them all.
- Gosh.
- That is...
I caught many of them.
A dolphin.
(Sae Ho's camera)
I caught them clearly.
- Do you see them?
- Let me see.
That's perfect.
I caught them clearly.
Well done.
Since you found the dolphins,
it's the end
of your Jeju exploration.
Thank you.
(The dolphin exploration
is a success.)
- It feels nice.
- It's nice.
(We're happy for you.)
- Is this my stick?
- Yes.
Okay.
(Team Baekrok Spring's journey
is nearing its end.)
Go.
(DinDin and Joon are ready.)
It's cold.
(The rainstorm welcomes him
as soon as he's out.)
(Rushing because it's cold)
Let's go.
(Off to Baekrok Spring again
after warming up)
Thank you.
Is it windy at Baekrok Spring?
Yes. It is open.
It's cold, even though it's summer.
It's freezing.
Gosh.
I'm dying.
(15 minutes to their destination)
I don't normally say it's cold.
I never thought...
I'd say it's cold in summer.
I can't believe this is happening.
(Raining Mount Halla in summer
is colder than winter training.)
What? Are we going down?
Does it mean we have to go up again?
My goodness.
I want to stop going up.
(It's a repetition
of downhills and uphills.)
(A rough journey
to meet Baekrok Spring)
(This is
a real and wild road variety show.)
(They run out of strength
as they reach the peak.)
(A crazy collaboration...)
(between the endless uphills
and the fierce rainstorm)
(The wind gets stronger
as they go higher.)
We're almost there.
(Their destination is near.)
We're entering now.
Okay.
I think we're here.
(Ragged)
Is this the way?
This place hasn't been
disturbed yet.
(Finally)
- Do we go this way?
- We have to keep going.
(They must take the byway
to reach the spring.)
- Here?
- Yes.
Let me present you
the best secret sight.
- Do we go this way?
- Good work.
But this isn't a path.
(The members step on the land...)
(that has never been opened
to the public before.)
I barely passed it.
There is no path to it.
- What?
- There is no path to it.
Right, there's no path.
(Walking the real wild road)
This is awesome.
- Yes.
- It's the real wild.
We're like a fellowship.
(1 Night Expedition is as tough
as the fellowship of the ring.)
This is almost like
"The Lord of the Rings."
This is the best exploration.
(The last-minute rainstorm attack)
(Baekrok Spring is
at the end of this road.)
This way.
(It's time to meet the treasure.)
That's Baekrok Spring.
(That's Baekrok Spring.)
Is this Baekrok Spring?
- Yes, it's Baekrok Spring.
- Here?
You climbed for two hours...
- for this.
- That's right.
(They've only seen pictures
of Baekrok Spring.)
(It's right before their eyes.)
(The highest spring in the country,
Baekrok Spring)
It was hard.
Let me take a picture of it.
Finally.
It was hard.
Let me take a picture of it.
Baekrok Spring, to see you...
Oh, Baekrok Spring.
Why do you live so far?
When the weather is clear,
you can see Lake Baengnok...
behind this.
- Gosh.
- When the weather is nice...
(This is Lake Baengnok.)
The water from Lake Baengnok...
could reach here.
Is it connected to Lake Baengnok?
There's a possibility.
We don't know for sure.
- The water is really clean.
- It's clean.
It's so clean.
(Baekrok Spring never dries
throughout the year.)
(Through Jeongbang Waterfall,)
(it enters the sea.)
(Baekrok Spring is the lifeline
and water source of Jeju Island.)
You reached Baekrok Spring.
You completed the expedition.
- Along with Joon.
- What are you doing?
(Joon smiles brightly at last.)
Today, again...
I'll take a photo to commemorate
your visit to Baekrok Spring.
One, two, three.
(Baekrok Spring expedition cleared,
A total real wild road.)
(Team Baekrok Spring's epilogue)
We're at Baekrok Spring.
DinDin, Joon, well done.
Baekrok Spring. Okay.
I hope you enjoy the show.
(Enjoy the episode.)
(Se Yoon, Moon Grylls)
(Lee Joon,
Dreaming of Mount Everest)
(DinDin,
I want to trail run next time.)
(They saw Baekrok Spring,
the treasure of Mount Halla.)
(It's always exciting
to go down a mountain.)
(Groaning)
How much farther must we go?
(They safely descend the mountain.)
(The 5-hour trek
to Baekrok Spring ends.)
Hello and welcome.
The year 2025
is Visit Jeju Heritage Year.
We're the first ever variety show...
to show you Baekrok Spring.
The treasures of the Jeju sea.
The dolphins are here to say hi.
If you want an unforgettable trip
in raw nature.
Come to the fascinating
and thrilling treasure paradise.
Tamra is Jeju.
- Come and have a look.
The best in Korea.
A real wild road variety show!
Who are we?
- 2 Days and 1 Night!
Mission complete!
Goodbye!
(The Jeju expedition
is a huge success.)
(Next episode)
(A curse has been following him
since the Jeju trip.)
(Team up with Lee Joon)
(Definite loss)
(Find the true Defeat Fairy.)
(The 1st Defeat Fairy Pageant)
"Lee Joon always loses"
is like a proverb now.
(Lee Joon always loses.)
(Is he truly a Defeat Fairy?)
(It's time to find out the truth.)
What's important...
(Who comes 1st isn't important.)
(It's who comes last.)
(Who will be...)
(the official Defeat Fairy?)
This is why men don't live long.