(An island that maintains the mystery of the ancient times.)
(A gift of nature)
(Ulleung Island)
(My Ulleung Island Notes)
(Enjoy the blue sea...)
(and the refreshing forests.)
(Our eventful trip)
(There's also)
(A special guest)
(Dokdo protector Professor Seo Kyoung Duk)
(October 25 is Dokdo Day.)
(2 Days 1 Night...)
(goes to Dokdo.)
- Yes.
- For real?
(The furthest point east of the Korean territory)
(We're heading to Dokdo.)
(Join Professor Seo Kyoung Duk)
(Fascinating and Useful Dokdo Encyclopedia That You Should Know)
(It'll be a close match between Jong Min and DinDin.)
(DinDin takes the lead.)
(So does Jong Min.)
(They're both correct.)
(Who will win the unpredictable quiz?)
(2 Days 1 Night)
- Okay.
- Number four.
- It's number 4 already?
- The 4th question.
Okay?
- Please.
- During King Sukjong's reign.
Oh, dear.
This person went to Japan twice...
and got confirmation of the Japanese government...
that Dokdo belonged to us.
I heard all of this before.
The name of this man.
- What is it?
- Shall we end this?
- Answer it and stay out.
- Answer and stay out.
If you get two right...
- Answer and go outside.
- Okay.
- What?
- Wait outside.
That's a good idea.
Get it right and go outside.
The name of that man is...
An Yong Bok.
Applause.
(Well done, Dokdo DinDin.)
That's right.
My gosh.
He deserves the applause.
Seriously, DinDin...
(Japanese fishermen illegally crossed the border...)
(to fish near Ulleung Island.)
He was a commoner,
but he disguised himself as a magistrate...
and told them off.
He then got confirmation that the territory was ours.
- Gosh.
- Your image is improving.
Such knowledge...
Did you study while writing the lyrics?
(Japan's report on An Yong Bok from that time...)
(states Gangwon Province owns Ulleung Island and Dokdo.)
Because of what An Yong Bok did,
Joseon's government...
becomes greatly interested in...
proclaiming their territory...
and maintaining fishing boundaries.
They also increase inspection around Ulleung Island.
I think it's very important that he brought about that change.
We mentioned two people related to Dokdo.
Yisabu and An Yong Bok.
- Yes.
Dokdo is our territory,
- so there's a Korean address.
- Yes.
There are roads that include...
- their names.
- The names are there.
(To honor their memory, roads were named after them.)
Well done, DinDin.
I acknowledge you. You can take over.
Thank you.
Good for you, DinDin.
- Gosh.
- DinDin.
- He won some squid and pork belly.
- Yes.
He's guaranteed a portion.
- There are two spots left.
- Two spots left.
I'll give you the fifth question.
There are many heritage records...
that state Dokdo is our territory.
I know this one.
You must name one of them.
This record says the following about Dokdo.
(The two islands, Usan and Murung, lie close to each other.)
(On clear days, they can be seen from afar.)
This book was written in the early Joseon era.
What is it called?
Jong Min, get it right and sit it out.
So the rest can fight like dogs.
- What?
- You answer.
This is... Isn't it easy?
(This is easy?)
I mentioned a hint earlier.
"Dokdo Is Our Land."
- Think of the song.
- I know that.
Play it in your mind.
(Something-something third line)
You know the part I mean.
And then the fourth line.
(Thinking hard)
(It's this, isn't it?)
(DinDin's correct.)
(The answer DinDin wrote)
("The Veritable Records of King Sejong")
- Okay, so...
- The Veritable Records.
(As if he received a revelation, )
(Jong Min remembered a few words.)
The book's title includes the syllable "se."
- Jong Min!
- Me!
Okay.
- It's Jong Min.
- It's over.
You can sit it out too.
- I'll get this one.
- Okay.
- I was confused for a bit.
- I see.
"The Veritable Records of King Sejong."
- Yes, that.
- Oh.
Give him some applause.
- I've heard it from somewhere.
- I had to think.
What do the song lyrics say?
- "The Veritable Records..."
- "Of King Sejong."
Page 50... What was it?
(The lyrics Jong Min knows)
(The Veritable Records of King Sejong)
(Page 50, line 3)
The lyrics have since changed.
"The Veritable Records of King Sejong,"
"Gangwon Province, Uljin-hyeon."
Those are the new words.
That part has changed. That's why I was confused.
(Lyric change)
(87K, Ulleung-eup Dokdo-ri)
(Average temperature 13°C, rainfall 1,800)
(Cod, mussel, barnacles, Choi Jong Deok, Kim Seong Do)
(19,000m², 799 and 805, Gangwon Province, Uljin-hyeon, Joseon land)
(Hawaii belongs to the US, Daema Island belongs to Joseon)
(Dokdo is our land)
Here's one more thing everyone might know.
Have you heard of the Map of the Eight Provinces?
- The Map of the Eight Provinces?
- Yes.
- No one seems to know that.
- Right.
- No one seems to know what it is.
- What a surprise.
- That's quite a bold name.
- The Map of the Eight Provinces.
- That's what it's called.
- I love that ramyeon brand.
It was the early years of the Joseon Era.
The map marked Ulleung Island and Dokdo.
But unfortunately, the places of the island switched.
But that's not so important...
because it clearly proves that during the Joseon Era,
we were already aware of those two islands.
- Right. We were.
- That's what's important.
- We know their locations.
- Indeed.
I just told you about the two records...
our country established. Right?
Then there were also records from Japan.
Those records confirmed that Dokdo indeed belonged to our country.
- Right.
- There were two records.
- Yes, I heard about them.
- They're quite important.
It's called the Dajokan Order.
Dajokan referred to a government office.
Nowadays, it'd be equivalent to the Prime Minister's Office.
That's of the same importance.
The document verified that...
Ulleung Island and Dokdo...
had no ties to Japan.
(Note that Ulleung Island and Dokdo had no ties to Japan.)
They drew up an official document that confirmed this.
(It's an official document Japan voluntarily acknowledged...)
(that Ulleung Island and Dokdo were not part of its territory.)
The Dajokan Order that I just went over...
- was one of the records.
- Yes.
Then there was another one. It's called...
the Map of the Three Countries' Adjacent Territories.
- I don't know about this.
- Yes.
- That's what it's called.
- It's a map.
A Japanese geographer...
drew up a map that showed the borders...
- around Japan.
- Yes.
- He colored Joseon in yellow.
- I see. He colored it.
- He colored it.
- Yes.
Then he clearly drew Ulleung Island...
- and Dokdo.
- Did he color them in yellow?
Then he colored them in yellow.
Do you know what it said next to Ulleung Island?
"Joseon's island."
- Really?
- Yes.
- He wrote that clearly?
- They had acknowledged it...
- It's game over then.
- in the past. Yes.
- They already marked it as ours.
- This should be available online.
- All right.
This is frustrating, isn't it? All right.
- Seon Ho, your eyes are gleaming.
- Right now... Yes.
- Now...
- All right. Great.
- Everyone.
- What was the name of the map?
The Map of the Three Countries' Adjacent Territories.
- Correct.
- My gosh. Great.
- That was... Right.
- What was the first document?
The Dajokan Order.
You know what? I'll give him a point.
- What?
- Yes.
- He told us just now.
- No.
It's not easy to memorize both documents together.
- Give him a point.
- Yes.
- For your information...
- Sir.
- Yes.
- You're the best.
(You're the best, Professor.)
(The score status of the FUDE)
(Jong Min and DinDin won the seasoned squid and pork belly.)
We're already at Question Six.
- It's our sixth question.
- This is the last question.
- Seon Ho will win with 1 more.
- It's Question 6.
- We have two more questions left.
- If Seon Ho gets it, it's over.
There's only one spot left.
This was issued for the 1st time in 1954.
Back then, the Japanese media regulated it...
- Come again? Violence?
- as an act of violence.
It stirred up a huge controversy.
- An act of violence.
- I see.
In the end, it was covered up with black ink.
Afterward in 2002 and 2004,
it was issued two more times.
Through this, it was once again confirmed...
on an international scale that Dokdo belonged to Korea.
- Sae Ho.
- Yes.
Stamps.
He got it. It's over.
- It's over.
- Stamps.
What kind of stamp?
What? What do you mean?
- What?
- What's this?
- I mean...
- What kind of stamp?
- Right.
Why are you doing this to me?
Sae Ho, it has four syllables.
Dokdo Stamp.
- Correct.
- Okay.
Yes.
(Obtaining 1 point)
Let me tell you about the stamps.
In 1954, the trio of Dokdo Stamps with the scenery of the island...
- was manufactured.
- I see.
In response to these stamps,
the Ministry of Foreign Affairs of Japan declared...
they wouldn't accept any mails with the stamps.
According to the Universal Postal Union,
there's the freedom of transit in the Universal Postal Union.
Our mails with Dokdo Stamps...
- were delivered to Japan.
- I see.
But the Japanese government...
painted the stamps with black ink.
Then the mails were delivered to the recipients.
- Instead of returning the mails?
- I see. To cover them up.
- Yes.
- My gosh.
And there's one more thing we must note from this.
In 2004, we manufactured...
four different kinds of Dokdo Stamps...
with natural landscapes of Dokdo.
This garnered a lot of attention in both Korea and Japan.
We got an immediate response from Japan.
Here's how things escalated.
The far-right organization of Japan...
used boats to stage a protest at sea.
They even tried to come onshore on Dokdo.
What they did was just unheard of. A crazy incident like that occurred.
(The history of stamps that proved the sovereign authority of Dokdo)
(They weren't just simple stamps.)
(The stamps were a declaration of Dokdo's sovereignty.)
I'll come clean about the seventh question.
I also learned about this...
- while preparing for the show.
- Really?
- Then how could we know about it?
- Gosh, it will be a headache.
- Can I participate then?
- Right.
- Here's the question.
- Here it is.
- Okay. It's the 7th question.
- The 7th question.
It's the song all Koreans know.
I kept telling you to remember the lyrics.
It's "Dokdo Is Our Land."
The song was written...
by a KBS director, Park Moon Young.
- I see.
- Okay.
But the show where the song was introduced...
for the first time has a unique title.
- I knew the answer before.
- Okay.
- What's the title...
- I forgot, though.
Of the TV show...
where "Dokdo Is Our Land" was released for the first time?
- Sae Ho.
- Yes.
"Humor No. 1."
- What did you say?
- "Humor No. 1."
- But...
- It's such an old song.
- It is.
- Correct!
(Sae Ho answers it correctly.)
- Really?
- Jeong Kwang Tae sang the song.
- He used to be a comedian.
- That's right. Kwang Tae.
My guess was that he probably sang it during a segment.
- You're right. It was him.
- My gosh.
Gosh, he knew the history of comedy in Korea.
- Right.
- Sae Ho.
- I was right?
- Yes.
- I didn't know it'd be that.
- "Humor No. 1."
The show was funny.
- I didn't know.
- Director Park...
was working on "Humor No. 1" back then.
Then he read an article that...
Japan claimed that Dokdo was their territory.
He decided to write a song that claimed Dokdo as ours.
What happened next was really funny.
He was trying to produce the song.
They couldn't find a time when everyone was free.
- Only Kwang Tae...
- Kwang Tae recorded the song...
- alone.
- I see.
That's crazy.
(On stage, he sang the song alone.)
(But now, every Korean citizen sings it to the world.)
(No matter how much they claim it as their own)
(Dokdo is our land)
All right. Then Jong Min,
- Sae Ho, and I can eat dinner.
- My gosh.
- Congratulations.
- My gosh. That was great.
(Congratulations.)
That was quite unique. What a fun quiz this was.
- Sae Ho got this right.
- So...
- This feels great.
- Yes.
(Agreeing)
(The two islands, Usan and Murung, lie close to each other.)
(On clear days, they can be seen from afar.)
("The Veritable Records of King Sejong")
(Every historical evidence proves that Dokdo is our land.)
(Dokdo has always been our territory in thousands years of history.)
(Dokdo will forever remain our island beyond time.)
The three of you can eat with the professor.
(The 3 winners will eat seasoned squid and pork belly with him.)
The rest of you will get some food.
You can all pick a meal each.
- I'll take mussel barnacle rice.
- Me too.
I'll take the Amur wallflower meal.
- I'll take mussel barnacle rice.
- The wallflower meal is tasty.
Two Amur wallflower meals.
Mussel barnacle rice for the rest. We'll serve you right away.
- That looks so good.
- Here you go.
Hello.
(The delicacy of Ulleung Island is brought in.)
(The local meal of Ulleung Island)
(A one-dish meal that utilizes local products of Ulleung Island)
The side dishes look tasty.
(It's served with 11 side dishes, enough to fill up a table.)
- The squid looks great.
- Yes.
Personally,
seasoned squid and pork belly is my favorite.
(Mussel barnacle rice, Amur wallflower rice)
The squid was caught this morning.
- This morning?
- This morning? Gosh.
- Is this seasoned goat's beard?
- Yes.
- That was tasty.
- It's good.
- We're getting side dishes too?
- Of course.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
No way.
This is the most we've gotten on the show as losers.
- Right.
- Today...
- What a feast.
- It's a good day.
Gosh, this looks good. It's a healthy meal.
- That startled me.
- My goodness.
(Butting in)
What was that?
Gosh, this looks good. It's a healthy meal.
(The camera ambushes the table of Team Losers.)
What was that?
(Flustered)
I thought you were going to take it away.
I'm not joking. I thought there was a dinosaur.
It came at us.
(Fascinated)
That was a shocking experience.
(A shocking camera angle since his debut)
- Great.
- The Amur wallflowers look tasty.
We have to add some soy sauce.
- Let's add some soy sauce.
- Yes. Add a bit.
(Drizzled with a dash of the special soy sauce)
(The representative delicacy, mussel barnacle rice, )
(is a collection of the ocean's gems.)
(It's nature in a bowl.)
(The Amur wallflower rice with a fresh, aromatic scent)
(We invite you to the world of new flavors.)
(The professor has a bite first.)
It's tasty.
(The flavor brings a smile.)
- My gosh.
- Have a bite first.
Gosh, it's tasty.
(Sae Ho has it with the victory onion.)
- The victory onion.
- Right. We have to try it.
I get why she told us to mix it with the victory onion.
It has a hint of bitterness. It tastes great.
It's so good.
My gosh. The food here is so good.
Have some Amur wallflower rice. It's good.
(It's too good not to share.)
The food today is crazy.
You can only get a meal like this here.
Try the deodeok.
It's so good.
The vegetables are so good.
- It should be ready, right?
- Seriously.
- Right.
- I'll serve everyone now.
(It's packed with plump squids from Ulleung Island.)
- This is yours, Professor.
- Thank you.
I'll give you more.
I was actually curious about this dish.
We can easily get this dish in Seoul too.
But whenever he comes here, he always gets...
- seasoned squid and pork belly.
- Yes.
- It's so good.
- He said the squid was different.
Right.
(He has a bite of his favorite dish.)
My gosh. The food here is so good.
(The spicy and chewy squid and pork belly...)
(blend into an amazing flavor.)
(It's like there's a live squid in his mouth.)
- The squid is indeed different.
- Isn't it good?
- The squid is different.
- It's nice and plump.
- The squid is so good.
- The squid is crazy.
- Liars.
- You must have them together.
Liars. Stop lying.
- I'm serious.
- Really?
Stop lying. I bet they're the same.
I bet it tastes like the one in Seoul.
When you eat it in Seoul, squid can be a bit tough.
But this one...
It's so easy to chew it.
- You're lying.
- I'm serious.
Hey, it can't be that different.
- Gosh, it smells amazing.
- My gosh.
(I just want a bite of this.)
(Feeling bad for them)
I prepared more questions.
It's One Bite Quiz.
One Bite Quiz?
- Stop eating, Jong Min.
- What?
Why did you get more when he said there was a quiz?
Okay.
This isn't a difficult question.
- Okay.
- It's not hard.
Listen up.
To stand up to Japan's encroachment on Dokdo,
the residents of Ulleung Island formed...
the Dokdo Volunteer Garrison.
(Dokdo Volunteer Garrison)
- You've all heard of it, right?
- Yes.
You all know about them, don't you?
Some people helped recover...
the bodies of deceased members...
of the organization who drowned in the ocean.
Who are they?
They helped recover the bodies.
- They're people, right?
- Of course.
- Joon.
- Go ahead.
Haenyeos.
Really?
(Restless)
Wait.
- Haenyeos.
- This is what happened before.
- It has four syllables.
- Gosh.
- Seon Ho.
- Hey.
- We should let him answer first.
- Okay.
- You go 1st.
- It has 4 syllables.
- He must be partially correct.
- Then...
Cool haenyeos?
(Like Dokdo Stamps?)
- Then...
- Cool haenyeos?
(He didn't see this answer coming.)
(But he was quite close.)
- They're so cool. Right?
- Yes, they are cool indeed.
- But it's something else.
- The word before haenyeos...
is a name of another island.
- Seon Ho.
- My gosh.
- What?
- Seon Ho.
- Go ahead.
- Is this it? Jeju haenyeos.
(Jeju haenyeos)
- I guess he's right.
- Correct!
(Seon Ho gets it right.)
They came from Jeju to help out?
- Yes.
- The haenyeos came?
How...
(Even the Dokdo Scholar didn't know about this.)
Back then in 1950s,
haenyeos from Jeju came here...
and went underwater in order to make a living.
- They are cool indeed.
- They used to...
go underwater for food.
As I told you,
they also helped recover the bodies...
- of the fallen guards.
- Really?
My gosh. They're so cool.
They harvested and sold seaweed from Dokdo.
That's how they made a living.
(They set up an economic base on Dokdo...)
(by harvesting seaweed and abalones.)
It's very important to note that they engaged in...
economic activities on Dokdo.
- Yes. Right?
- Our country...
This was possible because Dokdo was our land.
- Right.
- Yes.
This is an important event to note.
Such activities took place on Dokdo.
- It'd be nice to remember them.
- Gosh. Jeju haenyeos.
Jeju haenyeos.
Let's give him a big piece.
How does it taste?
- It's so good.
- It is indeed different.
It's tasty.
His answer was the funniest today.
- Cool haenyeos.
- That could very well be correct.
(He gets a bite thanks to Joon.)
(Disappointed)
- Let's use this spare time...
- Here you go.
And give you one more question.
Do you have another question?
- Here it is. Listen up.
- Gosh.
The most famous volcanic island of Korea is Jeju Island.
- We all know that, right?
- Yes.
Ulleung Island is another volcanic island, right?
- Dokdo.
- Dokdo as well.
Then rank the islands in order from oldest...
to youngest.
- That's hard.
- The islands...
That's easy.
- Do you want to go first?
- Should I?
Sure.
Jeju Island, Ulleung Island, and Dokdo.
- I'll go with the reverse order.
- Why don't you...
Think about it. A volcano must've erupted first.
The biggest piece fell first like Jeju Island. Boom! Like that.
(Joon speculates that they were formed in order of size.)
(Wrong!)
- You see, the theme is Dokdo.
- Can I try it?
- Sure.
- Stop eating!
Let's give Se Yoon a try.
- Yes.
- Sure.
I don't need your pity.
- You didn't get to eat it, Se Yoon.
- Go ahead.
- I feel bad for you.
- I can't be sure.
Okay. Which one do you think was formed first?
- We're talking about Dokdo today.
- Yes.
Dokdo has to be the first one.
- Dokdo.
- Right.
That's the oldest island.
- Right? Then...
- Which one is next?
If I pick Jeju Island next, it wouldn't fit the theme.
I should go with Dokdo, Ulleung Island, and Jeju Island.
- That's the vibe I'm getting.
- That's correct.
(Se Yoon gets a bite.)
(The islands were created from the volcanic eruption.)
(Dokdo, about 4.6 million years ago)
(Ulleung Island, about 2.5 million years ago)
(Jeju Island, about 1.8 million years ago)
When you guys film the show,
you at least give some food to them, right?
We're giving them a lot more food today...
- because you're here.
- They don't give us this much food.
- Really?
- We rarely get this much food.
- This never happened before.
- It never happened before.
We'll meet the professor...
Okay.
- again tomorrow...
- What?
- on Dokdo.
- You can't do that.
He should sleep over, so we can talk.
- He's leaving after the meal?
- Yes.
We can sleep outside and talk.
(There's so much we haven't covered.)
- I'd love to stay over.
- We should talk about history.
- I'd love to.
- You know?
I'd love to play some games. You know?
- We'll meet him again tomorrow.
- We'll meet again tomorrow.
We'll say goodbye to him for now.
- Really?
- Yes.
We will soon be going to Dokdo together.
- As for everything I covered,
they're very important.
- Let's discuss that more on Dokdo.
- Okay.
Discussing that on Dokdo will be so meaningful.
Thank you so much for today.
- See you tomorrow.
- Thank you.
- I'll see you tomorrow morning.
- See you tomorrow.
- Yes.
I wonder where we'll go on a full stomach.
We'll go to our base camp now.
My gosh.
- It's nice here.
- My gosh. Seriously.
Coming here for a few days...
- sounds good.
- Gosh. Let me open up the window.
- We ought to.
- ACs can't compete with this.
Of course not.
(The drive along the coast on Ulleung Island is romantic.)
I can feel the breeze on my skin.
(The breeze on my skin feels great.)
I'd love to have Dokdo shrimp alfresco here.
(Having Dokdo shrimp alfresco must feel amazing.)
That would be the best.
And imagine having a clean room...
- where you can sleep behind you.
- Right.
(Imagine how great it'd be to lie down and sleep.)
It looks like we'll be sleeping outdoors.
- Right? I don't see any houses.
- Seriously.
I don't think there's a proper house for us.
Wait. We're going to a port?
- I hope we can go to sleep now.
- But...
everything is usually around a port.
I don't see any boats.
Wait.
Will we have to catch squid?
- Ulleung Island...
- Are you serious?
But that can't be our base camp.
Did they book the lodging facing the ocean?
- Did they?
- To leave right away tomorrow?
Going to Dokdo after catching squid will be tough.
Whoever ate a lot of squid should go.
Jong Min ate a lot.
(Jong Min should go.)
Shouldn't the professor go then?
It would make sense if Jong Min and the professor go.
(Will he end up going on a boat to catch squid?)
I see a huge boat. Look on my left.
Is that for the Korea Coast Guard?
That looks pretty cool. I've never seen anything like that.
Are we going to get on their boat?
- Where?
- What?
- Are we getting on that boat?
- It can't be, right?
- No way.
- That can't be.
- What?
Will we spend the night with the Korea Coast Guard?
- They set up cameras over there.
- What?
- What is this?
(The staff members are in front of the boat?)
This can't be happening.
- The professor said earlier...
- Yes.
- we could enter Dokdo for sure.
- Right.
- Enter where?
- But you can't guarantee that...
when it comes to Dokdo...
unless you're with the guards.
Are we going to sleep on Dokdo?
- Enter where?
- But you can't guarantee that...
when it comes to Dokdo...
unless you're with the guards.
Are we going to sleep on Dokdo?
- Everyone.
- What's going on?
- What's this? What's going on?
- Why did you turn on the lights?
- What are we doing here?
- What is it?
What's going on? What?
Aren't they the Korea Coast Guard?
- We have now...
- What?
- Will they arrest us for a crime?
- Did we do something wrong?
Arrived at our base camp.
What? We're sleeping on that vessel?
- This is our base camp?
- For real?
What are we doing here? This is for the Korea Coast Guard.
- The vessel behind you...
- What?
Is your base camp for the night.
The Korea Coast Guard?
- The scale of this thing is crazy.
- What's going on?
No way.
So people said there was no base camp.
Last night, I slept on a cruise. Today...
- On that?
- The vessel...
protects our territorial waters...
around Ulleung Island and Dokdo in the East Sea.
This is the guard ship...
for the Korea Coast Guard of the East Sea.
- That's an important ship.
- This is crazy.
You will now board the guard ship...
- Will we go to Dokdo?
- and head to Dokdo.
You'll spend the night on the water.
- What?
- How long does it take?
- It will sail slowly like a cruise?
- It will sail slowly.
Yes. And...
I've invited someone to introduce the guard ship.
My gosh. This is...
- Hello.
- My gosh.
- Nice to meet you. Welcome.
- Hello.
- Please stand in the middle.
- Nice to meet you.
Okay.
Hello.
I serve the Korea Coast Guard Vessel 3017 in the East Sea.
I'm Police Corporal Lee Jin Woo.
- Nice to meet you.
- Lee Jin Woo?
Yes, I'm Lee Jin Woo.
- Corporal Jin Woo.
- Corporal Lee Jin Woo.
- Then...
- The Korea Coast Guard.
Instead of being in the military, you're the police?
Yes, as a police officer,
- I guard the sea.
- That's amazing.
(Protecting Ulleung Island, Dokdo, and the East Sea)
(Korea Coast Guard of the East Sea)
(Defending our maritime territory, )
(preventing maritime crimes, and performing disaster relief...)
(Heroes who carry out a wide range of missions 24 hours a day)
(Protecting Dokdo by monitoring and responding to Japanese vessels)
(The Korea Coast Guard of the East Sea protects Dokdo.)
How did we get invited?
Dokdo Day is October 25.
- Right.
- To commemorate the day,
we will take you to Dokdo in our vessel.
This is unbelievable.
I can't believe that we'll go to Dokdo in this vessel.
We will move now under the corporal's guide.
- Okay, let's go.
- What an honor.
- I feel so honored.
- Isn't this meaningful?
I can't believe that I'm getting on a naval vessel.
This is incredible. Let's go.
- I'll film it.
- Everyone.
We will move with the corporal.
- Here we go.
Goodness.
Is this a boat?
Is this a lifeboat?
When you go to Dokdo tomorrow, you'll take this boat.
After anchoring the naval vessel?
(8 hours later)
(The members got on the boat to get to the island.)
It's very...
(The moment they've been waiting for to set out to Dokdo)
(To our island that fills us with reverence)
No matter how much they claim it as their own
(Soon, we will meet Dokdo.)
(They start to board the patrol vessel.)
Hello.
It's nice to meet you.
Oh, my. It's completely new. It's a new ship.
Joon, this was built last year.
Right. I can tell that it's new.
- It's brand new.
- The paint hasn't even chipped.
It's totally new.
- It looks amazing.
- What's this metal?
It smells like metal.
It seems like it was recently painted.
The fire hydrant.
Fire.
Goodness.
- Like this...
- These are private rooms.
(Dormitory)
This is awesome.
(First time seeing the inside of a patrol vessel)
- There's a laundry room.
- Please go upstairs.
- Upstairs?
- Okay.
(Once you pass the rooms and go upstairs)
Please go this way.
- It's the pilothouse.
- We're here.
- This is the pilothouse.
- Hello.
- Hello. Thank you for inviting us.
- My gosh.
(Impressed)
- Gosh.
- Hello.
Hello.
- Gosh.
(They enter the pilothouse.)
What is this place?
- The pilothouse?
- Yes, it's the pilothouse.
Is this what we saw in "Real Men?"
(Pilothouse)
(Where navigation and speed are managed)
(It's the control center of a patrol vessel.)
During navigation, we coordinate...
radar, steering, engine control, and communication systems.
We oversee all ship operations.
How many people operate a vessel like this?
One person in this seat.
Are there also assistants?
Everyone else assists him.
If the vessel deviates from its course due to the wind or current,
then corrections are made.
The structure underneath the chair is unusual.
They look like chairs at a hair salon.
While navigating, the highest wave...
we encountered was 11m.
- Gosh, 11m?
- Did you say 11m?
That's like a tsunami.
(Despite the towering waves, )
(their deployment mission has to continue.)
- As the chairs sway back and forth, - Yes.
- you get less tired.
- Right.
- That's why they look like this.
- It's fascinating.
(The members move onto the next place.)
- Do we go downstairs?
- Yes.
The stairs are quite steep.
The stairs are almost perpendicular.
(Extremely steep)
- Please go all the way down.
- Okay.
- It's perpendicular.
- When they get dispatched,
they would have to jump down.
- You could get hurt easily.
- The employees fell down...
- Right?
- when there were big waves.
- I can imagine.
- Really?
- When you go down in a hurry.
- You could get seriously injured.
- On the stairs?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
- They would move in a hurry...
- when there's an emergency.
- Right.
Since we're in the sea, there's a lot of humidity on the stairs.
Gosh, what's this?
It looks amazing.
This is it.
(The hull of the East Sea patrol vessel)
(The deck)
This is it.
(The central area for helicopter operations)
Transferring emergency patients or delivering supplies.
This is where it takes place.
(The central space for naval operations)
- It's nice and clean.
- Isn't this a heliport?
Yes, it's a heliport.
We got to see everywhere inside.
In order to defend the East Sea,
the Coast Guards are...
I feel very reassured.
They're working very hard.
Spending eight nights on the vessel...
- Of course.
- must be stifling.
- I miss my family the most.
- Right.
His children are 1 and 4 years old.
- Do you have children?
- Yes.
He got married at an early age.
With the distance, you must miss them a lot.
Four-year-olds are adorable.
It's sad to say goodbye to them,
but my heart flutters when I'm about to return home.
- That's what keeps me going.
- Before seeing your children?
Yes.
(Working in the perilous sea)
(While being away from their families, )
(they prioritize the safety of the people)
(They're the unseen heroes.)
- Everyone.
- Yes?
- The ship will be departing soon.
- Right.
(The Coast Guard vessel is preparing to set sail.)
Coast Guard officers will take shifts...
- and be on duty for 24 hours.
- Goodness.
They will safeguard not only Dokdo but also the East Sea.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- We can't just sit back and watch.
- Of course not.
- So, - Are we sleeping outdoors?
We will select only the two of you.
The two of you will join the Korea Coast Guard...
on their night duty shift.
Like what we did on Buchi Peak?
- By the way...
- In the morning,
- the officers will get to rest.
- Yes.
What about us?
Since you're on 2 Days 1 Night team,
you'll follow our schedule.
Are we staying up all night?
(Turning gray)
- What if...
- Are we staying up all night?
Joon and Se Yoon get picked?
That would be the worst.
It'd be our worst trip to Ulleung Island.
I'm about to lose my mind.
I've already lost it.
All right.
Night duty shift is staying up all night.
That's right.
Doesn't their shift end at eight in the morning?
If I get picked, it'll be over for me.
This is too intense.
This is night duty shift game.
- How do we pick the two?
- It's a game.
Let's invite those who will join the mission.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Is it the two of you?
- Yes.
- Please stand here.
- Welcome.
Could you introduce yourselves?
Hello, I serve the Korea Coast Guard...
Vessel 3017.
I'm Constable Cho Min Ji.
- She's a police officer.
- Constable Cho Min Ji.
May I say what I prepared?
- Of course.
- Okay.
It's really nice to meet you. Thank you very much.
I serve the Korea Coast Guard.
I'm Constable Song Bo Geum.
- Sae Ho, could you show us?
- Hello, Bo Geum.
It's really nice to meet you. Thank you very much.
- Yes.
- Hello.
- Thank you.
- RNMY, TYVM.
- Exactly.
- It was RNMY, TYVM.
Thank you.
- Gosh.
- You sent her a heart.
The three of them are team leaders.
Each leader will pick two team members.
Are they picking us?
Moon Se Yoon.
(They pick their favorite members.)
- I pick Cho Sae Ho.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Could you stand with your team members?
The teams have been decided.
- Okay. Let's go.
- All right.
Here's your first mission...
with the three police officers.
It's a mission where you have to be in sync.
- I see.
- Let's try our best.
It's Zero People.
Do you know Zero People?
- Zero People?
- Yes.
- We have to sit down.
- I see.
- Do we move ourselves instead?
- Yes.
He's the best celebrity of Zero People game.
- Really?
- Yes.
All we have to do is stay seated.
- We did it last time.
- I don't remember.
Sit down. Let's do an example.
- One, two, three. Two.
- Next...
(The celebrity in this team doesn't know.)
- If you get caught, you'll be out.
- Next...
- We've played it before.
- Right.
(What was it?)
- It's based on luck.
- It's all about luck.
Each team will play.
The team that lasts the longest...
will be exempted.
- It's based on luck anyway.
- Even if we work, we'll have fun.
Of course.
Team One, please come to the center.
(Sighing)
- That's right.
- Please.
Song Bo Geum.
- I bet Joon won't get up.
- Let's not stop each other.
You can get up often or stay seated.
This is all about how you feel.
Trust your feelings.
Night duty shift is at stake.
Please watch each other carefully.
DinDin is ready to cheat.
What are you talking about?
How can I cheat in front of the police officers?
- Okay.
- Is this even possible to cheat?
(Playing dumb)
They'll arrest you if you cheat.
- All right.
- We can do it.
- One, two, three. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Give it your all.
- Okay.
- What do you think?
- That's a great idea.
Of course.
- Just trust your feelings.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Okay.
- Shall we start?
Go.
- Okay.
- Here goes the first team.
- Get ready.
(I hope they get doomed.)
Let's start. One, two, three.
One.
(They succeed 1 time.)
One, two, three. One.
(What?)
I knew this would happen.
- Okay, they lost.
- In that case...
(We thought that they were dodging well.)
One, two, three. One.
(Flinching)
(Sae Ho and Joon succeed 1 time.)
(Cheering)
What about a practice round?
- Who's next?
- Wasn't that a practice round?
- There's no practice round.
- Okay.
(They wasted the first round.)
- We can consider ourselves safe.
- Goodness.
- Fight hard today.
- This is...
Fight all day long.
(Only scars remain in their teamwork)
Let's get started.
This is DinDin's team.
Here we go.
- Zero.
- One, two, three.
- Two.
- Gosh.
One, two, three. One.
(They succeed 2 times.)
(They already outran Sae Ho and Joon.)
- It's over for us.
- One, two, three. One.
One, two, three. One.
Okay.
- I didn't have to get up.
- Okay.
Are we still playing?
Didn't you just get up?
- Play until the end.
- Okay, let's focus.
(He's feeling jealous.)
- Either way...
- You understand it, don't you?
One, two, three, One.
One, two, three. Zero.
(They were slightly late.)
(They succeed 5 times.)
(They're quite good.)
One, two, three. One.
(Getting up)
- One.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
(You still did a good job.)
- It was difficult.
- We succeeded many times.
Jong Hyun.
Cover your mouth.
- You were looking at my mouth.
- Cover your mouth.
When you hear that, get up.
If I don't hear anything, stay seated.
(Staring)
Zero.
(His lips don't lie.)
He's going to cover his mouth.
- He'll cover his mouth.
- Then we have to listen.
For you and the corporal, it's up to you.
I'll be listening.
We'll be fine as long as you do well.
Only I will get up. The two of you should stay seated.
Let's do it.
Three.
- Okay.
- Okay?
(He shares the secret with a bright smile.)
I'll keep that in mind.
- One, two, three. Three.
- Like that?
(DinDin and Seon Ho are ahead with 5 points.)
(Jong Min and Se Yoon's attempt)
Here's what I think.
The corporal is a bit nervous.
The corporal is nervous right now.
- It's because he's cold.
- He's very nervous.
- He'll get up right away.
- He's coming down with a cold.
- I'm getting nervous.
- Jong Min.
The two of us will stay seated. Only you will play.
I know, but I feel nervous.
- The team in first place survives.
- Right.
It's hard to tell the result. Only the first place survives.
That's right.
- We're good to go.
- We already placed first.
All we have to do is go to bed.
You think so?
We have the King of Zero, Kim Jong Min.
(King of Zero)
It's only about luck.
- All right, here we go.
- The corporal will get up.
One, two, three. Three.
(They succeed 1 time.)
(King of Zero concentrates only on what he hears.)
(Will they succeed more than 5 times?)
Do you feel it?
One, two, three. Zero.
- He got up late.
- That was slightly late.
- He was late.
- Jong Min is doing well.
One, two, three. One.
(They succeed 3 times.)
(They succeed 4 times.)
One, two, three.
(Surprised)
(If they succeed one more, their scores will tie.)
One, two, three. Three.
(They succeed 5 times.)
(Their scores tied in an instant.)
(If they pass this time, Jong Min and Se Yoon will get exempted.)
One, two, three. Zero.
(They succeed 6 times.)
(King of Zero made it.)
That was amazing.
(Jong Min and Se Yoon are exempt from the night duty shift.)
How many times have we done it?
(Speechless)
You'll play as long as you can.
One, two, three. One.
One, two, three. Zero.
(They succeed 9 times.)
(Jealous)
One, two, three. One.
One, two, three. Two.
(What's the matter with them?)
(Jong Min and Se Yoon succeed 12 times.)
We're free.
- It's King of Zero, Kim Jong Min.
- What?
(He proved himself as a king.)
- That's enough.
- I'll stop.
- How many times did we win?
- I won't do it anymore.
Se Yoon and Jong Min are exempt from the night duty shift.
He survived.
It will be one of us.
- Unlike them, we had no strategies.
- I'm jealous.
Here's your second mission.
(Night duty shift game, Round 2)
The second mission is a knot game.
- Knot?
- That's hard.
Maybe they have to undo a knot.
In maritime rescue operations, the rope knotting techniques...
are essential for saving lives.
That's why we prepared it.
(An essential training for Coast Guard officers)
Please set them up.
- We should step aside.
- Right.
I feel bad, but...
Let's get some fresh air.
The four types of knots were made...
by the rescue workers.
Two of them get undone when you pull them.
The other two are impossible to undo.
You'll succeed if the knots get undone.
The member to pick knots that are impossible to undo...
will get the night duty shift.
- So the knots should get undone?
- Yes.
If you undo the knots, your life will be without problems.
They said that they know by looking at them.
(The officers know the answer because they're trained.)
That's amazing.
How can you tell?
(Impossible to distinguish with the naked eye)
Do we have to pick from here?
- Don't go over the line.
- That's fine.
(Don't step on the line.)
(Being wary)
In what order will you choose?
I'll pick number one so that it's clear-cut.
- Number one?
- Yes.
Then I pick number two.
Let's stand in order.
I pick number three.
This one is the worst.
I don't care anymore. I pick number four.
I think I can tell.
I can't tell from looking at them.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
(Pit-a-pat)
Shall we start with number one?
- Let's go.
- Number one.
I can pull it slowly, can't I?
Hold this rope.
Se Yoon.
He will pull your wrist.
No, right there.
- Cho Sae Ho.
- Here I go.
- Pull it slowly.
- The Coast Guards are with us.
(We'll be right back.)
(They start pulling.)
- Pull it slowly.
- The Coast Guards are with us.
- Here I go.
- Pull it slowly.
(They start pulling.)
- The Coast Guards are with us.
The Coast Guards are with us.
It looks like number one could get undone.
(Slowly)
(The knots get undone neatly.)
(Sae Ho is exempt from the night duty shift.)
Number one looked too obvious.
You're exempt from the night duty shift.
(Dancing steps)
No.
- She's so disappointed.
- Oh, no.
I thought the last knot would stay entangled,
but it didn't.
You're safe.
My chance of losing is two-thirds.
(His chance of losing is two-thirds.)
He won't do the night shift. Oh, my.
(Celebrating his victory)
- Do a double under.
- Goodness.
(He's so excited.)
Look at his performance. He's celebrating.
Look at that.
(He skips twice.)
Number two?
(The pressure of the night duty shift gets worse.)
- Number 2.
- Who is number 2?
Isn't it over once number two gets undone?
- I guess so.
- I feel bad.
- Maybe number two won't get undone.
- I bet it will.
You're doing it in order. We don't know the result.
- The worst trip to Ulleung Island.
- This won't get undone.
The worst trip to Ulleung Island for Joon.
(The reason why Joon is so desperate)
(He gets picked to depart one day before the shoot.)
(Groggy)
(He hiked as soon as he arrived.)
(He placed last in the quiz without saying a word.)
The worst trip to Ulleung Island for Joon.
The man of Ulleung Island.
(What will happen to the man of Ulleung Island?)
He shoots 3 Days 2 Nights by himself.
A night duty shift on top of that.
Here we go, Joon.
- There's something wrong with it.
- The man of Ulleung Island.
One, two...
(Looking away)
Three.
- Three.
- Let's go, night duty shift.
(Being dragged)
Let's go.
(I pity you.)
Goodness.
Joon gets the night duty shift.
- These knots look...
- Oh, no.
Connected.
These are called butterfly knots.
When we hook something on it...
- Do you hook it on here?
- Undoing them is impossible.
You told me to get here a day before.
That's when everything went wrong.
Can we do it at the same time?
(Only one of them will get the night duty shift.)
- Put your wrist in.
- Let's do it simultaneously.
(DinDin versus Seon Ho)
These two are the most confusing ones.
These won't get undone.
- I'll put my finger in.
- Grab the rope here.
(It's hard to tell from the shape.)
- They both look impossible.
- One of them gets undone easily.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Sighing heavily)
(A wail resonates quietly.)
(He doesn't care who wins.)
- I don't think this will be untied.
- I agree, but yours also...
- I think this one will be untied.
- I mean, it goes in here...
Okay. Let's start. I can see it.
- It's tied tightly.
- This won't untie.
- Pull it already.
- It's coming loose.
- It's already coming loose.
- Oh, that's right.
- One, two, - It's coming loose already.
Three.
(They pulled the ropes!)
Let's go!
- Three.
- Let's go!
(Tightening)
(Teasing DinDin by showing his front teeth)
(Seon Ho is exempt from the night duty.)
(DinDin stays still like a rock just like Joon.)
Jump rope with this.
- Do it here.
- Let it go.
(The two losers are together in the same frame.)
Please just let it go.
(They might jump rope all night long.)
Gosh, hey.
(He throws a tantrum after a long time.)
So he'll be on the night duty.
- Congratulations.
- Right.
(It's good to make good memories while working the night shift.)
Great job, everyone.
We thank all the officers for joining us.
- It's awesome. I won.
- This patrol vessel will leave...
- for Dokdo shortly.
- Got it.
Joon and DinDin should start working the night shift right away.
The other members will go to bed.
- Let's get some sleep.
- That was crazy. Nice.
Viewers, we're finally leaving for Dokdo.
We will complete the night duty without any problems.
2 Days!
- 1 Night!
- Let's go to Dokdo!
- Let's go!
- Great job.
- That was amazing.
(Now we will head to Dokdo!)
- This is amazing.
- Right.
(Tidying up all the things that are on the land)
(Everyone is finishing up the preparation for the departure.)
(The ship drifts away from the land slowly.)
(We'll get going now.)
(Vessel 3017...)
(of the East Regional Headquarters Korea Coast Guard departs!)
This is really nice.
It's the best.
It's so nice.
- Oh, it's nice.
- It's really nice.
It's great.
(The real bedroom for the officers working in the vessel)
Gosh, my back. My back hurts.
- My back hurts too.
- It feels so refreshing.
(Se Yoon, who's on a 3-day trip, lies down right away.)
It's so refreshing.
(Seon Ho gets into the bottom bunk.)
This is nice. I'm happy.
I want to sleep with you.
(Joon and DinDin changed into uniforms for the night duty.)
Hey, you look good in it.
Joon, you seem reliable.
I feel relieved, thinking you guard the sea.
You see... I don't know about DinDin.
But Joon, you do seem reliable.
- Good luck with your night shift.
- Sleep well. We'll guard the sea.
- Thank you.
- Constable Lee Joon.
- Do your best to guard the country.
- I will.
- Sleep well.
- Do your best to guard the sea.
Got it.
2 Days 1 Night.
- At ease.
- You can rest up now.
If you...
have night snacks, send me a message.
You don't get a signal here.
Come here and tell me.
(They leave while the other members cheer them on.)
(What will the members on night duty do?)
Oh, my. What place is this?
(Joon arrived at the place where he'll work.)
- What place is this? Hello.
- Oh, welcome. Hello.
(Joon will work the night shift at the engine room.)
- Hello.
- You look great in the uniform.
- Hello. Oh, thank you.
- You look great in it.
- Indeed.
- Thank you. Yes.
- This is the engine room.
- We say, "The engine is the heart."
- I see.
The engine room plays the most important role in a vessel.
(The power sources of the vessel are centralized in the engine room.)
- We operate the engine...
- Yes.
Using various alarms and monitors.
We also check all the equipment in the engine room.
The engine room contains various systems.
I understand. What are my responsibilities here?
Wear gloves and ear protection and take the flashlight...
- to go on a patrol.
- Understood.
- Shall we go together?
- Yes.
(After wearing protective gear, they go on a patrol!)
(The equipment in the engine room causes high levels of noises.)
(Look with your eyes.)
Pardon me?
(Suddenly, Scream in Silence game begins.)
(With your eyes)
(What should I see with my eyes?)
(Look at everything with your eyes.)
(He failed to read her signal.)
(He starts the work, trying to do as his senior does.)
(He can see the spot to be checked, following her hand movements.)
(The engine room work log)
(Check if oil leaks on machine joints.)
(This time, they check another machine.)
(40°C)
Why is that an issue?
It means that the oil temperature is in the normal range.
(Check the oil temperature and the pressure.)
- The oil temperature is normal.
- Yes.
It's in the normal range.
You should check the pressure by monitoring this gauge.
- Checking the pressure.
- It's in the normal range too.
It's working fine.
(They check everything thoroughly.)
(The engine room patrol is over.)
- It's like "Family Entertainment."
- Right.
I had to read her lips.
- It felt like a game on the show...
- Right?
When I was a trainee.
I was just like you back then.
It's very noisy in the engine room.
It was so loud that I couldn't even think clearly.
I couldn't hear her at all.
Oh, my. It's so dark in here.
(DinDin arrives at a dark place?)
(DinDin will work at the pilothouse.)
- Hello.
(Constable Cho Min Ji welcomes DinDin gladly.)
Why does it have to be so dark in here?
If it's bright in here, we can't see the outside clearly.
(The lights were turned on before the vessel departed.)
Can you see anything?
I can't see anything.
Exactly. My goodness.
We use GPS like when we drive a car.
We use GPS and the radar, which you can see over there,
to check if there are ships or rocks around this vessel.
This system can detect physical objects.
Until what time do you work?
A night shift...
starts at midnight and ends at 4am. It goes on for 4 hours.
- You take turns like a night watch.
- Yes.
You have to come out while sleeping.
- How many shifts in a day?
- We work in three shifts.
I guess you don't have much time to rest.
(While they're talking, the phone rings suddenly.)
(Is everything okay?)
We communicate with the officers in the engine room.
For example, we let them know we'll use the engine.
(Fascinated)
Yes, we'll increase it to 650 RPM.
You can stay there and try to adjust the speed.
- You can try to increase it.
- Try it.
- Check the speed here.
- What's the speed now?
It's 557 RPM now, as you can see. Push it gently.
- So it should be...
- Increase it to 650 RPM. Gently.
(It's an important task to adjust the speed of the vessel.)
I will increase the speed.
(He repeats what he is to do loud and clear.)
- Is it to increase the speed?
- Correct.
(DinDin calmly increases the speed.)
It's 650 RPM now.
- You did a good job.
- I adjusted it to 650 RPM.
(DinDin adjusted it to the assigned speed accurately.)
- You're quite good at it.
- Thank you.
I tapped it gently to adjust it accurately.
(He completed his first task without a hitch.)
Oh, my. It feels strange.
It's like pressing the accelerator in a car.
- My gosh. It's so scary.
- How should I go up?
Hey, don't do that. My gosh.
Stop. It might fall.
(Climbing up)
Goodness. He went up to the top bunk.
- The bed must be bent now.
- You bent the bed.
- You're lying.
- It's true.
- I see it in the mirror. It's bent.
- It's bent now.
- Stop lying.
- It's true. It's sunken.
Sae Ho, you're my friend, so tell me the truth.
- It's bent.
- Okay. I'll go down.
(He's convinced right away.)
(You should never have gone up there in the first place.)
Shall I sleep on the top bunk?
- Go ahead.
- It'll be hard for them...
to go up on the top bunk when they're back.
Shall I sleep on the top bunk so they can sleep comfortably?
That'd be nice of you. Then I'll sleep on the floor.
(Sae Ho will sleep on the top bunk for the members on the night duty.)
Se Yoon, please turn the light off.
(It's time to end their day which has been a long day.)
As of now, I will turn off the light in the room...
of the 2 Days 1 Night team on the coast guard's vessel.
Police.
(He salutes loud and clear before turning the light off.)
- What?
- Oh, it's not bad.
(Lights off)
- Can you hear the waves?
- Yes.
It's shaking less than the cruise ship did yesterday.
- Really?
- Yes.
But you can feel the motion, right?
Definitely. It's swaying to the sides, and it's tilted.
- It's swaying gently.
- It's tilted to one side.
This room is quite clean and nice.
(Listening to the waves, they sleep in an unfamiliar, special place.)
Good night, guys.
Sleep well.
(They fall asleep while imagining Dokdo they'll see soon.)
We actually monitor what happens in this room...
during a night shift.
Sir, may I ask how long you've been working here?
I've been working here for almost 27 years.
For 27 years? Hold on. That's amazing.
(He's been working here for 27 long years.)
I'll be retiring soon.
- Really?
- Yes.
While working this job,
you must've experienced a lot.
Yes, I've seen a lot of accidents as well.
- Accidents?
- Yes.
Accidents that damaged equipment or caused casualties.
Exactly.
I've come this far, going through a lot.
You must've gained skills and knowledge from your experience.
But there must've been a lot of difficulties as well.
You're amazing. It's not easy...
That's our duty.
Because I've been working here, I got lucky...
and got to meet a top star like you.
I'm flattered.
Goodness, I'm just...
I'm just a kid who dropped by.
(It's my honor.)
Working for 27 years for the same job...
This is incredible, isn't it?
You still have to go out to the sea even when the weather is bad.
- That's right.
- How do you handle it?
When the weather is bad,
- It must be tough.
- it really is hectic.
I can't even stand properly because I lose balance.
- You get swayed like this?
- Yes, it gets that extreme.
- My body gets bent over.
- Right.
- So you keep rocking then.
- You sleep like that too?
- Yes, in the same condition.
My goodness.
Some people fall down while sleeping on the bunk beds.
- When the weather is bad?
- That's right.
That must be really tough.
(Even in harsh weather and challenging working conditions, )
(the Coast Guard silently stands and watches over the sea.)
(And the important task of...)
(the East Regional Headquarters Korea Coast Guard)
(Protecting Dokdo)
I thought only the coastal guards protect the island.
Here's the most important thing about protecting Dokdo.
We have to stay alert to the Japan Coast Guard.
- They have this patrol boat.
- Right.
They come up to our area every ten days or so.
It comes towards Dokdo at a very fast speed.
Why? Why do they do that?
They want to insist that Dokdo belongs to Japan.
- They just want to insist...
- They want to show...
- Right.
- We make sure they don't get...
any closer to Dokdo.
We get really close to the boat so that they don't approach us.
(Close maneuvers to prevent Japanese patrol ships from approaching)
- That's how it works.
- Do they leave soon?
They just go after taking a few rounds.
That means...
they can't approach us because you're protecting it.
They can't come closer to the island.
That means the island belongs to us.
Right, it belongs to us. That's why we always...
We're protecting it.
We never leave Dokdo alone.
There is always at least one boat of Korea Coast Guard...
that protects the island throughout the year.
- Is that so?
- Right.
You guys work really hard.
This is why we are here.
- We protect our territory.
- That's amazing.
(The Coast Guard tirelessly protects our seas day and night...)
(to safeguard Korea's maritime sovereignty.)
(Expressing sincere gratitude to the Coast Guard officers...)
(who are protecting Dokdo even at this very moment)
Could you take over my shift?
(Duty shift is over at 4am.)
It's 120 degrees.
You guys work really hard.
Aren't you hungry?
(They got hungry because they worked so hard.)
I'm hungry, I need late-night snacks.
(Finally, it's time to have late-night snacks.)
- Here is your ramyeon.
- It's huge.
Is it heavy?
- Let's eat.
- This looks so good.
What did you put in there?
- It just looks amazing.
- It has cabbage. Please start.
It smells amazing.
(Special ramyeon with cabbage)
- Enjoy your meal.
- Enjoy.
What did you put in here?
The late-night snack vibe is amazing.
(Smelling the ramyeon melts their fatigue away.)
You added all the ingredients.
(Slurping)
Gosh, this ramyeon is so good.
(Very satisfied)
- Gosh, it's hot.
- I can literally have it every day.
The spiciness is okay, right?
(DinDin who worked hard is also slurping the noodles.)
How is this different from the usual ones you have?
I added a lot of cabbage.
- Cabbage has this sweetness.
- Right.
The cabbage helps remove the garlic flavors.
And it has this spiciness too.
(No wonder it tastes so good.)
Gosh, now that we're eating...
- I feel we're lucky to be here.
- Right.
This is so delicious.
- I'm glad you like it.
- It's so good.
- Please have some more.
- Enjoy.
(A satisfying late-night snack for everyone)
This is delicious.
It tastes even better after taking your shifts.
So I heard...
that the sea waves were strong during autumn and winter.
- I know, the waves are so strong.
- You can't have this then.
- No, we can't.
- The vessel must sway a lot.
- Yes. It sways a lot.
- Right.
All the utensils fall.
Then how do you eat?
We do get to eat.
- You eat like this?
- Right.
- We get swayed when we lie down.
- You'll have an upset stomach.
How long have you been working like that?
- About a year and six months.
- About a year.
- A year and 6 months?
- A year and 6 months.
(Bo Geum and Min Ji have been working for 1 year and 6 months.)
It must have been tough in the beginning.
I heard that you were married. What does your husband do?
He and I are from the same academy.
- Is he here now?
- No, he isn't here.
He's on another vessel.
- He's also an officer.
- That means...
What happens if you two can't meet your schedules?
- We don't get to see each other.
- Really?
So it must take months to see each other then.
No.
We saw each other for 12 hours in September.
- You saw each other for 12 hours?
- Right.
We saw each other for 12 hours because of our shifts.
- In one single month of September.
- Right.
- You saw him for 12 hours?
- Right, 12 hours.
That is so tough.
(They all work so hard.)
So how long has it been for you two to have such shift schedules?
We have been on board last year and this year.
It has been a year and six months.
So you couldn't see him a lot then.
So throughout a month, I only get to see him for less than seven days.
You must miss him a lot.
I can't really remember his face.
You can't remember his face?
- But I think she's right.
- You meant it, right?
- I really don't...
- My goodness.
Do you want to send him a video message?
"Are you seeing this? Officer Park, are you protecting the island?"
This is awkward.
Just send him. Come on!
Was it really tasty?
- It was good.
- Really?
I was about to get hungry.
- It was so delicious.
- I'm glad you liked it.
It touched my heart.
(Feeling happy)
We'll do the dishes.
- You can leave now.
- You cooked for us.
(Thoroughly washing the dishes)
It's all set.
(Joon and DinDin's night shift is over.)
(Vessel 3017 continues to approach towards Dokdo.)
(Faintly visible Dokdo)
(It's time for them to wake up at 5:30am.)
(They're still soundly asleep.)
Everyone...
(Sae Ho getting up)
- It's time to get up.
- Okay.
How's the weather?
Luckily, the weather is nice.
- Really?
- Yes.
What's happening?
You have to get up now.
I'll turn on the lights.
(Turning the lights on to wake them up)
It's 5:30am already.
(Checking the time now)
- Let's get up.
- Se Yoon, get up.
Joon.
(Quickly waking the others too)
Jong Min.
(He went back to his bed.)
The weather is nice, you'll be surprised when you get to the deck.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Is there anything that would surprise them on the deck?)
- It's so pretty.
- Good morning.
Goodness, let's take a video of that.
- Gosh, the dawn has...
- It's so pretty.
(Did he spot something?)
Goodness, let's take a video of that.
- Gosh, the dawn has...
- It's so pretty.
(Did he spot something?)
The view is amazing.
Gosh, it's so pretty.
(Finally, it's showing...)
This is crazy.
(The final destination of their trip, Dokdo)
Is that Dokdo?
- Is that Dokdo?
- What you see over there...
is Korea's easternmost island, Dokdo.
(An island that protects the easternmost area of Korea)
The place on the Korean Peninsula where the sun rises first.
- My gosh, it's pretty.
- I'll take a photo with the island.
(The place on the Korean Peninsula where the sun rises first)
It's splendid.
(A sense of mystery in harmony with the first light before dawn)
It's marvelous.
Gosh, it's so pretty.
- It's very touching.
- I know, it's touching.
- First time visiting Dokdo?
- Yes.
It's magnificent.
Dokdo is incredible.
Yes, it is.
It's my first time visiting there at this hour. It's amazing.
(The breathtaking scenery of the easternmost tip...)
(gradually revealing its beauty)
This place gives me mixed feelings.
(For the first-time visitors...)
(as well as the visitors who visited here before)
It's like someone painted that.
- It's wonderful.
- I know.
(They all can't take their eyes off the island.)
It's a very precious video.
Yes, it's an amazing video.
It's beyond being beautiful.
It just feels different.
You two, please turn around.
The island will be in between you two. There you go.
(They're taking pictures to cherish this honorable moment.)
Okay.
One, two, three.
(The unforgettable first glimpse of Dokdo)
(Meanwhile, )
(the darkness clears.)
The sun is about to rise soon.
- It's rising up.
- It is.
- Gosh.
- It's rising up.
(Impressed)
It rises up very quickly.
The sunrise is more beautiful than any other ones.
(The moment of sunrise at the easternmost point of Korea)
It rises up very quickly.
It rises up really quickly.
It's like the sea is pushing it up.
That's how quickly it's rising up.
Is it because this is the easternmost place?
It's rising up really beautifully.
- It's really red.
- It's refreshing.
(It's a touching moment they want to remember for a long time.)
(Let's all take a moment to enjoy the sunrise at Dokdo.)
How would we ever come here at this hour?
That's right.
It's really not easy to watch the sunrise at Dokdo.
Right.
(Before the shining sun and the tranquil Dokdo, )
(everyone feels touched and falls silent in reverence.)
(The members can't take their eyes off it for a while.)
The silent sunrise of Dokdo that shone like a jewel.
(Sae Ho: The silent sunrise of Dokdo that shined like a jewel)
(It's time to head to Dokdo, )
(the final destination of the great journey.)
- It's coming up.
- Pull it up.
(They'll go to Dokdo via a Korea Coast Guard boat.)
Keep pulling.
They're pulling up the boat.
Are they pulling it?
Pull it up high.
Keep lifting it.
It's very high-tech.
Thank you.
(Boarding the boat)
Amazing.
(It's their first time going to Dokdo on a patrol boat.)
- This is a unique experience.
- Right.
Well done.
You all look better in person.
Thank you. Be healthy.
At this hour.
(They're also getting on the boat on the other side.)
It's all written at the front.
That's the setting.
(It's going down.)
It's like an amusement ride.
(It's fascinating.)
(They safely reach the sea.)
- Bye.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
- Bye!
- Bye.
(They don't forget to thank them.)
- This feels interesting.
- It's touching.
(The water is rougher than they thought.)
How did people come out to such a sea to fish in the Joseon era?
- I know.
- That's right.
It's amazing.
This is how it feels.
(They finally head to Dokdo.)
We're getting to go to Dokdo.
It feels weird.
This is amazing.
It's really incredible.
(Standing tall in the middle of the East Sea)
(Dokdo, territory of South Korea)
As dokdo grew closer,
the excitement inside me grew too.
(DinDin: As dokdo grew closer, the excitement inside me grew too.)
It makes you clench your fist.
(It's as if a sense of energy was rising within.)
(They can't take their eyes...)
(off Dokdo, our island.)
(They get splashed with water.)
Hey.
(Sae Ho, the biggest victim, is flustered.)
This...
(Laughing)
It feels like we came to do water sports.
The water suddenly came.
(Entering Dokdo isn't easy.)
(It's chaos at Jong Min's boat too.)
Dokdo... Gosh.
Goodness!
We look too ugly to go to Dokdo.
(They just keep shouting because of the fast speed.)
(I'm scared.)
- Dokdo...
- It's over there.
We're going to Dokdo on a boat.
Look at Dokdo.
(That's why you have to see Dokdo right now!)
(Trying his best to look at it.)
It's amazing.
(They can feel the waves with all their body.)
Goodness.
- Along the sea route southeast - Southeast
(Along the sea route southeast for Ulleung Island for 78km)
(No, 87K)
(They naturally sing at the thought of going to Dokdo.)
No matter how much they claim it as their own
(Dokdo is our land)
We circled it once.
(As they enjoy the scenery...)
- We circled it once.
- Already?
Yes.
(Dokdo)
(Dokdo is right in front of them.)
(A place that makes you...)
(just stare silently)
Taegeukgi.
(The Taegeukgi welcomes them first.)
(A paradise for seabirds...)
(and a habitat for countless plants and animals)
(We came to Korea's easternmost area, Dokdo.)
I really came here.
It's so beautiful.
It's like a sculpture.
Right.
My first visit to Dokdo.
Up close, it was even more beautiful and touching.
(Joon: Up close, it was even more beautiful and touching.)
- Thank you.
(The members finally set foot on Dokdo.)
Thank you.
- It's Dokdo.
- I know, right?
I just stepped on Dokdo.
It's Dokdo.
You have to write a diary today.
I will write a picture diary today.
(The 2 Days 1 Night team arrived on Dokdo.)
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Stay healthy.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
(They thank them and turn around.)
Have a good day.
- Stay healthy.
- Thank you.
- Professor!
- Welcome!
- What?
- Right.
(Welcome.)
When did you get here?
Of course, I should come.
Did you sleep on Dokdo?
- Right.
- Where did you come from?
I appeared suddenly again.
(He appeared on Ulleung Island yesterday.)
Where were you?
(He appears on Dokdo today.)
I disappear and appear. This isn't easy.
- First, to welcome you, - Yes.
- there's a gift.
- What is this?
A small gift...
- was prepared.
- What is this?
- Is it like a scarf?
- That's right.
It has the national flag.
- I want to wear it.
- Is it a scarf?
Yes.
- There are eared seals!
- There are eared seals.
- Right.
- The pattern of the Taegeukgi,
Dokdo, and eared seals.
(A scarf with the Taegeukgi, Dokdo, and eared seals)
Thank you.
You're welcome.
First of all, I'm so glad to have you guys here.
This place, Dokdo,
- is a natural monument.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- It's a natural monument.
Every corner...
is a hidden gem and a breathtaking sight.
It's like it was sculpted.
- It's like it was sculpted...
- It makes no sense.
By hand.
Right.
(A scenery that looks sculpted by someone)
- We arrived at the dock.
- Yes.
- This is Dongdo.
- Dongdo.
That's Seodo.
- Yes.
- This is Dongdo, and that's Seodo.
- That's Seodo.
- The sun rises like this.
(Dokdo is made up of two islands.)
(Seodo, Dongdo)
(Only Dongdo is open to the public at present.)
- I'll give you...
- Yes.
A great tour...
- I feel very reassured.
- around this place.
- All right.
- I'm excited.
When we came here on our own last time,
we just went up there,
- took a look, and came down.
- Yes.
Now we're going to take a tour with explanations.
How far up did you go then?
- Over there.
- We went up there.
- Up there.
- Up to the Mangyangdae Pavilion.
- Yes.
- That's right.
We went to that spot.
- Today, - Yes.
We'll head even higher.
- Really?
- We'll go to the top.
I'll take you...
- on a detailed tour...
- I'd love that. We have no time.
- Yes. Let's hurry.
- of Dokdo today.
Let's slowly start moving.
- Okay.
- This is great.
(The unprecedented Dokdo tour begins now.)
First of all, when you look here,
- the first thing we see...
- Dokdoisabu-gil.
Yesterday, I...
- You mentioned it yesterday.
- Yes.
- This...
- Dokdoisabu-gil?
Since Dokdo is Korea's territory,
it would have an address.
- Right.
- Yes. So,
it's Ulleung-gun, North Gyeongsang Province.
- It's also Ulleung-eup.
- Ulleung-eup.
Then, for Dongdo, it's Dokdoisabu-gil.
Dokdoisabu-gil.
(In the 13th year of King Jijeung, )
(Yisabu made a lion out of wood and compelled the people...)
(of Usanguk to surrender. In "History of the Three Kingdoms")
(General Yisabu made Ulleung Island and Dokdo our land.)
(The address took his name in Dongdo.)
Then, on Seodo, we talked about it yesterday...
- An Yong Bok.
- Dokdoanyongbok-gil.
Let us listen until the end.
- That's right.
- Who doesn't know?
Get a tutor if you want to do that.
- Stop showing off.
I'm sorry.
- Who doesn't know?
- Stop showing off.
I'm sorry.
- Right.
- Yes.
Where is Dokdoanyongbok-gil?
- That way.
- That's Seodo.
- Right.
There's a sign over there.
- The blue one.
(Seodo's road name address: Dokdoanyongbok-gil)
(An Yong Bok said to the Japanese, )
("Songdo is Jasando and our land. Why set foot on our land?")
("Veritable Records of King Sukjong")
(An Yong Bok, the civilian diplomat...)
(that got Japan's confirmation that Dokdo is Korean territory)
(To preserve the hearts of the two great men...)
(who protected Dokdo, )
(Dokdo's new addresses were made in 2008...)
(based on a citizen's proposal.)
This is where many people take photos...
when they come to Dokdo.
It will be meaningful to take one together.
- Along with Professor Seo.
- Right.
There's someone who takes good photos here.
Director Joo! He'll take it for us.
I'll take the photo. One, two, three.
(A photo at Dokdoisabu-gil)
Gosh, it's amazing back here.
It's beautiful.
The water is so clear!
Gosh.
(The clear sea stops them.)
- Gosh, the water is so clear.
- Gosh.
I think it's the clearest sea I've seen in our country.
The color of the waves are completely different.
(Dokdo's sea is especially blue.)
And here!
- We learned about Jeju's haenyeos.
- Right.
Who was the one who called out "cool haenyeo?"
- Here.
- "Cool haenyeo!"
Right.
(Answer: Jeju haenyeo)
(He called out a cool answer yesterday.)
Do you see a flat rock...
- right over there?
- Yes.
The Jeju haenyeos...
- The cool haenyeos?
- Yes. They rested there.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Is it flat?
Seaweed was dried up there as well.
So that is called the Haenyeo Rock.
- The Haenyeo Rock.
- Yes.
(Jeju's haenyeos worked for the fishing industry around Dokdo.)
(This is a strong piece of evidence...)
(that a Korean citizen has made economical activities in Dokdo.)
(Dokdo consists of many rocks besides the Haenyeo Rock.)
(The Sea Lion Rock where eared seals would've jumped around)
(Small Sea Lion Rock, Big Sea Lion Rock)
(Seaweed Rock)
(Three Brothers Cave Rock, Candlestick Rock)
(Battleship Rock, Neopdeok Rock, Goose Barnacle Rock, )
(Elephant Rock, Chicken Rock, Fan Rock, Duck Rock, Face Rock)
(All of the rocks were named with Korean native words.)
Learning the names of the rocks...
- is part of the fun...
- Right.
Of coming to Dokdo.
Gosh. Look here.
- This is another...
- "The easternmost point of Korea."
amazing spot.
- Is this it?
- Yes.
The view here is great.
- If you look here, - The view.
The whole of Seodo can be seen, right?
(The stone tablet with Seodo in the background)
What does it say here?
- "The easternmost point of Korea."
Right.
(The easternmost point of Korea)
We've berthed...
- at Dongdo, right?
- Right.
To celebrate the construction...
of the berthing facility,
- this stone tablet was made.
- Right.
The font of "the easternmost point of Korea..."
is the handwriting of former president, Kim Young Sam.
- Really?
- The font of this?
- Yes.
- I see.
"The easternmost point of Korea."
The berthing facility of Dokdo has been built...
and with President Kim Young Sam's writing,
the stone table that clearly states that Dokdo is Korean territory...
was revealed today through an opening ceremony.
The government strongly claims...
that the construction of the berthing facility...
is a valid exercise...
of territorial sovereignty and jurisdiction.
- The will of the country...
- Right.
Was revealed...
- by this stone tablet.
- Right.
- It looks amazing here.
- The view here is amazing.
- Dokdoisabu-gil mentioned earlier.
Tourists come here...
- and take many photos here.
- Right.
- The easternmost point of Korea.
- Here?
(We can't miss out on photos.)
One, two, three.
(A photo at the easternmost point of Korea)
Gosh, the water is so clear.
(Gasping)
Look! There are fish!
- There were a lot of fish.
- Of course.
- There are a lot of fish here.
- Right.
- Surely.
You can see them, right?
(The fish greet them in the clear sea with their nice colors.)
The water is so clear.
It looks like the water of a swimming pool.
How is it so clear?
It can't be compared with another place.
- It's unrivaled in how clear it is.
- Right.
It looks beautiful here!
(A scenery that must be captured by a camera)
I want to try going in the cave.
It's up to right here.
This is how far a regular tourist can visit.
- It ends here.
- Right.
- Just for today, - Gosh.
We were granted permission to go further in.
For the members of the show.
Is this area usually blocked?
Yes.
We were granted official permission to move further in.
Let's go!
- We're going to the highest spot.
- Right.
(This shoot was done with the aid of the related organization.)
Look to your left and right.
We will be seeing Seodo from the bottom...
- and from the top.
- I think it will feel different.
There's a massive difference.
There are so many of these flowers. What are these?
(This flower)
(I am called the coastal moss-like stonecrop.)
(Dokdo is a beautiful habitat of wild flowers.)
Gosh, check out the color of the flowers.
(Panting)
Can it be seen through the screen?
(Capturing the color of the wild flowers)
(Se Yoon is curious about how Seodo looks from up top.)
It's great to see you, Seodo.
Is it mugwort? I guess it's not.
No.
We have climbed up a lot.
We have just a bit more left.
Are we almost there?
So we're climbing up to the top over there.
Right.
We still have a long way to go.
This is one of the toughest courses.
Don't push me.
(The stairs become steeper.)
Gosh, the stairs are very steep.
(While walking facing forward, )
(if you turn around...)
Gosh, this is insane.
Gosh, it feels different.
It's already beautiful from this high up.
(A new sea view appears.)
Gosh, it's so clean.
The water is so clean.
It must be because the water was unharmed,
but the water is really clean.
I think the East Sea is the most beautiful.
- Right.
(The bottom of the clear sea can be seen.)
This is Moon Se Yoon looking at the Haenyeo Rock.
You look like an eared seal.
(You look like an eared seal.)
- I really want to see eared seals.
- Right.
They would've played around there.
It feels upsetting as they were announced extinct.
Too many of them were killed.
How bad was it for them to become extinct?
Gosh.
(Dokdo was also called Gajido as there were many eared seals.)
(Then eared seals became extinct due to...)
(Japan's reckless capture for their leather and oil.)
(Their hearts feel heavy as they can not be seen again.)
They were completely annihilated.
Right.
Let's move to the first spot.
- Right.
- Let's go.
We have just a bit more left.
(Se Yoon's camera)
It was quite exhausting to come up here,
but it didn't feel that way.
It must be because we got to see many different views.
- Stick to the left.
- Gosh.
Gosh!
- Gosh!
- It's spectacular.
- It's amazing.
- It's thrilling.
Take a look.
- All the way down there.
- This is crazy.
- Gosh!
- It's amazing.
- Right by the cliff.
- This is a spectacular sight.
This doesn't make sense.
This was formed by nature.
Right.
We managed to make it here...
- when the sun is shining this way.
- Right.
Talk about perfect timing.
(They stay for a while to enjoy the view.)
- Gosh.
- It's beautiful.
Right.
- Let's move now.
- Right.
Let's move to the first destination.
This is the first thing that I feel after coming here.
- The Taegeukgi is right there.
- Right.
(The Taegeukgi is guarding the easternmost point of Korea.)
It just feels overwhelming...
- Gosh.
- when you come here.
It feels emotional.
(Let's head toward the treasure that lies beyond the Taegeukgi.)
It's Dokdo!
"Dokdo" is written on it, right?
(The place with the stone tablet of Dokdo)
This is the first spot...
that I will introduce.
- It's the Mangyangdae Pavilion.
- Mangyangdae Pavilion.
- "Mang" means to look.
- To look.
"Yang" means vast sea.
A place where you can look at the vast sea.
- It's really nice.
- Right.
As it's Mangyangdae Pavilion,
You'll be amazed at how our sea, the East Sea, looks...
- if you go behind this.
- I see.
(What kind of sight awaits them?)
- My goodness.
Even the sunlight is helping us today.
- It's endless.
- Right.
My goodness.
This is a truly vast ocean.
The ocean is huge.
(The endless sea stretches out before their eyes.)
(East Sea)
As you all know,
- this is the East Sea.
- Yes. The East Sea.
These days, the name "East Sea" is...
often used interchangeably.
And a lot of maps have changed the name to "East Sea."
We must build on this momentum...
and keep working hard to make...
more changes.
This is truly the best.
- It's fascinating.
- The easternmost part of Korea.
(The East Sea seen from beneath Taegeukgi)
This is amazing.
- I'm getting emotional.
- I know.
It feels strange. It's somewhat touching.
Of course.
Because of the things we've heard since childhood.
Dokdo, a lonely island that has long protected...
this vast sea.
(Dokdo, a lonely island that has long protected this vast sea)
It will be backlit.
Good.
One, two, three.
(A photo in front of the East Sea at Mangyangdae Pavilion)
- We have one place left now.
- Okay.
I'm really grateful.
My goodness.
(Jong Min's camera)
You probably haven't seen this view a lot before.
This is the view.
Such a beautiful view
(A view that was probably intended)
(Jong Min's camera)
You must've been surprised.
(We will keep Se Yoon's view to ourselves.)
We've reached the top...
- of Dongdo now.
- Yes. We're here.
(Team 2 Days 1 Night has already reached the top.)
My goodness.
We are starting to see some letters.
- Korea?
- Yes.
What's the letter below it?
- Below it...
- Yes.
Just tell me the initial, and I'll try to guess.
I must say it starts with a T.
Korean Territory?
- It says Korean Territory.
- Korean Territory.
Korean Territory. Yes.
(A rock with the letters "Korean Territory" written on it)
Everyone, yesterday,
we talked about the Dokdo Volunteer Garrison.
- We did, right?
- Yes.
It's an important group...
that protected Dokdo and is an integral part...
of Dokdo's history.
(During the Korean War)
During the Korean War,
we couldn't afford to take care of this island.
- Of course not.
- Japan took advantage of that...
and came here to drive stakes.
(Japan, taking advantage of the war, landed on Dokdo without permission.)
(They installed Japanese territorial markers on Dokdo...)
(and expelled Korean fishermen.)
(It made the young people of Ulleung Island...)
(volunteer to take action.)
(Dokdo Volunteer Garrison)
(A sign carved to protect Dokdo, )
(indicating that Dokdo is Korean territory)
There's one date I'd like you to remember...
regarding Dokdo.
It's November 21, 1954.
Here's what happened.
Three Japanese patrol boats...
and a patrol aircraft attempted to enter Dokdo,
but the Dokdo Volunteer Garrison repelled them.
- They fought back?
- Yes.
The Dokdo Volunteer Garrison was truly amazing.
- They faced harsh conditions...
- Right.
And had no weapons.
But they came up with a brilliant strategy.
They wanted to look like...
they were armed with good weapons from a distance.
They wanted to look strong.
That's right.
They painted some logs black...
to make them look like cannons from a distance.
(The conditions were so harsh that camouflage tactics had to be used.)
They even used such a clever strategy.
The Dokdo Volunteer Garrison...
played a crucial role in protecting Dokdo.
(The great men risked their lives to protect Dokdo.)
We all felt the same way.
(Kim Yeong Bok, a member of the Dokdo Volunteer Garrison)
Even though I was injured too,
but all those injured felt the same way.
That Dokdo was our territory.
(A sign carved into a rock with the sole purpose...)
(of protecting our land)
If we hadn't...
- If we hadn't stopped them...
- stopped them...
or been on the island at that time, they might have occupied the land.
- I don't even want to imagine it.
- I know.
(Their hearts are filled with reverence before the sign.)
All right. So, we saw the rock that says "Korean Territory."
This way. Let's go.
(And other people who protected Dokdo)
It says "Republic of Korea" here, right?
- Yes.
- This is a monument.
This is where we stand in solemn reverence at the top of Dongdo.
A monument stands here...
for the police officers...
who died protecting Dokdo.
- While carrying out their duty?
- Yes.
It's important that the police have protected this place for so long,
hoping that future generations...
will remember it.
- I believe that's what's important.
- Right.
Now that we're here,
I'd like us to take a moment to pay a silent tribute.
- Come here.
- Oh, right here.
There are two people my age here.
Attention.
Pay a silent tribute.
(At the summit of Dokdo, )
(we met heroes we never knew existed.)
(I felt a sense of reverence before the monument.)
(Even now, the work to protect Dokdo continues.)
(I will remember the sacrifices made to protect Dokdo.)
At ease.
This is why we came all the way here.
There's one more place to go.
- Really?
- Yes. There's something left.
- There's nowhere to go from here.
- Right.
I think we're at the top.
(They just follow Professor Seo.)
- My goodness.
- Gosh, what's that?
My gosh.
(What awaits Team 2 Days 1 Night is...)
Taegeukgi.
My goodness. Look at this.
- It looks so cool.
- At the top of Dongdo,
there's Taegeukgi.
There's no denying this.
- Of course not.
- This is game over.
Look right behind you. It's the lighthouse.
- It's a lighthouse.
- Yes.
The sea was so beautiful that I didn't even look up.
One of the lighthouse's most important roles is...
- To prevent getting lost.
- Exactly.
It serves to guide boats...
and protect fishermen...
on the sea, right?
The fact that we have such a lighthouse...
right on this island...
proves that Dokdo is...
Korean territory.
- That's right.
- Sure.
It goes without saying.
(Another piece of evidence that Dokdo is Korean territory)
(On our way to the summit of Dokdo, )
(we have encountered...)
(countless great people.)
(Just to protect this lonely island, )
(countless people are...)
(still working hard.)
(From the KBS documentary, "Three Days")
(72 Hours on the Coast Guard's Sambongho to Protect Dokdo)
How does Dokdo look from the sky?
I think it's a precious, beautiful, youngest island...
of our country,
worth our effort to protect.
(Dokdo, our precious land, protected by so many people)
How was it looking around Dokdo with me today?
- It was a valuable experience, - I see.
Making me realize that this is our land.
How nice. How did you feel?
It was such an honor...
to be here as a citizen of our country.
And I feel like I learned so much from you,
so I want to express my gratitude.
Every time I see Dokdo, the word "wonder" comes to mind.
It's not just beautiful.
There are no words to describe its beauty.
- It's wonderful.
- Yes.
I hope many Koreans will come and see Dokdo.
That's right.
- Did you see the boat coming in?
- Yes.
- They're Korean tourists.
I hope our tourists will visit often...
- That's right.
- so we can all work together...
to revitalize tourism in Ulleung Island and Dokdo.
(Everyone...)
(who visits this island...)
(harbors the thought that flutters...)
(from the moment they set foot on Dokdo.)
(An island with blue seas...)
(and breathtaking scenery)
(Pristine nature)
(And)
(The first place to meet the morning on the Korean Peninsula)
(Everywhere you look is beautiful, )
(and at times, it makes you sad.)
(The colorful story of Dokdo)
(You'll love this island even more if you visit in person.)
The easternmost point of the Republic of Korea!
Our beautiful land!
Visit...
Dokdo!
- 2 Days 1 Night!
- 1 Night!
(2 Days 1 Night)
- Visit Dokdo!
- Dokdo is our land
(The end of Our Dokdo Notes)
(Next episode)
(The game has begun.)
(A survival game suddenly begins.)
That's pretty.
(It was...)
(a happy autumn picnic.)
It's not this kind of program.
(Sit. Don't sit.)
(Spin the magazine. Shoot as is.)
(Every choice determines your fate.)
(Who will be the final survivor?)
(See you next week.)