(Where refreshing citrons grow close to the sea)
(Today's starting point is Goheung.)
What is this?
Are we going to an island today?
Are we going to an island?
(Laughing)
- It's such a lovely day.
- Are we going to an island?
- Hello.
- This is nice.
Hello. The weather's lovely today.
- It's such a nice day.
- What incredible weather.
- It's amazing.
- Everyone.
Let's start with some applause.
- Yes.
- Let's applaud.
(Why are they suddenly clapping?)
- What for?
- What's going on?
- Sae Ho's hair got quite long.
- Yes, I grew it out.
In case he wins the Grand Award,
- he's keeping it long.
- What are you saying?
- Applause.
- No.
- Congratulations.
- Congratulations in advance.
No. It's not that at all.
For the Cho Sae Ho Grand Award Project,
- he's keeping his hair long.
- No.
I wanted to try a different hairstyle...
He permed it too.
- Jong Min, congratulations.
- Yes.
What for?
For growing older? Is that it?
You're the oldest of the day.
(Kim Jong Min, today's oldest member)
I'm a Young Forty.
- You're an Old Forty.
- Old Forty.
You're totally a Young Forty.
(Drawing the line)
I saw this look online.
- Se Yoon's look today...
- What?
A man with a bulging belly. I saw a guy just like him.
Sae Ho's not a Young Forty, though.
- Why not?
- What's a Young Forty?
- A copycat?
- Someone...
who cluelessly copies the fashion.
- Sae Ho has his own unique style.
- He does.
He's an exception.
(Is impressed)
- Sae Ho...
- You get better each week.
He's an exception.
- Really?
- Good for you.
Jong Min's an exception too.
- Why?
- Jong Min...
has zero sense of fashion.
He doesn't copy anything.
I just put on anything that fits me.
But you have to think carefully about this.
You'll be a Young Forty soon.
- Hey, DinDin.
- You know?
- No.
- He'll turn 40 soon.
Hey, I still have five years to go!
And he likes following trends.
- He likes following trends.
- Joon is a Young Forty.
Right. I'm a Young Forty.
But what does that mean? Is that a good thing?
- It's a good thing.
- Everyone.
- It was a long journey here, right?
- Goheung!
- All right.
- Are we going to an island?
Our destination today is located...
on the far edge of South Jeolla Province.
It's the number one spot known for citron.
- Right.
- This place is famous for citron.
A culinary heartland...
- for the southern provinces.
- A culinary heartland.
(A culinary heartland, full of tasty food)
(The edge of the southern sea...)
(embraces countless islands and the open ocean.)
It's Goheung in South Jeolla Province.
Goheung!
- Goheung!
- Goheung.
- I love it here.
- Goheung is famous for citron...
- Eels.
- as well as food.
- We're in Jeolla Province.
- This province is famous for it.
As we're in Goheung...
where citron and good food are at their peak,
- Yes. I'm hungry.
- we prepared an amazing dinner...
that will definitely satisfy your expectations.
- Really?
- My gosh.
(A fantastic feast...)
(with Korean beef from Citron Valley)
(Well, that was the plan.)
- Just a while ago, - Yes?
- the meal thief, - What?
- Hungry Lupin, - Okay.
- stole your entire dinner.
- Hungry Lupin?
(What on earth is he talking about?)
It was you, right?
- Was it you?
- What's going on?
- Was it you? Who was it?
- Who was it?
(1 hour ago)
(7:01am)
- Hello.
How come I don't see any of our members' cars?
What's this? Where am I going?
I can just go by myself?
(Where's Seon Ho going?)
What's this?
What on earth is going on? You're making me anxious.
- What's all this?
- So...
(6 cards are placed in front of him.)
There are six cards here.
One of the cards...
will say Hungry Lupin.
You'll randomly draw a card...
to assign the role of Hungry Lupin.
- Why am I going alone?
- What's this?
What? I'm going there alone?
Wait. Where am I going?
What are we doing?
(They came earlier than usual to pick Hungry Lupin.)
(2 Days 1 Night)
Choose carefully.
- Carefully?
- Yes, carefully.
Okay.
- That's the card you drew.
- Yes.
(They pick a card after much deliberation.)
What's this?
You've been chosen as Hungry Lupin...
who stole the members' dinner.
What?
(Trailing off)
Why...
Is this a good card or a bad card?
- It's 1 of us.
- So 1 of us...
is Hungry Lupin now, right?
That's right. Hungry Lupin.
- It's 5 versus 1.
- Yes.
(Someone among them stole their dinner.)
(Who is Hungry Lupin?)
If I try to survive, I'll die. But if I try to die, I'll survive.
Let me do my best to fool them.
From now on, you must work to arrest...
Hungry Lupin who stole your dinner...
and get your dinner back.
- We have the upper hand here.
- Gosh, we have the upper hand.
- We know a lot about each other.
- Yes.
The 6 of them must figure out which 1 of them is Hungry Lupin...
while not knowing each other's identity.
(Voted as the culprit)
If they successfully arrest Hungry Lupin...
(Meal acquired)
the five of them except for Hungry Lupin will get to eat.
(Voted as the culprit)
(Citizen)
If they fail to arrest Hungry Lupin...
(Meal acquired)
Hungry Lupin will have dinner...
all to himself.
Who will get to have dinner tonight?
- All right.
- How can we guess who it is?
Every time you complete the group mission throughout today,
you'll be given a hint about Hungry Lupin.
- That's good.
- We'll figure out who it is then.
- Then Hungry Lupin...
- Yes.
Will try to make mistakes...
- to prevent us from getting a hint.
- Of course.
- Probably.
- My gosh.
It's you.
- What was that? What?
- Seriously.
- That sounded really awkward.
- My gosh.
- I have my own reasoning.
- Really?
- Hey.
- It's you.
That's how an entertainer with 20 years of experience reacts?
- I have 25 years of experience.
- It's 25 years?
Yes. I have 25 years of experience.
- You're on the suspect list now.
- All right.
Are we going to start now?
- Yes. Starting now...
- What? DinDin.
- What was that, DinDin?
- You're acting weird.
- You're acting weird, DinDin.
- No. I was just asking.
You're acting weird.
Hey, you sounded so awkward.
Honestly, things have been weird for me every day.
Seriously. I'm having a tough time.
- Joon is acting weird too.
- My gosh.
It's not me. I swear.
Typically, the one who easily suspects people...
- turns out to be the culprit.
- Right.
Right.
- What?
However, there's a way for everyone including Hungry Lupin...
to enjoy dinner together.
- Okay. This is the best option.
- I like that.
If you complete all of the three missions,
everyone will get to have a filling dinner.
Hungry Lupin has two options.
(Mission 1, Mission 2, Mission 3: Success)
He can help complete all three group missions,
so they can all have dinner together.
(Voted as the culprit)
Or he could make them fail to catch Hungry Lupin...
and eat dinner by himself.
(Make them fail to catch him and eat dinner by himself.)
- That's good. We can all eat.
- Yes.
But Hungry Lupin will mess up on purpose.
- He wouldn't do that.
- Why?
The chance of completing all three missions is low.
- But still.
- Here's what I think.
- For the first mission, - If we try hard...
Hungry Lupin will do his best...
- just in case.
- Right.
But if he thinks it won't go well for him,
he'll mess up the second mission.
What's important is that we'll get hints.
But let's say we fail the mission.
- Is it you?
- It's not me.
- Jong Min, your acting is good.
- It's not me!
(It's not me!)
You're rarely this energetic during the opening segment.
Why are you so chatty today?
- I'm just working hard.
- Why all of a sudden?
- Why around this time of the year?
- I'm just working hard.
- What's going on with you?
- Why do you work hard...
- only in the second half?
- He starts working hard...
- starting November.
- This is an important period.
- Is there a reason?
- Why...
I must work hard in November.
He works hard for two months.
This is the last chance...
to get more points for the awards ceremony.
Guys, this is the time.
- Now?
- All right.
- Joon, you're not saying anything.
- Right now...
- What?
- What was that?
What kind of reaction was that?
I've always been like this.
- Can we just casually ask him?
- Yes.
- Are you Hungry Lupin, Joon?
- Gosh, you... I'm not.
- "You are not?"
- Gosh.
Do you know the worst part about me...
being the culprit in a game like this?
- I can't lie for the life of me.
- Right.
- I know.
- It would've been obvious already.
- It's obvious now.
- It's obvious.
- Joon.
- My gosh. Listen.
It's not me. Let's just move on. I don't want to be in the spotlight.
Joon!
- Joon wants us to move on.
- Gosh, it's really not me.
- He wants us to move on.
- It's not me. Stop suspecting me.
He's acting odd.
- We might find him quite easily.
- Who is it?
No. It's really not me.
- We believe Hungry Lupin is...
- Okay.
- Joon.
- Yes.
- We'll arrest him now.
- It will end at 8:35am.
- I don't want dinner now.
- Let's perform at an event.
- Let's end it now.
- Yes.
(From this moment on, )
(Hungry Lupin...)
(will lie during games, )
(meals, )
(and even interviews.)
(He will lie the entire time.)
(One of them is lying. Who is Hungry Lupin?)
I'll never get caught.
Catch me if you can.
(Stay tuned!)
Let's begin your first group mission now.
The mission you will try here is called...
Hit the Drum, Head, and Belly...
While Swaying the Hips.
- It's been trending these days.
- Yes.
- I saw it too.
- Doesn't it go like this?
- It's one of the short-form videos.
- It's this.
In the video, they can't stop swaying their hips.
(Let's break up.)
(Is it because I can't stop swaying my hips?)
(Let me go clubbing since she broke up with me.)
I'm sorry. But we'll look it up ourselves.
We'll look it up.
All right. Set it up, please.
(Bring in the props.)
- Could you move back a bit?
- Gosh, that reminds me of Nanta.
- Yes.
- What's that?
(They bring in drums after drums.)
(What kind of mission awaits them?)
- Stop that.
- All right.
The rule is simple.
You have to sway your hips on the beat.
Then follow the action commands I give out...
such as hit the drum, head, and belly.
- Do them in the correct order.
- Hit the belly?
- Whose belly?
- The belly?
- That's confusing.
- All right.
I'll go over the action commands.
When I say, "hit the drum,"
use the stick to hit the drum.
Hit the drum.
When I say, "hit the head," hit your own head...
with the toy hammer.
- Hit the drum. Hit the head.
- Right.
- Okay.
- Hit the drum. Hit the head.
What's next?
- When I say, "Hit the belly,"
- The belly.
Se Yoon, raise both of your hands.
- Raise my hands?
- I see.
Those who are next to Se Yoon must hit his belly.
Okay. Like this?
- That's a hard one.
- The rest of you...
- can hit your own belly.
- With the toy hammer.
(The rest of them will hit their own belly.)
Four random action commands will make up one set.
If you successfully execute five sets in a row,
- your mission would be completed.
- What a pity.
I'll give you three chances.
Hold on. If that's the rule,
we should place people who are quick...
at picking up these commands next to Se Yoon.
- By the way, - Of course.
- Can we switch places?
- here's what we know from this.
It's that I'm not Hungry Lupin.
- Why?
- It'd be so obvious for me.
I need to raise my hands for the last action command.
- No.
- You could get confused.
Hit the drum. Hit the head. And hit the belly.
Hooray. You could mess it up like this.
Right.
(In other words, it will be easy for Hungry Lupin to mess it up.)
- Do you want to practice?
- Let's practice.
- Hit the drum.
- Bam.
- Hit the head.
- What was that?
- Right. I got confused.
(He messed up even during the practice round?)
- I got confused. It's not me.
- It's not even that confusing.
I'm sorry. Let me try again.
- How can this be confusing?
- "This..."
(Is Sae Ho Hungry Lupin?)
- Okay. Let's try again.
- Hit the drum and the head.
Hit the head. Bam.
- You said it wasn't confusing.
- One more time.
Hit the head. Bam.
So that's how it goes.
All right. You must dance at the same time.
- Go.
- How do I sway my hips?
- Like this? Or like this?
- Like this.
One, two.
- Is that how you'll sway your hips?
- Of course.
He's going to sway his hips like this.
- Isn't that too fast?
- That's too fast.
Why is he working so hard in November?
- One, two, three, four.
- Two, three.
Hit the drum, hit the drum, hit the belly, and hit the belly.
- Hit the drum, hit the drum, - Hit the drum, hit the drum,
- hit the belly, and hit the belly.
- That's the rule.
- Like this.
- That's too easy.
- That's so confusing.
- Come on. You said it was easy.
- Right?
Come here, Jong Min. Seon Ho, you go over there.
- He's good at this.
- It got confusing with the hips.
- All right.
- It's so easy.
- Seon Ho is good at this.
- You got it now, right?
Let's have one more practice round.
Start with the left side.
- One, two, three, four.
Hit the drum, hit the head, hit the drum, and hit the head.
- Why...
- What was that?
One, two, three, four.
Hit the drum, hit the head, hit the drum, and hit the head.
- Okay.
- Hit the drum. Hit the head.
- Like this.
- Okay.
(Suspecting him)
- This is confusing.
- Okay.
- Jong Min is acting weird.
- No, it's really confusing.
- It's confusing with four commands.
- He's acting weird.
- This is so weird.
- Right?
- I'm saying you're acting weird.
- Me?
How interesting.
Because Jong Min is Hungry Lupin,
he'll pretend to struggle from the get-go.
(Is he pretending to struggle?)
Hey, don't get nervous.
The judges might get it wrong too.
But you should feel a bit nervous.
- Let's do one last practice round.
- Okay.
Jong Min, don't be distracted.
- It's not that hard.
I'm sorry.
One, two, three, four.
- Left side.
(Left side)
Left side.
Hit the drum, hit the drum, hit the head, and hit the drum.
(Hit the drum, hit the drum, hit the head, and hit the drum.)
To one side.
- Left side.
- One side?
Hit the head, hit the drum, hit the drum, and hit the head.
- Left side.
- Someone got it wrong.
Someone got it wrong.
- Who is it?
- Who got it wrong?
Jong Min got it wrong.
- No, it wasn't me.
- He...
It was hit the head, hit the drum, hit the drum, and hit the head.
- But he hit the drum at the end.
- Wait.
Seon Ho skipped one command.
See?
- Why did you skip it?
- My gosh.
(A new suspect shows up.)
- He kept suspecting us.
- No.
(Hit the head, hit the drum, hit the drum, and hit the head.)
(It was a mess.)
My gosh. I really got confused.
Something feels very awkward about him.
I think even a kindergartener can follow the commands.
I mean, he's young too. How could he get this wrong?
How is this confusing?
(I found you, Hungry Lupin.)
- How is this confusing?
- Are you Hungry Lupin?
No.
All right, everyone. Let's try it.
- Gosh.
- It's so confusing.
- Seriously. Seon Ho.
- This isn't going to work.
You'll be sorry.
Let's begin.
- One, two, three, four.
- This one will count, right?
Left side.
(Will they succeed or fail? What will Hungry Lupin decide?)
Hit the head, hit the drum, hit the head, and hit the drum.
Hit the head, hit the drum...
- The command was hit the head.
- What?
Why did you get this wrong?
- What was that, Jong Min?
- Sorry. Let me try again.
- How many times must we redo it?
- I suddenly forgot.
- Are you Hungry Lupin?
- No. Forget about Hungry Lupin.
You must be Hungry Lupin.
- Hey. No.
- How could you get this wrong?
I was thinking about something else completely.
- Why were you distracted?
Let me say something. We should exclude Jong Min...
from the suspect list.
He's not capable of playing games like this.
- Right.
- Yes.
(Were you really distracted?)
I really didn't get how to play it. It was such a difficult game.
(Dodging the question with a smile)
This is your second try.
- You failed the first try.
- How many tries do we have left?
- Three.
- You must succeed in three tries.
- Okay.
I think we can pull this off. Let's focus and finish it.
- Yes. Let's do it.
- Here it goes.
One, two, three, four.
(Left side)
Left side.
- Left side.
Hit the head, hit the drum, hit the head, and hit the drum.
(They succeed with the 1st set.)
Hit the belly, hit the belly, hit the drum, and hit the head.
(They succeed with the 2nd set.)
Hit the drum, hit the belly, hit the drum, and hit the head.
(They succeed with the 3rd set.)
Hit the head, hit the drum, hit the belly, and hit the head.
- Wrong!
- Who was it?
- It's him.
- My gosh.
- I confused the drum and the head.
- Did you also get it wrong?
Someone got it wrong. No, it was Seon Ho.
- It was Seon Ho and Jong Min.
- My gosh!
You got it wrong too.
- Hey.
- You...
- You're Hungry Lupin, right?
I'm bad at this. But you're not.
- What a great sight.
- I think Jong Min is...
- Jong Min is struggling for real.
- Right.
(Hit the head, hit the drum, hit the belly, and hit the head.)
(Hit the head and hit the drum: Correct)
(Hit the belly, and hit the head: Wrong)
(Jong Min was hanging in there, but messed up the last two.)
Jong Min was pretty good in this round.
Right?
Usually, he can't execute more than one command.
But you made it far this time.
- I was super focused. I'm serious.
- Yes.
- I can see that he was focused.
- Right.
- I was so focused.
- Jong Min tried his best.
- He did his best.
- So it's okay.
- But Seon Ho...
- What were you thinking?
- I confused the drum and the head.
- Why?
(Hit the head, hit the drum, hit the belly, and hit the head.)
(Wrong)
(Was he not even trying to get it right?)
- You have to be Hungry Lupin.
- If he's not Hungry Lupin,
- Seon Ho...
- I'll be so disappointed.
I'm worried about what will happen to him in ten years.
(DinDin is serious.)
I'm sure even the viewers...
will be understanding when Seon Ho and Jong Min mess up.
- They've been watching these two.
- That's true.
We don't even need to suspect them.
We must exclude them. They can't be Hungry Lupin.
I think the one who tries to use this situation must be Hungry Lupin.
That person must be Hungry Lupin.
How's it going for you, Joon? Good?
My gosh, I'm working hard.
You got two helpers.
It's written all over his face. I can see it on Joon's face.
"This is too much."
"Why did I draw that card?"
"How can I pretend not to be it?" His face screams Hungry Lupin.
- Is it going as planned?
- Joon.
You're happy because things are going your way.
You're trying to frame me, but I got all of them right.
Hungry Lupin is trying to do his best.
Because Jong Min and Seon Ho keep messing up,
Hungry Lupin must secretly be satisfied.
All right. This is your last try.
This is our last try. It's our third one.
The one who messes up on purpose now...
could be Hungry Lupin in my opinion.
Let's keep an eye on Joon.
- Let's begin.
- Let's do it. Let's go.
One, two, three, four.
Left side.
My gosh. Should I start acting again?
Let me do my best to fool them.
- Left side.
Hit the head, hit the drum, hit the head, and hit the head.
- Hit the head, hit the drum, - Hit the head, hit the drum,
- hit the head, and hit the head.
(Wrong)
Jong Min is struggling a lot.
(Is it Seon Ho again?)
- It's DinDin.
- What?
Come on!
(An unexpected culprit)
- No. I wasn't the only one.
- Who was it?
- I wasn't the only one.
- Raise your hand.
- Joon messed up too.
- Seon Ho too.
See? Everyone got it wrong. Why are you blaming only me?
- What? Only we got it right?
- Seon Ho.
Did you mess up again?
- Did you mess up again?
This is just crazy.
(And these two...)
You were doing well.
Why did you two mess up on the last try?
- On the last try.
- All of a sudden.
- We all know Jong Min is a fool.
- Jong Min messed up too?
- But why did you two mess up too?
- Hey.
I'm just stupid. But why did you two mess up?
- Why did you mess up?
- All of a sudden.
- We all know Jong Min is a fool.
- Why did you mess up?
- But why did you two mess up too?
This is our last try. It's our third one.
(DinDin expected Hungry Lupin...)
(to mess up on purpose in the last round.)
- Why did you mess up?
- It got harder.
It was hard.
- It suddenly got harder.
- Why was that hard?
- Your ears are getting red.
- What?
- It was a hard one.
- No. Joon must be it.
- I messed up because it was hard.
You messed up every single time.
- You don't deserve to suspect us.
- You stay out of this. Seriously.
How can we catch Hungry Lupin when we are all bad at this game?
It was hard. I'm serious.
This is the set of commands you messed up.
Hit the head, hit the drum, hit the head, and hit the head.
- Try it. Why is that hard?
- Hit the head...
What was it? Say it again?
- His pronunciation...
- I thought he said, "belly."
- Come on.
- Right? His pronunciation...
"Hit the head, hit the drum,"
"hit the dad, and hit the bed."
- That's what he said.
- No way.
- On the last try? All of a sudden?
- It did sound off.
- I couldn't hear him well.
- It did sound off. I'm serious.
You couldn't hear him at the end when you heard him well before?
I lowered my guard, I guess.
- You were great. Why mess up now?
- Exactly.
- You two were doing well.
- Why did you mess up?
They were great and didn't get any command wrong.
Why did DinDin mess up in the last round?
So one of us is acting right now. That's for sure.
But in my opinion,
Hungry Lupin didn't mess up at all during this game.
- He actually did well?
- Not even once.
- He was focused.
- Did you get anything wrong?
I didn't get anything wrong.
- But I'm not Hungry Lupin.
- What?
- I'm serious.
- So...
- He just excluded himself.
I'm serious. I did my best.
- How come you didn't mess up?
- Basically...
- He's suspected for not messing up.
(Suspecting the one who didn't mess up)
This is weird.
Hungry Lupin...
needs to win people over.
Personally, I think Se Yoon played the game too well.
Left side.
- Because he didn't mess up...
- Will you give me time to explain?
Okay. I'll give you time.
- Can I get 30 seconds?
- Okay.
- Yes?
- All right, Se Yoon.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
I entered the Recreation and Leisure Department in 2001.
- I was the student representative.
- Yes.
I've been training to follow separate commands orally...
and physically since I was 20. I became used to that.
I just wanted to beat this game as soon as possible.
But I didn't know we had this many dummies.
So who do you think is Hungry Lupin?
- Two suspects are on my radar.
- Who are they?
I believe that Joon is Hungry Lupin.
I can bet my right wrist.
- If I were to take a risk, - He's sure of himself.
I could bring down Joon.
If something unexpected happens,
there's another candidate that comes to mind.
- Who is it?
- It's you.
Me?
(It's you.)
Sae Ho has...
absolutely no reason to suspect me,
but why is he going after me when I'm just an innocent citizen?
It's his strategy to attack me...
before anyone starts suspecting him.
However, he's making a huge mistake.
(The two of them started to suspect each other.)
You failed your first team mission.
(Failed the first Hungry Lupin mission)
You won't get any hint about Hungry Lupin.
Did we also lose our chance to have dinner together?
- That's correct.
- Right.
Unfortunately, dinner for the entire group has been lost.
- We must catch him no matter what.
- Gosh.
Anyway, Hungry Lupin will step up even more now.
From now on,
do your best...
to figure out who Hungry Lupin is throughout the trip.
Let's go.
Okay.
All right.
- Se Yoon seems suspicious.
- Right.
(They failed to earn the hint due to Hungry Lupin's interference.)
Am I behaving awkwardly?
We will definitely catch him.
This is how I usually am.
Thank you. Interview me again later.
I will catch you soon.
(Who is Hungry Lupin?)
(Hungry Lupin is hidden among the six of them.)
(With everyone eyeing each other suspiciously, )
(the vibe in the bus is completely different from usual.)
Will it be a long ride?
It will take...
about 25 minutes.
Se Yoon must have asked that question...
to do his best during the game.
He could be Hungry Lupin.
I'm just saying without thinking.
I'm actually hungry.
- You're actually hungry?
- When are you giving us food?
- I'm also very hungry.
- I'm starving.
When we start early, give us food early as well.
All of us are hungry.
Can't we discuss freely among ourselves?
- Of course.
- About who it is.
Earlier, I suspected Se Yoon a lot.
However, I couldn't help suspect Cheol as well.
It seems like Cheol is very much at ease today.
- I see.
- More...
- He got all wrong at the end.
- That's why...
That's what I'm wondering about.
(DinDin is much calmer than usual today.)
(He also got it wrong towards the end of the mission.)
(Is DinDin today's Hungry Lupin?)
Usually,
Sae Ho is... How shall I put it?
How can I say it in a nice way?
- What?
- Being obnoxious.
- Being obnoxious?
- Just say that I'm obnoxious.
How can we say obnoxious in a nice way?
- He's obnoxious.
- He takes the lead.
He often takes the lead.
Taking the lead is being obnoxious in a good way?
Usually, he's nice and takes the lead.
You try to say things in a positive way.
- You've changed a lot.
- By the way...
He did something which I thought was over the top.
- Okay.
- While looking for Hungry Lupin,
he stepped back and looked at us from behind.
- Was that necessary?
- He kept doing that.
He pointed at Se Yoon.
- From behind us.
- He behaved in a particular way?
(He kept stepping back during the mission.)
(Sae Ho pointed at Se Yoon for being Hungry Lupin.)
I think it's either Sae Ho or Joon.
Seon Ho, you're guessing the wrong person.
Cheol keeps suspecting me.
It makes him very suspicious.
Since I'm following the order of the queue...
- I thought about that too.
- You know what I mean?
- That's exactly what I thought.
- Right.
- Time-out, Sae Ho.
- That's what I also thought.
When someone suspects Mafia,
Mafia suspects him in return.
- He suspected me all of a sudden.
- No way.
- His reaction was immediate.
- May I bring this up?
Can we share what we said during the interview?
Whom we suspected?
I said casually that I suspected Se Yoon and DinDin.
That's why I'm talking eagerly...
about Se Yoon and DinDin.
- I don't think it's Sae Ho.
- Right.
- Here's why.
- That's possible.
He just asked...
if he could share whom he suspected during the interview.
They probably asked Hungry Lupin...
- if things were going well.
- Right.
He probably wasn't asked whom he suspected.
- However, - Right.
Based on what Sae Ho said,
- he knew what the question was.
- Goodness.
- Nice.
- That's why he asked...
if he could share what he said during the interview.
- Sae Ho must be exempted.
- Exactly.
On the other hand, Se Yoon hasn't said a word.
- Joon is being strange.
- I said it in the beginning.
Se Yoon, why did you smile?
- How you play is interesting.
- What?
- Se Yoon.
- Yes?
- You can relax.
- It's not me.
You can make me feel uncomfortable.
Anyway, it's very obvious.
Do you also see several cards in front of you?
- I was the first one.
- When I asked...
There were six cards in front of me.
They told me that we were called in the order of age.
- From youngest to oldest.
- At first, there were six cards.
Each person picked a card.
I think I was the fourth to arrive.
- Right.
- I had three cards in front of me.
Let's share what each of us got.
We can talk about it, right?
- Share which card we had...
- Then it will be over.
(A huge chance for the citizens)
(A huge crisis for Hungry Lupin)
- Wait.
- Then it's game over.
Se Yoon.
What was on the back of your card?
There was nothing on it.
There was nothing on mine.
- What about you, Jong Min?
- It was blank.
Mine was blank.
- You know what?
- What?
Se Yoon said that there was nothing on his card.
There's no doubt that Sae Ho repeated what Se Yoon said.
Say what was on your card instead of talking about others.
- What was on your card?
- There was nothing.
Then was it black or white?
White.
- Was it white?
- White.
- Are you sure?
- Sae Ho, which color was yours?
White.
- Was yours also white?
- Yes.
See? This won't work.
- Se Yoon isn't Hungry Lupin.
- He should've said something else.
I don't think it's Se Yoon.
- So it's not Se Yoon.
- We should've asked Sae Ho first.
- Exactly.
- Are you suspecting me now?
- He is.
- Wait a minute.
- Goodness.
In my opinion, it's neither Sae Ho nor Cheol.
- Okay.
- What's your reason?
Everything they say is correct.
You may take time to narrow down the list.
- Okay.
- We're going to the next location.
Gosh, there's a lot of citron on the trees.
So that's citron.
- It's just...
- Bunches of citron are hanging.
Let's make an acrostic poem with "citron."
- "Ci."
- It's citron.
- "Tron."
- You brat.
- "Ci."
- You're not alone
- "Rin."
- Don't change it out of the blue.
Suddenly, I wanted to change it to "yuringi."
Goodness.
(Laughing)
(They arrive at a village after being suspicious for 30 minutes.)
Gosh, the smell is amazing.
The citron smell is incredible.
Goodness.
This is where the history of citron started in Goheung.
- It's Daecheong Village.
- Daecheong?
- Daecheong Village? I see.
- Yes.
I didn't expect it to be filled with the citron smell.
Right? You can smell the citron everywhere in the village.
In Goheung,
the largest amount of citron is produced in the country.
The whole neighborhood is filled with the fragrance of citron.
This is amazing.
- Incredible.
- It feels like there's a diffuser.
- I know. It's amazing.
- Right, a citron diffuser.
Look at the mural.
"Exemption from the military service?"
"If someone cultivated eight or more citron trees,"
"they could be exempted from military duty."
It shows how important citron trees were.
(During the Joseon Dynasty, citron was a rare fruit.)
It smells so good.
(Looking at the citron while forgetting about Hungry Lupin)
- It smells incredible.
- It smells so good.
(Sniffing)
The citron smell is nice.
This is amazing.
- Do we sit?
- I never tasted something so good.
Yes, please sit down.
Citron has three times more vitamin C...
than lemons.
- Three times more?
- Yes.
Here's the next mission that will take place...
at a beautiful and golden citron field.
- It's called Eating Citron Relay.
- Okay.
You'll be given five minutes.
- Five minutes? That's enough.
- Yes.
You must eat all ten citron to succeed.
Ten is too much.
Each of you must eat at least one citron.
Feel free to distribute the remaining citron as you wish.
Once you swallow it completely...
and whistle, the next player can start.
In this game,
- there are two key points.
- What?
Don't try to watch everyone.
We should only observe Se Yoon and Jong Min.
- Se Yoon is good at eating citron.
- Right.
If Se Yoon struggles to eat it,
it will be worth suspecting him.
Jong Min loves things that are sour.
If he gets disgusted and spits it out,
- we'll have to suspect him.
- Right.
I like sour food,
- but I can't eat it fast.
- Jong Min can eat a lot,
- and Se Yoon can eat fast.
- Right.
I think Se Yoon will be the best at eating it.
Right, he should play last.
- We will put Se Yoon at the end.
- At the end?
- Then you should go first.
- I'll go second.
Shall I go first?
I'll eat one and a half of citron to make it simple.
- You should eat 2.
- You have to eat 2.
- Two?
- Yes.
- You should eat 2.
- There are 10.
Jong Min should eat two.
- Se Yoon should eat 4.
- Se Yoon should eat 2.
Then I will go...
- I'll go 2nd.
- You will play 2nd.
Seon Ho, you'll go third.
- Seon Ho, you'll go 3rd.
(Thinking)
Joon, you'll go fourth.
He was talking much more than usual.
He decided the general flow of the game.
It's because he's Hungry Lupin.
- Joon will go fourth.
- How many will you eat, Joon?
- I will eat the maximum...
- Are you aware...
that you're suspected the most?
How many will you eat?
- I'll eat as many as possible.
- How many will you eat?
- As many as possible.
- Can you eat three?
- I'll eat three.
- Okay.
Could you switch seats with him?
- He'll eat three.
- Okay.
- Two of you, change your seat.
- I will...
- I'm bad at eating it.
Joon, it's the perfect chance for you to clear your name.
I don't think people suspect me much.
It's easy to tell how dedicated you are...
- in the game.
- Of course.
You can tell how hard they work.
It's obvious.
To be honest, I can devour all the citron.
There's a minute difference of 1mm.
(Key point to watch: Minute 1mm)
Let's start.
You have five minutes. Are you ready?
Get ready.
Set,
- It will be sour.
- go.
I don't think it'll be that sour.
It's easy for him.
- The seeds...
- Is it sour?
- He's good at eating it.
- He's good.
- It's not sour.
- It doesn't seem sour.
- That's...
- Don't chew thoroughly.
Can you eat the next one?
- You're good at eating it.
- It doesn't look sour.
I think he lost his tooth.
I heard a loud crack.
It has seeds.
- What if...
- I guess it's not sour.
What if I spit out my tooth instead of seeds?
- That would be fun.
- It would be fun.
Then you'll win the Grand Award.
- It'd be an accident.
- It will be nice.
Can I eat this? I'll whistle when I'm done.
Yes.
I guess it's not sour.
He's eating it well.
- He's doing well.
- Yes.
He's working very hard.
He's eating it easily. It must not be sour.
Are you good at eating sour food?
- He's doing well.
- One minute.
He's working hard.
It's been one minute. Hurry up. What are you doing?
- What's wrong with you, Sae Ho?
- Hurry up.
- There he goes again.
- What's wrong, Sae Ho?
It has so many seeds.
- Hey.
- Look at the time.
You should eat the seeds.
Gosh, what is he doing?
- It must be Sae Ho.
- He took longer than a minute.
It's definitely Sae Ho.
Is it possible to take longer than a minute?
- Jong Min.
- He's taking long to whistle.
Go.
- I worked very hard.
- Sae Ho passed.
He's chewing with his front teeth.
Hurry up. You're eating one anyway.
(DinDin also spits out the seeds first.)
- He's suspicious too.
- Goodness.
- Isn't it his tooth?
- It has so many seeds.
- Hey.
- It must be sour.
What are you doing?
(Separating the seeds seems harder than eating it.)
- He's spitting out his front teeth.
- Hurry up. That's good.
Two minutes.
- It takes longer than I thought.
- Two minutes?
We only have five minutes. We must hurry.
Hey, what are you doing?
Next.
(3 minutes remain. What's important starts now.)
- We only have 5 minutes.
- I'll eat a big 1.
Hurry up.
- Don't tell us which you're eating.
- We must hear your whistle.
- Goodness.
- What are you doing?
(It was greed.)
Hey, you punk.
So it's you.
- Why you...
- Eat it fast.
Wait.
I told you that it was definitely him.
- We must reach the last player.
- You brat.
- Goodness.
- What is he doing?
We caught him.
- We must reach the last player.
- We got him. The game is over.
- We got Hungry Lupin.
- We caught him.
I've been telling you that he was suspicious.
We can't wait to eat it. Hurry up!
You Hungry Lupin.
- We need to get to Jong Min. Hurry!
- He's definitely Hungry Lupin.
- What did I tell you?
- Look at him act.
He's being suspicious.
I know how to judge people.
He spat out two seeds.
- What is he doing?
- He's chewing so thoroughly.
- It's not what you think.
- What's this?
- Gosh.
You can't do this, Joon.
(The members are narrowing down their investigation.)
Didn't I tell you that he was being strange?
(Everyone is watching Joon.)
Hurry up and eat.
That's why...
Stop talking.
This isn't some fine dining.
Why are you taking so long to eat? You're being annoying.
There's no time to laugh. You have to chew.
Don't make me laugh.
What is he doing?
Hurry up.
(Is he acting or is he really having a hard time?)
- This is...
- Hungry Lupin is...
I don't think it's him.
- It's very sour.
- Four minutes?
- Hurry up even if you can't.
- Four?
He's making it way too obvious.
- What?
- What is he doing?
(It's almost certain that they failed the mission.)
- Do it fast.
- Ten seconds.
- He's done.
- Eat it in small pieces.
It's so sour.
(It's finally Seon Ho's turn.)
Can you give us one more minute?
- Is it sour?
- This is impossible.
It's not sour at all.
Is something wrong with me?
- Five, four, - How is it not sour?
Three, two, one.
- Time is up.
- It's not sour at all.
- You failed to clear the mission.
- I'm sorry, but it's really sour.
Here's what I thought when I tasted it.
It's not so sour that it's impossible to eat.
- Also, - He's lying.
He chewed a lot.
It's delicious.
- That was intense.
- It tastes good.
Why did you do that?
I'm being honest.
I'd like the viewers to try it and see.
- It's the members who are strange.
- You're being ridiculous.
- It was as sour as lemon.
- What?
Mine was as sour as lemon.
- I'm serious.
- I didn't think you'd go this far.
What was the last thing he said before eating?
He said that he was eating the biggest one...
- before eating it.
- Right.
(Joon declared that he was eating the biggest one.)
He took a big one. What does it mean?
It was to justify that he had a hard time chewing.
So we don't suspect him.
I'm not that smart.
- I know, - I was only trying...
- but this was probably your plan.
- to sacrifice myself.
Based on how he played it,
all the pieces came together.
- Here's what I think.
- It wasn't a coincidence.
It's Joon.
I'm 100 percent sure.
When the fruit is big,
- it's usually less sour and sweet.
- That's right.
It's very strange.
Honestly, it wasn't that sour.
(While everyone is pointing out Joon, )
(what does Sae Ho think?)
The look on Joon's face was strange since this morning.
- What if...
- But what I ate...
Joon isn't Hungry Lupin?
- Hungry Lupin will be ecstatic now.
- I know.
We're suspecting someone...
other than him.
I know what Joon is like.
I think he really had a hard time eating it.
I really had a hard time. It was very sour.
- He's being honest.
- No, he's lying.
I thought that it was Joon's true side.
He just acted naturally.
He should've closed his nostrils...
or held his breath to eat it somehow.
DinDin is very clever, isn't he?
Cheol could have sat here...
expecting that it was impossible to get to the end.
- He could've thought that.
- By calculating it?
- That'd be amazing.
- If that's what he thought,
- he'd be very smart.
- He'd be very clever.
He placed himself in second.
After playing his part,
he could eliminate the possibility of getting suspected.
By the way, who made Joon sit here?
He did. It was you.
- I didn't know...
- Hey.
That Joon would be this terrible.
He also put Se Yoon at the very end.
- That's also strange.
- He decided the entire order.
It was DinDin.
- Wait a minute.
- I don't eat fruit like this.
- Detective Kim Jong Min.
- Yes?
What do you think?
This is...
It's hard to say that it's Joon because he was terrible.
- It was way too obvious.
- I know.
In that case,
is it worth suspecting him?
Exactly.
(Shaking his head)
I have no idea.
- Did I call you a detective?
- Yes.
- I take it back.
- Okay.
Then how about this?
With some hint at stake,
Se Yoon will eat 5 citrons in 1 minute.
Don't do that.
The seeds will come out like bullets.
Se Yoon can chew while spitting like a machine gun.
- Jong Min...
- Because they couldn't play?
And Se Yoon didn't get to play.
Two for Jong Min, and three for Se Yoon.
If you eat 5 in 1 minute, we'll accept it.
- Jong Min.
- Is that possible?
I can eat a lot, but I can't eat fast.
- Then let's do this.
- Jong Min.
- Eating 4 in 1 minute.
- You can do it.
No, five.
I'm still suspicious of DinDin.
Eating 4 in 1 minute is a better condition for us,
- but he insists on 5.
- Eating 5 is definitely possible.
- Really?
- Eating four is too easy.
Eating four citrons is too easy.
He's not the type to make things...
harder for everyone.
Why is he being so enthusiastic about the game?
So I'm suspicious of DinDin.
- He's being strange.
- Eating four is too easy.
Eating four citrons is too easy.
(Joon is also getting more suspicious of DinDin.)
- Jong Min, you know why you can?
- Why?
- This is November.
- What about it?
- I see. Okay.
- You can do it.
- You can definitely do it.
You can definitely make it.
2025 KBS Entertainment Awards.
The Grand Award goes to...
He ate two citrons.
The name has been announced up to Kim.
- Kim.
- Up to Jong has been said.
- Kim Jong.
(Glorious days suddenly come to mind.)
Do you know how powerful Jong Min is in November?
You got married, and you can win the Grand Award.
- That would be wonderful.
- What should you do in November?
- I just have to eat two citrons?
- Of course.
Jong Min in November will be shown in a clip.
- Darn it.
- Get ready.
The Grand Award in 2025 goes to...
We said it up to Kim Jong.
Start.
(Rushing)
No, that won't work.
(He separates the seeds in 2 seconds.)
It's possible.
No one can stop Jong Min in November.
(He eats 1 in 10 seconds.)
He's unstoppable.
(Refilling the citron fast)
- It's delicious.
- What are you doing?
Chew them. What are you doing? Hurry up.
- Hurry up.
- Hurry.
- It's been 20 seconds.
- You have no time.
- I have to eat it too.
- You're taking almost a minute.
- I might not get to eat. Hurry.
- You're taking too much time.
I might not get to eat. Hurry.
(He stuffs his face with the next citron.)
- That's impressive.
- You're using up one minute.
(Overload)
Hurry up.
- Hurry, Jong Min.
- This is ridiculous.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
(He's about to throw up.)
- How many seconds?
- Forty seconds.
Forty seconds.
(He tries to whistle without swallowing everything.)
Hurry up.
- Forty-five seconds.
- He's doing very well.
(His head is spinning from the sour taste.)
- Never mind.
- Fifty seconds.
- Time is up.
- It's over.
- Failed.
- Oh, come on.
- He did a good job.
- He did well.
He wasn't acting. It's not easy.
You did a good job.
I couldn't swallow it.
- I know.
- It's tough.
You were eating a lot at once.
I can't say that he did an outstanding job.
He ate two citron so slowly while spitting out all the seeds.
I don't like how he did it.
He definitely spent more than a minute.
(It seems like he failed on purpose.)
(As Se Yoon expected, did he fail on purpose?)
- He wasn't acting.
- How about 3 in 30 seconds?
(A groundbreaking proposal)
- Do you accept it or not?
- Se Yoon.
There are people who are curious about it,
- so could you just try it?
- No way.
He can't do it for free.
- I get paid for my eating shows.
- All right.
He's a professional.
Guys.
- Look at the seeds.
Look at the seeds.
(Suddenly, it turns into a citron festival.)
(This isn't allowed here.)
What do you say? I can give it a try.
The public is saying that I give you too many chances.
But...
You don't want to see Se Yoon eat it?
Give us some citron tea.
- Right.
- It's the least you can do.
Then we'll give it to you...
- after your meal.
- As a dessert.
- Okay.
- Shall we go?
- I don't think it's possible.
- I'll start when I'm ready.
Please don't try this at home.
- Don't try it at home.
- What did you say?
- What?
- Don't try it at home.
- I'm telling them not to try.
- Don't try this?
It's possible for those who have done eating shows for ten years.
- Only professionals can do it.
- Don't try it at home.
Is this really possible?
- Get ready, - Do your best.
- set, go.
- You have to chew it all.
(Start)
He chewed the seeds.
- Set, go.
- You have to chew it all.
(The human blender is activated.)
He's chewing the seeds.
- He chewed the whole thing.
- He finished 1 in 5 seconds.
- Ready. Go.
- You should chew it all.
(The human blender is activated.)
He chewed the seeds.
- I told you, he can do it.
- He just chewed the seeds.
- He chewed the whole thing.
- He finished 1 in 5 seconds.
(He put all 3 in his mouth only in 8 seconds.)
He finished 1 in 5 seconds.
(Shocked)
(He's on another level as we all know.)
How many seconds are left?
Fifteen seconds.
(He just has to swallow it and whistle to succeed.)
He's amazing. It has a lot of seeds.
(He spits seeds out like a machine gun.)
(He does it one more time as everyone seems to like it.)
- How many seconds have passed?
- Twenty-four, twenty-five,
twenty-six, twenty-seven... Twenty-nine, thirty.
(He succeeds in eating 3 citrons in 30 seconds.)
(All members will get citron tea.)
(Applauding in awe)
He finished the 1st one only in 5 seconds.
- That was crazy.
- This is how you play a game.
It took him only five seconds.
(Super cool)
My, that was really cool.
- Did I do okay?
- You're the best.
(You're the best.)
You failed to complete the mission.
So you won't get a hint on Hungry Lupin.
- We'll do a brief interview.
- Okay.
I'll slate. One, two, three.
- Come for the interview.
- Okay.
- That way? Okay.
- You were confident, right?
Okay, good. Shall we do it over there?
- Okay.
- Could you stand here for me?
Here?
This is interesting.
(They split up and begin their interviews.)
(The staff comes up to Hungry Lupin during his interview.)
- Let me tell you something first.
- Okay.
You have to choose one member as the helper...
who will assist you.
Oh, my. That's great.
Whom will you choose as your helper?
(The helper, who will help Hungry Lupin, appeared.)
There's a helper to help Hungry Lupin now.
(Four citizens and one helper)
The member who's been chosen as the helper by Hungry Lupin...
will share the same fate with Hungry Lupin.
He will have to help Hungry Lupin...
so that Hungry Lupin doesn't get caught by the other citizens.
If Hungry Lupin is not caught at the end of the game,
the helper will get to have dinner.
(The helper gains food.)
If Hungry Lupin is caught at the end of the game,
(Chosen as the culprit)
the helper can't have dinner.
(The citizens gain food.)
In brief, Hungry Lupin and the helper are on the same team now.
(Whom will Hungry Lupin choose?)
(I choose this person as my helper.)
With this member by my side,
I'm sure I can prevent it.
You have been chosen by Hungry Lupin...
as his helper.
(Who was chosen as Hungry Lupin's helper?)
Okay. Now we'll get going.
(The helper selection and the interview ended.)
- Please do it.
- I'll do it.
It's me
Do you guys know what Goheung is famous for?
- Goheung?
- Yes.
- Goheung? I know something.
- What is it?
The Naro Space Center...
- is located in Goheung.
- That's right.
(The Naro Space Center, Korea's first satellite launch site, )
(is located in Goheung.)
How did you know that?
In the drama "The Silent Sea,"
I had this line in a space scene.
"This is Naro 11. Come in. Over."
- I had this line.
- I see.
So I watched a lot of space-related videos.
- For your information, - Yes.
Another rocket is scheduled to be launched from Goheung...
on November 27.
- Really?
- I see.
(Fascinated)
- That's amazing.
- At the end of November.
- It's amazing.
- Didn't they succeed recently?
- Nuri was successfully launched.
- That's right.
Anyway, who is Hungry Lupin?
I think it's Jong Min.
- Why?
- I think...
- you were chosen as Hungry Lupin, - Yes?
But then you forgot about that.
(Laughing)
(Dumbfounded)
There's a very high probability that it's the case.
Jong Hyun would ask Jong Min,
"Jong Min, you do know you were chosen as Hungry Lupin, right?"
- Jong Min would say, "What? Me?"
- "Me?"
He'd be like, "Me? When did that happen?"
- No, that's not the case.
- I'm suspicious of Jong Min.
I absolutely believe that it's DinDin. I'm sure of it.
He belittled me for no reason.
He said there was no way I was Hungry Lupin...
because I wasn't capable.
- Sorry for suspecting you, DinDin.
- Okay.
But the DinDin I know...
would get mad and deny the suspicion.
- Right.
- But he's been so quiet.
- Is it because he's changed or...
- He's now a thoughtful celebrity.
I'm not sure what's happening.
He would keep trying to convince us that he's not Hungry Lupin,
- Right. You felt that too, right?
- but he's been too calm.
Because it's so obvious that I'm not Hungry Lupin,
I can't find any grounds on which to deny the suspicion.
He's trying to convince everyone that you're Hungry Lupin.
Whom do you suspect the most?
- I suspect you.
- Me?
- Even if it was hard to eat, - Right.
It's still absurd that he talked while eating it.
(He seemed absolutely suspicious at the citron farm.)
It didn't seem to work, so I gave up and talked.
I shoot a video with Joon for "Workman" from time to time.
He works really hard when he's given a task.
He puts his life on it even when it's really exhausting.
But he couldn't eat a citron?
- That makes no sense.
- I work even harder on this show.
By the way, Hungry Lupin is supposed...
to try not to succeed when playing a game, right?
Joon, I can't believe you just said such a thing.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Do you have to go that far?
It just crossed my mind. That's all.
Wasn't what he just said ridiculous?
- What was that?
- Exactly. I'm dumbfounded.
He wouldn't seem so suspicious if he stayed quiet.
Why would he say such a thing? Edit that part out.
- Don't look down on me.
- Your comment will make people...
believe you're Hungry Lupin and switch channels.
- I also...
- Oh, gosh.
Joon, just admit that you're Hungry Lupin.
I guess DinDin is sure that Joon is Hungry Lupin.
Suddenly,
I want to believe Joon.
I mean, he often talks nonsense as he just did.
He seems suspicious because of the situation,
but he usually behaves that way.
I'd be so sad if I was Hungry Lupin.
I'm getting more confused because of our conversations.
- Sae Ho, who do you think it is?
- Whom do you suspect?
- It's hard to tell.
- I suspect DinDin and Chang Seon.
- Wasn't it obvious?
- I don't think it's Joon. If so...
That'd mean he totally fooled me this time.
Really? Then whom do you suspect?
As I said earlier, I suspect DinDin.
- DinDin?
- It's either Seon Ho or Lim Cheol.
- I'm not...
- Come on.
(Se Yoon is simply excited about eating food.)
Good.
Today's lunch...
has the rich flavor of the clean sea of Goheung.
You'll have the sea set meal.
(The Goheung sea set meal)
The South Sea is really incredible.
(The dishes made with seafood caught in the clean South Sea)
Whole eel stew,
- grilled eel, - Oh, my.
And seasoned raw tongue sole will be served.
Seasoned raw tongue sole.
(The Goheung sea set meal will invigorate the members.)
- It sounds amazing.
- You know...
He said "whole eel stew."
- Does it have a whole eel?
- Is it whole eel stew?
(Correct. A whole eel is in it without being ground.)
What is tongue sole?
- It's the name of a fish.
- Right, tongue sole.
- Flatfish and tongue sole.
- I see.
(Raw tongue sole mixed with a sauce is also one of the best delicacies.)
- I'll be sure to eat those dishes.
- I can tell they make great food.
Through this game with lunch on the line,
we'll see how observant the detectives are.
It's Magnifier Food Quiz.
(The lunch mission, Magnifier Food Quiz)
- Exactly.
- This is an individual game.
- I'm really bad at this game.
- I like team games.
You'll see part of a photo of food that's enlarged on three levels...
and guess what food it is.
(Level 2, marinated crab)
(Level 3, large intestine over rice)
(The answer is large intestine over rice.)
Only the top three members who got the most right answers...
will get to eat food.
The member who places first...
will be given a hint on Hungry Lupin.
- That's good for all of us.
- Right.
If the member who got the hint gets the right answer,
will he get food?
- Pardon?
- What did you say?
- Seriously, Jong Min...
Don't get me wrong. Go wash your face with cold water.
This is not good.
Wash your face with cold water or something like that.
- Shall I spray water on you?
- Right. No, that's okay.
- Are you good?
- Yes.
What if Hungry Lupin places first?
- If Hungry Lupin places first...
- Why are you asking that?
He will get the hint.
- But...
- He may lie to us.
(Hungry Lupin can lie about the hint.)
So if Hungry Lupin places first, there will be no problem.
- Joon seems very curious about it.
- Why? Tell us.
- It doesn't make sense.
- He's acting suspicious again.
- I mean...
- I was suspecting DinDin, but...
- It's strange.
- Come on, Joon.
- Are you making it obvious now?
- Hungry Lupin wouldn't ask that.
- Hey.
So it doesn't make any sense.
Maybe he asked the question because he didn't understand the rules.
- Right.
- Okay. Now...
- Can we practice first?
We'll give you a practice question.
How about we get one bite of food if we get it right?
What about one piece of grilled eel?
- Sounds great.
- That'd be great.
Here goes the practice question.
(The practice quiz begins.)
Isn't that a pimple?
It looks a bit disgusting.
I've seen a photo like this at a dermatology clinic.
- What is that?
- Let me answer.
(It's an enlarged image.)
(What food could this be?)
I see some chili oil.
It has chili oil on it, so it must be a Chinese dish.
I think it's a Chinese dish...
- based on the chili oil.
- Sae Ho. Crab egg foo young.
- Se Yoon.
- Go ahead.
Guobaorou.
- Incorrect.
- Seon Ho.
- Is it incorrect?
- Malatang.
- Incorrect.
- What is that?
- What is it?
- Moving on to the next hint.
We'll get the next hint.
It's Level Two.
(Level 2 shows a bigger part of the image.)
(What food could this be?)
- Joon.
- What?
What are you waiting for? Say the answer.
Pepperoni pizza.
- Incorrect.
- Jong Min.
- Seon Ho.
- Jong Min, go ahead.
Cheese tteokbokki.
Correct.
- Okay.
- Oh, yes!
(The answer is cheese tteokbokki.)
Oh, it was cheese tteokbokki.
It looked like some kind of soup, right?
- I saw the rice cake at the bottom.
- Right.
- This will be difficult.
- Can you show us Level One?
(But then...)
(Picking up)
(Siren wailing)
What's going on?
(The siren sound wails suddenly?)
(Team Security appears.)
- What's going on?
- Me?
- What's going on? Why?
- Why is he taking me away?
- Why?
- What's happening?
- What is he doing?
- Why?
(The security team has arrived.)
- What's going on?
- Is it me?
- What's happening?
- Why is he dragging me?
- What? What's going on?
- Why is he doing this?
- What's happening?
- What's going on?
- What happened?
- What did he do?
- I didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything, you saw me!
Hungry Lupin... I'm hungry!
What are you doing?
I just got the question right.
What's going on?
Did he take Jong Min because he got the answer?
It has nothing to do with that?
- Wait a second.
- What did Jong Min say?
(Dumbfounded)
What did Jong Min say?
We can't say anything then.
- What did he even say?
- He wasn't doing his best?
(Is it because he wasn't doing his best on the show?)
Did you just eliminate the worst player or what?
- What's happening?
- What was that?
Let's keep the seat vacant because it's unlucky there.
- Goodness.
- No, it can't be happening.
It's so funny how he got out after he got the answer right.
He can't eat then.
What's going on?
I was supposed to have a bite because I got the question right.
- We'll take off now.
- Where are we going?
What's going on?
Why are you doing this?
(The van is setting off without knowing the destination.)
What did I even do? I didn't do anything wrong.
(A procession full of questions)
(All I did was...)
Cheese tteokbokki.
That is correct.
(I just got the question right, that is all.)
You didn't have your bite there?
No! I was supposed to have a bite because I got the question right.
Bad timing.
(What's the truth behind Jong Min getting eliminated?)
- Jong Hyun.
- Yes?
He didn't go because he got the answer, did he?
- That's not true.
- You sure?
You're not telling us the reason?
- You will know the reason later.
- Okay.
Let's play the game now.
Here is your question.
(The winner exclusively gets the hint for Hungry Lupin.)
(What is this food?)
That must be garlic.
Seon Ho, aglio e olio pasta.
Incorrect.
They zoomed in the picture, garlic can't be that big.
That must be a sesame seed.
- Right, it's a sesame seed.
- Sesame seed.
- It is a sesame seed.
- Right, it's a sesame seed.
So it's food.
- Seon Ho.
- Yes.
A hamburger.
(A hamburger)
- It must be the answer.
- Correct.
I knew it was...
a burger with patties and a bun on top.
(This sesame seed image, enlarged 160 times, is...)
(A burger with sesame seeds on top)
Se Yoon mentioning sesame seeds...
- You gave a big hint.
- I know.
Here is the second question.
Here it is.
- Goodness.
- It must be soup.
It looks like soup.
(Soup...)
- Joon.
- Yes.
Sundae soup.
- That must be the answer.
- For real?
(It must be the answer.)
- Correct.
- Goodness.
(Joon got the answer.)
(He guessed the menu right away after he learned that it's a soup.)
Zoomed out two notches.
- Three notches.
- It's totally sundae.
(The best soup there possible, sundae soup.)
Joon earned a point.
Joon got the answer? My gosh, this is humiliating.
That puts me in a bad position.
All right, here is the third question.
(Green garnish on top of yellow food?)
(He can't even take a guess.)
(Is that green thing parsley?)
Seon Ho, steamed eggs?
- Incorrect.
- DinDin.
Egg tart.
Incorrect.
- That was very sharp.
- Se Yoon.
I think it's zoomed in a lot.
Pumpkin cream soup...
and parsley on top.
Pumpkin cream soup.
- Incorrect.
- Zoom out.
- I'll zoom out now.
- Okay, zoom out.
- What can this be?
- What is this?
(A glimmer of bronzed food peeked through the opening)
(It's made with at least three ingredients or more.)
I see cheese peeking out.
Sae Ho. It's a hamburg steak.
Incorrect.
Se Yoon.
That's jjajang ramyeon and cheese on top.
What's it called in a short form?
- I know.
- DinDin.
Hey, this one.
Jjajang ramyeon, egg, and cheese.
- It must be the answer.
- That is correct.
What is that?
(Se Yoon got the answer.)
Yes, it's that jjajang ramyeon with egg and cheese.
Jjajang ramyeon with egg and cheese on top.
It actually is a menu.
- You can find it in cafeterias.
- Really?
It's a popular dish among young people.
- Jjajang with egg and cheese.
- That's right.
Here is the fourth question.
(Leveling up the difficulty for the fourth question)
(Sighing)
(Why did they all sigh?)
- This is crazy.
- What can this be?
My stomach is growling.
(A glossy brown dish)
Seon Ho, jokbal.
- Incorrect.
- DinDin.
(Thinking)
A strawberry cake.
- Strawberries?
- Incorrect.
- It looks like a strawberry.
- I can't tell from this.
Will any of us get this right?
I don't think so.
- I'm sure you have eaten this.
- Right.
(Revealing the photo after zooming out)
Oh, the name of this...
I don't know the name of this.
- I think the name was...
- It must be...
(Half a year ago, while filming Six Jong Min Special)
(All of them loved this dessert.)
(He ate it so happily, yet...)
- The name...
- When did we eat that?
The name!
Dried persimmon with cheese.
- It's something like that.
- DinDin! I know.
(Here is the answer.)
(This dish that evokes the appearance of jokbal)
(Dried persimmon roll with cream cheese)
- DinDin.
- Incorrect.
Cream cheese and dried persimmon...
Cream cheese with walnuts and persimmon.
- Incorrect.
- Joon.
(Shouted by all in the nick of time)
- Seon Ho.
- Let's try.
Seon Ho was faster.
Seon Ho.
Dried persimmon bits with cream cheese.
Incorrect.
It is with cream cheese. But how does it look?
It looks like this.
(Like this?)
Delicious?
What is it?
- It's rolled.
- Se Yoon.
Rolled.
(That's the name!)
Dried persimmon...
with cream cheese.
Sae Ho, Sae Ho!
- Incorrect.
- Sae Ho.
Dried persimmon roll with cream cheese.
DinDin!
That is correct.
What is it called? Cream cheese?
Dried persimmon roll.
(The game is over when Joon hasn't even spoken a word.)
I need to get at least two more questions.
(Sae Ho 1, Seon Ho 1, Se Yoon 1 Joon 1, DinDin 0)
This food...
- I'm sure you all know this.
- Okay, it must be popular.
It's sweating.
(Tiny drops of water)
- It's sweating.
- It looks like a human finger.
(Scared)
- Sae Ho.
- Yes.
- Pork skin.
- Incorrect.
- It's not?
- Joon.
The surface has some oil.
This is what I think.
It looks like oil or cheese.
It does look like fat. However, I feel...
that those are noodles.
(Oily)
- Joon.
- Yes?
Aglio e olio.
Correct.
That's a shrimp.
(Se Yoon has been giving hints to everybody.)
- That's a shrimp.
- I see.
Please show us the original picture.
(It's that grease on top of the aglio e olio shrimp.)
Here is the sixth question.
- What is that?
- This is...
Are you kidding me?
Whoever gets the answer is the weird one.
- Sae Ho.
- Yes.
Salt bread?
(Salt bread)
- It must be the answer.
- He's right.
(Eyes shaking)
- It must be correct.
- That is correct.
That's amazing.
- That's salt.
- It's salt.
- How is that salt?
- That's bread on the bottom.
- Salt crystals on top.
- Goodness.
- Salt bread.
(Sae Ho got the answer after only seeing the salt crystal.)
That was crazy.
(Sae Ho and Joon are the co-winners.)
Okay, this is making me scared.
Here is the seventh question.
What is that?
- Seon Ho, it's hot pot.
- What?
- Hot pot.
- Incorrect.
The next hint is...
(They can now see some vegetables and fruit.)
Se Yoon.
Tomyumgoong.
I thought of that too.
That is correct.
(I should have gone for it.)
I'm sorry.
- Well, this wraps up...
- I'm sorry.
Joon, Sae Ho, and Se Yoon...
- can eat.
- Goodness.
(Joon went from last place to grab a meal in no time.)
We will play the final round.
This will decide the winner.
(A first-place battle to decide the hint recipient)
I'm not Hungry Lupin.
So it would be nice if you make me the winner.
You two are the most suspicious ones.
And you are here.
This is a very good chance to see who Hungry Lupin is.
- I mean...
- Let's eat.
I'll share with you, Seon Ho.
You have to share the hint to get Hungry Lupin.
- Joon, let me be the winner.
- Of course, we have to share.
- I mean it.
- He might lie.
- I won't lie, I mean it.
- All right.
Here is the question.
(The final round that will decide the winner who gets the hint)
- What is that?
- I think I can guess what it is.
- What is it?
- I think it's white soup.
- It must be mixed with...
- It also has chili oil on top.
Joon, seolleongtang.
Incorrect.
I have no idea.
I see some textures.
(This is difficult.)
We zoomed it out.
(Revealing the picture as it's zoomed out)
Here you go.
(Noodles served in a light, clear soup)
- Sae Ho.
- Joon.
Gosh, it's easy.
- You have to say it correctly.
- Don't miss your chance.
Sae Ho.
Mul makguksu.
- What?
- What are you doing?
(How can he miss this?)
- Incorrect.
- Joon.
- Here is your chance.
- Naengmyeon.
You are missing this?
Joon got the answer.
I thought it was cold buckwheat noodles.
I thought it was arrowroot cold noodles.
- But it's all right.
- Joon got the hint.
You aren't Hungry Lupin, are you?
What?
I should have gotten the hint.
(Hungry Lupin can't have the hint.)
You are right.
Let's trust Joon for now.
- Please share with us the hint.
- It must be Joon.
Then he would lie to us.
Isn't Jong Min coming?
His name is there. I feel bad for him.
(Jong Min was brought to this place without any explanation.)
It's an event location.
(When the citron turns golden, )
(this place bustles with visitors.)
(Goheung Citron Festival)
There's a citron festival here.
Why did you bring me here?
From now on, you'll earn your own allowance...
- and buy your own lunch.
- My allowance?
You will change into a human citron now...
and take photos with the tourists...
who came to the citron festival.
(Taking pictures with the tourists)
You'll get 10 cents for every person you take a photo with.
- Ten cents?
- Yes.
How many pictures am I supposed to take?
Let's get changed.
I'd need at least 50 dollars for a meal.
Okay.
(Jong Min is turning into a human citron.)
(Laughing)
Is this okay?
- It's okay.
- Is it okay?
Is this right?
(Laughing)
(Revealing Citron Jong Min)
Let's go.
I'm going to earn money.
(He starts earning his allowance.)
Do I have to take photos with people?
With people?
Shall we take a picture together?
Really?
(He attempts to appeal as the photo subject.)
- Thank you.
- Can I take one too?
Sure.
- Two, three.
- Let's take a picture.
Thank you.
(Photo requests continue to come.)
The best!
(Taking a picture with a cute baby)
(He's not popular with babies.)
Hi.
I'm a citron.
- He's Kim Jong Min.
- I guess he's very scared.
(citron feels awkward.)
(He took pictures with 9 people in no time.)
Hold on. I should first check the food.
(He first checks the prices of the food.)
(A variety of food stalls attracts visitors.)
Stir-fried pork?
(Delicacies that delight your sight and taste)
There are so many tasty foods.
(Your mouth waters just by looking at them.)
This is...
I roughly scanned them,
and the most expensive one was 15 dollars.
Most of them cost ten dollars.
I have to take pictures 150 times.
(He has to take pictures with at least 100 people.)
- With 150 people.
- With 150 people?
Hello. Please come if you want to take a photo with me!
Photo!
(He'll starve if he doesn't do anything!)
Let's go! I love you!
- Thank you.
2 Days 1 Night!
(He takes a photo with the girl fans.)
(He takes a photo with an elementary school friend.)
Hello. Hi.
(This time, we have a puppy visitor.)
You're going to count the puppy too, right?
(Count me as well.)
- 2 Days 1 Night!
- 1 Night!
(Crowded with people)
Thank you.
You look handsome.
- Come here, kids.
- Come here.
(Crowded)
I'm the citron Man.
- 2 Days 1 Night!
(The allowance money quickly goes up thanks to the group visitors.)
- 1 Night!
Hello.
You look nice.
-You look nice.
- How pretty.
Thank you.
(Kim Jong Min fan meeting opens.)
Jong Min, I love you.
- Good luck with 2 Days 1 Night.
- Thank you!
One Night!
(He's the idol of the seniors.)
(The number of people he took pictures with until now)
Thank you.
Hello.
Would you like to take a picture together?
- Please take one.
- Yes.
- 2 Days 1 Night!
- 1 Night!
(He shouted 2 Days 1 Night 15,464 times.)
(He made babies cry 28,469 times.)
I love you.
(He was loved by the seniors 896,549 times.)
(Current allowance: 16.1 dollars with 161 people)
Let's take a photo.
Shall we take a photo?
- Count them in.
- Come in.
(The dumb brother is interacting with his fans.)
- Hotteok?
- There's hotteok.
- How much is this?
- It's two dollars.
- Two dollars?
- Yes.
- Two dollars.
- Let's take a photo.
We'll take a photo.
(He takes a photo and earns money for the hotteok.)
- 2 Days 1 Night!
- 1 Night!
Here you go. Two dollars.
- No.
- No. I'll pay you today.
- Thank you.
- I'll enjoy this.
Look over here.
(Please look over here, Jong Min.)
(He's a walking photo zone.)
Look at that.
(Current allowance: 16 dollars)
Let's go and eat.
How many people?
(Why was Jong Min left behind?)
(We'll reveal the identity of the helper only to the viewers.)
(At the restaurant, only Joon is given the Hungry hint.)
Joon will listen to the hint while the food is being prepared.
Okay!
- Joon.
- Share it with us right away.
I'll share it.
You're 100 percent going to lie.
No. Why do you all think of me as such a person?
(He moves to get a hint.)
(He smiles.)
How does it turn out like this?
It's a relief. I did my best.
It's a relief.
- Now...
- Give me the hint.
I'll give you the hint.
(Could it be?)
(1 hour ago, Citron Village)
(The individual interviews end.)
(One person heads to a remote place alone.)
You have been chosen by the Hungry Lupin...
to be his helper.
(Helper?)
(While choosing the card)
What is this?
You chose an empty card.
Why was I chosen?
(Joon was chosen as the helper.)
Why was I chosen? I'm not good at such things.
You can only have dinner...
if Hungry Lupin isn't caught in the final selection.
If Hungry Lupin gets caught, you won't have dinner.
Hungry Lupin.
I'll tell you who Hungry Lupin is.
Hungry Lupin is...
Hungry Lupin chose Lee Joon as his helper.
(Helper)
Hungry Lupin and his helper know of each other,
and they can share information or updates.
The helper can earn his dinner...
only if Hungry Lupin doesn't get caught.
As the helper,
you get one benefit.
As the helper, you'll have the authority...
to eliminate one member, excluding yourself.
- The next location...
- Hold on.
My heart is racing. I'm bad at these things.
Hold on.
The helper has a special benefit...
even Hungry Lupin doesn't know of.
(Benefit)
The helper can eliminate...
one member who is the most threatening.
It's a privilege that will let you take the game in your favor.
What sign will you use to decide the person to eliminate?
I'll do this. If I'm standing in the middle...
and I do this, it's the person standing on my left.
If I do this, it's the second person on my left.
(They arrived at the restaurant.)
(The helper has to eliminate someone.)
(The members don't know about the helper.)
(During the mission, he looks around.)
(While everyone is focusing on the food pictures...)
(He leans back and points.)
(He points once.)
(He chose Kim Jong Min who is sitting next to him.)
(The siren rings.)
- What is it?
- Is it me?
- What is going on?
- What is it?
- Why?
(They're all confused.)
- What's going on?
- What?
(He is excited all by himself.)
Did he get dragged because he answered the question?
(Without anyone knowing, )
(he succeeds in leaving one member out.)
(As the helper, he even won the game and got the hint.)
It's a relief.
- Now...
- Give me the hint.
I'll give you the hint.
This is a video of a five-year-old drawing the Hungry Lupin...
after looking at his picture.
Listen carefully and play it.
Okay.
I'm looking at the picture now.
The eyes look funny.
His nose...
is triangular.
His lips are funny.
He looked like a bear.
(Hungry Lupin seen through a child's innocent perspective)
This is amazing.
They'll never know.
Goodness.
(He looked like a bear.)
He's coming.
(Only Hungry Lupin knows that Lee Joon is his helper.)
Share it with us.
- You should share.
- It's really difficult.
- Is it?
- Let's figure it out together.
I figured out who it is.
- What?
- Because of one word.
- Really?
- I watched a video.
- A video.
- Outside.
- I went out and watched a video.
He can share it, right?
- Video?
- He can share it.
Seriously...
It wasn't Hungry Lupin.
- Guess the person.
- It's you.
(Se Yoon is pointed out.)
- That's accurate.
- It's you.
It's 100 percent you.
A five-year-old child...
drew Hungry Lupin...
after seeing his picture.
Then the child explains the drawing.
Don't get hurt.
The eyes look funny.
That's Sae Ho.
Keep going.
His nose is triangular.
- Triangular?
- They're triangular.
His lips are funny.
They all look funny.
- But...
- Is he fat?
(His nostrils are flaring.)
- What is it?
- He looks like a bear.
He looks like a bear.
(That's me.)
(Our bear)
Honestly, the front bits are useless.
He did his best at the beginning.
Do I look like a bear?
No.
- Does he look like a bear?
- Hey, DinDin.
- That was why.
- Definitely not.
- I thought you fooled us.
- No.
I swear. I spoke the exact truth.
You bear!
(Cornered)
- Hold on.
- We got you.
This is what I have in mind.
Will you listen to this?
First, I really want to eat. Second,
- I thought trouble had come.
- Why?
Are you saying you're in trouble?
No. In all honesty...
Look at you!
- We got you!
- Actually...
We got you!
(True behavior of Se Yoon who feels flustered)
I feel completely wronged.
I developed a heart of understanding.
A heart of understanding for those who were wrongly imprisoned.
"So this is how they could feel."
Why did the five-year-old say it was like a bear?
Listen carefully.
I'll speak logically. Listen carefully, Seon Ho.
- So the hint was crucial.
- It can't be eaten.
You have to think wisely as a smart one.
"Like a bear" was mentioned.
What would the production crew think with that expression?
It's the perfect hint.
- A hint can't be that obvious.
- You're right.
"Like a bear" is some sort of trap.
It's to make everyone think it's me.
Who enjoyed that situation the most?
- It was him.
- What? Oh, come on.
"Bear? Yes!"
(Acting just like him)
- Hear me out.
- Hold on.
- You have to think wisely, DinDin.
- Hey.
You'll be in big trouble. You won't be able to have dinner.
- DinDin.
- He's making sense though.
I'll be really honest.
I missed the timing to say this.
The hint said that person looked funny.
Who is the one who looks funny?
Hey, who is the one who looks funny?
I'll be honest.
I do look funny.
No! You look funny and ugly.
Right. I look funny and ugly.
But I'm certainly not a bear.
- See that? Isn't he overreacting?
- It's obvious.
- Listen, DinDin.
- Gosh, Se Yoon!
- Early in the morning...
- Se Yoon is lying!
- I'm not sweating at all.
- Seon Ho.
Early in the morning, I said this.
The Hungry Lupin is surely...
I'll show you my heart rate.
A bear was mentioned.
I thought it was...
a really big hint.
Who else could be thought of with that hint?
It was just like giving the answer away.
(Se Yoon struggles with Joon's strategy.)
(Se Yoon's identity gets revealed only to the viewers.)
What?
(The card Se Yoon picked)
It's a blank card.
(Se Yoon is not Hungry Lupin.)
You all know who it is.
Even through this interview,
I feel dumbfounded.
We won't be able to eat at this rate.
(Joon is the helper.)
(The Hungry Lupin is 1 of these 4 members.)
I'm going to make it clear. I'm going to eat a lot.
- Gosh.
- I'm going to have dinner as well.
- Right.
- Gosh!
It's for us. They aren't allowed to eat.
(The colors of the dishes make your mouth water.)
The mustard greens kimchi was made with our own ingredients.
- Really?
- This was picked from the sea.
- The seaweed was picked?
- Yes.
- These were all collected?
They look different.
(The side dishes all have the taste of Goheung.)
(I did it.)
The bowl for the stew is huge.
- It's really big.
- Gosh. I really want to eat this.
(Strong eels caught from the sea of Goheung)
Gosh!
This is totally a restorative dish.
They will taste delicious as they were freshly caught...
and sent in the morning.
This is such a healthy dish.
If you are willing to make someone not be able to eat,
you can't come to a good place like this.
(Making a stubborn claim)
- What are you doing?
- It's coming.
(DinDin's whining is completely ignored.)
(A special sauce is applied to the grilled eel.)
(Grilled eel)
(Sweet and sour seasoned raw tongue sole)
(A legendary sea meal of Goheung)
- Thank you for the food.
- This is the best ever.
This is insane. I've never seen anything like this.
- This is surely good for you.
- It's so good!
Eel.
If Se Yoon is taking a picture, it means it's...
It's because it's his last meal today.
He won't be able to eat if he gets caught as the Hungry Lupin.
I didn't think he was that much of a fool.
What a disappointment.
- I'll start eating now.
- Gosh.
- The meat is just...
- How does the soup taste?
The soup is so good.
It's so rich.
- Is it like yukgaejang?
- No.
How should I put it?
The sticky taste is amazing.
It tastes savory...
as the eel's oil gets mixed into the soup.
It feels completely different...
from a regular fish stew.
It feels refreshing just like the moray eel soup.
Right. It feels a bit like the moray eel soup.
Gosh, that must be good.
- Also, the eel is so soft.
- Right.
Try some of the grilled eel and the seasoned raw tongue sole.
Was it grilled with the sauce?
Gosh!
(Unable to speak)
It's amazing.
(They enjoy the plump grilled eel.)
Gosh.
- The sauce isn't overbalanced.
- Right.
The meat itself is really firm.
- Gosh, this is killing me.
- A wrap is to die for.
Gosh, this is great.
(Wrapping it with the pickled perilla leaf)
I think this is one of the best lunches we've ever had.
Seriously.
More than anything, I feel healthier by eating this.
(Having another piece with the mustard greens kimchi)
It tastes so clean.
- It's good for your body.
- I love kimchi.
- I think the kimchi will be good.
- Look at its color.
Is it aged kimchi?
- The seasoned raw tongue sole.
- Gosh!
Se Yoon loves that kind of kimchi.
- The very sour ones.
- Gosh, this is great!
The mustard greens kimchi is really good as well.
(How does the seasoned raw tongue sole taste?)
There's no other way to describe the sauce...
and the tongue sole is so chewy.
It looks like the ones served with raw fish naengmyeon.
The ones served with naengmyeon have a tougher texture.
- It has a fascinating texture.
- It's really savory.
- Gosh.
- You can feel the small bones,
but they make it taste better.
You can certainly feel them, but they don't get in the way.
- Like gizzard shads?
- They're easy to chew.
I didn't expect it to be like this.
The soup is so clear.
What about me and Seon Ho?
All right. Se Yoon mentioned this before.
He said the kimchi rights of the members should be protected.
I don't think people in the Joseon Dynasty...
would've eaten like this.
This is the precious kimchi handmade by the owner here.
- Gosh.
- You can't get seconds.
Kimchi from the Jeolla Province is a separate dish.
I did want to try the kimchi.
It does look good.
(Sniffing)
- Gosh.
- The kimchi does smell amazing.
This would be amazing as a kimchi stew.
The mustard greens kimchi was handmade here.
- It's amazing.
- Gosh, it's amazing.
- Gosh.
It's really good.
The kimchi tastes really good.
I'll eat it with the eel.
We're eating it with the eel.
Gosh.
It's been a while for me to finish the whole bowl.
(Clean bowl)
It has the oil of the eel.
This is the first time I finished the whole bowl this year.
I never usually drink all of the soup like this.
It's the taste of Jeolla Province.
(Jeolla Province's food never disappoints.)
By the way, is Jong Min being tortured somewhere?
- Right.
- Will we not see him?
I feel lonely eating on my own.
(He's having a bite now after earning some pocket money.)
(Citron Jong Min's lunch)
(Yukjeon and rice)
(The shrimp is a bonus.)
(Peeking)
- Does it taste good?
- Yes.
Is it the jeon?
(Don't be eyeing someone else's food, Jong Min.)
I have some yukjeon.
(He attempts to make a trade.)
Should we trade?
I'll give you some of my shrimp.
- How does that sound?
- That sounds good.
- It's a trade.
- Isn't that too much?
- Around this much?
- Yes.
- Thank you!
(His meal has become a lot more abundant thanks to her.)
I have to try different kinds of food.
- Enjoy your meal. Thank you.
- Enjoy your meal.
It's the yukjeon made with the two-plus grade beef.
I'll make sure to enjoy it.
(Eating)
(It's delicious.)
Gosh, I'm having pajeon with rice.
(This time it's a collaboration between pajeon and rice.)
(I don't know which punk sent me here, )
Gosh, I finished everything. My plate is clean.
(but I ate as much as I worked!)
(Helper)
(Joon is the helper.)
(Citizen)
(Se Yoon is the citizen.)
(The Hungry Lupin is still lying at this moment.)
(These two got on the car first.)
That was nice.
(Putting his thumb up)
The hint was hilarious.
- I went exactly with it.
- Right.
I didn't exaggerate one bit.
I know what you're like.
Just right now,
Se Yoon got all of the spotlight...
because of the bear hint.
I don't think there will be any issues for me...
at this rate.
(The two become quiet as Bear Se Yoon appears.)
(DinDin and Seon Ho get on as well.)
Let's set off!
(They head to the next spot.)
(No one knows about the helper except for the Hungry Lupin.)
We're setting off without Jong Min.
Where has Jong Min gone?
- He's been away for so long.
- When he left earlier,
it felt like he was just visiting the restroom.
I don't think he has even eaten.
Don't you know where he has gone?
I do.
So he was sent away by someone?
- He was sent away.
- It wasn't because of a mistake.
- Definitely.
- He would never say anything wrong.
I'm 100 percent certain the Hungry Lupin sent him away.
The Hungry Lupin sent him away on purpose?
Right.
He just didn't like Jong Min in general.
Jong Min didn't really close down on someone...
with a certain deduction.
This is a basic principle in the Mafia game.
The one who hasn't done much should be removed.
- Really?
- That's how suspicion is avoided.
Let's see how Se Yoon carries on with the game.
We'll see how much he pretends not to be the Hungry Lupin.
I found this so cute. He kept rolling his fingers.
Right. He couldn't keep his hands still.
(Anxious)
No way.
If you're not the Hungry Lupin,
you have to desperately say you're not.
- Desperately? Hold on.
- That means we're on the same team.
Listen to this. I was pointed at by that poor hint.
Falling for that is a big shock to me.
You and DinDin.
It's really baffling.
They all look like fools.
Everything is going according to the plan.
Justice should be served. Then they will know.
But I feel strangely bad that they suspect me.
Se Yoon, just say what's on your mind.
Who do you think it is?
I'll tell you who's not Hungry Lupin.
Yoo Seon Ho and DinDin.
These two suspect me, I don't think they're Hungry Lupin.
I suspected you 80 percent.
- But it went down to 50 percent.
- I see.
(Happy)
Honestly, I don't trust anyone but Sae Ho.
- You trust me, right?
- I'm sure it isn't Sae Ho.
- You're right.
- Are you suspecting me?
I'm not 100 percent sure.
- Really?
- I'm 100 percent sure about Sae Ho.
There's a possibility that it could be something shocking.
None of us is suspecting Jong Min.
- Right?
- Exactly.
He sent himself on purpose?
I think that's possible.
- If he were Hungry Lupin...
- Himself?
- Not to get caught?
- He can be really cunning.
He can use petty tricks.
(Jong Min was dragged away, not knowing what was going on.)
(It turns out it was Jong Min and Lee Joon's plan?)
(I'm hungry.)
I think we will find out once we go and see him.
For your information,
once you get there, you will be doing the last mission.
It is your last chance to get a hint.
- Okay.
- It's really important.
- We have to try hard to do well...
- Oh, dear.
- so we can get a hint.
- We should do that.
We have to succeed and get a hint.
- Se Yoon, then...
- Yes.
(With the identity of Hungry Lupin left mysterious, )
(they are heading to the next spot.)
- We're in trouble. What's that?
- What?
- Is that a mudflat?
- What's that?
- Are we going to a mudflat?
- Is there a mudflat?
- Now, we are...
- What are we doing?
(A wide mudflat)
We found out who Hungry Lupin is!
That's too much mud.
We've decided who it is.
The mudflat is so wide.
Isn't this the South Sea?
Why is the mudflat so big?
This is too much mud.
Unbelievable.
(This is all mudflats.)
What's that bridge? It's really long.
Is it a rainbow bridge?
Did you wonder where Jong Min was taken to?
Yes. Where is he?
What?
- What?
- He's a parking attendant. What?
What?
(Citron Jong Min, the parking attendant)
- What?
- What is he doing?
- What is he wearing?
- He's a human citron.
- He's a citron.
- He's become a citron.
(Hurry and get off.)
- What is this?
- What?
- What are you doing, Mister?
What are you doing here?
I don't know. Did I do something wrong?
(He doesn't seem to know why he was taken here.)
Your face... The makeup...
He was being exploited.
There's something you should know about Jong Min.
What did he do?
He was taken out by the helper's choice.
- Helper?
- Helper? What does that mean?
Who's the helper?
So, Hungry Lupin has a helper.
- I'm full now.
- Are you full?
(The existence of his assistant has become known to everyone.)
He's got a helper.
- But...
- So, two of us are lying.
Then, why did he pick me?
Why Jong Min?
So, you were taken away because the helper said so.
I was just taken to another place...
and had to make money to eat.
(Sae Ho quietly steps back.)
Who do you think is the helper?
What hint?
It's not me. Hang on.
- No. It's not me.
- Let me think.
Jong Min was taken out...
- by the helper's choice.
- He made the decision on his own?
We can't tell.
So it's 4 against 2, not 5 against 1.
- That's right.
- Two of us are lying now.
- So...
- The two people who are lying...
- Stay quiet.
- Why?
(The moment he starts talking, he falls under suspicion.)
- It's not me.
- It's you.
- Did you send me away?
- Is it me?
- It's not me.
- You're the helper.
- He's right.
- Did you do that?
Once I catch him, I won't let it slide.
- You are Hungry Lupin.
- Really?
And you tricked this innocent one into becoming your helper.
- Me?
- Yes.
- Then, did Joon send Jong Min away?
- He did?
- Was it you?
- No, I'm not.
(Did you send me away?)
- Is that true?
- I have no reason to do that.
- Why...
- Now that I think about it,
Joon was really bad at the games.
I can tell just by looking at your eyes.
(Madness)
You will be doing the mission here.
What is it?
You should get changed before the mission.
Jong Min has already changed.
You will change into the clothes for this place...
and gather again.
I went through a lot of hardships.
(Hurry and change your clothes.)
The weather is crazy today.
- It's hot.
- It's like summer.
Who on earth sent me away?
Who do you think it is?
It's Se Yoon or DinDin.
Is that what you think?
We also talked about it on our way here.
There was no reason to send Jong Min away.
- Exactly.
- He just wanted to send you.
- What's your identity?
- It's not me.
I know. He just sent me away for no reason.
(Happy)
Once we find out the helper,
you can say he hates you.
Exactly. So, I don't care...
who Hungry Lupin is. I'll just find the helper.
Good. You should try hard with that goal in mind.
Do you hate the helper more than Hungry Lupin?
(Proud)
- There are a lot of crabs here.
- Are there many crabs?
- You are right.
- They're Japanese ghost crabs.
Right.
We can eat Japanese ghost crabs, right?
- They are delicious.
- You can eat them.
- We can eat them, but...
- There are other crabs too.
This is amazing. It's getting into its home.
It's interesting that they go into their homes.
There's a mud hopper.
This is huge.
It's pretty.
(Udo Mudflat)
The bridge seen next to you...
is the longest pedestrian overpass in the country,
which is connected to the beautiful island of Goheung, U Island.
(But they will perform the mission on the ground.)
Your feet will be stuck.
You can't get your feet out.
This is really long.
This place will be covered with water.
Right.
(The worst place to fool the members)
- Hello.
Right.
You're in a mudflat.
- Yes.
- It's been a while.
- Right.
What shines...
as beautifully as Goheung's nature is...
your unity, right?
Is that so?
So, Hungry Lupin and the helper will do something...
to fail the mission on purpose.
Probably.
(Smiling)
All right. So,
- this is the last mission.
- It's not me.
We will set up the cameras first and tell you about it.
- Okay.
One, two, three.
(2 hours before Hungry Lupin's arrest)
- This is driving me crazy.
- Why?
The existence of the helper gives me a headache.
I have no idea who the helper is.
- It's not you, is it?
- I'm telling you it's not me.
- Now that we're at this...
- Why is everyone suspecting me?
To be honest,
I have no idea who it is.
You know who we should kill first in the Mafia Game.
- Who?
- The one who talks the most.
- Exactly.
- We should kill 1 of the 2.
It's upsetting.
(The one who talks the most)
The helper is DinDin.
When we were eating citron earlier,
Sae Ho took a really long time.
- What?
- Sae Ho took a long time.
- Right.
- After that, Joon finished it.
- Yes.
- One of them is the helper.
They are Hungry Lupin and the helper.
It didn't make sense. Those two ruined the game.
- Right.
- Exactly.
Why are they sticking together?
(Sae Ho is talking to Joon, the helper?)
They're alone.
(A rather suspicious scene)
- What?
- I get it.
All of a sudden? Wait. You two should go over there.
- All right. Say it.
- Okay.
- I get it now. Okay.
- Go ahead.
Is your brain working?
Hungry Lupin didn't know Jong Min was sent away.
The helper sent him.
- Right.
- That's true.
The helper knew that.
And Hungry Lupin was like, "What's going on?"
"I didn't do that. Why is he dragged out?"
- Exactly.
- Right.
- Joon is the helper.
- Why?
He sent Jong Min away. So he laughed a lot.
- Right.
- But Sae Ho was like,
"What? I didn't do anything."
"Why is he leaving?"
- He was as surprised as we were.
- Right.
So Sae Ho is Hungry Lupin, and Joon is the helper.
- What?
- Is that right?
- Am I Hungry Lupin?
- Right?
- Don't be ridiculous.
- And Joon is the helper.
You're the helper.
No! It's not me.
That's just what he says.
Why are you suspecting someone innocent?
The thing is, I thought one person...
- Gather around, guys.
- I was right.
- I'm telling you that's not it.
Why are you suspecting me all of a sudden?
(Groaning)
(Their feet sink in.)
Your feet don't sink in much there. Please stand there.
This is too muddy.
- This is bad.
- Help me.
This is...
- That doesn't matter.
- Look. They're sticking together.
You're mistaken.
If you keep being like this, we will have to suspect you.
All the pieces are falling into place.
You're getting it wrong. What are you talking about?
- What is he doing?
- Hang on.
- This is really...
- Stay there.
- No.
- All right.
Seon Ho, listen carefully from where you are now.
- It's so sticky.
- Here's the last mission.
It's Mudflat Impossible.
(Obstacles on the mudflats)
Five members will make a path...
by lying face down to make stepping stones.
If one member goes through all the obstacles,
passes the halfway point,
and grabs the flag without touching the mudflat,
the mission is complete.
(They succeed if the person on the bridge pulls out the flag.)
To go through the first obstacle,
you should zigzag through the three poles.
Then you should pass the halfway point.
(Section 2: Halfway point)
Do you see the hurdle there?
The person on the bridge should go over the hurdle.
Once you come back and pull out the flag, it's done.
- Jump over the hurdle?
- Yes.
- Okay. But...
- All right.
If you succeed in this mission,
I will give you a crucial hint.
You'll receive a crucial hint.
(They must succeed for a crucial hint.)
This person's a bit...
(Helper Joon must sabotage them.)
We must separate Joon and Sae Ho.
- Yes.
- That way, look.
- Jong Min.
- Jong Min...
- Jong Min, Sae Ho, - No.
- Se Yoon...
- Let's find Hungry Lupin later...
and win first.
- Yes.
- Let's strategize first.
I want DinDin to walk on the bridge.
Okay, I agree.
If we all do well and he somehow...
loses his balance on top...
- Then I'm guilty.
- Yes.
Then I'm the Hungry Lupin.
- Let's make a sturdy bridge.
- Okay.
What's wrong, guys? The citron...
I really tried to eat it.
He could've sacrificed himself even when he was Hungry Lupin.
Jong Min would never leave knowing he could eat eel.
That one mouthful...
I was guaranteed to eat one mouthful, okay?
- Yes.
- I could've had citron tea too.
(Sae Ho voices suspicion that Jong Min sent himself off.)
Can we play already? I'm as tall as Sae Ho now.
Let's play.
- Can we hurry?
- Let's do this.
- Do you have a plan?
- Yes. Let's go.
It's a struggle just to stand still.
This will take a long time.
It's not easy. It'll be a while.
Number one has to rush ahead.
If possible, stick your head into the bottom...
of the person in front.
That won't be a pretty sight.
I really don't like that.
(Punching)
I hate that idea.
We'll start the mission!
Ready, get set...
- Is this okay?
- Yes.
Can you handle this much pressure?
That's fine. I can manage.
Is this okay?
There's no way I'll fall off. Hang on.
I'm okay. Stay still.
Your mic's in the way. Just a minute.
I'm done. Okay.
I'm not okay.
Am I okay?
I'm still on top of you.
(Sae Ho goes ahead to extend the bridge.)
Wait. Hang on, Seon Ho.
(Acting annoyed for no reason)
No, wait. I'm not ready yet.
Stay closer to me. That's it.
- Gosh, you're big.
- This is...
I can't...
(Massive excuse of a bottom)
Look how big he is.
Joon, stay still.
Go!
(Screaming)
- Wait, stop.
- Don't overreact!
(You're too much.)
- Okay. Let's go.
- If we just keep doing this...
(The helper lets him go to stay safe.)
- Have you passed me?
- Wait. I'm still...
If we just keep doing this,
- there's no way we'll fail.
- Okay.
I'm just passing you.
- You're the sturdiest link.
- Okay, good.
- I'm fine.
- DinDin, where do I go?
- In front of Jong Min.
- To the front?
Position yourself slightly diagonally.
(Hungry Lupin is quiet too.)
(Moving forward)
- Sae Ho, you're totally fine.
- I'm good.
(Hungry Lupin candidate Sae Ho is doing well.)
I'm fine.
- Wait.
- Do I lower myself?
No, I'm not okay!
Stay still.
- We're totally okay.
- Are you done?
Wait. Keep still, Jong Min.
- Wait, Seon Ho.
- Okay.
(He passes safely, despite the ruckus.)
(They could succeed at this rate.)
We're totally okay.
(Stalling)
Joon's weird. Joon's acting strangely.
- What's wrong with you?
- Joon's being weird.
Go fast. I'm sinking.
Don't step on my spine.
- Keep still.
- Yes, that's fine.
That will do.
I'm 98.98 percent sure that Joon is the helper.
Don't you dare let me catch you. How dare you send me away?
You're on the right spot.
Okay.
Where do I go from here? Tell me the way.
We have to go round the halfway point.
I hoped to shake him off.
He didn't fall.
We were on hands and knees,
so I'll try to topple him by pretending to hold onto him.
(Hungry Lupin makes a move.)
Pretend it's a massage.
(Someone starts to act suspiciously.)
Wait. Hang in there.
You need to scoot back, Se Yoon.
Seon Ho's back is too small.
Are you okay?
(Spitting)
(Swaying)
I'll keep going.
(Seon Ho suddenly acts out.)
Hang on.
(Turning the halfway point)
Okay, good.
(I'm dying over here.)
- Hang on, Jong Min.
- Okay.
Aren't we guaranteed to...
(Jong Min has been making an extra big fuss on this mission.)
Hey!
(A clenched fist?)
Go up to the front.
(He leans on DinDin to stand up.)
Wait. Keep still.
- It's so darn far.
- No, don't. I'm tired.
Go slow. Okay. Yes.
(Keeping a distance on purpose)
- No, wait. Hang on.
- Okay.
(DinDin almost fell off.)
- Your clothes are muddy.
- Sorry.
(What a shame)
This means I'm at the hurdle.
Se Yoon has to be here.
Lie sideways.
Where?
Will you please move?
(Please, move quickly.)
- I should lie sideways?
- Yes.
Joon, you lie sideways too.
- Like this?
- Yes.
- I'm going forward.
- Shouldn't Se Yoon be here?
- No, you're fine.
- Keep going.
(He climbs onto Sae Ho's back.)
This will work.
- My face is getting dirty.
- Sorry.
- Don't get mud on my face.
- Sorry. I won't.
(Sae Ho creates extra space.)
(Next episode)
Now, we will...
(Time left to arrest Hungry Lupin)
(Time keeps passing.)
Don't trust him.
(Emotions run high and cracks form.)
(Everyone seems suspicious.)
(Doubts increase.)
(Did the helper betray Hungry Lupin?)
(Circumstances keep changing.)
(Don't let your guard down until the very end.)
(Who's the real Hungry Lupin?)
Gosh. He's not in his right mind.
He's insane.
(See you next week.)