(Specially today,)
(we film the opening
in a world of fantasy.)
(Lots of things to see,)
(to ride,)
(and to eat.)
(Let's go to the world of fantasy.)
(Unfortunately, however,)
(it started to rain
early in the morning.)
You don't have an umbrella?
- Hey, give him an umbrella.
- He needs one.
- Just in case.
- Don't try to be funny.
Why don't you have an umbrella?
- He gave it back.
- Yes.
- Why?
- He said he didn't need it.
- He refused it.
- This kind of rain is nice.
Yes. The weirder Joon is,
the better it is for us.
This feels great.
I just don't get you.
Do you like rain?
(During his trip
to Sin, Si, and Mo Islands)
I can't be bothered...
(He's mentioned it before.)
(It would be nice
to be in this kind of rain.)
(He's so consistent.)
I haven't been here in so long.
(It's 8 a.m.,
and the theme park isn't open yet.)
I can find my way
with my eyes closed.
Straight ahead is the store.
There's a zombie village.
A bit further on is the zoo.
Which way to my home?
- To Sangam-dong.
- I don't know the way.
I came here so many times.
We won't ride anything, will we?
- We can't if it rains.
- No.
- I can't do it.
- That's...
Why think of rides...
- when you can walk?
- Oh, I don't know.
(Coward number 2)
- Hello.
- Hi.
Joon doesn't care for umbrellas.
He returned his,
saying he didn't need it.
This kind of rain is a blessing.
- I offered him to share...
- I like it.
I offered to share mine,
and he sternly said, "Go away."
So I said, "Okay. Point taken."
He lives so close to here...
that he didn't get his hair done.
- He's that close.
- I see.
- He doesn't fear the rain.
- He can get wet.
It's 2 Days and 1 Night.
But I got here in 20 minutes.
- Does that make sense?
- But...
- It usually takes a few hours.
- You live next door.
- Yes.
- Stay dry.
This is romantic.
Jong Min looks really pleased.
"We can't ride anything if it rains,
right?"
(High hopes)
We can't ride anything.
That's great.
(It's a welcome rain
to these two who dislike rides.)
We came to Yongin,
which is a popular place...
to visit on the outskirts of Seoul.
- It's lovely.
- This is our destination.
Around this time
is when Sae Ho and Joon...
- It's their first anniversary?
- joined the group.
- That's right.
- Already?
(One stifling summer day
in August, 2024)
(To change things around
on 2 Days and 1 Night,)
(Sae Ho and Joon joined the family.)
(They underwent a tough hazing.)
(Now they have been with us
for four seasons.)
"So nice?"
(We laughed a lot
during the past year.)
(We are 2 Days and 1 Night.)
(We bring pieces
of our memories together...)
(to complete our own map.)
- Yes.
- Really?
- It has been a year.
- No way.
I made a lot of memories.
A year has passed already.
So today,
to celebrate the anniversary...
- "Goodbye, Cho Sae Ho?"
- To laugh a lot...
Come on.
- Don't be like that.
- For the past year,
I was pleased
to have been on the show.
- He's saying goodbye?
- I'll work even harder.
- Okay.
- No goodbye.
No goodbye.
To celebrate
their first anniversary,
so we can laugh even more...
and win the love of our viewers,
we'll go on Hoya and Joon's...
one-year celebratory trip.
- It's the Grab and Kill Tour.
- "Grab and Kill?"
Grab everything?
- Grab hold.
- What's "Hoya?"
- Cho Sae Hoya.
- I see.
It's from his name.
He mentioned it in the interview.
- He nicknamed himself?
- The crew contacted me.
I can't repeat all that was said,
but I said this and that
for over four hours.
What?
- Four hours?
- The interview?
What?
We stayed on the phone.
- For real?
- My gosh.
Weren't you the only one
to talk so much?
- How long was your interview?
- About 40 minutes?
- Forty minutes?
- Yes.
(Pretending he didn't hear)
He turned a 40-minute thing
into 4 hours?
The phone must've been so hot.
(Embarrassed)
- I don't see her.
- She's gone.
- Why didn't you meet up?
- The phone...
Here's why I came up
with the Hoya and Joon nicknames.
It's our one-year anniversary,
and I wanted a cute-sounding name
that would suit a one-year-old.
- Like a nickname?
- Yes.
I thought that would be nice.
Did your family
call you "Hoya" at home?
My elderly relatives would say,
"Hoya, did you eat?"
They called me that.
I used to be called Hoya too.
- He's Seon Ho.
- Yes.
He's Hoya too.
- It feels...
- Are they from Jeolla Province?
a bit contrived.
How do you feel?
You're making things up.
- No, I didn't make it up.
- You feel okay?
- I made up the four-hour interview.
- Did you?
- Yes.
- That was a lie?
You lied about that?
How long was it, then?
(Why would you make that up?)
It was just 20 minutes?
- It's Joon and Hoya's first year.
- Yes.
And it's been a year
since Hyun took over as director.
- Yes.
- Congratulations!
- It's Hyun's anniversary too.
- Is it really?
- Yes, you're Hyun.
- That's right.
Hyun.
The name of the tour,
"Grab and Kill Tour,"
came from a comment...
Se Yoon made during the last trip
that touched us all.
- That's where it came from.
- You had an idea?
I didn't, but we have a great crew.
We say random things,
but they pick them up
and turn them into content.
When did I say anything like that?
When did you say that?
For Joon and Sae Ho's
one-year anniversary trip...
- What do we want to do?
- Yes.
Call them Director Cho
and Director Lee...
and announce a new concept
where they just set off.
That could be pretty fun.
It would be amazing.
"Grab and Kill Tour"
where they practically kill us.
Something like that?
We asked Sae Ho and Joon
for a bucket list...
of what they'd like to do
with the members...
on their anniversary trip.
They had lots of good suggestions.
Doesn't Joon want to...
- walk across the country?
- No, I had realistic ideas.
- Ride a duck boat to Japan?
- There's nothing like that.
Today, we'll do things on Sae Ho...
and Joon's one-year anniversary...
bucket list as a group.
- Gosh...
- A bucket list?
Let me say something in advance.
I chose things that you'd loike...
- What?
- "Loike?"
What do we loike?
- Did you prepare this?
- "Loike."
(Melomashi)
- I chose...
- Was that a dialect?
things that you would like.
- But...
- "Loike."
Did you list things
you really wanted to do...
or add a few things
for entertainment's sake?
Rather than wonder
if it would make a good show,
- I listed what I wanted.
- Really?
That's what I told them.
I'm more worried about
what Joon said.
I'm most worried about him too.
He doesn't even remember.
- I really don't remember.
- Oh, dear.
I think I said things
that would be good for our program.
If things go wrong,
who will be held responsible?
It should be those two.
- Those two?
- Yes.
- If things go wrong?
They quit...
and we air
a goodbye Joon and Sae Ho special.
(Concerned)
- Forget about that.
- Yes.
Didn't you get a message
from the director?
"We'll end late tomorrow."
"Be prepared."
What was your reply?
- "I'll do my best."
- You'll do your best?
"Okay. Good luck this week."
I said, "Can't we stay even longer?"
What?
- Are you serious?
- Is that another lie?
- Let's see.
- Show us the text.
- Show us.
- Are you serious?
- Let's see it.
- What for?
Why does he keep lying?
Did that do you any harm?
I apologize.
(If it did, I'm sorry.)
Okay. As we did on their first trip,
you'll complete a mission
as a group.
You must buy lunch
with the allowance you win.
That's great.
The food here is good.
- It's good?
- First,
It's good.
Sae Ho...
We'll go
with Hoya's bucket list first.
- Really?
- Yes.
Let's do the usual cheer...
with the viewers before setting off.
Okay.
- To celebrate the anniversary?
- Yes.
Remember these members.
Anywhere in Korea,
wherever it may be.
We set off again, full of energy.
Will the trip make you laugh so much
that your belly aches?
Or will you end up
with high blood pressure?
Stay tuned and watch
our childish antics!
Let's get going!
Who we are?
2 Days...
- What?
- What was that?
What are you even doing?
"Who we are?"
- I was talking to our viewers.
- What was that?
That was weird.
You've been saying it for years!
"Who we are?"
- What was that?
- "Who we are?"
- "Who are we?"
- It felt like a quiz show.
- The rain stopped.
- It stopped.
(The weather's in their favor.)
"Who are we?"
(2 Days and 1 Night)
(Hoya and Joon's
1-year anniversary trip)
Let's set off
on the anniversary trip.
- Let's go!
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
You grew up nicely.
Thanks a lot, guys.
- What for?
- I lasted a year.
- You mean that?
- Seriously.
- You know...
- We got really close.
It felt like
it had been longer than a year.
Yes.
- For real?
- Yes.
It doesn't feel like
it was just a year.
It's because
they settled in right away.
- That's right.
- Yes.
During that one year, to me...
This isn't a lie. I'm not lying.
He needs a disclaimer.
- You all became special people.
- That's true.
Wherever I go,
when someone mentions one of you,
- It's extra pleasing.
- I lean in to listen.
- It's nice to hear.
- Yes.
That's true.
(Slightly moved)
- Where are we?
- What are we doing here?
You want to take photos. How sweet.
You can go inside.
- Into the toilet?
- Why?
- The toilet?
- We go into the toilet?
In here?
What is it?
(What awaits the members?)
What's this?
Are there clothes here?
Come to the world
- Of fantasy
- Do we go inside?
- Our faces are up there.
- What is this?
Our faces are up there.
What's this?
- You can go in there.
- What is this?
- Then you can get changed in there.
- Come to
Come on. What is this?
- Gosh, come on.
- I got my hair done.
Look what they gave me.
- What is this? Come on.
- You want me to put this on?
- What's this?
- Please go in and get changed.
- Why must I wear that?
- This is what Sae Ho wanted?
Are you serious?
My stylist already prepared...
- all of my outfits.
- What's this?
- What is this?
- I even got my hair done.
I got inner pants. What's going on?
You have inner pants?
I got a baby outfit.
What...
My pants... My gosh.
I don't have any pants to wear.
- You don't have pants?
- I guess you're going pantless.
What is this?
- Is everyone ready?
- Yes.
- You'll go out 1 at a time.
- Let me go out 1st.
(The first member comes out.)
It looks great.
(Is DinDin's outfit
rather ordinary?)
Everyone is complaining
in the changing room.
- But my outfit looks...
- It looks great.
- better than I thought.
- Yes.
So I wasn't that annoyed.
But everyone else was angry.
I stepped out to see
what was going on. My gosh.
(The other outfits
must not be plain at all.)
(Staff: Laughing)
I went to the beauty salon at 4 a.m.
Look what happened to me
within 20 minutes into our shoot.
(Laughing)
- All right.
- My gosh. Seriously.
(He gives off the vibe of a girl
one can't mess with.)
The level of resentment inside
is outrageous.
The members in the second half
are the highlight.
I'm curious about what we're doing.
(The members of unusual silhouettes
remain in the changing room.)
- Jong Min.
- Yes?
You're up next.
- I can just walk out?
- Yes.
It looks great on you.
What are you talking about?
No, it doesn't.
- How come you look so normal?
- Yes, my outfit is normal.
(He emerges from the fog.)
So this is on his bucket list?
Why is this on his bucket list?
(The granny is angry.)
But how can an old lady
have such defined shoulders?
How come your shoulders are
so broad? You're an old lady.
(Hoya)
- Hoya
- What?
Hoya
(Excited Hoya shows up.)
- What's this?
- Hoya
(Looking cute and cheerful)
(He's responsible
for this disaster.)
(He's the only one who's excited.)
I love it.
This outfit feels so cool.
So this is on your bucket list?
- Why?
- It's on my bucket list.
But you can easily do this at home.
Yes, I can.
But I can only do that
when we are together.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Let me fix this minor detail.
- What is it?
My gosh, What's he supposed to be?
No baby should look like that,
you know?
(Visually impactful)
He looks so scary for a baby.
(A cold gaze
with a rosy blush on his cheeks)
(Muscular arms)
Given his physique,
he must be on steroids.
(A muscular baby)
You know, you see this in movies.
He's like a lab-grown baby
from a failed genetic modification.
This baby looks so scary.
I like this ring, though.
- I can eat this, right?
- Of course.
- What?
- I like this accessory.
- Coming up next is...
- The highlight.
- an intense-looking lady.
- You know what?
- I fixed her up a bit.
- Great.
My gosh. Seriously.
You look like a cartoon character.
You know what?
I'm good at doing makeup.
- I can make it look classy.
- Should I do this?
(Cameraman: Laughing)
He looks so ugly.
(Laughing)
(This irresistible lady
made everyone laugh.)
(Laughing)
(I am...)
(so pretty.)
(Beauty is my weapon.)
(The makeup artist is
super satisfied.)
Hoya. Joon.
(They burst into laughter
when she calls their names.)
Hoya. Joon.
(Impressed)
Why are you doing this to us?
What have you planned for us?
I just wasted some good money
at the salon. Don't you agree?
- You...
- Yes.
- You can pull off 1,000 characters.
- He's a pro.
- This is so funny.
- Seriously.
- What is on your bucket list?
- Gosh.
To celebrate his first anniversary
on the show,
he wanted to wear group costumes
with everyone...
and take a family picture.
- So that's what we prepared.
- Yes.
Hoya and Joon would be twins.
You guys are their grandma, dad,
mom, and older sister.
- He's the dad?
- I'm the dad?
- I can't be married to her.
- I see.
- Come here, honey.
- Dad, come this way.
- My gosh.
- What if she beats him?
(I don't want to go to her.)
I told you to square your shoulders
when you come over.
Square your shoulders.
Show them your teeth.
- Okay.
- Great.
- I love you.
- Yes.
And Hoya came up with a rule too.
Everyone must be encouraging,
even when someone messes up.
We'll laugh at everything
anyone says today.
Everyone should participate.
I want us...
- To participate. To be happy.
- to be a happy family today.
So I want us to have
stronger teamwork than ever today.
- I want us to get along.
- Yes.
All right.
(What sort of day
awaits the family today?)
(Kissing)
All right. It's time
to take your family picture.
- Yes.
We're going to take it
in the photo booth behind you.
But your job won't be that simple.
All of you must take pictures...
alternating between the two booths.
I bet we only get ten seconds.
You can take eight pictures
at each booth.
You can pick four pictures
from each booth.
Okay. What next?
For each picture
that clearly shows...
all of your eyes, nose, and mouth,
we will give you two dollars
for your allowance.
Then the maximum amount
of money we can earn...
- is 16 dollars.
- That's correct.
We must go back and forth
at the right time.
- That's right. Yes.
- We don't have to hurry.
- We can just time it well.
- Of course.
- We just need four good pictures.
- Right.
We just have to gather our faces.
(Like this)
I've taken pictures at the booth
with my family.
My son is short.
I had to move back a little more.
When he tried to lower his head,
I made him stand tall.
Like how he usually stands.
Then I was leaning on the wall.
I was leaning on the wall
completely.
- I made him stand tall.
- Okay.
Only our eyes, nose, and mouth
have to show, right?
- Just our eyes, nose, and mouth.
- They must be in the picture.
No, you guys have to
adjust the height.
We'll start right away
once he gives you the sign.
You're twins. So the three of you
will do it together.
- The three of us should do it.
- Sure.
- The three of you here.
- You go in the front.
Come on in.
- What?
- Let's go.
- Behind Joon.
- Five seconds.
Come on in.
(Run, everyone.)
- Behind Joon.
- Five seconds.
Jong Min in the front.
Hurry. Three, two, one.
Come on in now.
- What?
- Hurry.
- Go to the other booth.
- My face is in it.
- Hurry up.
- Go to the other booth.
(Did they succeed
with the first picture?)
(Jong Min's mouth is missing.)
(Let's go to the other booth first.)
- Go to the other booth.
- Hurry up.
- My face is in it.
- Five, four... Hurry.
- Three,
- Three.
two, one.
- We must go to the other booth.
- We must go.
- Hey.
- Gosh, hurry.
- Se Yoon.
- We only get five seconds.
(Hoya left too soon.)
- We must go to the other booth.
- We must go.
- Hey.
- Gosh, hurry.
- Se Yoon.
- We only get five seconds.
- What is this?
- Your face isn't in it.
What is this? This is way too fast.
(But their time is already up.)
- What? Go to the other booth.
- It's going way too fast.
- You want us to have no money.
- What's this?
(Laughing)
- What's wrong with him?
- My gosh. How...
Gosh, we don't have much time.
- What is this?
- This is too little time.
- Gosh, we don't have much time.
(Taking a family picture
is such a challenge.)
- No way. This is over now.
- Gosh.
Go to the other booth.
(He takes a picture all by himself.)
- Come back here!
- My gosh.
(I won't let you get away
with this.)
Five, four, three,
two, one.
(But they smile
when they take pictures.)
- We got it.
- Move!
- Go to the other booth.
- We got it. Move!
- We got it.
(They run over to the other booth
as soon as they succeed.)
- We can't.
- The time is up for this one.
(Again,
Hoya is the first one to arrive.)
- How many seconds?
- It's over.
Come back. This isn't possible.
The timing won't work.
(3 pictures of Hoya)
We only have a second left.
I noticed that the timing was off.
What is this?
Hey.
(So far, they only succeeded
in one picture.)
(Is this even possible?)
(Let's not give up.
Let's keep going.)
- What is this?
- We have five seconds left.
- Hey.
- Three, two, one.
Only stick out your face.
(They succeeded at the blue booth.)
- Go.
- We got it.
- Seven seconds. Six,
- Hurry.
- five,
- We must go back.
- four, three,
- Three,
- two...
- two, one.
- We have to get this one.
- Hey, you're not in it.
- No.
- No, it starts here.
Seriously. We have a second left.
- All right. Five. Hurry up.
- Four,
three, two...
(They pick up the speed
after succeeding 2 times in a row.)
- Let's go.
- Go to the other booth.
- Hurry.
- Move.
- Five, four... Hurry.
- Come over here.
- Hurry up.
- Five.
- Four,
three, two, one.
- We got it. Go over.
- Hey, we can't.
- Go.
- It's over.
- I give up.
- How many seconds?
It's over there.
- Go.
- We'll never have enough time.
The timing is off.
- Three, two, one.
- Three, two...
- We must get four pictures here.
- Hey, you weren't in it.
- No.
- We must take it here.
- Stay here.
- They said we couldn't do it.
- They said we had to move around.
- Let's go.
- Just pretend to go there.
- Go and fail.
- Hey. Five.
- Okay.
(Grandma was a master cheater.)
- You must go to the other booth.
- I did.
- Four, three,
- It won't work.
- There was no time left.
- two, one.
(Come here, Hoya.)
(They got the last picture
by cheating.)
(The game is over.)
We must pick the ones
with all of our faces.
With all of our faces.
(Hoya and his sister
pick out the photos.)
- This has all of our faces.
- No, not this one.
- His mouth isn't in it.
- Right.
- Don't pick that one then.
- One, two...
- His mouth isn't in it.
- Why give us only five seconds?
Come on. This is so irritating.
Who would pay money
to take pictures like this?
This one. Here.
- This one is good, right?
- Yes.
- All of our faces show in this too.
- Yes, that one too.
- We're good, right?
- Yes.
This is more than enough.
Our photos are being printed.
(How much money
can the members earn?)
All right.
Give us the pictures first.
Let us review the pictures
for a moment.
Hey, guys.
You guys did a great job.
(Getting nervous for some reason)
I told you all of your eyes, nose,
and mouth must show.
- Yes.
DinDin, look at the photos.
The pictures on the bottom...
Only parts of Jong Min's mouth
were in the pictures.
(Grandma is flustered.)
(It seems all of their faces
are in the pictures.)
(But Jong Min's mouth wasn't
in the pictures.)
- Why...
- Jong Min.
(Distancing)
- Why?
- Hold on.
We're supposed to smile today.
You look handsome
without your mouth.
- This is great.
- Really?
Today is
all about giving compliments.
- So...
- You know what?
If everything goes well,
it won't be fun.
- Right.
- It's great that...
Jong Min messed up big time!
- Gosh, this was great.
- We don't have to criticize him.
But we can ask him.
- This is pretty good.
- We got a lot of pictures.
- Yes. Six photos.
- Per...
- Per picture, you'll get 2 dollars.
- It's 12 dollars then.
- Six of your pictures will count.
- That's not bad.
- You'll get 12 dollars.
- Okay!
Great.
- We can only get two churros.
- All right. Here's your allowance.
Are we going to get on the ride?
No.
(Mom is a scaredy-cat.)
- Everyone, Hoya...
- Hoya.
loved amusement rides...
since he was in his mother's womb.
- I loved them.
- Good for you.
This is exactly what he said.
- So?
- How could he know he liked them...
- even before he was born?
- That's what I said?
- No way.
- Sae Ho.
Hoya loved going
to amusement parks...
since he was in his mother's womb.
(Writer: Laughing)
- I see.
- I love going to amusement parks.
Hoya said that
getting on rides was...
- on his bucket list.
- I'm serious.
This time, all of you will go
and get on an amusement ride.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- What is this?
- I love it.
We'll throw up
even on a pirate ship.
- Jong Min and I will throw up.
- I did.
Same here.
I really can't go on that.
You'll be fine once you get on it.
- Let's go.
- Mom.
- I'll get going, Mom.
- Okay. Go ahead, son.
- You're my wife.
- I need to watch our stuff here.
- Mom, hurry.
- Mom.
Are you sure this will be safe?
Mom. You'll have to ride it.
Hey, it's not suitable for the elderly
and people in poor health.
- What?
- Mom.
- You were born in 1979.
- Over there.
- It's not suitable for the elderly.
- Let's go.
It's okay.
Mom.
Mom, hurry up.
Give your mommy a kiss.
Give me a kiss.
My son, give me a kiss.
You too, my daughter.
Why is this on your bucket list?
I love amusement rides.
- My bucket list is...
- Yes?
riding all the roller coasters
in the world.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Mother, will you be okay?
- If...
(Jong Min slows down
as he doesn't want to get on it.)
- What?
- Mother?
Gosh, it said
it wasn't suitable for the elderly.
But they're making me get on it.
- What?
- Hello.
- Say hello.
Hello.
Hello. Is this really scary?
- It's fun. It's not scary.
- Gosh.
- Really?
- Pair up.
- What?
- Could you stand here facing me?
- All right.
- Hello.
- They're already on it.
Are you guys ready for it?
- No. Not at all.
- Yes.
- I love it.
- I'm not ready!
This is considered
the most thrilling ride here.
You can earn more allowance
on the roller coaster.
Two of you will ride
the roller coaster.
They will present the question.
(The 6 presenters
will sit in front of them.)
A letter will be written
on their hands.
(A letter is written
on their hands.)
- You must combine the 12 letters...
- What?
- to come up with a word.
(They must look at the letters
and put them together...)
(to find the right answer
that fits the category.)
We'll sit in the back
and look at the letters...
when they raise their hands.
- Okay.
- That's it.
(Here's an example.)
(Category: 4-character idiom,
3 possible right answers)
(They must combine the letters
to find the right answers.)
(Then they can rack up
more allowance.)
(There are 12 letters
and 3 possible right answers.)
(But they must do this
while riding the roller coaster.)
We must say the right answer...
- once we get back?
- Right.
When you come back,
I'll ask, "What's the right answer?"
- That's when you can answer it.
- We must look behind?
Each right answer
will earn you two dollars.
Okay.
Each pair can earn
as much as six dollars.
If all 3 pairs succeed,
you can earn 18 dollars in total.
Then here's what we need to do.
We must pair up first.
- It's...
- In my opinion,
Se Yoon,
Jong Min, and Seon Ho
aren't good with roller coasters.
- The rest of us... Yes.
- We must split them up.
- Joon and Jong Min should pair up.
- That sounds about right.
Se Yoon and I will pair up.
Seon Ho and Sae Ho should pair up.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Then who's the first pair?
Get on the roller coaster now.
(How much money
can the members earn?)
- Will you be okay?
- I'll go first.
Hold on. What do I do with this?
Don't worry, Jong Min.
(Glancing)
There must've been fat people...
who couldn't ride it...
because they couldn't put on
the seatbelt.
(Is it possible to be turned away
because of the seatbelt?)
You'll have no problem riding it.
Is that so?
(Disappointed)
- So...
- Gosh, I'm so nervous!
Why is this on his bucket list?
(It's difficult to understand
Hoya's bucket list.)
- Sae Ho.
- Hey.
- You got this!
You got this!
Wait. The safety bar is still up.
- Lower it.
- I have to do it?
Why did it go back up?
- They'll do it for you.
- This is weird.
- Please help them.
- Gosh, the bar is going down.
- Why did it go back up?
- Sir, this isn't coming down.
(Gesturing with urgency)
This is safe, right?
- It is.
- This is good, right?
- You never know. Jong Min.
- Gosh, hold on. This...
You all know what you have to do,
right?
- Yes, we do.
- We'll begin.
- You...
- I'll take care of everything.
- Have fun.
- Don't worry.
What? They're going.
- What? Hold on.
- They're four-character idioms!
- We'll be back.
- They're four-character idioms.
(Jong Min, you're in trouble now.)
They're four-character idioms.
(Thanks to him,
Jong Min loosens up.)
- Don't worry.
- We'll be back.
- They're 4-character idioms.
- Jong Min, bye.
- I don't...
I don't think Jong Min knows
what he's riding now.
- Gosh. This is scary.
- Jong Min.
- Look at that.
- Joon.
- My gosh. That's way too high.
- Why is it so high?
It's been so long...
- since I got on a ride.
- It rained a lot.
Jong Min, now...
Hold on. I'm a bit scared.
(Their upper bodies are almost
perpendicular to the tracks.)
- Gosh.
- Oh, my.
Why am I scared?
I usually don't get scared.
Gosh, hold on. This is...
- It's way too high.
- Gosh, this...
It's way too high.
- Jong Min, relax.
- What's going on?
- What's that?
- What?
(Presenting the letters
without a heads-up)
- Jong Min, relax.
- What's going on?
- What's that?
- What? Did we start?
- What?
- You must give us a heads-up!
- Do that again.
I couldn't see anything!
You must give us a heads-up!
- You can't surprise us.
- I was looking at the view.
- What a great view. Jong Min.
- Show us one more time.
The view there is amazing.
(A dizzying view)
(Glancing)
- Forget about the view.
- Jong Min, we'll drop at 90.
Hey.
- My gosh, we're going up.
- What's going on?
I have a bad feeling about this.
- This is bad. We're at the peak.
- Gosh, the view...
Please hold onto
the safety bar tightly.
- Hold on tight.
- I'm so scared.
- It's so scary.
- I shouldn't put my hands up.
- Three, two, one.
- I can't.
- Here comes the drop!
- Gosh, it's...
My gosh.
(The moment of the descent
is about to hit them.)
(Descending)
No!
(His head drops low
as soon as it goes down.)
(Screaming)
Hey. My gosh.
(The letters are revealed
for the second time at the drop.)
(This time,
they're doing jazz hands.)
(But Jong Min can't even look
at the letters.)
(Joon is doing his best
to hang in there.)
(They must look at the letters
to figure out the right answers.)
(The first sudden descent
ends in a matter of seconds.)
I couldn't even see a letter.
(The same goes for Jong Min.)
(This time, they take turns
to show the letters.)
(Sad, bearing, too much, bad)
(Find 4 4-character idioms.)
(Misery, company, rind, trust)
(Sad, bearing, too much, bad)
(Joon tries to keep his eyes open
to earn more allowance.)
My legs are in the air.
- My gosh.
- Jazz hands.
(Was Joon able to see the letters?)
Did you see Jong Min just now?
Is he dead?
- He was like this.
Will they raise their hands
when the roller coaster goes down?
No. They have their own plan.
They will show the letters
several times.
- But...
- They just did it.
(Actually,
as for these brave presenters...)
Ready, set, go.
(On the verbal order
of the main writer...)
Go.
- Jazz hands.
(They're perfectly in sync
for each section.)
- We'll go with the rainbow one.
- Gosh!
Rainbow!
(Loves, in, all, table,
misery, company, rind, trust)
(Sad, bearing, too much, bad)
Please stop this.
(Joon has gotten used to
the roller coaster now.)
(He begins to see
the letters clearly.)
(Jong Min's situation
hasn't changed.)
I hate this.
(Laughing)
(Bouncing)
(He can't lower his guard
even for a moment.)
It's time. Let's begin. Go.
Let's go. One, two.
(He almost missed his chance
as he was busy laughing.)
(Loves, in, all, table,
misery, company, rind, trust)
(Sad, bearing, too much, bad)
This is the worst.
(He couldn't open his eyes
even once.)
(And he's arrived.)
Show me the letters!
Did you see them?
Jong Min, you kept your head down.
You didn't make any effort to look.
(We shot the crown
of Jong Min's head for 3 minutes.)
This is impossible.
Your head was completely down.
It was so scary.
- Gosh.
- This was fun.
Show us now!
Show us the letters!
(Dear customer, the ride is over.)
Why aren't you showing us
the letters?
You're back.
Are you okay? He's saying that
you didn't show him anything.
- They didn't show us.
- What's the answer?
Too much is as bad as too little.
Bearing in mind all the time.
Misery loves company.
(Too much is as bad as too little.
Bearing in mind all the time.)
(Joon said 3 4-character idioms
right away.)
Joon answered.
- He answered them all.
- He did.
(Will his 3 answers be correct
in his 1st attempt?)
- He answered them all.
- Two of them are correct.
Well done.
(There must be trust
between friends.)
(Bearing in mind all the time.)
(Misery loves company.)
(2 of them are correct.)
The 1st team got 2 answers correct.
- I did my best.
- Well done.
It's not scary.
(Shaking)
It's not scary?
Se Yoon, you can still give up now.
- You can still give up now.
- What?
You can still give up now.
Seriously. I'm not joking.
(DinDin and Se Yoon get on
with a lot of worries.)
- Gosh.
- Do you...
- need anything?
- No.
Hey.
- The seat is too small for me.
- Please get ready.
- This is...
- Excuse me.
Can someone take a look over here?
- Se Yoon says that it's small.
- The seat is too small.
No, it's okay.
(Requesting emergency assistance)
Hang on.
- My goodness.
- He must be serious.
(Pressing with all his might)
- The pressure is for safety.
- Okay.
Safety is the most important.
DinDin, Se Yoon.
This time, it's movies and dramas.
- Movies and dramas?
- Yes.
How many movies and dramas
are there?
- Are there three?
- Yes.
I know many movies and dramas.
"The Wild Days."
- "Sandglass."
- All right.
- It may not be four characters.
- "Autumn in My Heart."
(The answers may not be
four characters.)
Keep your back straight,
and look ahead.
You can stay still this way.
Okay.
- You can do it.
- Let's go.
Se Yoon, relax.
You're doomed.
They think that it won't be scary.
- "Oldboy."
- Please run it slowly.
- Yes.
- "Oldboy."
Let's go!
Show us the answers.
I weigh 120kg.
I got a health checkup yesterday,
and I weighed 122kg.
I'm the only one with shoulders
wider than the seat.
How did you position your shoulders?
This might hurt me.
- Push them back like this.
- But this is...
- Slightly.
- What's this?
Slightly.
(They blew
their first chance for nothing.)
- That's it?
- Hey, we were discussing.
Se Yoon's seat was too small,
so we were discussing.
(They missed the letters...)
(while the ride gets closer
to the peak.)
(Se Yoon's eyes are losing focus.)
We have to look forward.
I don't think I can.
- When you look ahead...
- Are we going down?
When you look ahead, it's not scary.
Please hold onto...
- Goodness.
- When you look ahead...
When you look ahead, it's not scary.
(Moaning)
- Oh, no.
- Three, two, one.
(Exclaiming)
Two, one. Descent.
(The letters were shown
for quite a long time.)
(He closed his eyes
and couldn't see anything.)
(Screaming)
(They let themselves go
on the roller coaster.)
- My gosh.
- I couldn't see it.
(In the flat section,
they have a moment to breathe.)
We're going to do the wave.
Ready, set, go.
- One, two.
Go.
(Yoo, gye, sae, bae)
- "Yoo, gye..."
- "Yoo, gye, sae..."
(Deul, lang, mi, po)
(Look for 3 movies or dramas)
(Shin, eui, tae, sae,)
(deul, lang, mi, po)
- "Yoo, gye..."
- "Yoo, gye, sae..."
(They saw a few letters
before going down.)
"Yoo, gye, sae, gae."
- "Yoo, gye, sae, gae."
- "Yoo, gye, sae..."
"Yoo, gye, sae, gae."
("Yoo, gye, sae, gae" echoes
in the amusement park.)
Thanks to Joon, we answered two.
- Right.
- I know. Without Joon...
Which characters did you see?
They're much harder to see
than you think. It's quick.
You couldn't see any of the letters?
When going up, I saw them briefly.
They're dead. Se Yoon is dead.
(Laughing)
Se Yoon passed out.
- "Yoo, gye, sae..."
- "Yoo, gye, sae, gae."
"Yoo, gye."
(Moaning)
Here it is.
- "Deul, lang."
- "Tae, sae."
(Shin, eui, tae, sae)
(Yoo, gye, sae, bae)
"Mol, ra, sae, gae."
- "Mol, ra, sae, gae?"
- "Mol, ra, sae, gae."
(I don't know anything.)
Please get ready for the rainbow.
Go.
Rainbow.
(Yoo, gae, sae, bae, shin, eui,
tae, sae, deul, lang, mi, po)
- I see "mi."
- "Deul, lang..."
(Meanwhile, Se Yoon caught "mi.")
One more time.
(Excited DinDin the Kid)
(Donald Fatty)
One more time.
(We go once again as he requested.)
One, two.
- What's that?
- I can't see any.
I can't see them at all.
(He's so excited
that he reveals his front teeth.)
(He's still being Donald Fatty.)
I couldn't see them.
(How many answers will they guess?)
"Sae, gae."
(DinDin keeps repeating
"sae" and "gae.")
"Sae, gae."
(Se Yoon's soul hasn't
returned yet.)
"Sae, gae." What could it be?
"Mol, ba."
I might have seen "Titanic."
I also saw "sae" and "gae."
(My head is completely empty.)
(DinDin and Se Yoon return safely.)
"Deul, mol, deul."
Moon Se Yoon.
- I couldn't see anything.
- Really?
- Everyone, what's the answer?
- He cried.
- Oh, no.
- He's crying.
- Se Yoon is crying.
(Se Yoon is crying?)
(There are definitely tears
in Se Yoon's eyes.)
He's really crying.
He really is.
(His tears match his makeup.)
- He's so ugly.
- He's crying.
All right.
- Gosh.
- What's the answer?
"Titanic."
"Sandglass."
I saw the word "bad."
"Bad Housewife?"
"Bad..."
- He's crying.
- I also saw "mi."
"Bad Married Couple?"
(He wipes off his tears first.)
- Three.
- "Bad Married Couple."
- Two.
- How many did we get?
So far,
- none of them are correct.
- What?
- Seriously?
- What are you doing?
"Titanic."
- He says that it's wrong.
- It's wrong.
- You have three seconds.
- "The Wild Days."
- In 3,
- "200 Pounds Beauty."
- two,
- "The Witch."
- one.
- "Sandglass."
Wrong.
- "Lovers in Paris."
- This team got...
- zero answers.
- What?
What are the answers?
(What are the answers that
DinDin and Se Yoon failed to get?)
("Yumi's Cells,")
("New World," "Veteran")
(0 correct answers)
We thought that
the titles were four characters.
- That's not true.
- You didn't explain it to us.
I'll go again with Se Yoon.
- No.
- Let us go one more time.
- Let me stop crying.
- Come on.
I'll cry only once a day.
- All right.
- Cry only once a day.
Let's ride it together at the end
as a celebration.
- Let's do that.
- To take a group photo.
They don't show you
when you're going down.
- Suddenly, while going up...
- Really? Okay.
- You have to keep watching them.
- Let's stay focused.
- Please get on the ride.
- They keep riding it.
Are you okay?
(They prepare
the next question calmly.)
- Take off your suspenders.
- My suspenders?
(The last team, Seon Ho and Sae Ho)
- Jong Hyun.
- What's the category?
- What's the keyword?
- All right.
We didn't set it up intentionally.
- But it's capital cities.
- What?
(The question went to Seon Ho
who's terrible at capital cities.)
- Capital cities.
- I don't know many capital cities.
- I don't know any.
It's very easy.
- Let's go.
- We can do it.
- Ottawa, Canada's capital city.
- You can do it.
Win six dollars so that we can eat.
Just keep looking forward.
What's that?
It's okay. We'll be going up there.
That's the hard part.
- They might show us suddenly.
- Doesn't it feel refreshing?
- You're okay, right?
- I'm okay for now.
Keep your back straight
and look forward, okay?
We're going up.
They'll raise their hands suddenly.
Look at your line.
I'll look at mine.
Once you read yours, read mine too.
- What's going on?
- What?
"La."
- I can't read the characters.
- I saw "la" and "am."
- "La, am?"
- "La, am."
(Seon Ho already read two letters.)
That's how they raise their hands?
We're here now.
(They arrive at the peak
with a big gain.)
That's the hard part.
"La, am."
They'll raise their hands again.
Amsterdam.
(He thinks of "Amsterdam"
before going down.)
- Amsterdam.
- Okay.
(Hoya's favorite moment)
(A thrilling drop)
(Hoya is excited.)
Remember "Amsterdam."
- Amsterdam?
- Yes, Amsterdam.
(Team Seon Ho and Sae Ho
started off smoothly.)
(Grandma Jong Min
is still out of it.)
- Jong Min.
- That's better.
You seem out of it.
(I'm not actually laughing.)
Are you okay, Jong Min?
Let's stop with the rides.
Let's have a corn dog instead.
- Gosh.
- Isn't it fun?
- Get ready, set, go.
- It's not fun,
- but I can bear it.
- One, two.
(Ha, reu, deu, deu)
(Ma, seu, la, li)
(Am, peu, dam, tae)
(Guess the 3 capital cities.)
- "Ha, ma."
- "Ha."
"Ha."
- What did you say?
- "Ha."
- Start.
- What?
(Ha, reu, deu, deu)
(Ma, seu, la, li)
(Am, peu, dam, tae)
- "Seu, peu?"
- What? I can't see them.
(Sae Ho saw "seu" and "peu.")
Go. Rainbow.
"Am, peu."
- "Am, peu."
- "Am, peu?"
A capital city with "peu" in it?
- It's Prague.
- Prague.
- Amsterdam, Prague.
- We got 2.
- We have 1 left.
The last 1 has 3 characters.
This is good.
Both of them have their heads up.
- Seon Ho and Sae Ho.
- Both of them have their heads up.
This is looking good.
(They can feel the successful energy
under the track.)
They're raising their hands again.
(Ha, reu, deu, deu, ma, seu,
la, li, am, peu, dam, tae)
- I see "seu."
- "Ma."
What? "Ma."
- Amsterdam, Prague.
- I see.
"Ma" is missing.
What could it be?
- What's Spain's capital city?
- Madrid.
It must be Madrid.
- You're right.
- Yes.
Madrid, Prague,
- Amsterdam. We got it.
- Amsterdam.
Okay.
- Isn't it fun?
- It's not fun, but it's doable.
I'm a little bummed out because...
- You couldn't enjoy it?
- I couldn't completely enjoy it.
Having the questions made it
better for me.
It made me focus.
Let's go back while laughing.
They look...
This is good.
- We saw them all.
- Nice.
What are the answers?
Amsterdam, Madrid, Prague.
- We got them all.
- Really?
You got all three correct.
(All three answers are correct.)
(Amsterdam)
(Prague)
(Madrid)
(3 correct answers)
- Wasn't it okay?
- It was doable.
We got them all.
- Good job.
- Now,
I'll give 10 dollars to the 3 teams.
- We earned ten dollars.
- Okay.
Can all of us ride it
one last time to celebrate?
Can I sit in the front?
All of us together one last time.
Let's sit in the front.
Come on.
- It's my wish.
- It'll be on camera.
- Where is he?
- Sit in the very front.
- Hurry up, Jong Hyun.
- They'll be filming it.
- Get on.
Hurry over here, Jong Hyun.
- Okay.
- We don't have much time.
(Director Joo got on
in place of Jong Min.)
Joo Jong Hyun is my savior.
The door is opening.
- Hoya.
- Yes!
All right.
(The examiners ride it again
because they want to.)
(Making a new memory
for Hoya and Joon's anniversary)
- Pose for the photo.
- We're friends!
(A roller coaster's highlight
is taking photos.)
(Roller coaster ride on Hoya
and Joon's 1st year anniversary)
(Sae Ho closed his eyes.)
(Jong Min, lift your head.)
(30 seconds before Se Yoon's crying)
(Hoya's bucket list is
a huge success.)
(What's next on Hoya
and Joon's bucket list?)
The weather got much better.
- Isn't it fun?
- Yes.
It's fun.
Being at an amusement park
makes me feel good.
Right? It makes you
feel like a child again.
(Full of excitement)
(2 Days and 1 Night family goes back
to being children again.)
(Cute)
(Adorable)
Hello.
Which school do you go to?
(Students who came as a group)
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Study hard.
What's this again?
- What's this?
- It's a cable car.
- A cable car?
We must be going on a cable car.
(Glancing)
That's what I mentioned. It's fun.
- That one?
- It's extremely fun.
I can't ride that.
It's really fun.
A long time ago, on a music show,
- I had to sing while riding that.
- What?
- On a music show?
- Yes.
While being on that ride.
Really?
(Jong Min's solo performance
14 years ago)
(Stay strong, Jong Min!)
(Screaming)
(Boys and girls)
(Singing passionately
with his eyes closed on the ride)
Many singers did that back then.
They performed at amusement parks
or swimming pools.
- But you can't get on rides.
- No.
It was very difficult.
I will work hard.
(Jong Min was full of passion
back then.)
Get out of the cable car.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Hey, guys.
There's slushy.
- I like that.
- Let's get some slushy.
- It's really delicious.
- Let's share one.
- Ask if you can get a taste.
- Oh, come on.
- Go and ask.
- Hurry up.
I don't have money.
- There's melon flavor.
- My goodness.
- Hello.
- We have no seven dollars to spend.
- It's seven dollars.
- We have no money, Grandma.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey.
Let's pick two people
for the slushy.
- No way.
- Listen to me.
- We have a lot more to do.
- No.
- We have to save money.
- We don't have much money now.
It's useless to save money
right now.
Are you thirsty or not?
- Just drink water.
- Drink water.
- Let's enjoy ourselves.
- We have to save money.
Can you pay with KakaoPay?
Let's not do this.
- But I want some.
- Give us more money.
No.
He has total control over the money.
Let me have one.
No, we have no money.
Are we just going to walk all day?
"Are we just going to walk?"
These corn dogs are amazing.
Go and ask if you can get a taste.
Those corn dogs are to die for.
They look delicious.
These corn dogs are delicious.
Grandma wants one cheese corn dog.
Can you buy me one corn dog?
- Corn dogs look delicious.
- By the way,
Grandma Jong Min kept talking
about corn dogs today.
Which one do you want?
A slushy or a corn dog?
- Right now, I want some slushy.
- Then let's just go.
No, corn dog.
(A quick change in attitude)
Jong Min kept saying
that he wanted it.
(He finally got his wish.)
All right.
(Half of the corn dog disappears
in an instant.)
(2 Days and 1 Night family shares it
and takes a bite each.)
Give some to the son in the back.
(Happiness in 5 dollars)
(Eating)
(Take a look again
for remaining crumbs.)
(Glancing)
Mom.
- What's wrong with you?
- What?
People might think that
I don't treat you well at home.
- Everyone, let's get going.
- Let's go.
- Goodness.
- Is everyone here?
Yes, Dad.
Honey, everyone is here.
- That's right.
- Here we go.
- Let's go.
Dad, please drive safely.
Wasn't Hoya's bucket list nice?
- Yes, it wasn't bad.
- I'm satisfied with it.
- Yes.
- I liked it. It'd been a while.
Was it difficult only for Jong Min?
It was difficult.
Aren't we going to do
what's on Joon's bucket list next?
I'm worried about
Joon's bucket list.
To be honest, I'm a little scared.
- Why?
- Joon is weird too.
- My beloved Joon.
- Yes?
Just tell me secretly.
What did you suggest on the list?
I don't remember.
Shall I make you remember?
How?
Wait a minute.
- Like this...
- I remember now.
- You remember, don't you?
- Yes.
What did you ask?
First,
I said that I'd like to stay
near my house.
Well done.
That's why we're here.
- So that's why.
- I raised Joon very well.
Then are we going to Joon's house?
- I remember it clearly.
- What?
I asked for a hotel staycation.
- I asked for a hotel staycation.
- I really did.
- Training or hotel?
- Hotel.
- Hotel staycation.
You should've pronounced
more clearly.
I'm telling you the truth.
Mr. Joo is calling me.
Hello, I'm listening.
Do you hear me, everyone?
- Yes.
Your next destination is...
one of the places
on Joon's bucket list.
You're going skydiving.
- Don't lie.
- Seriously?
You're going skydiving.
Is it possible with today's weather?
What have you done?
You're going skydiving.
(Frozen)
- Gosh.
- Now...
(Truly flustered)
Seriously?
- Did you really say that?
- He wanted to skydive together.
Are you out of your mind?
- See you when you arrive.
- I'm going to turn the car around.
We're going home.
I'm going to turn the car around.
I can't do that.
We're going home.
- I'm going to turn the car around.
- Seriously?
I don't remember mentioning it.
- What have you done?
- No way.
I'm sorry. Oh, no.
- Joon, I can't skydive.
- Me neither.
- I just felt pain in my heart.
Hey.
(Extremely serious)
- The weather is also bad.
- Why did you suggest it?
It was my idea? I never said it.
No way.
On Joon Tour, is there something...
that you absolutely want to do?
Group skydiving for Team Joon.
- You suggested skydiving?
- I never did.
(What he said carelessly
became a reality.)
What does this mean?
I'm going to turn the car around.
But we decided to humor him today.
- What should we do?
- Dad.
We can't do this just to humor him.
Mom, should I turn the car around?
We have to bite the bullet.
What do we do?
- What do I do?
- How can we skydive?
No, this is wrong.
I'm sorry.
- What?
Is this the place?
(Traces of laughter
disappear instantly.)
What's this?
(Filled with questions,
they arrive.)
- It feels cool in here. What?
- It's golf.
Hello.
What is he doing? Goodness.
- What?
- What is he doing?
(What's shocking the members?)
- What?
- What is he doing?
What is he doing? He's spinning.
(Someone who's flying freely?)
He's spinning his head.
- What?
- Gosh.
- Oh, my.
- What's going on?
He's playing with gravity.
What's underneath him?
How high does he go?
(Moving freely)
That's right.
(A sudden fall)
What?
(Their hearts skip a beat.)
He's bumping into the ceiling.
(Indoor skydiving
that uses the wind)
How is that possible?
How does he fall so suddenly?
It's dangerous.
Something seems wrong.
- Shouldn't we save him?
- He's dancing.
- I think he passed out.
- Passed out?
(Spinning)
(Posing)
(Nice to meet you.)
(Blown away
by the incredible fan service)
That's insane.
What's going on?
(He finishes up
with a splendid escape like a hero.)
(They clap like seals
as if they were back in childhood.)
(What did I just see?
I can't believe my eyes.)
- Oh, my.
- That was awesome.
- It was so scary at the end.
- How did he get out like that?
- Did you see that?
- Unbelievable. How does he do that?
- That was unbelievable.
- He got out and landed on his feet.
- Must we do that?
- The last move was amazing.
You all saw how it was done, right?
- This is Joon's bucket list item.
- What's his problem?
- Why is it on his bucket list?
- Let's hear him out.
Did I say I wanted to try this?
Is there something
that you absolutely want to do?
It'd be fun
if we tried a hard challenge.
For example,
we could travel to Dokdo Island...
on a duck boat.
Or group skydiving for Team Joon.
(The thought of it alone
makes him happy.)
I seriously don't remember
saying that. Trust me.
It's okay. This is doable.
Right. You're grateful to me, right?
It would've been really hard
if we had to fall through the sky.
- I'll introduce you to the coach.
- Okay.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
Please stand in the middle.
Oh, my. He looks amazing.
I'm Coach Yoo Hyeon Jae.
I'm an indoor skydiver,
and I do the freestyle,
- representing Korea.
- Great.
(Amazing)
The wind blows upward
at the same speed.
How do you fall down suddenly
while floating in the air...
- and stay down?
- He soared up into the air too.
With the wind blowing
at the same speed,
you need to control the movements
with your body.
You float
when your body is horizontal,
- and you fall when it's vertical.
- So, how...
- So it requires high concentration.
- You need high concentration.
- You also need strong core muscles.
- Right.
Can anyone try this
without a license?
Yes, of course.
What's the weight limit?
I don't think there's a suit that fits me.
- The weight limit is...
- There's a weight limit, right?
- about 120kg.
- So you can do it.
- No. I weigh 122kg.
- But...
I've taught someone
who weighed 130kg.
I shouldn't try this though.
Aren't I right?
Yes, you can do it.
- Now, change your clothes.
- Okay.
I feel so bad.
(Se Yoon is worried,
and Joon feels bad.)
Leave me alone for a moment.
(Give me a moment
to get myself ready mentally.)
Give me just a moment.
Guess what I hated the most
during the four-week military training.
Changing clothes.
All fat men would understand.
Where did they go?
They're really leaving me alone.
At least they do as I ask.
(Would I be able to fly?)
My gosh.
I never knew I would try this.
We've been trying
various activities today.
You will watch a video first.
It will show you
the steps of the training process.
Watch it carefully. Now,
you will try skydiving
in the wind tunnel, one at a time.
You can gain an allowance
through this mission as well.
Then we should do this.
We should do our best.
The game you'll play
to gain an allowance this time is...
Zero Gravity Speed Quiz.
You have one minute for each round.
The member in the wind tunnel...
will give questions
to the other members.
The other members will stand
in a row...
behind this line here.
You have to read the member's lips
and guess the answer.
Each of you will give questions
in the wind tunnel.
So we'll have six rounds in total.
Each member can pass
only one question in his turn.
How should we give a signal
to pass a question?
Let's move our tongues.
- Let's stick out our tongues.
- Like this.
- Okay.
- This time,
you have to get four right answers
or more to succeed.
- How much money do we get?
- Five dollars if you succeed.
- Come on.
- That's ridiculous.
If you succeed in all 6 rounds,
you'll get 30 dollars.
- Oh, I see.
- Oh, five dollars for each round?
(They understood they could get
5 dollars per person just now.)
What if only one of us succeeds?
Then you'll get five dollars.
- Come on. That's so little.
- Oh, gosh.
- This isn't the last mission.
- Are there more missions?
- If this isn't the last mission...
- You won't let us have lunch?
- Right. Give us food to eat first.
- When will we have lunch?
Now you will start the game
one at a time.
The session takes about two minutes.
For the first minute,
- you'll practice flying in there.
- We'll have time to practice.
And you'll play the game
for the remaining one minute.
- Okay.
Everyone, let's go.
- Okay. Let's go.
You think this will be scarier
than the roller coaster?
I'm scared of both of them.
No, I think this will be less scary.
- I think it'll be much easier.
- This will be much easier.
Are you sure?
While flying in there,
keep your legs straight.
And keep your arms straight as well.
(He enters the wind tunnel.)
(Nervous)
Let's go and see
how ugly Sae Ho looks in there.
How does he stand straight
like that?
Gosh.
Let's see how ugly he'll become.
My goodness.
(Surprised)
(His body floats in the air
in an instant.)
What?
(Peekaboo)
(Laughing)
His face looks funny in there.
(His face looks pretty bizarre.)
My gosh.
(Shocked by his looks)
(As he goes up higher,)
(his cheeks flutter like a flag.)
That's good. Oh, my. He's flying.
(Fluttering)
- What?
- What's going on?
(There is no CGI on his face.)
My goodness. Look at his face.
- Gosh. What's that?
- Look at his face.
I'm afraid
I might see that face in my dream.
(The face you'd never want to see
in your dream)
What? Don't do that.
Look at his mouth.
Ready, set, go!
(The first question: Blind date)
(Blind date)
(Blind date!)
- Blind date.
- Correct.
(Ball-shaped candy)
- Ball-shaped candy.
- Correct.
- Okay.
- What?
(Man)
- Me?
- Cho Sae Ho.
(Man!)
Man.
- Correct.
- Okay.
(Se Yoon got three answers right
alone.)
(Guess the answer.)
- Glade.
- Sliding.
- Sniks?
- Slice.
(What is that?)
- It's a four-letter word.
- Slime.
Slate.
(Frustrated)
(The answer is...)
(S...)
(St...)
(Stretch...)
(Stretching)
- It's a four-letter word.
- Slime.
- Slate.
- No, that's not it.
- Again. What?
- Skydiving.
Aerobic?
Stretching.
- Correct.
- Okay.
- He's good at this.
- He's spinning.
What is he doing?
(Eyes widening)
(Soaring)
(Falling down)
(Frightened)
Gosh. I won't do that.
I won't go in there
unless he promises he won't do it.
Oh, my goodness.
(You should try skydiving
since you're here.)
(His eyes are set on them.
That must be fun.)
Is he heavier?
How does he do that?
I really hate it.
- Is someone else up there?
- It's too high.
(He's trying to get out now.)
- What's that?
- What's going on? What's he doing?
(He's not a drunken man
being dragged out.)
What?
- I think it'll be fun.
- It's more like a funny act.
- Our faces will all look funny.
- We'll make people laugh.
- My gosh. That was so fun.
- Are you all right?
I really enjoyed it.
(The unexpected adrenaline rush
satisfied him.)
I'll come back here for another try.
That was amazing.
Can I not go up higher than this?
- It's too high.
- You can do it.
If I fall down,
I won't let it slide.
- How many answers did you get?
- We got all the questions right.
Really?
Sae Ho,
you're blessed with your face.
- This is how you looked.
- I know what you mean.
You know what I'm saying, right?
- It was so fun. It was amazing.
- Was it fun?
The second member is getting ready.
With such a strong wind like that...
(He enters with the coach's help.)
Hey. What?
- He looks so ugly.
- My gosh.
Why is he smiling?
- He must be enjoying it.
- Right.
But why does he open his mouth
like that?
(He got scared by the sudden turn.)
That's possible because he's light.
I don't think I'm able to do that.
He looks so cute.
He looks like a hamster.
Ready, set, go!
(Elephant)
- What is it? What?
- Nose?
- Right. Nose.
- Pinocchio.
- Elephant.
- Correct. "Elephant" is correct.
- It's hot.
- You're scared. It's hot.
- Fan?
- Heat wave.
Correct. "Heat wave" is correct.
- He's so good at this. I can't...
- How many letters?
- Look at him.
- It's a mountain.
(He describes a mountain.)
The Himalayas.
- The Himalayas.
- Correct. You got three right.
(They only have to get
one more question right to succeed.)
(Flustered)
- What's with him?
- What? Look at his face.
- Knucklehead.
- He looks so ugly. I can't guess.
- Head? Egg.
- I don't understand what it means.
- Egg.
- Stone-grilled egg.
- Sand lance.
- He looks like a different person.
Sand lance coffee.
(Frustrated)
(The answer...)
(is yolk.)
- Sand lance coffee.
- Yolk.
"Yolk" is correct.
(They got four questions right
and completed the mission.)
Oh, gosh.
- I just hate it.
- Look at his face.
(He's surprised
as his body goes up suddenly.)
I really hate it.
It looks so scary.
(With the additional 5 dollars,
they gained 10 dollars so far.)
We got the questions right, though.
(You can leave now.)
DinDin, turn around.
(He looks as if he were on top
of Mount Everest.)
I think he walked that way
on top of Mount Halla.
The wind was blowing strongly,
so we had to walk that way.
- He managed to walk out.
- He must be good at it.
DinDin, was it fun?
You seemed to enjoy it.
It's not scary at all.
It feels like there's a big fan
under your feet.
I was scared at first,
but later on...
- It was fun, right?
- Yes, it was fun.
I'll show you how you looked.
(He teases DinDin
when he has the chance.)
- You did well. We got it all.
- You really looked like this.
Who's up next?
- Jong Min, you've got this.
- Kim Jong Min!
I'll escort him and come back.
- I'll go by myself.
- He's been the cast for 18 years.
He'll fly in the air.
Here goes Kim Jong Min!
(Will the scaredy-cat oldest member
be able to do well?)
- Guys.
- Yes?
Since you guys did so well,
we added a longer word
to the questions.
Okay. That's fine.
Is it wrong that we did well?
No, it's good that you did well.
But it'll be even better...
- if there's more suspense.
- Seon Ho.
- That was the right question.
- Right?
Why would they raise the difficulty
when we did well?
- Go, Jong Min!
- Jong Min, you've got this!
(Screaming)
I'm scared to look down there.
(He saw where the wind comes from
and got scared.)
- Don't look down. Face forward.
- Got it.
(Stiff)
(Extremely nervous)
- What?
- Jong Min, you can do it!
Jong Min looks
like a different person.
That's what he'd look like
15 years from now.
Is he perhaps a different person?
Go, Jong Min!
Jong Min must be nervous.
I'm worried about him.
Once he overcomes his fear,
he'll be okay.
(Leaning on the coach,
he carefully lowers his body.)
That's good. Okay.
He's doing well.
He's doing unexpectedly well.
- What?
He's enjoying it.
(Smiling happily)
He's doing really well.
- He's good at it.
- What?
- He's the best among us so far.
- He's good at it.
He's better than the other two.
(Excited)
- He's doing so well.
- Indeed.
I knew he would do well.
All right. We'll begin now.
Start.
Is he saying...
(Gaping)
- Pizza.
Pizza.
- Water parsley.
(The answer is...)
(Killer move)
- Water parsley.
- It's water parsley.
(It looks like he's saying
"water parsley" at a glance.)
- Water parsley.
- Slug.
Slug.
(Killer move)
- Icy road.
- Let's pass.
Okay, pass.
(The next one
is a five-letter word.)
(Ox head soup)
- Beef tripe.
Ox head meat and rice soup.
(Ox head soup)
(It's a soup.)
What is he saying?
- You have ten seconds.
- Ox bone tripes?
- Oxtail soup?
- Oxtail soup with rice.
Ox head rice soup.
- We'll never get it.
- Three, two...
- Ox head soup.
- Correct.
- Time is up.
- What's this?
- The questions were horrible.
- I know.
(Flying up)
(Jong Min becomes a scaredy-cat
as he is scared of this.)
- He's good at this.
- Right.
He's actually good at this.
(Laughing)
(Trying hard to survive)
What's going on?
(He's almost like a drunk man.)
He seems drunk there.
He won't let go.
Goodness.
What's happening?
(Tottering to get out)
- What's wrong with him?
- It's hilarious.
(Sighing)
(You did a good job.)
Okay, thank you.
That wasn't so bad.
(I can't believe that I made it.)
Gosh, I'm drooling all over...
- It wasn't scary, was it?
- It was actually fun.
I told you.
- It was fun.
- Let me help you with this.
Give him a round of applause.
- How was it?
- It's actually nice.
- It's nice?
- It's better than I thought.
The man grabbed Sae Ho and me.
- But he let go of you.
- You did it all by yourself.
- You did it yourself.
- Well done.
You finally got to prove
your gymnastics skills today.
I think I can do it all by myself
after a few attempts.
- Really?
- Yes, I think I can do it.
Let's go!
Seon Ho could fly with a fan.
He's in it now. There he goes.
- Paper Doll.
- Here comes Paper Doll.
(Fluttering)
What's going on?
That's how he does it.
- He's too light.
- He'll fly away.
Maybe it's because he's too skinny.
He can't balance himself.
- His arms look awkward there.
- Let's go.
Ready? Start.
What is he saying?
Buldak ramyeon?
Buldak.
(It's a type of food.)
Something grilled...
Is it something grilled?
It's tteokbokki.
Yeopgi tteokbokki?
It's something grilled...
- Grilled tteokbokki.
- Thai curry crab?
That is correct!
Great.
(Here is the second question.)
(Sunday)
Is he saying...
An elephant.
Lee Hyo Ri.
- Pass.
What?
Canine tooth.
- Correct.
- It's a canine tooth.
He's good.
(He has about 10 seconds.)
Is that correct?
(It's a two-letter word.)
What is it?
(A telephone)
(Save...)
(Saving)
- Jeonnam?
- Reduction?
(Saving)
- To bow down?
- Three,
- two, one.
- Transfer.
(Mission failed)
What's going on? He's going up.
He's going up again.
(Excited)
(Going up straight
to a high altitude)
(It's fun.)
He almost got dragged out.
(Being dragged out)
(This is what he wanted
as it was on his bucket list.)
He looks so confident there.
(Joon is going to rock this game.)
(This familiar tension)
(This is it.)
(I know how to do it right.)
I think I can do better than him.
Joon looks different
even with his pose.
He's going forward.
There he goes.
(Getting up without any help)
(Flying up in a cool manner)
(Flying in a stable position)
(I think I'm good at this.)
He got it.
(Make them a heart.)
A heart.
- He's ready.
- Please rock this game.
He can't hear me, can he?
Start.
(Stone flicking)
- Stone flicking.
Correct.
(A whistle)
What is it?
- A whistle.
(Calf)
(This part right here)
Calf.
Correct.
- Piggyback.
- That is correct.
- We got it.
(He got 4 questions right
in just 30 seconds.)
(Joon is good.)
His legs...
Teeth.
- Molar tooth.
- It's a...
party.
- Bracelet.
Arms? Muscles.
Biceps?
What is it?
(You poke it on your bottoms.)
- Bottoms.
- Two, one...
- Vaccination.
- Time is up.
- BCG vaccine.
What is he doing?
(Let's go,
it's show time in the air.)
(Enjoying skydiving up and down)
How do we do that?
(Joon completed his mission
by getting four questions.)
Se Yoon, it's your turn.
Let's go, Se Yoon.
- I'll be back.
- Go, Se Yoon!
- Will I be okay?
- Sure.
You can do this. Let's go.
Okay, thank you.
(The last player is Se Yoon
who weighs 120kg.)
I can't wait to see this.
I think the coach will go down
with Se Yoon.
Can he do this?
Se Yoon surely is big.
Don't spread your arms.
Put your arms together like this.
My arms like this?
(Checking his posture)
(Power up)
(It isn't easy even for the coach.)
(Can he fly in a cool manner?)
Goodness.
(Laughing)
It's all going into his nose.
What's happening?
(Se Yoon...)
(is flying.)
(Laughing)
(Se Yoon's cheeks flying)
(Se Yoon's excited.)
Gosh, that man who weighs
120kg is in the air now.
(My friend is the best.)
(Se Yoon finds it surprising
himself.)
That man who weighs 120kg
is in the air now.
Gosh, he's in the air.
(Smiling)
- Goodness, the coach...
- He can't control Se Yoon.
(Se Yoon keeps sinking
due to his weight.)
He keeps sinking.
He's 30kg heavier than us.
(Sir, I'm sinking.)
He's sinking.
- He can't go up.
- The coach can't fly him up.
The coach can't control this.
(No, generate more power.)
He wants to increase power.
(The wind power is going up.)
(He finally got to balance himself.)
Let's go now. Ready.
Hold on a second.
His goggles...
Let's go now.
(His goggles slowly went up
to cover his eyes.)
(Flying away)
Hold on a second.
(He lost his goggles
because his cheeks pushed them up.)
(Unbelievable)
(Let's get outside.)
(Why is he so funny?)
His goggles are gone.
(Help me.)
(His goggles were removed
due to the heavy wind.)
(The coach puts on goggles
for Se Yoon.)
He had to put them on tightly.
My goodness.
This is something
you rarely see on TV.
We'll start right away
when he gets in.
(We'll start the game
as soon as he gets inside.)
(Se Yoon enters again
after reading himself again.)
He's so ready.
Let's start.
Ready? Go.
(Dopamine)
- Dopamine.
- Correct.
(Toilet)
- Toilet.
- Correct.
(He gets two correct
in a short period of time.)
Penguin.
(Mackerel)
- Squid.
Study dormitory.
(Pass)
- Pass.
(They answered two correctly.)
(BLACKPINK)
Implant.
Ribs with soybean sprouts.
Brazil.
(BLACKPINK)
BLACKPINK?
- BLACKPINK!
- Correct!
(Remaining time: 10 seconds)
Ten seconds!
(Ice)
- Carp?
- Ice!
Correct!
- Amazing.
- He got it right.
- Three, two, one.
- Letter.
- Time over.
- We have four.
(It's time to go up.)
(Wind strength at full power)
Will it work?
It's working.
(Let's fly.)
Se Yoon is flying.
(Up in the air)
(Se Yoon flies up.)
Se Yoon is flying.
Amazing.
- Amazing.
- Goodness.
(I want to fly
and embrace the night sky)
Goodness.
Se Yoon looks proud.
It must have been hard
for the instructor.
(Struggling)
Amazing!
I couldn't see anything.
- Instructor.
- You did very well.
(Se Yoon made it
through the hardship.)
You're really amazing.
My mouth was...
- Right.
- It affected you more.
- Well done.
- Se Yoon.
- Was it all right?
- How do you feel?
- Jong Min got all the answers.
Jong Min did? That's my best friend.
- Of course.
- How was it?
He has double eyelids now.
Before announcing the results,
- let's thank the instructor first.
- Okay.
That was really amazing.
- You lifted Se Yoon.
- Instructor Yoo Hyeon Jae.
- I remember his name.
- You're a little giant.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
In Zero Gravity Speed Quiz,
DinDin, Sae Ho, Joon,
and Se Yoon succeeded.
I said you'll be given
five dollars each.
- Twenty dollars.
- You'll get twenty dollars.
- Okay.
- Here you go.
Let's move to the place
where we'll eat.
- How much do we have?
- Do we have 37 dollars?
It's not that much. The corn dog...
Well...
We might have an animal quiz
with Joon.
- Right. There would be something.
- Yes.
- Shall we get changed?
- Yes. Get changed.
- Okay.
- Get changed.
- It was fun.
- I couldn't open my eyes at all.
I couldn't open my eyes.
I felt like I was flying.
It was quite fun.
Yes. It was fun.
It's a Grab and Kill Tour.
What did we grab?
It's about killing us.
We should grab laughter.
A few of us grabbed laughter.
Sae Ho grabbed laughter
with his face.
- Right.
- I was actually shocked.
My face looked so funny.
You can't beat
people who were born funny.
- He was born with it.
- The physique is different.
You'll get into trouble
if you try to imitate that.
I'm hungry.
I'm so hungry.
If we eat until we're full now,
we'll get a blood sugar spike.
- Right away.
- I want to eat ramyeon.
- I'm craving ramyeon.
- Let's eat ramyeon.
- Since it's raining,
I just want to eat ramyeon.
Ramyeon is nice.
- Ramyeon.
- And kimchi.
How many ramyeon packs
do you make for six people?
- About 9?
- We should make at least 9.
- Ten?
- If we're going to make nine,
let's put ten eggs.
- Okay.
- Green onions too.
(I want some ramyeon.)
Chicken and seafood soup?
That's nice.
Restaurants with rivers are great.
I don't have energy.
This place is very unique.
The building looks new,
and there's a river next to it.
It looks just like it.
Our first shooting.
People are inside.
I guess it's okay.
You can't put your feet inside
if the water is cold.
(The members
enter the water one by one.)
Let's go inside.
(The members
enter the water one by one.)
It's cold! It's no joke.
It's refreshing.
- This isn't cold.
- Goodness.
Goodness.
(They're whining more
than last year.)
Why is the water so cold?
(They all enter the river
while screaming.)
(Whining)
- Do you remember eating lunch...
- It's the same.
in the river at the first shooting?
- I remember.
- Yes.
Braised spicy chicken
with aged kimchi.
Joon was very hungry back then.
Don't they sell
soy sauce marinated crab here?
Thinking back
on that day one year ago,
we decided to have lunch...
- in the river.
- Nice!
Nice!
Joon talked a lot
about the memories of the river.
He said we should have lunch late
like last time.
Why did you do that?
- So...
- I didn't say that.
- Wasn't it someone else?
They recorded the call.
Really?
- Why doesn't he remember...
- Why did you say that?
what he said?
Similar to when we first came,
we could go to a river...
and eat around the time we ate
last time.
I think that would go well
with the show's identity.
(So we prepared lunch a bit late.)
- I'm sorry.
- Currently,
the money you collected...
- Isn't it 37 dollars?
- is 37 dollars. That's right.
- I'll give you the menu card.
- Okay.
(2 Days and 1 Night menu)
It doesn't make sense.
What's this?
(He saw the price of chicken
and seafood soup, 120 dollars.)
Hey. Chicken and seafood soup?
It costs more than 100 dollars?
(They only have 37 dollars. How will
they have chicken and seafood soup?)
This is too expensive.
Are you trying to irritate us
or what?
Don't give up.
This is the last mission
you can earn your allowance.
It's Guess Who in the River again.
We can do it.
You will see the picture
and say the name...
and one of the person's works...
in three seconds.
(Jeon Do Yeon!)
("Secret Sunshine")
(This will be a correct answer.)
You have five chances.
If you succeed
in your first attempt,
- you'll get 100 dollars.
- Okay.
We'd barely eat
the chicken and seafood soup.
Every time you fail,
20 dollars will be deducted.
Let's do this.
Who wants to go first?
- Joon.
- It won't come here.
- Everyone.
- I'm good.
- We'll go back to the basics...
- and time precisely.
- Okay.
- Are you ready, Joon?
- Yes.
We'll start.
One, two, three. Three!
Three!
Byun Yo Han, "Mr. Sunshine."
- Joon.
- He's good.
- Correct!
- I was confused.
One, two, three.
- Three, two, one!
- Goodness!
Nam Joo Hyuk.
- Wrong.
- Nam Joo Hyuk!
Isn't that right?
You failed the first attempt.
(Screaming)
(They all splash water on Se Yoon.)
Wait.
(He gets splashed instead.)
What are you doing?
Why are you doing it to me?
- He went behind you.
- He went behind.
I got it correct.
I'm not that good these days.
Something's wrong.
- Should I go there?
- Let's switch places.
They've become old too.
You should know right away.
(The weakest two members
are sent to the end.)
- This place is better.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Okay.
- What?
- We'll start from Joon.
- Okay.
- We'll start.
- Joon is the ace.
- Joon is good.
One, two, three.
- Who is it?
- Three,
- Moon Geun Young.
- two,
- one!
- This is hard.
(Moon Geun Young)
(The ace doesn't know.)
- This is...
- You failed.
You're amazing.
You splashed water on me earlier.
(He gets showered with water
2 times in a row.)
Do it well.
Are we going to do it again
when we're this bad at it?
I'm not joking. I'm confident
it will not come all the way here.
This is annoying.
- Why did I get it wrong?
- It's doable.
(They lost 40 dollars
in an instant.)
(They all lost their motivation.)
Let's go!
(They don't respond.)
Seriously.
There's no excitement at all.
This is amazing.
- I'm sorry.
- Let's bring some excitement!
- Okay!
- Okay.
- Let's start.
- Let's go!
(It's already their third attempt.)
One, two, three.
- Three.
- Yang Dong Geun, "Squid Game."
- Two.
- Correct.
(It's Sae Ho,
the second ace's turn.)
One, two, three.
Park Seo Jun, "Itaewon Class."
- Nice.
- Correct.
I'm in trouble.
It shouldn't come to me.
- The face...
- I can't think.
One, two, three.
Three, two,
- one.
- Jung Hae In,
"Something in the Rain."
- That's right.
- Correct!
- Okay. It's correct.
- It's correct.
- I'm in trouble.
- It starts now.
- One, two, three.
- I'm in trouble.
Three, two,
- one!
- Shin Ye Eun, "The Glory!"
- Correct!
- Good!
(Good! This is doable.)
Let's switch places.
- No.
- Please switch with me.
(The two weakest members are left.)
- No.
- Just guess two correctly.
Give us old-time actors.
- Three, two,
- Lee Dong Hwi,
- one.
- "Reply, 19..."
- "Reply 19?"
- "Reply 199..."
Four.
(Ventriloquism?)
- Four.
- Don't say anything, DinDin.
Don't say anything, DinDin.
I don't know.
- Three!
- "Reply 1994."
- It's 1998.
- Wrong!
- My goodness.
- It's 1998.
He...
(It's understandable
to feel wronged.)
Hold on.
(It's understandable
to feel wronged.)
- Hey!
- Look at him.
- I...
- Are you serious?
(When elephants fight,
it is Joon who suffers.)
- We can't get wet!
- Stop!
Hold on. I feel wronged.
Yoo Seon Ho cheated.
- Everyone,
- I cheated.
The audio team is on watch again.
- He cheated this time.
- If an illegal act is detected...
An illegal top?
If an illegal act is detected...
- An illegal top?
- Yes.
- What is an illegal top?
Come out, legendary top!
Illegal Top!
Super Grand Illegal Top!
We'll start with Jong Min this time.
- I want to go to the middle.
- No. Don't change spots.
I was going to do that
but it came out differently.
- What are you doing?
- Let's switch spots.
- Just stay here once.
- I'll do it for you.
You didn't even get a single shot.
Hurry up and do it.
You didn't get a single shot
on your own.
Hurry up and do it.
(The first individual shot
in the valley)
Sit down.
Please choose someone
who knows the answers.
You have failed three times.
If you succeed this time,
you will receive 40 dollars.
Each person can eat a serving
of pork cutlet with 40 dollars.
- Right.
- Right. Let's go and eat.
- Will you try it like this then?
- Okay. We'll do it like that.
The person who knows the answer
will say the answer and move away.
- Okay.
- Okay!
Leave the easy ones for us. Got it?
Okay.
What are the shows
with Hwang Jung Min in them?
Hwang Jung Min?
- We'll start.
- "You Are My Sunshine."
- "New World" and "Veteran."
- "Veteran."
"Narco-Saints."
Right. There's "Narco-Saints" too.
We'll start. One, two, three,
- go! Three...
- All right.
(Hwang Jung Min,
who they just talked about, appears!)
(All eyes are on Jong Min.)
(He doesn't have an answer
right after talking about him?)
- One!
- Sae Ho! "Veteran," Hwang Jung Min.
- Okay.
- We just talked about him.
- You must say it in three seconds.
- I forgot.
- How could you forget that?
- Are you serious?
- I can't believe this guy.
All right.
I'll go if I know the answer.
One, two, three, go!
- DinDin!
- Three...
Shin Min A, "Hometown Cha-Cha-Cha."
- Okay.
Nice one.
- Correct.
- I said I was going to go first.
All right. One, two, three, go!
- Go for it, Moon Se Yoon!
- Three, two...
Go for it, Moon Se Yoon!
(He doesn't know the answer.)
- Who is that?
- Two...
- Go for it.
- Seon Ho.
Park Bo Young,
"Our Unwritten Seoul."
- Correct!
- Hurry up and answer.
- Give me some time.
- All right.
One, two, three, go!
- Three, two, one.
- Go first.
It's Park Bo Young.
(Sae Ho...)
(and Joon don't know the answer.)
- One.
- It's Park Bo Young.
You know that show, right?
Oh, gosh! Come on!
Wrong!
I've seen her.
- "Seo Young, My Daughter?"
- Right.
(Just get splashed by water.)
- I didn't answer on purpose.
- Gosh, this is disappointing.
- So disappointing.
- Isn't that Lee Bo Young?
- Right.
- Why call her Park Bo Young?
You should've stayed still
if you didn't know the answer.
Why try to answer it?
I was in that show with her.
It's not the time to talk about
someone you know.
Are there more questions left?
I feel bad.
Se Yoon and Jong Min
have to get the answers.
All right.
We're a lot worse
than you expected, right?
Yes.
(The betrayal of the elder
with 18 years of experience)
We'll start.
(They are stuck in the valley.)
One, two, three, go!
- Three...
- Choi Min Sik, "Casino."
Yes!
- Move away.
- I should've gone first.
One, two, three, go!
- Three, two,
- Se Yoon.
- Lee Sung Min, "Misaeng."
- one.
- Correct!
- It's us now.
All right. One, two, three, go!
- Three,
- Lee Joon!
- two...
- Kang Ha Neul, "Squid Game."
Correct!
- We're in trouble.
- We answered a lot.
- I don't know.
- One, two, three, go!
- Three,
- You should know this one.
- two,
- DinDin.
- one.
- Kim You Jung, "My Demon."
- Okay!
- I saved all of us.
- Nice one.
I saved all of us this time.
I won't let it slide if you don't
get it right this time, Seon Ho.
- Me too.
- All right.
One, two, three, go!
- Seon Ho!
- Sae Ho!
Park Sung Woong,
"A Violent Prosecutor."
- Correct!
- Gosh!
- Sae Ho!
- Get ready!
- Get ready to get him.
- Gosh.
- Doing that will hinder me.
- Okay.
Let's just let him be comfortable.
(Which question will he be given?)
One, two, three, go!
- Go! Three, two...
- Lee Ha Nee, "Tazza."
Lee Ha Nee, "Tazza."
- Aren't I right?
- Correct!
(Cho Sae Ho is correct!)
- You will receive 20 dollars.
- Nice.
You can't do this
before I answer it.
We'll do it one last time...
as we bet 20 dollars.
With a 20-dollar bet?
How about getting another chance
with two people diving in?
- Okay!
- What are you doing, Jong Min?
- What are you doing?
- I'm cold!
Sacrifice yourself
for the young ones.
- The youngest should go.
- Just be quick, Jong Min.
(Kim Boomer)
Let's do this then.
Since we're doing this
as their one-year anniversary,
- the two new members should go.
- Right!
Just dive in to celebrate
your one-year anniversary!
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- You guys planned this!
All right. You go first.
Viewers, please watch us for a year.
- No. That's not what I meant.
- What was that?
Is it your first shoot today?
Viewers,
you were with us for a whole year,
and we were able to do well
thanks to all of you.
Please continue to show us
your support.
- Let's go, 2 Days and 1 Night!
- Let's go!
Thank you!
Gosh!
There we go.
Get in!
(Thanks to Sae Ho
and Joon's sacrifice...)
- Done.
- Gosh, it's so cold.
Done, right?
All right.
You'll get another chance.
(The final extra game starts.)
- Why won't that ever happen?
- Right.
But comedians...
- What's wrong with him?
- Do we need to save him?
- Are you a breakdancer or what?
- I slipped.
- What was that?
Did something happen?
He's a strange one.
If you fail this time,
you should give up.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- We were awful.
- We're really bad at this.
One, two, three, go!
- Yes!
- Three,
- two,
- Sae Ho.
- one.
- Kim Nam Gil, "The Fiery Priest."
- Okay!
- He was in a lot of shows.
- All right.
One, two, three, go!
Three, two, one.
- Jung Yu Mi.
- Jung Yu Mi, "Born 1978."
"Kim Ji Young: Born 1982."
- It wasn't 1978?
- Correct!
- Yes!
- Okay!
- What are you doing?
- Gosh.
Why mention 1978? Was she born
in the Year of the Dragon?
One, two, three, go!
- Three...
- We told you earlier!
- Kim Ji Yeon, "The Glory."
- Okay! Correct!
- Done.
- I heard Kim Ji Yeon.
- He shouldn't have gone.
- Lim Ji Yeon.
According to the Initial Sound Law,
it's Lim Ji Yeon.
It sounded like Kim Ji Yeon,
but he said Lim Ji Yeon.
- One, two, three,
- Who will go next?
- I won't know most of them.
- go!
- Here we go.
- Do you know this one?
- I don't know.
- Two...
Ji Chang Wook, "The Manipulated."
- Nice.
- It will be released soon.
It was already filmed.
He filmed it with Doh Kyung Soo.
- Really?
- They're done with the filming.
It will be released next January.
Right!
- Okay! Correct!
- I'm certain.
Get ready. Let's go!
- Joon.
- Say it right away if you know.
Let me take it if it's an easy one.
I won't know a lot.
All right.
It's just the two of you left.
One, two, three, go!
- You go.
- Three, two...
Chung Kyung Ho,
"Oh My Ghost Clients."
Correct! It's the last one.
- Joon will decide your fate.
- Okay.
- Get ready.
- Joon!
(We trust you, Joon.)
- Let's do this.
- We got this.
One, two, three, go!
- Let's go!
- Three...
Kim Sung Kyun, "Nameless Gangster."
He did it.
Correct!
You all have made it.
You will receive 20 more dollars.
Everyone, be quiet. Go.
- Lim Ji Yeon!
- One more time.
- Done.
We got the audio.
He said Kim Ji Yeon earlier.
He mentioned the member of Roo'Ra.
- Say it as you get up.
- Really?
Everyone, be quiet! Say the answer.
Lim Ji Yeon, "The Glory."
Done! That's a wrap.
- He got confused with the name.
- He said Kim Ji Yeon earlier.
I couldn't believe my ears.
We'll get three bowls
of seafood kalguksu...
and three servings of pork cutlet.
Got it.
(After the exciting time
in the water,)
(the members of the big family
feel very hungry.)
I wish we are served a lot of soup.
I wish they would serve us
this much rice too.
We should share the pork cutlet...
as a pair like this
and a pair like this.
Seon Ho and Se Yoon
can share one too.
- The pork cutlet?
- Right.
I'm going to eat
a lot of the pork cutlet.
Okay.
Who are you saying that to?
He must've been talking to Joon.
(The food is coming.)
- Gosh!
- That's a lot of food.
Gosh, there's a lot of seafood.
(Kalguksu filled with seafood)
Gosh, the seafood.
The kalguksu should be boiled
a bit more.
Gosh, it's the pork cutlet!
Gosh, there are three plates.
- Let's cut it in half.
- Okay.
- It will be evenly split.
- Right.
- Should we split it evenly too?
- Okay.
(Crunchy)
Gosh, it looks really good.
Is that okay?
- Okay?
- Okay.
- The rice too.
- Right.
(The rice is split
exactly in half too.)
Gosh, this is amazing.
Hasn't it been a while for us...
since we ate this well?
We always eat this well.
Am I the only one
who's living in a different world?
You say that every week.
It's because you always lose.
Would you like to try some?
(Joon these days...)
(has been failing
in every lunch mission.)
(He has barely eaten properly
during the day.)
Why does it feel like it's been
a long while since I've eaten?
(Because it really has been
a while.)
- Let's begin.
- Thank you for the food.
Thank you for the food.
(He makes a sweet and spicy sauce
with the wasabi.)
(He then takes a bite
after dipping it in the sauce.)
It's good.
The pork cutlet is so good.
- This is the Western style, right?
- Right
(Perfect after water activities)
Gosh, the pork cutlet is good.
(Sweet and crunchy
Western-style pork cutlet)
(Eating wildly)
(It tastes amazing
with a dip of wasabi.)
- What should we do?
- Let's eat.
Will you add the wasabi?
Sorry?
Gosh, there's hair all over me.
(His gray hair
keeps getting in his face.)
- The pork cutlet is so good.
- It's eaten like this.
- With this on it.
- Okay.
(A big chunk)
- The pork cutlet has a kick.
- My gosh.
This is the Western pork cutlet.
(Gasping)
What's wrong?
The wasabi...
(Shouting)
(The pungent flavor
at the tip of his nose)
My goodness.
(Giggling)
Why?
Jong Min...
He picked up a big lump of wasabi.
It was a lot.
And he shouted
as soon as he put it in his mouth.
(A disaster he brought upon himself)
Anything tastes pungent
when you eat that much.
(He neutralizes his mouth
with pork cutlet too late.)
How are you feeling, Joon?
- What?
- Did you want to do this?
(The reason he came to the valley
again after a year)
(Lee Joon's signature)
(His pitiful eating show)
(It all began with the "valley.")
(The turning point
in Lee Joon's eating life)
(He stared silently at his food
as if he'd drool at any moment.)
(And he's still obsessed with food.)
We should boil it more.
(He sometimes throws a tantrum.)
(He used to enjoy eating alone.)
The kimchi is good.
Se Yoon likes things like this.
(Now, he remembers
his members' tastes.)
- Welcome!
- Welcome.
(He's not just
a special guest anymore.)
(They've become family
who laugh together.)
(The changes over the past year)
(Now it's time to eat kalguksu.)
The mussels look nice.
I think it's ready to eat.
Are you trying the noodles?
(The mom tastes the food
to see if it's ready.)
He looks like a mom.
Now you can eat it however you like.
- Let's eat.
- Okay.
It has a lot of seafood in it.
This is a lot of seafood.
(Looking at the seafood piled up,)
(he can only smile.)
- Mother.
- Yes.
You have weak teeth,
so I'll give you only the soup.
It's okay. I have dentures.
- You have dentures? I see.
- Yes.
My gosh. It's really...
(Impressed)
It's just seafood itself.
(Kimchi is a must.)
(The warm soup seeps
into their chilled body.)
It tastes even better
as we eat it at the valley.
It's so nice and refreshing.
(They are twice as happy,
eating at the valley.)
(Getting a refill of kalguksu)
This is three servings of kalguksu,
so it's a little... Right?
Yes. I wish we had more.
- My gosh.
- Se Yoon, eat this.
(The daughter lets the mom
eat a piece of pork cutlet.)
- You can eat it. Gosh.
- I'm done.
(He's glad
to have a daughter like him.)
- Can we get more soup?
- No, it's okay.
(The daughter's sweet gesture)
We don't have this.
Why do you leave the food?
(The grandmother intercepts it.)
Because I want.
(He puts it in his mouth
without hesitation.)
Is this rice mine?
No, it's mine.
- Is it yours?
- You can have it.
(He even eats his grandson's rice.)
Se Yoon. Did you eat it already?
Did you eat it already?
- Eat what?
- The pork cutlet.
(Empty)
(Mother?)
Grandma!
Mom!
He gave it to his mom.
Why would the grandma
eat the mom's pork cutlet?
- How could you eat that?
- Did you really eat it?
(He lost his pork cutlet
with his eyes open.)
I forgot eating it.
Do you want me
to make you lose your memory?
(Grandma Jong Min is unstoppable.)
So is this
the one-year anniversary special?
Yes.
We came up with a lot of ideas.
The ideas weren't so bad.
Sae Ho talked...
about things like scuba diving,
baseball, arcade, and basketball.
I like that. They all sound good.
Joon's idea was...
going on an overseas trip
on a duck boat.
(Glaring)
Going from the Han River...
out to the sea on a boat
sold at a mall.
Going to another city
on a children's tricycle.
You were going to kill us.
You don't seem to like my ideas.
You can create your own channel
and do those things. It will be fun.
- I think so.
- No, I want to do them with you.
Did you enjoy your meal?
- Yes.
- It was really good.
To celebrate
your one-year anniversary,
we will give you some time
to enjoy dessert.
Right. We need a cake.
I need dessert.
(That sounds great.)
Let's go eat some dessert.
- I love it.
- Really?
I'll have a chocolate cake.
(What kind of dessert
is waiting for them?)
When is KOYOTE's new song
coming out?
On August 6.
Is it Songwriter Choi Jun Yeong,
- whom KOYOYE used to work with?
- Yes.
- And after a long time, again...
- Right. He wrote "Pure Love."
He wrote a lot of KOYOTE's songs.
He's famous.
- Can we listen to it?
- Sure.
I love your songs.
It's just an exciting song.
That's KOYOTE's style.
MC Im Cheol.
Let's go!
- What?
- It's REDM.
- It's really...
Retro EDM.
I want to go to a nightclub.
- One, two, three.
- Let's go!
(Dancing)
I love the song.
Nice.
(Shouting)
- What's the title?
- "Call Me."
- What?
- Give me a call.
("Call Me" by KOYOTE)
- My universe!
- Here we go, now!
(Are you going to kill me?)
(Today is our last Saturday night)
(More fun things
will happen next week.)
(Next episode)
(To blow away...)
(the midsummer heat,)
(they are coming.)
(Team 2 Days and 1 Night is here.)
(What? 2 Days and 1 Night?)
(They are coming to you
in a cooler way.)
(A mysterious voice
echoes through the building.)
(The moment you are discovered,)
(it's over.)
(The game has begun.)
(If you stay together, you survive.)
(If you split up,)
(you die.)
(Things are more difficult
than expected.)
(There's only one chance left.)
(Will they...)
(be able to survive?)
- This is...
- Shouldn't we leave right now?
- No. We should go later.
- Very sensitive.