[iQIYI Original]
Sponsored by OPPO Reno15
50MP Ultra-Wide Angle Selfie.
[OPPO Reno15 50MP Ultra-Wide Angle Selfie]
[OPPO Running Man Thailand
Never Stop Running]
[OPPO Reno15 5G
With Friends, Every Shot Is Trendy]
♪ Run, no matter how many times we fall ♪
[Oat]
♪ Run, even if the road ahead
isn't what we dream of ♪
[Jeff]
♪ No matter how challenging,
not giving up, we'll get there someday ♪
[Ink]
♪ As long as we're still breathing,
no matter how far the journey ♪
[Tay]
[NuNew]
♪ Just keep running ♪
[Daou]
[Phuak]
♪ Just keep running ♪
[OPPO Running Man Thailand
Never Stop Running]
Sponsored by OPPO Reno15
50MP Ultra-Wide Angle Selfie.
[OPPO Reno15 50MP Ultra-Wide Angle Selfie]
[RICH MAN Running Man Version]
[However...]
[Are there any remaining shares?]
Oat: Wow, and they won't even tell us
how many shares we've received.
Oat: Jeff, help me find Jeff.
[Chasing down Jeff!]
Oat: Oh no, there's nowhere left to run.
[Inheritance War—
Battle for the First Heir]
Tay: I won't give up.
[Absolutely cannot lose!]
[Which heir will survive until the end?]
[Pattaya City]
[Making a graceful entrance]
Phuak: I’m the second heir in the family.
Phuak: Wahahaha.
[R Group's Phuak, the big-shot trader]
Phuak: This weather
feels like my hometown, Miami.
[The sea breeze makes one
miss their Miami home]
Phuak: Hey. I miss...
[Hey]
Oat: Hey.
[The Wild Bear styled as the richest man]
-Oat: Did you take the car for maintenance?
-Phuak: Wow.
[R Group's Oat, owner
of a multi-billion baht diamond business]
-Oat: Didn't I tell you?
-Phuak: What?
-Oat: There's no need to fill the pool so full.
-Phuak: Wow.
[Who filled the pool
until it overflowed?]
[This is too much]
[Is this Oat's pool?]
-Oat: There's no need to fill the pool so full.
-Phuak: Wow.
[Typical Thai person talking nonsense]
-Phuak: Wow, is this your pool?
-Oat: This is my pool.
-Phuak: I'm staying overnight tonight. Oh boy.
-Oat: Ah.
[R Group's Tay Tawan,
heir to an international fashion brand]
[Almost tripped]
-Oat: Like this. It should be like this.
-Phuak: Open those eyes—use your eagle vision.
[Bad start, sad ending!]
-Tay: I'll start over.
-Oat: Actually, the way you just walked over was really cool.
[Image collapsed right at the start]
-Phuak: Who are you?
-Oat: Who are you?
-Tay: I'm the definition of quiet luxury.
-Oat: Wow.
Oat: No, if you're quiet luxury,
give me a call once you're rich because...
-Oat: because I'm very rich.
-Tay: Really?
Oat: That? Not the beach.
-Oat: It's my pool.
-Phuak: It's his pool.
Tay: Here’s the thing, Oat. This is called class.
-Tay: When you’re rich, everything just looks impressive.
-Oat: Oh, okay, so it's class.
Tay: Me? I’m rich… just low-key about it.
Tay: That’s what real wealth is—luxury.
-Tay: I could’ve taken a private jet here.
-Oat: Fine.
-Tay: But I care about the environment. So...
-Oat: Wow, Ink is here!
[But I don't do it because I'm eco-friendly]
[Scared me to death]
-Oat: Wow, Ink is here!
-Phuak: She's here, she's here!
Ink: I... actually, I don't know right now,
but I'm a very wealthy heir.
[R Group's Ink, big boss
of an entertainment company]
Ink: And I also want to be
the most powerful person in today's show.
Tay: Wow.
Ink: Pass the secret on to me.
[Pass the secret on to me]
Oat: Hahaha!
[Hahaha]
-Ink: Have I changed?
-Tay: Yes.
-Ink: I'm different now, right?
-Tay: You've really grown up during the 3 episodes I was away.
Oat: She's not the same Ink anymore.
Ink: Pass all the secrets to me.
-Oat: Wahahaha!
-Phuak: Well...
[We're proud of you]
-Phuak: Wow, who are these people?
-Oat: Hey.
-Oat: Wow!
-Ink: Oh my!
Ink: Wow, they... they look even richer
than we do.
[A mysterious team
and their rich personas]
Becky: Hello, everyone,
I'm Becky-Rebecca Praticia Armstrong.
[A charming actress]
TV Drama Scene: Shut up!
[Becky-Rebecca Armstrong]
[Girl From Nowhere: The Reset]
Becky: Princess of England.
[Princess of England]
Ink: Wow.
-Tay: She didn't come here to play a game.
-Oat: Ah.
-Tay: She came to meet her people.
-Oat: Wow.
[R Group Princess Becky,
heir managing overseas enterprises]
Bank: Hello, everyone,
I am Robert Banky Martin XI.
[Robert Banky Martin XI,
boss of the R Group real estate empire]
[Mos Long RattanaPraditkornHirankornNiran,
R Group's sports industry heir]
Mos: Hello, everyone,
I am Mos Long RattanaPraditkornHirankornNiran.
TV Drama Scene: If you don’t mind,
you could sleep with me tonight.
[The two leads of a hit drama]
TV Drama Scene: I just want to stay like this
and keep looking at you.
[Mos and Bank]
Offroad: Hello, everyone, I am Offroad,
heir to an oil tycoon.
[R Group heir Offroad, oil tycoon]
Ink: Wow, I miss Daou.
Offroad: It's okay.
I'm here representing him.
Offroad: Are you happy today?
[Daou’s man…]
Daou: I'm happy.
-Offroad: You're happy, right?
-Daou: Yes.
[Offroad]
-Offroad: Oh.
-Really.
[Leave it to me]
Oat: The richest person is here,
the richest person is here.
[My rival?]
Oat: The richest person is here,
the richest person is here.
[Jeff]
[Chairman Jeff,
R Group's Planning Department]
Everyone: Wow.
[You walked past us, Jeff!]
-Phuak: Ah, wait a second.
-Ink: You walked past.
Tay: I was just about to tell him
to keep walking.
[Smart and humorous]
Tay: I was just about to tell him
to keep walking.
PD: Okay, now we have everyone gathered.
[Gathered the children of R Group]
PD: Welcome, challengers, to compete
for the position of the R Group heir.
PD: We will divide into 3 groups,
3 people per group.
Oat: Okay.
PD: The winner of each mission
PD: will have the right to obtain
a higher percentage of shares.
PD: When the final match ends,
PD: the person with the most shares
becomes the heir to the R Group.
[The person with the highest percentage of stock]
[will be the heir to R Group]
PD: These cards in front of you
[9 envelopes containing stock percentages]
PD: are the stock percentages.
PD: There are 9 in total.
[The heirs are choosing their stock cards]
Becky: Wow.
Phuak: Hahaha!
-Tay: But looking at it, that smile isn't a good sign.
-Ink: I can tell it's bad.
PD: So now everyone has received
your initial stock percentages.
PD: Since you're going to be corporate heirs,
PD: you must have the ability
to choose people to join our teams.
[The top 3 shareholders will
earn the right to choose team members]
PD: The top 3 shareholders will
earn the right to choose team members.
-Phuak: Oh.
-Oat: Wow.
PD: The largest shareholder is...
[The largest shareholder]
[Could it be me?]
[The largest Shareholder: Becky!]
PD: Becky.
Oat: Wow.
Phuak: For real?
[Becky holds 10%]
-Oat: Becky.
-Ink: Wow, Becky.
PD: The second largest shareholder is...
[The second Largest Shareholder: Oat!]
PD: Oat.
Everyone: Wow.
[Oat holds 7%]
Jeff: Wow, our Oat cheated.
Tay: No wonder he dared
to wear green today.
Oat: Well, today, there's no need
to look at any percentages.
Oat: Just look at my clothes.
Oat: As everyone knows,
I'm the owner of a "green snack shop."
[The third largest shareholder is...]
PD: And the third person
with the right to choose members is...
Phuak: It's impossible, Tay. Impossible.
[Phuak!]
PD: Phuak.
Phuak: It's impossible, Tay.
PD: It's Phuak.
Bank: Ah, you’re such a liar!
[Even he himself is shocked]
[Phuak holds 6%]
Phuak: Hahaha!
[The highest shareholders need to pick teammates]
[10%] [7%] [6%]
PD: You will
take turns picking members.
[What will be the outcome
of the team selection?]
[Starting with our Princess]
Becky: How many times has everyone won?
-Phuak: Oh, are you conducting an interview?
-Becky: It's an interview.
[Picking based on win rates]
-Oat: Don't know how many times anyone won,
but we 2 haven't won at all. -Phuak: Yes.
[In terms of winning games,
they might not be qualified]
Oat: You can use this as a reference.
[Raise your hand if you've won]
Phuak: Who has won? Raise your hand,
Becky is asking.
Jeff: Excuse me,
I have never lost on this show.
[Sorry, but I'm always in first place]
Jeff: Excuse me,
I have never lost on this show.
[I'm just as good as him.]
Phuak: How many times have you won?
How many?
Jeff: 4 times.
[Both have won 4 matches]
Ink: 4 times.
[But Ink has lost]
Jeff: But Ink has lost.
She lost last time.
Ink: It was my first loss.
Becky: Then I'm going
to choose someone who has won.
[Then I will pick...]
Bank: Wow, here she comes.
[Jeff!]
Becky: I pick Jeff.
[Cunning fox!]
[Sorry about that]
-Phuak: Look, he's showing off.
-Becky: Have you really won?
Phuak: Jeff Satur?
Becky: Have you really won?
Jeff: Yes, I did win,
Oat: I love how Becky asks
after already choosing.
Oat: "Have you really won?"
-Phuak: You don't trust him?
-Oat: Have you really won?
[Oat's turn to pick]
Oat: Is it my turn to pick?
[Oat, Ink is over here]
[The best choice is here]
Oat: Is it my turn to pick?
Oat: Well, I'll do something different.
[Ink, come join me!]
Oat: Ink, come join me.
Ink: Hooray!
Phuak: He's taking a different path.
Oat: My goddess.
Oat: Because in today's games,
we might not need that much physical strength.
Oat: We might need luck. In terms of luck,
Ink has won many times.
Phuak: Great.
[Happy]
Phuak: And most importantly,
if we’re going to be a team,
[Prioritizing trust]
Phuak: we need to trust each other.
Phuak: I’ve been hurt way too many times,
Phuak: over and over again.
Jeff: Who hurt you like that, Phuak?
Phuak: It was you!
[Don't act all innocent!]
-Phuak: It was you!
-Jeff: Oh.
[Will I be betrayed, too?]
Phuak: But there's only one person
[Who?]
Everyone: Wow.
Phuak: who hasn't hurt me.
[Why are you avoiding eye contact, Tay?]
Mos: Why is this young man
keeping his head down?
Phuak: Come on, sell yourself a bit.
[Dear Tay, look at me!]
Phuak: Sell yourself a bit, dear Tay.
Tay: As I said, silence says it all.
The other person will understand.
[Silence says it all]
[Thais just love talking nonsense]
Phuak: I pick Tay Tawan!
[I pick Tay Tawan!]
Everyone: Hooray!
Phuak: I pick Tay Tawan!
[Full of blessings]
[Beaming with joy]
Tay: Happy.
Phuak: If you're happy, say it louder.
[Tay only has 1% stock]
[I'm going to make a fuss]
[Collaboration between the 3rd largest shareholder
and the 1% shareholder]
[Becky picks Mos]
Becky: I pick Mos.
Everyone: Yay!
Tay: She picked all the big ones—
everyone’s so high-end.
[Men with a great image]
Phuak: She prioritizes physical strength.
[A team of experts—Becky's team!]
Oat: Actually, I already had
an ideal team member in mind.
[Daou's request]
[Daou: Help me take care of Offroad.]
[Oat: Sure.]
Oat: Because an heir personally
Oat: asked me to take good care of him.
Oat: I pick Offroad.
Oat: Welcome, welcome.
Offroad: Hello, Oat.
[High energy and lucky—Oat's team!]
Ink: Daou asked you to take care of him.
Oat: Now we're in the same team.
[Oat's Team: Ink/Oat/Offroad]
Phuak: Finally, all the people
who have never won are gathered in my team.
Phuak: Hahaha, welcome, Bank.
[Team Bad Luck—Phuak's Team!]
Ink: Wow, so quiet.
[God, help me]
Phuak: Why is there a hand signal
for help?
Phuak: Hey, come over here.
Phuak: Don't ask for help with anything.
Phuak: Where are you going?
Tay: Others have strength.
We have nothing.
[Error 404] [Strength] [Brainpower]
Tay: We have nothing left.
Phuak: At least we’ve got heart.
Tay: Fair enough. Okay, I'm in.
[Selection results]
[Oat's Team] [Becky's Team] [Phuak's Team]
Female Assistant: Boss,
you have so many things.
Female Assistant: But fortunately,
the GAC AION V is really spacious.
Offroad: That's why I chose the GAC AION V.
Female Assistant: Here's your ice water.
Offroad: The GAC AION V's refrigerator
is really good.
Female Assistant: The temperature
can go as low as -15°C.
Offroad: So refreshing! Now I’ve got the energy
for today’s missions.
Offroad: Let's go.
[Pattaya, full of entertainment]
[What will the first mission be like?]
[Running Man Thailand Never Stop Running]
PD: Our first mission is the
"Finding People's Shares" mission.
Everyone: Wow.
PD: Do you all see these 2 wheels
in front of you?
[Share Hunt: Find the People Mission]
"Share Hunt: Find the People" Mission.
There are 2 types of wheels:
the Number Wheel and the Blank Wheel.
[Number Wheel] [Blank Wheel]
Before starting, each team needs
to send a representative to spin the Number Wheel.
[Number Wheel]
The number it lands on
[Number of People]
determines how many people
each team must recruit to participate in the mission.
The first team to bring people
to the starting point can challenge first.
[Start Mission]
If the mission fails,
[Mission Failed]
the next team can begin their challenge.
[Start Mission]
The team that succeeds in the challenge
[Mission Success]
will receive 2 stickers.
They can be placed on the Blank Wheel.
[Blank Wheel]
After all 3 games are finished,
the Blank Wheel with stickers will be spun.
If it stops on a team's sticker slot,
they will receive
the corresponding stock shares.
[Shares]
[The first game
of Share Hunt: Find the People Mission is...]
PD: The first game is jump rope.
PD: You need to find people
for "Unity Jump Rope."
[Gather people for Unity Jump Rope]
PD: Everyone jumps together
at the same time.
Oat: For example, if it's 10 people,
will they all have to jump together?
Oat: Wow.
[You guys really know
how to cause trouble]
Oat: If it stops on 10...
PD: Who will the 3 teams send
to spin the Number Wheel?
[Confident! Unafraid! Fearless!]
Becky: My luck is quite good today.
Mos: Okay, you do it.
Oat: Let it be Becky.
Becky has the highest stock percentage. Please.
Offroad: The minimum right now is 3.
[Hoping for the minimum number!]
Ink: Becky, spin a 3.
Becky: Okay.
Tay: 1, 2, 3.
[Just need a 3...]
Jeff: 3, 3.
[God, please...]
[5 People!]
Everyone: 5 people.
Becky: Not bad, right?
Phuak: Not bad, not bad.
-Oat: Pick kids.
-Ink: Kids.
[Prioritize looking for kids.]
[Around 10 years old is perfect]
Ink: Find young people.
[Oat's team thinks of children first]
-Ink: Because adults probably wouldn't be interested.
-Oat: Correct.
Jeff: That foreign guy
over there should be very capable.
Mos: Probably. What do you think, Becky?
[Becky's team is looking
for reliable-looking foreigners]
Becky: Exactly.
Tay: Hurry, hurry! Over there, over there.
[Phuak's team plans to go for the fans]
-Bank: We should pick our own people.
-Tay: Our own people? Okay, okay.
Mos: Jeff, where are you going? Come here.
[Teams depart!]
[On the 4-kilometer-long Pattaya Beach]
[Will they find people  successfully?]
Tay: I’m not even trying to hide it.
[The Red Team rushes out quickly]
Tay: You want to play a game?
Jump rope together.
Phuak: Coming?
-Tay: Yay! Great, great.
-Bank: Come jump rope with us.
[Tay successfully invited the first person]
[Go over there]
-Phuak: Over there, over there.
-Bank: Are you good at skipping rope?
Tay: Okay, okay.
[Sharp vision]
[The boy looks very agile]
[Phuak immediately calls the next person]
Phuak: Beautiful lady,
over here, over here.
Phuak: Can you play a game with me?
Let's play together.
Phuak: Can you come and jump rope with us?
-Phuak: The jump rope. It’ll be quick.
-Girl: I have to work.
-Girl: I still have things to sell.
-Phuak: Is that so?
[Rejected on just the second pick,
will the Red Team still make it through?]
Offroad: Let's try it first.
Can you show me how you jump?
[Meanwhile, the Yellow Team
is planning the recruitment strategy]
Ink: Do you know how to jump rope?
Offroad: The first question should be,
"Do you know how to jump rope?"
Offroad: Let’s communicate first.
Oat: Look, he's smiling.
He's smiling at us.
[Calling out as soon as eyes meet]
Oat: Hey, bro, wait a second. Wait up.
-Ink: Come here.
-Offroad: He's running.
Ink: Bro, come here for a moment.
Offroad: He's running. He's running away.
Offroad: Hey, he's running.
[Running toward the chosen person]
Offroad: Why is he running?
Oat: Kid, come here, come here.
[Like a reunion of old friends]
Oat: Kid, come,
come with me for a moment.
Oat: Kid, let's go be on the show.
Oat: Come join our show for a bit.
[Adults or children are both fine]
Oat: Come, kid, come film with me.
Ink: Can you jump rope? Can you?
[Yes!]
Ink: Wow, this one, he can jump rope.
-Ink: Can you jump rope?
-Offroad: Can you jump rope?
-Ink: You can't? Okay.
-Oat: Bro, let's go jump rope.
Oat: Let's go, we'll take a photo later.
Oat: Hey, do you have any other friends?
[Suddenly they have 4 members]
Oat: Any other friends?
Oat: 3 people now. 3 people.
[The Blue Team is still looking for members]
Mos: Is this one okay?
Jeff: Okay, okay. You should invite them.
[Who will be the first member to join?]
Jeff: And these two.
Those guys renting out the banana boat.
Jeff: Nice. Who else?
Jeff: Sorry, guys,
do you wanna play a game with us?
[Trying hard to invite foreign tourists]
Man: No, thanks.
[Better look for a new target]
Jeff: No, thanks.
Mos: Hahaha.
Becky: Bro.
Mos: Bro.
Becky: Do you want
to play jump rope with us?
Jeff: I'll pay for one banana boat rental,
then you come jump rope with me, okay?
-Becky: Is that okay?
-Mos: Is it okay? Is it okay?
[Successfully recruited the first member!]
Mos: Please.
-Jeff: Okay, okay, okay.
-Becky: Yay!
Mos: Do you have any partners?
I need 5 people.
Mos: It's very fun.
-Becky: Let's go. Let's go jump rope.
-Mos: Jump.
Jeff: It's very fast.
Do you have any other friends?
Becky: Come on, come, come.
Jeff: You invite them.
[While they are looking for team members]
Mos: 5 people. We need 5 people.
[Is there already a team
that has successfully gathered five members?]
Mos: They have gathered all the people?
Becky: What?
Jeff: Ah, how are they so fast?
[The first team to arrive is...]
Red Team: Wow.
Tay: You guys underestimated us too much.
Don't underestimate us.
[How did the Red Team
turn things around to be first?]
Phuak: Come, come, come.
Everyone, line up for a bit.
Phuak: Play a game.
Can you come play a game with us?
Girl: No, I have to work.
Phuak: Can you come jump rope with us?
[While Phuak and Bank
are repeatedly rejected]
Phuak: Jump rope, jump rope.
It'll be quick.
[Tay is fighting against fate]
Phuak: Can you jump rope?
Phuak: What kind of work do you do?
-Girl: I'm working. I'm selling things.
-Phuak: Is that so?
[CEO Tay tries hard to invite people]
Tay: Come with us. It's just jump rope.
It's very easy.
[2 members join together]
Tay: It's enough. We've got 3 people now.
-Tay: We got 3 people now.
-Phuak: 3 people. 3 people.
Phuak: Find 2 more.
[Trying to negotiate again
with someone who just refused]
Phuak: 2 more. Can you?
-Phuak: You can? Then come on.
-Tay: Go, go.
[Successfully found 5 people!]
Tay: Hurry, hurry. Go that way.
Phuak: Go, go, go. Hurry, hurry.
Tay: I won!
Phuak: See?
My team is just this impressive.
Phuak: Hurry. See?
Phuak: My team is just this impressive.
Ink: Have they got all the people over there?
Oat: Are there any partners?
Is that guy over there working?
Oat: Call him over, call him over.
[Let's finish this game!]
Oat: Bro, let's go film a show.
Oat: Bro.
Ink: Can you jump rope?
Oat: Let's go. Let's jump rope, jump rope.
Ink: Come, come.
[The Yellow Team has gathered 5 people]
Oat: Follow the flag, everyone.
[Meanwhile, the Blue Team is still looking]
Becky: Ah, why is no one coming with us?
[Jeff is still trying hard
to invite foreign tourists]
Jeff: Hi, sorry. Excuse me. Do you wanna
Jeff: play a game with us?
We're shooting a program.
Jeff: Yes, just one.
Jeff: No, no, no. We, you and...
[Continuous failures]
-Man: No, no, no. Sorry.
-Jeff: We'll be in a team.
Jeff: Oh, it's okay, it's okay.
Jeff: We're filming Running Man.
Do you know the Running Man?
Jeff: Alright. I'm so sorry.
Becky: Sorry.
[Need to change the strategy!]
Mos: Inviting foreigners
doesn't seem to work.
Becky: Thai people.
Let's look for Thai people.
Jeff: Hello.
Jeff: Can you come play a game with me?
We're short on people. Just one. It's very fast.
[Confused]
-Mos: Just jump. It’s really easy.
-Becky: It's very fast.
[Accidentally becomes
their last member.]
Jeff: Okay, let's go.
Mos: This way, please. Come on, come on.
Oat: Wow.
[Everyone finally returns
to the starting point]
Phuak: Where did you all run off to?
Oat: Where?
Jeff: We went looking
for the strongest people.
[The Blue Team's powerful members]
PD: For this mission,
Phuak's Red Team arrived here first.
PD: They will be the first team
to challenge.
PD: If the challenge is successful,
they can take over this mission's blank slot.
PD: Then we will start the next mission.
[There might be teams
that cannot participate in the competition!]
[Incredibly confident]
Phuak: Piece of cake.
Bank: We just need to succeed.
Offroad: You've played
jump rope before, right?
-Boy: I have. I jump every day.
-Offroad: Wow, every day?
[Round 1: Pass by jumping
more than 5 times]
Bank: It’s my first time here.
I want to win in the very first game.
[Burning fighting spirit]
Bank: I want it so much.
Bank: Kid, jump a bit higher.
You need to jump really high for this.
[I believe I can fly]
Ink: He looks pretty good.
Jeff: It might not even be our turn.
This isn't that difficult.
Phuak: Let's be serious!
[Start]
[Doesn't look like any mistakes?]
[Oh no!]
[Tripped...]
[Did it end just like that?]
[Heartbreaking end]
Bank: Just now... I don't know.
[We have to do this too, right?]
Ink: Ah, this isn't easy.
[Now the Red Team can challenge]
Oat: Come on. This way, please.
Ink: Let's go, let's go.
Jeff: Ah, you planned for so long.
[It isn't that easy...]
-Phuak: It's difficult.
-Oat: It's very, very hard.
[We still have hope, right?]
Mos: I thought we had no chance at first.
Becky: Mmhmm, it seems quite difficult.
[The Yellow Team's first round]
Oat: Offroad, let's stand closer together.
Oat: Closer.
Oat: Mmhmm, okay.
Phuak: Are you ready, Coach?
[Team Oat is arranging their positions]
[What are you doing?]
Oat: Hey.
Ink: Oat, you set the pose.
[Amidst the chaos,
someone is secretly being mischievous]
Phuak: Come on, come on. Start.
[If we don't win, you won't, either]
Phuak: Are you ready?
Offroad: Hey, hey.
Offroad: Eh, they're cheating.
[I was just joking]
[Tay is casting a spell attack]
Tay: Da-da-da, da-da-da-da,
da-da-da-da, da-da.
Offroad: Okay, from right to left, everyone.
Offroad: 1, 2.
Oat: Jump.
[Report: one student here
can’t even get off the ground]
[Causing 3 people
to get tangled in the rope]
[The Yellow Team failed
their first jump rope attempt]
Ink: It's really not easy.
Oat: Didn't we agree on the rhythm?
1, 2, jump.
[Oat conducts one-on-one teaching]
Oat: 1, 2, jump. 1, 2, jump.
[Maybe the odds will return to our hands]
-Tay: How was it? My spell?
-Bank: How was it?
Phuak: No success yet.
[It's the Blue Team's turn]
Mos: Bro, 2 of you come over to my side.
Mos: You need to be a good jumper.
Mos: Alright, everyone, I'll count to 3,
and then you jump with me.
Mos: 1, 2, 3, jump! Jump!
[Agreed in advance]
Mos: Jump. Good, just like that.
Wait until I count to 3.
Becky: We're serious.
[Why does it feel like they can do it?]
Phuak: Are those two covering their faces
national jump rope athletes?
Tay: Yeah.
Phuak: They look just like athletes.
[Is the Blue Team secretly
recruiting disguised national athletes?]
Jeff: Mos, let's start.
[The Blue Team's first round]
Mos: Go.
Mos: Jump.
[The 1st time]
[The 2nd time]
Mos: Jump.
[The 3rd time]
Ink: Ah, no!
[Will they really succeed?]
Ink: No!
Mos: Jump.
[Successfully jumped 4 times!]
[Only one last time...] [Please...]
Mos: Jump.
[The 1st time]
[The 2nd time]
Mos: Jump.
[The 3rd time]
[The 4th time]
Mos: Jump.
[But failed at the very last one!]
[It's my useless feet!
Why couldn't I jump over!]
Jeff: So close.
[What a pity]
Red Team: Yay!
[Our chance is back!]
Mos: Impressive, impressive.
You're so impressive.
-Jeff: Great, great.
-Mos: Impressive, impressive.
Mos: Everyone was very impressive.
[The Red Team's second round]
Phuak: Again, again.
[Using the 4:4 back-to-back positioning]
Phuak: Should we face
the opposite direction?
Phuak: Meaning splitting in half,
this side and that side.
Bank: Mmhmm, then let's split
into 2 sides.
[Will this method really succeed?]
PD: Are you ready?
Phuak: Ready.
Phuak: Everyone, get ready.
Tay: Let's go.
[Successfully jumped on this side, however...]
[The other side couldn't]
Tay: Are you okay? Are you okay?
Oat: Are you okay? Did you hurt?
[Before starting the second round,
the Yellow Team has a serious discussion]
Offroad: If we put our arms
over each other's shoulders, would it help?
Offroad: As for the jump rope...
Ink: Go, Yellow Team.
[The people also offered their opinions]
Ink: Oat, our team is about to challenge.
Oat: Let's go, let's go.
Offroad: Should we go back-to-back?
[Looks like a method that could work]
-Oat: No need for words. Just jump.
-Offroad: Let's try it. Let's go.
Oat: No need for words. Just jump.
[Executing the new plan discussed
with the people]
-Offroad: Is everyone ready? -Oat: Yes.
[Will the Yellow Team succeed
in the challenge?]
Oat: Jump.
[Failed in one second!]
Oat: Jump!
Oat: Oh, kid.
[Failed in the same spot for the 2nd time]
Oat: You kid, it's you again.
Oat: Why is it you again?
[Hahaha]
Oat: You stand at the very front.
Oat: You'll lead in the next round.
[The Blue Team starts the 2nd round]
Jeff: Stay in the middle.
Mos: Everyone, let's get closer.
A bit closer.
[Positions arranged, nice and neat]
Mos: Come in, get closer.
[This time it's for real!]
-Mos: Jump.
-Everyone: 1.
[The 1st time]
-Mos: Jump.
-Everyone: 2.
[The 2nd time]
-Mos: Jump.
-Everyone: 3.
[The 3rd time]
[The Blue Team jumps with a steady rhythm]
-Mos: Jump.
-Everyone: 4.
[The 4th time]
[Blue Team jumps with a steady rhythm]
[The last time, if it is a success...]
[Our team...]
[Our team will win!]
[No, victory is ours!]
Ink: Ah.
-Mos: Jump higher.
-Everyone: 3.
[The 3rd time]
-Mos: Jump.
-Everyone: 4.
[The 4th time]
[The 5th time]
[The Blue Team successfully challenged
Unity Jump Rope!]
Mos: Jump.
Jeff: You're very impressive.
Very impressive.
Jeff: Impressive, impressive.
[Congratulations...]
Mos: Everyone was very impressive.
Impressive.
[Won, but haven't adjusted yet]
Jeff: Impressive, impressive.
Super impressive.
-Mos: Everyone was very impressive. Impressive.
-Jeff: Impressive, impressive.
Phuak: It's like this again.
Satur won again.
Tay: But we weren't even
thinking about winning.
Phuak: Exactly.
Tay: Our wish came true.
Everyone: Thank you, everyone, thank you.
[Thank you, people,
for participating in our game]
[Bring on the next mission. I'm ready!]
[It's time to put on the stickers]
PD: The Blue Team wins.
Please place the stickers on the wheel.
Bank: Hey, but their members
were all very impressive.
Jeff: Stick them on opposite sides,
because...
Becky: Stick them like this?
-Jeff: If it doesn't stop on our slot, it's possible...
-Becky: I see. Okay.
Jeff: Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Everyone was great.
[The Blue Team received 2 slots]
[Running Man continues
under the bright sun]
[Will next mission continue
the intensity of the previous one?]
PD: For the second game,
PD: you need to find people
who look like the emojis.
[Finding people who look like the emojis]
[Again?]
Phuak: Ah, again?
[We have to play this again?]
Oat: Again?
Becky: What? We have to find people again?
[The second mission
also requires cooperation with people]
-Oat: Goddess, goddess.
-Bank: Tay.
-Ink: Again?
[Each team sends a representative
to pick an emoji]
-Offroad: Ink, go ahead.
-Oat: Tay.
Phuak: Go! Even the clothes are ready.
Mos: Should I pick for you?
Mos: Oh boy, oh boy.
Tay: Let's see.
Phuak: Good, Tay. Don't give in.
Mos: What happened?
Tay: I stole his luck.
Phuak: Good, good.
Ink: He definitely grabbed a bad one.
Phuak: I think so.
[Can we get something good for once]
PD: Alright, let’s see what each team got.
[Let's see which emoji
the 3 teams draw]
-PD: Yellow Team.
-Phuak: What emoji is it?
[The Yellow Team unseals first]
PD: Yellow Team.
[The emoji is the deciding factor
for mission difficulty]
[Yellow Team's Emoji]
[Item List] [Bandana] [Shirt] [Shorts] [Canvas Shoes]
[Difficulty Level: 4 Stars]
Ink: Wow, that's hard.
Oat: Exactly.
Oat: If we can't find it,
can we swap for a T-shirt?
Oat: Can it be a T-shirt?
[Start searching] [Let's pray]
PD: Okay. Top and shorts.
[Drawn shirt and shorts]
Oat: Uh, can we use a hat as a substitute?
[Yellow Team's Emoji]
[If without bandana...] [Difficulty Level: 2 Stars]
PD: Hats are not allowed.
[Must have a bandana]
Oat: Because this is very hard.
Oat: Looking around, there's not even one.
[Neither on this side]
[Nor on that side]
[Not a single one]
Oat: Because this kind of fabric
is very hard to find.
PD: Then as long as there's headwear.
[As long as there's headwear]
Oat: It could be a hat? Okay.
[The Yellow Team decides
to substitute with a hat]
-Oat: Hats are easy.
-Offroad: Hats will do.
Ink: But what about canvas shoes?
Phuak: Take a look at the picture.
Jeff: If we get a bad picture...
Phuak: What's our picture?
[What will the destiny stolen
from Mos look like?]
Phuak: Ah!
Tay: It's easy!
[Incredible]
Phuak: No, what kind of "easy" is this?
[How high does the similarity need to be?]
Phuak: Just how much
do they have to look alike?
[Red Team's Emoji]
[Item List] [Shirt] [Short Skirt] [Bangs]
[Difficulty Level: 5 Stars]
[They must have bangs]
-PD: Bangs, they must have bangs.
-Phuak: They must have bangs?
-Tay: Bring the scissors.
-Phuak: Come on, find them yourselves.
Tay: I'll cut your bangs for free.
Phuak: Hey, come on, find them yourselves.
[Maybe the PD should
try finding them instead!]
Mos: Hahaha.
[You grab it yourself, huh? Hehe.]
Phuak: Hey, come on, find them yourselves.
Tay: My heart is so tired.
I'm truly tired of this game.
[Look carefully]
[Fighting, Tay]
Mos: Oh, ours is considered easy.
[The Blue Team is secretly showing off]
[Easy-to-spot outfit]
Becky: The shirt also needs
to be like this, right?
[The Yellow Team's Emoji]
[Item List]
[Hawaiian Shirt] [T-shirt] [Shorts] [Flip-flops]
[Difficulty Level: 2 Stars]
PD: Everyone, spin the wheel to see
how many people you need to find.
[Next, drawing the number of people]
Oat: Tay, you go spin it.
Phuak: Tay, spin it.
Jeff: Tay, are you serious?
-Jeff: Tay, are you serious?
-Oat: Maybe Tay will spin a 9.
[Tay acts as the representative
to spin the wheel]
Phuak: Hey, wait a second.
[If we're going down,
we're going down together]
Phuak: No, wait a second.
Becky: Oh my god.
[Silence...]
[The wheel is spinning!]
Ink: Oh my god!
[What the...] [10?]
[What the fxxx!]
-Mos: Tay!
-Bank: Tay.
Bank: Are you okay?
[Please punish me]
Ink: Tay, why?
Oat: Tay.
[Speechless]
Ink: Can we spin again?
Offroad: Tay.
Becky: Is he hurt?
[This unlucky fate]
Bank: It took over an hour
to find 5 people earlier.
Ink: Can we spin again?
Tay: Can you understand?
I don't want to care about anything anymore.
-Tay: Let everything be as it is. I don't care.
-Bank: I love my job.
[Find 10 people who match the emojis]
[Red Team] [Blue Team] [Yellow Team]
[Outfits drawn by each team are..]
[The first team that can bring the people back]
[can take over the entire wheel]
PD: 1, 2, 3!
[Finding 10 people for similar emojis]
Mos: Oh boy, let's go.
[Game start!]
Oat: Let's go, go, go.
Offroad: Where did that person
go just now?
-Ink: I'm truly done.
-Oat: We don't need to wait; the cameramen have to wait for us.
[On this vast Pattaya beach,
will the agents find the people?]
Offroad: Let's go, let's go.
[Let's go!]
Oat: Go.
Ink: Oat.
Ink: Is this lady okay?
Does she have a hat?
Ink: Hello, I'm filming a show.
Can you help me?
Offroad: You just need to stand there
for a bit.
Ink: Just stand there.
-Oat: Beautiful lady.
-Offroad: We are looking for a clothing style.
Ink: They should be dressed just like you.
We need 10 people.
[Wearing a T-shirt and shorts]
Ink: You brought a hat, right?
Girl: This is from the hotel.
Offroad: Oh, that works.
-Ink: Can we borrow it for a bit?
-Offroad: Can we just borrow it?
[That's great]
Offroad: You don't have to do anything.
Just participate in the show.
Ink: Is it okay?
Just join our show for a bit.
[Nod] [The Yellow Team finds one person]
Ink: Thank you.
Offroad: Thank you.
-Ink: We found 1 person.
-Offroad: Thank you. We found 1. Let's go.
Oat: We'll be back in a bit,
back in a bit.
Oat: Let's go, go, go.
Oat: Hey, kid, do you have any friends
dressed just like you?
[Confirming with the image]
Oat: Wearing a hat.
[Awkwardness x 10,000]
-Offroad: I'll go look for others.
-Oat: That kid with the skate shoes.
Oat: If you see any, let me know.
[Can't miss the next one]
[The Red Team is also searching]
Phuak: Let's walk along the beach.
Phuak: Walk along the beach.
-Tay: They said it doesn't have to be plaid,
just a shirt and skirt. -Bank: This one.
Tay: They said no plaid needed.
[Found a target right at the start]
Tay: Just add a skirt.
-Tay: Look, we need a skirt.
-Bank: Skirt, skirt.
-Phuak: This looks super similar.
-Tay: Hello.
-Bank: Hello.
[Bangs + Short Skirt—complete]
Bank: Can you come play a game with us?
Phuak: Can you join our team?
[Nod]
Phuak: Done.
[Successfully found 1 person]
Phuak: Found 1 person.
-Phuak: Okay, okay.
-Tay: Thank you.
[Continuing to find the next target]
Phuak: We're doomed.
Bank: The skirt. It's exactly the same.
That person in white.
Bank: So many, so many.
Phuak: Great, found someone again.
-Phuak: Bank did great.
-Tay: Hello.
Bank: Hello.
[Encountered 2 beautiful women in skirts]
Tay: We want to invite you
to join our Running Man game.
Tay: We need people wearing skirts.
Can I invite you to join us?
[Say yes!]
Tay: Wow, thank you, thank you.
Phuak: The staff will take you over
to gather there in a moment.
Tay: Thank you.
Tay: You'll go with us.
I'll go find a few more.
[Thank you for your kindness]
[Found 2 people]
-Tay: Hello, hello.
-Phuak: Hello.
[The Red Team's current situation]
[Successfully invited 2 out of 10 people]
[The Blue Team agents all confirmed]
[Successfully found 1 person]
Blue Team: Yay!
-Jeff: Thank you.
-Mos+Becky: Thank you, thank you so much.
Oat: Ah, there's a group of women
over there.
Offroad: Where, where?
Oat: Over there, over there. I see them.
[Finally found]
-Oat: Dear...
-Offroad: Hello.
Offroad: You all came together, right?
[A group of all beautiful women]
Offroad: Do you have a hat?
-Oat: Hey, ladies, casting?
-Ink: Are you here on vacation?
[Confused]
Offroad: Do you have a hat?
Offroad: Do you have any?
[Just then, he happens to see]
[Child's hat?]
-Offroad: Do you have any?
-Oat: Ant Handkerchief?
[Stole it]
Ink: Do you have a handkerchief?
[It fits well after putting it on]
Offroad: Super cute.
[Waaa, where is my hat?]
[Oat will protect you from the sun]
Ink: Found 1. 1.
Ink: This one. A friend lent it to you.
Ink: It's from another lady.
Can you give it to this lady?
Ink: Can you give it to this lady?
Ink: Can you go with us?
[And now, the hat is passed
to Offroad's hand]
Offroad: Do you have canvas shoes?
Ink: Here, there's another person.
Ink: Can you give it to this lady?
-Offroad: Come with us.
-Ink: Sorry to bother you.
[Successfully found 3 people wearing hats]
Oat: Okay, let's go together.
Offroad: We found 2 people already.
[The Yellow Team acts quickly]
-Offroad: Go with us.
-Oat: Let's go, go, dear.
Oat: Here?
Girl: Why are you
so handsome in person?
Oat: Am I handsome in person?
Girl: You're not fat at all.
Oat: Not fat, right?
I'm just not fat in person.
Oat: Right, because I eat very little.
I haven't had much money lately.
Oat: Do you have money to lend me?
Oat: Wait a second, don't leave yet.
Oat: Wait for me a bit, wait a bit longer.
It'll be quick.
[Meeting time with the people is over]
-Oat: You wait for me first.
-Girl: Okay.
[Oat Pramote mini fan meeting]
[The Yellow Team's current situation]
[Successfully invited 3 out of 10 people]
[The Blue Team is walking toward a target]
Becky: Buy 1.
Jeff: Buy 1. Okay, I'll pick.
Jeff: Just buy...
Jeff: How about this one?
[Is it a Hawaiian shirt?]
[Cunning fox]
[The Blue Team is buying clothes identical to the emoji]
-Mos: This one works too. This one.
-Jeff: Okay, okay, okay.
Jeff: Thank you.
-Mos: Thank you.
-Jeff: Let's go, let's go.
[Hawaiian shirt bought]
Jeff: Yes.
Jeff: Okay, now anyone will do.
[Anyone will do now]
Becky: Okay.
[Hawaiian shirt: check!]
[Shorts: check!]
Jeff: Then we're done. Can we go first?
Becky: Here.
Jeff: Come on.
PD: Okay.
-PD: This team is okay. Pass.
-Jeff: Okay.
[As if he stepped out of the emoji!]
Jeff: Okay.
Jeff: Your friend. Your friend.
[According to the original plan]
Becky: You give it to your friend.
[Cunning people, even tricking the staff!]
[The Blue Team's current situation]
[Successfully invited 2 out of 10 people]
Bank: Wow, I think this beach...
-Phuak: Yeah, it’s hard to spot them on the beach.
-Bank: They probably won’t be wearing skirts.
-Tay: If we can find 10 people...
-Phuak: How about we buy skirts?
Tay: Right. Should we?
[The Red Team's idea is similar
to the Blue Team's]
Bank: Really. Oh boy.
-Phuak: What's wrong?
-Bank: There's a clothing store here.
Tay: Should we?
-Tay: Should we?
-Bank: The skirt.
Tay: Right, should we buy a skirt?
Tay: There's no rule saying we can't.
Tay: Ah, be careful.
-Bank: Hello, do you have any skirts?
-Tay: Any elastic waist short skirts?
Phuak: Not even one?
Phuak: Really? There are no short skirts
in this store?
Proprietress: No short skirts,
only long skirts.
Phuak: Just how long?
Proprietress: Down to here.
[Immediately heading to the next shop]
-Tay: Hello.
-Phuak: Far left, far left.
-Tay: Any skirts?
-Proprietress: None.
Phuak: No short skirts at all?
[There are no short skirts here]
Bank: Oh man, I want one.
Proprietress: Wow, you're so handsome in person.
[Asking with a tiny bit of hope]
Phuak: Any short skirts?
Proprietress: No.
[Hope is getting smaller]
Phuak: Oh boy.
Phuak: What should we do?
[Though sad,
they continue looking for shops selling skirts]
Phuak: Let's go, let's go.
Phuak: Oh boy.
[Walked... and walked...]
Phuak: Hello.
-Phuak: Hello.
-Foreigner: Hello.
[Likely to walk through all of Pattaya]
Phuak: Hey.
Bank: Wow, Phuak is covered in sweat.
[Walking back and forth,
Phuak's shirt has become a see-through shirt]
Phuak: Right, I'm now...
[Accidentally became sexy]
[Where on earth can we find skirts?]
Offroad: Better prepare yourselves,
you'll definitely get tanned.
[Even the Yellow Team is struggling to find...]
Ink: Yes.
Oat: Actually, a time limit
should have been set in this game.
Ink: Where, where?
-Ink: Oh! That person.
-Offroad: Thank you, come together.
-Ink: Orange bandana.
-Offroad: You come together.
-Oat: Wow, it's like she
-Ink: Let's go fast. It's exactly the same.
[Ink finds someone walking on the beach]
Oat: stepped out of this picture.
Ink: Exactly the same.
Offroad: Wow, this is completely correct.
[What does that person look like
for everyone to be so tense?]
Ink: You are exactly the same
as the picture.
Oat: See, she used to film with me.
[Bandana] [Shirt] [Shorts] [Canvas Shoes]
[Perfect]
Ink: Hey, you look like you stepped out of this picture,
as if someone hired you.
Ink: Do this pose.
Girl: My legs are longer than hers.
Oat: Do this pose.
Offroad: Quickly do this pose for us.
[Copy] [Paste]
Ink: Sorry to bother you.
Ink: It's so similar,
like you came right out of it.
Passerby: But my legs
are longer in person.
Phuak: Where's Oat?
[Score check during the show]
PD: Check the Red Team.
Bring out the original image.
-PD: Bring out the original picture.
-Bank: This is it.
Phuak: Does it look like it?
The hair color...
Tay: Actually, her hair has bangs.
Tay: But she tied them up
because they covered her face.
Phuak: Hey, does the hair color match?
Phuak: Just look how serious we are!
[It's really too hard, I want you to know
how much effort we put in]
PD: Great! Pass. Found 2 people.
[The Red Team successfully found 2 people]
Phuak: I'm impressed.
I'm impressed by this.
PD: Blue Team, okay.
PD: This one passed, Blue Team.
Mos: We've found 3 people.
[Wearing an identical Hawaiian shirt
plus similar body shapes]
[King Jeff's unfathomable cunning]
PD: Okay.
PD: Please show your sample picture.
-Ink: There are 9 people here.
-PD: Right now. Okay.
PD: 1, 2, 3, 4.
PD: 5, 6, 7, 8, 9 people. Okay.
[Will this team succeed?]
PD: Okay.
[The Yellow Team
successfully found 9 people]
-Ink: Thank you, thank you.
-Offroad:  Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Offroad: Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Ink: Thank you, thank you.
[Score Update]
[Find passersby similar to emojis]
[Red Team: 2, Blue Team: 3, Yellow Team: 9]
Oat: Hey, kid.
[The Yellow Team discovered 1 more person]
Oat: Kid.
Oat: Put them on.
Oat: Put them on, put them on.
Oat: Put them on, follow me.
[To get the same sneakers as in the emoji,
Oat is even willing to offer his own shoes]
Oat: Put them on, follow me.
Oat: Go, follow me.
[Victory in sight]
Oat: Follow me.
Oat: Follow me, follow me, follow me.
Oat: Ink, Ink! I found one!
Oat: I found one!
Oat: Go, hurry.
Oat: Kid, you come with me.
Oat: You come with me.
Oat: Kid, you come with me, come with me.
PD: Hold it.
[Yellow Team...]
PD: Pass!
[Yellow Team... wins!]
Offroad: Yay!
Offroad: Thank you.
-Offroad: Thank you.
-Ink: Thank you.
Ink: Thank you.
Ink: Hey, so tired.
Offroad: Whoa, Oat, you're amazing.
[The Yellow Team obtained 2 stickers]
Offroad: That's amazing.
Ink: Oat looks just like a member
of parliament.
Jeff: I was looking for the foreigners.
Offroad: Great.
[Satisfied]
PD: The last game is called
"Collective Posing."
[The first step to becoming the successor]
[The final mission: Collective Posing]
[Feeling uneasy just hearing the name]
[Every team must find passersby
for a group photo]
PD: Later, every team must find passersby
to come over
-Phuak:  Here we go again.
-PD: and pose together.
Oat: Whoa, I told you.
PD: Go spin the wheel first.
[Must spin the wheel
to determine the number of passersby]
-Tay, Tay.
-Tay, Tay, Tay.
[Tay is going to spin it himself]
-Tay, Tay.
-Tay, Tay, Tay.
[An experienced and brave volunteer]
Jeff: Tay, stop.
[Stay calm]
-Phuak: Tay, come here.
-Offroad: That's enough.
Ink: I bow to you, Tay.
Oat: You stop right there.
Oat: If you spin a 10,
I'll cut off your hand.
[Only death awaits]
Phuak: Should I beat the hell out of you?
[I've done my best]
-Phuak: You really like to walk around.
-Offroad: For fairness,
Offroad: Wait, wait.
Offroad: For fairness,
Offroad: the Blue Team has already spun,
Offroad: and so has the Red Team—
Oat: The Goddess.
Offroad: so only the Yellow Team is left.
[The Yellow Team hasn't spun the wheel yet]
Offroad: Ink, you go.
Ink: Everyone will come
and blame me later.
[Absolutely do not blame each other]
[The result of Ink spinning the wheel is...]
Ink: 1, 2, 3.
Ink: Oh boy.
-Ink: 1, 2, 3.
-Offroad: Everyone is screwed up.
Offroad: Then let everything be destroyed.
Ink: Oh boy.
PD: Let it spin. Let it spin.
[Is this even allowed?]
PD: You chose this,
you deliberately chose this.
Ink: I just... "Oh boy"
Ink: No? Okay. Again, again.
Offroad: Use the maximum strength you can.
[The wheel has spun]
-Mos: Eh, eh.
-Phuak: No.
[Now everyone is of one mind]
Becky: Oh no.
Offroad: No, no!
[Roaring]
[The result is...]
-Mos: Eh, eh.
-Phuak: No.
Becky: Oh no.
Offroad: No, no!
Tay: It's okay, Ink. It's okay.
Tay: It's okay.
[I fully understand this feeling...]
-Tay: It's a little better than mine.
-Ink: Will we be kicked off the show?
Tay: No, but we'll be hated by our friends.
Ink: Hated by friends.
[Need 9 people?]
PD: Whoever comes back first
can start first.
[Competition order] [The team
that finishes gathering first competes first]
PD: Okay, ready.
PD: 1, 2, 3.
Phuak: Go, go, go, go!
[Game start]
[Speed is the key to completing this task]
-Phuak: Go!
-Bank: Let's go!
[Completely different from rounds 1 and 2,
the Red Team is in full force]
Bank: By ourselves.
-Phuak: Stop playing, let's go.
-Bank: Over here, over here.
Phuak: Where? Where? We need 9 people, 9.
[If we don't win this time,
we won't get the sticker]
Bank: Hey, ladies.
Tay: Ladies, can you help me?
Tay: Just taking a photo, just a photo.
Tay: A group photo with 9 people.
[Hesitation]
Tay: Can you 3 join together?
-Tay: You only need to take 1 photo.
-Bank: 4.
[Even reaching the point
of kneeling to beg]
-Tay: Running Man show.
-Bank: There are 4 people here.
Phuak: How many? How many people do we have?
-Phuak: Uh, 4.
-Tay: 4 people, 4.
-Phuak: 4.
-Bank: Bro, will you join too?
Tay: We only need 1 group photo.
It'll be quick.
-Bank: 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
-Tay: Thank you.
Bank: Then you guys wait here for a while.
[Obtained 5 people after negotiation]
Bank: I'll be right back.
Don’t go with anyone else, okay?
[Moving toward the next target]
[The Red Team sends out its full main lineup]
Tay: Can you help me?
[Kneeling]
Tay: You just need
to take a group photo with me.
Tay: I need 9 people.
I've already found 5.
[A celebrity comes over to sit and chat]
Tay: Is it okay? Help me out.
Tay: Take a group photo.
[Tay's effort in kneeling a
nd begging has paid off]
Tay: Let's go, let's go.
Tay: 5, 6, 7.
Tay: Thank you.
[One person short]
Tay: 6, 7, 8.
-Tay: 1 short!
-Phuak: 1 short, 1 short.
-Tay: Hey, oh my god.
-Bank: 1 person.
[Tay is hit back by fate]
-Phuak: It's okay now. Go, go, go.
-Tay: Hurry up.
[Only 1 person short now!]
[The real Never Stop Running
is right here]
Phuak: Let's go. Go, go.
Tay: Take a photo with us.
-Phuak: Come on.
-Tay: Come on.
-Tay: Ma'am please do me a favor.
-Phuak: Let's go, go!
Just a while.
-Phuak: Ma'am, hurry. Now.
-Tay: Take a photo. Just a second.
Tay: A favor, please.
Tay: Photo, photo, group photo.
[Got the lady to help in one go]
Tay: Yeah.
Tay: Thank you, Ma'am.
Phuak: I’ll report first.
Phuak: We'll shoot later.
Tay: Really?
[Her daughter is a fan of Tay]
Tay: I'll take a picture with you and
you can show it to your daughter.
Tay: Is her name Beer?
Mos: Each of you should find
three passers-by.
[Blue Team's strategy is
to search separately]
Jeff: Do you have time?
Do you want to play game with us?
Passer-by: I'm sorry, I'm a foreigner.
Jeff: Yeah, that's okay.
-Passer-by: It's okay?
-Jeff: Yes.
-Passer-by: I speak English.
-Jeff: You two?
Jeff: Yes, that's okay.
[Show your good language ability
to attract tourists]
-Passer-by: Okay.
-Jeff: Okay.
Jeff: We'll just pose. That's okay.
-Passer-by: Okay. Okay.
-Jeff: Okay, you two.
[Becky is also trying to find her target]
-Becky: Sorry. Excuse me, are you free
to do something with us?
Becky: Could you come with me, please?
Becky: Can you?
Becky: OK, hold on.
[Too bad only one person joins]
[As for our Mos.]
Mos: Hey. Miss.
Mos: Can we take a photo together?
[I'm sorry]
Mos: Okay. Thank you.
[Failed]
[There are only three passers-by found
by the Blue Team]
[This way]
Jeff: Excuse me.
Jeff: Do you have time?
[A group of people are crossing the road]
Jeff: How many of you?
Jeff: Yes, yes.
[Surprised]
Jeff: Come on.
Jeff: How many of you are here?
Passer-by: Five.
[Inviting people and checking
the headcount at the same time]
Jeff: Come on. Let's go.
Jeff: Follow me.
Jeff: Do you have time
to play games with us?
[Will the Blue Team be
the first to arrive?]
Offroad: Should we go there, Oat?
-Ink: That way?
-Oat: Where?
-Oat: Okay. That way.
-Offroad: Okay. Let's go.
Ink: But we're behind.
Oat: Let them go. We are relaxed now.
Ink: It’s like we’ve already won.
Oat: We already won. Let's take
a nice and easy walk.
[The Yellow Team is completely relaxed]
Ink: We're...
-Ink: Here, that boy.
-Offroad: Kid.
Oat: Brother!
Ink: Hey, kid.
-Oat: Come here. You did a great job.
-Ink: Do it again.
-Offroad: You're a really good kid, boy.
-Oat: Want any food? I'll treat you later.
Oat: Come with me.
Ink: This one. This.
[The kid who took part
in the first mission]
Oat: No need to ride the bike.
We'll go on foot.
Offroad: No need to ride the bike.
-Ink: Here, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
-Oat: Okay. What do you want to eat?
[Boss Oat treats kids who helped and
completed the missions with them]
Ink: 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
-Ink: Oat, she's cute.
-Oat: Sister.
-Ink: Hey, sis.
-Oat: Can you support me?
Oat: Coconut water.
Ink: Do you know him?
Let's go on a show together.
[The Yellow Team invades
the coconut water shop]
Ink: Can you two join us
on a show?
Ink: Oat will take all of these later.
Oat: I'll buy 1,000 baht.
-Oat: You open the coconut first.
-Ink: Open coconut.
Oat: We won just now. It’s relaxed
for me to treat all of you.
-Offroad: Kid, you're amazing.
[Sweet coconut water comforts
the heat in their hearts]
Oat: This...
Oat: Can you come with us?
Offroad: Sis.
[Let me enjoy this refreshing sweetness
after the mission]
Oat: It's not gonna go missing.
No one will steal coconuts.
Offroad: No one will steal it.
-Offroad: Sis, come with us.
Ink: I drink this a lot.
-Ink: Be careful.
-Oat: Careful, kid. Don't spill it.
Offroad: Here. Have a sip.
[The boy who has been
with us all day. Have a sip]
Offroad: Okay. Do you feel refreshed?
-Offroad: Do you like it?
-Oat: What do you think?
[It's good]
[The kids are coming one after another]
Ink: Is he here? Is he here?
Ink: He's here.
-Ink: He's so cute.
-Oat: So cute.
Ink: They're all so cute.
[Come to the coconut water party]
-Oat: Of course they're cute.
-Offroad: This is our strategy.
Offroad: The kids are really adorable.
-Oat: How many more of his friends?
-Offroad: Two more.
-Oat: Two more?
-Offroad: We need to find three more.
Oat: Okay. See you there.
[Three people?]
Oat: Okay. Go.
Oat: This?
[The Little Hero of the Yellow Team]
Offroad: Please wait for a while
for the food.
[Daddy is here to escort the child
for the mission]
Offroad: Let's go. Over here.
Offroad: Let's go together.
Offroad: Hey, sir. Do you want to be on
the show together?
Offroad: You're invited.
-Passer-by: It's okay.
-Offroad: Let's go.
[Both father and daughter can participate]
Offroad: It's okay, sir. We can do
the show together.
Offroad: You two will look
so sweet together.
Ink: How old are you? Are you Eight?
-Ink: He's here. He's so sweet.
-Oat: Let's go.
Ink: He's so sweet.
Ink: You’re so sweet. Awesome.
[The little boy gathered his friends]
Ink: It’s OK. We'll go together later.
[The Yellow Team finally gathered
their people]
Oat: Enjoy it.
Oat: Do you know what
I look like now?
Oat: Like the movie "My Girlfriend".
Offroad: It’s relaxing.
-Oat: Like "My Girlfriend". That movie.
-Ink: Let's go. Let's go together.
[Which team will arrive first?]
Ink: I'll buy you all ice cream later.
[The first team to arrive is...]
Mos: Yes.
[The Blue Team arrived first]
PD: We need to check the headcount first.
Bank: OK. Let's go. Come on.
Bank: Come on.
[The Red Team is the second to arrive]
[The third to arrive is the Yellow Team]
Ink: We're the children's team.
PD: This is what you're supposed to pose.
[9 passers-by plus 3 Running Man members.
The group pose for them is...]
Phuak: Oh my lord.
Becky: What? What is it?
[Never seen this pose in life]
[Spin around 5 times before posing]
[Complete this pose flawlessly in
10 seconds and the team wins]
Mos: 5 spins of turn first.
[The Blue Team starts first]
PD: Countdown starts after the whistle.
Jeff: 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
Jeff: 2, 3, 4, 5.
Phuak: I haven't finished.
Phuak: Hey. You're not done.
Phuak: I only count to two.
I only count to two.
PD: 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
Phuak: It's just the second spin.
[As for someone who has done 5 spins]
[Dizzy]
Jeff: Enough.
Jeff: I'm done.
[The person in front is posing, but...]
Mos: Okay. Okay.
Jeff: I'm done.
[The people behind are still
spinning around]
Mos: OK. OK.
[Shaking]
[Let's see how the Blue Team looks like]
PD: However, the posture on
the sample given...
[Everyone is facing different directions]
[Blue Team failed]
PD: Requires every row to
be close to each other.
Phuak: Ah, Red Team. Red Team.
[The second round is the Red Team's turn]
Tay: Come on, everyone. It's our turn.
-Phuak: Let's do it.
-Tay: It's our showtime.
PD: 1, 2, 3.
[How will the result be?]
Phuak: 1, 2, 3.
Phuak: 4, 5.
Phuak: Ah, come on.
Phuak: 1, 2, 3.
[Their spinning stance looks steadier
than that of the Blue Team]
Phuak: 4, 5.
Phuak: Ah, come on. Get closer.
[The pose is more stable than expected]
-Tay: Oh, come closer. Closer.
-Phuak: Closer, come.
Phuak: Closer, closer.
[But two people disappeared...]
[Notice something wrong]
Phuak: Closer. Higher. Higher!
[Higher, higher, higher]
Phuak: Higher. Higher!
Phuak: Right.
[They jump high right away]
Phuak: Let's go and have a look.
PD: No.
Phuak: It depends on the timing of
the camera shutter.
Phuak: Here. Here.
[Out of shape and a mess]
[Failed]
PD: Failed.
[The third round is the Yellow Team]
Offroad: You want me to
stand behind you later?
[All set and totally ready]
Oat: Good.
Offroad: OK. Then you stay here. I'll...
Oat: We'll play it like this.
PD: Ready.
[Let's see how the kids spin around]
Oat: Okay. Come on.
PD: 1, 2, 3.
Oat: 1, 2, 3.
[Spinning around attentively]
Oat: 4, 5.
[They look relaxed]
PD: 5.
Oat: 4, 5.
Offroad: Hey, come closer.
-Offroad: Move closer.
-Oat: Closer.
Oat: Closer...
Ink: Higher like them.
Offroad: Oh, you're doing great.
-Oat: Yes! Great!
-Offroad: Exactly the same.
-Oat: Exactly the same.
-Offroad: Let's check this.
-Ink: Is anyone clenching their fists?
[Let's check the photos together]
Passer-by:  Exactly the same.
Passer-by: Exactly the same.
Ink: Oh my!
Ink: Why'd you take the photo
right at this moment?
Offroad: Bro, you messed up the shot.
[Seriously]
Ink: Did you have to rush
the shot that much?
Offroad: You snapped it way too fast!
This is really unfair.
[The shot catured at that moment
is no good]
[Failed]
-Ink: You're already great.
-Oat: You're great, kids.
Offroad: I'll buy ice cream
for everyone later.
Ink: I'll buy ice cream for
everyone later.
Oat: Let's step forward.
[Offroad takes care of his young members]
Offroad: Let's move aside a little.
[Back to the Blue Team]
PD: Are you ready?
-PD: 1, 2, 3.
-Mos: Okay.
PD: 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
[The Blue Team is doing better
than the last round]
[This time, they did 5 full spins]
[Let's see, if they do it right]
PD: Okay, ready.
Jeff: Come on, come closer.
PD: 4, 5.
PD: Okay, ready.
-Jeff: Come closer. Come closer.
-Mos: Move closer. Closer.
-Mos: Come closer.
-PD: Becky, Becky, in the middle.
-Jeff: Becky. Becky.
-Mos: Okay.
[Everyone else is in position]
-Jeff: Right, right.
Jeff: The camera is on the right.
[But Becky is yet to stand still]
Jeff: The camera is...
[I'm sorry]
[It's fun to watch this together]
-Ink: Hey, there's still a chance.
Ink: But someone is blocked.
[Failed because of the hand of
the person behind can't be seen]
[Red Team is back]
Phuak: Okay. When we pose,
we gotta stand side by side.
[Stress the point again]
[Red Team encourages their members
before the shoot]
Jeff: This team has got a chance.
PD: Get ready.
-Phuak: Ready.
-PD: 1, 2, 3.
[The spinning is more stable than before]
Tay: Here we go.
Phuak: I think I’m the only one
who's done the spins.
Phuak: Come on. Get close. Come closer.
Phuak: Come on, come closer. Come closer.
[Dizzy and disoriented]
Phuak: Be careful. Stand up.
[Coach Phuak helps teammates form a line]
Phuak: Stretch your arms.
Phuak: Be careful.
Tay: Stay still. Stay still. Stay still.
-Tay: Don't move.
-Phuak: Stay still.
[Don't move]
[Stay still]
-Tay: Do not move.
-Phuak: Stay still.
-Tay: Stay still until we signal to move.
[We've got this!]
Tay: Go and take a look.
Phuak: We did it? We did it?
Tay: Please give me a perfect shot.
Tay: Please.
PD: Coming.
-Tay: Hey.
-Phuak: Hey.
Phuak: Great! Great!
Phuak: Great!
[Well done]
PD: The Red Team wins this mission.
Yeah.
Phuak: What do you think?
What do you think?
Phuak: Our team.
Tay: Come on.
1, 2, 3.
Yeah!
Ink: I will buy ice cream for
every one of you, kids!
[Depressed]
-Oat: Kids. Kids.
-Offroad: I'll buy you ice creams.
Oat: Go buy ice cream, kid.
Oat: Buy ice cream.
-Oat: Take it to get some ice cream.
-Ink: Take it to get some ice cream.
[Rich Oat is giving money to the kids
to cheer them up]
-Oat: Take it to get some ice cream.
-Ink: Take it to get some ice cream.
Offroad: It's okay.
[Smiling]
Oat: Hey, boy. Take it and buy ice cream.
Offroad: It’s OK.
Offroad: Thank you so much.
-Oat: Take it to get some ice cream.
-Ink: It's okay.
-Offroad: Are you here to play?
-Oat: Go get some snacks.
[The mission with passers-by concludes
successfully in a warm atmosphere]
[Thank you for joinnig our game]
PD: Red Team wins.
[The Red Team wins the third mission]
Phuak: Go, go, go.
Phuak: Then we can balance each other.
-Phuak: Please. Please.
-Ink: We're all the same.
[Head up, chest out, marching over
with a dead-serious look]
-Phuak: Let Tay go.
-Bank: Let Tay go.
Phuak: Tay. Put it up confidently.
-Tay: Help me with this.
Oat: Huh?
Mos: To be honest,
our team is a bit risky.
[Red Team's sticker is up on
the wheel for the first time]
Ink: Why?
-Phuak: Yes, stick it.
-Mos: We got it too.
[The winning of the Red Team
results in 2:2:2]
Mos: Be careful.
[Be careful]
Phuak: Be careful.
Phuak: Great! We’re great!
-Ink: Yes! Yes!
-Mos: Yes!
PD: It's time to distribute the shares.
[It's time to distribute shares]
PD: For this mission,
PD: The person who get the shares
[The person who gets the shares this time]
PD: will get 20% of the shares.
[The person who gets the shares this time
will get 20% of the shares]
[Now all teams have a chance]
-Phuak: Be confident.
-Oat: Be confident.
Phuak: Go!
Bank: No, which one?
Phuak: Red, of course.
Phuak: Red. Red. Use your strength.
Make more turns.
Offroad: Turn and
push down. Push down.
[Everyone is excited about the 20% shares]
Offroad: Push harder!
-Offroad: Harder!
-Phuak: Push.
Phuak: Push harder. Make more turns.
-Offroad: This is a fair game.
-Bank: I don't know.
[The second share division in the game
"Find a Successor"]
-Phuak: Use your full strength.
-PD: 1.
PD: 2, 3.
[Which couple will get this share?]
Phuak: Hey, it's so sticky.
[Red Team?]
[Yellow Team?]
Phuak: Hey, stop.
Phuak: Stop, stop, stop.
[Blue Team]
[Which team will be the lucky one?]
Phuak: Hey, stop.
Phuak: Stop, stop, stop.
Phuak: Wow.
[The reward for defying fate]
PD: The Red Team got 20% of the shares.
[The Red Team got 20% of the shares]
[The first mission to test the
potential of the heir]
Phuak: Wow.
[Red Team wins]
[Test 1: People's Holdings]
[Gain 20% shares]
[Mission 2: The quality of a successor]
[Show up with a full spirit]
Oat: Come on. Come on. Come on.
Oat: Wow.
[What's showing up in front of them?]
Phuak: Water again.
[The water...]
Ink: Oh my!
[Huge outdoor swimming pool]
[The mission venue has
an amazing ocean view]
[OPPO Running Man Thailand
Never Stop Running]
[What kind of mission will they
carry out here?]
PD: This mission is called...
[PD: This mission is]
"The Progress Heir."
[Mission 2: "The Progress Heir"]
[Eager to know]
PD: What each team needs to do is that
[PD: Everyone should sit on the
conveyor belt at the back]
PD: to sit on the conveyor belt
at the back.
Bank: What is that?
[The conveyor belt placed
next to the pool]
Phuak: Oh, are we running?
Oat: Is it sushi?
[In short, this mission is for everyone
to sit on the conveyor belt like sushi]
-PD: It's sushi...
-Oat: Is it a sushi conveyor belt?
-PD: Conveyor belt.
-Oat: Okay.
[Mission: "The Progress Heir"]
PD: The mission rules of
"The Progress Heir."
PD: Each team must sit
on the conveyor belt
PD: and play 3 games randomly.
PD: The first game is "Dang! Dang! Dang!."
[Game: "Dang! Dang! Dang!"]
PD: When PD says Dang! Dang! Dang!
PD: and point the hammer to a direction,
PD: if the player turns his head
to the opposite direction,
PD: he or she wins.
[Success]
PD: The second game "Syllable Swap."
[Game: "Syllable Swap"]
PD: PD will say the exchange syllables.
[Chai-Miang]
PD: Players must say the right word
[Chiang Mai (Cheang-Mai)]
PD: to win this game.
[Success]
PD: The third game, Thai Proverb.
[Game: "Thai Proverb"]
PD: PD will say the first few words
of this Thai proverb,
[Seize the moment]
PD: and the players must finish
the rest of the proverb correctly
[It won't come again]
PD: to win this game.
[Success]
PD: The conveyor belt will be on
during the games.
PD: When all three players
finish the game,
PD: the conveyor belt
will stop immediately.
PD: The team
PD: with the most members left
on the conveyor belt
[Winner]
PD: will be the winner
PD: and get two stickers
PD: to put on the wheel.
PD: After the mission,
PD: you will turn the wheel again.
PD: Which team's sticker
will the needle stop on?
PD: the team will get
a specified number of extra share.
[Rotate the Roulette. Whichever team the pointer
lands on will get 20% extra share]
Oat: Becky, do you understand
what Syllable swap is?
[Oat: Becky, do you understand
what Syllable swap is?]
Oat: For example, Chai-Miang.
[Oat: Chai-Miang?]
Oat: OK. We can be relaxed.
[Oat: Haha, we will win]
Oat: We can be relaxed now.
[Found Blue team's weakness]
Jeff: Riding an elephant to grab...
[Can you answer the Thai proverb?]
Becky: Grab...
Jeff: Riding an elephant to grab...
[Jeff: What do you grab
riding on an elephant?]
Becky: Grab something. Grab.
[Becky: What to grab?]
Oat: Grab it tight.
Be careful, or you might fall.
[Oat: Grab it tight.
Be careful, or you might fall]
Oat: You'll fall, kid.
[Oat: You'll fall]
Oat: Grab it tight when riding an elephant.
It's very high. Be careful, or you might fall.
[The “Dang! Dang! Dang!” game is the only hope]
[Blue team will face a serious challenge]
[Round 1, Red Team starts first]
Phuak: Ready.
[The first person is the most nervous]
Bank: I don’t know why,
but I feel like I’m full.
[So nervous that he speaks faster]
Mos: Later he'll show us the fall move first.
[Mos: Later the first team will
show us how to fall into the water]
Offroad: We'll see it later.
[Red Team, acting as coaches,
will show how to fall into the water]
-Mos: And he's the first one.
-Offroad: There will be a demonstration.
Jeff: You are like tuna in a factory.
[Jeff: Like tuna in a factory]
Phuak: Yes, yes.
[Let's see what you'll be like
when it's your turn]
[Red Team, Round 1, start]
-Phuak: We're ready.
-PD: 1, 2, 3. Conveyor belt, go!
[Starting with Phuak]
PD: Dang! Dang! Dang!
[Dang! Dang! Dang!]
-PD: It's OK.
-Phuak: Hurry up.
PD: Syllable swap.
[Next, it's Tay's turn]
PD: Sa-mee-dong
[Syllable swap: Sa-mee-dong → ?]
Tay: Sa-mok-dee?
-PD: Again. Sa-mee-dong.
-Tay: What?
Tay: What?
-PD: Again. Sa-mee-dong.
-Phuak: Sa-mok-dee.
[The conveyor belt is nearing the end]
Tay: What?
-PD: Sa-mee-dong.
-Phuak: Tay.
-Tay: What?
-Phuak: You jerk!
[Too flustered to do anything]
Phuak: Tay, you jerk!
Phuak: You bad Tay!
-PD: Sa-mee-dong.
-Phuak: Tay!
-Tay: Sa-mok-dee.
-Phuak: You bad Tay!
[About to fall into the water]
PD: Sa-mee-dong.
Phuak: You bad Tay!
-PD: Sa-mee-dong.
-Phuak: You bad Tay!
[Tay, help!]
-Tay: Sa-mok-dee.
-Phuak: Tay!
Phuak: You bad Tay!
-PD: Sa-mee-dong.
-Phuak: Tay!
-Tay: Sa-mok-dee.
PD: Sa-mee-dong.
-Phuak: Tay!
-Tay: Sa-mok-dee.
PD: Sa-mee-dong.
Phuak: You bad Tay!
[Finally, Phuak falls into the water]
[Hey... you bad Tay!]
Oat: Smart.
Offroad: Smart.
Tay: Sa-mok-dee. Sa-mee-dong.
[Wrong answer.
Finally, Tay falls into the water]
[Bank fell into the water without
even having a chance to do anything]
[A perfect demonstration of
how to fall into the water]
Tay: What was it? What Sa-mee-dong?
[Tay: What was it? What Sa-mee-dong?]
[Phuak: Smart]
Phuak: Smart.
[Syllable swap:
Sa-mee-dong → smart (smong-di)]
[Tay: But why was it Sa-mee-dong?]
Tay: But what she said was Sa-mee-dok.
Phuak: Sa-mee-dong.
[You didn't hear it clearly]
[Angry]
-Phuak: Smart.
-Tay: It was Sa-mee-dok.
-Offroad: It was smart.
-Ink: Smart.
-Oat: Sa-mok-dee.
-Ink: Not Sa-mee-dok.
-Tay: Can we start over? Sa-mee-dong.
-Phuak: You are not smart.
[Tay: Can we play again? One more time]
Tay: I'm very smart.
[This is unfair]
Tay: But my ears are not good.
Tay: I didn't hear it.
Phuak: Sa-mee-dong.
Even I have heard it.
[Even a 40-year-old has heard it]
Oat: Great. Tay, you're really funny.
[You've had enough fun.
Stop complaining and come up]
Oat: That's funny. Sa-mok-dee.
Tay: I'm pretty good at Syllable swap.
[Tay: I'm pretty good]
[Tay: Again. I'll get every single one]
Tay: Give me the words now.
I can get them all right.
Phuak: You don't have to do it now. It's too late.
[Phuak: It's already too late. Enough]
Tay: It's too bad. I can't accept it at all.
[Tay: It's too bad. I can't accept it at all]
Phuak: Yes, I can't accept it either.
Phuak: I’m very disappointed in you.
[You were so bad]
Tay: Sa-mee-dong.
[So frustrating]
-Phuak: What the heck? Sa-mok-deek.
-Oat: Sa-mok-dee.
[Completely outclassed]
Phuak: This word was so easy.
[Still complaining]
Bank: Stop complaining about him.
[Bank: Stop complaining]
[Stop fighting]
[After Red Team, next is Yellow Team’s turn]
Mos: Let's crush them!
Offroad: Good luck!
[Thanks to the example of falling in the water,
Yellow Team looks way more relaxed than Red Team]
[But Oat’s expression doesn't look so good]
Oat: This... Um, I'm sorry.
[Oat: Wait a second]
Oat: Is this a life jacket or a neck brace?
Oat: The “Dang! Dang! Dang!” game.
May I use my hand instead?
Oat: Bang, bang, bang...
I can do it like this.
[If I play the “Dang! Dang! Dang!” game,
man I use my hand instead of my head?]
-Phuak: You must use your head.
-Bank: You must use your head.
[You must use your head]
Oat: But I can't turn my head right now.
[Oat: I can't turn my head at all right now]
[Even if my head looks like this?]
Oat: Like this?
Phuak: No, no. You must turn your head.
[Red Team is strongly against it]
Bank: You must turn your head.
Phuak: You must turn your head.
[Absolutely no]
Phuak: No, no, no.
Phuak: Turn your head.
[If he is to play the "Dang! Dang! Dang!" game,
he'll probably fall into the water]
Jeff: If so, he'll fall into the water.
Ink: Yellow Team, good luck!
Offroad: Yellow Team, good luck!
PD: 1, 2, 3, Dang! Dang! Dang!
[Round 1, Yellow Team, start]
[Dang! Dang! Dang!]
PD: Dang! Dang! Dang!
[Got the “Dang! Dang! Dang!” game]
[Great]
PD: Dang! Dang! Dang!
[Dang! Dang! Dang!]
Oat: Pass. Pass.
-PD: Pass. Pass. Next is Offroad.
-Oat: Pass.
[Next is Offroad]
PD: Syllable swap.
PD: Ran-pha-ya-bong.
[Syllable swap:
Ran-pha-ya-bong → ?]
Offroad: Huh?
[Huh?]
[Hurry up]
[If you don't hurry,
you'll fall into the water]
PD: Ran-pha-ya-bong.
Offroad: Huh?
[What is he doing?]
[Syllable swap:
Ran-pha-ya-bong → ?]
[Umm...]
[He seems to have no idea at all]
[Sigh...]
PD: Ran-pha-ya-bong.
[Syllable swap:
Ran-pha-ya-bong → ?]
Oat: Hospital.
[Syllable swap: Ran-pha-ya-bong →
Hospital (Rong-phya-ban)]
PD: Song-thi, Ink.
[Syllable swap: Song-thi → ?]
Ink: What Song-thi?
[Syllable swap: Song-thi → Gold (Si-thong)]
-Phuak: Just like us.
-Bank: Just like us.
[Now you've also experienced it,
do you understand how we feel?]
Phuak: Just like Sa-mee-dong.
[Phuak: Exactly like Sa-mee-dong]
[Phuak is extremely resentful today]
Tay: Sa-mee-dong.
[Meanwhile, Blue Team is also worried]
[Jeff: Or should we let Becky be the first one?]
Jeff: Should we let Becky be the first one?
Mos: Becky must be the last one.
[Making Becky,
who isn’t fluent in Thai, the last one]
Jeff: Oh, OK.
Mos: In case there's something
she can’t answer.
-Mos: We'll play the Syllable swap instead .
-Jeff: OK, OK.
[Jeff: We must make it]
Jeff: We must make it.
[Will this line-up work?]
Tay: I hope they get some legendary,
super obscure proverbs.
Becky: We can help each other.
[Becky: We can help each other]
Phuak: No, I won't help you.
I'm sorry.
[Crying...]
[Round 1, Blue Team, start]
PD: OK. It's a proverb: Dig a pond…
[Thai proverb: Dig a pond → ?]
Jeff: Water, pond...
[Jeff: Pond? Dig a pond?]
-Jeff: Dig a pond.
-PD: Dig a pond.
[The first person is already in danger]
Jeff: Water, pond...
-Jeff: Dig a pond.
-PD: Dig a pond.
[OMG...]
Phuak: Great. Lure the fish.
[Phuak: Lure the fish]
Oat: Dig a pond and lure the fish.
[They already know the answer]
[Thai proverb: Dig a pond → ?]
Jeff: What "Dig a pond"?
[The conveyor belt keeps moving]
Jeff: I don’t know.
Jeff: Dig a big pond.
[The further the conveyor belt moves,
the more frantic they get]
Jeff: Dig a pond, dig a pond.
[She can do nothing but scream and shout...]
Jeff: Dig a pond. I'm telling you, hey.
[Just blurting things out because
he can’t think of the answer]
[Ending up falling into the water]
[His expression looks like
he’d already given up before falling]
[Well... I don't know...]
[Falling into the water one after another]
Oat: Did they all go down in there?
Oat: All of them.
Oat: They all went down.
[The line-up was pointless]
[Thai proverb: Dig a pond → ?]
-PD: Dig a pond and lure the fish.
-Phuak: Dig a pond and lure the fish.
[Thai proverb: Dig a pond →
Dig a pond and lure the fish]
-PD: Dig a pond and lure the fish.
-Phuak: Dig a pond and lure the fish.
[The two answered it right]
Phuak: Told you it was dig a pond
and lure the fish. See?
Oat: Dig a pond and lure the fish.
Jeff: I've never heard of it.
[Jeff has never heard of this proverb]
Phuak: A piece of cake.
I got it right away.
Oat: I answered it right away.
Dig a pond and lure the fish.
[Pride of Gen Y]
Bank: You knew it right away?
Oat: For our generation, that’s common sense.
[So you need to be older to answer it]
Jeff: You have to be old.
Phuak: No, no. Use the word "mature".
[Hit home]
Phuak: In other words, none left, right?
[All failed in Round 1]
Oat: No.
Phuak: Again. Focus. Tay.
[Round 2 starts with Red Team]
[Muttering non-stop.
Keeps nagging even before it starts]
Phuak: Tay, focus.
[Yeah… I will]
Phuak: We can make it! We can make it!
[Phuak: We can make it! We can make it!]
PD: Conveyor belt, go!
[Red Team begins Round 2]
PD: Syllable swap.
[Syllable swap: Siao-Kee → ?
PD: Siao-Kee.
-Phuak: Green (See-Khiao).
-PD: Correct.
PD: Proverb: If you want it to last,
you must cut it.
[Proverb]
[Thai proverb: If you want it to last,
you must cut it. → ?]
Tay: If you want it to be brief,
you must connect it.
-Phuak: Good job.
-PD: Correct.
[Thai proverb:
If you want it to last, you must cut it. → ]
[If you want it to be brief,
you must connect it]
[The nagging actually worked!]
-Phuak: Good job.
-PD: Correct.
[But almost failed]
PD: Syllable swap.
[Red Team’s fate all rests on Bank]
PD: Sao-Ta-Yai.
[Bank] [Please]
PD: Syllable swap: Sao-Ta-Yai.
[Syllable swap: Sao-Ta-Yai → ?]
Bank: Farsighted (Sai-Ta-Yao).
PD: Correct. Stop.
[Syllable swap: Sao-Ta-Yai →
Farsighted (Sai-Ta-Yao)]
Bank: Farsighted.
PD: Correct. Stop.
[Stopped just in the nick of time]
[So frightened that my heart nearly stopped...]
[Perfect timing]
[We made it!]
[So frightened that my legs have gone weak]
Phuak: Take me back! Take me back with you!
[Immediately abandoned their friend and ran away]
[These cunning guys!]
Ink: Be careful. Don't run.
Ink: Hey, you made it. Great!
[Round 2, Red Team succeeds]
Phuak: Who pressed the stop button?
Who pressed it?
[Phuak: Who pressed the stop button?
Who pressed it?]
[Phuak: I'll pay you later]
Phuak: I'll pay you later.
Bank: Wow, that was so lucky.
Good thing I didn’t get a proverb.
[Good thing Bank didn’t have to play
the proverb game, right?]
Tay: It wasn’t luck. It was because we’re good.
Phuak: We’re good. It wasn’t luck.
It was skill.
[It wasn’t luck. We’re really just that good!]
Offroad: Oh, going with that story, huh?
Tay: Because we’re smart. Our brains work fast.
[Red Team is basking in the joy of success]
Jeff: You still need to be old, though.
[Skill? It’s all about old age]
Tay: You guys should be mature too.
[Tay: Then hurry up and be mature,
so you can catch up to us]
[Starting to get cocky]
-Phuak: We're gonna shine.
-Tay: We're gonna shine.
[They're so proud]
Phuak: This is the result of studying hard
when I was young.
[Phuak: Studying hard when I was young
really pays off, huh?]
Bank: We were just pretending earlier.
[Oh, come on...]
Bank: This is real skill.
[When Red Team is totally self-intoxicated]
Phuak: This is real skill. I like it.
So much positive energy.
[Yellow Team starts their 2nd round]
PD: Start. Conveyor belt, go!
PD: Syllable swap: Lai-Fod.
[Syllable swap: Lai-Fod → ?]
Oat: Bulb (Lod-Fai).
PD: Correct.
[Syllable swap: Lai-Fod → Bulb (Lod-Fai)]
[Ink, Syllable swap]
PD: Syllable swap. Soo-Chom-Pee.
[Syllable swap: Soo-Chom-Pee → ?]
Ink: Pink (See-Chom-Poo).
PD: Correct.
[Syllable swap:
Soo-Chom-Pee → Pink (See-Chom-Poo)]
[If Offroad can do it,
Yellow Team will succeed]
[Praying] [Falling into the water]
PD: Proverb.
[Offroad, Thai proverb]
PD: Choose friends by their faces.
[Thai proverb:
Choose friends by their faces. → ? ]
Offroad: Make...
[Offroad: Making friends?]
PD: Choose friends by their faces.
Phuak: Choose cloth by its texture.
[We already knew that~]
[Seems like he doesn't know
the answer again this time]
[Thai proverb: Choose friends
by their faces→?]
PD: Choose friends by their faces.
Offroad: Make...
Oat: I'm leaving!
[Soon] [About to fall]
[So unlucky…]
Oat: I'm leaving!
[Offroad has become
the Yellow Team's weak link]
Offroad: Choose friends by their faces.
Oat: I'm leaving!
[He shouted it
and immediately fell into the water]
Offroad: Choose dogs by their owners.
[Ink also fell into the water,
can't be saved now]
[Thai proverb: Choose friends
by their faces→?]
-Offroad: Choose dogs by their owners.
-PD: Choose friends by their faces.
[Offroad: Choose dogs by their owners]
[Answered wrong out of nowhere,
then instantly fell into the water]
[Nice one]
PD: Choose friends by their faces,
choose cloth by its texture.
[Thai proverb: Choose friends by
their faces→Choose cloth by its texture]
[You just couldn't answer it]
Offroad: Bro!
Offroad: Did you know?
[Offroad: Bro, did you know?]
Phuak: I know! Oat definitely knows too!
[Of course]
[Phuak: Oat definitely knows too]
-Oat: I don't know.
-Phuak: You don't know?
[Even Oat doesn't know this proverb]
Oat: I can't remember this one.
Ink: I don't know.
How would anyone know this?
[Ink: I really don't know,
how is it possible to know this?]
Phuak: See, you guys don't study properly!
[Phuak: See? It's because you
didn't study properly!]
[The Blue Team's mentality collapsed
after their first mistake]
Bank: I don't know any of the proverbs.
-Mos: I really don't know.
-Bank: I don't know.
Bank: I don't know any of them at all.
-Becky: I think it's hard too.
-Mos: It's too difficult.
[Can our team really
make it through like this…?]
Jeff: What should we do, Mos?
Mos: I'll go first.
Jeff: Uh, you go first.
Mos: It's fine even if I can't answer.
Jeff: It's fine, just fall into the water
like just now.
[A conversation completely devoid of hope]
[Will anyone actually succeed?]
PD: Ready, conveyor belt go.
[Blue Team begins Round 2]
[Mos → Syllable swap]
PD: Syllable swap.
[Mos]
[Syllable swap: Sa-Dee-Baeb-Nuak→?]
PD: Sa-Dee-Baeb-Nuak.
-Mos: It's convenient (Sa-Duak-Baeb-Nee).
-PD: Correct!
PD: Proverb: "Frog chooses..."
[Jeff → Thai proverb]
[Thai proverb: Frog chooses→?]
[Frog chooses master]
-Jeff: Master!
-PD: Correct!
[The Blue Team's performance
exceeds expectations]
Bank: Awesome.
[If Becky can answer correctly,
the Blue Team will succeed]
[Can Becky succeed?]
PD: Syllable swap: "Long-Kong."
[Drew a syllable swap question]
[Syllable swap: Long-Kong→?]
[The wordplay falls on
someone not good at Thai]
PD: Long-Kong.
[Why didn't she get
the Dang! Dang! Dang! game…]
PD: Long-Kong.
[Syllable swap: Long-Kong→?]
[What] [Is that?]
Becky: What is Long-Kong?
[In the end, couldn't avoid it…
fell into the water!]
Becky: What is Long-Kong?
[Screaming desperately
before falling into the water]
[Then Jeff also fell down, splash!]
[Entering the "let it be" Zen mode
once again]
Phuak: No way, no way!
[Blue Team fails Round 2]
Phuak: Can't do it, can't do it!
PD: After swapping syllables, Long-Kong
is still Long-Kong (Langsat fruit).
[Syllable swap: Long-Kong→?]
[Syllable swap: Long-Kong→
Langsat fruit(Long Kong)]
[Oh!]
[Even after swapping the syllables,
the word remains the same]
[What a pity]
Becky: Oh!
[Only one team succeeded in Round 2—
Red Team earns 2 stickers]
[Round 3 starts immediately]
PD: Get ready.
[Syllable swap: Khode-Tho→?]
PD: Khode-Tho.
-Phuak: Sorry (Kho-Thot).
-PD: Correct!
[Syllable swap: Khode-Tho→
Sorry (Kho-Thot)]
[Correct]
[Thai proverb: Little birds→?]
[Thai proverb: Little bird→Little birds build nests with effort]
PD: Little birds...
-Tay: Build nests with effort.
-PD: Correct!
[Correct]
[Syllable swap: Mang-Mee-Tai→?]
PD: Mang-Mee-Tai.
Bank: No money (Mai-Mee-Tang).
[Syllable swap: Mang-Mee-Tai→
No money (Mai-Mee-Tang)]
PD: Correct!
[Correct]
[Consecutive successes in Round 3
after Round 2]
[Two consecutive rounds of success,
momentum is strong!]
-Oat: Do you want to try going first?
-Offroad: Sure, I'll go first.
[Yellow Team lets Offroad go first]
Oat: Ink, you go last.
[Worried] [Anxious]
PD: Syllable swap: "Rod-Mai-Mee-Wan-Mak."
[Syllable swap]
[Syllable swap: Rod-Mai-Mee-Wan-Mak→?]
Offroad: Love is endless.
[Love is endles]
[Yellow Team's weak link
successfully passes]
[Thai proverb: Chicken sees snake's feet→?]
PD: Proverb: "Chicken sees snake's feet."
Oat: Snake sees chicken's breast.
[Correct]
[Snake sees chicken's breast]
PD: Khai-Pen-Fan-Dai-Mor.
[Syllable swap: Khai-Pen-Fan-Dai-Mor→?]
Ink: Can I date you? (Kho-Pen-Fan-Dai-Mai)
[Can I date you]
[Correct]
[Yellow Team succeeds in the Round 3]
[Weak link, Offroad's confidence
greatly increased]
[Blue Team sends their
weakest member first]
Phuak: Becky goes first.
PD: Dang! Dang! Dang! Pass!
[Passed thanks to the
Dang! Dang! Dang! game]
[Syllable swap: Ran-Ning-Man→?]
PD: Ran-Ning-Man.
Jeff: Running Man!
[Running Man]
[Correct]
PD: Correct.
[Thai proverb: Dancing poorly→?]
-PD: Dancing poorly...
-Mos: Blame the flute, blame the drum.
[Blame the flute, blame the drum]
[Correct]
[All teams that complete the mission
receive 1 sticker]
[Sticker count by team:
Team A-1, Team B-1, Team C-3]
[Round 4, Red Team goes first]
Tay: Hey, I'm afraid I won't
be able to answer.
Phuak: Don't be afraid, just do your best!
[Tay, don't be afraid,
just doing your best is enough now]
[Just enjoy the game now]
Tay: Yeah, don't be too nervous,
relax a bit!
Phuak: Yeah, relax Tay, relax!
PD: Start.
PD: Syllable swap: "Don-Man-Raed."
[Syllable swap: Don-Man-Raed →?]
Phuak: The sun is scorching (Daed-Man-Ron).
[The sun is scorching]
[Correct]
PD: Correct!
PD: Proverb: "Fast-flowing water..."
[Thai proverb: Fast-flowing water→?]
Tay: Let... don't block with a boat.
[Don't block with a boat]
-PD: What?
-Tay: Don't block it with a boat.
[Correct]
PD: Correct!
PD: Dang! Dang! Dang!
[Phuak is getting anxious—the game pace
can't keep up with the conveyor belt]
PD: Dang! Dang! Dang!
[Whether Phuak falls into the water
depends entirely on Bank]
PD: Dang! Dang! Dang!
[Will he succeed?]
[Dang! Dang! Dang!]
PD: Dang! Dang! Dang! Success!
[Pass]
PD: Dang! Dang! Dang!
PD: Success! Stop!
[Stopped right at the edge]
Phuak: Correct. Correct.
[That scared 10 years off my life!]
[It's nothing—piece of cake!]
Phuak: That was intense!
Phuak: So good!
Tay: When the current's fast,
you scoop quickly.
[Red Team—three in a row succeeded]
Phuak: No, that's wrong.
When the current's fast, you don't scoop.
That's when the water
rises that you scoop.
[Your Thai is impressive!]
Jeff: Your Thai is really good.
[So, how is it?]
-Phuak: Study Hard Team!
-Oat: So good! Awesome!
[This is "Study hard" Team]
[Super proud]
Phuak: Let's go. Great job, everyone.
[Red Team way ahead]
[Every time they win, it's "we've studied this,"
then they start showing off like crazy]
Ink: Ugh, as soon as they win,
they say it's because they studied hard.
Phuak: We may lack stamina,
but we've got knowledge.
[We may not have strength,
but we've got knowledge!]
PD: Ready? Start.
[Start from Offroad]
PD: Dang! Dang! Dang!
[Can Offroad pass?]
[Dang! Dang! Dang!]
PD: Oh! Correct.
[Passed]
PD: Oat.
PD: Swap-the-syllables word.
[Swap-the-syllables word]
PD: Swap-the-syllables word: Mai-La.
[Swap-the-syllables word: Mai-La → ?]
Oat: Zebra (Ma-Lai).
[Zebra]
[Correct]
PD: Correct.
[Is it Ink's turn this round?]
PD: In proverbs, giving a pearl.
[Thai proverb: giving a pearl → ?]
[Giving a pearl?]
Ink: Giving a pearl.
PD: Giving a pearl, a proverb.
[Looks like she doesn't know?]
Jeff: They're doomed.
[Giving a pearl?]
[Am I right in this round or...]
PD: Giving a pearl.
Ink: Giving a pearl.
[Giving a pearl?]
PD: Giving a pearl.
[Giving a pearl…]
Ink: Giving a pearl to...
Ink: To whom?
[Giving a pearl… for what?]
PD: Giving a pearl.
Ink: Giving a pearl to…
[Everyone starts to feel… this is the end]
Ink: To whom?
[Accepting reality, getting ready to fall]
[I'll go first then]
PD: Giving a pearl.
[Do I have to fall too?]
Ink: To whom?
PD: Giving a pearl to...
[Ah… looks like I really have to fall]
PD: Giving a pearl.
[I must have gotten the proverb wrong…]
Tay: I know, I know.
[Tay can answer it]
[Tay wants to answer!]
Phuak: Let Tay answer, let Tay answer.
[Giving a pearl to a monkey]
Tay: Is it "giving a pearl to a monkey"?
PD: Yes.
[Correct]
[Everyone is stunned]
[Red Team got
the Thai proverb right (super proud)]
Phuak: We're top students, you know.
[They really are the "study hard" type]
[Someone who has never
heard this proverb (Why give it a pearl?)]
Ink: Why give it a pearl though?
Phuak: Come on, tell her why.
[Standing tall with pride,
ready to explain it to them]
Tay: Because...
Tay: Because a monkey doesn't know value,
it won't appreciate pearls anyway.
[A monkey doesn't understand the value of pearls.
It's pointless to give it one]
[(Still confused) Then why give it
a pearl in the first place?]
Ink: Why give it a pearl?
Phuak: This is... giving a pearl to a monkey.
[(Hey, listen) This is the proverb,
"giving a pearl to a monkey"]
Phuak: Study hard.
[(Top-student mode)
They really did study hard]
[The monkeys in Lopburi know that!]
Ink: Monkeys in Lopburi know that, OK?
[Wait, is she saying we're monkeys?]
Phuak: Wait—Is she calling us
monkeys from Lopburi?
Bank: Giving a pearl to a monkey?
[Round four—Yellow Team goes last]
Jeff: Becky, say something quick.
Becky: Can we play
the "Dang! Dang! Dang!" game?
[(Can we play the Dang! Dang! Dang! game?)]
[Becky wants an easier one
because she wants to win]
[Not letting you play (so annoying)]
Phuak: No.
[So cruel]
[Round four begins]
PD: Conveyor belt, go.
[Swap-the-syllables word]
PD: Swap-the-syllables word.
PD: Che-Sa-Teph.
[Swap-the-syllables word: Che-Sa-Teph → ?]
Jeff: Jeff Satur.
[Jeff Satur]
[Correct]
PD: Next one.
PD: Proverb—holding a pestle.
[Thai proverb: holding a pestle → ?]
PD: Holding a pestle.
Mos: Chanting Buddhist scriptures?
[Chanting Buddhist scriptures]
[Correct]
PD: Correct.
Mos: Chanting Buddhist scriptures?
[Let's just stop at Becky]
[Thai proverb: where did it go → ?]
[Proverb?]
PD: Proverb—"Where did it go?"
[Where did it go… somewhere…?]
PD: Where did it go?
[Looks like she still doesn't know]
[This round's probably going to flop too…]
PD: Where did it go?
[Breaking the record
for most voluntary falls]
Phuak: Where did it go? That's it, bye-bye.
[With that fall, he could be a lifeguard]
[Everyone ready to fall]
Phuak: Where did it go? That's it, bye-bye.
Phuak: No idea where it went.
Becky: Go-go, come-come.
[(Is that the answer?)] Where did it go?
Go-go, come-come.
Phuak: Go.
[Ends with Becky falling into the water]
Tay: Where did it go?
Phuak: Where did it go? That's it, bye-bye.
[Where did he go? Over. Bye]
[After Becky's mistake, Red Team was cracking up]
Phuak: No idea where it went.
Ink: Bye-bye.
[Go Blue Team!]
-Phuak: Give us a harder proverb.
-Tay: No, what if we can't answer?
[This team is asking for harder proverbs]
Ink: Make it harder. Red Team's strong.
Offroad: Red Team's strong.
[Use whatever tricks you've got!]
[Round five begins]
PD: Proverb—learn the crow's strengths.
[Thai proverb: learn the crow's strengths → ?]
Oat: Learn the crow's...
[Tay is completely confused]
Phuak: Why is it so hard?
[How can it be this hard?]
Phuak: Like…
[Just say something first]
Phuak: Like… like a chicken.
[Guessing wildly before falling]
[Following the others and
dropping into the water one by one]
Phuak: It's so hard.
Tay: Learn the crow's strengths.
Phuak: What does that mean?
[Is it about flying high?]
Tay: Is it about flying high?
I feel like I've heard this before.
[What was it again? It sounds so familiar]
PD: Learn the crow's strengths...
[(Answer) Learn the crow's strengths,
not its flaws]
PD: Not its flaws.
[(Learn the crow's diligence, not its greed)]
[Round five—Blue Team]
PD: Conveyor belt, go.
PD: Dang! Dang! Dang!
[Dang! Dang! Dang!]
PD: Dang! Dang! Dang! OK, pass.
PD: Swap-the-syllables word.
[Swap-the-syllables word:
Kha-Hai-Khun-Met-Tor → ?]
PD: Kha-Hai-Khun-Met-Tor.
Jeff: Please have mercy
(Kho-Hai-Khun-Met-Ta).
[Please have mercy]
[Correct]
PD: Proverb—climbing perch.
[Thai proverb: climbing perch → ?]
Mos: The climbing perch has a big head.
[Climbing perch]
[A big head?]
Mos: The climbing perch has a big head.
[Successful Becky]
Mos: Climbing perch.
[As usual, still has to
fall into the water]
[Huh? What's big?]
Oat: Climbing perch what?
[Looks like this round ends here…]
[Self-declared diving expert
jumps in without hesitation]
Mos: For climbing perch,
you have to call a dog.
[Why call a dog?
Still inventing brand-new fake proverbs]
Phuak: For climbing perch,
you have to call a dog?
Phuak: Wow, amazing! "For climbing perch,
you have to call a dog"—amazing!
[Ends with falling into the water]
Mos: Climbing perch what? I don't know.
PD: Climbing perch—dies from biting too quickly.
[The answer: the climbing perch
dies from biting too quickly]
[Final group of Round 5—Yellow Team enters]
PD: OK, ready? Let's begin.
[Dang! Dang! Dang!]
PD: Dang! Dang! Dang!
[Cleared it—he turned left
and
passed the "Dang! Dang! Dang!" game with ease]
Oat: Cleared it. I turned left, you know.
PD: Swap-the-syllables word.
[Swap-the-syllables word: Saeng-Dee → ?]
PD: Saeng-Dee.
[Red]
Offroad: Red (See-Daeng).
[Correct]
PD: Proverb.
[Thai proverb: in the land of the blind → ?]
-Ink: Keep your eyes closed.
-Correct.
[Keep your eyes closed]
[Correct]
-PD: In the land of the blind...
-Ink: Keep your eyes closed.
[Stop! Stop! Stop!]
Stop, stop, stop.
Oat: That was too fast.
[Yellow Team—all members passed]
[Scared out of his wits]
[When it was our turn, we got “learn the crow's strengths”]
Phuak: What are you giving us
"Learn the crow's strengths"?
[I knew that one too!]
Bnak: I knew that one too.
[The Red Team, unwilling to
be outshone, jumps in to talk back]
Ink: What? Can't I know anything at all?
[What? Can't I know anything at all?
Let me have my moment]
[End of Round 5, with Ink still fuming]
Phuak: That
"learn the crow's strengths"...
Ink: I know some of this too.
[Sticker count—Red Team: 5, Yellow Team: 3]
[Blue Team: 1; 3 stickers left]
PD: Final round—fight for the last stickers.
[The last round will be for
the remaining 3 stickers]
[Starting with the Red Team]
PD: Red Team, please step in.
Take your positions.
Phuak: Bank, you going first?
[This is the final round]
Oat: This is the final round.
PD: Ready? Begin.
[Thai proverb: building heaven → ?]
PD: Building heaven.
-Phuak: In the air.
-PD: Correct.
[Building heaven in the air] [Correct]
[Building heaven in the air]
[Thai proverb: what ten mouths say → ?]
PD: What ten mouths say...
-Tay: Is not as good as seeing it with your own eyes.
-PD: Correct.
[Is not as good as seeing it with your own eyes]
[Thai proverb: slowness brings results → ?]
PD: Slowness brings results...
Bank: Slowness brings results… It's magic.
Bank: Slowness… Slowness brings results.
[We told you it's a proverb…]
Bank: Slowness brings results.
[It means you can succeed if you do it slowly?]
Tay: Slowness brings results. What?
Bank: Slowness brings results.
[Tay jumps straight into the water]
Bank: Slowness brings results. Slowness...
[Before falling into the water,
he kept shouting the question over and over]
Phuak: Slowness brings results. What's that?
[I don't know!]
Bank: Hmm… I don't know.
[Thai proverb: slowness brings results →
persistence brings benefits]
PD: Slowness brings results;
persistence brings benefits.
(Steady work yields fine results)
Bank: Even my mom wouldn't know this one.
[Even my mom wouldn't know this one]
[Red Team ends as Bank fails
to complete the proverb]
[Yellow Team's final attempt]
PD: Conveyor belt, go.
PD: Swap-the-syllables word.
[Swap-the-syllables word:
Yai-Pen-Khon-Thee-Chak → ?]
PD: Yai-Pen-Khon-Thee-Chak.
[I want to be the right person]
Oat: I want to be the right person
(Yak-Pen-Khon-Thee-Chai).
[Correct]
PD: Correct.
PD: Proverb—paint a tiger.
[Thai proverb: paint a tiger → ?]
PD: Paint a tiger.
[Can they get it this time?]
Ink: Show it to a monkey.
[Can someone who doesn't know
proverbs guess it right?]
[Did we hear that right? Hahaha]
Ink: Show…
Ink: Show it to a monkey.
[Show it to a monkey!]
[What are we supposed to do with that?]
Ink: Paint a tiger...
[This is terrifying!]
Ink: Feed it to a cow.
[Feed it to a cow!]
[In the end, everyone falls into the water]
Phuak: Paint a tiger and feed it to a cow.
[Paint a tiger and
then feed it to a cow, hahaha]
Bank: Paint a tiger what?
[Paint a tiger and feed it to a cow]
Oat: Paint a tiger and feed it to a cow.
[Paint a tiger
and then give it to a cow?]
Oat: That's crazy.
Ink: What is it?
[What even is that?]
PD: Paint a tiger to scare a cow.
[The correct answer is: Paint a tiger
to scare a cow]
[Since no one knew the proverb,
they at least had fun falling into the water]
Oat: "Paint a tiger and feed it to a cow"—
I'm dead.
[Almost dying laughing
at Ink's made-up proverb]
Oat: Paint a tiger and feed it to a cow.
[Paint a tiger and feed it to a cow]
[Completely dumbfounded]
Oat: I'm totally stunned.
[Finally, the last team]
PD: Conveyor belt, go.
PD: Swap-the-syllables word: Lom-Ook.
[Swap-the-syllables word: Lom-Ook → ?]
-Mos: Candy (Look-Om).
-PD: Correct.
[Candy]
[Correct]
PD: Proverb.
-PD: Apply gold leaf...
-Jeff: To the back of a Buddha statue.
[Thai proverb: apply gold leaf → ?]
[To the back of a Buddha statue]
[Correct]
PD: Swap-the-syllables word.
PD: Bee-Gek.
[Swap-the-syllables word: Bee-Gek → ?]
[If it's a swap-the-syllables word,
they might not get it…]
PD: Bee-Gek.
[Come on…]
[Becky looks completely confused]
[Could it be… she doesn't know?]
PD: Bee-Gek.
[Swap-the-syllables word: Bee-Gek → ?]
Becky: Becky.
[Becky]
[Becky! Becky!]
PD: Correct.
[Correct]
-Becky: Becky.
-PD: Correct.
[Becky did it!]
PD: Correct, stop.
[Didn't expect Becky to get it right]
[The last 3 stickers go to the Blue Team]
PD: So, the last 3 stickers
PD: belong to the Blue team.
[Total stickers—Red Team: 5;
Yellow Team: 3; Blue Team: 4]
Jeff: Go for it, Becky!
[The outcome now rests in the hands
of the final-round winner, Becky]
Oat: What was that just now? Blue?
PD: One, two, three.
[The wheel is spinning rapidly]
Tay: Hey, wait a second.
[Who will be the final holder in this game?]
[Where will the wheel finally stop?]
[Yellow Team wins shares]
Oat: See that?
[Yellow Team gains an extra 20% in shares]
PD: Yellow Team gains
an extra 20% in shares.
Offroad: This is what you call entertainment!
Now that's some real show effect!
[New Heir Mission;
Yellow Team +20% shares, Red and Blue get none]
[After all missions end,
only 1 person will be the final winner]
Oat: OK. Let's go.
PD: Next comes the final showdown.
PD: Today's mission is called—
PD: Name Tag Ripping: The Share War.
Ink: That's scary.
Offroad: I'm already getting nervous.
PD: To find the business heir of Group R—
PD: Since we're choosing an heir,
PD: there can only be one.
Jeff: Wow.
[From now on, it becomes an individual battle
to determine the sole heir!]
The first target is—
[Rule 1: The player with the fewest shares
will be targeted first!]
Target has been switched.
Next target.
[Rule 2: Targets cannot rip others' name tags]
Ink: Still not off yet?
[Others must eliminate
the targets within 15 minutes!)]
Phuak: How is it? Does it hurt?
[Rule 3: To get rid of the identity of the target,
you must survive for 15 minutes in pursuit]
[Rule 4: Find a hidden "whistle," and blowing it
forces a target switch!]
[Rule 5: The last 2 players remaining
will face off 1-on-1 to decide the final heir!]
Ink: Oh my god.
Mos: This could work—
I might actually make it out alive!
Jeff: Honestly, this stuff
is really hard to find.
Bank: Never Stop Running.
Phuak: Never Stop Running.
Oat: They're not revealing
how many shares each person has.
Oat: That's what makes it exciting.
Phuak: We'll keep rotating targets
until there’s a winner.
[Attack and defense roles
switch every 15 minutes]
Phuak: We're on our own.
Oat: Second floor, second floor!
Phuak: Block all the exits downstairs.
Bank: 15 minutes flies by—so scary.
[To become the final heir]
Becky: I don't want to be hunted down.
Mos: I'm being hunted right now.
It feels like a horror movie.
Tay: Is anyone there?
[An Inheritance Battle
with Survival on the Line]
Tay: Help!
-PD: Go. Five.
-Bank: This is the real version of Squid Game.
[The Running Man version
of Squid Game officially begins]
Four, three, two, one.
[ Name-Tag Ripping Game begins]
Name Tag Ripping: The Share War
is about to begin.
[The first targets are]
The first targets are—
[Jeff and Mos]
Jeff and Mos.
Everyone, before the two of them find a whistle—
[Rip off the targets' name tag
before they find a "whistle"]
rip off their name tags.
[The share ratio
of the 2 targets is the same]
Run.
[RUN]
The first targets...
[The first targets are]
Are...
Jeff
[Jeff and Mos]
and Mos.
Jeff
[Run for your lives before they come at you…]
Ink: Jeff and Mos.
Phuak: Jeff and Mos.
Offroad: I think
taking Jeff out first is a good idea.
Offroad: Because Jeff—
Offroad: he's really strong.
Phuak: Move fast!
Phuak: Oat, what should we do?
Oat: Help find Jeff.
[To survive, they have
to find a whistle first]
Phuak: Oh, here he is.
Jeff: Bro, we should deal with Mos first.
Oat: Jeff!
Oat: If you're the first one out,
that'd be quite a show.
Oat: Jeff!
Phuak: Jeff is here.
Oat: Tay, Jeff is here!
Oat: Tay!
Oat: Block him! Phuak, cut him off!
Oat: Tay, Jeff is here!
Bank: Hey, they're chasing
each other over there.
Bank: Why are you here? Down there.
Bank: Downstairs.
Bank: They're downstairs.
Offroad: Go! Move, go get him!
Offroad: Go, hurry!
Offroad: Now's not the time.
Offroad: Right?
Wait a bit—they'll get exhausted soon.
Offroad: They hid the keys, right?
No—wait, the whistle.
[Offroad's plan: Find a "whistle" first]
Offroad: I'm not coming
back to this area again.
Offroad: I've got it memorized.
Offroad: This is a dead end.
Phuak: Second floor. Second floor.
Phuak: Second floor, second floor!
Bank: Where? Where?
Phuak: Grab him, grab him!
Phuak: Rip it—hurry!
Phuak: Now's the moment—go for it!
Phuak: Hold on tight!
Jeff: Bro, we've got to take Oat out first.
-Jeff: Bro, we've got to take Oat out first.
-Phuak: Why?
Jeff: Otherwise, you won't
have me... helping you.
Phuak: Go, go!
Phuak: Turn him around—turn him!
Bank: I'm a fan of Jeff!
Phuak: Go, go!
[I can't do it… I'm a die-hard fan of Jeff!]
[When Jeff tried his best to resist,
and received support from his fan]
[What's happening with Mos, the other target?]
[Who's charging at Mos right now?]
[Gasp!]
[Tay]
[Hiss]
Mos: Tay. Hello.
[At least he has grabbed the name tag!]
[But his defense is insanely strong]
Tay: Becky, hurry!
Tay: Do it before he fights back!
Becky: Where is it?
Tay: Becky!
[Keep running for these 15 minutes! Don't stop!]
Becky: Just give up already.
[Mos, ranked sixth, refuses to give up]
Tay: Becky, rip it!
Tay: Why won't you surrender?
Tay: Without Nanno
(Becky's character),
Tay: this wouldn't be exciting.
Becky: Without Nanno,
it wouldn't be exciting.
[What? Even Oat has joined in?]
[Come on… just give up…]
Tay: Becky, hurry!
Oat: Mos!
Oat: Mos, let's finish this—Mos!
[Even Ink has joined?
That's 4 people attacking him!]
Ink: Still not off yet?
Ink: No, no.
[Just hold out for these 15 minutes!]
Ink: Almost there—
you'll be going home soon.
Mos: I want to go home.
-Tay: I'm tickling you.
-Oat: OK. OK.
[But…]
Tay: Where did Jeff go?
Jeff: Phuak's holding him off over there.
Phuak: Hurry, help me out!
-Phuak: Almost got it.
-Offroad: Come on, Jeff!
Jeff: Let’s make a deal.
Jeff: Come on.
[I've got to seize this chance!]
Jeff: Let's make a deal.
Jeff: Let’s make a deal.
Jeff: Come on.
Jeff: Let’s deal with Oat first.
Otherwise, no one...
Phuak: It's off!
Jeff: Not yet.
Phuak: It's off, it's off!
[What… did it really get ripped off?]
Phuak: Not yet.
Phuak: It's off! It's off!
-Bank: Jeff.
-It's okay.
Jeff: I'm exhausted.
Bank: Jeff—
did I do well as your fan?
-Bank: I love you, Jeff. I'll get going.
-Jeff: Just go.
[Jeff OUT]
PD: Jeff is out.
Phuak: Where did the guy I was chasing go?
Phuak: Oat—where'd he go?
Tay: Alright, stop struggling.
[Grabs his legs… climbs on and pins him down…]
-Ink: Oh, Oat.
-Oat: Tay. Tay.
Oat: Trust me.
Oat: Hey bro, it won't hurt at all.
It'll be over in a second.
[Four against one, surrounding Mos]
Oat: Tay, help me grab his hands!
Oat: Becky!
Oat: Becky, use your strength!
Ink: Becky, rip it—hurry!
[They turned Mos into a sacrifice]
[So, you finally felt the thrill of tearing off
a name tag yourself, huh?]
-Oat: Rip it off.
-Ink: Rip it off.
Oat: Rip it off.
Ink: Mos!
[The moment it comes off… it feels amazing!]
Ink: This is why the game is so fun, kid.
[Mos OUT]
PD: Mos is out.
[OUT]
[Jeff becomes the first to go to jail]
Jeff: I'm the first one here.
Jeff: First time in my life
getting wrecked like this.
Jeff: Not a trace of a winner left in me.
Jeff: Any plan? Any injuries?
Jeff: No. I didn't dare go all out.
This side of my face is still swollen.
[I've got to find a chance
to take back first place!]
[OUT]
PD: The target has been switched.
PD: The next target is
PD: Tay.
PD: The next target is Tay.
PD: The next target is
Tay.
Ink: The next target is Tay. Tay!
Ink: The next target is Tay!
Oat: Tay...
[Tay disappears from sight in an instant]
[See you later… Tay…]
Oat: Did he run?
Bank: He ran.
Bank: We need to cut him off over there.
[This guy suddenly starts
interacting with his fans]
[The fans]
[But when it comes to finding the whistle,
he's still totally serious]
Offroad: If I can't find the whistle,
I'm dead for sure.
Offroad: No matter how fast I run, I'm done.
They'll just gang up on me.
Offroad: The whistle's already hidden, right?
Offroad: What does this whistle even look like?
Offroad: This whistle is way too hard to find,
harder than the ring in the last episode.
[After hiding and dodging for a long time,
Tay finally shows up on the second floor]
Bank: Who is it?
Bank: 15 minutes per person?
Bank: How much time is left?
Tay: No.
Tay: Don't move.
[Whistle?]
Bank: Do you have a whistle?
Bank: Go ahead.
Bank: Blow it.
[Where did this whistle come from?]
Tay: No way.
[When he came in just now]
[he was looking for a place to hide...]
[Fortunately, there was a whistle there]
[Tay's finally getting lucky… he's saved]
The target has changed.
The next target is…
Ink.
The next target is—
The next target is Ink.
Becky: Ink.
Becky: Is it Ink?
Oat: Where is Ink?
Bank: I don't see her, bro.
[They have to find "Ink"
and the "Whistle" at the same time]
The target has been changed.
[Has the target changed?]
Next target.
[No way…]
Bank and Becky.
Phuak: Bank and Becky.
Offroad: Are they Bank and Becky?
Offroad: Hey.
Bank and Becky.
The next targets are... Bank and Becky.
Bank: Who?
Bank and Becky.
The next targets are
[So where did Ink go?]
[When Ink became the target]
The next target is…
Ink.
Ink: Oh, let's find the whistle.
Ink: Let's find the whistle.
[Looking for whistle calmly]
Ink: The whistle.
[The whistle?]
[A whistle was found in the closet]
[The whistle saved Ink's life]
Ink: Finally saved… I made it out alive.
Ink: I'm so happy to find it first.
The next target is
Bank and Becky.
[They have equal shares,
so they become targets at the same time]
Bank and Becky.
Becky: No.
[Bank is being chased]
Phuak: It's a dead end.
Phuak: Third floor!
Phuak: Elevator!
Ink: OK.
Phuak: Let's go. Tay is on the left.
[Out of breath]
Bank: You are, too? No way.
Bank: Oh.
Tay: Bank, trust me.
Tay: Otherwise, I'll call a lot of people over—
and you'll just end up getting hurt for nothing.
Tay: It's better to die in one person's hands.
Tay: Bank, trust me.
[Who will be the final winner?]
Ink: Becky.
Ink: Phuak, Becky's here.
Phuak: Come on. Ink, do it.
Becky: Give me a hug.
Phuak: Sorry.
Ink: Sorry, Becky.
Phuak: Come here, kid.
Phuak: It doesn't hurt. It doesn't hurt.
Just a moment.
Phuak: It'll just take a second.
Phuak: It'll just take a second. Kid.
Phuak: Just a second.
Phuak: It'll be quick. It won't hurt, kid.
Phuak: It'll be quick, Ink.
Phuak: Do it.
Phuak: OK.
Phuak: OK. It's over.
Ink: Phuak, pull hard.
Phuak: 1, 2, hey, 1, 2.
Phuak: 1, 2, hey.
Phuak: Let go. Let go. Kid. Let go.
Phuak: Let go, kid. Becky.
Ink: Becky, I'm sorry.
[Rip—]
Phuak: OK.
Ink: Becky, I'm sorry.
Ink: I'm sorry.
Becky: It's okay.
Ink: Are you tired?
[Becky is out]
Becky is out.
Tay: Everyone!
Tay: Here.
Tay: Is anybody here?
Tay: Help!
Oat: Turn him over.
Oat: 1, 2.
[I need to stay here for 15 minutes]
Oat: Let him lie down.
Time's up. The target has changed.
Time's up.
The target has changed.
[Finally escaped]
The next targets are…
Phuak
and Offroad.
Phuak and Offroad.
Oat: I'll be the next.
Oat: Where did Phuak go?
[Don't come this way. I'll hide quietly]
Phuak: This corner we're in right now is perfect.
Phuak: If they come from below,
we'll run up.
Phuak: If they come from above,
we'll run down.
Phuak: OK, everyone, take a break.
Phuak: Take a break.
Phuak: This game
requires teamwork.
Phuak: We can't just run on our own.
Phuak: We have to take
the photographers with us.
Phuak: Take a break.
[Just hang in here for 15 minutes]
Offroad: Wait.
Offroad: I think someone is coming.
Offroad: Hey. I can see him from here.
Offroad: Now I can see everything.
Offroad: I saw everything.
Offroad: I want to stay here
for 15 minutes.
Offroad: Someone's really close to me.
[Ink and Tay are coming]
Ink: Offroad.
Ink: Offroad. Tay.
Offroad is over there.
Tay: Everyone!
Tay: This way.
Tay: Hurry.
[He ran into a dead end?]
Offroad: Oh, my.
Tay: Hey, I'm exhausted.
Tay: Ink!
Tay: Oh.
Offroad: Oops. You surrounded me. Come on.
Oat: Where are you going, bro?
Oat: Surrender.
Oat: Let it end quickly. Offroad.
Oat: It's useless. Listen to me.
[Offroad is out]
Offroad is out.
[No matter how chaotic things are outside,
he still has the nerve to stretch]
Phuak: I need to stretch a bit.
Phuak: Or my muscles will cramp.
Phuak: Thank you.
Phuak: Thank all my fans
on social media.
Phuak: Thank you for your encouragement.
Phuak: Phuak.
Phuak: Seokjin. (Suk-jin)
Phuak: What was his name again?
[He's sitting down and chatting]
Phuak: That Korean
who always loses.
Phuak: Thank you very much.
Phuak: Have they announced it?
Phuak: It's changed. The target has changed.
[Successfully survived 15 minutes]
Phuak: It's changed.
Time's up. Change the target.
The next target is…
[The sixth target - Oat]
Oat!
The next target is Oat.
[Carefully searching for the whistle]
[Finally, Oat bumps into Ink]
Ink: Give me a hug, Oat.
[Leave the name tag to me, Oat]
[Completely defenseless.
Even Ink alone is already a huge threat to him]
[The only way to escape!]
Ink: Oat.
Ink: I can't run anyway.
[Tay comes to help
when he hears the sound]
Tay: Ink, where are you?
Ink: Tay, hurry.
Tay: I can't run fast. I have a cramp.
[Tay joins the team to besiege Oat]
Tay: Bro, hurry up.
[Ink lost Oat]
[Oat stops to breathe]
Oat: I'm exhausted.
Tay: Oat.
Tay: Bro, hurry.
[Finds a chance to ambush Oat]
[Almost got him]
Tay: Oat.
Tay: Trust me.
Tay: Why don't you just sit in jail?
Sounds pretty comfortable, right, Oat?
Tay: Oat.
Tay: Ink!
Ink: Why?
Tay: Here. Hurry.
[I don't want to chase the Bear anymore.
Too tired]
Ink: Oh, I don't want
to hunt the Bear anymore.
Ink: I'm tired.
[After getting lost for a while,
she finally made her way back]
Ink: Oat.
Ink: I love you.
[His arm was grabbed and held tight,
and he instantly lost his balance]
[Phuak, who had been hiding the whole time,
suddenly appears and jumps into the fight]
Phuak: Hey, who is it?
Ink: Oat.
Ink: Come on, Phuak.
Ink: Come on.
Ink: Help me put the Bear down.
Ink: Rip it off with force!
Phuak: Coming.
Phuak: Rip it off slowly. I got it. Got it.
Phuak: Got it! Got it!
Phuak: Take it off slowly.
[Oat fights with everything he's got,
desperately protecting his name tag]
Ink: Oat, don't kick me—ow, ow!
Phuak: Got it off!
Phuak: OK, OK.
Phuak: OK, OK, OK.
Oat: Oh, no.
Oat: Three against one—
I couldn't handle it.
Ink: Go—run, Tay!
[Oat is out]
Oat is out.
Target has changed.
The next target is
Tay.
[Announcement: The next target is Tay]
Target has changed.
The next target is
Tay.
[Phuak asks for a moment
to catch his breath]
Phuak: It's Tay, right?
Phuak: OK.
Phuak: Tay, huh.
Phuak: Who's left? How many are left?
Phuak: I'm already down 4 fingers counting.
Phuak: You get me?
Phuak: That darn "chomp chomp" took them out.
Phuak: Ouch.
[Whoa, who's this now?]
Phuak: Come here, baby—
come on, over here, over here!
[Tay slowly approaches the resting Phuak]
Phuak: Come here, baby—
come on, over here, over here!
Phuak: Hurry, let's hide—
quick, Tay, Tay!
Phuak: Tay!
Phuak: Come hide with me, hurry!
Phuak: What's the plan?
Tay: Fine… I don't feel like moving. I'm tired.
Phuak: Tired?
Tay: Yeah.
Phuak: Must be exhausted.
Tay: Dead tired.
Phuak: Found him, found him—
come here, everyone!
[Giving it everything to turn things around]
[Clinging to his name tag
and successfully breaking free]
Phuak: Where did everyone go?
[After shaking off Phuak,
Tay runs toward…]
[Did he just hide in a cabinet?]
[Hiding in a weird spot;
Even the staff are stunned]
Tay: Doesn't smell, doesn't smell.
Tay: OK.
[It's fine.
It actually feels pretty comfortable]
Tay: Very comfortable.
[It's so cramped. We can only hand the camera in
to him so he can film himself]
Tay: Alright.
[Quick! Close the door!]
Tay: So now…
Tay: Tay is hiding
Tay: inside a cabinet.
Tay: I can't move at all.
Tay: Help.
Tay: What am I even doing?
Tay: Right now…
Tay: you know what this looks like?
Tay: Like that kid
Tay: hiding
Tay: from the velociraptor
Tay: in the first Jurassic Park movie,
Tay: the kitchen scene.
Tay: Anyone seen it?
[5 minutes later]
Tay: Guys,
Tay: I've made up my mind.
Tay: I'm still
Tay: not giving up.
Tay: At this very moment,
[10 minutes have passed]
Tay: The oxygen left…
Tay: …what's left…
Tay: Has anyone come yet?
Tay: There's barely any oxygen left.
Tay: Please let these 15 minutes pass faster.
[Finding the whistle is now
more important than catching Tay]
[She searches through every drawer]
[Another whistle has been found!]
[A sudden noise comes from upstairs]
[While heading downstairs,
they run straight into each other]
Ink: Who are we going for?
Phuak: Tay.
Phuak: Next up
should be Ink, right?
Ink: Yes.
Phuak: Stay away from me.
[Looks highly suspicious]
Phuak: I'll keep watch here.
Phuak: Did you find it?
Ink: I did, but don't give it...
Don't give it to her.
Ink: Don't give it.
Ink: Don't give it, no matter what.
Ink: Don't come near me.
Ink: Stay away.
Phuak: Did you grab it?
Phuak: Open a gap, let me see—just a little.
Ink: No.
Phuak: Just a little gap, come on.
Phuak: Open a gap and let me see.
Phuak: Guys.
Ink: Phuak.
Ink: Phuak, don't do this.
Phuak: Ink found a whistle.
Ink: Phuak is lying.
The target has changed.
[Upon hearing the announcement,
she immediately grabs the whistle]
The target has changed.
The next target is
Ink.
Ink: Oh, no… starting over.
Ink: That was close.
Target changed.
Phuak: Lucky you.
Ink: Oh my—my hands are shaking.
PD: The next target is Bank.
[Ink escapes danger once again]
The next target is
Bank.
[Becky is out;
The target switches back to Bank]
Bank.
The next target is
Bank: The whistle.
[After holding out for 15 minutes,
he finally comes out of the cabinet]
Tay: Why did I put myself through this…
[Seriously… no one
told you to hide in there]
[Once was enough—I'm never
getting in a cabinet again]
Ink: Where's Bank?
[Searching for Bank
while also looking for the whistle]
Ink: Where is Bank?
Tay: What's the situation now?
[She runs into Tay,
who just came out of the cabinet]
Ink: That kid blew the whistle twice.
Tay: Did he find it?
Ink: Yeah.
Ink: He looked pretty confused too.
How did he even manage to find it?
[They put arms around
each other, proposing an alliance]
Ink: Today…
Ink: when it's our turn,
Tay: we just go down peacefully.
Tay: Let's just give up.
Ink: We… we stick together.
[They promise to protect each other]
Tay: Just give up.
Ink: Because we're… today we're...
Tay: Teammates.
Ink: Then let's be teammates for once.
[Phuak is searching for the whistle and Bank]
Phuak: This place has been completely searched.
Phuak: Someone already went
through everything here.
[This place looks very suspicious]
[He catches Bank hiding]
Bank: Have a seat, bro.
Phuak: Why not Tay?
Phuak: What,
you wanna go one-on-one with Tay?
Bank: No, I just want
Bank: Tay to advance.
[He walks over, ready to take out Bank]
Phuak: Bank.
Phuak: Did that hurt, baby?
Bank: Yeah.
[Trying to "gently" persuade him to give up]
Bank: I'm on your team, bro.
Phuak: Yeah.
Bank: And I really respect you, bro.
Phuak: But I'm just trying to help you
[Clearly, it's not working at all]
Phuak: get your freedom.
Bank: The game this morning was really fun.
Phuak: Yeah.
Phuak: True.
Bank: Don't come closer.
[The net is closing in]
Phuak: Bank, we're
such great teammates.
Phuak: Did that hurt?
[Bank loses his balance and falls]
[It's off!]
Phuak: You okay? You okay?
Phuak: You okay?
Phuak: Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Phuak: Does it hurt?
Phuak: It's over, it's over.
[Bank has been eliminated]
Bank is out.
The next target is
Phuak.
Ink: Tay.
Ink: Did you find him?
Ink: No idea where he's hiding.
Tay: Let's search together.
I think he's on this floor.
Tay: He probably can't go downstairs, right?
Ink: Who, Phuak?
Tay: Yeah.
Ink: Did he go down the fire exit?
I didn't see him.
Tay: Hmm…
Ink: But he's really gone.
[They have no idea where Phuak is]
Phuak: Darn it,
these 15 minutes are torture.
Phuak: I was supposed to hide according to plan.
[He's somehow still worried
about his gloves
tearing at the fingertips]
Phuak: During the game, I've already
lost 6 out of 10 finger guards.
[Around here!
Trying looking for the whistle!]
Phuak: Anyone got a whistle? Blow it!
[He survives the 15 minutes and escapes danger]
Time's up.
Target changed.
[Target locked on Tay — the chase begins]
The next target is
Tay.
The next target is Tay.
[Trying to hide under the table]
Ink: We still don't know
where Tay went.
Phuak: He's definitely hiding.
Phuak: Tay is definitely hiding.
Phuak: He's for sure hiding.
[Tay feels under the table isn't safe]
[Decides to switch hiding spots]
[Hides under a table covered with a tablecloth]
[Looks much roomier than the cabinet]
Tay: All I can do now is hide.
Tay: I have to stay hidden.
Tay: That's the only way to win.
[Another painful 15 minutes to endure]
[Tay successfully escapes again]
Time's up.
The target has changed.
The next target is
Ink.
[Ink couldn't find the whistle
and becomes the target]
Ink: Where should I hide?
Phuak: Where is she?
[Phuak is spotted
through a mirror reflection]
Ink: Where should I hide?
[Phuak also spots Ink running away]
Phuak: There! There! There!
[Running for her life]
Ink: Stop bothering me!
Ink: Tay, grab Phuak!
[Phuak quickly catches up]
[Falls to the ground, desperately
protecting her name tag]
Phuak: Stop running.
Ink: I hate you, Phuak.
Tay: Why didn't you run faster?
Phuak: Exactly.
Phuak: You're going to get caught anyway, Ink.
Tay: Why didn't you run faster?
Phuak: Flip her over—slowly, slowly.
Phuak: Tay, Tay—help flip her over.
Phuak: I can tear it myself in a bit.
Phuak: Careful, it might hurt.
Tay: Come on—snake god reincarnated.
Phuak: Mm, mm, mm.
Tay: Girl… I'm sorry.
Tay: We're going down peacefully.
[They had clearly promised
to protect each other]
Ink: We… we'll give up together.
Tay: Just give up.
Ink: Because we're… today we're...
Tay: Teammates.
Ink: Then let's be teammates for once.
Tay: Girl… I'm sorry.
[Ink has been eliminated]
Ink is out.
To compete for the sole heir position,
Tay and Phuak
[Phuak vs Tay — the final showdown]
now begins
the 1-on-1 name tag battle.
Phuak: A one-on-one, huh.
[1 vs 1]
[Entering the final heir selection round]
[Another challenger eager to claim victory]
[For the heir position of the R Group]
[A head-on clash between the two]
[The ultimate duel to crown the one true winner]
Phuak: Feels like Goku
taking off his weighted training gear—so light.
[Why take off the gloves?]
Tay: Phuak.
Phuak: Bring it on.
Phuak: Let's settle this, Tay.
Phuak: Hey—Tay,
don't squeeze my hand so hard!
[Tay adopts a "lying flat" battle strategy]
Tay: Ugh—hey, Phuak.
Tay: Phuak.
[Tay tries to bite again]
Phuak: Don't bite!
Phuak: What are you, a human or a dog?
[Grabs Tay's name tag]
[Grabs Phuak's name tag]
[Who will become the final heir?]
[Royal Cliff Grand Hotel]
[Rip—!]
PD: Alright, the name tag ripping mission
has successfully concluded.
Oat: I don't really care who won.
Oat: I just want to know who took me out.
Jeff: Who was it, bro?
Ink: Who did it?
Jeff: These are Phuak's finger guards.
Oat: One.
Oat: Here.
Oat: Two.
Oat: Three.
Jeff: There are 5 of them?
Oat: Four.
Oat: Five.
Ink: Five finger guards?
[Five finger guards scattered on the ground]
Jeff: Are all five here?
Oat: I don't know who inherited the fortune,
but I know who took me out.
Oat: Because there's only one truth.
Ink: Tsk tsk, adding drama now, huh.
Ink: Really milking it.
Ink: Seriously.
Oat: Oh wow, oh wow.
Phuak: Found the finger guards.
Oat: Tch.
Oat: How could you not?
Oat: They were all stuck to my name tag.
Phuak: Stuck to the Velcro?
Oat: All of them stuck there.
Phuak: No wonder I searched forever.
Offroad: I really want to know the result.
Mos: But look at these clothes…
Mos: Look at them—completely wrecked.
Mos: Tay.
PD: Time to reveal the answer.
[Phuak and Tay—
their clothes are completely torn up]
Offroad: Is it Tay?
[Who is the heir of the R Group?]
PD: 1, 2, 3.
[Now revealing the answer]
[Phuak made the first move]
[Tay launched a fierce counterattack]
[Phuak's name tag slipped
to his shoulder]
[Tay fought to the very end, refusing to let go]
Phuak: Why are you so strong?
[Phuak tried his best to defend]
[Tay went all out]
Tay: Phuak, I'm sorry.
Tay: I'm sorry.
Phuak: As long as you win, it's fine.
PD: The name tag ripping battle mission is over.
Phuak: Not bad, not bad.
Tay: Let's team up again next time.
Ink: Quiet luxury, quiet luxury.
Tay: Now you get what "quiet luxury" means?
Oat: OK. OK.
[The heir of the R Group is—Tay]
PD: Tay, please come sign to receive the shares.
Oat: Today,
we've prepared a special prize for Tay.
Oat: It's a full night's stay
at that hotel just now.
Tay: Any witnesses? Who's going to be my witness?
Jeff: Sure, I can do it.
Jeff: For the boss, of course no problem.
Phuak: Since he's taking the shares,
can I have the trophy?
Tay: Since you're the witness, we will…
Tay: hand over the entire second floor
to your management.
[What about my share of the prize money?]
Jeff: Thank you so much.
It's truly an honor.
Jeff: Good thing I've always
been on good terms with Tay.
Oat: That's not ours.
Phuak: Wait. You already took the shares.
Phuak: I just want a trophy
to take home and display, okay?
Oat: That's not ours.
Phuak: That's for second place.
Oat: No need, no need, no need.
[Looking especially cute today]
Phuak: It's for second place!
Tay: Alright, please stay tuned to
Running Man Thailand. Never Stop Running.
Every Sunday at 8 PM, exclusively on the iQIYI app
and iQ.com.
Running Man Thailand — Never Stop Running!
Ink: Where are we?
Phuak: Oh man…
PD: An Earthling has infiltrated
PD: to stop the aliens
from returning to their home planet.
Phuak: I can't hold on anymore.