=Faith & Fire=
=Episode 32=
(Ming, Xiu, sorry,
this act is exhausting)
How is it?
Did Nana
take good care of you?
Sure.
I don't even want to leave.
Isn't that simple?
You're welcome to come anytime.
But there are conditions, huh?
Making peace
is good for everyone.
Moreover, in name,
Five Lakes Alliance can remain
independent.
In name, right?
Chen Tianshuang.
I'm quite curious about you.
I'm a simple person.
Why curious about me?
Every time, you left
a deep impression on me.
Do you know why?
Because I'm handsome.
You're very rational.
Rational?
You seem to act on impulse.
But,
in fact, you see through
the current situation.
You may be talking nonsense,
but your purpose is clear.
That means the emotional appearance
is just your disguise.
Really?
Am I that amazing?
You know that yourself.
That's why I find it strange.
Why would a rational person
insist on fighting a losing battle?
Perhaps
it's not as complicated as you think.
I simply don't like you.
Have a drink first.
Try our specialty dish.
Boiled yellow croaker with noodles.
I specially invited a chef from Xiamen.
Really?
Then I'll try it.
Chen Tianshuang.
You haven't been telling the truth.
It's a life-or-death struggle
between us.
You want me to tell you the truth?
Not to me.
You are hiding the truth
from people around you too, right?
Do you do everything
because
you really care about the people
in Lian'an Town?
Or,
is this all your disguise?
And, the real you
has another purpose.
You are right.
Actually, I've been hiding my identity.
Actually,
I'm from
Alpha Centauri,
the Centaurus constellation,
40,000 light-years away
from Earth.
What you see now
is merely a humanoid shell.
My real purpose
is to lock down
your technological development
and pave the way for my companions
heading to Earth.
Your people
really are good at lying.
Came to Earth too early
and learned the bad ways
from your humans.
So you are determined
to oppose the chemical plant,
truly to stop
the progress of human technology?
Yeah.
No room for discussion?
Of course.
Then why did you still come?
I was going
to assassinate you.
But my weapon was confiscated.
I couldn't do it.
What a shame.
A small regret.
But fortunately,
other arrangements were quite nice.
Nice.
What's it called?
Boiled yellow croaker with noodles,
right?
It's delicious.
I want some more.
Another possibility.
You're not from outer space,
and you don't intend to kill me.
You came today
just to see
how high a price
you could get from me.
But there's bad news.
Not long ago,
you lost an important bargaining chip.
Stop it.
It's been half a day.
But there's no news at all.
Did something really happen?
What could happen?
Everyone knows he went to meet Anle.
But when Anle killed Heilun,
he didn't keep it a secret.
It's different.
How is it different?
It is just different.
What's different?
What is different?
Tianshuang.
Are you okay?
What could happen to me?
What did you do there?
I just had a meal.
Tianshuang.
You smell good.
Do I?
I also had a spa.
What spa?
In short,
he just gave me some incentive,
using threats and temptations.
Anle said
he wanted to settle things
with me in one go
and told us not to resist.
Tianshuang won't fall for that.
I did.
You're joking, right?
Do I seem like I'm joking?
He agreed?
He said he would go back
and tell the others
that he was with me now.
He asked me to cool it
with the protesters.
He said he'd handle it well.
Starting today,
I, Chen Tianshuang,
officially join Tianhai Sect
and work for Anle.
But besides that,
I'm still with Five Lakes Alliance.
We are still buddies.
Alright?
Okay.
Tianshuang.
What act are you putting on?
What act?
Wasn't it already obvious before?
We couldn't beat them.
So what can we do?
I'm doing this for everyone's good.
But you didn't have this attitude
yesterday.
That was yesterday.
Today is different.
Anle.
Starting today,
I, Chen Tianshuang,
officially join Tianhai Sect
and work for Anle.
But besides that,
I'm still with Five Lakes Alliance.
We are still buddies.
Alright?
He did it so soon?
Chen Tianshuang has been determined.
Why did he change his mind?
He Shuyi has already told me
she's willing to cooperate
with Tianhai Sect.
No wonder.
Chen Tianshuang is not a chief.
His prestige comes
from the headquarters.
Now, since the head has said that,
he has no choice.
Not necessarily.
The head wants to cooperate with Anle?
Did he lie to you?
He played the voice message.
If you don't believe it, call Shuyi.
She's just taken over
the Five Lakes Alliance
and has a lot of things to do.
She can only focus
on the big picture now.
Try to understand.
That might be true.
But
if I chose to give up,
I would let down my perseverance,
those who support me,
Lian'an Town,
and those who protested.
Joining Tianhai Sect
is my own choice.
Xiu.
You are the Chief of the Lian'an branch
of the Five Lakes Alliance.
The future here
depends on you.
Tianshuang.
I see you as a buddy.
Since you came,
I've cared about every word you say
because you are right.
But this time...
I've decided.
Whether the head helps or not,
or whether others want to fight or not,
it doesn't matter.
As long as I'm the Chief here,
Lian'an branch
of the Five Lakes Alliance
will fight Tianhai Sect to the end
and never give up.
So this time,
you don't agree with me?
Then you'll go against
the Chief Protector of the alliance?
I am the Chief here.
I don't care about Chief Protector
or the head.
In Lian'an Town,
I have the final say.
Is the current situation
not clear enough?
Even Chen Tianshuang,
who tried to persuade us,
has announced joining Tianhai Sect.
You're still jabbering here.
The overall situation is settled.
If the chemical plant comes,
who will buy my fish?
Will you?
So you mean
you will be as stubborn
as the Five Lakes Alliance
and have your house burned down?
I'll call the police.
Seriously.
They've done lots of these things.
Would they leave any evidence?
Just think about it.
Is the safety
of your family more important,
or is your lousy aquaculture business?
Didn't Luo say it?
As long as we are united,
we won't be afraid of them.
Luo?
Where is Luo now?
He's still in the hospital.
My way now is
that while there's room for negotiation,
get some compensation
and leave here.
Otherwise, if this keeps up,
we won't get a penny.
Still arguing here.
What's the point?
Alright.
Is there any use in arguing?
Yu.
What should we do?
I...
I also think
that although Luo has his reasons,
given the situation now....
What situation?
Chen Tianshuang?
I didn't mean that.
Don't talk nonsense
in front of Luo.
I can't guarantee.
There's now a new way out.
Want to take a look?
A new way out?
Anle said
that as long as you
support the chemical plant,
everyone will have some extra
compensation.
Extra compensation?
So good?
How much money?
Really?
Of course.
Otherwise, why would I
have joined Tianhai Sect?
It's not in the agreement.
Right.
If you don't write it,
we can't be relieved.
Then just write it down.
Why make it so complicated?
Right.
Write it down.
(Bonus: 800,000 per family)
(Pay 20,000 within 3 days.
Chen Tianshuang)
Okay?
Right.
This is okay.
Sign it.
Tianshuang.
Are you being serious?
Give it to me.
When you said to join Tianhai Sect,
I even told myself
that things might not be what I thought.
You must have another way.
But just now....
Are you being serious?
Gave it to me.
What are you doing?
You once said
that you'd protect Lian'an Town
and its future.
Is that all nonsense?
What do you know?
Do you know the situation?
Don't act like a child, alright?
You got my dad involved.
He's in the hospital now.
Can your conscience live with that?
I'm telling you.
What happened to your dad
is not my fault.
His own health was not good.
Ming.
What are you doing?
You're going to hit me?
You had it coming.
Have you forgotten
the rules?
No moves against Tianhai Sect.
Are you messing with me?
Enough!
Chen Tianshuang.
The rules of the Five Lakes Alliance.
No fighting with buddies.
Do you get it?
What do you mean?
I can't control others.
But this is
the Lian'an branch
of the Five Lakes Alliance.
When we are fighting with Tianhai Sect,
you choose to join them?
Spineless!
Who do you think you are?
I am now the Chief Protector.
What Chief Protector?
Here,
I have the final say.
I'm telling you,
from now on,
Five Lakes Alliance
has dismissed you.
You're not with Five Lakes Alliance.
Do you get it?
Is it up to you?
Did you ask Shuyi?
I don't need to tell you
whether I asked her.
None of your business.
Fine.
Are you sure?
Yes, sure.
Yu!
Do you agree to the terms?
This...
This is a serious matter.
Let's discuss it internally again?
I want your answer now!
If you agree now,
you can get one more bonus.
Double.
How...
How much?
Triple.
I agree.
- I also agree.
- I agree.
I can't hear you.
We agree.
Ming.
Let's go.
Go!
Ming.
Why aren't you going home yet?
Qi.
I...
What kind of person
do you think Tianshuang is?
Still thinking about it?
When I first met him,
we had just joined
the Five Lakes Alliance.
He had all sorts of little tricks
which made me furious.
How could someone
be so shameless?
I could hardly believe it.
He was indeed like that.
But after getting along with him more,
I found him actually quite nice
and reliable in times of trouble.
Later on,
I started to see him as my buddy,
even my best buddy.
Because I believe
that no matter how critical
the situation,
as long as he is there,
things can be resolved.
But today he...
I don't know.
I'm not sure
what he's thinking, either.
But after knowing him,
what I can be sure of is
that he definitely
isn't an ungrateful person.
Since he did this,
there must be a reason.
What reason?
Anyway, you don't need
to regret seeing him as a buddy.
He's still reliable.
Really?
Now I really can't see through him,
though I couldn't originally.
He might be
a complicated person,
but he's also
quite simple.
But if,
I mean, if.
If one day I'm not with you
and I have to entrust you guys
to someone,
I'll still choose Chen Tianshuang.
Actually, Tianshuang knows Shuyi...
Alright.
I've already said
that no matter what he does,
I'll trust him.
♪When the name is buried in dust♪
♪There's still a heartbeat
piercing through dawn and dusk♪
♪If there's no applause for the ending♪
♪At least the shadow
still makes a person♪