(Di) Network micro drama preparation (2025) No. 016.
Global First Line (Beijing) Movie and Cultural Limited Company
Beijing
Global First Line (Beijing) Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
What happened?
The car can only stop here.
Peiyu.
We've been in the mountain for half a day.
You carry so many.
Are you going to treat me to a feast?
Let's go.
This Mount Causeway is in the chest of the Nangan Dragon Vein.
Zhong Ling is outstanding.
He's a famous man.
Are you interested
stay here for a few months?
I happen to have a hostel.
You even open a guesthouse?
If you're willing to stay, I'll open tomorrow.
A big discount for opening.
I'll give you 20% off.
I heard that the dragon vein is full of geomancy.
I don't know what it says.
Mr. Zhang is an expert.
The three dragons came from Kunlun.
Our South Dragon
is spiritual.
It's a beautiful place.
There are more scholars to assist.
Since it's on the Dragon Vein,
it should be a good place.
But why is Mount Causeway sealed for a thousand years?
Could it be...
something is inside?
Mount Causeway.
There are wild people.
Boring.
Don't you think the fog is weird?
It's like he doesn't want us to see what's inside.
Let's go.
Wait.
The bamboo forest is foggy.
Sorry to bother you.
I'll turn back now.
You're playing tricks.
Just leave when I tell you to.
Go yourself if you want to die.
No one dares to enter the foggy mountain.
Peiyu.
Am I a dragon or a human?
A dragon or a human?
Is it a dragon or a human?
It's Snake Fairy.
Miss Xu.
Say it's human.
What demon?
Bai Qi.
You're so annoying.
Wait here.
I'll go in and find him.
Peiyu.
Why are you here?
Bai Qi is mine.
There's evil.
Shut up.
Don't talk from now on.
Let's split up.
Every five steps I take, I knock a few Bamboos.
I'll knock a few times.
You guys knock too.
Ah.
What are you doing?
You're asking for trouble.
It's so ugly.
Bai Qi.
Bai Qi!
Wake up.
Did you see what it was?
When I was mopping,
I was knocked out.
There's a spirit in Mount Causeway.
can tell good from evil.
It must be one of you
That's why Mount Causeway warned you in this way.
Xu Peiyu.
Tell me the truth.
If I don't make it clear,
I won't take another step forward.
Okay, I'll tell you.
Great-grandpa said there is a magical medicine in the Copper Rain Mountain.
can cure my nightmare.
We came here to find the medicine.
There is no magical medicine in Mount Causeway.
If you don't want to be the guide,
we'll find it ourselves.
Peiyu.
Wait for my 700,000 yuan.
Believe it or not, it's up to you.
There's no magical medicine in Mount Causeway anyway.
If you can't find it,
don't forget to pay the rest.
My great-grandfather won't lie to me.
Jang Gyu Ho.
Qian Yigua.
Bai Qi
No.
This voice
Something is wrong.
Oh no!
It's Bamboo Ghost! Run!
Actors team.
Actor.
Lin Chen, Chen Kaixin.
Xu Yinyu. Zhao Shuai.
Xu Yunyu and Zhao Shuai.
Actor.
Lin Chen, Chen Kaixin.
Zhang Jinghao, Ye Zijing.
Lanjingling, Ye Miaomiao.
Sophie.
Zhang Jinghao, Ye Zijing.
Lin Chen, Chen Kaixin.
Actor.
Xu Yunyu, Zhao Shuai.
Qian Yiqian, Luo Jing.
Qian Yigua, Luo Jing.
Xu Yunyu, Zhao Shuai.
Bai Qi Guo Jinbiao
Zhang Jinghao, Ye Zijing.
Xu Lanyu, Zhao Shuai.
Sophisticated Ye Miaomiao.
Qian Yigua, Luo Jing.
Lin Chen, Chen Kaixin.
Xiang Yunjian, Tang Qijun.
Softy leaves of blue.
Zhang Jinghao, Ye Zijing.
Qian Yijin, Luo Jing.
Xu Yinyu, Zhao Shuai.
Xu Yuanbao.
Bai Qi, Guo Jinbiao.
Qian Yi Jia, Luo Jing.
Sophie.
[Yang Li, Lan Yao Ling's mother.]
Qian Yigua, Luo Jing.
Bai Qi Guo Jinbiao.
Master Xu, Yuanbao.
Bai Qi, Guo Jinbiao.
Xiang Yunjian, Tang Qijun.
Qian Yigua, Luo Jing.
Yang Li, the mother of Lanjingling.
tour guide, Yao Yunren.
[Lanjingling's mother, Yang Li.]
Mr. Xu, Yuanbao.
Xiang Yunjian, Tang Qijun.
Bai Qi, Guo Jinbiao.
Mr. Xu, Ji In-gun.
Han Shihua, chief of the village.
[Lanjingling's mother, Yang Li.]
tour guide, Yao Yunren.
Xiang Yunjian, Tang Qijun.
Trainee guide, Yao Zhi Yan.
Young Xu, Xu Xiaojia.
Mr. Xu, Ji In-gun.
[Yang Li, Lan Yao Ling's mother.]
Villager Secretary Han Shihua.
Young Master Lin, Wang Rui.
Village secretary, Han Shihua.
Mr. Xu, Ji In-gun.
Han Shi-hwa, chief of the village.
Yang Li, the mother of Lanjingling.
Young Mr. Xu, Xu Xiaojia.
tour guide, Yao Liren.
Let me introduce grapefruit, Yu Yanyan.
Young Mr. Lin, Wang Rui.
Young Mr. Xu, Xu Xiaojia.
Han Shihua, the village secretary.
Mr. Xu, Ji Renjun.
A Japanese magician, Xie Yi.
Japanese sorcerer B, Sun Shengwen.
Young Master Lin, Wang Rui.
Let me introduce grapefruit, Yu Yanyan.
Young Mr. Xu, Xu Xiaojia.
A Japanese magician, Xie Yi.
Japanese Sorcerer B, Sun Shengwen.
A Mong Liang, Chinese Road.
Chinese Taoist A Monkey Liang.
Let me introduce grapefruit, Yu Yanyan.
Japanese magician A, Xie Yi.
Japanese magician B, Sun Shengwen.
Join the performance, Zhao Dezhong, Li Kangcheng. Zhang Jingbin, Sang Yu.
Chinese priest A Monkey Liang.
Join the show, Cho Deok-chong, Lee, and Jang Sunbin.
Japanese sorcerer B, Sun Shengwen.
Chinese Taoist A Monkey Liang.
Let me introduce grapefruit, Yu Yanyan.
Join the performance, Zhao Dezhong, Li Jucheng. Zhang Jingbin, Sang Yu.
Japanese magician A Xie Yi.
Japanese magician B, Sun Shengwen.
Chinese Taoist A Monkey Liang.
Let me introduce grapefruit, Yu Yanyan.
Join the performance, Zhao Dezhong, Li Jucheng. Zhang Jingbin, Sang Yu.
Japanese magician A Xie Yi.
Japanese sorcerer B, Sun Shengwen.
Chinese Taoist A Monkey Liang.
Join the performance, Zhao Dezhong, Li Kangcheng. Zhang Jingbin, Sang Yu.
Japanese magician A Xie Yi.
Japanese sorcerer B, Sun Shengwen.
Chinese Taoist A Monkey Liang.
Join the show, Zhao Dezhong Lee and Zhang Jingbin.
A Japanese magician, Xie Yi.
Japanese sorcerer B, Sun Shengwen.
Chinese Taoist A Monkey Liang.
Join the performance, Zhao Dezhong, Li Kangcheng. Zhang Jingbin, Sang Yu.
Japanese magician A Xie Yi.
Japanese magician B Sun Shengwen
Chinese Taoist A Monkey Liang.
Join the show, Zhao Dezhong, Li Kangcheng. Zhang Jinbin.
Japanese magician B Sun Shengwen
Chinese Taoist A Monkey Liang.
Join the performance, Zhao Dezhong, Li Kangcheng. Zhang Jingbin, Sang Yu.
Join the performance, Zhao Dezhong, Lee, and Jang Jinbin.
Chinese Taoist A Monkey Liang.
CaSTING.
Join the performance, Zhao Dezhong, Lee Jungcheng. Jang Geubin, Sang Yu.
Join the show, Cho Deok-chong and Jang Sunbin.
Actor director Xu Xiaojia
CASTING.
Assistant Chen Kaixin, Chang Bo.
Assistant Zhao Shuai, Wang Rui.
Production crew
Assistant Zhao Shuai Wang Rui
Assistant Chen Kaixin Chang Bo
Chief Planner Yu Yan
Production crew
Chief Planner Yu Yanyan
Chief Producer Zheng Jianbo
Production crew
Chief Planner, Yu Yanyan.
Producer Xue Fei
Chief Producer Zheng Jianbo
Chief Planner, Yu Yanyan.
Production crew
Producer Xue Fei
co-producer, Sang Yu, Chang Haibin.
Producer Xue Fei.
Chief Producer Zheng Jianbo
Chief Planner, Yu Yanyan.
co-producer, Sang Yu, Chang Haibin.
Producer Xue Fei.
Chief Producer Zheng Jianbo
Chief Planner, Yu Yanyan.
co-producer, Sang Yu, Chang Haibin.
co-producer Sang Yu Chang Haibin
Production crew
co-producer, Sang Yu, Chang Haibin.
Producer Xue Fei.
Chief Producer Zheng Jianbo
co-producer, Sang Yu, Chang Haibin.
Production crew
Production director, Xue Fei.
Producer Xue Fei
co-producer, Sang Yu, Chang Haibin.
Producer Xue Fei.
Production crew
Production director, Xue Fei.
Producer Dong Feifei
co-producer, Sang Yu, Chang Haibin
Meng Shaoqiang
Mang Keliang.
Director of Production, Xue Fei.
Producer Dong Feifei
Meng Ke Liang.
Han Shihua.
Mang Ke Liang.
Producer Dong Feifei
Producer Director, Xue Fei.
Drama photo Yu.
Monk Liang, the venue director.
Producer Dong Feifei
Drama photo Yu.
[Monkey Liang]
Han Shihua.
Meng Shaogang
Photo Yu.
Han Shihua.
Monk-Leung.
Meng Shaogang.
DIRECTOR
[Photo Yu]
Han Shi-hwa.
Producer Yin Xiantao
DIRECTOR, directors.
Yin, He Ziqiang.
Director He Ziqiang
Joint director, Wei Ran.
Action director, Xie Yi.
Producer Yin Xiantao
DIRECTOR, directors.
Screenwriter, cabbage.
Director Wei Ran.
Joint director, Wei Ran.
On a snowy day,
Action director, Xie Yi.
Director He Ziqiang.
Producer Eun Hentao
Joint director?
Screenwriter, cabbage.
Joint director Wei Ran
The nine lights are peaceful.
[Joint Director Wei Ran]
On a snowy day,
Action director, Xie Yi.
The director, Wei Ran,
[Writer: Cabbage]
Planning Yang Haha
Good luck.
Camera Photographer Team.
Photographer Seol Kyung-hui
Team A photographer Tang Huailiang.
Camera Photographer Team.
Photographer Sheung Hwi
Planner Yang Haha.
Team B photographer Feng Yuepeng.
Photographer, Xue Jinghui.
Team A photographer Tang Huailiang.
Camera Photographer Team.
Aviation photographer Chang Haibin
Photographer, Xue Jinghui.
Team B photographer Feng Yuepeng.
Photographer Chang Haibin
Team A photographer Tang Huailiang.
Photographer, Xue Jinghui.
Good luck.
Team B photographer Feng Yuepeng.
Assistant Liu Kang.
Focus. Wish you satisfied.
Photographer, Xue Jinghui.
Team A photographer Tang Huailiang.
Photographer Chang Haibin
Assistant Liu Kang
Gu Xuefei.
Team B photographer Feng Yuepeng
Team A photographer, Tang Huailiang.
Good luck.
Focus. Wish you satisfied.
Photographer Chang Haibin
Team B photographer Feng Yuepeng
Gu Xuefei.
Assistant Liu Kang
Hope you're satisfied.
ECTRICS Lighting Team.
Assistant Liu Kang
Focus. Wish you satisfied.
Photographer Chang Haibin
Assistant Liu Kang
Good luck.
Gu Xuefei.
ECTRICS Lighting Team
GAFER lighter Shen Ruicheng
Gafer lighter Shen Ruicheng
The lighting team.
Zhu Xiangyu.
Gafer lighter, Shen Ruicheng.
Huang Xinhui.
Gafer lighter, Shen Ruseong.
The lighting team.
Gafer lighter, Shen Ruicheng.
Zhu Xiangyu.
Huang Xinhui.
Gaffer lighter, Shen Ruicheng.
Gafeer lighter, Shen Ruicheng.
Beast Boy Lighting assistant. Wang Xiuzhi.
Huang Xinhui.
Zhu Xiangyu.
Art instructor, Sun Tianyong.
Execute the art Yang Hongpeng.
Execute art, Yang Hongpeng.
Art instructor, Sun Tianyong.
Xie Zhishan.
Xie Zhishan, a prop for the show.
Art instructor, Sun Tianyong.
Execute art, Yang Hongpeng.
The main focus is Xie Zhishan.
We focus on Xie Zhishan.
Execute the art Yang Hongpeng.
Xie Zhishan.
The main focus is Xie Zhishan.
Art instructor, Sun Tianyong.
Execute art Yang Hongpeng.
Execute art, Yang Hongpeng.
Execute the art Yang Hongpeng.
Art instructor, Sun Tianyong.
Focus on Xie Zhishan.
Xie Zhishan.
The main focus is Xie Zhishan.
CoSTUME Costume Team.
Execute the art Yang Hongpeng.
The stylist, Yang Li.
CoSTUME Costume Team.
The main focus is Xie Zhishan.
Xie Zhishan.
Cosplay team.
The makeup artist, Zhu Mingcong.
Costume, Li Yichen.
Makeup Wang Jinyuan.
Costume designer Yang Li.
CoSTUME Costume Team.
Makeup assistant, Liu Jiahui.
Makeup artist Zhu Mingcong.
Dress Li Yichen.
Makeup, Wang Jinyuan.
Makeup Wang Jinyuan
Makeup assistant, Liu Jiahui.
Makeup artist Zhu Mingcong.
Costume, Li Yichen.
Costume designer Yang Li.
Costume main focus, Li Ya'nan.
Costume Li Yichen.
Costume, Li Yichen.
Makeup assistant, Liu Jiahui.
The makeup artist, Zhu Mingcong.
The makeup focus is Li Ya'nan.
Makeup artist Zhu Mingcong.
Costume main focus, Li Ya'nan.
Costume assistant, Gangnam.
Makeup, Wang Jinyuan.
Makeup assistant, Liu Jiahui.
Costume, Li Yichen.
Costume main focus, Li Ya'nan.
Costume assistant, Gangnam.
Makeup, Wang Jinyuan.
Makeup assistant, Liu Jiahui.
Makeup artist Zhu Mingcong.
Makeup assistant, Lau Ka-wai.
Makeup assistant, Liu Jiahui.
Costume main focus, Li Ya'nan.
Costume assistant, Jiangnan.
Makeup, Wang Jinyuan.
Costume assistant, Gangnam.
Costume main focus, Li Ya'nan.
Makeup assistant, Liu Jiahui.
STUNT Martial Arts Team.
Kung Fu instructor Guo Jinbiao
Kung Fu instructor Kwok
STUNT Martial Arts Team.
Kung Fu instructor Guo Jinbiao
Editor team.
Edit editing team.
Martial arts instructor Guo Jinbiao.
Editor Zhang Shiqi, Wei Ran.
Editor Zhang Shiqi, Wei Ran
Edit editing team.
Editing assistant Sun Shengwen
Editor Zhang Shiqi, Wei Ran.
Martial arts instructor Guo Jinbiao.
Kung Fu instructor Guo Jinbiao.
editor Zhang Shiqi, Wei Ran.
Edit editing team.
Editing assistant Sun Shengwen
Editor Zhang Shiqi.
The editor, Zhang Shiqi, Wei Ran.
Editing assistant Sun Shengwen
Color Mix.
Teddy Kuma.
Color Mixing.
Chamber Lai.
Color Missing.
Personality assistant Zhou Yangyang.
Personor Lai.
Teddy Kuma.
Personality assistant Zhou Yang.
Color Mixing.
Sound Production.
Personal Assistant Zhou Yangyang
Beijing Vocal Walk Culture Co., Ltd.
Sound Production.
Personal Assistant Zhou Yang Yang
Production director Tao Zhe
Beijing Vocal Walk Culture Co., Ltd.
Production Director, Tao Zhe.
Sound Producer
Production Director Tao
of Beijing Voice Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing Vocal Walk Culture Co., Ltd.
Effective fat fish.
The line editor, kiki Liu.
Producer Director Tao Zhe
Sound Production
Effective Fat Fish
Foley is over.
Beijing Vocal Walk Culture Co., Ltd.
Effective Fat Fish.
Producer Director Tao Zhe
Line editor, kiki Liu.
Effective. Fat fish.
ADR recording Guan Xiao and kiki Liu.
DR Fat Fish.
Beijing Vocal Walk Culture Co., Ltd.
Foley, after all.
Producer Director Tao Zhe
[Line editor, kiki Liu]
Effective. Fat fish.
ADR recording Guan Xiao and kiki Liu.
The line editor, kiki Liu.
Mix. Fat fish.
Production Director Tao Zhe
Foley is complete.
Foley is over.
ADR recording Guan Xiao and kiki Liu.
Voice director Yi Ruoxun Miao Taegyeong
The lines editor kiki Liu
Mixed recording. Fat.
Mix, Fat Yu.
The dubbing director, Meow Taegyeong.
ADR recording Guan Xiao and kiki Liu.
Effective. Fat fish.
Foley is over.
"Mixed Fat Fish".
[Voice director, Yi Ruohun, Meow Taegyeong]
ADR recording Guan Xiao and kiki Liu.
Dubbing Match Meow Taegyeong
Foley.
Mixed fat fish.
Voice director Yi Ruoxun Miaow Taegyeong
[Voice director]
A dubber?
Mix, Fat Fish.
Dubbing Match Meow Taegyeong
Lin Chen, Gong Hanchen.
Mixed filming Fat Fish.
Dubbing Matchmaker Miao Taijiu
The dubbing director, Meow Taegyeong.
Voice director Yeo-hoon Miao Taegyeong
A dubber?
Xu Peiyu, Ou Wenjing.
A dubber.
Lin Chen, Gong Hanchen.
[Dubbing Match Meow Taegyeong]
Voice director, Yi Ruoxun, Meow Taegyeong.
The dubbing team, Miao Taijiu.
Magnoli, Tuchuan.
Lin Chen Gong, Han Chen.
Xiang Yunjian, Sun Jiuo.
Xu Peiyu, Ou Wenjing.
Dubber.
Zhang Guihao, Cao Xiahao.
[Green Admiral, Tuchuan]
Zhang Guihao Cao Xiahao
Xu Peiyu, Ou Wenjing.
Lan Zhenling, Tuchuan.
Qian Yigua, Afu.
Xiang Yunjian, Sun Jiuo.
Lin Chen, Gong Hanchen.
Zhang Guihao Cao Xiahao
Bai Qi, Guo Peng Bo.
Lan Zhenling, Tuchuan.
Qian Yigua, Afu.
Zhang Guihao, Cao Xiahao,
Bai Qi, Guo Peng Bo.
Qian Yigua, Afu.
Xiang Yunjian, Sun Jiuo.
Other dubbing actors, Xue Ying, Tau,
Liu Haoyu.
Other dubbers, Xue Yingchen,
Other dubbers, Xue Ying, Shaanxi,
Zhang Guihao, Cao Xiahao,
Bai Qi, Guo Peng Bo.
Qian Yigua, Afu.
Meow Taegyeong.
Other dubbers, Xue Yingchen,
Liu Haoyu.
Meow Taijiu.
Bai Qi, Guo Peng Bo.
Other dubbers, Xue Yingchen,
Liu Haoyu.
Meow Taijiu.
Bai Qi, Guo Peng Bo.
Other dubbers, Xue Ying, Shaanxiu,
Liu Haoyu.
Meow Taijiu.
Meow Taegyeong.
Spiel Efforts. Special effects production.
Other dubbing actors, Xue Ying, Tau,
Liu Haoyu.
Meow Taegyeong.
Spiel Effacts. Special effects production.
Zhang Liang, a synthetic.
Specil Effacts. Special effects production.
Visual Director, Zhang Haitsui.
Visual Director Zhang Haitsui.
Visual Director Zhang Haitsui
Yu Peng Chao.
Visual Director Zhang Haitsui.
Zhang Liang, a synthetic.
Jiahao.
Yu Peng Chao.
Zhang Liang, a synthetic.
Jiahao.
Spiel EFESTS. Special effects production.
Langyin.
Video Director Zhang Haitsui.
Mu Jiaxin.
Visual Director Zhang Haitsui.
Yu Peng Chao.
Jiahao.
Zhang Liang, a synthetic.
Visual Director Zhang Haitsui.
Feng Chenhao.
Mu Jiaxin.
Visual Director Zhang Haitsui.
Yu Peng Chao.
Jiahao.
[Combination Master Zhang Liang]
Zhang Liang, a composer.
Feng Chenhao.
Mu Jiaxin.
Jiahao.
Poster exclusive announcement.
Yu Peng Chao.
Feng Chenhao.
Poster exclusive announcement.
Mu Jiaxin.
Global First Line (Beijing) Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
Poster exclusive announcement.
Marketing Director He Junhong
Marketing Planner, Yang Xiao Ning.
Marketing Planning Yang Xiao Ning
Media Director He Junhong
Poster, exclusive announcement.
Global First Line (Beijing) Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
Marketing Director He Junhong
Marketing Planner, Yang Xiao Ning.
Marketing Planning Yang Xiaoning
Marketing Director He Junhong
Global First Line (Beijing) Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
Poster, exclusive announcement.
Media executes Ji Min Dong Lan.
He Junhong, Director of Media.
Global First Line (Beijing) Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
Marketing Planning Yang Xiaoning
Media execution, Ji-min, Dong-ran.
Visual Design, Jung Gun-taek.
Marketing Planner, Yang Xiao Ning.
Marketing Director He Junhong
Media Director He Junhong
Media execution, Ji-min, Dong-ran.
Visual Design, Zheng Qinze.
Marketing Director He Junhong
Marketing Planning Yang Xiaoning
Tian Yan, new media editor.
Marketing Planner Yang Xiaoning.
Marketing Planning Yang Xiaoning
Marketing Director He Junhong
Media Director He Junhong
Visual Design, Zheng Qinze.
Executive assistant, Chu Jinbi.
Media Executive, Ji Min, Dong Lan.
Tian Yan, new media editor.
Marketing Planning Yang Xiaoning
Executive assistant, Gin Bi Zhu.
Tian Yan, new media editor.
Media executive Ji-min Dong-ran.
Visual Design, Jung Gun-taek.
Media execution, Ji-min, Dong-ran.
Media Director He Junhong
Tian Yan, new media editing.
Music.
Introduction assistant, Gin Bi Zhu.
Long Song.
Lyrics/composer Wen Peng
Music.
Long Song.
Lyrics/composer Wen Peng
Arrangement.
Arranger: Zhou Yu.
Long Song.
Lyrics/composer Wen Peng
Singing Wen Peng
Arranger: Zhou Yu.
Ming Xie.
Arranger Zhou Yu
Lyrics/composer Wen Peng
Singing Wen Peng
Arranger: Zhou Yu.
Han Shihua, Xu Qingfeng, Zhang Xiaomin.
Ming Xie.
Singing Wen Peng
Arranger: Zhou Yu.
Han Shihua, Xu Qingfeng, Zhang Xiaomin.
Han Shi-hwa, Seo Kyung-feng, Jang Xiao-min.
Singing Wen Peng
Thank you.
[Photographer]
Han Shi-hwa, Seo Kyung-feng, Jang Xiao-min.
Ming Xie.
radiation film and cultural media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
Han Shihua, Xu Qingfeng, Zhang Xiaomin.
Han Shi-hwa, Seo Kyung-feng, Jang Xiao-min.
Photographer company.
radiation film and cultural media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
A product company.
Photographer company.
radiation film and cultural media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
Product company.
Photographer company.
Wenguang Hostel, Guangfeng District, ShangRao City.
The PR Department of Guangfeng District Committee of Shangcao City
Product Company.
radiation film and cultural media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
ShangRao City, Nongwen Brigade Group,
ShangRao Junjun International Film and television Industrial Development Co., Ltd.
radiation, television and cultural media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
Shangshao City Guangfeng District, Wenguang Hostel.
The PR Department of Guangfeng District Committee of Shangcao City
Global First Line (Beijing) Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
ShangRao Junjun International Film and television Industrial Development Co., Ltd.
radiation, television and cultural media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
ShangRao City, Nongwen Brigade Group,
Global First Line (Beijing) Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
radiation, television and cultural media (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
ShanRao Jiaojun International Film and Development Co., Ltd.
Global First Line (Beijing) film and cultural Co., Ltd.