Hey, be careful
Pull it up!
cut
Damn it!
oops
Who do they think they are?
You order me around so casually?
Do they know who I am? Damn it
When the boss made his first deal
The other party will definitely be very vigilant
Are they the only ones who are wary?
- We also have to stay vigilant
-knew
Hide some knives.
Big Brother
Hey, take another knife.
-knife?
-Um
Brother, they asked you to go over now.
Hey, did you see what those guys look like?
I didn't see their faces
Didn't see the face?
Yeah, I can't see it.
Damn, could it be a ghost?
damn it
-Hide the knife
-yes
-How many knives did you bring? Two?
- I just brought one
-Brother, this way.
-Um
What the fuck?
I really can't see anything.
What's that bag over there, bro?
Oh shit
Fuck it
What's this?
Is it US dollars? What is this for?
Hey, I heard
Are you looking for other distribution channels besides us?
Why do the same job twice?
What a hassle!
Leave it to us.
We can do it all cleanly and neatly
Hey, take this.
ah!
So what exactly are you distributing?
"Beyond the Gun"
(Probation officer bastard)
It's fucking endless. Really.
What happened again?
I am the supervisor
Where are you now?
I'm calling you to confirm your location.
Stop it, you bastard, are you looking for death?
Hey, please don't swear.
I just want to make sure you're coming home.
There are 20 minutes left until curfew.
I'm on my way home!
I'll be home soon!
I'm hanging you bastard!
Damn asshole fucking asshole
You stinky bastard are really looking for death
-it hurts
-Who are you?
Hey, I told you it hurts.
Driver, have you ever driven this person before?
This person just got off the car
senior!
This is Quan Yuancheng's electronic anklet and mobile phone.
If it's the police
You should say "I am a police officer" before entering.
How can police officers run around with hammers?
Aren't there things like stun guns?
What is your relationship with Quan Yuancheng?
Jeon Won-sung? I don't know this person.
You went to a stranger's house to look for a package?
Oh, I really don't know
I received a courier box a few days ago.
It's loaded with bullets.
And it is divided into categories
Only bullets?
What about the gun?
What gun?
There are only bullets in the delivery box
So you're here looking for a gun?
You're not a policeman.
Why do you always hold a hammer?
Tell me the truth quickly
I'm telling the truth.
There are only bullets in the delivery box
There is also a contact book
Address book?
Um, name, address, phone number
A fully organized address book
I was curious too, so I came here to look for it.
But when I got here, I was scared.
So just wander around
Then I saw the people who lived here suddenly ran out
Is this the person?
That's right, it's this person.
He was in such a hurry to go out that he left without even closing the door.
I took this opportunity to come in and look at the box.
It's all empty inside
Then
You just come in
It's me
Did you find Quan Yuan?
No, that guy seems to be deliberately deceiving us.
I left my phone in a taxi.
What about the gun?
No guns in the car?
No guns
We'll find this guy as soon as possible.
- Be careful and stay connected
-Um
Hey, thank you for your hard work.
I am Patrolman Li Dao from Daoming Police Station.
Please confirm
The surveillance camera in the alley at No. 45-2, Zhengri Road
We received a report that Jeon Won-sung is out.
Please confirm
"Please confirm."
Yes, I will contact you as soon as possible after confirmation.
Okay, please.
Is it Jeon Won-sung?
Does he have a gun?
I
Will help you
Don't move
one
Wait and don't move
two
three!
Hello, Patrolman Lee Dao
I checked Jeon Won-sung's whereabouts
He seems to be on the move
On the move?
Please continue to track his whereabouts.
Hey you bastard!
Caught
But who is this person? He doesn't live there.
（Surveillance video control room）
Did you find him?
-Yes
-Where is the exact location?
25 minutes ago
In front of Shuanglong Hotel, 3 km ahead
Found the whereabouts of Jeon Won-sung
Can you leave right away?
Yeah but
I can't rush over right now.
Hello, Patrolman Zhang?
I am under the surveillance camera at No. 45-5 Road, Xiping District
Arrested the man who broke into Quan Yuancheng's house
Please send someone out immediately
-Yes, we will go out immediately
-good
Where to go now?
-Hello, Chief
-Um
I'm leaving. Please tell me his moving route.
From now on we will track backwards
Quan Yuancheng's movement traces in the first 28 minutes
All team members
Please follow the moving route of Quan Yuancheng to track his location
-knew
-Wow, so nervous.
ten
Nine, eight
seven
how?
Oh, this? This is what I just said.
A bunch of different types of bullets
We're all ready here.
Patrolman Li Dao, are you ready?
I'm ready.
Yes, please tell me.
From now on, I will tell you the movement route of Jeon Won-sung
Tell you exactly as it is
Be careful
200 meters ahead, turn right in front of Shuanglong Hotel
Let’s go!
(Shuanglong Hotel)
I saw Jeon Won-sung on Park Road
Cast on the big screen
He turned right at 4 o'clock on Parkway 409th Street
Go straight for 30 meters from your current location...
- Turn right after 10 meters
-Turn right!
Continue straight
I found where Jeon Won-sung was 21 minutes ago
Next turn right at the Laundromat
(laundry)
16 minutes ago, Quan Yuancheng entered the blind spot of the surveillance camera
This road leads to the lake crossing
Check the roads adjacent to the lake intersection
You can find it immediately
Check it out now
Found it!
He walked into the underground passage from the lake crossroads
Underground passage?
Vehicles cannot enter there.
I need to find a detour. Please wait.
There's no time. Please hurry up.
Let's go first
Turn right!
Please confirm his appearance and clothing.
The color of the clothes or some other feature
He is wearing an orange hoodie and windbreaker
Yes he is wearing an orange hoodie and windbreaker
And overalls
Yes, that's right.
Oh, that's right.
He also had a fishing bag or something like that on his back.
Is the director still carrying a fishing bag?
Carrying a similar bag
There must be a gun in there.
What? A gun?
17 minutes ago
Jeon Won-sung walks through the underground passage and turns right
I rely on
But can we do it?
"us"?
Yes, we are a team now.
Stop kidding, focus.
Is this a fucking blank?
Are you kidding me?
He entered the modern market.
Keep going forward
Then turn right along the fruit shop towards the Modern Market
Turn right over there
14 minutes ago he appeared at the convenience store door
Saw him at the pharmacy 13 minutes ago
Wait a moment
This is an area with no surveillance video.
We need to check the surrounding surveillance before telling you.
There are three roads intersecting here
Please check the directions of Dongil-dong No. 34, No. 46 and No. 41
knew
I found Quan Yuancheng
Do you see the drugstore?
pharmacy?
Yes 12 minutes ago
He turned right in front of the Green Cross Pharmacy
Turn right!
No. 92, Park Seok-ro, turn left ten minutes ago
(Park Seok-ro)
No. 87, Puxi Road, turned right eight minutes ago
No. 76, Jincheng Road, turned right six minutes ago
Park Seok-ro? Geumseong-ro? Why is it so complicated?
Over there, No. 76 Jincheng Road
(Puksuk-ro, Jincheng-ro)
No. 96, Jincheng Road, turn right five minutes ago
No, he turned left.
No. 96, Jincheng Road
Reverse!
Enter Jincheng Road and go straight ahead for 500 meters
(Jincheng Road)
Turn right now
Go straight ahead for 800 meters
But where is Jeon Won-sung going with the gun?
What about you? What are you going to do with the gun?
Stop doubting me. I'm still driving for you.
After catching Quan Yuancheng, you will be the next one
"After we catch Quan Yuancheng, you will be the next one"
(aunt)
Your aunt called.
Director, someone is calling me, please wait a moment
OK
Hello Aunt
I have an emergency now
Can I call you later?
Oh ok
Ok sorry to bother you
OK, I'll call you later.
I'm back
There is a three-way intersection at the end of the road ahead.
Turn left there
There will be a downhill slope after 200 meters
The whole process is to walk from there to the city center.
city center?
Ah, let’s go!
Don't worry, I will take you to find Jeon Won-sung.
-How are you?
- Let's go
Confirmed 4 minutes ago
Confirmed three minutes ago
Confirmed 2 minutes ago
Keep going down
Confirmed 1 minute ago
He was heading towards the square.
Confirmed 10 seconds ago
Live video playback on the big screen
There are too many people here.
Please stay within 100 meters of the square exit
Tracking each surveillance video
I started tracking from the entrance of the square
OK
The 30-meter west side of the square did not capture Quan Yuancheng
Excuse me, is there any other clue?
Viewing
Surveillance video of the square exit
Nor did they capture Quan Yuancheng.
The surveillance video 50 meters to the north did not capture him either.
The surveillance video on the south side did not capture him either.
Wait a moment
This is a bit weird
How could he disappear from the surveillance screen?
Even if we missed it
If you want to go to the square
He must be heading in the direction of the monitor.
We should see more clearly.
(Gyeonginse Police Station)
If you ignore my human rights
This has been suppressing me.
I won't give up.
Is it possible that he went to the police station?
Police station?
I found it
Where?
His last location before he disappeared two minutes ago
Yes, he is on his way to the police station.
Gone?
(Gyeonginse Police Station)
There's more to guns than just these
Hello, Patrolman Lee
Jeon Won-sung seems to be carrying a gun
Went to the police station
What?
I'm on my way to the police station too.
Strengthen security from the entrance
See you in the parking lot
OK, I'll go to the parking lot now.
(Police Human Rights Action Plan)
(Ministry of Women and Youth Affairs)
This guy seems to be here for revenge.
-revenge?
- I caught him.
How many people in the bureau have access to weapons?
Most people are out.
Now there are only a few office staff
Ah, that Jeon Won-sung is driving me crazy
That is to say
Want to ruin my career?
Haven't you received any news from the Criminal Police Team yet?
If they caught them, they would have called me.
Hello
Um?
Squad leader, give me a pair of handcuffs first
-Why handcuffs?
- I'll tell you later
Hey, what are you doing?
ah!
What about me
I have something to ask you.
- Damn it hurts
-Stay here quietly.
What's going on?
Hey, let me go! I want to go too.
I want to go with you too
What's wrong?
“I am the supervisor
Where are you now?"
Tell me
I am the supervisor.
You...where are you now?
What's that sound?
It's this sweet voice
Is that you?
How does it feel? You bastard!
Do you understand my suffocating feeling?
Please
Please forgive me.
When you oppress other people's lives
That's the kind of awareness we should have.
I just want to get the job done.
You know it too
that
That's my job.
So why do you work so hard?
Creating trouble?
-ah?
-I...I
I…
I have a five-year-old daughter.
and a son
So please
Please forgive me just this once.
Do you have children?
What does this have to do with me?
Hello!
Oh shit
All the people I wanted to find found me.
Jeon Won-sung calm down and put down your gun
Hey, Quan Yuancheng, stop it!
The more you do this, the more serious the problem will be, kid.
Put the gun down
You idiots
The problem is already serious
Isn’t it?
Are you two okay?
Turn off the lights first
-Squad leader, are you okay?
-Well, what about you?
Um
Li Dao, what should we do?
This gun alone isn't enough, right?
Monitor, you know
Where are the guns we found in the examination hall?
In the evidence storage room
But didn't you say those guns couldn't be used?
There are no bullets.
I have bullets
-What is the password?
-0920
Oh shit!
I'm going to get his attention.
You brought these police officers
Run to a safe place
So these guys aren't that great.
How dare you be so arrogant?
Hello
Do you think you can avoid death this way?
Um?
damn it
Fuck it
Oh shit
You fucking bastard!
Damn bastard
Fuck it!
come out
Run!
Squad leader!
He's bleeding a lot and we need to stop the bleeding first
What are you doing?
Hello here!
Can you please let me go soon?
I just drove for you.
Let me go quickly
Okay? Damn it.
Hey, I told you to let me go!
- Give me the gauze first
-Good for you
- And a bandage.
-good
I'll cover you.
You shoot whenever you get the chance.
Yes, I understand.
(Evidence Storage Room)
It feels disturbing.
What happened over there?
(Reporter)
(Inspector Seo Hyung-joo of Gyeonginse Police Station)
Hello
Monitor, are you okay?
We'll be there soon
Don't come up straight after you arrive.
Act with the support team
Got it?
Don't come up by yourself.
What are you talking about?
Wait for me
Please answer
Due to the storm, we cannot identify the enemy and our own troops.
All members are isolated and must retreat!
- Please wait a moment
-Save me
Li Dao's retreat is the top priority
This is an order to retreat quickly!
No, there are still survivors at the scene.
Leave a message
We will be wiped out, retreat quickly!
Hey I'm so fucking scared of you people
There has to be a limit to pretentiousness.
Especially your subordinates
That stupid big guy
That bastard
He turned off the surveillance and beat me up.
As a result, that bastard
See me holding a gun
Like a dog, he ran away trembling.
Look at you, you little bastard.
how?
Can't you escape after being shot?
Yes, that's right
You are right
I no longer have the strength to resist you
So what?
but
I will never beg a bastard like you
Spare my life
Wow
Are you still trying to be brave until the end?
Feed me
I have a question
you…
How many children do you have?
You little bastard
What the fuck...
What are you doing?
Why don't you bastards come out?
Where the fuck are you hiding?
Come out here you bastards!
Which asshole fired that shot?
Come out you bastards!
Oh shit
Come out here, asshole!
come out!
damn it
You bastard
How dare you, a bastard, play tricks on me?
Then give it a try, you bastard!
Are you the cop from before?
Are you scared?
Come out you bastard!
Why the hell is it always against me?
Jeon Won-sung, put down your gun
Fuck you
One last warning, put down your gun.
OK, I know. I know.
Here
The gun is here
Monitor, are you okay?
Yes, squad leader, it's ok.
I don't want to hold a gun anymore.
If you have a gun...
Put down the gun!
To save someone's life
I'll end up killing someone else.
Please put down your gun.
Subtitle translation: Guo Jing