(This episode contains scenes of school violence)
(This may cause discomfort to some viewers)
Is this the person?
Could you please confirm the other address?
Okay, tell me.
13-1 Xizhong Road, 319-2 Cangdong Road
417-1 Shanggu Road
27 Dayuan 3rd Road, 21 Meiting Road
Hmm?
The address you mentioned has this person
I checked it.
The address you gave me has this person in it
Oh, I see.
Oh, really.
You should be happy to see someone.
"Beyond the Gun"
Is everyone okay?
Are you all okay?
No one was hurt, right?
-Yes
Looks like everyone is okay.
So lucky. Please take the kids out with you.
yes
Hey, wait a minute.
Hey, Kuijin, I'm sorry.
sorry
Sorry, Kuijin
Wait a moment
Although I don't know
What have you been through?
But what you have to do now
It will only hurt you in the end
Don't pretend to understand me
It's too late now
It's not too late
If you could tell me about this time
What have you been through?
I should be able to help you
I just want to hear your story
real
But first
You have to put that gun down.
We can talk
You can, right?
That guy
What a jerk.
You have endured for so long
It's really amazing. Kuizhen, you did a great job.
It's amazing that you've endured this long.
here you go
I told you my kid is in there!
I'll explain it later.
Chengjun!
-Oops, what happened?
-Sungjun!
Chengjun, wake up!
-It's mom, look at me.
- It's Daddy, Daddy
What is going on?
Chengjun, cheer up!
Don’t you recognize your parents?
Sung Joon is the dad
Auntie, please don't push me. I'm in danger now.
Kui Town!
Excuse me
I am his mother...I am his mother
Kuizhen, let me go
- You can't go in.
- I said I'm his mother
What happened to Kuizhen? Why are you standing there?
Kuizhen, you didn't do anything wrong. Say you didn't do anything wrong.
Hurry up and say you don't have Kuizhen
No, Kuizhen, what should I do!
Kuizhen, why did you get in the police car?
Kuizhen: No, don’t go up!
Kui Town!
Detective Xu
Well, tell me.
The arrest is ready.
All personnel are in place. Do we need to launch a surprise attack?
Wait a moment at your respective locations
Don't worry
I will take you to find Quan Yuancheng
Wait and don't move
Caught
There was only a piece of paper and some bullets inside
Where is that address book now?
I threw it away
Those who got the gun
For those people
Guns may be the real justice and a force
There's a high school student here.
Don't you want to go and have a look?
Children nowadays have to hand in their cell phones to school
(Detective Seo of Gyeonginse Police Station)
(Wen Bai was arrested after the incident)
Brother, are you ready to catch me now?
Go grab him now.
knew
Group Two Move!
What?
Where did he go?
Hey where did that guy go?
-Did no one see him?
- I haven't seen it.
- Block the front and side doors first
-Okay, got it, let's go.
Control all entrances and exits
You three come here!
senior
Dongyue Industry just sent
Wenbai's identity investigation data
He is not the same person as the Wen Bai we know
(Dongjin Apartment)
（Subscriber address directory）
(Li Dao)
The so-called Republic of Korea
The title of "gun-free country" has become tarnished
Citizens are concerned about the ongoing terrorist incidents.
Feeling increasingly uneasy...
Unfortunately
Following the recent
After the shooting incident
This time even in high school…
A convenience store in Gyeonggi Province this morning
An armed robbery occurred
The incident happened around 2 a.m.
A convenience store...
The sources of the guns currently in circulation
And the forces behind it are talking about it...
Continuous shooting incidents
As a result, citizens have been asking the government for relevant countermeasures...
Where did the guns come from?
Did you find the source of the gun?
Is it really related to a criminal organization?
-What are the measures to deal with shooting incidents?
-Director
How many more shootings do you think will happen?
Are there any guns out there?
People are worried
Are there more guns?
Or do you not know about this either?
Please do not speculate or make assumptions
Please trust the police and wait patiently
Oh, here he comes.
-Ouch!
-Hello
I got a call from the police today.
Although we are not law-abiding people
But if you want to make a living in Korea
There is one thing you absolutely cannot touch.
That's the gun
Isn’t this better?
What era is it now?
How long can you survive with a knife?
Now is the era of globalization
Violence, fraud, drugs and even murder
Can be settled in court
But not guns
Because the military will intervene
That's right
The moment I picked up the gun
We will be beaten to death like dogs
Damn, if I take a wrong step
I'm going to go all in on my own.
What about the guns in the warehouse?
Hello
Call the "Fake Officer"
yes
Is this reasonable?
There are so many people at the scene
You actually let that guy get away?
Are you all blind?
Find that guy immediately, no matter what method you use.
Let him sit in front of me
No matter how many
All the guns in the address book must be confiscated.
If there is another shooting incident,
Did you know that both you and I will be fired?
- It's the Director.
Li Dao
You will resume your job from today.
I will take all the responsibilities and join the investigation team.
(Call from Kong Shihao)
Fuck
Damn, I'm really anxious.
Give
This is a real gun
Don't come over here, I'm going to shoot you.
real
Fuck, don't shoot.
Where did this gun come from?
ah
That meth dealer, President Kim
He said he would sell me his nightclub at a low price
So I bought it.
Then I found these in the basement warehouse.
Where is that guy called President Jin now?
I have no idea
When you find these
I even wondered if he was deliberately framing me?
I want to catch him and kill him myself
I couldn't find him at all.
Oh wait a minute
You expect me to believe you?
Ouch, wait a minute.
Hey, look at this.
Check this out
Oh fuck
There is a guy named Gu Zhengwan
Work under me and run errands for me
The guy that Patrolman Li is looking for
It was Gu Zhengwan's subordinate.
I don't know how he knew.
But he's been to the warehouse of the nightclub
And wandering around in front of a warehouse with guns
What are they doing?
He must be looking for a gun.
Do you understand?
Why would you confess all this to me?
There are guns in my business!
The gun is pointed at my head
How could I just sit there and do nothing?
I will help you 100%
So Patrolman Lee
Please don't involve me in such a complicated matter.
I have nothing to do with these guns.
I'm just an innocent citizen.
Okay?
I said, didn’t you take them all away last time?
We? You mean the police?
They all showed their police IDs.
I handed it all over, why are you still bothering me?
-Hello
-Um
Is there anyone else coming here besides us?
No, we are responsible here.
I don't care. You guys can do whatever you want.
We've never been here before.
-Didn't you give it to me?
- So...
- I already gave it to you.
-Wait
Damn, I'm really going crazy
You have already taken it, what else do you want me to take?
Now this is no joke
If you lie, it will be really bad.
Give us the guns now.
I'm going crazy, damn it.
Forget it, just go.
No sir, you didn't give us a minute to wait.
Sir, wait a moment. Hello, sir!
How many guns were found?
About half of the contacts in the address book have been confiscated.
Only half?
What if a madman starts shooting randomly tomorrow?
sorry
I will mobilize all manpower to find these guns as soon as possible.
What about the guys who stole guns by claiming to be cops?
We are also doing our best...
From now on
The Joint Investigation Headquarters is in charge of this case.
Pass all the investigation materials to them.
Stop caring about it.
Director
(Joint Investigation Headquarters)
The Ministry of Health and Welfare has designated a regional designated hospital
A guide to dealing with gun patients was issued
In response to this, the medical community, centered around local hospitals…
I've heard that eating food made with flour will make your stomach uncomfortable.
I bought some bread again.
Thanks
Are you so stupid that you can't understand what people say?
Graduated from a second-rate university and worked in a university hospital
At least you have to be good at something.
Isn’t it?
yes
How many times do I have to tell her before she understands?
Is he trying to show off that he graduated from a reputable university?
Head Nurse
I'll order your favorite mango shaved ice later.
You have a good eye.
But the head nurse
I'm signing up for a private trainer starting next week.
Can you please not assign me to work the night shift for the time being?
You didn't work much night shift last month, did you?
Head nurse, please
Really
Got it, I'll adjust your working hours
Anyway, there are people working night shifts.
Oh, thank you, head nurse.
I'll order shaved ice now.
I heard that many people now shop in overseas online shopping malls.
Spending sprees on counterfeit guns or accessories
We should also start a public discussion
Is it allowed to use guns?
What are you talking about?
South Korea is a country with the highest security.
How can we openly discuss whether to allow the use of firearms?
So this is a hidden problem.
We have to legislate, institutionalize, and systematize
Let this question...
What to do now
Can't draw conclusions right now
In view of the current
Several unprecedented gun-related shootings
If any of you in the audience
Someone has a gun
Please report the case to the nearest police station as soon as possible.
(Fentanyl)
I heard that Kong Shihao is assisting the police in their investigation.
The guns that had been delivered by courier began to move
It has also been confirmed in other regions
Situations where guns are used
What is Gu Zhengwan doing?
He seems to have only got half of the gun so far.
Only half?
The incident has become so serious
Shouldn't something happen now?
We sent it so they could shoot.
Whether it's fighting each other for guns or fighting the police
We have to do something, right?
Do you like it?
This isn't a toy.
This is not a toy, don't play with it, you bastard
Didn't you serve in the army?
Are you fucking crazy?
Wait isn't it?
Oh my god, so handsome.
Ah, I'll say it again. My mouth hurts from saying it.
Why are you so suspicious?
We are the best money launderers in this area. Yes.
In stock? Ouch!
Don’t you know that “spot equals cash”?
No matter how dirty the money is, we can wash it
I'll wash it for you, don't worry.
Can you just send it directly?
Ouch
Bro, isn't that a cigar?
Oh, this is the gift I received.
It is said that cigars are a symbol of gentlemanliness and fashion.
What's it like in Cuba?
-Is it suitable for me?
-Yeah, it's cool.
Come take a sip, huh?
Hey you bumpkin
Who smokes a cigar like this?
For You
It's time for us to get rid of the rusticity.
Speaking of this
I have an important matter to deal with this time.
Try your best again.
Big things mean...
I plan to take over all of President Kim's business locations.
Um?
President Kim?
Yes, it's the President Kim that you and I both know.
I have to sort it out this time.
Hello, President Jin, from across the ocean
Got some new stuff to sell.
It is said to be a "money tree".
But President Kim's place seems too big.
This is the command given to me above.
The two of us just need to deal with President Kim.
Our Gu Zhengwan is an expert in handling this kind of thing.
Um, brother.
After this event
Can you give it to me and my brothers?
A separate business location?
well
Your words are really sad.
If this succeeds
Do you think I'll just give you a place?
Should we do it or not?
Yes I can
That's right!
We are
You are the only one I can trust.
Hey give me
Brother, why do you think so much?
Anyway, we have guns, so we can just wipe them out.
Did you know?
Lions also wait for their chance to catch rabbits.
It's not because of lack of strength but to avoid mistakes
Wait until the time comes
I want to solve them all at once
How many times do I have to tell you?
Gu Zhengwan is the only one
Someone who knows where President Kim is
-are you sure?
- Of course what the fuck...
If you don't believe me
Then go ask Gu Jung-man yourself.
Are all these in President Jin’s hands?
Yes
So far
Are the guns used in the case all circulated by President Kim?
-Disguised as a courier?
-Yes, that's right.
Where is that bastard President Kim?
The current location of President Kim cannot be confirmed
If we can use Koo Jung-man and Minister Kong
Find the missing President Kim
We can find out the real forces that are spreading guns
Very good, quickly formulate a battle plan
Share the investigation status with the Joint Investigation Headquarters
Yes I know
Please sign it
Hello
I clearly told you to stop interfering
Director
Guns continue to spread
There are gunshots everywhere in Seoul
Today alone, three incidents occurred.
Our job is to find those guns as quickly as possible.
Stop this from happening.
(Name in Chinese and English in the identity investigation report)
This is also the person who spread the guns in the hands of Patrolman Li Dao.
Director, please focus on finding this guy.
at the same time
We'll definitely try to find more guns.
This guy's tail
He will definitely be caught.
Headquarters Notice
We have clues
Suspects were found impersonating police officers to obtain guns
Start Today
All police officers are on emergency alert
Please collect all the guns in the address book as soon as possible
Repeat again
We have clues
A suspect was found posing as a police officer...
(My daughter)
Your call was not answered
Please call again later
(Real estate, sales, leasing)
dad
Could you please help me?
Huh? What's wrong?
Can’t I get Dad’s pension in advance?
Are you crazy, girl?
-Why do you do such an abnormal thing...
-Can't you help me?
President!
Then go to the police station and report the case.
-President
-What?
Please help me
Without that money I would be dead.
President, I beg you, please.
Let go of me
That money is the result of my father's hard work all his life.
-Accumulated pension
- I told you to sue me.
President, please help me just this once.
Minister Kong is here
Why the hell is he here?
-Take it away!
-Hide it now, fuck!
Oh shit!
Hey, hurry up.
It's over, damn.
hurry up
Hello
We are Gu Zhengwan
Hello, Brother
What's going on? What's the atmosphere?
What are you doing?
Why are you out of breath?
Um?
We were just cleaning the room.
Hey, this building is already so rotten
Just live wherever you want
Is this the first time your brothers are seeing me?
Hello, Brother
Oh, okay.
Sit down, bro.
I saw a famous bakery on the way here
Oh ok
Thanks
Didn't you ask me before
Do you know the names of your brothers?
Um?
I've always been concerned about this matter.
I guess there are about 20 people.
So buying this much should be enough, right?
Yes, that's enough.
Hey, let me share it with you.
Just ten thousand
can we talk?
Can you please step aside for a moment?
We will enjoy it
Oh, you're welcome.
Just ten thousand
yes
I miss President Kim a lot lately.
How is he?
It should still be buried underground, right?
Why are you suddenly mentioning President Kim?
Isn't it very clear to me, brother?
yes
I do know
Ding ding
This is President Kim's cell phone.
These idiots just took the phone without asking for the password
All his clients are here
But I can't get cash
Oh but
I don't know the password
I know
But we can definitely unlock the code
Me?
Go chop off all ten of President Kim's fingers
After all, you know his location.
The sooner the better
Before his fingers completely rot
I tried it out.
Gu Jung-man must have hidden President Kim
I asked him to come to the club tomorrow so you are ready
Don't forget to exclude me.
"A fake police officer"
Oh fuck
Hey, Jung-Wan
What did that bastard Minister Kong say? Huh?
Why are you staring at me? It's really depressing.
President Jin, do you believe me?
Hey, why are you so scary all of a sudden?
Of course I believe what that guy said?
He told me to cut off your fingers
All ten
let's go
It's the eldest brother
Gu Jung-man is here to look for President Kim's finger
OK, I understand. You keep an eye on him.
OK, got it.
Wow, if I was buried in a place like this
No one will ever find you again.
He is looking for President Kim's finger
What are those guys doing?
That is to say
Big Brother
But why do you care so much about Gu Jung Man?
If you're worried, I can get rid of him quietly.
you?
You don’t know what advantages Gu Zhengwan has?
What other advantages does this kid have?
Gu Zhengwan really loves his younger brothers
Give me
Forget it, just smoke your local cigarettes
-Give me the photo
-yes
As expected
No one can handle the aftermath better than us.
How come you are so awesome?
This is labor fee.
Thank you. If I have money, I can do anything.
After all, there are still many younger brothers to take care of.
So even though he has been doing this for more than ten years
The number of younger brothers has not decreased
On the contrary, more and more
Having said that
They are just a bunch of useless errand boys.
That’s the problem
Do you know that useless garbage?
There are guns everywhere outside now
If a face is unfamiliar
A man whose name you can't remember is running towards you with a gun
Can you bear it?
so
We need to use the help of the police to get rid of Gu Zhengwan
But if Gu Zhengwan
Tell the police what happened during this time...
When did I say
Will you hand him over alive?
Look at it
What is my plan?
-Is everything installed?
-Um
Gu Zhengwan was digging the ground early in the morning.
Now we are setting off again
It's the eldest brother
These guys are in the bathhouse now.
bathhouse?
Taking a shower after digging graves is a common activity for those guys.
Keep a close eye on them and wait for Gu Jung Man to leave.
You go to his office.
I'll go over after I finish my work here.
Hey you bastards!
Why don't you get out of here?
Fucking bunch of trash
Hey, Director Kong is still waiting for President Kim's finger.
Go now
Just ten thousand
Turn on the hot water before you go.
Hey, move your head away so I can see that thing.
Look at that bastard's little thing.
This idiot mother
(Yakham Tourist Hotel)
What are these guys doing? What's taking so long?
But this doesn't look like an ordinary bathhouse.
Are these guys kidding us?
Senior Gu Zhengwan is there
Detective Xu
Gu Jung Man is going to the nightclub now
(Gu Zhengwan:
I am leading President Kim’s finger over there.)
Already out
Everyone, check your guns and bulletproof vests.
There is a possibility of a shooting.
So be on high alert
Cheer up
Oh come in
What's wrong?
Nice to meet you
Minister Kong, you stinky bastard
Didn't you ask me to give you my finger?
so
Are you going to chop off my fingers?
No
I don't use knives anymore.
so what?
Just go there with your ten fingers.
I'll give you a gun
Gu Zhengwan, this bastard
What the fuck is going on?
Hello!
How about this thing?
Isn’t it amazing?
Subtitle translation: Guo Jing