(Year 1999)
(Police)
(Uhm Jung Hwa)
(Song Seung Heon)
(EL, Oh Dae Hwan)
(Cha Chung Hwa, Hyun Bong Sik, Jo Yeon Hee)
(My Troublesome Star)
(Production Sponsors)
(Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism and KOCCA)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed under production guidelines.)
Wait, why did you bring me here?
The story broke.
How did this happen?
The reporters are coming back.
We have to go. Hurry.
- Ms. Lim Se Ra.
You're Lim Se Ra, aren't you?
Ms. Lim, why use a different name?
You've been going by Bong Chung Ja, is that correct?
- Ms. Lim, please look here.
- Please, just say something!
After vanishing since the accident,
did you come back just because you were struggling?
Please answer us.
So you're Bong Chung Ja, but you're really Lim Se Ra, right?
- You're Lim Se Ra, aren't you?
- What?
No pictures.
Just a moment.
You can run, right?
- What?
- On three, we run.
How? The reporters are everywhere.
One,
two, three!
Move away!
(Episode 8)
Where are we?
My place.
Why your place?
Well, you never know.
They might follow you to your gosiwon.
Hurry, get out.
No one's looking.
Oh, wait a second.
- Okay?
- It's okay.
I know it's messy when men live alone.
Just a minute. Hold on.
Darn it.
Can I come in now?
Yes.
I'll be right there.
I'm coming.
It's done.
Come in.
Over there.
Want something to drink?
- Just water.
- Water it is.
Okay.
Here.
Thanks.
Okay, what do I do now?
You look flustered. Why don't you sit down?
Oh, should I?
Okay.
Hey, why are you on the floor when there's a couch right there?
Oh, I rarely sit on the couch.
It's more of a backrest.
Like this.
Oh, I see.
So that's your routine.
Sitting right there, having a drink, and watching TV.
How did you know?
What else is a bachelor to do at home?
Should we watch TV?
Sure.
Wait!
Wait.
Hey, for the time being,
maybe we shouldn't watch TV.
Okay?
Why not?
Well, you never know.
If you pop up on the news again,
it'll just make you feel bad.
This whole situation is absurd.
How so?
Right after the accident,
it felt so strange that nobody recognised me.
Like Alice in Wonderland.
But...
But to be recognised again after just a few months...
It feels so awkward.
You'll get used to it in no time.
My only worry is...
I know.
How people will react.
I know what to expect.
To all the people expecting the old Lim Se Ra,
the way I am now...
must be such a disappointment.
The truth is, the real Lim Se Ra is even more pathetic.
You wouldn't know this, Detective,
but I was really nasty and selfish.
What Go Hui Yeong said...
That's Lim Se Ra.
The mess you're in now.
You brought it all on yourself.
You did this to yourself.
She must've resented me so much...
that even after 25 years,
she still holds a grudge.
And who knows?
There might be others besides her.
People hurt by my entitlement and arrogance...
might still hate me to this day.
Even the person who tried to kill me...
Maybe that's why.
No.
The Lim Se Ra I know would never be like that.
How would you know, Detective?
You didn't even know me back then.
I deal with violent criminals every day.
So I'm surrounded by crazy people.
I can tell just by looking into someone's eyes.
Maybe you hurt people by accident, like a stone thrown without thought.
But you're not the type to throw a stone on purpose.
Back then and now,
you seem the same to me.
Are you saying you're not a fan of me...
both then and now?
What? Not a fan?
- When did I ever say that?
- You said it back then.
When you had drinks with Tae Sook.
You said you really weren't a fan of Lim Se Ra's.
When did I say, "Really?"
I just said I wasn't a fan back then.
- I never said...
- It's the same thing.
What's the difference?
You kept putting down the rookie detective.
So what if I praise or critique him?
What's it to you, Detective?
Come on, it does concern me.
It's...
I mean, the thing is...
Right.
I guess so.
I mean, as a fellow detective...
A sense of humiliation, you know?
A modicum of responsibility.
Or a sudden sense of camaraderie, or...
You know, things like that. Right?
Where's the shower?
A shower? Why now?
My hands.
I need to wash my hands.
I see.
Well...
I mean, you could go to the restroom.
The restroom, the shower.
It doesn't matter. I'm just washing my hands.
Do you just call it a restroom?
I brought you a change of clothes.
I'll leave it here.
Come on in.
Come in. It's okay.
You can sleep in here.
What about you?
Oh, I'm fine with the couch or floor.
Yes.
Get some rest.
To everyone waiting for Lim Se Ra,
I must be...
such a disappointment.
Love
One more time
Quick, quick, slow, slow
Quick, quick, quick
One, and, two
Wait.
Why am I suddenly so hyped?
Pull yourself together, okay?
Snap out of it.
Get a grip!
Darn it.
Hold on, I'll call you back.
Gosh!
What was that?
Did she see it?
I don't think she did.
You...
Excuse me.
Were you startled?
If you're up, do you want a beer?
Is she asleep?
She's sleeping.
Gosh, she snores so loud.
How dare he.
Next, we have an update on Lim Se Ra.
Many fans were eagerly awaiting her,
and Lim Se Ra has returned.
But her unexpected appearance was a shock.
(Darn thing)
The phone is turned off. Please leave a message after the tone.
I don't know why she had to crawl back to that world,
only to end up like that.
You're home.
Was that why?
What was?
The way you opposed my becoming a celebrity.
Was it about Auntie?
Why bring up the past?
Why did you hide the fact that she was Lim Se Ra?
What about it?
Is it something to brag about?
So what if she used to be famous?
Look at the state she's in now.
Mom, why do you hate her so much?
Whatever mistakes Auntie made,
everyone is pointing fingers at her.
Why on earth does her own family have to pile on?
Da Hee.
- I have my reasons, you know.
- No matter what your reasons are,
aren't families supposed to have each other's backs?
Whatever the situation is between you and Auntie,
- I'm not like my aunt.
- What's that supposed to mean?
Da Hee.
I think it's ready.
Come on out and have some food.
Is she sleeping?
Time to eat.
Come on out and eat.
Let's eat.
What are you looking at?
Let me see.
Give it here.
Hurry.
(Bong Chung Ja)
Seriously, I told you not to look at these things for a while.
I was just going to read the article about our show's finale.
As if the algorithm would just leave you be.
When it comes to "Love Is Not a Crime,"
Bong Chung Ja is Lim Se Ra.
I used to be sad when no one recognised me,
but it's heartbreaking...
to be recognised like this.
Hurry up and come out to eat.
I've completely lost my appetite.
Let's go.
How dare you cast Lim Se Ra?
I looked the other way when you brought her to the agency.
But forcing her into my project? That's crossing a line.
- How is it different?
- Seriously? You know what I'm like.
I'm not asking you to roll out the red carpet for me,
but I will not tolerate you sabotaging my work.
How did you find out faster than the reporters?
Did you plant a spy on my team or something?
I'm not going to say it again.
Get her off the project. Now.
I think you're misunderstanding something here.
It's my project, not yours.
What?
This is my 1st official project with 2ONE Entertainment.
So...
why are you making a fuss over the cast?
Darn it, why?
You're not the only one suffering.
I've been holding back, too.
And if you were going to leak this to the press,
at least learn to pick your moments.
I'm trying to fan the flames on this,
and you just had to ruin it?
What are you talking about?
You're the one who tipped them off.
How much longer do I have to clean up your mess?
Hey, Kang Du Won, you...
It's amazing how you haven't changed one bit in 25 years.
- You punk!
- See? There you go again.
We may be like family,
but let's try to respect some boundaries, okay?
Hello, everyone.
I'm Dokgo Cheol, Bong Chung Ja's manager.
I'm in your care.
- It's a pleasure to meet you.
- Hello.
I'm Dokgo Cheol. It's nice to meet you.
You crazy punk!
I'm going to kill you.
Hey!
And who are you?
Oh, Mr. Kang asked me to come.
Yes, come on in.
Let's discuss this together.
The male lead will be Won Ban,
and the female lead is Go Hui Yeong, the Queen of Cannes.
And the supporting female role is Bong Chung Ja.
- Excuse me?
- Scratch that.
Let's call her Lim Se Ra. Right?
Pardon me? Yes.
Wait, that's the next biggest role.
That's the role. Get her ready.
Tell Ms. Lim about this.
Fine, then hold an audition.
What?
I mean, come on.
This is our first major production.
It's a waste to just hand over a major role, isn't it?
So it wasn't a done deal after all.
Well...
An open audition with Lim Se Ra means buzz.
I want to be a judge, too.
But on one condition. The judges and everyone else...
- must come to a unanimous decision.
- Okay, I can agree to that.
Okay, let's do it.
We'll be on our way.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Let's go.
Gosh! Really?
For real?
Oh, my goodness!
You're that happy?
Happy doesn't begin to cover it.
Like lightning in a clear sky...
and seeing a double rainbow.
Unbelievable!
It's not final yet.
You still have to audition.
I'm going to get this part.
I'll get this role, no matter what.
That accident kept me from working with Director Choi Young Guk,
but this time, I'll see it through.
I'll do everything I can to help.
Okay, then. Can you take me home first?
What?
To that gosiwon?
I need to get home and start preparing for the audition.
Hurry! I'm going to change.
Be right back.
It was chaos here this morning.
Sleazy reporters were snooping,
filming this rundown gosiwon...
and interviewing anyone.
Oh, no. I made it hard on everyone.
And I already had a bad reputation.
I wonder if Pistol is going to kick me out.
Shall we go in?
Hey, what's with you?
Gosh.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I heard I gave you a rough time.
So you're Lim Se Ra.
Why didn't you tell me?
There was never a good time.
Gosh.
Wait, are you really that mad?
Oh, I'm not prepared for this.
She even touched me.
I never imagined that I would...
meet Lim Se Ra in my lifetime.
I'm a huge "Jewellery Store Girl" fan.
I've watched it so many times.
I've seen it 22... No, maybe 24 times.
Are you really Lim Se Ra, though?
You look really different now.
I know what you did to that woman.
What do you mean?
I know what you made me do.
What did I make you do?
The orders came from you.
We're trying to help your situation.
We're not here for you to shift blame.
What was that?
Are you blaming me now?
Choose carefully.
Who did it?
It was Ju Seung...
I see.
That's your game?
Okay.
I won't die like this.
Tell them this, loud and clear.
If that's your game, I'll sing like a canary.
- I've got nothing to lose.
- What?
You're turning yourself in?
I just might.
I'm a dead man anyway.
Misery loves company.
What was that?
Hey.
The primary is in two days.
One mistake now and it's all over.
We've sunk a lot of money into this,
and we'll walk away with nothing!
You punk!
Darn it, he won't even flinch...
Hello?
What's this about?
Yes, speaking.
Right now?
Yes, I'll be there right away.
Yes, of course.
You'll have nothing to worry about.
You're the one who should worry,
not me.
Handle her before the primary. No excuses.
Yes, sir.
I'll handle her, even if I have to beat it out of her.
Until this is resolved,
stay away from the campaign.
Sorry?
Wait, but...
If you interfere and it goes south,
you become a ticking time bomb to us.
You're not going to show up, are you?
This is what I like about you.
You're quick to know your place.
And that's how you got this far.
Gosh.
This punk!
Darn it, you little punk!
Jung Do!
Let's call the cops!
The police are on your tail.
And they already have solid proof.
What do you mean?
- You should lay low.
- Lay low?
Lay low, my foot!
My hard-earned money is about to vanish!
What did you say?
Telling me to lay low? You punk!
What is this now?
A vehicle is approaching.
Find someone to take care of it cleanly.
Yes, sir.
Stand back.
Where is the patient from jail?
What happened?
Luckily, his heartbeat is back,
but he's in a coma.
How did this happen so fast?
He has a history of epilepsy.
So we scheduled an EEG and an MRI.
Could it be an external factor?
We're looking into that right now.
But if sleep apnoea lasts too long,
it can cause a seizure.
So, maybe he was purposely suffocated?
Hello, everyone!
Hey, Chattaeng! Chavely is here.
I said I'd have a flash sale today.
Gosh.
What's happening?
Gosh!
We broke 20,000 viewers?
Gosh.
I've never had so many viewers.
Gosh, I'm so nervous.
Oh my gosh, what do I do?
Okay.
Ta-da! Ta-da!
You know what this is, right, Chattaeng?
The lip gloss worn by the Queen of Cannes, Hui Yeong, herself.
For today only,
everyone who buys the full set...
(That's awesome!)
(I heard you were Lim Se Ra's stylist)
(Lim Se Ra?)
(Is that true?)
(No way, right?)
(Live broadcast has ended, 29,482 viewers)
She turned it off?
Did you see that?
Did you see her face fall?
See?
I thought you were paranoid over her.
And it looks like she's innocent after all.
- Gosh!
- Ouch!
Come on, you!
Gosh.
But it's strange she ended it like that.
See?
That punk Chavely worked so hard to set the stage,
so she wouldn't just end the stream like that.
When she turns it back on,
let's change our ID and comment.
- So no one can tell.
- Okay.
- What?
- What is it?
I got a message.
(Who are you?)
What do we say?
Oh, what do we do?
We know what you did...
- twenty-five years ago.
- Sent.
Come on, what are you saying?
You don't know a darn thing.
But you never know. We're just dangling bait.
And if she takes the bait?
And if she does?
Then she's caught red-handed.
You're dead.
(I know what you did 25 years ago.)
What do you know?
(You're nothing without Go Hui Yeong.)
Who on earth are you?
(Go Hui Yeong)
I need the necklace you borrowed back.
- Whatever.
- Excuse me?
Go ask the one who threw it. Gosh.
I heard from Lim Se Ra...
that she's just biding her time until the awards ceremony.
She's planning to drop the bomb at the press conference right after.
That's not my problem.
The one with something to lose should fix it themselves.
As for me,
I don't really have anything to lose.
How long have you been there?
I'll be on my way.
No way.
Did you hear all of that?
Gosh.
Darn it.
Thanks for coming to my commercial shoot.
Gosh.
You should've told me you were coming.
If you had, I would've...
I'm glad to hear you had a reshoot.
I was worried it might fall through.
I'm sorry I haven't been a good sister to you.
To be honest, I haven't been a good daughter either.
Use this for the repairs...
and pay off your debts.
How did you know I was in debt?
You could've made a comeback like this all along,
so why have you been living like that?
Tell me about it. I'd like to know too.
What on earth has been holding me back all this time?
But I'm not going to run away anymore.
I'm going to find whatever I lost.
Be it my memories or something else, I'll find it all.
And I'm going to set everything right.
Is there a grown-up we can call?
If your mom isn't available, what about your dad?
Can't we reach your dad either?
My dad can't come.
You're saying you won't take the CSAT?
You've already been accepted to so many colleges,
and all you have to do is meet the minimum score on the CSAT.
So many kids would kill to get into those schools.
Are you really going to throw your life away like this?
The 2001 CSAT took place nationwide today.
Despite the chilly morning air,
test-takers went to the exam sites with nervous expressions.
Yes.
I'm Bong Chung Ja's sister.
Why do you ask?
It's such a relief.
Your sister has a rare blood type, so she was in danger,
but luckily, you have the same blood type.
Mom.
Yes?
Where are you off to on the weekend?
I told you I'm going to the library.
When will you be back?
After dinner.
What about money?
I have some.
I'm heading out.
Hey, Bong Da Ri.
- You messed up your moves again.
- Sorry. I got the moves confused.
No one told you to join late. Did they?
If you get us cut from our debut, will you be responsible for it?
That's enough.
Am I the only one affected?
Everyone's working so hard for this.
She joined late. So she must try harder.
Then instead of complaining, you could show her how it's done.
Riley.
The CEO wants to see you.
A call-up from the CEO.
You know this is a fast track to the debut group, right?
Yes, I do.
Make it count.
I worked so darn hard.
I gave it my absolute all, every single day.
I'm sorry.
I worked so darn hard.
I gave it my absolute all, every single day.
I never had a day of peace.
That's how I lived my life.
But...
why did it end up this way?
Why am I the only one suffering?
(Lowering the hand as if understanding)
(A desperate cry, sadness, rage)
I worked so darn hard.
I never had a day of peace. That's how I lived my life.
Why am I the only one suffering?
I worked so darn hard.
(Judge Go Hui Yeong)
I gave it my absolute all, every single day.
But why did it end up this way?
Why me?
Why am I the only one suffering?
Okay, that's enough.
Could I please try Scene Three?
I'm confident about that one.
Go home.
Thank you for coming in.
Drink this while it's warm.
Thanks.
Okay, relax. Do what you practised.
- Okay?
- Yes.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Ms. Bong Chung Ja?
Yes?
- They're ready for you.
- Okay.
You can do it.
Hello.
I'm Actress Bong Chung Ja.
She's last. How about some freestyle?
I'm tired of the same performances.
Well, isn't that asking a bit much without any prep?
Oh, come on. She's not some amateur.
For goodness' sake, she's Lim Se Ra. She won the Best Actress Award.
Of course, she can do it.
They're on the last audition right now, correct?
Yes, that's right.
Let's wrap up now.
Understood.
Maybe I asked for too much.
I guess age catches up with you.
Just do the scripted scene.
Is she nervous?
Why are you looking at me like that?
You still don't get it, do you?
What it is you did wrong!
- What did I do that was so wrong?
- What are you looking at?
Are you crazy?
Keep going.
- Keep what going?
- Mad because I hit you?
Furious, are you?
Think about what you did to me.
You shattered my dreams...
and destroyed my life.
Seeing you all polished up,
it looks like you've been living the good life.
After you left me to rot in this nightmare!
Right.
To you, it's just a distant memory, isn't it?
You went on with your lives and forgot I even existed.
You were...
You were probably hoping I was dead.
So?
How does it feel to see me back, alive and well?
I haven't had a single peaceful night's sleep.
Every day, I fought to survive, like I was coughing up blood!
All for this very moment!
What should I do to you?
It wouldn't be any fun to end this too quickly.
Just you wait.
My revenge...
is just getting started.
Gosh.
So, how was it?
How did it feel seeing Lim Se Ra after 25 years?
Honestly, I was shocked.
I can't believe she recalled a scene from a 25-year-old film so well.
In that movie from 25 years ago. What if she had been cast...
instead of Go Hui Yeong?
I thought so then, and I still do. Lim Se Ra is a brilliant actress.
In fact, she's gotten even better.
It's been such a long time...
since I've met a true actor...
and my heart pounded at the thought of making a new film.
It's not even a big role. What are you so happy about?
But someone recognised my talent and sought me out.
I'm going to get this part.
I'll get this role, no matter what.
I...
I think I really bombed the audition today.
You did great.
You were really great.
Really?
Was I really okay?
Well,
that was the best performance I have ever seen.
I guarantee it.
No one else could have done it that well.
I was so worried.
That's such a relief.
It's all thanks to you, Detective.
Thank you for being there for me.
It's true, right?
You didn't have to release an article...
about Lim Se Ra failing her audition.
He said to handle things quietly if we could.
That was his idea.
So I'm supposed to just take care of Lim Se Ra quietly?
Well...
That guy I sent last time was a real paper tiger.
He was useless.
Should I try scouting somewhere else?
What's with that look?
What's wrong with my eyes?
I mean, why are you glaring like that?
- You got a problem with something?
- No, it's just...
I'm wondering how much longer I have to do this,
and it's really weighing on me.
- "This," you say?
- Lim Se Ra, as well as our talent,
are all assets of 2ONE Entertainment, right?
Oh, my abs are killing me.
And you thought they were yours?
They're not mine?
To help you not become penniless,
we fed you rice, and now you think you're human?
You're just a little puppy.
Woof, woof.
After 25 years, shouldn't my accounts be settled?
And who do you think does that accounting?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- First off,
a slave has no right to talk about ending contracts.
That doesn't make any sense, now does it?
Slavery is a lifetime commitment.
A slave?
What, you think you can break off your shackles now...
to become some kind of runaway?
Go on then, you punk.
Let's see you try.
I doubt you'll make it.
You won't even get halfway before your ankles are broken.
Whether I end up broken or a free man...
There's only one way to find out.
So this is why you brought Lim Se Ra back?
Leaking her comeback to the press.
You've been writing your own little script?
You'll break it.
Stop looking at me like that, you punk!
Darn it.
Hey. Release the article now.
Now that you're going to be in a drama,
shouldn't you find your own place and move out?
I did think about that,
but I'm comfortable here for now.
It's not like I have family to go to.
Oh, I was so worried you might move out.
What a relief.
I haven't even been that nice to you.
Did my being here even make a difference?
You're the only person I've really been able to open up to.
And you...
are the only one who has conversations like this with me.
- When's your exam again?
- I stopped the countdown.
I'm trying not to think about it until it's time.
Counting down the days was making me feel like I was suffocating,
- and I can't seem to focus.
- I know what you mean.
Just try to relax.
You're young. Your whole life is ahead.
Failing now is a lesson for the future.
When you're my age, you'll see.
Just how wonderful your youth was.
Why are your hands so cold? Why are your hands so cold?
Oh, I keep the heat off to stay up.
Here. Let me warm them up for you.
Warmer?
Gosh, what are you doing?
That punk.
Yes, it's me.
So, how did it go?
(Lim Se Ra's Comeback In 25 years, From a Supporting Role To Main Role)
Come on!
Stop fidgeting with that.
I need to lose weight right now.
What, all of a sudden?
I mean, I never used to have a big appetite.
But I've let myself go for 25 years.
I get hungry right after I eat,
and I lose control when I see food.
I just can't seem to control myself.
But that's not needed for the role.
But I don't need to gain any weight either.
I owe it to the fans who have waited for Lim Se Ra.
But you can't get fit overnight from here.
The fat...
I mean...
Anyway, what's the plan? Getting a personal trainer?
Where would I get money for that?
Gosh.
You okay?
Need a break?
Gosh. Come on.
Come on. That's it.
More.
All right. Four more.
Little
More.
You can do it!
Aren't you the one working out?
Yes!
Then why am I so exhausted?
This is hard too.
Enough!
I'm really not what I used to be.
Here.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, that's a lifesaver.
So what about the culprit?
- The culprit? Why ask now?
- You told me before.
That crucial evidence turned up.
Is he still refusing to talk?
Well, he's in no position to talk.
What situation?
Well, the thing is...
We may need to investigate further.
You know how in movies they have things like, in-person testimony?
If I meet him, maybe I can tell if he's...
No, absolutely not.
That won't be necessary.
Ms. Bong, just focus on your life.
Keep exercising in crowded places like this.
Got it. Got it.
Try to avoid places without security cameras.
I mean, I'll stick with you as much as I can, but...
You just never know, right?
Don't worry.
I'm ready for anything.
Just keep a close eye on him.
So, no improvement at all?
I'm worried he might never wake up.
The fear is that the attacker might return.
Sorry?
Oh, never mind.
Anyway, I'm counting on you.
You know, in dramas,
people wake up miraculously after a couple of months too.
- Keep up the good work.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Yes?
What diet were you on? Your face is thin.
Really? Is it obvious?
Yes.
But you wanted to lose belly fat.
What's the point if it only comes off your face?
If you lose weight wrong at our age, you'll look like Gollum.
Gosh.
Do I look like Gollum?
No, it's not that bad.
Wait, hold on a second.
Let me try to fix it with your hair.
- How about we try it like this?
- Any better?
Yes, that's a little better.
Why can't I lose this fat?
It's middle-age spread.
It just won't come off.
You'll just lose muscle mass,
and end up with osteoporosis.
You're the one who needs upkeep.
What upkeep does a manager need?
My only job is managing the building.
That's a fine way to talk for someone...
who got a role thanks to her.
Should I curl that big mouth, too?
- Yes, let me just...
- Ouch!
Goodness.
Do a better job this time.
I do a great job.
But the people just don't get it.
If they don't get it, you failed.
That's why you get cut.
What do they know about art?
Art? Please. Be an artist in your own room.
You need to earn your pay.
Am I wrong?
That's why art stagnates.
Stop with your nonsense.
Just do your job properly.
And no more nonsense about art.
Do it commercially.
- Hello.
- Coming through.
Coming through!
Whenever you're ready.
What is that behind you?
What?
Oh, it's nothing.
Come on, you've been hiding something.
Are you hiding snacks from me?
No, that's not it.
It's a sponsorship gift.
Really?
Oh, of course.
You're Lim Se Ra. This is the bare minimum.
- What is it?
- Want to open it?
Yes.
Gosh, it's so beautiful.
Is it?
Yes, absolutely.
It's so pretty.
Well?
It's not Lim Se Ra. It's Bong Chung Ja.
Don't tell me Go Hui Yeong is scared of someone like Bong Chung Ja.
Scared? Who said I'm scared?
Then what's this?
You're drinking soju? Not even beer?
Reporters are swarming outside.
They're here for Go Hui Yeong and Won Ban.
Not Bong Chung Ja who's middle-aged and fat,
but you, Go Hui Yeong, the Queen of Cannes.
If you're not going out there, reeking of booze...
to make a scene, get it together.
Hui Yeong, this is where it begins.
The Go Hui Yeong, Lim Se Ra's double from 25 years ago?
Now, let's go crush Lim Se Ra for good...
together.
Okay?
It's the perfect setup.
Bong Chung Ja will make you shine even brighter.
Just you wait.
(Epilogue)
Gosh, it's so expensive.
You're back again.
Oh, yes.
Okay. Goodbye.
How about a necklace?
A necklace?
It's not over-the-top,
but a necklace is a great accessory.
What's her style like? What's her style like?
Oh, yes. Thank you.
How can I describe her?
She's not flashy, but you can't help looking at her.
And she has an understated elegance.
And... What's the word...
Like, a classy yet elegant air?
Yes.
Like Actress Lim Se Ra's style?
- Are you all right?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Not at all.
- No, really, I'm sorry.
Gosh.
I was just using her as an example.
No, you're right.
Lim Se Ra style.
You nailed it.
Gosh, yes.
Oh, in that case,
this would be perfect for her.
It's the perfect piece for an elegant beauty like Lim Se Ra.
Gosh.
It's beautiful.
It would look so good on her.
(My Troublesome Star)
She was like Lim Se Ra in her prime, shining so brightly.
Didn't you say she'd make me shine?
That you'd crush her for good?
Lim Se Ra!
Go Hui Yeong, where are you?
What will you do without evidence?
Says who?
Who says I have no evidence?
Go Hui Yeong did that to Se Ra?
She's just the same.
Still gorgeous and radiant.
You know, right?
About their scandal.
This won't work.
I'm sleeping here tonight.