[Characters, locales, organizations, religion,
and incidents in this drama are fictitious]
[Child actors were filmed safely and
under the guardian supervision]
Pay phone...
Are you okay?
Are you determined to die or something?
Tell me it's a dream.
Please...
Tell me this is...
Tell me this is all a dream, please.
Please, please.
[Episode 2]
Mr. Kang.
Free up my calendar...
and schedule the surgery.
Don't tell anyone that I have hemorrhoids, okay?
Away!
Ms. Bong Cheong Ja.
Take this to the pharmacy.
B-Bong-
Where did she go? Where did she go?
It's me. Look into someone.
Find out if there was
a patient named Im Se... no...
Bong Cheong Ja at a major hospital.
Get in.
Are you really a police officer?
This isn't fake, is it?
Get off if you don't believe me.
Why are you getting angry?
It's unfair that I skipped 25 years overnight.
I don't know if my family is around.
I don't even know if they're alive.
I woke up...
looking like this as an old woman.
Do you understand the tears
I'm shedding even a bit?
You got discharged to be an outpatient.
Make sure not to miss a treatment.
Where are we going?
We're going home.
Your current residence.
W-Where is that?
[Jumbo Student Apartments]
Was I studying for an exam?
The student apartments are mainly
for people who failed to study these days.
Why? I wasn't even studying.
Why did I live in this tiny student apartment?
You must know because you live here...
Whether it's a student or a studio
apartment, we live within our means.
Do I own this building, by chance?
Ms. Im, you...
Why do I keep saying Im Se Ra?
You go inside and check, Ms. Bong.
- I'm leaving.
- Wait...
Are you telling me to go inside alone?
You're a car accident victim,
and I'm a traffic officer.
We are nothing more than that, okay?
I went there to get a statement, and I got shit-
Oh, sorry.
I got stuck with the burden, okay?
But it's too bad. I lost my memory.
Let's forget about the statement.
I'll go since I did more than enough.
Let's never see each other again, okay?
Make sure to go to the hospital, okay?
What, what? Is something behind me?
What's the deal, Ahjumma?
You scared me.
D-Do you know me?
Where have you been? You couldn't be reached.
S-Something suddenly came up.
I thought you ran away and got scared.
Run away? Me?
Why would I?
People run away without paying all the time.
Oppa.
I don't remember.
Which room was mine?
[406]
Oh, yes. No. 406.
That's it.
Oppa,
I don't remember the passcode.
I hate being bothered while I'm eating.
The noodles must've gotten all soggy. Geez.
Im Se Ra lived in a place like this?
Get away!
Where am I?
Coming in or getting off work?
Can't you tell by looking?
You came in as soon as you got off.
Didn't you interview the victim
from the Obong Intersection accident?
Gosh, don't even go there.
I went to get a statement today and... Geez.
You should've stayed at the crime department.
Look at me. I'm still securing my spot.
You've always been at the traffic
department, and I had a little hiccup.
I've always been in the middle ground
and you slipped and are down there.
Do you find it funny?
Hey, don't get angry. Acting like
an old bachelor in midlife crisis
will have the women coming toward
you take illegal U-turns.
Seriously. Is today some kind of a day?
The victim and everyone else
are bothering me. Geez.
Was the victim weird?
She's not just weird. She's totally crazy.
Is it a complication from the accident?
She apparently has memory loss.
Or she could be a pathological liar.
She says she's Im Se Ra or whatever.
She's out of her mind.
Just do a background check
and put her away as a fraud.
I know. How dare she say she's Im Se Ra?
[Ju Seung Pil]
What?
Why is this here?
Hey, is she the one who calls herself Im Se Ra?
You've got to be kidding me...
[Bong Cheong Ja]
Do you have amnesia or something?
P-Pardon?
You forgot how to charge this.
Do you know how to turn it on?
Wow, how did you do that?
It has face recognition.
Why not just say there's
fingerprint recognition, too?
Where's Dad's number?
[Younger sister, Baek Ja]
Can you still not reach Ms. Bong's guardian?
But she said not to call because she's busy.
She hung up on me.
How could a family do that?
There was a similar case once.
They were in critical condition,
but their guardian won't show up.
So, what happened?
It turns out…
they attempted suicide.
I got abandoned by my family
and the entertainment industry ousted me.
How have I been living all this time?
I'm hungry.
[No. 406's spot]
[Wuri Ramen]
Gosh, that looks like a laptop. What is it?
It's a tablet PC.
PC?
Is it a computer?
Yes.
Gosh, can I have a look?
I need to look something up.
So crazy. How could this tiny thing be a computer?
What's the name?
Im as in "imja*"
(Means "owner")
Im.
Se as in "sesu*"
(Means "face washing")
Se.
- Ra as in "ramen."
- Ra.
Okay.
[Im Se Ra]
It's up. It's up.
"A former star who disappeared."
"Where's Im Se Ra?"
What's the deal? So, do they know or not?
There's a lot of fake news these days.
How could the news lie?
Cyber bullies make up lies
to get views all the time.
Cyber bullies?
Where do you get real news, then?
The last article on her was
20 years ago. There isn't much.
She hasn't been around for 20 years?
No way.
For 25 years…
So, after that accident, I disappeared?
I disappeared from the face of the earth?
But why?
What happened?
A film starring a national star, Go Hui Yeong,
was nominated for the Cannes Film Festival
And she was nominated for Best Actress.
With "Your Day and Night" from 1997...
Turn it back on! Turn it back on!
She didn't get much attention at first,
but she took on the lead role
in Choi Yeong Guk's "Sad Voice,"
which was initially Im Se Ra's role, she proved her acting skills.
Is that real news?
Yes. Since that's on TV.
After winning the Best New
Actress award that year,
she has solidified her career through many TV dramas and films.
Can she win the Best Actress
award at the Cannes Film Festival?
Go Hui Yeong is going to Cannes?
Daebak, right? I'm a huge fan of hers.
So pretty.
[Ju Seung Pil]
Hey, where are you going? You just got here.
- Let go.
- Hey.
You ended up here while going
after Ju Seung Pil. What will you do?
I'm not going to him.
Where are you going, then?
To return a lost belonging.
[Younger sister, Baek Ja]
Why won't it work?
[Jumbo Student Apartments]
I'm here to meet Ms. Bong Cheong Ja.
Who are you?
Do I need to share private matters?
Find out privately, then.
I can't reach her.
Did her phone die again?
Noona.
She was just here.
- That Ahjumma...
- Ahjumma...
just went upstairs.
- Upstairs?
- The rooftop.
- Which way is it?
- That way.
Noona...
No!
Are you okay?
I thought I was going to die.
Oh, gosh!
Ahjussi. Ahjussi!
Gosh, Ahjussi! Ahjussi!
What do I do?
Wake up. Ahjussi! Ahjussi!
CPR.
I learned how to do it on set.
How do you do CPR?
CPR.
What do I do?
Ahjussi! Ahjussi!
Ahjussi! Wake up, Ahjussi!
What do I do? Gosh...
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
Stop this!
He's alive.
I almost died.
I should be saying that.
I saved your life, Ahjumma.
I'm your savior.
You're not exactly a savior.
- You attempted murder, more like.
- Attempted murder?
You say that when I risk my life to save you?
How could you say that to a police officer?
You didn't save me.
I was holding my phone to find a signal.
But you pushed me and made me fall.
You could've extended your arm outside the window.
Why did you come up on the rooftop?
The window doesn't open in my room.
Goodness. Ahjussi, are you
really a police officer?
What police officer falls
while saving someone's life?
Ahjussi?
I know I look old, but I shouldn't
be called that by you, Ahjumma.
Ahjumma?
You're Ahjumma. Do you expect
me to call you Noona?
Wow. Someone who's rotten
inside out shouldn't say that.
Have you seen what I'm like inside?
I actually look pretty good without clothes on.
Pretty good, my foot.
You're skinny like an anchovy.
A-Anchovy?
Do you want me to take my clothes off? Anchovy?
It's probably too subtle for me to notice.
Anchovy...
Let me show you what an anchovy looks like.
- I'll show you.
- What are you doing?
- I'm serious.
- Gosh, you're crazy.
I'll take it off. Look, look, look.
Get away! Away!
Go! Please go! Go!
Nothing has been going well ever since I met you.
Please, leave! Leave!
Leave! Please, leave!
Leave!
At the age of 50,
I got tangled up with this loser.
Please leave. Please leave...
What are you doing in here?
Well, we aren't doing anything.
What do you mean?
Who does this in the truck bed?
No, no. It's not like that.
It's not like that, Ahjussi.
It's not like that.
Hurry up and come out.
Okay, okay. I'm sorry.
- I can't believe this.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Remember what you said when you left?
As if you'd never see me again.
You didn't want to see me again.
You say you did more than enough.
Why did you show up again?
I'm already confused as is.
Why would you put me in this mess? Why?
You think I came here because I wanted to?
I had to give you something
and ask you a question, too.
Give me what?
Here. It was in my car.
Since you gave this to me,
we won't have to see each other. Bye.
Hold on. Hold on.
What is it now? What? What? What?
Well…
do you know someone named Ju Seung Pil?
I wasn't trying to peep.
I saw a business card while looking for your ID.
Have a look.
[Ju Seung Pil]
"Great Ju Seung Pil"?
What's this?
What is he, Hong Gil Dong?
Do you remember?
I have memory loss.
Did you forget? Or are you mocking me?
Is this some kind of new scam?
Doesn't it ring a bell? Do you have a hunch? Or...
do you think he's your family?
Ju Seung Pil, Jo Pil Seung, or whatever.
I don't know him.
I don't even want to know.
[2668]
2668?
[Bong Dumping Shop]
"Bong Dumpling Shop"?
Turn left in a moment.
[4,800 won]
Ahjussi,
that's the total, right?
I guess you know the total in advance these days.
Are you from the '90s?
That's the base fare.
The base fare is 4,800 won?
Gosh, ahjussi. Stop!
I'm sorry.
How is it 5,000 from there to here?
What's with the economy?
How could the taxi base fare be more
expensive than jjajangmyeon?
[Bong Cheong Ja]
I'm working. Call me later.
Here. Your penalty is 15 points.
Congratulations.
[Bong Cheong Ja]
Geez, this Ahjumma.
Good day.
Seriously. This Ahjumma.
Done.
[Bong Cheong Ja]
Geez, seriously.
What is it?
How many times did I tell you?
We need to identify you.
I didn't bring my ID.
Give me your resident ID number. Will check.
I don't know my resident ID number.
You're leaving us with no choice.
Should I call the police, huh?
- Hi.
- I didn't call him.
What's going on?
I...
I called him.
What's this about?
She took a free ride.
But I couldn't identify her. That's why we're here.
Unbelievable.
How could they demand 30 times more for a fine?
What's ridiculous is that I paid that fine.
Geez, I even missed lunch.
Why didn't you pay the fare?
This is so unfair.
Everyone scanned their phone to enter.
So, I did the same.
Didn't you register your card on your phone?
Register what…
I said I don't remember.
But how could you forget how to ride the subway?
We had the subway 25 years ago, too.
I haven't been on the subway since I was a kid.
You call that an excuse?
I wasn't one to take public transportation
so freely like this, you know.
Oh, I see.
Let's say that's true. Why didn't
you let him identify you?
You could've just given him
your name and ID number.
Why did you make me come when I'm busy?
What if I did and they wrote an article about it?
Will you take responsibility?
Seriously, this Ahjumma. Geez!
Ahjumma...
He keeps calling me Ahjumma. That Ahjussi.
I'll pay you back. Don't worry.
[Bong Cheong Ja: Block contact]
So annoying.
Why is it so hard to find Bong Dumpling Shop?
[Bong Dumpling Shop]
Baek Ja.
Are you Baek Ja?
Why did you change so much?
My sister, Baek Ja.
What are you doing here?
Why aren't you at Hanguk University?
Why are you making dumplings here?
Tell me. Why are you holding this thing?
I heard you were sent to the
hospital after an accident.
Did you completely lose it?
Why are you doing this?
Well, what happened in the last 25 years?
I sent you to the best academy and got you
a private tutor and supported you.
But you ended up as a dumpling shop owner?
I mean...
of all things out there,
why a dumpling shop? Why?
Why not a pasta shop or a bakery?
Are you sick, by chance?
Don't tell me…
something ridiculous like you
lost your memory of the last 25 years.
Did you forget everything?
No way...
E-Everything?
- I'm back.
- Hey.
Seriously...
Go straight to the academy today.
Don't play hooky.
You had a child?
What's wrong with Aunt?
She had memory loss, apparently.
Geez. Daebak.
I thought that only happened in dramas.
That's what I'm saying.
It's ridiculous to witness it, isn't it?
Hey, you're supposed to be my niece.
But all you did was nod at me?
Is that how you greet me?
Your kid is like that because of how you are.
Geez. Yes, I could see what's going on here.
Looks like you don't even have a husband.
Did you get a divorce or something?
By chance,
are you an unwed mother?
Oh, my God.
You're crazy.
Seriously.
But still, you should've taught
your daughter properly.
You shouldn't do that.
Are you crazy?
She couldn't even look me in the eye before.
How could she change so much?
Time is scary. It really is.
Who is this?
How long will you stay in bed?
Don't you know we all hurt if
even one person isn't here?
It's been days.
Tell me if you'll quit.
- I'll find someone else.
- Pardon?
I-I'm coming. I should work.
I was going to go now.
Come right now.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Where would you like me to come?
[Obong Middle School]
[Cafeteria Regulations]
You want me to cut all these? By myself?
There isn't much today.
We're making 10 tubs of radish kimchi.
Gosh.
I can't use a knife.
I've never held a knife before.
Here's a knife…
I can't cut fruit, either.
How could I cut radishes?
How much did you hurt your head?
♫ You can smile now, smile again ♫
♫ This is a happy moment, happy days ♫
♫ Stand straight and forget
about all the hardships in life ♫
♫ Forget about sadness, never cry ♫
I have amazing knife skills.
I must have a lot of experience in this.
Mix it now.
There are so many other jobs.
Why did I work at a place like this?
My neck…
My back…
Gosh...
Huh? You have another batch left.
Thank you.
- Want a lot of rice?
- Yes.
- What do we have today?
- Jjajangmyeon, I said.
It's jjajang rice, you fool.
- I don't want this.
- You have it.
Yes.
Her only aunt is looking like this.
Of course, she's embarrassed.
Im Se Ra! Im Se Ra! Im Se Ra!
Enjoy.
Take this.
Give me pork or jjajang instead.
It's heavy.
No, no.
Make it the same.
That wasn't wrapped right.
My back…
My back hurts since I'm old.
[Reserved for elders]
Gosh, seriously!
No!
Ahjumma!
Scrub harder. Come on.
It's on the steps, too.
Geez.
Geez, damn it.
Seriously.
I didn't do it on purpose.
You should've sealed it tight
if you were going to carry kimchi.
It's hard to remove the kimchi smell.
Scrub harder.
Geez.
Why did she put it in a bag?
Hello?
Did you spill radish kimchi on my daughter?
Oh, yes. You must be her mother.
This is a misunderstanding.
I swear I didn't do it on purpose.
You attacked her because
she didn't give up her seat for you.
Gosh, attack?
It was clearly a mistake.
I won't just let this go.
She needs to see a psychiatrist
because she is in shock.
I'll get a doctor's note and sue you,
just so you know.
Sue?
Hello? H-Hello?
[13th Trainee Audition]
[Jewelry Shop Girl]
Are you ready, Ms. Bong Da Hui?
Yes.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Hello, sir.
She looks familiar.
Do you know her?
She's a good performer.
But it'd be a waste to be
an idol with a face like that.
She should be an actor.
Hey, what made the busy
national star, Go Hui Yeong, call?
Me?
Sick? I'm fine.
I was on a brief vacation.
The mighty Go Hui Yeong is worrying about me.
I'm so touched.
Of course, I will. When should we meet?
Right now?
No, of course not. I'll be right there. Wait.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Of all days, why call now?
- Be careful.
How am I supposed to sit? Geez.
Is this too polite?
Nice.
This will make me look stuck up.
Geez, what do I do?
Hold on.
You came, Noona.
Aren't I polite?
It's chewy because it's wild-caught.
Try it.
I can't eat raw fish.
I guess you still don't know.
I need to get a new secretary or something.
How can he not know your taste,
the face of Two One Entertainment
and the biggest actor in Korea?
This is no good. I should fire him now.
I was going to, anyway. I'll fire him now.
Bastard. Where's my phone?
No.
It was about time you called.
But maybe you forgot. I didn't hear from you
so, I called you first.
What… What did I forget?
Come on now.
My contract is expiring in a month.
Even the youngest hairdresser knows.
I know.
That's why I brought this with me.
This isn't why I wanted to see you.
But I'm still curious.
Hey.
How come you can't stop being
a thug as you were 20 years ago?
- Seriously...
- Noona,
watch what you say.
Hey.
You still think of me
as Im Se Ra's gofer, don't you?
That's first-class treatment in this industry.
Think of your age.
Even the S-Class becomes dirt cheap after 10 years.
How many decades do you expect to milk it?
Hey, do you think Cannes
and the Academy are a joke?
If you like raising the cost by
doing ads, raise a model, not an actor.
That's what I'm saying!
Don't you know how I raised you?
What do you mean by that?
In the span of time we spent together,
there were trust, hope,
and secrets.
I think I saw someone recently.
Has it been 25 years?
It's already been that long...
since Im Se Ra disappeared.
Why would you splash alcohol? Geez.
You were always a substitute for Im Se Ra.
But let's say Im Se Ra returns.
Wow.
That would be so fun, wouldn't it?
[Two One Entertainment Exclusive Contract]
I'll let you rest, Noona.
You were always a substitute for Im Se Ra.
But let's say Im Se Ra returns.
Die!
[Go Hui Yeong]
The party leader Min Guk Hui,
who was in office for three terms
officially announced to run as mayor of Seoul
and garnering the political circles' interest.
Leader Min recently stepped down
as the assemblyman
and expressed his intention to run, saying it's time for Seoul.
[Assemblyman Min is running for mayor of Seoul]
Excuse us.
The political circles think his decision to run
could shake up the Seoul mayoral election.
[DUI Checkpoint]
We're checking for DUI. Thank you for your cooperation.
Closer. Closer.
Like this. Blow.
No, don't burp...
Checking for DUI.
Blow.
Did you drink?
Turn the car off and hand me your license.
I didn't drink.
It's hand sanitizer. I sanitized my hands.
Give me your license unless
you drank hand sanitizer.
Geez. I said I didn't drink!
You tax parasite. Why won't you believe me?
Yes, please hand your license to this tax parasite.
Did you see me?
I'm asking if you saw me drink.
If you resist, you could get up to
five years in jail or up to 50 million in fines.
Damn it.
I'll give you 50 million.
I'll give it to you.
It's okay. It's okay.
- Shit.
- If you keep doing this,
you'll be arrested for aggravated
obstruction of justice.
Arrest me.
Geez.
- Hey...
- My back.
Hold on. Hold on!
The police are beating me up!
Let go! I didn't drink!
Now here.
At the news of Actor Go Hui Yeong's
contract with Two One
Entertainment expiring this month,
their soaring stock value suddenly plummeted.
Ms. Go Hui Yeong has been a top star...
What? T-Two One Entertainment?
H-Hey, turn up the volume. Hurry.
Just one second.
The rumor of the contract non-renewal appears
to have affected the drop in stock value.
Two One Entertainment stated
they're ready to work with Ms. Go...
- You can't move.
- Geez.
Why would the company be
in crisis because of one celebrity?
Why are they so weak?
Go Hui Yeong isn't just a celebrity.
She's probably worth more
than everyone in the agency.
Do you know about this industry?
Well, my first love was a very famous celebrity.
Who?
Everyone's first love, Im Se Ra.
How many weeks has it been?
I know.
I heard it was a serious accident.
What if she can't wake up?
That can't be.
I wanted an autograph,
but I couldn't...
since she fell unconscious.
I see.
You worked at Daemin Hospital.
How did you know?
If she kept acting, she'd be
no comparison to Go Hui Yeong.
A world-famous actor by now.
I'll turn it up. Okay.
You can't move. They'll fall off.
If an actor does physical labor,
her body will be ruined instantly.
Should I just quit?
I'll get a doctor's note and sue you,
just so you know.
No.
I need to work.
Hello?
Police?
Why does the offender ask for my number?
Settle?
Sunbaenim.
The Obong Intersection case isn't on PDA yet.
Should I do it if you're busy?
Why would you? It's my job.
There's a deadline, but you haven't handed it over.
It's not that I'm refusing. It's just-
I just have more to investigate.
That's our job.
You just need to report the situation.
Seriously. I know.
I know, too. I know.
I'll hand it over soon, Hoobaenim.
I will. Okay?
Did you check the truck driver's
navigation history?
No. I only checked his dashcam and CCTV nearby.
What?
You should've checked it first
to see if it matched his testimony.
I took his memory card just in case.
- I'll check now.
- No, I'll do it.
[Obong Intersection]
[Kang Dae Gu's navigation history]
[Navigation history]
[Personal Information]
[Jumbo Student Apartments]
Whether it's a student or a studio apartment,
we live within our means.
What's with this guy?
It's not suspicious at all.
You scared me.
It's not suspicious at all. So, eat. Eat.
I mean,
he's been lurking around the victim's
residence before the accident.
He must've had business in the area.
Why was he wearing a cap while driving at night?
He must be balding.
He was chewing gum intensely, too.
Isn't that suspicious?
I chew gum intensely when I'm sleepy.
- You even kick while sleeping.
- I'm not joking.
Just finish it up and send it
to the investigation department.
Stop wasting your energy.
I need the victim's testimony.
You don't know when she'll get her memory back.
You're obsessing over her
to go after Ju Seung Pil, right?
Don't poke around and lose your job.
Just stay quiet and give out tickets.
That's how you can survive.
Aren't you... Aren't you eating?
Anything suspicious when the
offender was here?
I'm not sure. He wasn't in his right mind.
He was totally out of it.
Nothing from the blood test, either?
No.
There was one thing kind of creepy.
He panicked, asking what would
happen to him if the victim died.
So, I told him she's not in critical condition.
Is she really okay?
Was she not injured at all?
H-How could that be? I ran into her really hard.
Are you sure she's okay?
Don't worry, Sunbaenim.
I think the victim will settle.
What do you mean?
He wanted to settle with the victim.
He asked for her contact info.
So, did you tell him?
Settle?
You mean, you'll pay a settlement?
Yes, not at all.
You want to settle. I should come.
He didn't mention where they're meeting?
I'm not sure...
[Bong Cheong Ja]
Why does he want to meet somewhere like this?
Yes, I'm almost here. Where...
What's this about?
Why didn't you answer? Where are you?
- I'm out to run an errand.
- So, where are you right now?
Why are you yelling?
Go back to your apartment. Hurry.
W-What's wrong?
Stop talking and go now!
I'm going.
W-When are you coming, by the way?
So, when will that be?
Hurry, hurry.
Ms. Bong.
Can you hear me?
Ms. Bong!
[Epilogue]
[Three weeks after Im Se Ra's accident]
How many weeks has it been?
I know.
I heard it was a serious accident.
I'll go in just once.
You can't. Please leave.
Why?
Oh, yes. I'm a detective in this country.
You cannot.
Why not? I said I'm a detective!
Seriously.
What's that?
Stop, stop!
Ms. Im Se Ra, you need to wake up!
Remember, you promised to see me again!
Hold on. Hold on. I'll be waiting!
Hold on!
I'll wait! I'm serious!
H-Hold on!
Ms. Im, I'll be waiting!
You need to wake up, okay?
Hold on! I'll wait without eating!
Ms. Im, keep your promise!
I'll be waiting!
Ms. Im, you have to wake up!
[Police - Dokgo Cheol]
♫ Splendid smile ♫
♫ Twinkling eyes ♫
♫ They're seeping into my heart ♫
♫ The faint image of you ♫
♫ Just like the midsummer night's dream ♫
♫ The beautiful stars disappeared ♫
♫ Your radiant smile ♫
♫ It lingers faintly ♫
♫ Just like the stars too far away to approach ♫
Don't follow me. I'm embarrassed.
I don't want to follow you, either.
But you keep going down dangerous paths.
Why look into a car accident from 25 years ago?
I think he's been following you.
Who'd follow me?
Who are you?
Did you hear?
Im Se Ra reappared.
Do you know why she hates me so much?
You apparently ruined her life.
You did.
I need to get it back.
My position.