♪Like a flock of birds
pressing ever forward♪
♪Stranded on an island
shrouded in heavy mist♪
♪We may seem small
beneath the vast world♪
♪But not once have we felt despair♪
♪We've crossed waves
a thousand layers deep♪
♪Stepped on reefs hidden in the dark♪
♪Facing sharper winds head-on♪
♪Our wounds now stitched
into battle robes♪
♪The long night
is branded by starlight♪
♪We embrace this deep blue together♪
♪At the edge of the vast unknown,
I remain unchanged♪
♪Holding fast with lonely courage,
roaring without fear♪
♪Determined to be
both my friend and my rival♪
♪No one dares to blindly
urge me to turn back♪
♪I choose what I believe is worth it♪
=Rose and Gun=
=Episode 18=
Captain Wu.
What should I do?
Do you want this child?
Yes, of course I do.
Do you know what having a child means?
Do you know
what I remember most from my childhood?
It was my mom waiting by the phone
every day, hoping it'd ring.
Sometimes, we get
one phone call a week.
Sometimes, we'll go one whole month,
half a year, or even longer
without a single call.
You're not from a military family,
so you don't understand.
But it's pure suffering
for the kids and family.
It's much better now.
We can contact every week when off duty.
When things are good,
we can go home a few times a week.
But that's not enough
to raise a child.
Even the basics,
what if she can't eat from nausea?
What if she can't walk
and can't go to pregnancy checkups?
What if you don't have leave
on her due date?
You can't even be sure.
Yangyang has to expect the worst.
You should
see things from her perspective.
She has to imagine
you'll be absent all the time.
What should she do?
Captain Wu.
If it were you, what would you do?
Just thinking
of my pregnant wife
getting up at night
with no one there
to pour her a glass of water,
makes my chest feel tight
and heavy.
I understand you.
Yes, it's a huge responsibility.
But you have to carry it.
If you can't,
everything you said at the warship
was nonsense.
Zong Qing.
Explain the flag signals to the brides.
Let the sea bear witness.
With the ship as our matchmaker,
we'll be together
forever!
What a rare guest.
Sorry, I need to trouble you again.
Something urgent came up at work.
I'll leave Yangyang with you for a bit. I'll pick her up after.
It's alright.
I just got off shift, so I'm free.
Yangyang, you're with me today.
Go on. Why are you being shy?
Mrs. Wang, sorry to trouble you.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Mrs. Wang.
You're due soon.
Why are you still working?
I still have a few days to go.
Staying home is boring.
Have you prepared everything?
What's there to prepare?
I'll just deliver the baby
when it's time.
Want to touch her?
No thanks.
Are you scared?
Aren't you scared?
What's there to fear?
It's just pregnancy.
When I was pregnant
with the first child,
I was scared too.
Wang Lang was in the army then.
I stayed with my mother-in-law
back home.
I watched my belly
grow bigger day by day.
I was so panicked.
I thought
I was not even ready.
How can I be a mom?
The worst part was that Wang Lang
wasn't around during the pregnancy.
Not until the due date
did he get leave to come home.
But who knew
he got an urgent order on the train.
He was called back halfway.
I broke down when I heard that.
Wang Zhaoyang
was born prematurely that day.
Three days after giving birth,
Wang Lang finally called me.
On the phone,
he was crying so much
that he couldn't even
finish apologizing.
Brigadier cried?
Have you heard a man cry?
That kind where he chokes up
and sounds terrible.
It's like he's suffocating himself.
Actually, having a child
is a shared responsibility.
But giving birth
is something women face alone,
from start to finish.
You'll be pregnant for ten months.
Think about it.
Not only does your body lose shape,
but your memory also worsens.
You'll be throwing up every single day.
In the end, your feet and hands
will swell too much to wear shoes.
Especially during labor.
The pain is so intense
that you forget how to scream.
But it's strange.
When the nurse
places that ugly little thing
on you,
that wrinkly and red little hand
just grabs your finger.
In that moment,
you instantly calm down
and forget all about the pain.
Your heart will melt.
Mrs. Wang.
I'm pregnant too.
I could tell.
That's why Xin brought you to me.
But I don't know what to do.
I'm a little scared.
Yangyang.
Remember this.
Giving birth is not a duty.
It's a personal choice.
After I had Wang Zhaoyang,
I thought
I'll never
have a second child.
But look at me now.
Pregnancy is tough.
But you know what?
After the baby is born,
many unexpected things
will happen.
Really.
So
I hope you think it through.
(I forgot to tell you.)
(The day after you gave
the porcelain shards to Wu Si,)
(I sent them to the museum.)
(I hope it would catch
Cultural Relics Bureau's attention.)
(Also,)
(if it's true that someone is stealing
underwater cultural relics)
(more relics)
(will be smuggled overseas)
(for every day we delay.)
Xin, Mr. Tian asked you
to join the meeting.
Got it.
(Atocha,)
(a company registered
in the Roman Islands.)
(Check out that company.)
(The address is 56, Torini Street.)
(What can I find with just a name)
(and an address?)
(Then it's up to your abilities.)
(I'm just a reporter.)
(I'm not that powerful.)
(Any other leads?)
(Tell me all of them.)
(That's all for now.)
(One New Email Received)
(But perhaps you'll get lucky)
(and find something.)
Find me a company
registered in the Roman Islands.
Is it related to the relics?
It's important.
I need all the information.
Mrs. Wang.
I don't feel anything.
I'm not happy
or excited at all.
I don't look forward to it.
Am I unfit to be a mom?
Of course not.
Do you know
when I stopped regretting?
When Wang Zhaoyang turned one month old.
Wang Lang applied for leave
and came home.
I recall waking up
one morning
to vaguely see Wang Lang
clumsily feeding the baby.
Scared to wake me,
he didn't turn on the light.
He just opened
a small slit between the curtains,
turned the baby toward it,
and tried to feed the baby the pacifier.
He was so clumsy
that he was sweating all over.
Watching him like that...
Honestly,
when Wang Zhaoyang misbehaves
or Wang Lang upsets me,
I think of that day.
I think
of the warm sunlight
that shone through the slit that day.
And I'll feel
that
it's all worth it.
Can I touch her?
Of course.
She's turning around
to say hi to you.
Did you feel it?
Our little one is saying
"Yangyang,
we'll be meeting very soon."
How did it go?
I did find something.
This company
(Atocha, 56, Torini Street)
is registered in the Roman Islands,
but I couldn't find anything else.
Maybe try pressing
your informant again.
If he relents,
he might tell you others.
I've pressed him for days
before he told me about Atocha.
Alright, work on something else.
I'll think of something.
Dad, Mom, I'm home.
You're home.
Hurry over.
Let me officially
announce some good news.
What good news?
Lan Yangyang
is pregnant.
This is great news.
I'll call Lan Weiguo later
to congratulate him.
At the very least, Xin should share
some good fortune
from his becoming a grandpa.
Dad, must you always
drag me into everything?
Who else would I drag in?
I'm just jealous.
Look at them.
How annoying.
Let me help you.
How nice.
Sergeant Cheng.
What's up with Captain Zong?
How long will he run for?
You don't get it.
He'll stop running
when he figures things out.
Captain Zong, your wife texted you.
Are you going to read it?
If not, I'll toss your phone.
(Lan Yangyang:
I'm going to Dad's. Talk later.)
What?
No, again?
What happened?
Guess he didn't get good news.
(A needle is inserted through
the mother's spinal foramen)
(to guide a thin catheter)
(into the epidural space.)
(It's a potential space)
(outside the spinal canal,
filled with nerve roots.)
Tell me what you think.
That's all the informant gave me.
After what happened last time,
he's probably wary of you.
This confirms again
that my suspicion of Changzhou
was correct.
I think he still has clues.
Think about his last statement.
"If you're lucky,
you might find something."
You're saying
he'll give me more clues
if I go to Roman?
It's possible.
Or
he's testing you.
This trip is worth it then.
You can go
but not alone.
I'll bring Hai.
I'm saying
it's not the same abroad
as it is at home.
Your safety must be taken seriously.
Before you go,
you must report
to the relevant authorities.
Got it.
(Chinese People's Liberation Army)
The Gulf of Aden is a key route
from the Indian Ocean
into the Mediterranean
and the Atlantic Ocean.
It's also a major route connecting
East Asia,
Western Europe and North America.
Each year,
hundreds of countries and regions
send about 20,000 vessels
to sail through this route.
They take up one-fifth
of global sea cargo.
Since we sent
our first escort fleet in 2008,
long-range escort
has become a regular deployment
and a tradition
in fulfilling our duties.
This escort follows old rules.
Three warships in one formation.
Wenzhou Ship will lead.
Wang Lang.
Yes!
This escort crosses unknown waters
for the first time.
You must boost your leadership.
Also, the higher-ups decided
to let you form
this time's special ops team.
Lead well. Train well.
I'll complete the mission!
At ease.
Attention!
Chief.
Blue Blade Team is assembled.
Awaiting orders.
At ease.
Yes!
A command.
At ease.
I'll spare the nonsense.
A new round of escort missions
is about to begin.
I'm here today to select candidates.
Same rules.
We'll train first.
Winners join the mission.
Don't let me see Blue Blade fall behind.
Can you do it?
- Yes!
Fire!
- One, two, three, four!
No showers tonight.
Avoid water for the next few days.
Can you be more gentle, Dr. Qiu?
Don't move.
No tough guy will whine.
How can you join special forces
without getting injured?
Bear with it.
Does it still hurt?
No.
Well, Dr. Qiu.
Can you work a bit faster?
I have to help in the kitchen later.
Bear with it.
Cut down on the firewood. Don't burn it.
How's it going?
Captain, almost done.
Alright.
Report!
We're back to help in the kitchen.
Aren't you applying ointment
for sunburn?
All done. I'm fine.
Captain.
Do our tents
have to be that close to the beach?
The sound of waves keeps me
from sleeping at night.
You can't sleep with waves?
What will you do on a warship?
You need to listen more
and get used to it.
Overcome it.
Yes.
Mr. Yi Nanwang.
You know how bad
your swimming is, right?
Practice more. It'll be helpful.
Get used to it.
I'll go over first.
Alright.
Where are you hurt?
My back.
Here?
Ouch.
Ouch!
How is it, punk?
Blue Blade isn't easy, right?
I'm doing great.
Stop lying.
You can't even sleep
with the sound of waves.
I'm doing great.
When will the food be ready?
I'm starving. Hurry up.
Tactical rowing.
Enemy.
Enemy cleared.
Alright, go straight ashore.
Zong Xi.
What are you looking at?
There are no fairies in the sky.
What I'm thinking about
is way better than fairies.
I'm thinking about my son's name.
What do you think of Zong Xi?
My dad picked it.
Zong Xi?
Why not call him
Zong Dong, Zong Nan, or Zong Bei?
[*These mean directions in English.]
Why must it be Zong Xi?
Do you know anything about culture?
It's the "Xi" that means bustling.
Who names their kid
something like direction?
Your kid's name should be
Wu Liuqi, Wu Basishi,
Wu Jiusishiwu, or Wu Dang.
[*These mean numbers in English.]
Actually, Wu Dang sounds pretty good.
The kid should stand on his own.
Spoken like
a true major battalion commander.
I'll name yours.
You're definitely up to no good.
I'll give your kid a nice name.
How about Zong Shi?
[*Means a master.]
Alright, my kid's name is Zong Shi.
Yours is Wu Dang.
[*Means an ancient sect.]
They will grow up
to become special forces.
How about that?
Unbelievable.
Zong Xi sounds nice.
Right? I think so too.
Zong Xi!
♪A battle-hardened company♪
♪With battle-hardened men♪
♪Battle-hardened minds are red♪
♪Battle-hardened bullets
with deadly aim♪
♪Battle-hardened bayonets
stained with blood♪
♪Impacting like a strong wind♪
Put him down!
Gather round!
Let me show you how it's done.
- Good job!
Keep up!
Can you do it?
No, stop.
You can't handle it anymore?
Captain.
A few more times left.
Hold on a bit more.
Yes, Captain.
Resume training.
Hurry.
One more, and you'll finish all four.
Here. Stand still.
Okay, keep rocking.
Investigate in the Roman Islands?
Tang Xin, you've gone a little too far.
You found nothing in China.
Do you think
you'll find the truth abroad?
This is the only lead I have now.
I've looked into it.
Organizations
registered in the Roman Islands
don't disclose corporate information,
so many companies
engaged in illegal activity
choose there as their base.
Since the informant gave this to me,
Atocha Company
must hold valuable info.
He gave you
lots of leads.
And what's the result?
You went to sea three times.
You didn't even see a sunken ship.
Once you're in Roman,
can you get more information from him?
Hello, Mr. Bai?
Tang Xin, the identification results
for the porcelain shards
you gave me last time are out.
They're indeed sunken ship relics.
Wait, Mr. Bai.
I didn't catch that.
Can you repeat that?
I said that the identification results
for the porcelain shards
you gave me last time are out.
They're indeed sunken ship relics.
If the porcelain were intact,
it would be highly valuable.
Cultural Relics Bureau
has officially decided
to begin underwater archaeological work
at Dayan Reef.
That's great.
Thank you, Mr. Bai.
We should be the ones thanking you.
The head of Cultural Relics Bureau
asked me to pass along their thanks.
Don't mention it.
We're just doing our duty.
Alright, bye.
Mr. Tian, you heard that.
Don't you think I should go to Roman
and finish this investigation?
Alright.
Good luck then.
But be sure to stay safe.
After some intensive training,
the new selection list
for the escort mission is out.
Selected personnel will undergo
isolated training at sea.
Only those who pass the training
are qualified to board the ship
for the mission.
I now announce
the selection list of escort personnel.
Wu Si!
Here!
Zong Qing!
Cheng Yuan!
Here!
Dai Wei!
Zhou Keyang!
Here!
Li Xu!
Ye Haiyang!
Here!
Yi Nanwang!
Wang Chen!
Here!
Peng Tiechao!
Yu Bo!
Here!
Su Hong!
Liu Xiangsheng!
Here!
Ke'er.
Cheng Yuan, why are you here today?
I know.
You're here to make up
for my birthday, right?
I'm about to leave for escort duty.
How long will you be gone?
Not sure. It depends on the mission.
But you're getting discharged
in September.
I probably won't make it back in time.
I understand.
Anything else?
If not, I'll go back first.
I'm sorry.
Don't be mad.
You're afraid I'd be mad?
Escort duty is a mission. I have to go.
I never said you couldn't go,
but why couldn't you tell me in advance?
You knew I'm getting discharged
this September.
And you knew clearly
that escort duty would overlap
with that time.
But you still chose to sign up.
You only told me
once the list was confirmed.
Are you trying to avoid my discharge?
No.
Don't worry.
I'm a soldier too.
I won't hold you back.
I chose to join the army myself.
I'll leave on my own too.
Ke'er.
There's no signal at sea.
Calls have to be made
within the permitted time frame.
I can't contact you often.
I'm sorry.
Take care of yourself.
Cheng Yuan.
Do you know what I've heard
most often these past two years?
It's exactly what you just said.
"I'm sorry.
Take care of yourself."
What else?
If I don't take care of myself,
am I supposed to count on you to do it?
Alright.
Go back.
Be careful while you're at sea.
Guess who I am.
Honey.
Why are you back?
I missed you.
Alright.
Why were you gone so long this time?
I thought you were mad at me.
I dare not be mad at my goddess.
Are you joking?
I just finished training
and didn't even get changed.
Hurry, let me show you something.
I went shopping today
and bought
some items I really like.
You're not allowed to dislike them.
And then,
I don't know
our baby's gender,
so I bought clothes in neutral colors.
Look. Navy blue. Is it cute?
Honey.
Have you thought it through?
Yes.
Honey.
I'm not that scared anymore.
Let's bring our baby into this world
and be
the coolest parents.
They say pregnancy makes me silly.
You'd better take care of me then.
You're not allowed to say
I've become dumb, fat,
or ugly.
I've thought it through.
You'll come home once a week.
Accompany me
to birthing classes in the morning.
In the afternoon,
you'll help set up the nursery.
Okay?
Honey.
I...
was selected
for a marine escort mission abroad.
I leave tomorrow.
For how long?
At least two months.
I'm sorry.
You'll be home by yourself again.
It's okay.
Mom can take care of me.
The baby and I
will wait for you at home.
Honey.
Enough.
Again? At this hour?
What do you want to say?
Say it to your daughter.
Darling.
I have to leave.
Be good and listen to Mom.
Don't give her a hard time.
I'll hold you and Mom every day
when I come back.
You
leave in one piece,
so come back safe and whole.
You hear me?
Lie down.
I'll walk you out.
Don't. If you do,
I won't be able to leave.
You're still playing brigadier at home?
Be good.
Honey.
I'm off to handle my duty.
Approved. Go ahead.
Wang Lang.
Come home soon.
Zhaoyang.
Why are you still up?
Dad.
When Mom gives birth to my sister,
are you not going to be home?
If I'm not home,
will you be scared?
No.
Daddy, you can't be scared either.
I already know how to take care of Mom.
Do you remember the number of that guard
I had you memorize?
If Mom doesn't feel well,
call him right away.
He'll come and get you.
Remember to bring Mom's maternity bag.
It's in her closet.
It contains toiletries
and your sister's items.
Also...
I also have to bring enough cash
and documents
like household registration book, ID,
mother-child health records,
birth permit,
and medical records.
I know all the things you tell me.
Wang Zhaoyang.
I'll hand over this family to you.
Take care of your mom and sister.
Can you do that?
Yes!
(Honey, you're awake?)
(I didn't want to disturb you,
so I left first.)
(Here's a kiss.)
(Soy Milk Maker Manual)
(The machine in the kitchen is new.)
(I chose the simplest one to use.)
(I wrote notes on the manual.)
(Please familiarize yourself
with it soon.)
(Soy Milk Maker Instructions)
(I got rid
of all the sodas in the fridge.)
(No Cold Drinks! More Fruits and Milk.)
(Fruits and milk are ordered daily.)
(They're delivered daily at noon.)
(If you want something else,
call the number on the sticky note.)
(I've sorted out
all the things you bought.)
(Things you'll need soon
are right in front.)
(Postpartum Is Easier This Way)
(I took a few books to study.)
(You can test me when I'm back.)
(I disinfected the pregnancy pillow.)
(Use it when your back hurts.)
(The baby heart monitor
is a bit tricky.)
(I recorded a short video.)
(Remember to check your WeChat.)
(Before entering the bathroom,)
(make sure you change
into anti-slip slippers.)
(If the anti-slip mat's dirty,
call customer support.)
(Don't clean it yourself.)
(I scheduled the cleaner.)
(You're not allowed to do any chores
while I'm gone.)
(Got it?)
(It's my first time wrapping corners.
I'm inexperienced.)
(I ruined the fancy drawer you bought.)
(Please forgive me.)
(There's no signal at sea,)
(but I'll still greet you
good morning and night every day.)
(Your only job)
(is to stay healthy and gain weight.)
(Wait at home with the baby for me.)
(I love you both, Honey.)
79.
80.
81.
You okay?
Get up and walk.
The more you crouch,
the dizzier you'll feel.
We've now reached the training sea zone.
All members, please gather quickly.
Gather!
Yi Nanwang, what are you doing?
Move!
Attention!
Helicopter unit, prepare for flight.
♪The vast sky and sea,
this deep blue expanse♪
♪So deep, so boundless♪
♪Just like your arms♪
♪Shielding me from the dark clouds♪
♪Always bearing it all in silence♪
♪Even the long, long road gives me peace
when you're there♪
♪Not one to show romance
in front of others♪
♪You speak of dreams
with such calm simplicity♪
♪But I know your heart
holds much deeper hopes♪
♪I truly understand♪
♪You speak of love so slowly♪
♪But your eyes have already
told me everything♪
♪Using up all my fortune♪
♪Just to trade a lifetime with you♪
♪Thank you for awakening♪
♪The courage once hidden in my fear♪
♪Turning every chance into certainty♪
♪Turning every tie into companionship♪
♪Blooming into brilliance
for all the years to come♪
♪No one can tear us apart♪
♪Each time my palm feels warmth again♪
♪The memories return,
and I'm no longer alone♪
♪No matter how far
across time and space♪
♪My longing reaches you in silence♪
♪No need to call out loudly♪
♪No matter how much it takes♪
♪To bring this drifting heart to shore♪
♪Thank you for standing behind me♪
♪Lighting up the darkness and despair♪
♪The bigger the world,
the lonelier it feels♪
♪Only by your side♪
♪Can I truly feel this warmth inside♪