You have nobody to wear
That's true
后会哪有时后避
What will you compare including many filme
Beyond the ocean, through evil stuff
We'll still blindfold ourselves
till the day we sociable
With you, I'll be
Blackpink
I'm so hungry.
Chen Jing!
What are you doing?
Wait.
Go to the door.
Go.
You're not alone.
Don't go to the door.
Chen Jing,
you can't open the door.
Go.
Chen Jing,
you can't open the door.
Go.
I can't open the door.
It's open.
It's out.
We're doomed.
It's open.
You're a bad boy.
Don't go.
It's okay.
What's wrong?
It's all right.
The stool is rolling on the ground.
Goodbye.
What's the matter?
It's all over the place.
It's on the ground.
Goodbye.
It's open.
Are you okay?
How did you come back?
The neighbors didn't see me, did they?
No.
I was relieved.
Guo,
the neighbors said you went on the street.
What's so good about going on the street?
Doctor, please save my son.
He's been lying on his head.
He's unconscious.
This...
You're back.
Are you okay?
What's the matter with me?
This old man.
Someone got sick at home.
Well...
You're sick.
Is it serious?
Not serious.
That's good.
Well...
Let's go.
This clothes...
What's going on?
Renyi.
This arrangement is too terrible.
will have something with you.
before the wedding,
I'll rest at home,
and may you go back home to rest.
My dear
A-bu,
have I yet to eat to
feed you?
fordly.
Go quickly,
find his wife to go upstairs to feed him first.
Lord Chaos is taking care of us.
Our step Photoshop Tschu.
Will you go upstairs to do it first?
I can't remember his family.
I finally got a good experience.
And I came here.
I'm so cheap.
I haven't used all the money in the bank card.
I haven't read all the three novels
just finished.
What the hell is this place?
What is this?
And the magic tree.
Can't they really go out?
No.
If they can't do anything,
I'll be mad.
I won't go.
I want to eat a meal.
Just come here at the right time.
I'm not here.
How can I eat?
Sister, you're the best.
This dish is so delicious.
Brother, what's wrong with him?
He was laughing just now.
This is called
the magic short-term comprehensive medical test.
This is only a major blow
in the specific situation.
The memory may completely disappear.
But the basic skills of the body
won't affect.
The behavior
won't be a big problem.
You don't have a seat, do you?
Feng Ni, have a seat.
Just one meal, okay?
I said,
why are you so confused?
I'm not the one who's fast.
Give me a break.
Oh, right.
Just have a good rest.
No big problem.
But don't mention the past.
The memory will be confused easily.
Leave the rest for a while.
I'll be back.
You're so kind today.
How dare you help me?
Sister,
why are you always looking at me?
I just think
you're different from before.
You're different in words and actions.
How could you break the case?
Of course.
I'm also a big fan of you.
How could you break the case?
The past is probably like this.
So our family was released.
It's here.
Why didn't I think of it?
You're so rude.
You even don't know how to hold a cold.
Uncle,
when they were buying the silver,
weren't you at the market?
Oh,
you gave me a bottle of wine.
I didn't know the wine.
I was so thirsty.
I just drank a few cups.
You didn't say anything in the word.
I don't think
it's a small thing.
Small thing?
You almost killed my family.
I'm so stupid.
I won't drink wine again.
Mom,
Mom, you're so sweet.
Why's going wrong again?
I've been saying
it's Yan Z现在's problem.
Just now, I saw brother this time
and said it drank fine.
Jani!
I'm the one who broke the gold.
The Rainbow...
ja, the rainbow is the cake.
It's okay.
His Majesty ordered us to
practice fake sleepiness here.
He said that this thing
is powerful and powerful.
It's a great reward.
But we failed to practice it in a hurry.
We didn't have any progress.
Please, Sister Caiwei,
wait for us to clear the way.
Sister Caiwei,
you've seen the practice fake sleepiness yourself.
Why?
Yes.
It seems that it's not a problem.
But he did practice it.
The legendary practice of the ancient legend,
Shen Ao Hui Si.
It's not that you can learn it
if you say it here.
You need to practice the magic tree
to practice the skills.
I'll teach you a word of the first word.
It's a word of the first word.
Qinghai, Li Pingpong, Danan,
Funan, and Meizhu Guilin.
Qinghai.
What's the meaning of this word?
I don't know what it means.
Anyway,
the word of the first word is Xu Qian.
Xu Pingzhi, the son of the emperor,
ran in the seven-spanning law.
You can find him.
By the way,
the fake silver is from him.
Master.
Cai Wei is here.
What is the golden tree?
I don't know.
There are things that master doesn't know.
That's too much.
Master doesn't know
where the few thieves
went 19 years ago.
Here we go again.
Master, you always say
the thief was hateful 19 years ago.
You can't tell me who they were.
What did they steal recently?
You can't steal anything.
Master.
You know it, but you don't say it.
It hurts to choose a new one.
It's really me.
Well, master.
Your taste.
You can control the past and the future.
It doesn't matter.
Then you must know
why Xu Qian
is the one who knows the golden tree.
This one.
Today is the seventh day of my life.
I've gradually accepted
the reality that I can't go back.
I've accepted this move
but I've thought about my future.
In short,
the team I knew
is in the process.
In this way,
I can plan my life peacefully.
The family of the owner
seems to be nice to me.
Uncle, don't say it.
Take me as your son.
He is a master of seven-digit jade knives.
Xu Qian.
He is a worker in the company.
He lives in an outside house.
His family is a seven-digit jade.
Uncle, you saved us.
You have taken out
the silver in the house.
What should we do?
Yes.
Get up.
Your right leg.
Lift it up.
I'll give you one.
Then remember
to go to the moon last month.
This month?
Last month.
Aunt
is not good at dealing with it.
Like the finance director
of our company.
Two sisters
are good at personality
and can do administrative work.
They are smart and smart.
They are good at everything.
They are good at looking at people.
They are good at understanding.
They are good at being in love.
As for the little sister,
she is a good friend.
Or a good friend.
By the way,
I almost forgot my brother.
He is a scholar.
But he looks
like a man with a bad temper.
He is a man.
He has a thousand gold.
No.
I have to observe him
to prevent him from eating the building.
From now on,
I am not Yang Ling.
I am Xu Xi'an.
In my last life,
I gave up my dream.
And here,
I am the best in the business.
I will
make my dream come true.
How is it?
Are you all clear?
Anyway, this is my plan.
I want to make money.
You have to make money, too.
I know that
I have a bad plan.
You can't understand
the asset management and the contract.
But please don't worry.
I believe in my ability.
Many people
are just not good at
developing themselves.
Mingyue,
the clothes are dirty.
I got it.
Brother,
I heard that you are in
some kind of school, right?
Yunlu School.
How about this?
Get a fund for your brother.
When I am in business,
you can count the money
in your room.
Okay.
Uncle,
I heard that you are a carpenter.
You are not good at business.
You are a carpenter.
Help me.
I want you to be a little antique.
Daodiang,
do you have the money to make money?
Give him some money.
I will give you the money to buy a car.
Okay.
Meizi,
you are in charge of the money in the house.
Be patient.
I will help you to make money.
How about it?
What do you want?
Xu Ningye.
First, don't quarrel.
I am thinking for this family.
Okay.
Mingyue.
Brother,
you have to take care of it.
What do you mean?
You owe this family
tens of years of money.
The rent of your room
is 632.5 yuan.
If you can make this family well,
you can change the clothes for your mother.
You can make money
by making money.
Make money?
It's impossible to make money.
I can't make money in my life.
Uncle,
I just said that you don't understand.
Go to your wife.
Hurry up.
You will deduct money
if you are late.
You...
Meizi,
don't be impulsive.
I didn't hear you.
Help me.
I will make money for you.
You don't need to wash clothes here.
I will wear you.
Lin Yan.
Go to play with Mu Maqian.
Xu Ningye.
Help!
Kill them!
I won't let you go!
No one can stop me from making money.
According to my guess,
today is the 15th year of the year.
It's not far from the end of March.
The business plan is officially starting.
I think
the world is using the blood to build a house.
There is a mirror.
Let's buy a mirror.
I know why
the invention failed.
All the things
were made by the Four Heavens.
Inventions are not allowed.
I can still be injured.
I believe that if there is no longer any medicine,
I can have a bright future.
You'd better think about it.
I have the limit.
Gongzi,
Do you really want to buy it?
You're wrong.
I'm not buying it.
I'm just saying.
I'm not saying I'm not buying it.
So what's your profit?
Just tell me, boss.
The cost is 20,000 yuan.
It's the profit of the five-letter company.
I have another idea.
If I write out the five-letter novel
and the net text,
I can earn money by lying down.
Oh my god.
I give up.
I wrote out a few hundred million
with a pencil.
It's not realistic.
And I can't remember the content of the novel.
Okay.
The plan is temporarily suspended.
Actually, doing business is not that easy.
And it requires jazz.
1,000,000 yuan
Quick‧
Who′es?
Chang Le, keep your hand up,片子 long Philoogic
Fine.
I can go to eyesee the work day.
Blend into a big fan
to discover progress.
This is a beautifulаш so get some money
before you get off work.
Who lost the money?
Let's get some money.
I'm not getting any money.
You're so unlucky.
You can't break the case.
You lost your money.
Don't let me be a fool.
I'll kick you to death.
Xu Qian.
Why are you back?
Isn't it Liu Fangzi?
So...
the case broke?
Ning.
You're so unlucky.
You were in jail for a few days.
You were in the hospital.
You were killed by a broken-up wound.
You're in prison for a day.
You're chasing Wang Butong every day.
He ordered me to break the case.
Wang Butong was in jail.
He couldn't get away.
But don't worry.
Ning.
You weren't there.
It's okay.
I'll ask for your help.
I'll keep you
no matter what.
I'll be honest with you.
How about...
touching the fish?
Touching the fish?
You're touching the fish too?
I mean,
since the case is hard to handle,
it's a job.
It's not a fish.
Please relax.
Relax.
Touching the fish is good.
Ning.
You're right.
It's a job.
It's better to relax.
Don't worry.
We're all
the messengers of the prison.
We're all bad people.
Touching the fish?
You mean, you're looking for the body?
It's a head.
Although they're in prison,
they're not guilty.
You're talking about touching the fish?
How about
giving me the body?
I dare to ask you, Xu Bupai.
Who is the murderer?
Where is he?
The victim, Jiang Yourui,
is in the hospital.
He was left alone in the morning.
He was 20 years younger than himself.
20 years younger?
He's got a brain.
The old cow is really noisy.
Go!
But
the murderer is the one.
How did you two kill Zhang Yourui?
Find him from the pool.
Of course, we didn't kill him.
How could he kill his own father?
Let me ask you.
When the case was closed, where were you?
In the study.
Why didn't you kill him?
I was looking at the pictures.
And the witness.
Where did the witness come from?
Zhang Yang.
You married Zhang Yourui for 10 years.
Why are you pregnant now?
Tell me.
Are you dating the son of the emperor?
You're trying to kill your own father?
My lord.
I'm wronged.
I'm not well.
I was so ill that I couldn't get pregnant.
How could you do this?
My lord.
You said you were pregnant.
You said you saw the man who killed the man.
Why didn't you search the garden today?
You didn't find any footprints.
You didn't find any traces of flowers.
Well...
My lord.
How did the thief get into the house?
How did mother know?
If you can't find out,
you'll be punished by my mother.
You're so polite.
You even turned the tables.
This man looks like a seal.
He even turned the tables.
Guards.
Yes, my lord.
Give me the account book.
My lord.
My lord, you're so cold.
Are you going to fight Chengzhou?
The family is in a hurry.
Of course.
Aren't you afraid of being punished?
How dare you!
What's the meaning of the word?
The meaning...
Can't be used in front of the hall, right?
You...
You're so shy.
Zhu Jianling was going to fight Chengzhou.
Did you see the crowd?
How dare you!
My lord!
We're not the only ones left.
I have a choice.
My lord!
Don't be nervous.
I'm here to help you.
You can call me Xu San.
Xu San?
Yes.
In the evening,
Li Cheng and Jiang Yourui went to the
trial together for the criminals.
Hence, you can cover up the crime
for the criminals.
Re système is a public threshold.
You can put to太 armor
to be blamed.
Everybody will let therap attack you.
My lord,
you can't be so bold.
The line is only the corner of the exit.
There's no corner of the house.
If there's a good way,
the escapee will be able to fund it.
It's impossible to leave the corner.
This is the first.
Second,
Zhang Youwei died in a fight.
He was forced to die.
The scene didn't find the tool to make the case.
It means the murderer was brought along.
Every thief will be punished at any time.
Isn't it a matter of love?
You can't say that.
Third,
when Zhang Youwei died,
the body was on the ground,
with the legs on the court.
The wound was on the back of the head.
This means the murderer was brought along.
So the thief was in the hospital.
And he was behind Zhang Youwei.
If he was a thief,
either he was a secret weapon or he was completely gone.
He was behind the main entrance
while the master was trying to kill him.
How is that possible?
He was almost alive.
The next one is the key.
When I came in,
the county magistrate gave me a statement.
Zhang Xian's statement.
What do you want?
I heard that...
Give me back my bag.
I want to know why you've come in.
I broke thesighs'
które
meeting the ruffial mask.
Why didn't you tell me that?
You forced all the things
that you wanted to do.
You killed the person.
So he wants to give you 500 taels of silver
and pay the price of the people in the family.
Use this statement as a reference
to understand this case.
I just said that I was here to help you.
As long as you confess to the crime,
you will be punished by the late Lord of the Alliance.
You will be punished by the death penalty.
Tang Zhen.
You are so stupid.
How dare you call me a man?
This is my late Lord of the Alliance.
Even if it's the end of the world,
you have no right to interfere.
In the past years,
he dared to use the death penalty
that he was afraid of.
It must be a war.
I was also looking for it.
From Zhang Xian to the late Lord of the Alliance,
Xu Dane went to the Ministry of Justice
and didn't leave yet.
Let's talk about the conclusion.
It's not a good idea to let people go.
I think it's better to let people go first.
This matter can be a big deal.
You mean...
I heard that
Li Yucheng, Li Yingluo,
who was a man of the people,
was just appointed as the late Lord of the Alliance.
If he can make up for this matter,
he might be punished.
I think it's better to let people go.
Zhang Xian, you can go now.
It's delicious.
Let's have a toast.
Cheers.
Here, have a taste.
I've got this
fresh and sweet orange.
Thank you.
Have a taste.
Thank you, Lord.
This case
is not bad.
I also want to
give you a little credit.
How many years have I been doing this?
I've never heard him say this.
Ninth Brother.
Brother Ding.
Let's have a toast.
Ninth Brother.
This case,
you're the head of the company.
Yes.
Thank you, brothers.
Ninth Brother.
You don't look like a man.
We're so capable.
How can you break up with us?
Tell us.
Actually, it's nothing special.
That woman's ears are soft.
She's not surprised.
When she saw it,
when she saw the statement we wrote,
she was shocked.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Come on.
Head.
I heard that Zhang Xian was released.
Mingye.
As a fast-grower,
our duty has been done.
The rest is to be handled by the head.
Can you handle it?
Don't worry.
Come on.
No, no, no.
Wait.
If we can't handle it,
Zhang Yang will be dead.
After all, he provided the statement.
I told you to rest assured.
You put the letter in your stomach.
I saw it.
Chief Xu
has already dared to go to the gas station
with the statement.
Gas station?
What are you doing?
I'm here to see Li Yingluo,
the head of the county department of Changle.
The family is gone.
They are going out to work.
Chief Xu really went to the gas station?
This is the Wan Nian boat of Xiaoxin City.
We thought about a long-distance line,
but it was full of expensive and expensive goods.
Of course, we should be careful.
What is the matter in the gas station?
We can't handle it.
You drank too much.
Where is the big man?
Big man?
The heaven's dance
is a firefly.
You really drank too much.
Where is the big man?
Who is the big man?
The big man.
Go, go, go.
Head.
The big man is the spy.
The heroine is the heroine.
I'm the heroine of Xiaoxin City.
I'm the heroine.
Especially Wei Yingwei.
Wait for me to go back to the water.
Okay.
When you have the chance to see him, you'll know.
My lord, we have a good plan.
Let's reward Mingyu.
I'm so happy.
Let's shake the money.
Head.
You are the rule.
I'm not.
Black.
Yes.
Just like you said.
Shake it.
Boss.
Come and drink some sugar.
Just a little.
Wait a minute.
Well,
take care.
Thank you, boss.
Why are you so quiet?
A group of people from the Five Great Trees
came to the water pool.
And a sip of sugar.
There must be a situation.
Second-class merit.
Take your water.
Be careful.
There is a problem.
The Great Trees are in a hurry.
The law is not allowed.
The court is at 30.
Close the door.
The King of the Trees.
The court is at 50.
Die.
I'm going to...
Ouda Yai entered the prison for three years.
Let's go.
Boss, the ball is here.
The ball is here.
The dead is not dead yet.
Just kill perfection
Kill
Finish
Who's that?
cendo
No.
Come out.
I'm so happy to be back in the top qi class Live until that when I find you
everyone even I met me
I cry
All the time
Hello Daniel
So maybe I can go back
Su plateau
armor hunting did well
the efforts are
I can not run away fromb
a mere plot
You are still a Ogre after all
The first round of the game is over.
The first round of the games is over.
I will sing the song of the past, and sing the song of the future
You are my companion, I will sing the song of the past, and sing the song of the future
The world is not a city, but a place where we can meet
The fate is not fair, but it is not a city
The people are not cruel, they are cruel
Only want me to be the black and white part, and I will be the blue part of the road
Who is he?
I have lost my balance and blame the one for my nature
I lied and don't like to be gentle, and I feel the same as before
I was an abortion girl from North Harlem, and I consider my Lord
Who is he?
I have lost my balance and blame the one for my nature