I'm a friend who has lost all the tears
I'm afraid I'll be a little bit late
I'm curious what I'm talking about
I don't want to think about the future
The whole book in my mouth
Let this bowl of soup and a piece of cake
It's not too much
When you're here
I'll give you the rules
I'll keep my mouth shut
I'll take this big piece of bowl
We're all like a step by step
We're like a step by step
Me and my enemies
We're all together
We're all like a step by step
Everyone appears in my heart
I can't focus my both hands
I'm looking at the disc with too many heart pauses
Looking back, I'm needing more more
The time has passed and my heart wants to change
Don't you dare butterfly
Xiaohou, Xiaohou, Tsinghua, ChupShop
Episode 1
The End
The throat hurts.
I can't take it.
I can't either.
The throat is dry and it hurts.
It might be the virus.
It's a disease.
Episode 1
The End
No.
I'm just a small person.
I think you don't need to hide this.
Can you return the mirror?
Episode 1
Are you all right?
If you're all right, let's go.
I'll be on the road tomorrow.
No.
You've been staying here for so long.
Can you tell me your true name?
Xing Mu Ge Ping.
I'm not a man of your word.
I'm Chen Jing Nan.
You made this?
Yes.
But there are some coincidences.
Tell me.
You can see that the He Xing Cheng Yuan of the Heavenly Emperor
is a long-time member and also a supporter of the Yushu Mirror.
With the name of the Mirror,
No. 1 is now in the capital.
He's a man of the court who is not afraid of the small things.
No. 6, Xing Ge Ge Zhi.
Nice to meet you.
He's a good breakthrough.
No. 3, Ying Jun Xiao Sa.
Xing Ge is a man of the word.
He's a man of the word.
He's really a man of the word.
As for No. 5, No. 7, No. 8,
we've got no discussion on this until now.
No. 2, Li Miao Zhen.
He's in Yun Zhou,
he's hot-tempered and has a good name,
He's called the Flying Pigeon.
No. 4, Chu Yuan Zhen.
He's a big disciple of the Ling Bao Ge.
They're similar in style and have been dating for a long time.
Chu Yuan Zhen.
He's a man of the word.
No. 10, Wei Gong.
Li Miao Zhen is a man of the word.
There's been a long battle between the two.
There must be a battle between the two.
Do you have any questions about the purpose of the Tian Di Society?
Jin Lian said that the first leader is the master of the sect.
So he's the one who's the master of the Tian Di Society.
They've split upmond seedlings have any choosing between the three other?
They convinced them to?
They hope they'll do well in their job in the future.
Secretly możemy.
I still have no idea what'sемoch
What do you think this is about the first?
Yes.
I meant
the position of 먹는 Taoist
as a mayor
may come Laoduo.
From now on in
you may work
in the panel or
with higher audience.
When you need some,
do me a favour!
Yes!
You'veudent enough, I guess.
I've been practicing the juexue for a long time.
I'll ask Li Yu to pick one for you
until the time you're in the Cangjing Pavilion.
Are you using a knife or a sword?
A knife.
When choosing a sword,
you must choose a simple and pure knife.
You don't need to change all the complicated and fancy things.
Remember,
the dancers and other body parts are different.
There are not many gods and demons.
There are only monsters.
So,
the simpler the dancers are, the better.
In the future, you'll understand
the more advanced you are.
Thank you for your help.
The juexue is so good.
It's a good place to play.
Wei Gong asked me to do it.
I can't help it.
This way, please.
No need. Let me do it.
There are 407 knives in the secret library.
They're all here.
I'll go and get them.
Do you want to ask me
which of the most powerful knives in the secret library?
There are two types of juexue.
One is ji and the other is dao.
Don't think about the latter.
The sweet one is not as weak as the strong one.
It's just a person.
This is my Yanxi knife.
Do you want to tell me?
70 or 20?
When you choose,
you must choose the simple and pure knife.
You can't change all the complicated and fancy ones.
Caoer,
I think this knife is too wonderful.
I'm afraid it can't be used in my palace.
Don't say it's you.
Even I'm not fully familiar with the content here.
Choose one yourself.
Yes.
Fire Cloud God Palace.
There's really something like this.
Jiu Long's method.
I'm not good at learning this.
One hundred and thirty-six knives in a juexue.
What kind of knife is this?
It's not that good.
It's not done yet.
Is there a new juexue?
I know.
Two days ago, I sent a juexue to the palace.
I asked the master to make a magic weapon.
I sent it back to the school.
Otherwise, it's like a paper.
Magic weapon?
That's a good idea.
Bro, please bring it here.
I want to study it.
Okay.
One knife.
There's nothing that can't be broken with one knife.
If there is, my suggestion is to run away.
The enemy of the five is the most natural.
How can you run away easily?
One knife is like a heartless fish.
The world can be broken.
When you find something,
kill it.
There is a man who can break your heart in the earth.
He can't save remaining exist for long.
Even if the гр geschengdom of the dropping soils means
in the earth.
Look at this.
It's intentional and elegant.
And i don't get it.
I think...
What exactly would be preserved in the future,
the samänderttening correctivesfect anymore.
One last chance,
Pyre?
Nothing.
Just he.
Earth moon sword?
It is true.
I have told him
to show firm watermelon
Well...
What's the matter?
After Xu Tongluo learned this,
he needs to learn 300 or 200 words,
saying he didn't have enough money to make it up.
I don't think he would want to give it to him.
He should deduct it from his salary.
Yes.
Situ Tianjian.
Teacher,
with Wei Gong's plan,
we should be able to find out
what he's doing.
It's okay.
Anyway,
we can't hide it from him.
I really can't hide it from you.
It's indeed Princess Huaiqing's plan.
I knew it.
It's too coincidental that
she came here today.
I visited Situ Tianjian before.
I followed the witness
and asked her to take care of him.
You know this well,
but you're too much.
You can't tell anyone
about this.
You're not Situ Tianjian.
You're just a spy.
You're not guilty.
About this?
What happened today?
I...
I think I've lost my memory.
I don't remember
what happened today.
I'm here.
I'm here to help you.
I'll treat you to a drink today.
Sit.
Mr. Nian.
Princess Huaiqing
is a noble and virtuous lady.
She's a noble and virtuous lady.
She's a good woman.
She's my wife.
Come on.
I'll drink.
Let's start with the princess.
Thank you for your mercy.
Cheers.
It's your turn.
You're the senior
of the position of the court.
Cheers.
You mean
you're willing to follow me
to reward me?
Of course.
If someone
rewards you more,
and rewards you more,
even if it's not Huaiqing,
will you
be willing to follow me?
How is that possible?
Although I'm not like the master of the treasure,
I know how to repay you.
I won't be the one
who's been cursed by the master.
Don't be so nervous.
I'll just drink.
What if I agree?
You agree?
I agree.
In this case,
you're not the one
who's been cursed by the master.
Are you willing
to follow others?
Let's say so.
What's the condition?
You're willing to
not follow Huaiqing,
but follow others?
I'm not.
I understand.
Why are you leaving?
The princess is looking for a lover.
Why does she have to do that?
Don't worry.
I'll give all my love
to the princess's team
in my heart.
I'll be the one to disturb them.
Girl.
I...
I... I didn't mean that.
Xu Qian,
what are you doing?
I said I didn't mean that.
What... What do you mean?
I just said it casually.
Cacally?
You asked me to change my mind.
It's not a secret.
It's to protect the last image.
I should break up.
I drank the wine and wanted to sing.
I swear.
If I'm a secret,
I'll be the one to take it.
I can't be a fan.
Xu Qian also swear.
I'm worried about the princess.
No matter what,
the sky is long and the sky is wide.
I'll never change.
I'll fight with the princess.
Isn't thatigo bad?
Taisou,
how did she ashamed me?
That's inappropriate.
Shen Hao.
From now on,
I'll be a fanator of the princess.
You can leave now.
We haven't finished drinking yet.
Get out!
Okay.
Then I won't bother you.
You're so sweet.
You're so sweet all day.
Princess, that's not the way.
Xu Qian is so fond of Princess Huaiqing.
Now she can be happy.
Fond of Princess Huaiqing?
Then kill her.
Five-year-old Yuwen, ten-year-old Shunzhu,
a positive experience.
This kid is really sweet.
I'm Xu Qian, the eldest son of the Heavenly Buddha.
I'm a genius.
You're so red-skinned.
I'm just a little bit of a hypocrite.
I'm a little bit of a hypocrite.
Today's show is over.
Happy birthday.
Come to the New Year's Day party.
Open the full of year-long love.
Change your life and become a father and a son-in-law.
The atmosphere in the legend.
He's the best.
All good brands.
Like it, bring it home.
Go to the event.
Go to the red street.
The brand you want.
The price you like.
All at the event.
Take it.
You said that
how can you build that
unbreakable heart between people?
How simple is it?
You take it to the office.
Drink some wine.
It's not possible to keep it.
The other party is too high.
It's not worth it.
Why don't you keep it?
I'll give it to him.
It's not enough.
He's still a hundred percent to me.
Wang Xiao, did you see that?
He's got half of the money.
Take it.
He's working hard for the money.
We're in the wrong place.
If not for him,
he would be the one who's curious.
Boss, I've finished the lunch.
Give me the spoon.
Okay, thank you.
I'll go back to the bar.
I'll go to the second floor.
It's so fragrant.
What's so fragrant?
The money you're giving me
is my money.
I've been giving money to you
all the time.
I'm giving you that 20 silver.
Don't say that.
You're the one.
Write down your name.
Tell me.
Look,
I said that to you.
It's mine.
Really?
Where did you get the money?
I don't know.
What's going on?
Hong Guang is trying to get us.
He's usually in a situation of
surveillance or surveillance.
Maybe that big brother
met a suspicious person.
He ran away.
Hong Guang's distance
should be close to us.
Bro, what's going on?
The bear was killed.
Two colleagues who were responsible for the crime
were also injured.
The thief escaped with a secret place.
He's not in the police station for now.
Pingyuan?
What's the secret?
Why are you standing there?
Hurry up and leave.
Okay, get in.
Everyone,
I'm No. 6.
I'm in the capital.
Can you help me?
No. 6,
what trouble did you encounter?
I was trapped in there.
I was facing
the search of the Dagger.
No.
The Dagger didn't find me.
But in less than an hour,
the number of people in the temple
would be reached.
I'll be in trouble
when I get there.
But my distance is too far.
The border is too long.
Pinghao,
how do you think
I can get through it?
No.
The distance is too far.
There are still Dagger and
the person in the temple.
Besides,
there are still
the city and the city outside.
Do you have a secret weapon?
No.
Pingdao has it.
I can't just send it to you.
Don't worry,
if I can't escape this time,
I'll keep Xiaojing in the place.
You can find the weapon tomorrow.
No. 6,
what nonsense are you talking about?
No. 1,
he's in the capital.
can you help me?
What did you do?
I burned Pingyuanbo.
Sorry,
I can't help you.
No. 1,
I believe that
the same person in the temple
can help you.
No. 6,
I don't think you can do anything.
you helped me once.
I can also help you.
But you have to tell me
why you killed Pingyuanbo.
Why?
If he's a good person,
I'll help him.
I'll take him to the temple.
If he's a bad person,
I can get his trust first.
Until he's in the right place,
I'll give him a fight.
I'll take him to the palace.
I can't do anything anyway.
You can say no,
but you should think it through.
Only I can help you.
No. 6,
since he's willing to do anything,
don't hide it from me.
Right.
You broke into such a big trouble.
You want people to help you,
but you still don't get any sincerity.
A year ago,
my junior disappeared.
I suspect that he was sold by others.
You secretly took the path to send him out of the capital.
I've checked and checked
the market.
I've finally decided to organize a mute organization.
And the behind-the-scenes of this organization
is Pingyuanbo.
So you're the one who killed him?
I went to Pingyuanbo's mansion
and forced my junior to go down to Wei State.
Then I killed him.
I was so guilty.
So you're a criminal.
You can actually report to Pingyuanbo.
You killed him and you don't know the truth.
You're a criminal.
Why don't you report to the police?
Look.
The number one is Li Zhidu.
You're a criminal.
If the report is useful,
I would have died long ago.
I'm a official and a rich man.
I'm a criminal.
This is better than the number six.
I have a reason.
In a year,
I saved many children.
Most of them are disabled,
and have a bad memory.
They suffer from a lot of torture.
They are suffering from a lot of problems.
If they can get some money,
they will have a cold meal.
If they can't get money,
they will only be able to eat a lot.
Then,
where are those children now?
I will take the children to the orphanage.
I found out later that
they were all being controlled by the orphanage.
They came from different places.
The number six,
do you really mean it?
Yes, I do.
Pingyuanbo secretly cultivated the orphanage.
They tried to take revenge on the people in the capital.
They sold the children and women
who came from the orphanage
to the brothels and black-stained rooms.
They couldn't even raise the bandits.
Even the bodies of the disabled
were all killed.
So,
even if I don't have my junior,
I will never let go of Pingyuanbo.
Only by killing him
can I destroy the orphanage.
So that more people
can face the difficulties.
Good.
You killed him well.
You are so useless.
Not bad.
The number six
is the five-time-taste of the orphanage.
No. 3.
If you can save No. 6 this time,
I will owe you the money you saved.
You owe me the money.
No. 3.
I hope you can save the orphanage.
Although the cause is true,
but the death of the nation is serious.
It's hard to save the people
from the gang.
It's even harder to save the people from the south.
No matter who wins,
they will definitely save the people from the south.
You are too many people.
It'll be great trouble
if we go and save
people,
and save people.
No. 6
Listalk coloca
Where is Listalk coloca?
I wanna know their Definitly
I'd like to know
Is there a mistake
I need to check
Have any ideas
Go
Take your dust pack
Commander
Forever
Report
Commander
Han Deru
Here.
Furnace of an attribute puts stating that attachegon of a son.
She might even eat on the land.
Immediately suspected it was a yarn from theervist Support Committee.
Why'd you pick her up?
Gold and steel.
This brother word is theaktik.
Weird.
Why is the sky no longer visible?
I saw it.
Chunfeng took Song Mingfeng,
Chunfeng took Zhu Guangxiao,
and defeated Jiang Jinluo.
Did you find the murder of the murderer?
We searched the street and found it.
I didn't find anything here.
My Lord,
Xue Guang is here.
Are you questioning us?
I dare not.
Have you searched the next place?
I have.
Not yet.
In your portrait they are
assologating to me?
My Lord.
The murderer…
Master,
my Lord.
Let's go.
It seems like a magic weapon.
How could there be a magic weapon in the water?
I think it was a murderer.
Go back to the report.
Yes.
Wait.
Mr. Xu.
You haven't been to the Four Heavens, right?
Brother Song is waiting for you.
Yes.
Mr. Xu,
please come to the Four Heavens to have a tea.
We are waiting for you to ask for the training.
Training?
I'm doing the work.
Okay.
Sir, this is mine.
Yours?
Which hall are you from?
He's from Chunfeng Hall.
His name is Xu Ji'an.
Sir,
this is from Wei Gong.
Can you please come to the Garden Master?
Why are you in the collusion?
I was just making a mess.
Maybe it's
when you were doing the work,
you came out.
Come in.
Sir, if you won't believe me,
you can ask the Wei Gong for purgatory.
Son, he's so cute.
excess interchangeable official刻 squad
We are the jegians of Ordinaryよしolol that know each other.
I've been knowing Wei Gong,
and he may know me.
What?
Brother Song team, you know that point, right?
He went and vegaged 100 years in prison
He's a master of the art of learning.
But what did you know about
what Brother Song said recently?
Xu Ningye is really a master of martial arts.
Tomorrow you go to the Chunfeng Hall
and bring this kid over.
Yes.
Brother Qi, you're so good.
You really give us the whole Chunfeng Hall.
Shut up.
You're a good person.
Why are you afraid of Brother Xu?
He's a little bit nervous.
How can I help you?
Look at him.
Practice martial arts.
We can't do it.
I can't afford it.
I'll run first.
What are you laughing at?
Sir.
Steal the car.
Hurry up and search.
Okay.
Don't laugh.
Hurry up and search.
davonoyer.
Henry,
why do you throw me here?
I'll go get it.
Come on.
It's been a night.
I got nothing.
I caught two little bandits.
Not bad.
At least I can win the prize.
I don't know how I'll win the prize.
I have to go home and report it.
Lin,
do you want to go with me?
I have something to do.
You go back first.
I'll see you at the door.
This guy...
No.
What's wrong?
Is he a stranger?
No.
He's not a stranger.
He's wearing a suit.
He must be
a little different.
His feet are a bit thin.
He's like a grasshopper.
And
he's from that place.
Could it be that...
Not bad.
He must be.
I went to teach Fang Si.
I want to teach Fang Si too.
I'll go tonight.
I'm so tired.
Let's go home and rest.
I don't want to
teach Fang Si at all.
Let's go.
Brothers.
What time is it?
Can we help you?
We've taken care of your paper box.
Now,
we welcome our лousy customer to
I didn't even get a chance to talk.
Why are we in such a hurry?
It's not right.
It's not like it's a big deal.
There's something strange.
It's not good for the shape.
Weiguang, you can't help but be a assistant.
You should die quickly.
Weiguang is like this.
You can't be a good student.
You should be a good student.
I've searched all over the city
with people from the night.
All the famous guest houses
in the city
may not find any traces of the murder.
The White Doctor of Siyan Sword
has also been visited
for the benefit of killing people.
I'm willing to do my best.
You're really a good person.
If you have someone from Siyan Sword
you can let them run away.
Do you know
the various ghosts and snakes in the court
are waiting to see
our brother's effect?
I'm going to send people
to expand the search area.
I'll definitely
take this brother in today's case.
I hope I can get him back safely.
All right.
You've been looking all night.
You're tired too.
You should go back and rest.
Yes.
I dare to ask you
if you can give the legal wife
to him today.
As the saying goes,
I have another thing to report to the Wei Palace.
Father,
I'm willing to do my best
to investigate the case.
I'm afraid I want to find the murderer first
and attack the person who killed him.
I can't find the clues
of the person who killed him.
What can I find
from those bandits?
Greetings, Wei Palace.
Thank you.
I'm Xu Tongluo.
I have a key report.
Father.
Wei Palace,
I have a key report to you.
What?
You want to push us back
with a little coin?
You may leave.
Come up and talk.
Yes.
The case of the world conference
is the choice of Ping Yuanbo.
The one who killed Ping Yuanbo
is the sixth of the world conference.
What's the reason?
You let the criminal go.
You're guilty of the crime.
Are you crazy?
I'm guilty.
I know I'm guilty.
I'm in the dark.
I can't escape from the suspicion.
I'll confess to Wei Palace.
Do you want to kill or release me?
I'll do it.
I'm in a dilemma
with Tong Liao today.
I know
he was punished by His Majesty.
He was arrested by the court.
He was attacked.
If you want to take me to Enzhong,
I...
Shut up.
Enzhong is too much.
Tell me the reason.
Ping Yuanbo is keeping the teeth in the case.
He's trying to get rid of the criminal.
The teeth are deceiving the girl.
He sold her to the brothel.
He sold her to the black kitchen.
He let me be a criminal.
He even killed the body.
Even after I heard it,
I can't stop him.
Get up and talk.
Yes.
Xu Qian.
How much do you know about the Heavenly Emperor?
How much do you know about the Emperor's
and the Heavenly Emperor's death?
Maybe
Ping Yuanbo involved in other things.
the teeth organization
did something
to kill the body.
Have you thought about
all of this?
He asked me to do something.
He really wants to be with me.
No matter what,
don't worry about it.
I'll send others to investigate.
You'll continue to be in the Heavenly Emperor's meeting.
The main goal in the meeting
is to clear everyone's identity.
And
protect yourself.
I'll do my best.
You're so rude.
Tang Tang Jin Luo
was killed by Tong Luo.
He didn't put you in his eyes.
Give me the sword and mask.
You know what he's thinking.
I want to train him.
You know it too.
What do you want?
But he didn't put you in his eyes.
You know it too, right?
But he's in my mind.
That's true.
Good.
Wait for me.
Take care.
I should take it.
You're finally back.
Why are you dressed like this?
I did something.
You can't take the pot in Tang.
I'll figure out a way
to solve the silver.
Sixth.
Sixth, are you safe?
How is it?
Are you safe?
I didn't know about it.
I didn't even dare to ask.
Thank you for
being safe for now.
So...
did Third save you?
Yes.
Thanks to Third,
I could escape.
Why didn't Third show up?
Something happened, right?
Third is the most responsible person.
Nothing happened.
Third.
Sixth, I got the news.
Someone has found the clues
that are unknown.
They will investigate you.
You have to be prepared
and be prepared.
Thank you for the news.
No.
Third saved No. 6
and entered the inner part of the building.
He's really a good guy.
Sixth,
Third is here.
Can you tell us
how you saved him?
Third.
I...
Can I say it?
Why not?
You're a gentleman.
Please.
Okay.
Here's the thing.
Third
gave me a mountain.
He helped me
to stop the sand.
That's right.
But the sand is not enough.
So I have to take No. 6
to a secret inn.
Hide.
That's right.
You're a gentleman.
How did you escape?
Of course I escaped.
Of course,
I found the clue No. 6
and the evidence.
I have to be prepared.
What did you say?
I found No. 6 in advance.
I took his jacket.
I put it on him.
I broke through the door.
I hid in the room.
I was there.
No. 6 was safe.
Right?
No. 6.
Yes.
It seems that
No. 6 is a bit different.
It's okay.
It's amazing.
No. 3
is really interesting.
you hid in the search again.
To be honest,
I'm in the water now.
I searched the whole night.
They still didn't give up on my chase.
Then
do you still have the evidence?
There is only one thing
that Da Ru gave to Rushan.
I gave No. 6.
It seems that I can only wait for the strength
to disappear.
If I was arrested before this,
please rest assured.
I will not let No. 6
and everyone in the world know.
No. 3
for No. 6,
you actually...
You are a dead person.
The plot before No. 6
is to drive people to the grave.
To make the right decision
to the justice of No. 6,
he shouldn't be arrested.
He shouldn't be beaten
by the people inside.
As No. 6's classmate,
I should take these as my responsibility.
Don't worry.
Even if I die,
I will not regret it.
No. 6