What did you mean just now?
That how we met here is not a coincidence?
If this is all true, tonight...
that is, two nights before the student teacher dies,
there was an incident where she suddenly disappeared.
Thankfully, a townsperson found her.
It was revealed that she simply lost her way
so it ended as a small happening. But actually,
she looked like she was being chased by someone.
Do you know where they found her?
By the river.
If it's the closest place from the bus station and village office, it should be about here.
What the—?
Ms. Lee Joo Young!
- Ms. Lee Joo Young...
- No, it's not! It's not me!
What the hell are you guys doing? You all want to die?
Mr. Yoon Hae Joon, it's you again!
Shit.
It's not enough that you failed once. You want to repeat it two or three more times!
You released Go Min Soo?
Why?
I just followed orders.
That's a very responsible thing to say.
Since this is the way you conduct things...
This one mistake must end now, Detective Baek Dong Shik.
If we're not lucky,
someone's life is in danger again because of the punk you released tonight.
Was it Go Min Soo just now?
No way. Could he have again...
No matter what he does, you guys have nothing to say. Right?
It drives me crazy that I had to do such a stupid thing!
Just answer my questions straight.
Was it Go Min Soo just now?
I don't know.
- What? You don't know?
- I could've found out
who it was and what he was going to do if we caught him, but
we don't know anything, thanks to you-know-who.
Of course, even if I knew, I had no intention of sharing it with irresponsible police.
So please, let's not run into each other again.
You just...
lost your way?
Yeah, that's right. I can't see very well at night.
I was scared for no reason.
But you weren't scared for no reason. Right?
There was someone.
He even ran away.
Well, I didn't even know there was anyone.
For someone who didn't know, wasn't that a very specific reaction?
Don't you remember?
You yelled out earlier that it wasn't you.
No, it's not! It's not me!
What's not you?
Has anyone questioned you about anything?
The one who escaped?
Do you know who that was?
I'm not sure what you're talking about.
Ms. Lee Joo Young,
I know it's hard to believe, but I'm trying to help you right now.
We can only prevent what's to come if you tell me honestly.
If you're being chased or threatened by someone, you have to share everything, whatever it is.
- Ms. Lee Joo Young.
- Thank you...
Thank you for your concern, but...
you have a misunderstanding.
I was not chased...
or threatened by anyone ever.
My relatives will be worried. Can I head home now, Mr. Yoon?
Wait a minute.
All right, you should go home for now.
We should go, too, Yoon Young.
Then I'll see you at school tomorrow.
But it's dangerous right now...
Let's get some twisted breadsticks you like.
Why are you talking about twisted bread sticks?
You can tell she's hiding something just by looking at her. How can we send her away like that?
On top of that, she doesn't seem to realize what's going to happen to her in two days.
Wait, but is this the way home?
You wanted to make sure she got home all right.
In case something else happens that I don't know about.
Would there be?
If it's according to what I know, nothing else will happen tonight.
But I don't know if it's the right answer.
Since I don't know what you know and what you don't know.
Although you may feel the same.
Shall we find out? From now on?
Let's go. There's an appropriate place for that.
Raise it together.
- Raise it.
- This way.
To the left. This way. This way.
Here, here. To the left side.
They say the letters fell off last year by lightning.
But seeing how they're only fixing it now,
you can tell how indifferent and irresponsible the boss is.
So it wasn't spelled with "H."  (ㅎ)
That name is already familiar to you.
It's like a hometown for those damn matchboxes.
Done. Turn it on.
♫  I found the meaning of life  ♫
♫  Come to me, darling  ♫
♫  If there's anything you want, I'll give it all to you  ♫
♫  If you have any doubts, just rest your worries  ♫
♫  I'll lead you only down the flower path, so just come to me  ♫
♫  Please hear me out for a little while  ♫
♫  Your gaze that is like the starlight has stolen my heart  ♫
♫  Your love that is like destiny  ♫
I don't know if you already know, but here...
there was a serial murder case in Woojeong Village in 1987.
As you might have guessed, I have been following those cases.
Were you a detective?
If you happened to watch the news on weekend evenings, you'd recognize me.
Were you a criminal?
Perhaps like standing in photo line-ups...
Isn't it reasonable to assume I was an anchorman?
Oh, is that it?
Oh, you were on television. I don't really watch the news. Sorry.
So that's how you viewed me?
Oh, no... It's not like that.
I just have various imaginations.
As someone living off of you, I also want to be safe.
So, because of interviews or something?
Well, something like that.
When will the incident take place?
Two days later, on the 14th.
And then two days after that, on the 16th.
Two women's lives were lost in total and
- on the 20th...
- One person disappeared.
She left a note, so it was treated as a runaway case.
But she actually died.
What did you say just now?
She died.
There were three victims in total.
For more than 30 years, there was no body or any trace whatsoever.
The police, victim, and family all don't know. But how do you...
I know it must be hard to believe, but I...
just told you what was written here.
It's a novel.
Written by Go Mi Sook.
Ms. Go, can't you share a small spoiler from the novel you're currently writing?
Should I say it's a kind of confession?
Confession?
The main character...
reveals everything about a perfect crime that someone committed over 30 years ago.
It was kind of a shame to keep something like that
- to himself all his life.
- Whoa...
But if it was 30 years ago, it must have taken place around the same time as this.
This time, I really wanted to tell my story.
I'm joking. It's all made up.
I wrote the truth all in there.
Oh, of course. Gosh, Ms. Go...
I was the editor in charge of Go Mi Sook's works for a long time.
Go Mi Sook?
That's why I had Go Mi Sook's new novel that hasn't been released to the world yet.
I had completely forgotten about it since I came here.
But ever since I saw the student teacher, I felt a strange familiarity.
So you opened it up again, and the descriptions are the same as the novel?
I never imagined she would write about events that actually took place in real life.
Anyway, that's what it said.
Starting with that student teacher, three women died, and
the real culprit was never caught.
There's mention of a real criminal?
Check the second page. Last sentence of the last paragraph.
"In the end, the truth was never revealed.
The person who made all these deaths happen...
was me.
Not even that delightful truth."
Now that you're not here in this house...
it feels really good.
Do you really think Go Mi Sook did this?
The culprit was never caught in real life, either. Right?
They did catch him.
The culprit denied it until the end, but we can't know the truth.
Right. That's why she said that.
She stole my mom's work for her first novel.
And this was really her story.
Then, this could be considered as new evidence.
We can't make that conclusion.
In any case, this is a novel.
Even if it's based on true events, you can add to it with more imagination.
And here, when she says "I," there's no guarantee she is talking about herself.
But there's no guarantee it's fake, either.
You saw it earlier. She even wrote where the missing student teacher was.
Someone who knows more than you do.
Wouldn't that be the culprit?
Since she lived in the same town,
she could've written down what she heard and saw at the time.
Even if I had investigated, those are all official records.
Why do you keep saying it's not her?
Why do you keep pushing her to be the culprit?
Do you want Go Mi Sook to be the culprit?
You said you knew each other, so why—
That's why I'm suspicious of her.
Go Mi Sook that I know is more than capable of doing that.
What did you just say?
You want to marry me?
What?
When did I...
What? You again?
What? Get married?
You didn't even date each other yet. You're still kids!
No wonder you caused trouble so early on!
When did you even call her out to meet alone?
Yoon Young! What's wrong with you? Why?
What trouble did I cause, you dummy? Seriously!
I never said anything like that!
You said let's have a son and a daughter and live happily ever after!
What?
Soon Ae, do you have a hard time understanding?
When did I say "let's live"? I said I "want to live."
You asked me what my dream is, so...
I said I would like to have a family!
I'm sorry, but I'm already dating someone, so I can't accept your feelings.
- You have what?
- What do you have?
Actually, we are supposed to meet in front in a bit.
Oh! He's there.
That guy is really... your boyfriend?
You said Dad was your first love...
It's true. That's why I came out to tell you.
Then, I'll get going.
And I don't like flowers.
Have a good evening.
Soon Ae!
Shit! Soon Ae!
You need to explain what I just saw.
I was going to tell you eventually.
By chance...
is it your family?
Earlier, when they said "a son and a daughter,"
I'm the one playing the daughter's role.
You are the suspect Baek Hee Seop's daughter?
I'm so scared.
How can I report it?
I cannot get involved with the police!
I don't think I can stay here long, either.
Yeah.
Who could it be that knows who I am?
Oh, okay.
I understand you're very flustered.
I felt like that, too.
It was crazy enough that I was sent back 30 years after a car accident.
But the man who hit me is a time traveler,
my mother's family lives right across from where he lives...
Wow!
So why did you get into school?
And why were you behaving that way at the cafe?
That's a bit complicated.
I was trying to separate my mom and dad at the cafe.
What are you trying to separate?
I was only trying to make sure Mom and Dad never meet, but
the longer I stayed, it became...
- By chance, are you an idiot?
- What?
Fine. Let's say everything is a coincidence.
Let's say you woke up after a car accident and saw your young parents in front of you.
And you thought of separating them?
Did you think about what kind of result that would bring? You may disappear—
So what?
What did you say?
So what if that happened?
You think I don't know that?
One small act can completely change another person's future. You told me on the first day I arrived here.
So what if that happened?
You asked me...
what I was doing by that river before I came here, didn't you?
That day by the river, my mom left us behind.
I didn't have the right to be resentful.
Because maybe we were the ones who abandoned her first.
Loving us without receiving love back like a fool.
She became a name who could be deleted like a fool.
Maybe one day she suddenly realized it.
There were too many moments she couldn't turn back.
It was already too late.
I thought earnestly that day by the river.
If I were given one chance...
It'd be so nice if I could change just one moment in time.
Maybe I just look like an idiot.
But I really don't care what happens to me.
Thinking about the things my mom didn't get to do before she reached that river,
I couldn't bear anything else anyway.
I'm sorry. I wasn't going to tell you all this.
Let's go inside. I think it's best to get some rest tonight.
Yes.
I should have asked him about this.
No way. No way.
That day by the river, my mom left us behind.
You picked it up, by chance?
Exactly when and where?
I just saw it floating in this town's river.
I just picked it up without thinking.
Then, why was that there?
Where did you come from?
There's something you should know.
If it's because of what I said last night, don't worry.
That's just my personal situation. I won't interfere with your work.
For me, "Mom" is not a loving name.
My so-called mom left
without holding me once after giving birth to me.
So I don't really understand a mothers' feelings.
I don't know if there's anything special or loving like others talk about.
I never really wanted to know.
But no matter who it is,
I know there's no way the person receiving love wouldn't know.
You love your mom so much to the point where you don't care what happens to you.
Do you think your mom didn't know that?
- What do you mean...
- Do you think she chose to do that knowing that?
What are you saying...
Listen carefully.
At the first murder scene tomorrow night, an item familiar to you will show up.
A matchbox.
And the note inside.
This...
The police determined it was an indication that the suspect planted it on purpose at the time.
Because the same item was found in the second victim's belongings.
An indication?
Then why was this...
Why was an item used by the suspect from 34 years ago
discovered again in the year 2021?
And why, of all places, was it at the river where your mom died?
Can't be...
There's no definite answer.
All right, so let's just say maybe your mom didn't know
about your feelings and sincerity. But what if...
What if...
your mom ran into someone else by that river that night?
And what if it was the culprit who was never caught 34 years ago?
Then you're making a mistake right now.
You carelessly hated yourself and tried to give up on your life.
Aren't you the one who has to save your mom...
until the very end?
Yoon Young.
You were very surprised yesterday, right? Sorry.
I really wasn't trying to deceive you on purpose and meet Baek Hee Seop.
That's right.
How did I miss this?
I want to play with you forever until I'm an old grandma.
WIth love, Mom.
That wasn't a suicide note. It was a letter.
She was making a promise to me that she'd always be by my side as usual.
How could I have misunderstood that?
How did I...
not realize that even until the end?
Yoon Young.
Are you that disappointed in me?
I'm sorry.
Why are you always sorry when I'm the one who didn't understand you?
No, no, that's not it. I really didn't know.
He had left a note inside the matchbox, asking to meet at Bong Bong Cafe.
Don't worry.
I will make sure...
I'll make sure you never experience something terrible like that ever again.
No matter what. I will protect you.
Thank you, but... is that really that terrible?
I can at least meet to drink juice with him, right?
It's not like I'm going to marry Yoo Beom Ryong.
Ji Eun,
what are they doing?
I don't know.
The grades just came out. Maybe Soon Ae's ranking dropped?
- Thank you.
- You worked hard.
- Mr. Choi.
- Yes.
- Take this and go eat something.
- Yes, thank you!
Yes.
- Yes.
- My son sent this for me from America.
Oh, from America?
- How is it? Doesn't it look luxurious?
- Wow, yes!
Wow, maybe because it's from America, it seems different!
- You can touch it.
- Thank you!
Then you're making a mistake right now.
You carelessly hated yourself and tried to give up on your life.
Geez! My goodness.
I didn't have to confront her so harshly. I should've said it nicely.
Oh, gosh.
Yes, that's right. It's truly a large country.
Since it's a large country, the clothes are large...
and it looks very good.
- Hello.
- You're here.
Why would you throw that out?
Ms. Lee, come here.
I'll give you these precious gummies that traveled 14 hours in a plane.
- Come over.
- Yes.
I didn't tell anyone about last night's incident.
Bring me some while you're there.
Excuse me?
The gummies from America.
I will.
Thank you.
- Isn't that better?
- Definitely, American ones are different.
Here, here. Try one.
Thank you.
- Wow, look at that.
- Is that maybe...
- What's the rank?
- Let me see.
First place?
First place.
Oh, my gosh!
You did this well in school?
Gosh, I'm so proud of you!
How do you place first? Wow, first place!
First place in the entire grade! First place in the entire grade!
- First place in the entire grade!
- Oh, yeah!
Oh my gosh! What happened?
First place!
Hey.
I'm so proud of you!
Wow! What is this?
People who didn't do well would be too sad to go on.
Hey, move.
You pretended as if you did badly on your exam.
Lee Soon Ae always does this, though, doesn't she?
Are you that happy?
Do you want me to write it huge on your forehead?
Are you crazy...
You crazy Kim Hae Kyeong!
- Oh, geez.
- Hey, let's go.
Kim Hae Kyeong!
Hurry up and go inside!
Let's go.
Bring it back!
This school, interestingly... must post only the lower rankings.
Why would she like that punk?
What does she see in him?
Oh, I see.
So this is how the equation works.
This is so fun!
The last place in the entire grade, Yoo Beom Ryong!
Please get a hold of yourself!
Oh, geez.
What do I do with this idiot?
What's wrong?
Good god!
No, it's nothing. That's fine.
I don't want to lose our friendship.
No way.
Things didn't go well yesterday?
Even the flower I gave you didn't work?
What's that?
Why did you go through so much to pick those?
The bought ones are much prettier.
Gosh! Seriously.
Take it.
Girls don't like ones that look pathetic.
Is that so?
But you're really not going to tell me who you're confessing to?
I said I'll tell you if it goes well!
Okay. Fighting!
Thank you.
Hee Seop. Fighting.
Never mind the flower.
So what about you?
Did your girlfriend like it?
Of course! She always says she doesn't like them, but that means she likes them!
Just being coy.
If she says she doesn't like it, it means she doesn't like it.
But didn't you say you're giving her only one?
And you gave me one. What did you do with the other one?
Oh, that?
Well, I used it... for something good.
Hello.
Why are you saying it's not Go Mi Sook?
What if the suspect from this time commits another crime 34 years later
and that was the reason my mom died?
Then I think the more the reason it could be Go Mi Sook.
Yes, that is more than likely.
But then, who is the man who ran away after sneaking a look at the student teacher?
I think that's the guy I've been waiting for.
I've been waiting, thinking the answer lies in Lee Joo Young's route.
Lee Joo Young's movement on the night she was murdered.
​
That night, Lee Joo Young left the school at 10:00 p.m.
She went straight to the Bong Bong Cafe we went to last night.
Welcome.
She came out at 10:30 p.m. after spending 20 minutes inside.
The next destination was, of course, Motel Woojeong.
But that night, Lee Joo Young did not arrive at the motel.
Even at a slow pace, it only takes three minutes from the cafe to the motel.
She disappeared within that short distance.
Until she was found dead the next day.
The suspect was not there within that short distance?
No one saw who she ran into within that distance.
That's why I plan to see that for myself tomorrow.
Same time, same place, and same route.
I'll be right behind Lee Joo Young.
Then I would see that man in the blue cap again.
Blue cap?
The only person Lee Joo Young met during the 20 minutes in the cafe.
She was arguing with someone?
He was a very suspicious character, but the police weren't able to figure it out in the end.
But the guy I followed last night had a blue cap on.
I'm not saying I'm completely eliminating Go Mi Sook.
I'm going to fully consider and watch her.
But it's too early to say anything about Go Mi Sook.
I will definitely catch them here.
That person will not be able to kill anyone both in the years 1987 and 2021.
That's why I came here.
So just have a little faith in me and wait.
That Yoo Beom Ryong, I said I don't like it...
I'll just check if she gets home safe.
Should I go with you?
It's something I should do. It's no big deal.
And... take this.
Don't go alone. Go with your mom and uncle.
Yoon Young, let's go together.
Wow, these are American gummies!
You have a misunderstanding.
I was not chased or threatened by anyone ever.
Her face said she was definitely hiding something.
Let's get some twisted bread sticks you like.
He knew I was following and deliberately made me hear that.
As though he knew that woman would be in danger.
Where are you going, Hyungnim?
Hey, Baek Dong Shik!
Where are you going by yourself?
Yes, there's something I wanted to check.
What are you trying to check?
If you'd bring a scoundrel like the hospital director's son again, please stop. Okay?
- Okay?
- Yes.
There's a new student teacher at Woojeong High, but her situation is a little strange.
I'll go check it out.
Hey!
What's strange?
You didn't know who she was, Hyungnim?
That student teacher has three prior convictions.
We were all pretending not to know. But she's no ordinary person.
It's going to be tonight.
If there's no other variable, it will be tonight.
Is there really nothing I can help with?
This is related to me, too. I can do anything.
I'm used to doing things on my own.
What if there is a variable?
You go ahead.
- Hello.
Don't forget your name tags.
- Over there.
- Hello.
I just asked you what's going on.
I also told you to move.
I wanted to give you a chance to do your part with the little conscience you have left.
But you didn't come here to help Lee Joo Young, did you?
You want me to help someone like that?
Mr. Yoon, you could have been killed because of that woman.
Did you know that?
Hey! Go get her! Don't let her get away.
- Yes!
- Let's go.
Oh, my gosh. My foot.
How is she so fast?
I should have exercised more.
Dad, they really said they'd make me Miss Korea if I just paid 500,000 won!
What kind of crazy talk is that!
Even if you donate 5 million won, there's no way you can be Miss Korea, dummy!
W-Why? What's wrong with me?
Dad, I'm Woojeong Village's Kim Wan Sun.
(Popular, sexy Korean pop singer from the mid-80s to 90s)
I look the same, don't I?
What?
Even the melon is laughing!
So annoying!
Which is the fastest bus to Seoul?
It will be here in five minutes.
- Please give me a token.
- Token?
Wait a bit.
- Hurry, please.
- Why is everyone sweating early in the day?
What?
Shit. Just a moment!
Hey, catch her!
How dare that ugly weasel orders me around!
But since I saw you once before, I'll listen to you, wench!
- Oh, gosh.
- Let go!
- Hey, Ms. Lee.
- Wait a minute.
Let go!
I don't know why you're doing this, but you have to stay here tonight. Okay?
That's how we can catch him.
Probably so.
That Korean teacher is coming, too!
- It was you guys.
- Lee Joo Young.
You think I didn't know you were watching me every night outside my motel?
Even finding me below the bridge that night wasn't a coincidence!
You were planning to hand me over to the police from the start!
You have a misunderstanding.
Please calm down and put down the knife.
I can't trust anyone.
You dirty little moles!
Please, believe me!
We are trying to help you, Lee Joo Young!
Let me go!
Let go!
Lee Joo Young, please!
The police are on their way, so please lower your voice.
Isn't there anywhere we can hide?
Oh, yes! In here!
Go, go.
Are you all right? You're not hurt anywhere?
I'm okay.
Is everything going to be okay?
Yes.
Well, the bus already left, and I don't know who you're talking about.
Yeah. We were here talking about Miss Korea the whole time.
Hello!
I told you, you can't be Miss Korea!
Dad, I told you I'm Woojeong Village's Kim Wan Sun.
- Let's try the motel again.
- Yes.
Yes, sir.
Your dad peeled it for you, little wench!
Geez!
It's all because of me.
An unexpected occurrence happened because of my wrong judgment.
In any case, it will be dangerous to send her to the cafe tonight.
Yes, let's take her somewhere safe for now.
I thought I was alone...
and I was so scared.
I'm sorry.
Will you really be okay going alone?
I'm only going to see his face and come back.
If luck is on my side, even if Lee Joo Young is not there,
he may appear at the same time and same place.
If luck is on your side, please look at the face carefully.
That person will be the suspect who kills my mom 34 years later.
This is nuts.
♫  I found the meaning of life  ♫
♫  Come to me, darling  ♫
♫  If there's anything you want, I'll give it all to you  ♫
♫  If you have any doubts, just rest your worries  ♫
♫  I'll lead you only down the flower path, so just come to me  ♫
The mysterious man in the blue cap, one of the suspects.
Baek Hee Seop, the one most likely the culprit whose route matches.
If the one with the blue cap really is the suspect, it means he killed her mother and his wife.
- The blue cap is your-
- I know.
I saw him myself.
I never thought he was that kind of a person.
He's just one of the suspects.
Are you saying my dad is the one with the blue cap?
What did you say?
No way.
How could this be...
How could you do something like that and just...
Don't come near me!
Don't come any closer!