3 Days
March 8, 8PM
The bill of impeachment introduced.
If I don't stop at this point,
there will be another person who gets sacrificed.
Whenever that happens, I'm going to ask myself again.
"Will you continue on this path?"
The answer is always the same.
I will not give up.
Because I am a President, who gave an oath,
to protect this country's constitution and justice.
I cannot step back.
Until I finish that work, I...
have to be the President of this country.
Until then,
will you be able to protect me?
This is your first actual experience, right?
I... have been doing this for 13 years up to now.
But, it's the same for me.
I am nervous just as much as you are.
Especially... on a day like today.
Ok. Let's start!
When did you exactly hear the election results?
December, 2012
Right now, the Blue House PSS Agents have arrived at the
newly elected President Lee Dong Hwi's house.
As soon as the results were announced
by the National Election Committee,
the same security services given to the current president has started.
Episode 8
You came later than I thought you would.
Congratulations on being elected.
This is the PSS team who will be with you,
from today until the day you finish your term.
You look very young.
How long have you been with the PSS?
He's a rookie PSS Agent, but he has great abilities.
I heard that the PSS Agents can die for the President.
But, you're too young to die instead of me.
I can do that.
You're the first President that I'll be serving.
No matter what happens, I will protect you.
I am the Chief of PSS, Ham Bong Soo.
I am PSS Agent, Kim Han Joon.
I am PSS Agent, Kim Hyo Sung.
I am PSS Agent, Han Tae Kyeong.
Back then, I
thought I had it all.
I had an illusion that I could change the world according to my thoughts.
What I have left now is...
Nothing.
The NIS, the police, the prosecutor,
and even the people inside the Blue House...
I can't trust anyone.
The person I can trust,
is only PSS Agent Han Tae Kyeong.
I am the President, only in name,
but there is something I must do.
Until then,
can you protect... me?
I...
am not sure.
Back then, everything was clear,
but now,
I lost my confidence.
In this state,
I can't remain at the PSS.
I think this is the end for me.
It's not just one.
The NIS material that the Chief Economist
Han Ki Joon investigated,
The army investigation material from then,
that General Kim Ki Beum and Colonel Yang Dae Oh, investigated.
Material from fund manager, Kim Woo Young, who investigated
the source of the slush funds that were delivered to North Korea.
With the evidence that was collected from
the different organizations each person belonged to,
and the confidential documents that each collected,
were what your father had put together,
the file for Confidential Document '98.
He passed away while tying to deliver that to me,
and the Special Prosecutor Choi Ji Yoon.
Your father fought and struggled alone for 16 years.
He told me the truth and won over other people
who shared the same thought.
He didn't know how to give up, even once.
The biggest reason why he did that,
was because more than anything else,
he wanted to be honorable for his son.
Even if you... don't believe me,
please don't question
your father's... sincerity.
Special Prosecutor's
investigation results,
are true.
It's not important what kind of a person the President is.
He was elected by the people.
Why?
Do you want to sit there?
I wouldn't dare.
What do you want?
The Chief of Civil Administration and the Chief of Political Affairs, along with the other office secretaries,
and the employees of the Blue House.
35 people have submitted their resignation letters.
Other employees are also in agreement.
What about you, Chief Secretary?
Why isn't there a resignation letter from you?
I...
will protect you till the end.
We were together in the beginning,
so we should be together at the end as well.
The Prime Minister will soon be arriving back from China.
Do you have any message for him?
Then... I'll be back.
While the impeachment of the President
Lee Dong Hui, is being processed,
Prime Minister Lee Kyeong Wan is returning to Korea
after an unofficial visit to China.
Prime Minister!
They announced an impeachment.
What is your thoughts on it?
Did you know about his criminal activities?
What do you think will happen?
Please give a comment!
What happened with the thing I asked?
It was handled as you had ordered.
This has to be a secret between,
the Director and me.
I know that.
What was the Blue House doing till it got to this point?
We had no choice.
What do you mean you had no choice?
The Special Prosecutor's investigation results
are true.
Are you serious?
You're going to have to prepare to replace the President.
The Republic of Korea's fate,
is hanging on your shoulders.
The Blue House will do our best to help.
And before that,
There is someone who wishes to meet you, Prime Minister.
So, how will Chief Ham Bong Soo's funeral be taken care of?
Ahh... I heard he doesn't have any family members
who can take care of his body.
Chief Ham Bong Soo tried to kill the President.
He even shot his agents himself.
But still, I feel bad for him.
He didn't get married and dedicated himself only to PSS.
So, are you saying that he should be buried at the National Cemetery?
It was a one-time mistake.
He's never wavered in his life,
but this was a one-time mistake.
So . . . Are you regretting it?
You'll still have to shoot if the same situation arises again.
If you can't, you should leave from this position.
Yes.
That's why I'm thinking of doing that.
Tae Kyeong.
Hey, Han Tae Kyeong.
Tae Kyeong, why are you being like this?
Resignation letter
Hand this in for me.
Are you really thinking of leaving the PSS?
Chief Ham Bong Soo, it was his only mistake,
but it was a mistake that should never have been made.
Don't be shaken. It's not like you.
If it were you, what would you have done?
If it was me who made that mistake...
If I was pointing my gun at the President, and you were there...
And if you had to shoot and kill me, how would you have felt?
PSS Agents must protect the President.
You can't waver and you can't think about anything else.
But, I am a human with emotions and a heart.
I won't be able to kill someone
to protect another person again.
So, I have to leave.
♫ In my room that is only full of darkness,
A single ray of sunlight comes in.  ♫
♫ I cover my eyes, and to run away from that light,
I hide in a different space. ♫
I heard you were suspended.
Because of me...
I'm sorry.
It's not finalized yet.
I will prove to the disciplinary committee that my actions were justifiable.
Do you need the report of my father's case
as materials for explanation?
Did you come from the funeral?
I did too.
I came from three funerals.
Commander Kim Ki Beom, Fund Manager Kim Moo Young,
and Colonel Yang Dae Ho.
I wanted to meet with the families of the deceased,
to see if any of the articles that were left behind
could be used as materials for explanation.
So, were you able to gain any?
No,
materials to explain my case weren't what was important.
I want to reveal the truth.
Everything started with your father's incident.
If we start searching from this, we'll find out why
they died and what they were involved in.
Constable Yoon.
Of course, I'm just a Constable from the country side.
But, I will do the best I can.
Resignation letter
Post office receipt
Type: Normal; Weight: 250g; Unit: 1; Cost: 1,800 Won (~$2)
Yangjinri documents
Confidential Document '98 (Chief Economist Han Ki Jun)
Enter password
Father's password is the date of the Yangjinri Incident,
February 6th, 1998.
Confidential Document 98 - Han Ki Joon
1998, February.
Due to about 10 reconnaissance scouts sent from the North,
including civilians, there were 24 casualties
and 19 injuries, becoming one of the worst incidents ever.
I am reporting the dirty truth behind this incident.
The main culprits who concocted the Yangjinri Incident
were high-ranking officials, and chaebols.
With Falcon backing, the first time they contacted
the North was January of 1998.
They met in Beijing, after an unofficial economic cooperation conference with between the South and the North.
January, 1998
Beijing
- Here, please accept my drink.
- We should try to meet more often.
Thank you.
Please accept this drink.
We should do our best to help each other out.
From the North, there were
People's Armed Forces Deputy Chief of Staff Hwang Kyeong Joon .
And People's Armed Forces Deputy Chief of Staff Lee Chul Gyu.
Okay, now shall we actually start the meeting?
Let me ask you straightforwardly.
For the submarine to just go down for a bit and come back up,
is that really all you need?
Would that level of a boat ride seize the people's attention?
I'll also ask straightforwardly.
A submarine and the lives of some tens of people.
How much are they worth?
A downpayment of 10 million dollars. After everything is successfully accomplished, 90 million dollars.
In all, I'll pay 100 million dollars.
All of this is the testimony of
Lee Chul Gyu of People's Armed Forces.
However, there is no evidence to support his testimony.
You're saying this is all true?
I am. The Prosecution has already given indictment
and a written arraignment has been filed.
Then...
He'll be the first incumbent President to stand trial.
Korea is now in crisis.
The citizens are uneasy.
You are the only one that can
control this crisis.
I, just as the law provides,
can only execute duties in lieu of the President.
But, during that time,
you are the number one person in Korea.
As part of the financial world,
I want to be help to you, Prime Minister, whether it be big or small.
For the sake of this country.
He's a typical second-in-command style.
While he is good at doing his job, he doesn't have ambition.
For him, his own safety is important.
We don't know when he'll switch sides.
So, you need to watch him.
There's not much time left until D-Day.
Just until then, we just have to use the Prime Minister well.
Someone asked to give this to you, Chairman Kim Do Jin.
People's Armed Forces Deputy Chief of Staff Lee Chul Gyu was
the first person to testify the truth about the Yangjinri incident to me.
- Asylum?
1998, Nanjing, China
Soon, the government will start its extensive purge.
Professor Han Ki Joon,
you're the only one I can trust from the South.
Wait... But first, give me some time.
There is no time.
What is this?
The Yangjinri Incident, A Unilateral Provocation from the North
Last time, remember the 10 million dollars you gave me?
You mean the fund to provide food for the North?
Do you still believe that lie?
That money was a down payment.
Wh...what do you mean?
It was the price of the people who died here.
That makes no sense!
That was a fund for food.
That was just something that the Americans and South Korean government fabricated.
was a deal to achieve several billion dollar deal
involving weapons.
I'll contact you again after a month.
Then, I'll bring evidence to substantiate what I said.
Until then, please complete my asylum preparation.
Say that again.
You're lying, right?
Answer!
Answer! That's a lie, right?
Why can't you say anything? Answer me!
Answer me!
Dad!
What did you say? What did you say? Talk!
-Dad... stop.
-You're lying, right?
Dad... stop... Please don't. do that.
After that day, I couldn't contact Lee Chul Gyu
and I, through the refugee human rights organizations in Incheon,
started to inquire whether or not he was alive.
However, eventually. Lee Chul Gyu,
during the 1998 purge,
was executed.
Deputy Chief of Staff Lee Chul Gyu?
How would I know that person?
I'm only a restaurant manager.
How many years in prison does a broker for North Korean defectors get?
Gosh... this guy ..
What are you trying to do?
Go back quietly.
You know Chief Han Ki Joon who recently died?
I have all the information he investigated about you.
You said you knew Chief Economist Han Ki Joon?
Yes.
Are you really sure the People's Armed Forces Deputy Chief of Staff was executed?
That man...
That he was executed during the purge,
the rumor spread everywhere.
Then possibly... does anyone here
know him well?
Relative,
or the same department?
Han Ki Joon asked the same thing.
I am Han Ki Joon.
Do you know him by any chance?
Lee Chul Gyu.
There is no one like him here.
Yes, this is Han Tae Kyeong.
Agent, did your father have any acquaintance in Incheon?
Incheon? Why are you suddenly...
What? Where?
Well.. this place is...
Yoon Bo Won was here.
Someone sent me this picture.
1998. North Korea-South Korea Economic Cooperation Meeting
This picture... who...?
This conference was secret. No news article was on this.
Who do you think it was?
This person requested it from the employee.
You!
Major Lee Chul Gyu!
How did he...
Didn't you tell me this definitively back then?
That as the North purged the opposition party,
he was executed.
That he can never say anything again!
There's no dangerous material.
Chief Economist Han Ki Joon was the first one to think about this method.
You also contacted me using the same way.
99 + 06000 = 5578
Haven't you told me?
That you don't feel safe even inside the Blue House.
99, Urgency
06000, 6AM
5578, the point at which I would be
getting in and out of the car for the event at Cheongju Station.
What is the urgent reason for which you have called me out here?
I have met Major Lee Chul Gyu.
from the Ministry of the People's Armed Forces (MPAF) of North Korea.
Major Lee Chul Gyu is deceased.
I checked multiple times through the other organizations.
No. That person is alive.
He's alive, and he's in our country right now.
If you use him, you can do what you're planning to do.
I have issued a search warrant for Lee Chul Gyu as a North Korean spy.
I also called for support.
Since he smuggled himself in from China,
there's a high possibility that he's in Incheon.
What would be the reason he has sent this to me?
If his existence gets revealed,
he would clearly know his life would be in danger.
He probably wants money.
He probably didn't come empty-handed. He must have something worth making a deal with me.
So he contacted me.
And so he should be killed all the more silently and surely.
Lee Chul Gyu was an elite secret agent that the North revered.
He has a lot of experience and is a fast thinker.
If we underestimate him, we'll suffer.
Even if we kill him, it's after we confirm what information he has
that we must kill him.
Why did you change your mind?
Why did you decide to work again?
Someone has said this.
That she wants to reveal the truth.
It's someone who only went through hardships because of this case.
She has no reason to be responsible for this at all.
But she still said that she just wanted to reveal the truth.
After hearing that, I came to know what's really important.
That's why I intend to do the same.
Agent Han Tae Kyeong.
I want to ask one more thing.
Do you trust your fellow agents?
What are you saying?
Is Agent Lee Cha Yeong... someone you can trust?
Yes. She's a trustworthy colleague and friend.
Why... are you asking that?
I just wanted to know what you thought.
Then, be careful.
Briefing on Induction Ceremony of New Employees
Report on Modifications of Safety Personnel
of the Presidential Security Service
Presidential Security Service
09000 + 3595 = rain shower
- Chief Secretary!
- Let's talk later.
This is an urgent matter. The President has asked to hold a special press conference.
A special press conference?
A press conference?
He is probably trying to create public sympathy.
I'll pressure the press and other media
to handle this situation without compromise.
The problem is not the press conference.
He scheduled it without even discussing it with the PR department.
How about the text of the speech? What is he announcing?
There was no talk about that either.
The President wrote it himself.
What's going on?
We have only received the message.
Where is he holding the press conference? In the Chunchugwan (Press Hall) or the Sungjoogwan?
Neither of them. The VIP is planning to hold his press conference outside the Blue House.
Outside?
Press conference for President usually takes place at Chunchugwan in Blue House.
However, why did Lee Dong Hwi
choose to hold his press conference on the outside?
How did it go? Did you find Lee Cheol Gyu?
Yes, we found him.
He was staying long-term at a nearby motel.
However when we arrived, he had already checked out.
So, you can't find him?
Rather than that, there is something more important.
According to the woman in charge of the model, someone came to meet Lee Chul Gyu.
After I asked about their appearance, I showed her a picture.
They were Agent Han Tae Kyeong and the woman police officer.
Then, are you saying he went with them?
Circumstantially, yes.
Lee Chul Gyu is siding with the President.
The PSS and the President are planning something.
What do you mean?
I found a code at the security office.
It's the code that body guards use.
Deceased Chief Han Ki Joon and General Yang Gi Ho
also used this technique to pass information to the president.
I have seen the code book at the investigation for the attempted assassination.
So, exactly what information did they exchange?
0900 + 3595 = Rain shower
0900 is 9 AM
35 is press, 95 is meet. Press conference.
So...
What does "rain shower" (sonahgi) mean?
A guest ("son")
A guest has been prepared for the special press conference today.
What? What is it?
The Blue House can't have outside people.
All the more if it's a North Korean refugee who was smuggled in.
What are you speaking of?
That's why the press conference is outside.
To hold a press conference together
with a guest who is not able to enter the Blue House.
Surely not...
It's true.
Lee Dong Hwi is planning to put Lee Chul Gyu on the stand at the Press Conference.
Lee Chul Gyu
must be blocked.
It's breaking news.
President Lee Dong Hwi is planning to hold a special Press Conference in one hour.
After maintaining silence, what is it that the President wants to say to the people?
The citizens of South Korea will be waiting to hear the voice of the President Lee Dong Hwi.
It's me.
I need the security plan for this event.
I don't need to know how Lee Dong Hwi is getting there.
I need to know which way Lee Chul Gyu will be entering the Press Conference.
The security plan is secured even inside the security.
If they're not the body guards assigned to that day's event, it's impossible to obtain it..
Nothing is impossible.
If they find out what we've done,
Chairman Kwon Jae Yeon's will also becomes a lie.
You wouldn't want the special investigation to start over, would you?
This is the East Entrance.
Lee Chul Gyu is not here yet.
-There's no abnormality, right?
-Right.
There's nothing wrong at the West Entrance, either.
PressConferenceEventSecurityStrategy.hwp
(.hwp is a Korean word processing file.)
You take the left, and you take the right, okay?
Press Conference Event
Performance Team - Security Plans
Exit at the selected points.
Hurry up.
After the meeting, body guards will come soon.
As you know,
taking out the security plan is prohibited.
I know.
This is our secret.
I have the security plan.
I found out Lee Chul Gyu's route.
Let's go.
Other than the place where the President gets off the car, there is another place.
Basement 5, entrance for guests parking lot.
Is there anything strange?
No, there isn't.
They are planning on transporting him in a car with license plate 5198.
Where is Agent Han Tae Kyeong?
He is planning on meeting the security team at basement 5 parking lot at 8:53am and move together.
Did they arrive?
No. They haven't arrived yet.
8:57 AM
Press Room
[President Lee Dong Hwi's Special Press Conference]
9:06 AM
What should we do?
Should we clear out?
No.
Let's start the press conference.
The President is entering.
People of this nation,
I am President Lee Dong Hwi.
It's been awhile. Major Lee Chul Gyu.
The press conference must have started already.
I'm looking forward to what he will say without you,
Major Lee Chul Gyu.
The Special Prosecutor's investigation announcement
on March 6th,
is not the truth.
Are you denying the investigation itself?
Do you not have any connection to the Yangjinri incident?
Do you have concrete evidence to refute the
Special Prosecutor's investigation announcement?
If you use him, you will be able to do the things
you want to accomplish.
What do you mean by using him?
The people you are up against are
people who move the Republic of Korea.
They're monsters without justice, blood, or tears.
You have to be prudent.
Are you saying, I need concrete evidence, that
no one could deny?
Yes. To gain that evidence
I need the President's and the PSS's help.
Yes.
I have the evidence.
What is that?
Can you tell us?
President Lee Dong Hwi Special Press Conference
You sent a picture to me.
Didn't you want to make a deal with me?
I am a business man.
Since you made me move all the way here,
it must be information that is commensurate, right?
What information?
The evidence that you caused the Yangjinri incident?
It's hard to establish that, just with your testimony.
Who will listen to the testimony of a North Korean defector?
I'll give you a new identity and 5 million dollars.
Hand over the evidence you brought with you.
Your words are right.
It will be hard with just testimony from a
North Korean defector.
Unless there is other evidence.
That's why... I became the decoy.
To be exact, it's not evidence,
but a witness.
The evidence that will make it impossible
to deny Lee Chul Gyu's testimony.
We needed a live witness.
March 9th, 9:18 AM
13 hours and 18 minutes after the Bill of Impeachment was introduced to the Assembly
Three Days
This document states that the real culprit
who caused the Yangjinri incident,
is Chairman Kim Do Jin.
Do you have any concrete evidence to
prove those boring scenarios?
The PSS has become a scamming organization
that the President bosses around.
PSS Agent Han Tae Kyeong has become a murderer.
Stop the prosecutor's investigation.
Do you still believe the President?
CEO Kim Do Jin is scheming something else.
The 2nd Yangjinri incident...
Whatever you do, people will die.
Remember this.
Those people are dying because of you.