THIS DRAMA SERIES IS FICTIONAL,
AND IS NOT RELATED IN ANY WAY
TO ACTUAL PLACES, PERSONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, SETTINGS AND EVENTS
(ominous music)
(Bongseok breathing shakily)
BONGSEOK: What?
MOVING
(Bongseok panting)
(Bongseok screaming)
(wind gusting)
(Bongseok panting)
MALE VOICE: Bongseok.
BONGSEOK: Who are you?
BONGSEOK: Are you God?
(whimpers)
(Bongseok screaming)
(crashes)
(panting)
(sighs)
That dream again.
(breathes deeply)
What was that?
(groans)
NAMSAN DONKATSU
(light music)
(knife tapping)
BONGSEOK: Potato.
Mushrooms.
Tofu.
Chopped zucchini.
(Mihyun sighs)
Soybean stew.
(sniffing)
(sizzling)
(sniffs)
Bulgogi?
Kim Bongseok!
Do you want to be late
for your first day of school?
No! Just getting ready!
Bulgogi.
OPENING SOON
Ta-da!
JUWON: Wow.
We're actually doing this.
How do you feel?
Fine. But, Dad, isn't it better
to franchise one of these?
You're starting at a new school.
You sure you don't need
a new uniform for this school?
Mm. It's only for one semester, you know.
I'll just make a deal with my teacher.
Hey, your teacher deserves
your respect, okay?
Uh, wait, here, just in case.
How much do you need?
Don't worry, look,
I'm already running late. Goodbye!
Good luck, hun!
Thanks!
You be careful, all right?
Love you, hun.
Yeah.
(panting)
MIHYUN: I'll increase
the weights later tonight.
(grunts)
I want you to wear two each today.
It's fine, Mom. I'll be careful.
I don't think so. Put them on. Two each.
Strap them tight.
Mom, that's exactly
why I keep losing weight.
They tire me out.
All right, then.
You just be very careful. Okay?
Here.
-Stand. There we go.
-(Bongseok grunts)
Why is it so heavy?
I put more in the backpack, just in case.
Here.
It's okay, I don't have a break today.
Yeah, take it, anyway, just in case. Here.
When you get to the classroom,
hang your bags on either side of the desk,
stay seated as much as possible,
don't let your guard down.
And also, don't fall asleep at all.
Got that?
Why don't you put on two today? Huh?
-Just for today.
-I'm already late!
-Ah, Bongseok... Hey, Bongseok, wait!
-I'm leaving, Mom! Bye!
MIHYUN: Take the weights!
Don't run or you'll trip and fall!
If they bust you for being late,
just say your mom's really sick!
No, no, just say you got hit by a car!
Honey! Good luck!
SUBWAY LINE 9 ROUTE EXTENSION CONSTRUCTION
PRELIMINARY FEASIBILITY PASSED
Hmm...
#ACCIDENT
(uplifting music)
(panting)
Thanks a lot.
HUISOO: Wait, please! Don't leave yet!
-BONGSEOK: Wait for me! Don't leave yet!
-HUISOO: Please wait!
-(Huisoo sighs)
-MACHINE: The balance is insufficient.
-The balance is insufficient.
-Okay,
go add more money and get on the next bus.
It's in 12 minutes.
Then I'll be late for school.
(scoffs)
You're already late, though.
The other students
all hopped on the last one.
Grab the next one.
-Hello, sir.
-Every single day, you say the same thing.
Uh, I'll pay for her, too.
Ooh, quite the gentleman.
MACHINE (beeps): Transfer valid.
Dude, thanks. I'll pay you back.
I owe you 720, then, right?
Oh, no, I transferred from another bus,
so it's already covered.
All right, then.
Why are you...
speaking so casually?
We just met, you know.
Aren't you in high school?
I'm a senior there.
All the students talk in a casual way.
It's cool. It's okay.
I, uh, but it's not good manners,
to be so familiar
when we don't know each other.
Why are you so old-fashioned?
Set your bag down.
Oh!
What's in this?
(groans)
(tense music)
Three-point-one-four-six,
five-nine-three...
Three-point-one-four-six...
Three-point-one-four-six,
five-nine-three...
(thuds)
(groans)
What are you doing?
Three-point-one-four-six,
five-nine-three...
(sighs)
I really should get her
a new uniform for her school.
(groaning)
(breathing heavily)
(sighs)
GANGDONG-GU GUIDE MAP
MIHYUN: I should have put
at least two on him.
Oh, god, I hope
there were no incidents today.
CUSTOMER: Excuse me, are you open?
Oh, yeah!
EPISODE 1: SENIOR YEAR
-(students clamoring)
-ILHWAN: Ten, nine, eight, seven,
-six, five, four, three...
-Don't close the gate!
...two, one!
(speaker chimes)
Hey, you. Sorry, Bongseok.
You're too late!
(panting)
A late student on the first day of school,
and from my class, no less.
I had to run the whole way.
Oh, and I had to eat breakfast, too.
And, uh...
Our home isn't that close.
It's a ways from the main road.
It's a long walk, to the bus.
-And breakfast was very good--
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, enough.
All right. I didn't know you'd come up
with a good excuse. Huh?
You're gonna clean the toilets.
No, I'm... I'm a second-semester senior!
-And?
-Uh, but...
The school rules should be followed
without exceptions.
Right.
(car horn honking)
-Hello.
-RAEHYUK: Yes, hi.
Hey.
RAEHYUK: Slow down, you'll fall.
TEACHER 1: I don't know
what they're talking about.
-RAEHYUK: Morning.
-Hello.
-RAEHYUK: Yes. You're doing great.
-Hello, sir.
-RAEHYUK: Yes, hi.
-Hello.
-RAEHYUK: Hi.
STUDENT 1: Hello.
STUDENT 2: Hello.
STUDENT 3: Hello.
-Yes, hi.
-It was there when you were coming in.
Hmm...
(background chatter)
-STUDENT 4: When?
-STUDENT 5: Just now.
(sniffs)
-You're here, sir.
-RAEHYUK: Mm.
Hey. We could've greeted you outside.
No need.
-(chuckles)
-Mm.
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE
(sniffing)
-RAEHYUK: It's going well, then?
-SUNGWOOK: Yes.
(sniffing)
RAEHYUK: Then why don't we have a look?
Because of security precautions,
we're unable.
(scoffs, sniffles)
-I have jurisdiction over here.
-Yes, I'm aware of that.
Indeed, I suppose security is crucial.
We've only got one semester, anyhow.
(sniffs, clears throat)
I'll see them then, though?
(Raehyuk sniffs, coughs)
RAEHYUK: Ah, don't let me tell you
what to do.
-Hm?
-Yeah.
Your contract is ending soon.
So you should start looking
for something long-term.
-Hm?
-Yes.
-(sniffles)
-Sir. I'll do my best.
Keep taking care of this school. Hm?
Yes.
RAEHYUK: I'm going, then.
All right, goodbye, sir. Take care!
(sighs)
You're not gonna say anything?
Goodbye, sir.
So you're a real teacher now?
(sniffles)
Mm.
(door opens)
You're going?
After I clean this.
(ominous music)
Whoa.
(grunts)
What's wrong?
(sighs)
Go on.
3-3 SMARTPHONE BASKET
(background chatter)
I need your cell phones.
He's Lee Ganghoon, our class president.
The cutest guy in the entire school,
hands down.
The dude's a genius, and he's athletic
and so good-looking,
tall and a really super smart guy
that can just--
-Hey. I have to take your phone.
-What?
This isn't a phone, it's a camera, Lee.
Do you really have to take it away?
Just don't film during math.
Mm-hm.
GANGHOON: Phone, please.
So you see that?
He's about as kind as it gets.
(chuckles)
No. What? No way.
HAN BYUL: Whoa! Whoa!
(Han Byul exclaims)
No way! Oh, my gosh.
That's so freaking cool.
Whoa!
Whoa.
Wow, that was nuts. This is Kim Bongseok.
What's your channel's name again?
Han Byul's SeniorSeniorBong.
Hey, how are you? Kim Bongseok here.
Um, subscribe to SeniorSeniorBong.
Also, like it, and stay tuned,
because I'm subscribing as well.
-All right, thanks. Mm.
-Yeah.
GANGHOON: Okay, everybody, take a seat.
This year's welcome speech
will be a video of the principal.
KISOO: What are you looking at, shithead?
Why are you staring at me, huh?
(sighs)
Sit up straight, okay?
COUNSELING IN SESSION
Come on!
I'll only take scholarships in Seoul.
Yeah. Let me tell you again, huh?
With your current grades,
you might only get a scholarship
at a national college.
Look, if I go any farther,
it'll cost too much,
food, dorms, transportation.
I'll be staying with my dad.
(Ilhwan sighs)
ILHWAN: Let me see here.
Oh! You're good at sports.
What about physical education?
An Art and Phys-Ed College.
Phys-Ed?
Looking at your transcript here,
it's quite good.
And if you get a great score
on the practical exam,
you can get into a four-year
college degree program in Seoul,
and you wouldn't have
to pay an admission fee,
you might even get
a scholarship to that school.
Well, still, a PE degree is tough.
Aren't those elite schools?
They're very expensive.
Not all. You don't need to worry about it.
All you have to do
is basic fitness training.
You know there's a track field outside.
You can train and do athletics here.
There's a lot of equipment sitting there.
I'll make sure that you're the only one
who can use it. I'll support you.
You will?
Why are you so nice to me?
Hey, silly bean.
I'm the teacher, you're the student.
Of course, I'll be nice to you.
Oh, well, thank you, sir.
Can I ask one more question?
Go ahead and ask me anything you want.
Could I wear
another school's uniform instead?
(groans)
I've been teaching for 15 years here.
Uh, you might be the first person
who wants to wear
another school's uniform.
You're a strange one, huh?
JANG HUISOO
Hello. Jang Huisoo here.
Nice to meet you, guys.
ILHWAN: That's it?
Introduce yourself.
Um, I used to live in Taebaek, Gangwon.
But I like eating potatoes and corn,
and there isn't much to do in Gangwon,
it's a small town.
Anyway, one semester left
and we're almost done.
ILHWAN: You can take
that empty seat there.
HUISOO: Okay.
All right, she's a transfer student,
so be nice to her.
-ILHWAN: Don't argue.
-(students greeting)
-Hey.
-ILHWAN: You're all seniors now.
-(students exclaim)
-KISOO: Not for long, though.
ILHWAN: That is true.
All right, quiet down.
Hey, Mr. Lee, come see
the Guidance Counselor.
All right.
TEACHER 2: This statement proves
that aspects of life
are reflected in the language.
Now, based on these facts,
let's take a look
at how the Korean language
has changed over time in different eras
and discuss its future trajectory.
Ancient Korean...
Yian, why don't you read it?
YIAN: Sure.
"Historically, the time periods
of the Korean language are divided."
"The earliest period of Korean
is called Ancient Korean,
commonly used
until the early tenth century..."
(heartbeats)
(gasps)
(panting)
Three-point-one-four-six,
five-nine-three...
Huh?
(breathes nervously)
Three-point-one-four-six,
five-nine-three...
(indistinct PA chatter)
(tense music)
(ominous music)
(sighs)
(exhales deeply)
(suspenseful music)
(beeping)
JEONGWON HIGH SCHOOL
(overlapping chatter)
Jang Huisoo.
Oh, I don't have a phone. Thanks.
No, the teacher,
he told me to show you the auditorium.
HUISOO: He did, really?
GANGHOON: Mm-hm.
Let's go.
-Now?
-GANGHOON: Yep.
Three-point-one-four-six,
five-nine-three...
GYM
(gasps)
This is not the auditorium, is it?
Lots of our PE classes are held in here,
'cause the field is all dirt.
The standing long jump, and sit-ups,
long-distance running...
(gasps)
HUISOO: Vertical jump.
Here, this is the key.
Mr. Choi wanted you to take it.
We have two sets of keys,
so you can have the extra one.
Okay, thanks.
I'll do a few laps before I go.
Mm. Lock up before you leave, huh?
Yep.
(knocks on door)
Yeah?
ILHWAN: Oh.
She said she doesn't have a phone.
She's running around
the auditorium right now.
Okay. That's all.
Sir, Jang Huisoo has an ability?
Is it just like mine?
Yeah, both of you are alike.
We're gonna keep an eye on her. Relax.
Is that it?
Yes.
You should relax.
STUDENT RECORDS
-(urine trickling)
-(sighs)
BONGSEOK: I feel like I could fly.
(sighs)
Hm...
Ah, it's not as dirty as I thought.
I'll be quick.
Now, shall we start?
(panting)
JINCHEON: Okay.
EMPLOYEE 1: Come on, let's get to work.
-Let's work harder!
-JINCHEON: Louder.
-EMPLOYEE 1: Let's work harder!
-Hey, excuse me.
What do you need?
Delivery.
-Just leave it there.
-No, no, no, directly.
Uh, I have to deliver it in person.
Who is it addressed to?
Jincheon.
EMPLOYEE 2: Jincheon?
There's no one here by that name.
You sure that's right?
Guys.
Go have some lunch now.
EMPLOYEE 2:
It's not lunchtime yet, though.
It's time to have lunch, right now!
(tense music)
Jincheon, your name, right?
Hey.
How'd you find that out?
Right there, it's in black and white.
And what is that?
List, retired.
Uh, hm...
You're retired. This is the list.
-A list of retirees?
-Uh-huh.
And so what, there's a list,
what about it, hm?
Why don't you explain exactly
why you've come over here?
In detail, please.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I, uh... Where are my manners?
Oh, now you have manners?
Sometimes I do.
Let me ask you, again.
Why on earth are you here now?
To delete you.
Delete, huh?
Come here, Jincheon.
I have to explain?
Come here.
How dare you talk like that?
Wait, no, you have no manners.
(scoffs)
Hey, come on.
"Hey, come on"? Look at this punk.
Am I your friend now?
Ooh, don't even try, Jincheon.
I've dealt with college punk-ass guys
like you before,
and I know your type well, huh?
-What you need...
-(metal screeching)
...is a good beating.
Wow, do you want to fight, yeah?
It's on, baby. Eat the club!
Whoa. Wait, wait, wait!
Hold on, wait a sec!
-(clattering)
-(Jincheon yells)
(shouting)
Yes, I am Jincheon, you asshole.
(groans)
Have you had enough?
(Jincheon screaming)
(suspenseful music)
(yelling)
-(glass shatters)
-(groans)
(Jincheon whimpering)
(grunts)
Do you have children?
Hm?
(spits)
No, I don't. No, you stupid fucker.
"Stupid fucker"?
You're a second-string asshole.
What'd you say?
You...
(groaning)
(coughing)
You must come back home, stupid fucker!
(glass shatters)
(Jincheon screaming)
(flesh splatters)
(woman screams)
(beeping)
PERSONAL DETAILS
NAME: JANG HUISOO
AUGUST 21, 2018
ASSIGNED HOMEROOM AND COUNSELING...
You knock.
(knocking)
She here?
-Yeah.
-And PE? She's in?
-I'll handle her test.
-I got it.
Um, I teach PE.
-That last thing was--
-I said I got it.
I'm her homeroom teacher.
I'm her co-homeroom teacher.
But you're a temp.
(chuckles)
Then I'll observe the test.
Yeah.
Huh?
Why are you here?
I just cleaned the toilets,
because I was late.
That's why you were acting
so strange today.
You were drinking so much water, too.
Well? You going?
-Yeah. Yeah.
-(Huisoo chuckles)
-But your pants, they're soaked.
-Your bag's heavy, right?
-A little bit, yeah.
-I can... I can carry it for you.
Why? You're not my servant.
You helped me out earlier today,
so I got it.
I'm trying to lose weight, please?
(background chatter)
BONGSEOK: Good afternoon.
Um... Getting on?
Uh, not today, I gotta take another one.
Thanks for carrying this for me.
See you later.
Mm-hm.
-Tomorrow, then.
-BONGSEOK: Yeah.
Hello, sir.
CONSULTANT:
Three hundred fifty thousand for Korean,
four hundred fifty thousand for math,
1.55 million total.
But I can let you sign up for 1.5 million.
The college admission exams
are starting soon,
and if you start at the regular level,
you'll be way behind.
(exhales deeply)
(Mihyun humming)
MIHYUN: There.
He's lost way too much weight.
All right.
(humming)
BONGSEOK: I'm home, Mom.
You're early.
Yeah, it was the first day,
and they let us out really early.
Did something happen at school?
We just started.
(Mihyun groans)
(sighs)
I'm so tired today.
You should try telling
your face that, huh?
Hey, Mom, will you increase
my bag's weights again?
Mm-hm. I'll put some more in tonight.
Mmm!
(Bongseok sighs)
How did it go at school today?
CHEONGSOL CRAM SCHOOL ADMISSION COUNSELING
HUISOO: I'm home.
Oh! Oh!
Hey, honey, you're done early.
Yeah.
I'll help you, Dad.
Oh, no, no, no. I'm all done.
-Dad.
-Huh? It's all done, just rest.
I need money.
Oh, sure.
Of course, sure, yeah.
Transferring to a new school,
and it's your final semester,
yes, of course, you'll need some money.
So, how much do you need?
A hundred and fifty thousand
for a uniform.
Oh.
Why?
So you didn't make a deal
with your teacher?
Sure, let's get you a new one.
I suggested that.
I also, uh, need a uniform for PE.
Sixty thousand.
Just get it now, huh?
I'll give you cash to buy it, okay?
Why are you worried, huh?
(scoffs)
Buy all of them, okay? You had me scared.
Ah.
(water running)
(dog barking in distance)
ILHWAN: A student will transfer here.
Her name's Jang Huisoo.
-Ganghoon: You found her, then.
-ILHWAN: Mm.
ILHWAN: You've waited a while.
You can get close to her.
Jang Huisoo.
HOON'S SUPERMARKET
-(beeping)
-(chuckles)
Ganghoon... Ganghoon...
Ganghoon, you're here.
GANGHOON: Yes, Father.
I'm home.
Hey, I'm home.
GANGHOON'S MOM: Oh, honey, you're back.
How was your day?
-GANGHOON: Good.
-GANGHOON'S MOM: You must be hungry.
-GANGHOON: Yes.
-GANGHOON'S MOM: Let's sit down and eat.
NAMSAN DONKATSU
(Mihyun humming)
Why does he sweat so much at night?
-(humming)
-(beeping)
#MYSTERIOUS DEATHS
(suspenseful music)
SOLEMN DEVOTION SOLELY TO THE PROTECTION
AND HONOR OF OUR NATION
AGENCY FOR NATIONAL SECURITY PLANNING
5TH DEPUTY DIRECTOR MIN YONGJUN
YONGJUN: Jincheon is dead? How?
Fell out a window.
But there were signs
of an attempted strangulation.
Scars on his neck
from broken bones show he was choked,
and we have evidence
of a violent fight in his hideout.
So then, who was it?
WOONKYU: We're still confirming.
(grunts)
The situation is taking a strange turn.
How did we wrap up the case?
We ruled it as an accidental death.
So it won't garner much attention
from the press.
But...
(inhales)
...there is the issue of social media.
We will erase it all,
but it's going to take some time.
(scoffs)
Shit! Fuck, this world has gone to shit.
(breathes deeply)
I had it good in the old days.
Work was exciting, then.
WE WORK IN THE SHADOWS
TO PROTECT THE SUNLIT LAND
And the breeding program?
We finished replanting them, sir.
Let's speed up the cultivation, huh?
WOONKYU: I'll let them know, sir.
POSSIBLE SUMMIT MEETING OF TWO KOREAS
AT THE END OF AUGUST IN PYONGYANG
(sighs)
(tense music)
BONGSEOK: I have a secret.
Mom said I'm just a little different
from other people.
As I got older and gained weight,
I was able to control it a bit on my own.
But even the smallest change in weight
or my emotions affected me a lot.
I always had to control my body
on my own, for my mom.
MIHYUN: Everything that was posted
on social media
has been deleted.
Which can only mean...
that someone is deleting them.
(closing theme music)