THIS DRAMA SERIES IS FICTIONAL,
AND IS NOT RELATED IN ANY WAY
TO ACTUAL PLACES, PERSONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, SETTINGS AND EVENTS
JUWON: He left like that
and I stayed behind.
The ANSP was downsized the next year,
so the Black Team was disbanded.
I was the only one left in the bygone era.
MOVING
WE WORK IN THE SHADOWS
TO PROTECT THE SUNLIT LAND
JUWON: With the reorganization,
I had to get into any department.
(sighs)
JUWON: I couldn't lose my job.
Everything seemed foreign.
I had to make a living.
GENERAL AFFAIRS TEAM 2
JUWON: Excuse me.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
Oh!
Hey, my bag!
Ugh!
Ahh!
JIHEE: Jang Juwon!
Goodness.
Did you leave your bag again?
(sighs)
(chuckles)
(exhales sharply)
You should've stayed home.
Why did you come out?
I was getting groceries.
My goodness.
-JIHEE: Are you hungry?
-Yeah.
Let's have barbecue for dinner.
SANGROK, CIVIL SERVANTS
Here comes the bride and groom.
(both humming "Bridal Chorus")
EPISODE 13: JANG JUWON
-JUWON: Gosh, I'm hungry.
-JIHEE: Go wash up. Let's eat barbecue.
GENERAL AFFAIRS OFFICE
(indistinct chatter)
-I'll take these.
-Okay.
THIS FORMULA HAS AN ERROR
(breathes deeply)
(computer blaring)
THE PROGRAM IS NOT RESPONDING
(sighs)
(Juwon exhales heavily)
JUWON: By the way,
is today a special day?
It's just the day
we eat barbecue once a month.
It feels strange
to eat pork belly without soju.
Why didn't you get any?
What fun is it to drink on my own?
You don't drink alcohol for the fun of it.
You drink it like water.
Have you never been drunk?
I don't get drunk
no matter how much I drink.
Isn't that a good thing?
Not necessarily.
What is it like to get drunk?
It depends.
Sometimes I drink to feel good
and sometimes I drink
to forget something bad.
I wish...
I could get drunk.
Has work been tough?
It's tough...
because it isn't tough.
Do you miss being in the field?
I feel like...
I'm worthless to this world.
(Juwon mumbles)
(coughs)
You have worth to me.
And I have worth to you.
JIHEE: Hmm?
Are you crying again?
(Juwon gulps)
The wrap was too big.
Whatever.
What do we have to worry about?
We have a home we can live in,
we have each other,
we can have barbecue once a month, and...
Anyway, that's all I need.
There's nothing we can't do as a family.
Do what you want.
Do what you want, okay?
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
(light music)
(exhales sharply)
EXTENSION OF RENTAL HOUSING
FOR CIVIL SERVANTS
(keyboard clacking)
(clears throat)
Excuse me.
How do you do this?
Ah.
You live in the rental housing
for civil servants, right?
-Yes.
-You want to continue living there?
Yes.
Then you must apply for this
before the term expires.
How do I do that?
You're renewing this
every two years, aren't you?
Submit your property tax certificate,
family relation certificate,
and most importantly,
include proof of your employment
as a civil servant.
Got it?
(keyboard clacking)
Only...
civil servants can apply for this, right?
EMPLOYEE 1: Of course.
(background chatter)
(exhales deeply)
-JUWON: Ma'am.
-OWNER: Yes?
-JUWON: One more bottle, please.
-OWNER: Yes, sir.
CHOIR (singing national anthem on TV):
♪ Long live Korea, our country ♪
♪ Mugunghwa, three thousand li ♪
♪ Such a glorious land ♪
What are you doing there?
The motion sensor light went out.
(sniffing)
Did you have a drink?
Yeah.
How much?
I drank 24 bottles.
And you aren't drunk?
No.
I want a new bag.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Let's get you a new bag.
JUWON: I'm happy.
That's all that matters.
I'll just live like this.
(calm music)
(keyboard clacking)
-(grunting)
-(passengers clamoring)
Stop pushing.
(calm music)
(sighs)
(mumbles)
(Jihee laughing)
EMPLOYEE 2: Got it.
EMPLOYEE 3: We're on the move.
EMPLOYEE 4:
We're shredding them right now.
EMPLOYEE 5: It's an emergency, sir!
-EMPLOYEE 6: We're on the way.
-EMPLOYEE 7: We're going.
REPORTER 1: Breaking news.
The Ministry of Defense
has discovered
a wrecked North Korean submarine
early yesterday morning in Gangneung.
Based on the tracks left on the beach,
armed spy agents
seem to have infiltrated our borders.
The entire army has been...
Excuse me.
My computer is acting weird.
What should I do?
Restart it.
But everything I wrote will get deleted.
That's why you should've taken
computer courses.
It's not the computer's fault.
See you tomorrow.
(mutters)
(clicks tongue)
(sighs)
AN ERROR HAS OCCURRED
(ominous music)
(Juwon exhales deeply)
YONGJUN: This sure suits you.
A shirt and a tie.
What are you doing here?
What?
Did you think you'd never see me again?
Have you returned to your job?
I'm getting prepared.
I thought you were permanently demoted.
If you know a lot of secrets,
they can't do that to you.
By the way,
do you think this suits you?
Stuck in this office,
staring into your monitor.
Checking the pay scales
to collect your petty salary.
Jeez.
This doesn't show your worth.
Don't you miss the old days?
Back then,
you did things only you could do.
Let me make you an offer.
You're being given a chance.
A chance to prove your worth to the world.
REPORTER 2: North Korea used a submarine
to infiltrate 20 armed spies
into the East Sea this morning.
One was captured,
and eleven committed mass suicide,
but the remaining eight spies escaped.
We have a reporter
at the scene of the incident.
This is Reporter Kim at the scene.
What you are currently seeing...
RESIDENT: Who the hell is smoking?
-(cigarette hisses)
-The smell is going to get everywhere.
REPORTER 2: Under the cliff is the
submarine the armed spies had been on.
These armed spies are estimated
to have arrived at about 1:00 a.m...
(blows air)
(flesh squelches)
(sighs)
JUWON: Do I miss the old days?
Is something on your mind?
No.
Don't think about it too much.
I'll always be by your side.
Do what you want.
(soft music)
REPORTER 3: It has been one week since
the armed spies infiltrated Gangneung.
Of the 26, one was caught.
It's barbecue day, so come home--
REPORTER 3: The bodies were found,
but there has been no concrete progress.
So the search operation
is expected to drag on for some time.
The joint search team
of the military and police
found an armed spy who fled after shooting
near Gimabong, Okgye-myeon,
and started the search operation,
but the search was unsuccessful.
It is estimated that five armed spies
remain on the run...
OCTOBER 1996
INJE, GANGWON-DO
(guns clank)
(rustling)
It was just a water deer.
That scared me.
All right. Rest for five minutes.
SOLDIERS: Yes, sir.
SOLDIER 1: Watch duty.
-To your places.
-SOLDIERS: Yes, sir.
SOLDIER 2: Sir, do you think these guys
already escaped to the North?
They couldn't have slipped through.
It has already been over ten days.
So many have died on our side, too.
By the way, who is the man
all the way in the back?
Who?
Ah.
Don't worry about him.
SOLDIER 2: He was following us
since this morning,
but even the commander left him alone.
He told us to not even speak to him.
He seems to be a civilian.
SOLDIER 1: I heard he's a secret
special agent sent by the government.
-ANSP?
-(shushes)
How would I know the details?
We just do as we're told.
ILHWAN: Secret agents.
Is that even real?
I'm sure that's why he's here.
Get some rest.
SOLDIER 3: Hey, is there any kimchi?
SOLDIER 4: I'll look for some, sir.
-Enjoy the food.
-SOLDIERS: Enjoy the food, sir.
-Enjoy your food, sir.
-You, too.
SOLDIER 1: May I come in?
Yes, come in.
Is there anything I can get for you?
I'm fine.
I thought you might be hungry.
-It's still ho--
-(hissing)
I'm the company commander
of the third special forces brigade.
I was given the orders to work with you.
-Well, I'm...
-It's all right.
I was ordered
not to ask for your identity.
I see.
What is your shoe size?
(mutters)
I wear 280.
Same as me.
I'll lend you my combat boots.
I'll also get you a uniform,
so please wear it.
Your civilian clothing stands out.
It might put our team in danger
during an operation.
I understand.
The noodles will get soggy. Enjoy.
Thank you.
SOLDIER 2:
How can we see the spies with that?
The sound of the helicopter
will scare them away.
It's already been three weeks.
We must do whatever we can.
(gunshots)
-SOLDIER 5: Run!
-SOLDIER 6: At twelve o'clock!
-SOLDIER 7: Hurry!
-SOLDIER 8: At nine o'clock!
-SOLDIER 9: Hurry and move!
-SOLDIER 10: Hurry!
(groaning)
SOLDIER 2: What kind of guys can evade
even the helicopter?
Those fucking North Korean bastards.
(raindrops pattering)
(gloomy music)
SOLDIER 1:
Hands up! If you move, we'll shoot!
-SOLDIER 1: Butterfly!
-RAEHYUK: Railroads!
-RAEHYUK: I'm not someone shady.
-SOLDIER 1: Identify yourself!
RAEHYUK: I'm from the ANSP.
I heard an agent
was already dispatched here.
RAEHYUK: Chief Min sent me.
I heard a lot about you.
I'm Jo Raehyuk. I used to be
in Anti-communist Division Three.
I'm Jang Juwon.
You seem older than me,
so speak comfortably to me.
Rank is all that matters
in an organization.
I'm a Grade Seven Junior Manager.
I worked for 20 years,
but I'm lower than you.
(chuckles)
You said you're
in Anti-communist Division Three?
I used to work there.
But I was replaced
after getting caught
pocketing some public funds.
(chuckles)
Thankfully, Chief Min called me back.
Anyway, I heard legendary stories
about the Black Team
while I was working there.
Back then, I used to wonder
if those stories were real.
Well, I'm honored
to be working with you from now on.
I hope we work well together.
What do you mean, "from now on"?
You didn't know?
Chief Min is trying to restart everything.
We have a very good opportunity.
So we have to make this
a grand success no matter what.
We'll be able to proudly make
a contribution.
This will become the basis
for rebuilding our organization.
(chuckles)
What organization do you mean?
Guryongpo.
Chief Min has been assembling people with
powers that were hidden within the ANSP.
Thanks to that, I have been chosen, too.
Do you have some kind of ability, too?
Heavens, no.
I don't even have a code name.
There's one thing
I have been acknowledged for.
How should I put it?
I'm good at investigating.
Investigating?
Yes. Locating.
I'm very good at locating people.
No matter who it is, I can find them.
Everyone leaves a trace behind, you see.
(Raehyuk scoffs)
Wherever they run away to
or wherever they hide,
I never miss that trace.
(sniffing)
I always pick up on the scent.
Don't worry.
From tomorrow,
all you have to do is follow my lead.
(laughs)
(tense music)
Let's go that way.
Yes, sir.
(exhales deeply)
49TH DAY OF THE SEARCH
NORTHERN PART OF INJE
-Is this the right way?
-Yes.
What are you actually looking for?
I'm looking for traces.
RAEHYUK: Based on the tracks
left on the ice,
they passed this place
about 30 minutes ago.
It's that way.
Wait.
There was something strange
in their tracks.
Something strange?
The one guarding
the rear seems to have powers.
The tracks and the strides are different.
RAEHYUK: That's one person's stride,
but a normal person can't run like that.
A normal person's stride is about 60 cm.
A trained soldier's quick pace stride
is about 90 cm.
But even though it's on ice,
those strides are over two meters.
You don't think...
"If the South has them,
the North can have them, too."
-What?
-Chief Min told me that.
Some of the spies may have powers.
That's why he dispatched you.
That's excessive speculation.
It isn't just speculation.
After July 1994,
we got intel that the North
has been training people with abilities
in response to the South.
We must confirm that now.
That way, we can rebuild the organization
to fight against that.
July 1994 was...
Isn't it strange?
Over 30 military units
were sent to join the search team.
Hundreds of thousands of reservists
were mobilized.
A total of two million searched for them
for over 40 days,
but they all failed to find them.
This is solid evidence
that some of them have powers.
Let's go after a little while.
(yelps)
It'll only take a moment.
The truth is, they only passed here
about ten minutes ago.
There will soon be a shoot-out.
-What?
-Wait.
Did you forget?
We must proudly accomplish something.
Our accomplishment will shine
when we do something normal people can't.
We must show up
when the normal people are in danger.
Wouldn't that be more dramatic?
What the fuck are you saying, you bastard?
(suspenseful music)
(gunshot)
SOLDIER 1: Get down!
Open fire!
(gunshots)
(distant shouting)
SOLDIER 1: Spread out and fire!
Keep firing!
(groans)
(gunshots)
SOLDIER 1: Fire!
Keep firing!
(suspenseful music)
Cover him!
SOLDIERS: Cover him!
Charge!
SOLDIERS: Charge!
-SOLDIER 1: Hold fire!
-(groans)
Are you okay?
SOLDIERS: Hold fire!
Grenade!
(soldiers shouting)
(explosion)
(grunting)
What? No way.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
(groans)
SOLDIERS: Sir!
Eleven o'clock mortar fire!
(blasts)
(flesh squelches)
SOLDIER 11: Rockslide!
SOLDIERS: Run!
Charge!
(soldiers shouting)
(rocks rumbling)
Watch out!
(background grunt)
(exhales deeply)
(soldiers screaming)
(panting)
Rocks falling! Watch out!
So you're the one with abilities.
The South continues
to train sons of bitches.
(grunts)
(suspenseful music)
(screams)
(groans)
(sighs)
I will come back
and seek revenge for the Republic.
(panting)
(exhales heavily)
What a shame about our accomplishment.
Is your face okay? How was that guy?
So there really was
a strange guy as I said.
It's a shame that we lost him,
but it's fine
since we confirmed his existence.
(Raehyuk sniffs)
We have a reason
to rebuild the organization.
(chuckles)
Don't let me see you ever again.
I'll kill you.
(sniffs)
(somber music)
REPORTER 4: During the operation,
13 armed spies were killed,
11 were found dead,
and one was captured alive,
while our forces lost 21 in the battle
including three colonel-level officers,
seven noncommissioned officers,
and 11 enlisted men, and 31 were wounded.
Meanwhile, there's no trace
of one armed spy who didn't get caught.
Our military is contemplating
whether the remaining armed spy...
You fixed the light.
(TV chatter)
JIHEE: I did.
(soft music)
Thank you for coming back.
(sobbing)
I want some ramyeon.
YONGJUN (in English): Hey, Mark.
(in Korean) Why didn't you tell me
that the North
was training people with powers?
(in English) If you knew,
there might have been
an unforeseen skirmish.
(in Korean) An unforeseen skirmish?
(snickers)
I suppose so.
MANY HIDDEN ASPECTS
IN THE MOP-UP OPERATION OF ARMED SPIES
YONGJUN: We have confirmation
of the enemy's existence.
He was treated as missing,
but there's a much higher possibility
that he returned to North Korea.
As long as we know the enemy's existence,
I'll be returning to the central soon.
And you will be forming
a new Black Team under my command.
Guryongpo, who played an active role
in this operation, will take the lead.
He's an original member.
Say hello to each other.
I'm Bongpyeong.
I was part of Team Mirim,
which is now disbanded.
I'm old, but I don't have
a lot of experience in the field.
I'm Naju.
I was in Mr. Shin's
Overseas Operations Team Two.
I heard that there was
an amazing character
among the original members.
I'm Jincheon.
I'm Jang Juwon.
JINCHEON: I used to catch
communist college students
back when I was at
the Anti-communist Investigative Office.
But there was a small incident
that got me demoted.
I'm fine in every other way,
but sometimes I just can't control
my own strength.
-(hand crunching)
-(grunting)
(Jincheon groans)
(ominous music)
Consider yourself lucky.
(door shuts)
(scoffs)
(chuckles)
(door shuts)
(breathes deeply)
(somber music)
JIHEE: Another business trip?
I'll find out when I get there.
It's barbecue day, though.
(Juwon sighs)
Let's have it later.
I'm off.
It's only once a month.
Do you know what "once a month" means?
(scoffs)
We get to eat barbecue?
We can actually eat barbecue any day.
Then what is it?
On that day, I hoped you wouldn't
work late and come home early.
That's why I lured you with barbecue.
What kind of day is it?
It's my ovulation day.
You didn't know, did you?
Did you want to have a baby?
But I couldn't get pregnant.
We've been together for a long time.
I became more and more desperate.
I wanted to have a daughter
that took after you.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I couldn't bring myself to tell you.
Why not?
(sobs)
Because I thought it was my fault.
What?
Don't you remember where and how we met?
I wondered if this is all because...
I lived like that.
(somber music)
(sobs)
I'm sorry.
(lively music)
Bye, Dad.
Daddy.
ON A BUSINESS TRIP
-Let's say goodbye.
-Have a safe trip, Dad.
It's for the country.
Do it with a sense of duty.
(lively music)
JIHEE: Let's say goodbye.
-Have a safe trip, Dad.
-Have a safe trip.
Huisoo.
(smooches)
Shall we eat something yummy?
What should we eat?
ENTERING KOREA
(background chatter)
Anyway, where did our great leader
run to in such a rush?
His phone battery died,
so I guess he went to call his family.
(scoffs)
Despite the way he looks,
he cares deeply for his family.
I want to go back
and see my daughter, too.
Jeez. I'm not close to my son.
We've been chosen as the Black Team
by our country.
Why do we worry about our families
like civilians?
JUWON: Yes.
Yes.
(tense music)
(siren wailing)
EMERGENCY PATIENT ENTRANCE
(breathing heavily)
(somber music)
(Juwon sobbing)
(Juwon wailing)
(wailing continues)
(somber music)
DEEPEST CONDOLENCES
CHIEF MOURNER OF THE LATE HWANG JIHEE
(wailing)
(Juwon sobs)
(exhales heavily)
I'm here.
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of Huisoo.
(sobbing)
(closing theme music)