He is an indisputable presence in front of outsiders.
When did you start lying to me?
Since I started working here... but
I just always wait for you
Wait until you confess everything to me on your own.
I'm very afraid.
The truth, when spoken
I might not be able to stay at this company anymore.
I'm going to pour myself a cup of coffee.
Can someone like me get close to you?
From now on, you are mine.
What happened to the data stolen by xiaoya?
Mr. Tanaka, I have obtained the information you requested.
Have someone steal the information and then report him.
What happen to you
Don't let that quietly growing fondness slip away
undermine our plans
When you're not around
Xiaoya frequently evades the security system
Abnormal number of logins to the backend
What are you up to?
Never mind. Go tell him what to do next.
leiji
How come you answered the phone?
I knew you and Mr. Tanaka were on the same side.
Tell Tanaka
I am prepared to withdraw from this bid.
By the way, I'll tell you too.
I will protect Xiaoya.
Just like how I take care of every dessert I make.
I hope
You can meet someone who like you
Why do you want me to give away the real recipe?
The recipe can be copied.
Expect you
No one can take away my heartbeat at that moment.
That is my unique magic.
The most important thing is temperature
At that time, I thought he was a very cold-hearted person.
With temperature
Only then can hearts truly connect.
Until I discovered
He just hides his feelings.
Your handwriting is beautiful.
Very steady hands
Very suitable for desserts