[Love of the Divine Tree]
[Episode 2]
[Eternal Sect]
[The dungeon of Eternal Sect]
Tell me!
What's your name?
Who ordered you to come to
Mount Eternal in disguise?
Tell me!
Take him to the Exorcising Tower tomorrow.
Let the sovereign interrogate him!
Yes!
You're so tough.
I really wonder who you are.
[Prince Zong's residence]
Brother.
Brother!
Alright, stop crying.
Thank you, Master Mu,
for stepping in
and saving my son's life.
You've done us a great favor.
I truly don't know how to repay such kindness.
I just returned Yu's favor.
It's no big deal.
Miss,
you're so good.
Brother,
you should marry
Miss Mu soon.
Master Mu, please forgive him.
My son's just a little boy.
He spoke out of turn.
He's just a kid.
Maids.
Take them both
inside to rest.
Have a good rest.
Qingge.
Father prepared a banquet
to thank you.
Why are you leaving so soon?
I need to take someone important
as my disciple.
But…
If something comes up,
just go to Mount Wester to find me.
Qingge.
I want to stay in the capital.
You've always loved lively places.
Mount Wester is indeed a bit boring.
Okay.
You can stay.
Take this jade whistle.
If you're in danger, blow it.
I'll come to your aid right away.
Then I'll take my leave.
Are you here to interrogate me, Sovereign?
You've suffered all night.
Have some water first.
Sovereign,
you're showing me mercy.
I already know everything.
No need for further interrogation.
Su Yishui,
how is
Prince Ping doing?
How did you…
You're so talented,
yet you've intentionally hidden your strength.
Every time you left the mountain for training,
you spent a few days in the capital.
You're such a special disciple.
I just needed to pay a bit of attention
to uncover the truth of your identity.
Sovereign,
I did that
only for cultivation.
Heavenly Sects can't get involved in mortal affairs.
They don't accept nobles.
That's why I hid my identity.
At this point,
you don't need
to keep lying.
This is my token as the sovereign.
If you wish to go to the library,
just agree to one thing.
What is it?
As a Heavenly One,
I don't ask for much in life.
Aside from completing cultivation,
all I wish for is a worthy successor.
From the day you came to Mount Eternal,
I've had the intention
to take you as my direct disciple.
Unfortunately, you've hidden too much,
and I couldn't just expose you for no reason.
Now that we've put it on the table,
it's actually a good thing.
Yishui,
if you're willing to kneel down,
drip your blood onto the jade tablet,
and swear a soul oath
that you'll join my sect
and never betray it,
you can
take this token.
From now on,
I'll teach you
all the Heavenly arts I know.
What do you say?
I hereby take a soul oath.
From today on,
I'll join your sect,
focus on cultivation, and never betray it.
Good boy.
You've made the soul oath.
Serve me a cup of tea,
and you'll officially be my disciple.
Don't give up halfway.
You…
You tricked me!
So what?
I'll kill you!
You lost the bet and tried to back out.
I'm just claiming my wager.
Alright.
Hurry up and offer me the tea.
No way!
You'll offer me the tea as my disciple.
There's no escaping it.
Done.
From now on,
you're my disciple.
Shui,
let's go back to Mount Wester.
Don't waste your energy.
Blood in the jade tablet; soul bound to the sect.
It's useless.
The demoness, Mu Qingge!
How dare you break into the prison?
Thank that old man Kaiyuan for me
for giving me
such a pretty disciple.
Go report to Master!
Yes.
Master, what should we do?
Senior Kaiyuan,
I knew something was wrong.
Su Cheng has always been upright.
How could he suddenly steal books?
It seems
he was forced by that demoness.
We should go to Mount Wester to rescue him right away.
But Su Cheng
has become
Mu Qingge's disciple.
Whether he was forced
or not,
since he's made his choice,
he's no longer an Eternal.
So what reason do I have
to go to Mount Wester and demand him back?
Besides,
he did sneak into
the library,
breaking the sect's rules.
His life and death
are no longer our concern.
This is my Mount Wester.
Master. Master. Master.
Master's back.
Master, you're finally back!
Why were you gone so long?
You're collecting pretty boys everywhere.
So dissolute.
Master,
who is this?
This is your new fellow disciple,
Su Yishui.
Master,
after being away so long,
you brought back a new disciple.
Come on.
Let us give you a tour.
From now on,
we'll train together
under Master.
Let's go.
Mu Qingge!
You want to hurt people again?
I'll kill whoever dares
to touch me!
I'll seal your power for now.
Zeng Yi.
[Zeng Yi, disciple of Mu Qingge]
Yes.
Take him to his room.
Junior Su,
I'm your 14th senior brother.
Come with me.
[Wang Suizhi, Mu Qingge's disciple]
Master.
I
read Junior Su's fortune.
It's not good.
He might even
drag you down.
Suizhi, I know you're good at reading fortunes,
but if I can
keep this talented little brat
here in Mount Wester,
wouldn't it make me
look impressive?
[Carefree Pavilion]
Well,
Master said
you've suffered internal injuries
which caused a lot of stagnant blood.
She wants you to take those medicines
and then take a herbal bath.
Get lost!
I've been waiting for a long time.
Turns out you still haven't cleaned yourself up.
You vicious demoness,
I won't give in to you!
So you know I'm a demoness.
Then why aren't you behaving?
Just kill me already!
You're so handsome.
It would be a shame to kill you.
I'd rather keep you around just to look at.
Good.
This way,
I can see clearly
and get things done.
I knew it.
The Eternals tortured you,
but the wounds should be external
instead of internal.
So it's the Bone-Eroding Fire.
Is it a punishment from Prince Ping?
Your face is so cold
it's practically frozen,
but there's still a trace of warmth inside.
You locked Second Young Master up and didn't kill him.
No wonder Prince Ping punished you.
Who are you?
Please don't kill me!
Sir, I beg you.
Don't come any closer.
I have longans.
Please, don't kill me. I beg you.
I'll give you all of it. Look.
Dried longan!
It's really tasty. I'll give you all of it.
Please don't kill me, okay?
Get up.
Come with me.
I sent you to Eternal Sect to learn immortal arts.
I told you to kill a kid, yet you lost him.
Yishui.
Whether what you said is true or not doesn't matter,
but there's one thing you need to remember:
if you can't carry out
my orders,
you'll wish you were dead.
Young Master,
sorry for the offense.
Am I right?
It's none of your business.
I helped you force the boiling blood out,
yet you're still so rude.
Take your clothes off.
Get changed.
Do you want to live here
covered in blood?
Stop looking at me like that.
You really think my disciples
are all my toy boys?
They're your disciples,
but none of them are powerful.
If they aren't toy boys, what are they?
Lyu Yuan excels in music.
Jiang Huaimu loves plants.
Wang Suizhi can read fortunes.
Zeng Yi loves crafting magical tools.
Each of my disciples
has their own unique talent,
but none are skilled in martial arts.
In other Heavenly Sects,
they'd be considered losers.
What a waste that would be.
I brought them to Mount Wester
and got a group
of interesting disciples.
Stop justifying yourself.
You received them
only because they're good-looking.
Once they become my disciples,
even if they cause a huge disaster,
I'll take responsibility for them.
So what's wrong with me
picking the pretty ones?
So everything you did before
was just to toy with me?
Shui.
Everything you did
was arranged by Prince Ping,
right?
You're so talented.
Why settle to be a pawn?
Don't you think it's a waste?
How do you know I'm the pawn
and not the mastermind?
Before I become
the strongest,
there's always no choice.
But one day,
I'll have them
in the palm of my hands.
The obsession with becoming the strongest
will only bind you with desire.
In the end,
you won't even be able to control yourself.
That way,
you'll lose yourself easily.
Don't lecture me
with pointless words.
Tell me.
Why do you insist on
taking me as your disciple?
Because for all these years,
you're the only one I've encountered
with the Five Spirit Roots.
You're the most suitable to be my successor.
Second,
you have too much bloodlust.
If I hadn't met you, you could just stay that way.
But since I've met you,
I have to teach you properly.
If I leave you unchecked,
you'll end up killing indiscriminately
and wreaking havoc.
I've made it quite clear, haven't I?
Then let's see how long you can trap me
in Mount Wester.
I'll kill those
I want to kill sooner or later.
I see.
That's easy.
I, Mu Qingge, sovereign of Wester Sect,
free my disciple, Su Yishui,
from power restraints
and the constraints
of the jade tablet.
He can try to take my life.
You want me to kill you?
Since you're so eager to kill,
then I'll bear that killing intent.
From now on,
you can use
all kinds of methods to kill me.
If you're not powerful enough
or lack skills,
I'll teach you.
As long as you kill me, your master,
you can break the soul oath
and leave Mount Wester.
Don't regret it!
Your sword moves are too direct.
Trying to kill me has a price.
Every failed attempt
comes with a punishment.
Killing me by injuring yourself?
Do you have a death wish?
I just want to kill you.
You brat,
you're cruel to others,
but even more so to yourself.
You need a different punishment.
What do you mean?
Play the qin for me.
What kind of punishment is this?
It's nothing for others,
but for you, it's a heavy punishment.
I won't play.
Then I'll take your sword.
From now on, you can only play the qin.
Being a qin player wouldn't be so bad.
This piece is called "Drunk Breeze."
Learn it for me.
It's a beautiful melody,
but you're playing it like a war song
that's full of blood and killing.
Your temperament needs improving.
Come with me.
Mu Qingge.
What exactly do you want to do?
Killing intent needs to be suppressed.
Take care of
these little things.
If they lose one hair,
you'll play ten more qin pieces.
Is Junior Su
really going to play the qin all night?
He fed the rabbits and chickens
and played the qin all night.
Don't mess with him.
I made some sweets just for you.
I saw that you had
sea salt dried longans in your bag,
so I thought you might like it.
I tried making some for you.
Since you came here,
you've been beaten up seven times.
Here,
seven pieces as compensation.
Go ahead.
Try them.
What?
They're that bad?
I swear, I'll kill you!
[Uncle Ye Xin's residence, Puxin Village]
Qingge.
You promised to come back every three months
to visit Uncle Ye Xin.
You were almost late.
But didn't I make it just in time?
Where's Uncle Ye Xin?
Being late doesn't matter.
I'm happy enough
that you still remember me.
Chestnut cakes!
Years ago,
when I found you by the roadside,
you were both hungry
[Ye Xin, a cultivator]
and crying.
So many years have passed.
I can't believe
you've grown up so much.
Qingge,
I heard you took on a disciple.
What kind of person is he?
The youngest son of Prince Ping,
a rebellious lad.
I heard he's tough.
How do you plan to train him?
First, I'll tame his killing intent.
Then, I'll teach him the true Heavenly arts
and help him form his Golden Core.
That way, the universe
will have another righteous immortal master.
Taking him as your disciple
will involve the imperial family.
Do you
favor Prince Ping?
Of course not.
Prince Ping is ruthless
and quite infamous.
On the contrary, Yu's father,
Prince Zong,
is a kind-hearted
and well-respected prince.
But I don't care about all that.
I felt like taking on a disciple, so I did.
But this could be troublesome.
A few days ago, I had your fortune read.
The reading showed
a rising sun,
but suddenly, dark clouds covered it.
Qingge,
now that your cultivation is complete,
you should follow the will of heaven
and ascend as soon as possible.
Taking Su Yishui as your disciple
might bring you trouble.
Thank you for the warning.
But even if there is trouble,
I'll face it as it comes.
Ascension
sounds so lonely.
The immortals up there
must be so bored.
I prefer to live freely in the mortal world.
Eating, drinking, playing,
and having a rebellious disciple to train.
How interesting!
There are people I care about in the mortal world.
I can't bear to leave them.
Caring for others
sometimes becomes a burden.
If Su Yishui can't be changed,
what will you
do to him?
I'll have no choice
but to kill him myself.
I'm afraid you can't bring yourself
to do that.
You're always protective of those close to you.
You like
to take everyone under your protection.
But you need to understand that
everyone has their own fate.
Sometimes,
you can save a person
but can't change their fate.
Don't let yourself get caught up in it.
I won't.
Never mind.
I know,
sometimes
there's no convincing you.
I've been living here for so long.
I'm getting tired.
It's time to go out.
Where are you going?
I'll just wander around
and see
the interesting mortal world you mentioned.
Your power has greatly improved.
Hurry up and meditate to channel it.
Direct your power to the acupoints Bing Fen,
Xia Bai,
and Yao Yu.
What are you waiting for?
Do as I say.
When did you leave sword energy in my body?
Your sword moves are too direct.
Focus.
The qin melody is the melody of the heart.
Align your spiritual power
with the rhythm of "Drunk Breeze."
Concentrate your power.
Alright.
Your power has solidified.
You've passed the final test.
When it's time,
you can form your Golden Core.
So, you previously punished me to...
The punishment isn't over yet.
Have a rest.
There's more to come tomorrow.
Father.
It's been so long.
If I hadn't
activated the Spirit Spring in your body,
you probably
wouldn't have come down the mountain to see me.
I didn't know
about your arrival.
Is that so?
Don't forget.
With the Spirit Spring
I injected into your body,
I can control you.
This Heavenly Bottle
is the container of the Spirit Spring.
With just a slight shake,
I can stir the Spirit Spring inside you,
causing you unbearable pain.
So,
don't try to play tricks on me.
I wouldn't dare.
Do you know
by switching to Wester Sect,
you've exposed your identity?
The Eternals have been asking me
why I messed with the Heavenly Sects.
I know.
Then why did you go to Mount Wester?
Mu Qingge has a fondness for pretty boys.
Don't tell me
you've been charmed by her.
I want to kill her every day,
but she tricked me
into taking a soul oath
and put me under her thumb.
What?
You really took a soul oath?
I thought
you were clever and cautious,
but it turns out you're an idiot!
I should've killed you when I had the chance!
Father, calm down.
I've come up with a plan.
What?
You're about to form your core?
Mu Qingge entered Mount Eternal
as if she owned that place.
After I learn her skills,
taking the demonic magic from Eternal Sect
will be a piece of cake.
Alright.
But remember this:
even though you took a soul oath
for Mu Qingge,
your life
is still in my hands.
Why did you bring me to the town?
You'll find out soon.
Thank you, Immortal Master.
You're welcome.
Thank you, Immortal Master,
for saving my wife.
No trouble at all.
Thank you.
Thank you for finding my son.
You're welcome.
Thank you, Immortal Master.
Thank you
for fishing out my donkey from the river.
Thank you, Immortal Master.
You're welcome.
Mu Qingge,
you're actually making money off of me.
Calm down.
There's still a big deal to close.
[Dongxi Village]
You're not trying to make money.
You're helping people, right?
Can't fool you, huh?
There are countless people
in this universe who need help.
These small acts of kindness
are meaningless.
I'll just help as many people as I can.
It's better than doing nothing at all.
Besides,
I can make some money from it, can't I?
What?
You're helping people,
but why do the Heavenly Ones call you a demoness?
Those old fools
only know to cultivate with long faces.
They call anything
that's not their way evil.
I follow my own path.
Who cares about them?
Let's go.
Save them.
Thank you.
How strange.
We were inexplicably
tied to the pillars.
Yeah.
Shui,
there's a child over there.
Always finish what you start.
Hurry up.
Don't be afraid.
Do you know
who hung you up?
No.
This is for you two.
Thank you.
Mind your own business.
What's going on?
The boy who took the girl away
should be an Earth Immortal.
He cast the Shadow Spell on us.
That's why we move in unison.
You helped others
but ended up in trouble.
How laughable!
Isn't this fun?
Just seal that Earth Immortal back into the ground
and save the girl.
Fun, huh?
Alright.
Don't make big moves.
Didn't you say it's fun?
As an Earth Immortal,
instead of guarding your land,
you're here harming people.
You can't escape.
Break the Shadow Spell.
You two
[Earth Immortal]
are on my turf now.
You'd better behave!
[Sealed Domain]
This is...
The Shadow Spell no longer works.
It seems
we've been pulled into his Sealed Domain.
You know quite a bit, huh?
I've been trapped here for thousands of years,
guarding this land.
It's so boring.
I finally found a chance to sneak out
and look for a playmate,
but you two messed things up.
You'll just stay here forever!
You're dead!
Celestial Ice Thorn?
You really showed no mercy.
This is a small place.
You can't escape.
Let us out.
You want to get out?
No problem.
But every inch of this Sealed Domain
is bound by the celestial contract.
Now that you're here,
you must abide by its rules.
This land of mine
requires two guardians.
The Immortal Realm's negligence
left me here alone for thousands of years.
Now that you three are here,
only two of you can leave.
One must stay.
That's nonsense!
Even if you kill me,
two of you
will still have to stay here.
The exit is over there.
You decide.
Shui.
He's not lying.
The celestial contract here
does indeed restrict us.
But I have an idea.
What is it?
Don't be afraid.
Go back home.
Where's the young lady just now?
She...
She stayed inside by herself.
You're out.
How did you manage that?
I tickled
that Earth Immortal until he couldn't stand it.
Then he admitted that
he opened the portal
with 300 years of cultivation
and came out to mess with people.
So I made him
use another 300 years of cultivation
to open the portal again.
It's not too bad.
I also got a piece of the priceless
Blood Chalcedony as an apology gift.
Were you worried about me?
I was just curious.
I got out
but brought a bit of trouble along with me.
What trouble?
Three.
Two.
One.
The Shadow Spell!
This is the trouble I was talking about.
Once we left the Sealed Domain,
the Shadow Spell took effect again.
How do we break this damn thing?
We can only wait for it to break itself in four hours.
Let's go.
Send the girl back to the village first.
Come on. Hold his sword.
[Hexing Restaurant]
Respect your master.
Let me drink first.
Don't you dote on your disciples?
Why don't you let me eat first?
You won't back down?
Alright.
Let's see how long you can hold out.
They...
A minx and a libertine.
Shameless!
Let's go.
You ruined my image!
You started it first.
And you don't care about
others' opinions anyway.
Calling me a demoness is fine,
but calling me a minx is too much.
Stop it.
It seems
we're embarrassing ourselves more than each other.
Truce.
After we eat, we'll meditate in the inn
until the spell breaks.
[Qingzhu Inn]
Didn't we agree on a truce?
Why are you doing it again?
Hasn't it been four hours already?
You got hurt earlier?
Didn't your defensive aura
block the attack?
Celestial Ice Thorns are pretty powerful.
It's said that
the demoness, Mu Qingge,
has never been injured before.
Then this scar
is the first one?
I was just lucky.
When you help people and seek justice,
it's inevitable to get hurt.
It's just a scar.
No big deal.
♫Ripples shimmer among the flowers♫
Let me do it.
♫The wind plucks the clouds in the sky♫
♫Because of you, my fleeting life is filled with endless thoughts♫
♫Since my lips touched your beauty♫
♫I envy nothing in this world♫
♫Even butterflies and swallows gift us their graceful dance♫
Lower.
♫If the full moon is destined to wane♫
♫If time is bound to change everything♫
♫Then I wish to follow you like a migrating bird♫
♫Never tired of gazing at you, longing for you day and night♫
♫I wish to be with you forever♫
♫Braving every trial and tribulation♫
♫A red thread weaves our fates together♫
♫Every loop and circle is filled with my longing for you♫
♫With love, I fear no winds or storms♫
♫Through all these fleeting years♫
♫You're the best thing that's ever happened to me♫
It's been a busy day.
I'll take a nap.
Shui,
go take a walk in the town by yourself.
Don't disturb me while I sleep.