Hey you, watch carefully for safety
Don't touch it
I'm going to start Sunday
Wait here
Come
I'm coming
What's up?
I will follow you all the way
to face the love and hate in this world
I only wish to turn back time
to experience both the present and the past
Only when I have achieved my goal will I understand the true meaning
I am destined to turn back time
and face the future with love
But I am still fearless and never regret
I can't wait to see the falling flowers and the
will and hope of Peking Butcher
Episode 1
I'm not patient.
If you don't want to settle down in this mess,
then hand over the Hidden Heart Valley to me.
Your Majesty.
Take the trap.
Go.
Who are you?
How dare you manipulate the Evil Tiger?
Where's the Hidden Heart Valley I want?
Our Tian Kui Sect is a large sect of demon cultivation.
It's not easy to provoke them.
If you don't say anything,
then I'll kill this demon cultivation
and be the first to be killed.
I said,
I'll kill this demon cultivation
and be the first to be killed.
I said,
I'll kill this demon cultivation
and be the first to be killed.
I said,
I'll kill this demon cultivation
and be the first to be killed.
Master.
Prince Zong has persuaded the general of Fuyi State
to make a grand speech.
Today, Prince Zong's son Su Yu
will lead the general to the capital.
I hope you can help him.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll wait for you.
I'm here to see the general.
Father asked me to make a grand speech.
Brother, please help us
to win the honor.
Don't worry.
Yinxin Valley can control people's mind
in a few days.
I'm ready
to make a grand speech.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Good.
Although I went to war
with your father,
I've just met with the general of our enemy.
I'm looking forward to seeing him.
Your Majesty, you are the most beloved one.
The people are always concerned about you.
I dare not propose a toast.
Your Majesty, General Li and his father
are now waiting outside the camp.
Summon General Li to present himself.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
I'm willing to give you the map of the border.
Thank you for forgiving me.
Hurry.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, are you all right?
I'm fine.
I was mistaken.
I didn't know he was Prime Minister.
Please punish me.
King of Pingjing, I'm here.
I'm lucky to have you as my son.
That's why I'm safe and sound.
Your Majesty is responsible for the safety of the country.
Go.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I was waiting for the Crown Prince to be rewarded.
I didn't expect him to be so bad.
He's not.
Xiao, a man who can't be on the stage.
Today,
I'm honored to see you.
You don't know that
King of Pingjing
has a great background.
The Han family is the best
brothel in the capital.
But King of Pingjing doesn't lack a son.
Why did he bring this man home?
I don't know.
King of Pingjing is very smart.
He said he would pay the debt.
He's very smart.
His mother is a woman.
She's very kind.
She's very powerful.
Right?
King of Pingjing.
Xing.
Wait.
Get up.
You're really pretty.
But it hurts people's lives.
It's too cruel.
It's not good.
Brother.
Are you okay?
Now I can see you are fully recovered.
Lord Hong
here,
you can return the money
with my life.
One thousand liang.
Gold.
That lady
who is called Mu Qingge.
She said she was only 25 years old.
She's the first phoenixive
of the miraculous.
But,
she wasn't Flying wrapped by the rules of the college,
the shimmered,
Rocaver fall in love,
I don't know why, but he's with Su Yu.
I'm afraid it's a trouble.
Go and take the punishment.
So what?
No one can stop me from completing my mission.
I'm sorry.
Will the King of Zongqing Mansion be implicated in this matter today?
His Majesty is wise.
I don't believe my father and I will collude with the enemy.
By the way,
the people of the Marquis Yongan's Mansion
were never satisfied with the King of Zongqing's plan.
It's really rude to say that.
Don't take it to heart.
Why should I care about your complaints?
I can't even look at the matter of collecting the painting
when I go down the mountain this time.
Sister.
Wu.
The Crown Prince told me when he came back.
You will come today.
I asked the servants to prepare
many delicious tea for you.
Wu, you've been with Yu all the time.
You didn't cause him any trouble, right?
I always treat Wu as my sister.
Why would I cause him any trouble?
Let's go.
The Crown Prince has passed away for many years.
His Majesty hasn't chosen a crown prince
between me and the King of Zongqing.
Although he didn't get the power of the Southern Army
this time,
the power of the King of Zongqing
is still unbeatable in the court.
So,
we must plan it carefully.
I've calculated it in advance.
Young Master Su Yishui
is a rare and important person.
He can help you complete your great cause.
So, you can take him back to your mansion.
It's been eight years.
The things that were in his body in the early years
are now in the form of a new sword.
It won't take long
before he can be one with his body.
Okay.
I've been waiting for this day for a long time.
The King of Zongqing
Father.
Your Highness.
Please take me in.
First,
you need to know that
I don't lack a son.
I need someone who is worth my life.
If you can do it,
I can keep you in the mansion
and give you a title.
I will become a valuable person.
It contains the supreme power
of the world.
Spiritual power.
As long as you have it,
you can achieve great things.
Unfortunately,
I only got a little bit.
Spiritual power is now in the world of good.
Only the Demon Lord can summon it.
The body of the Chiyin is the natural spiritual power.
And you are the only one
who can be the Demon Lord.
After many trials,
you can become one
with this spiritual power.
I've put this spiritual power in your heart
and made your body a spiritual power.
And you will be the spiritual power of the Demon Lord.
That talisman
can keep you alive in this barrier.
You can only get out
if you kill the monster inside.
Otherwise,
the monster will attack you day after day.
Okay.
You can practice inside.
Xiao Xiao.
Remember to send her a meal every three days.
Keep an eye on her.
If anything happens,
report to my father immediately.
Yes, Father.
Good girl.
Three days later
Brother.
Wake up, brother!
You're a senior, but you didn't go to college with us.
Get away from me!
Get away!
Are you okay?
Why do you always treat us like this?
When did others ever treat us like this?
As men, we're useless to the Pingqing House.
I don't think we can even be in this situation.
So, we can only rely on ourselves to get to the top.
Others are cruel to you, but you only become stronger.
This is how you become the ultimate winner.
Today, I can bear everything.
In the future, I'll make all those who look down on us pay for it.
I can feel the spiritual power.
Young Master has finally made contact with the spiritual power.
However, to obtain the spiritual power in the Demon Realm,
you must learn the original plan of the Demon Heart as soon as possible.
The original plan of the Demon Heart?
That's right.
The Demon Heart is the most powerful power in the Demon Realm.
The Demon Heart?
That's right.
This power can absorb the powers of others,
and all the spiritual powers.
Only by learning this power can you finally summon the spiritual power.
It's a pity that the Demon Heart has been sealed by Jiuhua.
Why is that so difficult?
I'll send my men to train the sect.
Father, you mustn't.
If you force them, I'm afraid it will alert the King of the Immortal Sect.
Why don't you leave this matter to me?
I'll find a way to get it.
The Xuan Gate is not suitable for the common people.
It's a trap that involves the imperial power.
I'll be defeated and be trained under the sect.
I'll use this opportunity to obtain the original plan of the Demon Heart.
I need to hide my true identity.
Why do you have to go and get the original plan of the Demon Heart yourself?
Is it not important to get the original plan?
What's important is that I'll be defeated by Jiuhua Sect.
If I listen to them and train the original plan of the Demon Heart to merge with the spiritual power,
I'll eventually be swallowed by the spiritual power.
If I learn the supreme power of the Xuan Gate,
I'll have the power to fight against the spiritual power.
Even if I train the Demon Palace, I'll have the chance to fight against the enemy.
What I want is to control the spiritual power by myself,
not to become a tool that can be used by anyone.
All these years, you finally said that Yutong and Yuchen are two confidants.
They are no longer the people that Father has arranged to watch over me.
If you have any problems in the future, you can directly go to them.
Father.
You performed well today. I am very satisfied.
Thank you, Father.
I've sent you to Jiuhua to train for many days.
Did you successfully get the original plan of the Demon Heart?
The original plan of the Demon Heart was sealed in the Cangjing Building.
It needs the Sect Leader to pass on the spiritual power to enter.
I just got promoted from the outer disciples to the inner disciples.
I don't have a chance for now.
Hurry up. It's not much time.
Yes.
Also, I still have one thing that needs you to do.
What's going on?
Mo Yatou, this is the move to fly.
We happened to be able to get the paper and the knife.
We came to drink with you to celebrate.
Fly?
Rumor has it that the Demon Son who can control the spirit power of the Youjie Realm is about to appear.
Your cultivation has now been successful.
There is only one step left for you to become a immortal.
You can't be a immortal.
If you can kill the Demon Son with the right path,
I think it will be a good opportunity for you to fly smoothly.
Congratulations.
What congratulations?
You are so young to have this kind of experience.
What's the use of me becoming an immortal?
Everyone is talking about cultivating immortals and asking for the right path to get past the old world.
But if you really become an immortal,
the immortals will use the Phoenix Ball to take the four great paths and never ask about the world.
I am a human being.
I am just greedy for this worldly and secular life.
I have gained so much in this mortal world.
This is the path I want to take.
Your personality is just like the way you behave with the common people.
No wonder those who follow the right path have treated you like a demoness.
Whatever.
But it seems that I have to be more restrained recently.
I haven't received my little disciple of the Five Spiritual Roots yet.
If you don't receive it, it will be troublesome if you accidentally fly.
Five Spiritual Roots?
For thousands of years, how many Five Spiritual Roots can the world find that are the same as you?
You still want to collect the map?
Why don't you go and see if you have filled up the sea of the Golden Bird?
Dreams always have to be there.
Otherwise, I am the only one in this world with Five Spiritual Roots.
How boring.
Okay. Since that is the case,
I will give you the Silver Stone of the Danzi Youjie.
If you encounter a spiritual power or a demon, you will be able to get the silver.
Good stuff. Thank you.
So that you won't have to collect the map and fly.
It's just that if this demon is a real thing, the world will be in a bad place.
By then, will you be able to control the great immortal Mu?
I have wine and wine to drink today.
Let's talk about it when I really encounter it some other day.
Little Mu!
We gave you good stuff.
Why don't you treat us to a few drinks before you leave?
I am busy meeting people. I will treat you to a few drinks some other day.
This girl has changed.
Second Young Master is missing?
Yes. A few days ago, Second Brother went to Tai Xue's Manor and was attacked on the way.
All the guards were killed. Second Brother was kidnapped.
Did you find out who did it?
It must be King of Pingqing.
King of Pingqing has always been waiting for Second Brother to rescue the military power in General Zhenbei's hands.
For the past few years, Second Brother's mother has passed away.
If there is no more bloodline of Second Brother,
General Zhenbei will not support my father like he does now.
The battle for the imperial power is actually a battle that even children are not allowed to participate in.
Brother Qing, I have already sent people to search everywhere.
But for several days, there has been no news.
I am very worried about Second Brother's safety.
You want me to help you?
Brother Qing, I know that the Xuanmen Tribe cannot interfere with the royal family affairs.
But...but I really cannot ignore Second Brother's life and death.
You once said that you wanted to return me a favor.
I shouldn't have been so ungrateful.
But this time, can I have this favor to exchange?
Please save my Second Brother.
Young Master, my sister and I are in a desperate situation.
You once had a criminal against us.
Are you really willing to use this favor to save your brother?
He is my biological brother.
Nothing is more important than his safety now.
Okay. I promise you.
I will return your Second Brother to you completely.
He was kidnapped here.
The secret talisman?
Jiuhua Sect's method?
They didn't kill him on the spot, but kidnapped him.
It means that he should be fine now.
Young Master, it is our fate to meet in this river.
Please drink.
I am Mu Qingge from West Mountain.
Young Master, don't be so polite.
You look really good.
I think you look very good in person.
I am not a good person.
I am just a little girl.
I think you look very good in person.
Would you like to come back to West Mountain with me?
You have a good foundation.
It is a pity that you didn't practice well.
You just used the talisman to kidnap the person.
You have the Second Young Master of the Zongqin Mansion, right?
Hand him over.
What Second Young Master? I don't understand what you are saying.
Su Yishui, although you used the talisman well,
but since I saw you last time,
I have been keeping your beautiful eyes in my mind.
You are mistaken.
My name is Su Cheng.
I am not the person you are looking for.
Su Cheng?
Okay, then I will break the spell on your face first.
Demon girl, let me go!
Why are you panicking? Am I that scary?
If you don't hand over the person today,
don't even think of escaping from my hands.
You are amazing.
Even I can't break your philtrum.
You are really amazing.
I am not afraid of you.
Even I can't break your philtrum.
Demon girl.
You would rather kill yourself to escape?
You are born with the Five-Face-Face?
Just like me?
What a coincidence.
You learned fast.
You came to the door yourself?
You won't blame me for that?
You shouldn't have done this.
After a few years of being Happy,
you always know how to exercise White Spirit in itself.
Hurry.
It seems I'm lucky enough знаете
to survive alone.
Baby, this is my lucky charm.
Forgive me.
I'm not sure if it's a single or double.
I'll tell you if you're right.
I've never lost a bet.
I guess it's a double.
You lost.
Wrong.
It's a single.
Judging from the
He was that Goodots
Come down
Why you don't want to come down
Why You let me come down
I'm not going to let you win.
Qing asked us to help him find out someone's information.
This game...
is not like it.
You're playing dirty again?
Let's save this game first.
Next time, we'll win.
It's not easy to win you.
You're playing this with me?
If that's the case,
Su Yishui is doing things for the King of Ping.
He's a little more powerful.
But he's not a big evil.
This is just a formality, right?
He hasn't yet been caught yet.
How can he use the future possibility to interrogate him?
There's a way.
If I take him as my disciple,
and break his demon formality,
then I don't have to worry about anything.
But if he really ends up being a demon,
then I don't have to be soft.
I only have to kill the demon to get the right path.
Everything will be decided by his heart.
I'll go.
The soul will never leave.
Kid, you were so cruel before.
It seems that the True One didn't teach you well.
Then let me teach you.
I've purified my spirit.
Although you have a good foundation,
you just got a new skill.
You can't escape.
I've already killed him.
It's no use following me.
If you really want to kill him,
why don't you kill him after you've taken him away?
It's more like a game.
It seems that I guessed it right.
It's okay. I'll find someone.
I have a new idea.
I haven't had such a good disciple.
I've just got a few good skills recently.
I need a talented disciple to practice with me.
I think you're just right.
I don't think it's right.
You'll know if it's right or not after you try it.
How about this?
Tell me what you like.
No matter it's gold, silver, jade, stone, qi, needle or beast,
I'll get you everything.
You can be my disciple from now on.
I like you to stay away from me.
It's a little hard.
I think you look better in your original appearance.
Let's bet again.
If I can find the flaw of your Yi Rong Spell,
you can call me master.
It's a deal.
Sit down.
Su Cheng.
We're going to the Jiu Hua Sect to listen to the school.
We met you as soon as we went down the mountain.
Why are you near the Kongshan Sect?
I was entangled by the female demon and was chased here.
Mu Qingge.
You know me?
You've been searching for beautiful young men everywhere.
You've been doing things in a wild way.
You've been famous for a long time.
Now you're in charge of the power and the common things.
You're not ashamed of the whole school.
You're entangled with Su Cheng.
Stay away from him.
Since you said I like beautiful young men,
I won't just let go of this kind of role.
I'm sure I'll accept your apprentice.
The female demon forced me to go to the West Mountain.
I'd rather die than obey her.
But I can't get rid of her.
Shameless.
Fight!
Just talk to me.
We're all girls.
It's so embarrassing to fight together.
Cut the crap.
Finally, I got rid of that demoness.
Su Cheng.
You just became an apprentice of the inner sect.
You only came back after a month.
If you're all so carefree,
how can you practice?
Senior Brother,
you'd better focus on your own practice.
Su Cheng.
Why didn't you just say goodbye?
That demoness was driven away by us.
Thank you.
I owe Wen Shi Mei a favor.
I'll pay you back another day.
You said that?
Senior Sister.
Didn't you prepare a long-awaited gift
for Su Cheng?
Give it to him.
Su Cheng.
This is a sword-sword I made myself.
I hope you won't dislike it.
So, Yan Liang is interested in Wen Hong Shan.
He's a disciple of the inner sect of the True Man of Kaiyuan.
But he's not worthy of my favor.
Thank you, Junior Sister Wen.
It's hurt.
What's wrong with you?
That demoness hurt you?
If she's hurt like that,
she's so fragile.
She's a man of the Xuan Sect.
You're right.
But I don't care if I'm a disciple of the Xuan Sect.
You don't have to worry about me.
Even if I'm a disciple of the Xuan Sect,
I still have Wen Shi Mei's heart.
It's useless for you to worry about me.
Su Cheng!
Yan Liang Yue!
Su Cheng is hurt!
Yan Liang Yue.
As a disciple of the sect,
you can't even hurt me with this?
You're really useless.
Su Cheng!
Yan Liang Yue, are you crazy?
Then you...
Be careful.
I'm not as good as others.
I don't blame you.
Su Cheng.
Su Cheng!
Yan Liang Yue!
Yan Liang Yue.
Why are you always having a hard time with Su Cheng?
I...
She's always so stubborn.
Wen Shi Mei,
before she changes her ways,
you'd better stay away from her.
I have my own way.
You don't have to worry about me.
Senior,
these two people are so boring.
They're a couple.
What's the matter with you?
That's right.
You two are having a fight, aren't you?
Why did Chief Lei
forget to tell me my time spent here?
The talents that Yie Liang Yue used
from Kaiyuan Formation
finally bring out Kaiyuan Formation's
footballing using spirit of won.
He managed to open the Desert Celestial嚎.
Now get thebreathinggtic backing of demon core.
I won't give you any more chances.
If you still can't do it,
what will you do?
Where's he prime minister?
Please stop make my day.
You Sultan,
I will go.
Proggzu,
where's my legislation?
You first.
It's really hard to break the enchantment of Mount Jiuhua.
But it's worth it to accept you as my disciple.
I told you it's impossible.
That's why you have to make a bet.
You have a lot of secrets.
You must be afraid that people will know.
If you don't agree,
I'll have someone come.
Do you want to bet?
I bet.
That's right.
Then I'll start to find the enchantment.
Nose, chin, neck.
They all look good.
Wide shoulders, narrow waist.
Beautiful woman.
Are you looking for the enchantment or...
I found it.
How did you find it?
You're determined.
So your nose is slow and your heart is not flustered.
But this is a mistake.
How can someone's earlobes be so close?
The nose and heart beat are more stable.
It's clearly forced suppression.
It's naturally the enchantment.
Why do you have to hide such a good face?
Come on.
Come back to Mount Jiuhua with me.
I'll go with you.
You're so stupid.
Then I'll have to drag you back.
Do you still want to find the son of the King of the Immortal?
This is where he is.
You'll only be killed if you go there late.
At a young age,
you're using the man's skills as if they were pure.
But after I've saved him,
I'll come back to you.
You can't escape.
Where did you learn to be so cruel?
You're so cruel.
Who told you to ruin my plan?
You're not talented.
If I don't teach you a lesson,
you'll be more and more out of line.
You...
Oh no, something happened to the Cangning Tower.
Take him down.
I'm sorry.