Ooh.
to face the love and hate of the world
I only wish that by turning back time
I can experience both the present and the future
Only by achieving the reincarnation can I understand the preciousness
Even if I know that the true meaning of life is to be returned to the past
I am destined to be tamed by love
But I am still fearless and never regret
The love and hate of the world
Will eventually be erased
The Legend of Chusen
Episode 16
It's all in the past.
Since it has changed,
I should let go
and live my own life.
Sister Feihua,
keep these talismans for emergency use.
If there are still some that you can't handle,
come to Xishan to find me at any time.
Take care.
You are right.
Chu Zhenhe and Ranran actually...
You are the only one who is right.
It has been so long, and you still can't see the owner's love and hatred for her.
They are like this now.
I am not surprised at all.
Then, you also know that the owner was sealed.
I only thought that the owner knew that Brother Mu Qing was a demon,
but still loved him.
I didn't know that the truth of the matter was like this.
So it was him who was protecting the owner.
We actually misunderstood him for so many years.
So, Master was sealed
and couldn't say anything.
No wonder I feel that Ranran looks more and more like someone.
It turned out to be the master I met before.
The temperament is indeed like him,
but the appearance is different.
I couldn't recognize those noblemen.
After all, they have been reborn once.
What?
Are you going to be my identity?
No.
We just got all the information,
and our brains are still in a daze.
I haven't decided yet
whether to call you Ranran or your master.
How old am I?
Of course I am your junior.
Senior Brother,
don't think that you can just pay me back
with the three taels of silver.
Xiao,
you are not allowed to tell Second Brother
that you are secretly making up secrets and ignoring me.
I will be jealous.
Just now, Master said that
you used your five-factor spiritual root
to save him.
We need to use our spiritual power to protect you.
How is it? Is it warmer now?
Thank you.
It's not as dangerous as Master said.
And I said that
you all have no idea
about the danger we are facing now.
Master is a demon son.
His spiritual power is now with him.
He will surely become a great envoy
if he follows Master.
And we are going to the You Realm.
The Demon Realm is like a temple.
It's hard to understand the danger.
Master wants me to ask you all.
The most stable thing for you now
is to announce the separation from West Mountain.
How can this work?
I don't break the rules.
Master can't drive me away.
I will never betray my master.
This is the shame of a cultivator.
I will never leave you again.
Besides, we are of the same family.
We can't just be together.
You even lost your spiritual root
and you still want to go with me.
I will not lose to you.
Yes.
You and Master are very loyal.
As cultivators, how can you be so careless?
And even if you are misunderstood,
there will always be a day when the truth is revealed.
This is a good opportunity.
I want to be like you
and do something amazing
Yes.
Let's seal the spiritual power back to the Demon Realm
and protect the world.
Okay.
Let's do this amazing thing together.
The way to enter the Demon Realm.
Blood Moon.
Blood Moon is born in the Demon Realm
and only shines on the most sacred land in the human world.
It absorbs the anger and nourishes the Demon Realm.
It only stays for one moment.
The purple stone is the Moon Line
and the demon is the blood line.
It can connect Yin and Yang.
The book only says
that Blood Moon only appears in the most
killing place in the human world
but does not indicate the specific direction.
The most killing place
is it the battlefield?
The border between the Qi and the Lin State
is always covered with rubble.
The war is frequent and the battle is fierce.
Especially the recent battle of the Demon Realm.
It's the most fierce.
If Blood Moon is born in the human world
the battlefield of the Demon Realm is the most likely.
The cracks in the Silver-Blooded Pond are getting worse.
We have to send Lin Quan back to the Demon Realm as soon as possible.
Let's set off now.
I'll inform Yu Tong and the others.
I'm sorry for causing you so much trouble.
I forgot that you just lost your spiritual power.
You can't be so tired.
Let's rest for a night and set off tomorrow.
It's fine.
But I do want to set off later.
I have some preparations to do.
What preparations?
I can't use the spiritual power to transform.
I can only use the pen to draw.
The Demon Realm is a place of the Yin and the Yin.
The cracks are huge and the danger is hard to predict.
I can only use the pen to draw.
But I haven't finished yet.
The spiritual power of the person who draws the pen
will also increase the power of the pen.
You just lost your spiritual power.
The power of the pen will also be reduced.
I know.
I can only use the pen to draw.
It's not that troublesome.
Just change the paper.
The power of the pen can be ten times more than the ordinary paper.
The paper is so expensive.
You have so much money.
I'm also from the royal family.
The family of Xishan
can't beat those big companies.
The Jixing Prefecture,
the Mumao Prefecture,
and the Lingduan Prefecture.
You've drawn them all.
Your spiritual power
and the paper are all added.
Isn't this the legendary best-quality talisman?
The world is in danger.
Your spirit is broken.
There's no way you can borrow it.
I'm worried about the paper.
By the way,
can you borrow the power of the heaven and earth?
I can borrow the power of the heaven and earth.
We can borrow the power of the heaven and earth.
But the power of the pen is different from the power of the pen.
If you want to draw the pen at any time,
you have to use the magic of the soul-losing lock
to draw the pen.
Of course, I can't use the power of the pen.
But don't forget,
I used half of the golden elixir to exchange you.
The power of the golden elixir in my body is born to be able to draw.
Even without the magic, it can be used.
I've given you all my spiritual power.
Try to borrow it.
I can borrow your spiritual power.
So, no matter where you go,
remember to stay by my side.
You can use my spiritual power as you like.
As the saying goes,
there's a limit, there's a return.
Since our spiritual power is interlinked,
I'll teach you the skill of breaking the star box.
If one day, I borrow a lot of spiritual power,
you can borrow my spiritual power to fight against the enemy.
Okay.
You're my master for one day.
Su Yu.
Xue Ran Ran.
You all wait.
I won't let you live easily.
I think after using Su Yu water's antidote
to remove the grudge,
I've finally been able to control it.
I'll be able to control it.
I think after using Su Yu water's antidote
to remove the grudge,
I've finally been able to control it.
What did he do?
You can't keep doing this.
What?
Seeing me so weak,
you don't even call me a master?
You're still a master?
Or did you hear some rumors
and you're so disrespectful to me?
I've stewed the spiritual juice.
You need to get better first.
The courtyard in the mountains is quiet and secluded.
It's suitable for you to cultivate.
What's the use of eating this spiritual juice?
From tomorrow,
I'll have you send me ten sticks every day.
I want to be a
Some minds just simply
die at the hasta when an incident like this is to happen.
So what else do you have left?
The disciples from eastVISHAN
followed me.
I told them
nothing about the rock incident
because you're in the disadvantaged moment.
When things are Monglons...
you will share it with them.
Xiao Wu.
What he said is true.
Did I really…
Didn't I say it completely?
I just thought it's hard to tell.
I swear if that's what you wanted to see,
the murderer could have told us.
Only those who could find an owner
could stay to kill the murderer.
but we haven't yet.
Do you have to show me what you want?
Be honest with us
and tell us what you really want.
If that's what you want,
we should look for an Place of Last scattered parts for us.
Let's find a way out
Go
You have promised that
I would confess with them personally
But why...
When did I promise it?
Su Yu
Crown princess
The crown princess
and Su Yun
Bi throughout the whole family
Crown Princess Consort,
and Consort Zhan.
All the best of them
were in my hands.
But when I turned around,
nothing was left.
I didn't have any way out.
At worst,
I'll die here.
In case I'll suffer
the humiliation and despair of being shameless.
Why are you doing this?
Xiaowu.
Fine.
I won't say anything.
Why?
You like me?
Do you think I should be
grateful to you
for my love?
No.
Do you remember
when you saved me
at the foot of the West Mountain 25 years ago?
I've been self-righteous
and bullied by my brothers.
You're the one who helped me.
I thought you were a disciple of the West Mountain
and you were the one who helped them.
I'm grateful to you.
Every time you go to the West Mountain,
I'm happy to see you.
I've always hoped
that you could live a happier life.
Now,
I hope you can stop
and think about what you really need
and where you should go.
I need the spiritual treasure.
I need to be reborn.
I need to get everything back.
You're obviously angry with me.
You're so lucky.
You're so rich.
But you don't want to give me
more spiritual treasures.
Yet you still say these nonsense
to fool me.
I'm just an ordinary soldier.
I'm more confident in my talent.
But I'm not a talent.
Master also taught me
to be upright and honest.
Only when you have the ability
to make the right choice
can you make the right choice.
Master, Master, Master,
you're always right.
He's lucky.
He has everything he wants.
He doesn't need to fight for it.
But I
rarely get what I want.
I'm wrong if I want more.
You said you liked me.
You feel like money but you like nothing
herbs wine...
Are you trying to hostile me?
Ziplling the royal family
to poison the people.
Oh my poor son.
This kind of thing should be scratched
Yes
Thief
Catch him
Be careful
You are over there
chase
The Chu Jianjun of the Yugu Chu is so dirty
Defeated me, the reputation of Xingshan
Not only
I guess he also told the identity of Master's demon son
To all the schools
To kill us with a knife
Once the Xuanmen wants to intervene
I'm afraid we can't control the enemy
Be careful
Yanlu has set up a barrier
Can only cover up the appearance with a sword
But can't hide the Xuanmen
The time to seal the Linquan can't be missed
If you meet the people of the Xuanmen
If you can avoid it, avoid it
Less trouble
Yes
Not enough
I want better
But this is the best quality of the spirit medicine
That's the problem with the elixir furnace
Go find me a better elixir furnace
You are in trouble
Then you can leave
I didn't force you to stay
I know you still need some time
Can think through
I can wait for you
rest assured
I won't leave you
There is no way out
You came in so fast
how
Su Yu decided to kill me
You misunderstood
I'm not here to harm you
But to ask for cooperation for the crown prince
Cooperation
How is it possible
I heard it with my own ears
He ordered you to kill me
Now the crown prince is in danger
I need to find a great power to kill him
If the immortal teacher is willing to help
The identity of the Queen of War is still yours
In the past, everything was returned to the hands of the immortal teacher
Not only that, that great power
It can also help you to obtain supreme spiritual power
I'm sorry
What you want will come back
Then who is the great power he is looking for?
It's him
But he has disappeared for a long time
How do you know where he is?
He suddenly disappeared at the beginning
It was sealed by Mu Qingge in the Youjie
Su Yishui is going to the Youjie now
You just need to get into the Youjie in the midst of chaos
You can find him
With his help
I can definitely get back my spiritual power
Step on him
Just according to my current power
How can I hide Su Yishui and get into the Youjie?
Don't worry
His Highness has already declared the identity of Su Yishui and the Demon Son
To all the sects
You just need to add another fire
Those sects will be used by you
When I took the disciples to the East Sea
Su Yishui had already escaped
He didn't even return to the West Mountain
Where did the Demon Son escape to?
I know where the Demon Son is
I'll go and find him
Mu Qingge
Why did you pretend to be the Demon Son
and fool us all?
Please don't be angry
Su Yishui threatened me with the life of Wu
He forced me to admit my identity as the Demon Son
He could control the spiritual power and take the world
But I don't know what went wrong
He brought me back to life and transferred my attention to everyone
I only knew when I was reborn that he lied to me
Wu was already killed by him
After that, he forced me to set up the soul world
As long as I say that Su Yishui is the Demon Son
It really is the soul world
Now he is taking the spiritual power to the Youjie
Please stop the Demon Son from coming to the world
Calm down, immortals
Even if there is a soul world
it doesn't mean that what he said is true
He can't even get rid of his previous evil deeds
I know that I'm sorry to all of you who are suffering from the Heaven's Prowess
He forced me to do so
He was the one who planted my grudge
I had no choice but to say that in the Heaven's Prowess
Now I finally have the grudge
I don't want to help the evil
I don't want to be the pawn in the world of the Demon Son
Such a vicious man
It's really hard to escape from the Heaven's power
Where is the Demon Son now?
He is taking the disciples of Mount Xi to guard the direction of the demon
Jiu Hua disciples, listen to my order
Now I'm seriously injured
Liang Yu, you will be the host
We will gather the power of the whole sect
to capture the Demon Son, Su Yi Shui
Yes
Take back the spiritual power with us
Fei Yun's disciples, follow me
Chase the Demon Son
Yes
Our Kongshan Sect is also willing to do so
There are many Xuan Meng disciples on the way
Xuan Meng is going to attack us
It seems that
there was a big battle here before
A lot of grudges are coming out in the air
The spiritual power seems to have a special feeling for this place
It seems that the two sects are fighting each other
They are fighting each other
There is a special feeling here
It seems that the entrance to the
Contemporary World is here
I have planted the talisman here
Blood and blood will appear
There must be a reaction at the same time
In the next few hours
You go to the nearby town to feed the stomach
But at this time
I can't eat anything
Relax
The more dangerous it is
The more we have to eat, play and drink
The camera is short
We will have something to do after the fight
Be low-key
Eat high-key, right?
You are right, Ran Ran
The water gate is still looking for us
There are many people outside
Why don't we take separate actions
Wait for the blood to appear
Come back here for a meeting
Although it's the first time I came to Wuma Town
I feel a little familiar
Because you came in the last life
No wonder
Chenji Water Buns in Wanjing
There is also here
You just saw it in Wanjing
You can try it now
Let's try it
it is good
Master, you don't look nervous at all
So many storms have come
I believe I can get through this time
Besides, didn't you say
Eat well before the big battle
It's busy here
I'll take you around later
it is good
Come and try the dipping sauce in Wanjing
How about it
After returning the spiritual power to the Youjie
We will travel around the world together
Eat all over the world
it is good
Eat quickly
Master, skewers
Yangchuan in the refrigerator
How many skewers do you want?
Come boss, come to Wuchuan
it is good
Take it
Thank you
it is good
Take care
It smells good
Yangchuan, Yangchuan
it is good
Awesome
Congratulations to this girl
Won the treasure of our shop
it is good
The treasure of the shop
That's the prize?
Girl, don't underestimate this mirror
This is called the marriage mirror
It is said that there is a mirror fairy in it
As long as you sincerely knock on the mirror
You can see your ex-lover
So magical, really
Girl, look
Come on, next one
Next one
Come on
Master, am I being deceived?
This mirror is not bright at all
How can it be not bright
You close your eyes and try again
Open it
Look
The ex-lover is here
Go
This nowb and ed Hmm
This advance Professor
Lots of plants
우와
Let it be
why
The lanterns are so good.
You may not know,
the lantern festival is in a few days.
The single men and women will give each other lanterns.
It's a good deal.
So everyone is in a hurry to buy
their favorite lanterns in advance.
Boss.
Lantern festival.
I heard that in a few days,
there will be a lantern festival in the Wuma Town.
Master,
these lanterns are so beautiful.
These are beautiful.
Don't you think the lanterns I made are beautiful?
The lanterns you made?
Some people
are not only jealous,
but also very stubborn.
I was impulsive.
How about
I make one for you?
Is it good?
Really?
Yes.
I've studied it.
The bamboo on the mountain is the best for lanterns.
Master,
I'll lend you some spiritual power.
There's a spiritual power vibration.
It's my original spiritual power.
Did I hide something
in this cave before?
Let's go and have a look.
Okay.
Let's go.
Eternal Fire?
I'll use the precious Eternal Fire
to light these lanterns.
Let's go to the lantern festival together.
I'll show you
something good then.
Are these
breaker seaweed Powder?
This is...
I just remembered something.
You used to like lanterns.
So I made these to give you.
But I don't remember
why you like lanterns.
I was poor when I was young.
I saw children on the street
walking on the street with lanterns on that festival.
I was envious.
I comforted myself every time.
I will be able to see lanterns next year.
I
need change.
Then I took these money.
Come and save me, please.
These memories may not historically stay.
However, there's something between the two.
Only those who care about others
can know like them even without their words.
Are you...
You hurt others by XXXX.
And you lost a family to someone?
Look!
How dare you!
Is that how much ahiling I mean?
You burned him. I want your life.
Don't let your life
be destroyed.
You missed the only chance to kill me
and get freedom.
Don't you feel sorry?
I, Su Yishui, never take advantage of others.
Besides, I will defeat you
with my strength
and break the relationship of the world.
Okay.
Then I'll wait for that day.
But before that,
you have to take care of yourself.
If you really want to be lazy,
just tell me if you need anything.
I'll take care of it for you.
Zhu He.
I'll be with you
forever.
day after day,
year after year.
Okay.
In the end,
the story is
in the past.
The years
are just
a thousand years.
I heard that in a few days,
there will be a lantern festival in the Wuma Town.
Let's go to the lantern festival together.
I'll show you
something good.
At this moment, I can remember
the mood of every lantern
that is made here.
You once said
that it's not only my past,
but also my love.
Wuma Town
has a custom of sending lanterns to express their love.
The lanterns in the town
are the answer.
I think
I used to
be your fan.
Ren Ren.
I used to complain that my fate is not good enough.
But actually, I've been
by your side
for a long time.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Yun Dong has a reaction.
The Right Sword appears.
Inform them.
Blood Moon.
When Blood Moon is completely visible,
the Soul Trap will appear.
Demon Lord!
Hand over the Spirit Spring!
Su Yi Shui.
You've deceived the world with your own master.
Now you're still a demon,
yet you're using the Spirit Spring to enter the fire.
My disciples from the Xuan Sect
will never allow you to harm the people.
I advise you to destroy the object in time
and seek to get rid of it.
Su, it's not too late to turn back now.
I won't kill you like I did before.
My master is a demon,
but he doesn't want to use the Spirit Spring to cause trouble.
We're doing this to seal the Spirit Spring,
not to use the Spirit Spring to enter the fire.
That's right.
You're stupid.
How can the demon's words be true?
Since you chose to use the Spirit Spring to help the evil,
don't blame us for being rude.
There's only one minute. We have to hurry.
The Demon Realm has been sealed.
Wait a moment.
Xi, what's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Why did I lose my mind just now?
I only have hatred and hatred for you.
It must be because of the demon aura.
What should I do?
The demon aura will seduce people and lead them to the demon.
Take this Green Heart Pill.
You can dissipate the demon and regain your consciousness.
You're on the same side with the demon.
Who knows what you're up to?
I'll show you.
My Qin.
Now you are here.
Team Leader is here.
Gold Fall?
Silver Boss.
Cang Li sale it.
Cun Jing,
Sea Bass,
Dragon Yetater,
I want the basic skills of Jade Pond mansion
and the life ahíre in the important place.
I think
こと
Why is that?
Pass on my boomerang
Give back my boomerang
Miss
My Search
Mitre
Yes
My broom
Didn't my legacy
I'm fine.
Are you telling the truth?
So, you really want to seal the spiritual power?
If Master really wants to enter the Demon Realm,
why must he save you?
No.
Where is Mo Ran?
Are you all right?
The Demon Realm is in a state of panic.
You're using the Talisman Spell and still need to adapt.
Is this the Demon Realm?
I think the entrance is already closed.
How do we get out?
If the Demon Realm opens the entrance once,
it will give birth to an exit.
But the exit can't come out or come back.
And it only exists for three hours.
The most troublesome thing is
to open it in the mortal world.
Then this time...
This time, we have to open it in the mortal world.
This time...
This time, we're lucky.
The exit is in the mountain not far from the Five-Horse Town.
Look.
It's on that peak.
In three hours,
we'll find the ancient town of the seal.
Then we can leave.
Where are the others?
Watch out!
Su Yi Shui, you're quite smart.
Xue Ran Ran,
no wonder I thought you were interesting.
So you're the Mother.
Don't worry.
Once I've solved Su Yi Shui's problem,
we'll calculate the last century's problem.
I'm sorry.