She's only 19 40 years older.
She is only timeline-wise.
It is fate了
etermine
I'm not dead. Look at me.
Xing.
Look.
I'm fine now.
Don't blame yourself, okay?
Go away. Lin Xuan is coming back.
I can't control myself.
I don't want to hurt you.
Go away. Go away.
Go away.
What are you going to do?
I'm fine now.
As long as I'm dead,
no one will hurt you again.
It's not like that.
You didn't hurt me.
Have you forgotten?
You defeated Lin Xuan and protected me.
I'm still alive.
Lin Xuan will never control you again.
I really didn't hurt you again.
I'm fine now.
Lin Xuan is still alive.
You can rest in peace.
I'm fine now.
Lin Xuan is dead.
You're still alive?
I'm alive.
Don't be afraid anymore.
Let the nightmare end.
It's good that you're alive.
When a house has a tree,
it's not just a house anymore.
It's a home.
You can't even change the name.
Master.
Okay.
What is this?
I found it.
Master, Mr. Rong Yi.
ами
I see.
Master.
There's so much of smoke in the room.
This is what a woman wants the most.
We're living in the same house.
It's not like you don't know why.
When the smoke rises,
Yanran.
There was no place for me to stay.
But I should have stayed by your side
as my all-time favorite.
Yanran!
Qingge!
I'm here.
I can't go back to the past.
The last one of the flash was successful.
That's great.
How is he?
The dream is gone.
He can receive the golden pill.
Your Highness.
Watch out for the fire.
I know it's fire.
I can see everything.
But this red-haired girl
I can't help but be happy.
My body is so numb and painful
that I can't feel anything.
So I want to try
to put this flesh into the fire.
Will I be able to do it?
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Get up.
Xue Yi, have you ever thought
if you were to start over
in this life,
which one would you choose?
I've never thought
that I would never be able to turn back.
No!
There are countless possibilities in life.
In the Three Thousand Realm,
there is always a starting point
that you must start over.
Su Yu!
If you want to destroy the Heavens,
you must act on behalf of the heavens!
Don't touch him.
Xue Yi,
come to my side.
My good third brother
just went to the inn
and was released by Father.
Are you going to do it now?
Why didn't you deal with it?
Just because you were going to the Three Thousand Realm,
so you don't care
about anything here?
Zhou Fei Hua,
how does this matter have anything to do with you?
When did you know it was me?
I can't see clearly,
but from the beginning,
I could feel your body and breath.
After all, we are too familiar.
If you draw your sword for me again today,
would I still be unable to recognize it?
You...
are you not willing to let me go?
Your Highness!
Your Highness, you're awake!
Where am I?
Your Highness,
this place is very far from the capital.
It's very quiet and secluded.
Can you rest here quietly?
How dare you!
You dare to take me hostage?
Do you know what you have done?
You have been in the palace for so long.
Take her away and hide her well.
This place is very high up in the sky.
There are also barriers that block your path.
Your Highness, you can't go back.
Why?
Zhao Fei Hua,
have you ever taken revenge?
Let me go back.
I want to go back!
Just because of those three thousand barriers?
Brother Qing once said that
everything has its rules.
How can a journey against the heavens be free of cost?
The one who told you that everything would change
has ever told you the price?
You know but you don't want to tell me.
That must be a very severe price.
Right?
Your Highness, do you know what this is?
The water in Qizhou has been cleared.
Thanks to Your Highness's three years ago
for not being against each other
and the construction of the farm has been successful.
The officials and the people
all have the provisions to fight the disaster.
Your Highness,
this is a great virtue.
The people are grateful.
The people from all over the country are celebrating
with fireworks.
Your Highness, please pray for us.
Your Highness, in your heart,
there are still people.
Your Highness, your promise...
The saltcarving miscarriage
has been performed on a very large scale.
Please let the honors be contributed
by the Imperial Church for my sake.
It is Su Yueshui.
You're sending someone to catch Jiang Long.
My chance
is to find the person who can make Jiang Long talk
and get rid of the impotent Jiu Tong.
With this,
I will never let him escape.
Let go of me.
I...
I'll help you find Jiang Long.
Xiao...
Don't panic.
I just helped him to untie the spiritual ground
and at the same time, I gave him the power to stop him.
After all,
to catch Qing Long,
you need a huge power.
I've agreed to your deal.
Xiao Wu.
Are you okay?
Just now,
I helped him to get into the death curse.
If you can't find Qing Long within five days,
Xiao Wu will definitely come back
and die in a broken hole.
Don't worry.
Five days later,
I'll find him.
I've heard about Jiang Long.
I won't let him die.
Xiao Shuai.
Ran Ran.
It's great.
You're fine.
It's Master's voice message.
The hidden gold building of Jiuhua Sect
may have records of double-dead ghosts.
You should hurry up
and remember to be careful.
It seems that your Master
has already won the spiritual power.
That's great.
When we find the clues,
we'll go to Ran Ran and find him.
Yes.
I'll go with you.
I'll go with Ran Ran and Master right away.
Wait.
Jiuhua Sect is controlled by the Zhe Yin people.
We have to think of a perfect way.
By the way,
Senior Brother's diamond armor
has been able to break through the East Palace.
We have one more Master Zeng now.
We can successfully sneak into Jiuhua Sect.
Xie Er is right.
It's up to you.
You're not bad.
Let's split up and look for him.
I found him!
The book says that if we can find the first infected person
who can break through the Zhe Yin people,
after we kill his Zhe Yin people,
the rest of the Zhe Yin people will be eliminated.
That's great.
Let's quickly bring this news back.
Gao Mu,
you're here.
I'm here.
You recovered so quickly.
Very good.
Give it to me.
Let go of me.
Let go of me!
It was a dream.
My spiritual power has decreased.
He's acting like a dream.
He's taking my spiritual power?
You still took the Jiu Tang Sect's head.
Xiao Wu!
What's wrong?
I have some questions.
Do you still remember the origin of the Ice Lotus Pool?
You were the one who took my spiritual power
to the Sky Mountain to protect me.
Do you still remember the lantern I made for you?
Every time I return to the West Mountain,
you always leave me a lantern
to light up the path ahead.
In the cave of the Five-Horse Formation,
you personally lit up the entire cave.
But in this life,
you forgot the past
and broke the lantern I made for you.
Only later did I realize
that I had taken the
wrong path.
Do you still remember
how you took me to the West Mountain?
And the wood chips on your head?
How many times did I give them to you?
Can you still remember them?
You were worried
if I would be able to remember them?
I remembered everything.
Every little bit of us
is engraved in my heart.
Only when you fall in love with me again,
will the soul-washing talisman be broken.
So, in order to not hurt me,
you'd rather break your own golden azoth.
For me,
you'd rather sacrifice all that moment
to remember everything, right?
Fortunately, this time,
I didn't hurt you again.
What fortunately?
If I had known that it would be so dangerous,
I would have broken your soul-washing talisman.
I'd rather you didn't remember the past.
I only pray that you are safe and sound.
That won't do.
Only if you remember everything that happened to us,
wouldn't I be very ashamed?
Until I entered the Demon Realm
and heard what you said,
I only knew that
you took my spiritual power
to protect the people.
But it was also because you saw
the ending of me being trapped in the Heaven Book
and being possessed by the Demon,
and being in a state of disarray.
That's why you wanted to save me.
Even if you defy the Heaven,
you still wanted to change my fate.
I didn't know about all of this.
You've done so much for me.
I know nothing.
Xiaoshui,
I saw your heart in your dream.
You always feel sorry for me.
You think
if I hadn't met you from the beginning,
I would have been better, right?
That's not true.
Have you ever thought about the opposite?
I'm very happy
that I can meet you.
Whether it's in the past or in this life,
it's always like this.
Even if there are twists and turns in life,
and difficulties,
in life,
there's no right to do what you want.
The experiences we've had together
make me feel that
every day we've had
is full of life and death.
I'm so happy
that I can meet you.
I'm not a living person.
I'm a living person.
I made some medicinal food.
You can eat it while it's hot.
Xiaoshui, let go.
You have to listen to your master
or I'll punish you.
Master?
Are you my master now,
or am I?
What should I do?
I was the one who took you as my disciple.
There must be a way.
Of course I'm your master.
You have to listen.
Fine.
But,
there's still a chance to turn the tables.
And unfortunately,
I'm...
Dragon God.
It seems that Su Yishui's problem is solved.
Then I'm relieved.
Thank you for your kindness.
You've caused a lot of trouble for Long Island.
You're the saviors of Qing Luo.
As long as you're safe,
everything will be fine.
Qing Luo?
This reminds me of something important.
Dun Tian is going to start the Three Thousand Sects.
He's going to the Great Ling to sell his position.
He needs to use the Three-Sons to make a living.
I saw it on Long Island that day.
Dun Tian needs the son of the Demon.
So he's been trying to lure you into the Demon.
As for the son of the Emperor,
he's Su Yu.
But the third son...
The third son is the son of the Dragon.
The son of the Dragon?
I've learned from Dun Tian.
To start the Three Thousand Sects,
you need to gather the son of the Emperor,
the son of the Dragon, and you.
Although the demon in my body is out,
I won't be the demon he wants anymore.
But I was always forced to escape from the Ling Quan.
Dun Tian has been in the dark for so many years.
I'm afraid he won't have any other preparations.
So I think we have to guard Long Island.
Please be careful, Dragon God.
Qing Luo and the others are playing around the island.
I'll go get them back.
To strengthen the barrier of Long Island.
In case something happens.
Dun Tian needs the third son
to start the Three Thousand Sects.
I'm afraid he won't let you go easily.
You have to be careful.
Then just now...
The West Mountain is in trouble.
Zeng Yi and Gao Cao have already arrived at Cuiwei Mountain.
Master.
Yes.
What happened?
There's good news and bad news.
The good news is that we've found a way to eliminate the Veiled Man.
As long as we kill the first Veiled Man of the Double-Eye-Devil,
the other Veiled Man will naturally disappear.
That means...
the other Veiled Man will disappear?
Yes.
That means we have to find out who is the first Veiled Man.
This is good news. What about the bad news?
We wanted to return to the West Mountain
and tell the news to He Da Bai.
But we just arrived at the entrance of the mountain and found a blue blood stain.
I didn't think they would still attack the West Mountain.
Did you get stained by those blue blood?
Fortunately, you gave us a special pill.
The pill will not disappear until the end of time.
This will not affect our scent.
What about the others?
When we arrived at the mountain,
we already used the scent of the single-leaf clover to detect the wrong ones
and prepared to lure the enemy.
But we didn't even see the shadow of the enemy.
Those blue blood stains were like rain.
Many people were attacked.
Wen Hong Shan and Yan Liang Yu, two seniors,
took advantage of the opportunity and sent out a full-scale formation.
They took some people to escape and are now hiding in the mountains.
I didn't expect that the West Mountain could not be helped.
Fortunately, the Cui Wei Mountain has already set up a barrier.
But the shadow of the enemy still cannot be easily defeated.
The West Mountain is out of control.
The Ling Mai is now in the hands of the Heaven.
I'm afraid that his plan has been pushed further.
The first shadow of the enemy to be eliminated
is the fastest way to get the Ling Mai back.
Who?
Be careful. He is the shadow of the enemy.
The power of the shadow is so weak that
you still dare to sneak around here.
Who is sneaking around?
I came to find someone to cooperate.
I know who is the first person like this.
You...
Let me go!
It seems that he didn't want to live.
That day, I met that double-headed ghost.
I thought he had killed Tu Jiu Yuan.
I cut his head in a fit of rage.
I just had a little bit of blood on my hands.
So you mean that the shadow of the enemy is Yuan Tong?
I was the first to be attacked.
The shadow of the enemy is a double-headed ghost.
It is infected and then re-invaded.
After you killed him, the blood was still wet.
That is indeed a good thing.
You are the first one.
You don't know that the fake goods
were not able to kill me on the spot.
Instead, you used another way to poison me.
But when you fall asleep, you are in a dream.
You are in need of spiritual power.
That's right!
Every time I close my eyes,
I can see someone who looks exactly like me.
He is holding my neck and breathing on me.
What are you looking at?
I have not closed my eyes for a few days
just to prevent the fake goods.
Even more despicable is that he...
Why do I smell a strong smell of vinegar?
I came to look for you because I was lost.
Otherwise, you would think that I wanted to see you two
kissing each other.
Just tell me.
Are all these strange things related to that...
Dun Tian?
That's right.
Then I have found the right person.
When I was in the You Realm, he was the one who attacked you.
He is the one who came to you.
In the end,
I owe you everything.
So, if you don't solve all these problems,
I will not spare you.
If I am killed,
No need to say that.
Because of the death of so many people,
we must solve the current crisis as soon as possible.
But, what is Dun Tian doing with so many people?
What does he want to do?
He wants to use the Zhe Yin Man to control the Xuan Gate.
He wants to open the four doors of the Xuan Gate and the spiritual veins of the Immortal Mountain
to build the Three Thousand Towers.
Three Thousand Towers?
What is that?
There are three thousand in the world.
One is a thousand and one is a thousand.
There are different existences of us in every world.
There are even different immortals.
The Three Thousand Towers
are the entrances to the Three Thousand Parallel Realms.
Every realm has different us?
Then...
Then, what is Dun Tian trying to do?
He wants to enter the Three Thousand Towers
to find a parallel realm that he is satisfied with.
In that realm, he did not choose to fly.
He stayed with his wife.
The family shared the joy of the Celestial Wheel.
Dun Tian regrets it.
He wants to replace that realm's self
and come back.
There is such a regret in the world?
I am not a person who can regret it.
Why do you have such a regret?
The realm and the realm are separate and separate.
They are not connected.
If you want to forcefully cross the realm,
you have to pay a huge price.
That is to destroy
the realm we are in.
Only if our world becomes a cloud
and the jade in the Three Thousand Towers
will completely collapse.
Only then will its path
truly begin.
He treats me as a pawn
and let out the devil's devil's devil.
Now he wants to kill me and rely on himself.
It was not easy for him to get all this.
Stop thinking about it!
It is a good thing that the Three Towers in the Three Thousand Towers
are no longer under the control of Dun Tian.
Now, we just have to get rid of
the people from all the sects
and get back the spiritual vein.
Then Dun Tian will have no other choice.
Perfect.
You help me get back the Chiyan Mountain.
We can then solve
that fake goods that pretended to be mine.
We can then solve that fake goods that pretended to be mine.
Let's work together.
You want to persuade us to help you get back the Mountain Gate?
We indeed have to go to Chiyan Mountain
to get rid of that person who is your enemy.
But we can do this ourselves.
Now, you are low on spiritual power
and only have the remaining specks left.
What use is it to you?
I know a secret path.
We can sneak into the inner part of Chiyan Mountain
and kill them without any hurry.
We can save a lot of trouble.
Deal.
But,
if we sneak into Chiyan Mountain, we can't kill them.
We also have to prevent
being stained by the blue blood.
I've been studying the shadow of Zhao Ying
for the past few days.
If I wear this on my body,
once I have something to collect,
I can turn it into a shadow barrier
and protect people from it.
I'm thinking of a way to strengthen it.
I should be able to block the blue blood.
Bai Shan,
these past two days, help Uncle Zhao Ying
to make these shadows.
Yes, Master.
Once we have done this, we can immediately go to Chiyan Mountain.
Wait.
There's one more thing.
I know a secret path to Chiyan Mountain.
But I have a condition.
Su Yushui,
sleep with me.
I haven't slept for several days.
That fake goods
is just a demon power
that can take advantage of my
tiredness and lack of sleep.
It's a spiritual power.
But if I can use a strong
spiritual power to disturb it,
it won't work.
Help me protect it.
I'm not interested.
Su Yushui,
I'm with you now.
If I die, it's not good for you.
Just let me
sleep peacefully.
I promise,
I won't bother you in the future.
Su Yushui,
only you and Brother Mu Qing's
two skills can help me protect it.
If you don't help me,
then I'll go to Brother Mu Qing.
There's a beautiful girl
in the back.
She's a romantic ghost.
Beauty Mu,
I...
Come with me.
Master and Wei Jiu,
will they be in trouble?
Give me some peace.
Don't worry.
I have you.
I won't bother Beauty Mu.
Then I won't bother you.
Sleep here.
I haven't slept so comfortably for a long time.
Get out when you wake up.
You helped me absorb the spiritual power
from that fake body.
I'm afraid you'll drag your hind legs.
I've always been
a man of my word.
I'm afraid you'll drag your hind legs.
I'm always clear about my grudges.
I'll repay you.
You're helping me.
Tell me.
How do you want me to thank you?
Then please
throw away the rest of the quilt.
I love clean clothes.
I can't stand it.
I'm wearing a uniform with a lot of fabric.
I changed to a new one after I came out of Chiyan Mountain.
It's very clean.
You're loyal to the clan.
You're quite a man of your word.
You...
I...
You dare to threaten me?
You didn't sleep last night
because you were worried about Wei Jiu, right?
I'm very sleepy.
I haven't recovered from my injury.
Then after you finish your breakfast,
you can go rest for a while.
Don't worry about Zeng Yi and their magic weapons.
I'll help you.
What's so fragrant?
Buns?
It's really delicious.
Beauty Mu,
did you make this?
The sweet potato you gave me
was very delicious.
I didn't expect that
you would make something better.
Sweet potato?
When we were in the Tianmai Mountain,
you were healing and sitting down.
I saw that he was very hungry,
so I gave him some.
You didn't finish it?
Don't you know how sweet that sweet potato is?
Shut your mouth after you eat the buns.
Wei Jiu!
Did you drink up all the good wine
that you hid in your brain?
You said you were lost.
Can you be a little more patient?
Drinking a glass of wine
is a sign of your alcoholism.
Fine.
Let's not talk about the wine.
I saw you just now
throw away the quilt
that Ran Ran sewed for Su Yushui.
I couldn't stop it.
Su Yushui was seriously injured
and unconscious that day.
Ran Ran
stayed up for several nights
and sewed it by herself.
Where did you throw it?
I just found a mountain top and threw it away.
I don't know where it fell.
Where is he?
I looked all over the mountain
but I couldn't find him.
Are you a very virtuous man?
I didn't know it was you who sewed the quilt.
Otherwise, I wouldn't let Wei Jiu run away.
It's just a normal quilt.
If you lost it, then you lost it.
Why bother to look for it?
This is not a normal quilt.
It's the quilt you sewed for me.
It's more important than anything.
Fine.
If you like it,
I'll embroider a bamboo for you.
I'll be happy if you like it.
How about I embroider a bamboo for you?
If you can,
it's better to embroider a pair of round eyes.
You're quite good at it, Xiao Shui.
Don't forget
I'm the master now.
No one can be a master like you.
You can't even write a quilt.
I'll teach you.
Done.
So, the quilt-washing thing
can make people so satisfied.
Shan Shan,
you don't know how much I cherish
what's in front of me.
So, I won't let Dun Tian succeed
and take it away.
You two were here.
It's a bright day.
You two...
You two are all masters.
You don't practice.
You don't care about the situation.
You're so stubborn.
Why do you always like to talk about it?
Master Wei,
you're just saying that
grapes are sour.
You're not a person
who doesn't love you.
Tu Jiuyuan is willing to
sacrifice his life for you.
But you don't know your own good.
You...
He used to
sacrifice his life for me.
But I can't believe
he was so rude to me
in Chiyan Mountain that day.
I don't dare to think
if he's already...
Are you worried that
Tu Jiuyuan is fake now?
And he's dead now?
That bastard
won't even let go
of my wife and child.
I won't let him go either.
Wife and child.
If he accepts you,
he'll climb up the pole himself.
I...
And I heard that
there's a demon in the back of Chiyan Mountain.
Do you really think that
you can survive
if you fall into a coma?
Is it because you're lucky?
What do you mean?
You mean
he was the one who protected me that day?
Give us some more time
and have some luck.
When we lose,
our body and soul
will never change.
Go and buy some daily things
so that you don't get any jelly.
Give us then.
I'm here to tell you that Zhao Yongzhong has recovered.
We're going to kill him and save his wife and child.
It doesn't matter if he recognizes him. I'll recognize him anyway.
It's the direction of Jiuhua Sect.
Jiuhua Sect's spiritual vein has been opened.
Without Kai Ta's eye, there's no sign of the beast in his hand.
The shield hasn't given up on opening the Three-thousand-striking-Way Pillar.
It's true that he's hiding some kind of secret.
What secret is he hiding?
No matter what, we have to kill all the people of Zhe Ying.
We have to take back the Xuan Gate and close all the spiritual veins.
He has no three-thousand-striking-Way Pillar and no spiritual vein. What else can we do?
Let the Nine Immortals and Liang Wu Meng stay in the Mountain of Cuiwei.
Let's save a place first.
The rest of us, let's head to the Mountain of Seven Night.
What is that?
The Xuan Gate's spiritual vein should be in the direction of Mount Kong Sect.
The shield is about to open the Three-thousand-striking-Way Pillar.
So you still want to go to the place where you said it's the most suitable for Hu Xin Yi.
Whoever doesn't want to try what I want,
I have too many regrets, too many regrets.
Since I have such a chance, of course I have to try something different.
Your Highness, do you still remember him?
I don't believe it.
I can't conquer this little peach tree.
When I learn it, I'll blow it for you.
Okay.
It's really good to be young.
But...
I don't know how to be young.
I'm still young.
It's a pity that I can't go back to the past.
This peach tree is just a piece of object.
It's not even the same as before.
It's just a memory related to it that can bring back the love and memories in your heart.
Do you think that the so-called Hu Xin Yi's memory has that kind of thing?
The Qing Ge you've been waiting for,
in that world, he won't have that kind of experience and memory with you.
What's the point?
I can hear these songs every day.
What are they singing?
What they're singing is a song for peace and prosperity.
And they're praying that life like this can last forever.
The Wu family is old and young, hoping that I'll return.
Hurry and return home.
The water is so bitter.
What? You want me to plant this thing into the dust
and then kill it?
Please spare me, Your Majesty. I was just confused. I won't do it again.
When did you know that I was fake?
Did you do it quickly when I was kidnapped?
I don't know anything. I don't have that kind of ability.
Please spare me, Your Majesty.
Is this the secret passage you're talking about? What's the difference between it and the dog cave?
The secret passage naturally has to be hidden.
Could it be that I have to set up a pig's trotter gate?
The sky is blue, the clouds are dark.
The tears are like dreams, this part of me is so lonely, I'm already in tears.
The moon in front of me is returning, my heart is still watered down.
The tears in my eyes are still not resolved.
The wind is still blowing on my side.
With you by my side, I'm not afraid of the world.
If I could only have one more year,
I would be willing to sacrifice myself for you.
The moon in front of me is returning, my heart is still watered down.
The wind is still blowing on my side.
With you by my side, I'm not afraid of the world.
If I could only have one more year, I would be willing to sacrifice myself for you.
If I could only have one more year,
I would be willing to sacrifice myself for you.
I could not escape from this fate,
hoping that we could turn back time.
I once thought of you in my heart,
but we met again when I was in the prime of my life.