wasn't foolish enough to conspire against Her Highness.
The M defining of The W Policy
I will face the love and hate of the world.
I only wish to travel a few times,
travel to the north and west,
and only when I have achieved my goal will I understand the value of it.
Even if I know that I will return one day,
I will be destined to lose myself.
But I will not regret it.
The love and hate of the world.
Episode 16
Master!
Yaoshu!
Everything!
The Star-Breaking River!
The Star-Breaking River?
Mo Xi,
why?
Why are you willing to break everything for her?
Why?
If I could meet someone like that back then,
I would hate her so much!
The Royal Water Spirit has been used up.
Why did Xiao San suddenly leave?
Where else would he want to go?
Rong Yao.
It's you. Duan Tian, it's really you.
You shouldn't be like this.
It's been hundreds of years.
Hundreds of years!
Have you ever thought about what I should have been like?
When you abandoned me and my daughter,
have you ever thought about what we would have become?
Duan Tian, you have regretted it.
Shut up!
I was the one who should have killed the King of the Fogs!
It wasn't because you wanted me to fight for the right path!
I did it for justice.
I did it for the sake of the people!
Back then, I thought about it twice.
But I couldn't do it.
But now, I can get everything back!
I can make everything happen again!
Get everything back?
You can't get everything back.
You can't give up on the happiness and happiness you once had.
But now, you're just losing it forever!
You're not Rong Yao.
You're not qualified to talk about it here.
Get lost!
I should have taken the medicine.
Rong Yao,
Rong Yao, I can get everything back now.
I can get everything back now.
I will definitely reunite with my family.
Xiao Shui.
What did you call me?
Who told you to call me that?
Don't be like your sister.
No.
I should have told you the truth.
Actually, I...
Mu Qing Ge,
how dare you use your method to harm Ran Ran?
You're looking for death!
I'm not!
I'm Mu Ran Wu!
What did you say?
It's just that Mu Qing Ge's spirit and spirit roots are on me.
Forget it.
Don't you know who Mu Qing Ge really is?
Didn't you see the spirit and spirit of the heart just now?
In this world, besides Mu Qing Ge,
who else can use such a trick?
It's him who's been lying to you.
What?
You finally figured it out.
Since you lost your memory,
you can't just pretend that I've been lying to you.
The person you should be blaming is him!
Even now,
you're still like this.
I never thought that
our sisterhood
would actually fail like this.
I don't believe what she said.
I only listen to you.
That's right.
I'm Mu Qing Ge.
You...
You actually lied to me!
You said that I should fall in love with you again.
These are all your tricks to achieve your goal!
You're indeed the Mu Mei that I've been thinking about.
Whether it's in this life or in the next,
you've been holding on to your little disciple.
Su Yi Shui,
you haven't improved at all in the past 20 years.
You've been played around.
Are you excited?
It's not like that.
Then what is it?
I did lie to you about my identity.
But I didn't mean to.
It's because...
Because you've forgotten a lot of things.
I don't know...
You can't make it up?
Su Yi Shui,
I know my sister the best.
If she's determined to help the Emperor and be a good person,
that's the most enjoyable thing.
In the past, many people were as caring as you.
When she was a teacher,
she was so obedient to you.
Now that she's a disciple,
she's been loved by you.
She's really a fool!
Whether it's Mu Qing Ge or Xue Ran Ran,
killing or punishing is my own business.
Now she's my disciple.
How can I educate my own disciple?
I don't need to see you people having fun.
Oh no!
I'll go back to the set to find the fire of the crystal.
If I can't kill the demon,
I'll be in trouble!
Hurry up! We must stop him!
Let's go.
Hurry up!
You've been lying to me for so long.
Mu Qing Ge, you're so capable.
Did I lie to you about money or your color?
You're so wronged.
If you had taken the soul-gathering talisman,
you would have known my identity.
But I'm your teacher,
but I'm your disciple.
Su Yi Shui, you're so treacherous!
I...
You must have used some trick.
I'll keep you by my side.
Fine, I used tricks.
I lied to you.
When everything is over, I'll leave.
We don't need to be teachers or disciples.
We can just break up.
How dare you!
I...
I mean, how can we break up
our grudges?
At least...
I'll make you pay for it.
Su Yi Shui, you're so ungrateful.
So what if I'm Mu Qing Ge?
I've raised you so well.
I've given you enough time.
Now,
I remember our relationship.
It's so bad.
Since you hate me so much,
I'll ask the Nine Immortals to give me another soul-gathering talisman.
I'll also clean up your memory.
Then,
we'll be strangers.
It's over.
Hey!
If I knew I wouldn't help this girl
to get rid of her old spirit,
I wouldn't have asked her to get angry with me.
Master!
Are you okay?
Don't call me master!
Then I should call you Shui.
Or,
I should call you Mr. Su?
Are you trying to remind me
that I'm older than you?
If I wanted to remind you of this,
I wouldn't call you Mr. Su.
I would call you Uncle Su.
Uncle Su?
You...
Why did I
have to live with you
like a demoness?
Forget it.
I don't want to talk to you.
Let's go to the Golden Fire first.
Uncle Ye Xin.
You're like my daughter.
I can't bear to kill you.
But it's okay.
It's all temporary.
After I complete the plan,
I will never treat you badly.
Plan?
What do you want to do?
I just
want to get my wife back
and let everything
start over.
There's nothing in this world
that can make time go back
and make the past come back.
Do you know that there are three thousand realms?
Three thousand realms?
Dun Tian once told me
that there are three thousand realms.
Each realm has a different us.
Dun Tian wants to go to
a world where he didn't choose to fly
or sacrifice his wife.
He wants to start over.
Three thousand realms is the way to the three thousand worlds.
Dun Tian wants to take the Golden Fire
to imitate the King of the Human's Tomb
and start the three thousand realms.
No.
He doesn't want the Golden Fire.
The King of the Human's Tomb
has created the Golden Fire
to eliminate his evil spirit.
The King of the Human's Tomb
couldn't have used it.
Dun Tian must have a conspiracy
to lure everyone to the Golden Fire.
Luckily, the Golden Fire
is still in the Xuan Tian tribe.
I won't have to waste my time.
I found it.
The Golden Fire.
I finally got it.
Go back!
Don't act rashly!
It depends on whether you have the ability.
Don't hurt them.
Don't let the soul master get hurt.
Yes!
Go!
Who is Su Ye?
Master.
I asked Mo Zhi Xian
if he would agree to take the Golden Fire.
Go!
Watch out!
Everyone, stop!
Ran Ran!
The King of the Human's Tomb
hasn't been completely destroyed.
The spirit power is the spirit stone of the King of the Human's Tomb.
Xiao Shui is Mo Zi.
Could it be that Dun Tian's purpose
is to...
No!
Don't touch the Golden Fire!
There's a trap!
Break the barrier!
Stop!
How did you get the Glazed Bead
from the Xuan Tian tribe?
How... how are you?
I've been...
I've been keeping my promise.
You don't want to break the soul stone,
but you want to get the Golden Fire.
You just want to get the Golden Fire.
I told you not to do anything.
Do you think you can
just watch me
and not let me
help you clean up the mess?
You're a mess.
You've done a lot of work.
What do you want?
But I don't mind.
Even if you don't think about me.
I've already fulfilled my promise.
Please,
Your Majesty, let me go.
You...
Still not working.
Wei Jiu's power is so strong.
We can't break his barrier.
This is wrong.
Oh no!
The Demon King's skull!
Wei Jiu trapped us here
to use the evil aura to kill us.
It's the Night-Soul Skill.
I have to get rid of it.
Try to seal it
when the evil aura comes in.
I'm scared.
It's dangerous.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
Master.
Let go of him.
Yuan Ran.
Yuan Ran, are you okay?
What's going on?
Stop struggling.
The power that I have
is the destiny of the Demon King.
It seems that the evil aura
that the Demon King left
wants to take the Demon King's body.
Let's stand up and suppress him.
Okay. Everyone, stand up.
Su Yi Shui.
You're so confused
that you want to fight with me.
Do you think it's useful?
Yuan Ran.
Master.
I've already
dried the Chiyuan paper
and cleared the passage
of the evil aura.
Su Yi Shui.
That's the spiritual power
that you sealed.
Xiao Shui.
You're so stupid.
Stop.
Wu Ying.
Su Yi Shui.
The Demon King's
destiny is
to let go of the Demon King.
You all
should do whatever you want
in this world.
It's so easy.
Now I'm one with the spirit bone.
I can be like this.
If you want to get rid of me,
then Su Yi Shui will be dead.
And you
can't kill me.
I'll kill you today
and kill you.
Your body
hasn't been devoured by the demon.
You haven't taken this body.
Master.
Fan Yue.
You're so weak.
Master.
He's really possessed.
So the Demon King
has escaped from the world.
Where's the Demon King?
Ran Ran.
What happened?
He reopened the seal.
So the power of the spirit bone
has been in the Demon King's body.
Please
work with me.
Use the power of the Heavenly Emperor
to seal this gap.
Don't let the Demon King
take the body.
This is the most important thing.
Let's solve this first.
The Demon King
has been saved.
It's time to go back.
Master.
I'll wait for you.
Su Yishui, why are you fighting against me?
The people around you are angry with you, angry with you, and hiding from you.
Are you only worthy of being a pawn that they can settle?
Do you think they can manipulate you?
As the son of the devil,
you are born to be respected and strong.
You should be the sign of all the fates in this world.
Su Yishui,
you are the son of the devil.
You are the son of the devil.
You are the master of all fates.
Su Yishui, what's wrong with you?
Don't come any closer.
I've brought all the fuchsia seeds.
Just plant them.
Don't come any closer.
I see.
You want to use the daughter of the devil to get rid of me.
Your spiritual power will also be taken away.
You'd rather be a loser
than save my life?
You...
You are Su Yishui who has been washed out.
You are the only link between you and her past self.
A little blood connection
and the experience of sharing the same blood and bones
will make her believe in you.
The devil is as good as nothing.
Even if she is a little scared,
she will be swallowed by the devil
without any certainty or anxiety.
She will be led to the devil by the devil.
Why do you waste your energy?
You...
Yue Chen.
You are not Su Xiaoxiao.
Of course I am not the Su Xiaoxiao
who has full hope for you.
I came back from hell.
You abandoned me.
I hate you.
You forgot the promise you made to me.
You said that everyone can only be under your feet.
But what happened?
Why did you give up your promise?
For what?
For a woman to give up everything.
Do you believe in this nonsense?
I don't believe it.
How we suffered
and were hurt so much
have you forgotten it?
What did I do for?
Only useless people ask why.
To be me, to be the strongest and the most respected.
You are the only answer in the world.
Brother.
I finally could rest my body.
It was Frei Dantian who set this up.
I'm not sure where he is.
I have a big plan to settle this.
All the things that happened
and what we have been speculating on
are all these.
What is the Three Thousand Towers?
The Demon King destroyed it for hundreds of years.
There are no records about the Three Thousand Towers.
People only know
that it's a demon tower that destroyed the heaven and earth.
But they don't know
that it's related to the Heaven-resisting Spell you mentioned.
This is the information I collected from the Three Thousand Towers.
In fact, the Heaven and Earth are so small
that it's not only the world that we live in and know.
There are three thousand worlds.
There are you and me in each of them.
There are all living beings in each of them.
So if we say that the Demon King wants to revive his wife and children,
it's better to say that he wants to go to another world
and find the origin of his wife and children
and start over.
So,
the way to connect the Three Thousand Towers
is the Three Thousand Towers.
This is a game against the heavens.
It requires huge energy and a very high price.
To open the Three Thousand Towers,
we have to use all the dangers in this world.
That's why I said that the Three Thousand Towers
will destroy the heaven and earth.
You mean
that the Heaven and Earth will destroy this world we live in?
Do you
believe what he said?
Elder Yan,
is Dun Tian your ancestor of the Jiuhua Sect?
Dun Tian is a very capable person.
He was a man of many years ago.
I don't know his character.
But I and Junior Wen,
with Miss Xue and Clan Leader Su,
have traveled around the world together
and seen many things.
So I won't question their relationship anymore.
You should also make your judgment.
Now, this is a matter of my Xuanmen Qi heart.
I just don't know
how to open the Three Thousand Towers.
What should we do
to stop his plan?
This is the
Destruction Technique.
It's a skill that all mortals
can't compete with.
Moreover,
there are demons and demons around him.
Why do we practice immortality?
To protect the world and the people.
To achieve Taoism.
Now is the time for us to make an effort.
To lure the demon into the demon,
it should be to open
the ring in the Three Thousand Towers.
It's also an important step.
But only the demon is not enough.
He must have a follow-up action.
So please
check the information in detail.
Then find the follow-up action
of the Three Thousand Towers.
Is that all?
But the Demon King...
I'll go to Wei Jiu
to ask for the Golden Fire to solve this matter.
But I have a request.
After the Demon King is clear,
please allow me to use the Golden Fire.
You want...
My master is still alive.
The Golden Fire
can help me to pull him back.
If I want to use him,
I won't let him succeed.
I'll go back to theWelcome
What's wrong with the water lamp?
libation.
I was walking on the run.
You won't die as yet,
I will kill
you in the end.
Jin Mi and Taoabi
a centipede
is a righteous person
Mother
Demon King
Father,
do you want to go back to the time when we were on the top?
I would believe you?
You are standing here now
because I made it happen.
There is nothing in this world
that can be done without changing.
We both had our own positions back then.
Who said that now
we wouldn't cooperate
for the sake of the same goal?
Why?
Back then, you wanted to open the Three Thousand-Way Tower
and leave the Demon Realm
and leave those demons in the mortal world.
And my wish came true.
I just hope
that my wife and I can go back to the time when we first met.
You are going to open the Three Thousand-Way Tower?
Interesting.
It's very interesting.
Don't talk anymore.
Rest.
Clan Leader Wei is good at scheming.
He made others suffer because of the Soul Master.
But he still held the Golden Fire in his hand.
For the sake of your good use of the Gu Yuan Pellet
for Tu Jiuyuan,
I won't be mad at you.
Why are you still here?
Aren't you in a rush to find your
good master who has been possessed by the demon?
I'm going.
Are you really going to find your good master?
You should first settle the score.
If you didn't risk your life to take the Golden Fire,
how could the following things have happened?
What do you want?
I want to take the Golden Fire.
I also want you, Xuantian Sect, to cooperate with the Xuan Sect
to destroy the Demon Realm with the power of the Golden Fire
and save the world.
The Golden Fire was taken by my men
after they put their lives into it.
Why should I give it to you?
I'm not discussing it with you.
Don't you think that the world is in chaos
and you can control the demons with the Golden Fire
and you can be at ease?
This time, Duantian has attracted the Xuan Sect to Chiyan Mountain.
Aren't you also deeply hurt?
What he wants to destroy
is the heaven and earth where we live.
At this time,
are you still thinking of cleaning yourself up?
You...
Miss Xue is right.
The Golden Fire entered the Amber Pillar
and it did have an external effect.
I'm afraid that it's Duantian who did it.
Honorable Superior should see clearly what's happening.
Are you feeling better?
Then come out and teach me a lesson.
The Golden Fire
was taken by you.
If you're willing to give it to her,
why should I stop you?
Miss Xue and I have a life-saving ability.
Moreover, what she said is also very reasonable.
Okay, okay.
Miss Xue is suitable.
Miss Xue imitates the way of Orphanage...
Master is also suitable.
From now on,
in front of me,
I will tell you everything.
rapidly on time.
XiaoBai
Aren't you going home to rest yet?
It's time for me to go
I
Shopkeeper Xu, hearty representing
To you
Hurry
Don't you dare stand there
Thank you
Do you have 소빙frienda?
Come
Hold on
I'll leave it here if you like it.
If you don't like it, just throw it away.
I have enough of these.
Leave us.
Yes.
In the past,
Chi Wen Ling was the head of the old sect.
He was the leader of the sect.
The old sect leader gave it to you.
Now,
I'm the one who gave you the sect order.
Do you know what this represents?
These are useless to me.
Tu Jiu Yuan,
I'm willing to give you half of the leadership of Xuantian Sect.
You still don't appreciate it?
What else do you want?
I...
If you insist on making me like you,
then I could...
I've told you I'm leaving it here.
Just do as you wish.
Don't be a child
or fool me any longer.
But...
You were readers of order
but gaveịa person mix me up.
But you just said you liked me.
I still don't understand.
You turned away
and became merciless.
You're playing with me
and playing with me.
Listen,
I won't do that.
What I said is true.
The young man's feelings are true.
The feelings he kept for decades are true.
But now,
I have nothing to ask for
or to ask for from you.
I'm afraid that you'll be able to see
the pain I've been through for decades
and let me go.
I just hope
that in the rest of my life,
I can live my own life.
Okay.
I can't keep you.
Why should I ask for it?
Just leave now.
I'm afraid that you'll be able to see
the pain I've been through for decades.
Thank you featured to her Hey Yumal
so as to open up her head.
Shisi, no need.
You've grown old.
You'll be blessed
if you keep praying.
Master, I...
You can call me Ranran.
Ranran, as you wish.
You were drunk at that time, right?
It's been a long time.
It doesn't matter now.
You want to make weapons or weapons?
Just leave it to me.
Thanks to you and Xiaoshui
who took care of Xishan.
Xiaoshui is used to being poisoned.
But with you,
he can still talk.
If he didn't save you even if he tried his best,
I wouldn't have talked to him.
He said that
when you recovered your memory,
he would punish you.
But I knew you wouldn't blame him.
Now he...
Before I went back to Xishan,
Yuchun and Yutong sent me a message
that Xiaoshui is totally possessed.
Yuchun and Yutong were also badly injured
and hurt by the demon aura.
I brought them back
and told them to close the door and rest.
They need to rest for a few years before they can leave.
Take care of them during this period.
Duan Tian is really a man of his word.
If Su Yushui is totally possessed,
then...
I don't believe it.
I'll bring him back.
You'll bring him back.
By the way, master,
the whole Xiong Neng knows
about your identity.
They know that they've mistaken you.
Now they're all under Xishan.
They're so guilty that they dare not come up.
What do you think?
It's not their fault.
But they don't need to come back.
I don't know
what kind of trouble
Xishan will face after this.
Why bother to bring them in?
I'm afraid
there's not much time left.
Master,
the demon Su Yushui
broke into our Jiuhua Mountain.
Where is he now?
He's been bitten by a rock.
You had better tell him.
Tell the
guards,
How dare you touch my Nine Glowing container?
It turns out that you're trying to
Master!
Leave the real person to me.
Su Yi Shui!
Su Yi Shui is no longer here.
What?
Are you here to hide from me?
Su Yi Shui!
I want to return to you, but my heart is still watered down.
I cry for you, but my heart is still watered down.
The moon is in the sky, while I'm in the snow.
The snow is falling, but I'm still in the wind.
I'm not afraid of losing you, I'm afraid of losing the world.
If I could have a year of my life,
I would be with you forever.
I could only dream of the day we could meet again.
Why do I have to go through all the hardships alone?
I could only be with you forever.
If I could have a year of my life,
I would be with you forever.
I could only be with you forever.