=Dawn Amidst Hidden Clouds=
=Episode 2=
Little Patient,
my dad said
you should take your medicine.
I don't want it.
It's sweet.
You lied every time.
I won't fall for it again.
Look. I tried.
It's not bitter at all.
You lied!
Liangzhou is my hometown.
I won't allow anyone
to harm the city.
Mingye.
Dad,
Uncle Lou,
you're back.
Mingye,
play with Qingyao for a while.
I need to talk to Uncle Leng.
Don't lie to me again.
Then you need to take the medicine.
Deal.
Qingyao,
it's time to go home.
Little Patient, see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
Let's go.
(Justice and Virtue)
Dad! What happened?
Dad! Say something!
Dad!
Dad, are you okay?
Say something! Dad!
Dad!
(Lou's Mansion)
My Lord, you're losing
your sense of taste,
but sometimes I envy you.
Without the sense of taste,
you have no desire for food.
Without the desire for food,
you'll have less to worry about.
It's also a blessing.
I can share the blessing with you.
Hardships make heroes.
To become your best
right-hand man,
I should experience more hardships
in this big world.
My Lord.
You can hand over
the Carefree Powder's case
to someone else.
We came all the way to Changjing
only to investigate
the truth about General Lou's death.
We shouldn't be distracted
by something else.
Don't forget
Carefree Powder showed up in Liangzhou
ten years ago,
and my father was murdered by Leng Quji
as he dug into this.
(Justice and Virtue)
My Lord, are you suspecting...?
Carefree Powder showed up again,
and Leng Quji's daughter
suddenly got into this
after disappearing for a decade.
I don't think it's a coincidence.
There might be a bigger conspiracy.
I'll bring her back right now.
No rush.
You'll tip them off.
Keep her
so that we can find Leng Quji.
By the way, My Lord,
(Lan Che's File)
here's her household register.
She's been running a small gang
in recent years.
It's called the Greater World,
and she claims to be the leader.
(No Childhood Information)
The only four members
(Origin: Unknown)
often help their neighbors
(No Parents)
with some daily matters,
nothing important.
Okay. I got it.
(Lan Che's File)
Hurry up.
We need to visit Mrs. Chen Later.
Give back my money!
Guys, calm down!
Please trust us.
The Greater World
will get your money back.
Two consecutive days of protest.
She's impressive.
Give back my money!
I don't think it's a bad thing.
- What are they doing?
- Who are they?
Master Lan Che, do you want to get in?
My Lord.
I heard you saved me yesterday.
Thank you.
Did you get hurt?
Master Lan Che, thanks for your concern.
I'm okay.
My Lord,
you're impressive.
We're the officials.
Open the door.
Let's go.
You two, stay here.
I'll be right back.
Come on.
My Lord, your identity worked.
Your gangster identity will be useful.
We'll see.
My Lord, come in.
Hurry.
My Lord, this way.
My Lord.
Hurry,
get some tea.
Aye.
Have a seat.
My Lady.
My condolences, My Lady.
My husband
used to be an herbalist.
He was an honest
and righteous person,
and was always kind to the servants.
No one ever said
bad things about him.
However, I never expected
he'd sell illegal drugs.
She's already
dissociated herself.
She doesn't seem
to love him that much.
My Lord,
have some tea.
(Obvious, everyone in the Chen Family)
(is involved in Carefree Powder.)
Did Chen Zhisong do
anything strange in the past few days?
I don't think so.
However,
his birthday is coming.
We were going to
celebrate it together.
Who'd have thought...?
Chen Zhisong!
He knows what he's doing.
He was afraid of
being killed by his boss,
so he prepared Fake Death Pill
in advance.
I think he works for
a man named Wu Ming.
Was Wu Ming invited
to his birthday party?
Wu Ming?
My husband has never mentioned
this name before.
My Lord,
will when the mobs at the door leave?
And can we take back
my lord's body?
It's not
up to Lord Lou.
You should
ask me.
May I ask
know your name?
I'm Lan Che,
also known as
Little Dragon.
(Chen's Mansion)
What's your name?
Fang Tingge.
I'm Luo, and this is Dao.
Lan Che is our boss.
I know.
That's great.
Bro,
I have a question.
Did someone
kill Chen Zhisong after his fake death?
Can't comment.
It must be someone
who knew he faked his death.
Is it Chen San?
Can't comment.
Not Chen San?
Then it must be his family.
After all, that charlatan
would never tell others...
Can't comment.
Can anyone
at the Justice Department talk?
We'll only say
what we're supposed to say.
My Lord,
look, your boss and my boss
met each other twice
in the big city of Changjing.
It must be God's plan.
Can you please tell me something?
God's plan?
If my lord hadn't known Lan Che...
Tell me more.
I'm all ears.
My Lady,
do you know
how many bad things he did
and people he offended?
Do you have any idea
how much would people pay
for your family's lives?
Now you're
the lamb to the slaughter.
Do you really think
they'll let you get away?
It was Lord Chen who did all of this.
It has...
nothing to do with us!
My Lord,
please help us!
My Lady, don't worry.
However, the Justice Department
only cares about dead people.
If you really want us to do something,
this one...
What's your nickname again?
Little Dragon.
The slaughter Little Dragon mentioned
has to do something first.
My Lady!
He's asking us to wait for death.
What should we do?
Listen to me. My boss...
My Lord.
Send the land and house deeds we seized
to my mansion.
Aye.
Come on. Get out of here.
- You can only take his properties!
- Get out.
This is my dowry!
You can't take it!
Give it back!
- My Lord.
- You can't take it!
I didn't expect
our first cooperation
to be a huge success.
We're perfect partners!
My Lady! Are you okay?
My Lady!
It seems Chen Zhisong
has been betrayed for a long time.
As Chen Zhisong's wife,
why would she take
a personal item from the butler
so naturally?
Be careful, My Lady.
Perhaps
Mrs. Chen and the butler
conspired to kill him
to take over his properties
and get together.
But how did they know
you'd unmask Chen Zhisong
yesterday?
Are you
their ally?
Your mission is completed.
Just go.
Anything else?
My Lord.
We've tried our best
to help you
solve this case.
We've made contributions,
right?
You're still trying to get that deed.
Do you own that house?
Hurry.
My neighbor Madam Wang
was deceived by Chen Zhisong
and gave him that house.
Now she's a miserable
homeless old lady.
Whether she can be saved
is up to you, My Lord.
I heard you're from Changjing.
Yes.
I was born and brought up here.
I just came here.
Everything is new to me.
I could use a clever assistant.
Why don't you stay
and work for me?
If you say yes,
you'll get
that deed.
(I'm a gang leader.)
(How dare he ask me
to be his assistant?)
My Lord,
a fortune teller
once told me
to stay away from the Lous,
or we'd get each other
killed.
My Lord,
you happen to be a Lou.
We should
keep our distance for your safety.
My Lord,
farewell.
Let's go!
My Lord,
is Lan Che the person
you're looking for?
What's wrong?
If she was Leng Qingyao,
why would she ignore you
when she met you?
Even if you looked different
after all these years,
she'd at least remember your name.
Did she pretend
to have forgotten you?
Am I mistaken,
or are you lying to me?
Leng Qingyao.
(Huanxi Clinic)
It's enough.
So dramatic.
Did Lou Mingye
offer you a job as his assistant?
I rejected him.
I just told you yesterday
to stay away from him.
Look at you,
seizing any chances to meet him, right?
Why do you have to piss me off?
I didn't seize any chance!
I never knew he'd be there.
Master,
it's not her fault.
His assistant told me
Lord Lou went to Chen's Mansion
because he knew
Boss was there.
Why?
He saved you yesterday.
And went to Chen's Mansion
for you.
Is he in love with you?
After all, I'm a popular girl,
so it's possible.
Stop dreaming.
He's the Lord Chancellor.
Why would he like you?
Because you're ignorant and eat a lot?
I think it's because she's ignorant.
It'll be easy for him to persuade her
to go back to Liangzhou with him.
No.
I think it's because she eats a lot.
The more you eat, the stronger you are,
and the more work you can do.
Shut up.
Who's strong?
I'm old
but not dead.
How dare you ignore me?
Master,
you're not old.
Look at you,
eating well and sleeping well every day.
You're even stronger than Dao,
- right?
- I...
Yes, that's right.
- What? You...
- Master!
- What?
- Master.
I'll give you a massage.
Do you like it?
Sister Lan Che!
My grandma is begging for drugs!
Please help her!
- Be careful.
- Hurry!
Let's go.
Grandma!
It's Carefree Powder.
Hurry. Put it out.
Guazi, come here.
Grandma.
Grandma?
Grandma,
I've told you many times
you can't light the incense.
Why don't you listen to me?
Guazi's mother,
you're back.
Well,
she thinks you're her daughter-in-law.
Good girl,
did you see my deed?
The deed?
I've got it.
I'll bring it
and show you tomorrow.
Let's get some rest,
okay?
Master,
your Cure for Worries can help one
get clean, right?
Why didn't it work for Madam Wang?
It works for those who just started
to use Carefree Powder.
However, Madam Wang
is extremely addicted.
If she wants to get clean, she has to go
to the Justice Department.
No, she can't!
Madam Wang is old.
She can't take it.
She's been good to me
since I was little.
Guazi is her only family now.
If I can't get the deed,
I'm afraid she'll...
From what we know,
Lou Mingye must've taken
the deed.
Luckily, it won't go anywhere.
We'll figure it out.
I'm warning you one last time.
Don't mess with Lou Mingye.
I'll never do it again.
(Lou's Mansion)
Master,
don't blame me for this.
I wanted to listen to you,
but the deed can save Madam Wang's life.
When I get the deed...
(Elegance of Bamboo)
So beautiful.
I didn't expect
that poker face from Liangzhou
to have such good taste.
Where is the deed?
Sorry.
You got hurt because of me.
It's like a crescent.
It's pretty.
Don't worry about it.
No matter where you are,
I'll recognize you
once I see the crescent.
What are you looking at?
It's just a hug.
I won't be responsible for this.
Responsible?
I'm a gangster
who doesn't care about courtesy.
However, a gentleman like you
must care about your reputation.
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone.
Well, Miss Gangster,
you sneaked into
a gentleman's house
in the middle of the night.
What are you up to?
I'm here
to tell you
I've changed my mind.
I can
be your assistant.
Okay.
But you have to give me the deed first.
- No.
- Why?
Didn't we have a deal?
How can I know
if you'll break the promise
once you get it.
My Lord,
is that what you think?
Go around and ask anyone, okay?
As Little Dragon,
I'm always an honest person.
I never break my promises.
You can never be too careful.
Suit yourself.
This is Madam Wang's house.
How can you demolish it?
Whoever gets the deed
owns the house.
My boss has the deed.
How we deal with it
is not up to you!
Boss, doesn't Lou Mingye have the deed?
Do they work for him?
Lou Mingye,
what a liar.
(Justice Department)
My Lord,
we searched through the stuff we got
from Chen's Mansion
but didn't find
the deed you talked about.
No Datong District's deed?
My Lord, you care about it so much.
Is it important for Chen Zhisong's case?
Xu Chaozhi,
forget about the deed.
I need you to spy on Mrs. Chen.
I will
do my best.
(Focus on Details)
My Lord, something happened
to Madam Wang's house.
Get out of here.
Stay out of this,
or
I won't go easy on you.
- Stupid kid.
- Guazi!
- Are you okay?
- How dare you?
It's my grandma's house.
Get out of here!
My Lord.
It seems Chen Zhisong gave the deed
to someone else.
Get up.
How can you hit a child?
Get out,
or I'll beat women too.
Sorry about that.
Did you get hurt?
Is it serious?
Do you need my help?
Which gang are you in?
Tell me your name!
Don't ask. Just go.
Behave yourself.
Who the hell are you?
Lord Lou?
Lou Mingye,
didn't you promise to give me the deed?
What's going on?
Who's your boss?
Who the hell are you?
You don't deserve to know our boss's...
Ouch! It hurts!
I told you to behave yourself.
Why didn't you listen?
I'll tell you!
It's Lady Hu Zhi
from Yuyan Tower.
Get off me!
What's Yuyan Tower?
It's the biggest brothel in Changjing,
and Hu Zhi is the most popular girl
in Yuyan tower.
Boss,
how did Hu Zhi get the deed?
Are you an idiot? Chen Zhisong
must've given it to her.
The house belongs to my lady now.
She can do whatever
she wants.
How dare you beat us?
I'll report this
to the Justice Department!
(Justice Department?)
(They're not allies.)
(Great.)
You,
listen carefully.
My Lord likes this house.
Tell your boss
that we'd pay ten times the price
for the house.
Listen to her.
Brother,
my grandma told me
if you like someone,
you'll spend money on her.
You spent so much money
on Sister Lan Che.
Do you like her?
Does it matter
whether I like her or not?
It does,
because she likes me.
Look,
she bought me sugar-coated haws!
Guazi.
Thanks, Sister Lan Che.
My Lord.
You don't like candies, right?
Come on, Guazi,
take this one too.
(You broke the promise first.)
Sister Lan Che,
my grandma told me if I like someone,
I should marry her.
Can I marry you when I grow up?
Naughty boy.
Talk to me when you grow up.
Master Lan.
When will you pay back
the 3000 taels of silver?
When did I owe you that?
Did you forget
Lord Lou just paid ten times the price
for that deed.
It's beautiful and well-located,
at least 300 taels of silver.
Ten times the price is 3000 taels.
What?
Do I need to pay for that deed?
Or should I pay?
Get the deed for her
in Yuyan Tower later
and tell me the price.
Aye.
You're not coming?
My Lord.
I'm busy.
Do you like sugar-coated haws?
But if you marry Sister Lan Che,
you won't eat it anymore.
Why?
Because she's in deep debt
and can't afford it.
She owes me a lot of money,
so everything she has is mine now,
including the sugar-coated haws.
You...
Hey, stop crying.
Sister Lan Che!
My Lord,
I found Mrs. Chen...
Sugar-coated haws!
Did you bring it?
These are all the accounts
related to Carefree Powder.
(Accounts)
Here you are.
We had a deal.
You need to pay for the book.
We've brought the book.
Where's the money?
As Lord Wu said,
you said you had nothing to do
with Carefree Powder,
so you should never get involved.
Now I've got the book.
You must leave the capital.
Go back and wait.
Someone will pick you up tonight.
You can leave.
How dare you
try to kill them in public?
It seems you have great power
in Changjing.
=Dawn Amidst Hidden Clouds=
♪Somewhere in the snow♪
♪Tears stream down her face♪
♪Who am I waiting for♪
♪Sweet dreams never last♪
♪Searching for you♪
♪Finally met you♪
♪Like yesterday once more♪
♪I can't ignore♪
♪Waiting for love♪
♪Clinging to the past♪
♪I was all alone at last♪
♪Hope the stars can bring you home♪
♪Can't fight this feeling on my own♪
♪But I've never told you♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪Time has flown since we said goodbye♪
♪Can't see you again in this life♪
♪Destiny is nothing but a lie♪
♪Hope the stars can bring you home♪
♪Can't fight this feeling on my own♪
♪But I've never told you♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪Time has flown since we said goodbye♪
♪Can't see you again in this life♪
♪Destiny is nothing but a lie♪
♪Stars fade away like an illusion♪
♪Destiny never fulfills my aspirations♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall♪
♪Why can't I see you anymore♪
♪Still thinking about that rainy night♪
♪How I wish you'd be by my side♪
♪Just close your eyes♪
♪'Cause I'll protect you in this life♪