=Dawn Amidst Hidden Clouds=
=Episode 8=
I don't think they can catch us.
My Lord,
this is Lingxi Lake.
I didn't know
Huaisha Village has such a nice view.
How did you find this place?
Li Mo brought me here
after we sent Huali away.
He was so thoughtful.
This place is so beautiful.
He's never thoughtful when he's at work.
My Lord.
Are you angry again?
Don't be angry all the time
so that there will be
much less rumors about you.
What rumors?
But I don't believe them.
I only believe what I see.
Then what's your conclusion?
My conclusion is
My Lord, you're smart, strong, and kind.
You're not what the rumors say.
Lan Che.
You don't have to praise me
if you think it's hard.
My Lord,
it's too hard to please you.
Lan Che.
What?
If you can't remember who you are,
what will you do?
I'll live a life as Lan Che.
Don't you feel sorry for that?
Of course I do.
However, compared to
the unknown identity,
the current life of Lan Che
is much more important.
In other words...
My Lord,
now you're sulking,
but why don't you
enjoy the view around you?
My Lord,
you really look like a fool
when you smile.
You're adorable
when you shut your mouth.
I'm wondering how Li Mo is doing.
Help?
Somebody?
Stay back!
Stay back.
Somebody, help!
Have a good rest.
You too, My Lord.
Lan Che.
Are you okay?
Lou Mingye,
you used this chance to get back at me.
Last night,
if it weren't for my wisdom and courage,
I would've been torn apart
by those mad dogs.
We don't pay for useless people.
My Lord, you can handle a few dogs,
can't you?
You...
Li Mo,
Lord Lou left you alone
because he trusted you,
and you didn't let him down, right?
I believe
you two
will become
perfect partners
very soon.
Oh.
Okay.
For Lan Che's sake,
I'll put up with...
Look at him!
How can we be partners?
The dogs nearly killed me last night!
How could he do that to me?
Lan Che!
I can't believe it!
He took you away last night
while I was hunted by the dogs!
Lan Che!
(Come to the tea stall alone and give it
to the vendor for Jiuxiang's clues.)
Dear guest, what would you like?
Wait a minute.
Here's your tea!
Dear guest, you're a lucky person.
Hope you find a good husband.
The person will come in a minute.
Get out! Don't ruin my business!
Dear guest, I'm so sorry.
Who is she?
Well,
she's a psychopath,
but she seldom goes mad.
Have some tea.
Hurry up!
Lan Che.
Lan Che!
Wake up, Lan Che!
Lan Che.
Huali?
Where am I?
Why are you here?
This is the place
where the Huangs imprison women.
Right after you got me out,
they sent someone
to catch me on the way.
I can't believe it.
How dare they offend the law?
Somebody! Huang Fuxing!
It won't work.
- They only come when delivering food.
- Huang Fuxing!
Lan Che.
What should we do?
Don't be scared.
We will get out.
Don't you feel sorry for that?
Compared to
the unknown identity,
the current life of Lan Che
is much more important.
luminous pearl is beautiful,
but I prefer
the real night sky with stars.
Lan Che.
It's not for you.
Make it by yourself.
Remember to pay.
Hey! How can you do this?
How can you do this?
Lan Che.
Lan Che, are you hungry?
Would you like something to eat?
She doesn't want to talk to you.
Lan Che.
I'm Li Mo.
I asked the cook
to make your favorite food.
Shall we eat it together?
Lan Che.
Is she still sleeping?
Lan Che...
How can you get in?
What if you see something...
Where is she?
Brother,
The cuffs
are so heavy.
Don't play tricks.
Brother,
you look so handsome and smart.
Can you
open the lunch box for me?
I believe you won't reject
a simple request from a little girl!
The cuffs are really heavy!
If we don't
eat anything,
we'll starve to death.
What are you supposed to tell your boss?
Thank you.
They just got out.
They must be around.
Search everywhere!
- Aye!
- I'll distract them
- Over there!
Go to the inn and find
the man who always uses an umbrella.
- Understand?
- They're not here.
What about you?
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
Over there!
Where are they?
- Over there!
- Go!
Go!
Come on, hurry up!
Lord Teng,
where should I put this one?
- In the backyard.
- Okay.
Gardener Feng.
Why are you here?
You're the young man
I met by the lake last time, right?
It's me.
Teng,
why did you buy the flowers?
Everyone has them,
but I bought some too.
Did you see Lan Che?
Lan Che?
She left a while ago.
Left?
Where did she go?
I don't know. She didn't tell you?
(Beloved Son Huang Daping)
Let's go!
Hurry up!
Go.
Go!
- Don't move!
- My Lord, we've got her.
Huang Fuxing, how dare you catch me?
Don't you know who I work for?
Good-looking
but disobedient.
(Beloved Son Huang Daping)
Daping will be angry.
Daping desperately needed a woman.
I had no choice.
Let's put up with it this time.
We can find a better one later.
Forget it.
But Daping deserves better.
Huang Fuxing.
What are you going to do?
Girl,
it's your honor
to be married into our family.
As long as you behave,
Daping
will treat you well.
We will also burn
paper money for you
when we visit Daping.
No! You old woman.
You're also a woman.
Have you no conscience?
Girl, just finish the ritual
with our young lord.
Let's go.
I was born in a bad time.
I have a solitary destiny!
I won't go easy on you
when I turn into a ghost!
Nonsense! Unruly girl!
- Seal the coffin now!
- Let me go!
Go!
Get off me!
Let me out!
Huang Fuxing, Let me out!
Let me go! Let me go!
Bury the coffin!
Huang Fuxing!
I won't go easy on you!
Let me go!
Are you looking for Lan Che?
Move.
No.
Move!
Lou Mingye.
Why are you always under an umbrella?
So pretentious.
Give it to me.
You can't go out without it, right?
Lord Tuoba!
Huali, why are you back?
My Lord, please save Lan Che!
She was taken by the Huangs!
Daping,
you've finally got a wife.
Are you happy?
How I wish I could see you
one more time.
It's all that witch's fault.
Mother,
the past is in the past.
Huang Fuxing!
Give Lan Che back!
Lan Che just married
our young lord
and has been buried with him.
I think
the coffin has been sealed
for almost an hour.
I'm afraid she's already gone.
My Lord,
I suggest you apologize to Lord Huang.
He's a generous man.
Maybe he'll forgive you.
He's ruined my grandson's wedding
again and again.
Take him down!
I count to three.
Dig the grave and open the coffin!
Otherwise, today is the day you die!
Fuxing!
Three...
Don't do this!
- Fuxing...
- Two!
- Fuxing!
- I'll do it!
- Hurry!
- One!
Hurry, open the coffin!
Hurry up!
Don't move! Don't!
- I'll do it!
- It's open!
Dig it!
Lan Che.
Huang Fuxing,
you shouldn't have hurt her.
No! Don't kill my son!
- My Lord!
- No!
My Lord...
My son!
Lan Che!
- Lan Che!
- Lan Che.
Wake up!
- Lan Che!
- Lan Che, get up!
Hurry!
Follow us!
Get in!
Are you feeling better?
Much better.
Let me help you.
Gardener Feng, why are you here?
I just passed by
and gave you a ride.
Don't worry.
(Yongning Temple)
It's safe.
Get some rest.
Thanks.
Let's go.
My Lord,
are you okay?
I can't look at the sun.
I didn't use the umbrella.
I'm temporarily blind.
That's why you're always
under an umbrella.
Why didn't you tell us?
My Lord,
let me help you.
Come on.
I can't move around.
Li Mo,
go back to the inn.
Tie Teng up and bring him here.
Why tie him up?
Who do you think
helped Huang Fuxing to kidnap Lan Che?
Nasty rat.
I'll break his legs!
Lan Che.
My Lord, I'm here.
Sorry.
For what?
I was late.
No.
Not at all.
You found me, didn't you?
Do you trust me that much?
Since I met you, My Lord,
I've always known
someone will have my back
no matter what happens.
I asked you to find out who he is.
You found Lou Mingye
eliminated the Tuobas.
How could you not know it's him?
Useless trash!
Forget it.
He's already here.
There's no point
arguing about it.
Mother,
what do you think
we should do?
Lou Mingye is hard to deal with,
but I don't think
he's fully prepared this time.
Why don't we
get them first?
Huang Gui.
Ask them to close the village.
Let's trap them here.
Aye.
(Mercy for All)
My Lord,
how are your eyes?
Much better.
Try this.
Come on.
Thanks.
Hurry!
Tell them.
Lan Che,
I put the note under your pillow,
but I had no choice.
Lord Huang forced me to.
What did he give you?
I...
He received your money,
so he'd also take their money.
My Lord, I really had no choice.
The Huangs are crazy.
If I disobey them,
they'll throw me into Lingxi Lake
like when...
Like what?
Was anyone thrown into the lake before?
I can't tell you.
Say it,
or he'll throw you into the lake.
It was Huang Daping's wife.
Huang Daping?
Did he get married before?
Daping.
I still regret it.
(Beloved Son Huang Daping)
I shouldn't have let you marry her.
If it weren't for that witch,
you wouldn't have died so early.
You're so miserable.
Why did you have to
(Beloved Son Huang Daping)
fall in love with
a married countrywoman?
Her name
is Fang Baixue.
She was already married,
and her man was in the army
in Liangzhou.
However, Huang Daping
really liked her
and forced her to marry him
while her husband was away!
The Huangs
not only sell women
but kidnap other people's wives.
Huang Daping deserved this.
How did he die?
One year later,
Lady Fang's husband came back.
They wanted to run away,
but they were caught.
Lady Fang asked her husband
to leave first
but accidentally killed Huang Daping.
He was the only heir
of the Huang Family.
Lord Huang and his mother
were pissed off
and threw her into the snow
for an entire day.
She was frozen to death.
Then they threw her into Lingxi Lake.
When they did this,
she was frozen into an ice
and never floated up.
They're monsters.
Then...
What about her ex-husband?
He never showed up.
His wife died for him.
How could he forgive them?
Why are you surprised?
Most men in this world are cowards.
Don't you think so, Lord Teng?
Gardener Feng,
don't make fun of me!
My Lord, I've told you everything.
Can you let me go?
Huang Gui.
Lord Huang died in a weird way.
My Lord, thank you for doing this.
It's our duty to handle
every case equally.
Can you do an autopsy
or not?
I've seen others do it before.
I've been Huanxi's disciple
for many years.
How's that possible?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let's go out.
Why are you being so secretive?
There's no wound
or sign of poison
in his body.
Do you mean...?
Don't doubt my conclusion, okay?
It seems
he was frozen to death.
Frozen?
Huang Gui.
Did he go out
before he died?
Well...
My Lord, I need to tell you something.
My Lord.
Are you okay, My Lord?
My Lord!
No.
Lord Huang never left home.
It's not winter.
Isn't it too wild
to be frozen to death in summer?
Even if it's winter,
he can't possibly be frozen like this.
Lord Huang and his mother
were pissed off
and threw her into the snow
for an entire day.
She was frozen to death.
Did he
meet a ghost?
Could it be...
his wife?
Stop!
Who allowed you to bother my son?
It's all your fault.
You brought disaster to us!
Fuxing wouldn't dare to hurt you,
but I
don't care!
She's attacking us at all costs.
Stay close to me.
I'm afraid
we have to rush out.
Kill them!
(Mercy for All)
My Lady, what's wrong with you?
Hurry!
Qingyao.
Lou...
Are you alright?
Qingyao, I've finally found you.
Let's go home.
=Dawn Amidst Hidden Clouds=
♪Somewhere in the snow♪
♪Tears stream down her face♪
♪Who am I waiting for♪
♪Sweet dreams never last♪
♪Searching for you♪
♪Finally met you♪
♪Like yesterday once more♪
♪I can't ignore♪
♪Waiting for love♪
♪Clinging to the past♪
♪I was all alone at last♪
♪Hope the stars can bring you home♪
♪Can't fight this feeling on my own♪
♪But I've never told you♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪Time has flown since we said goodbye♪
♪Can't see you again in this life♪
♪Destiny is nothing but a lie♪
♪Hope the stars can bring you home♪
♪Can't fight this feeling on my own♪
♪But I've never told you♪
♪I can't stop loving you♪
♪Time has flown since we said goodbye♪
♪Can't see you again in this life♪
♪Destiny is nothing but a lie♪
♪Stars fade away like an illusion♪
♪Destiny never fulfills my aspirations♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall♪
♪Why can't I see you anymore♪
♪Still thinking about that rainy night♪
♪How I wish you'd be by my side♪
♪Just close your eyes♪
♪Because I'll protect you in this life♪