You
Oh
Wow
Um
What if they all disappeared?
What do you think?
Like, they can't even play the game?
The video.
That video...
That video must be there.
Hyunwoo ordered it.
Don't you remember?
Oh, the video is gone.
Hey, pick one.
I'll give you 10 seconds.
Wait, wait.
If you don't pick it in time, both of you will die.
There must be a place to store the video.
How do we find the video?
We can't search the whole building.
But we can't go in there.
What if they make us guide them?
Hey, where are you going?
Hey!
Call me when you're done.
Excuse me.
You're going to put the camera on me like this?
But you're not here because of the hidden camera, are you?
You're just looking at me as trash.
No, I'm just asking questions.
What's that?
What?
Hey, mask!
Is it a CD?
But can we use this?
I don't know.
A security guard?
You're not the one I used to know.
Yes.
You're so mean.
Are you okay?
I think we'll be okay if we go to Hyunwoo's house.
A broadcasting room?
Did we have a broadcasting room?
I didn't say anything when I came.
Isn't the chairman talking about the game room?
It's related to the chairman, so bring it.
I'm going to the bathroom.
You did a great job.
Oh, guys.
It's moving.
Wow, this is really cool.
A machine room?
Sang-yeop, we have to draw medicine from now on.
Okay.
No, not the right side.
Left side.
I think this is it.
Hey, Jin-ta.
Why is the chairman's package coming to this room?
What is this?
I don't know.
Take it away.
Hey, clean it up.
You dirty bastard.
I'm cleaning it up.
What's this?
Shall we open it a little bit?
Oh, my God.
I was so surprised.
There's medicine.
I think we can find it enough if we go inside the building.
Okay, let's go.
Shall we get started now?
I look forward to your kind cooperation.
Oh, my God.
What?
Hey, sir.
Hey, hey.
Check the red truck on the B-side of the basement.
Yes, sir.
Check it.
What's that sound?
It's a car.
Chairman, there's no one.
Take it to my eyes right now.
If you can't find it, you'll die.
Go down and find it.
I'm going to the basement.
I'll be right there.
Did you guys kill him?
Oh, my God.
Two, four, six, eight.
I can't count.
Let's go as planned.
Let's go.
Let's split up because there are a lot of opponents.
Woosol and Sang-hyuk are a team.
I and Yeon-jin are a team.
One of you just care about your body.
The other one just cares about getting in trouble.
The key is speed.
It's a good idea to speed up.
Let's go.
Go!
Let's go to the next level. I'll look for the evidence.
It's okay.
Run!
Go inside!
Run! Run!
Hey, there's a light!
Run!
It's here!
Jung-yong.
Run!
Shit.
Where's the video file of the recording?
File?
It's not here.
Tell me before you hit me.
Shit.
Are you crazy? Do you want to die?
Open everything. Hurry.
I don't know.
I don't know anything.
How is it?
I'm more than expected.
I'll go down.
Shit.
Are you okay?
Did you find it?
Shit.
I'm going to kill you!
Don't do it!
I'm sorry.
Oh, Jung-yong.
I really don't know.
What should I do?
Find this?
I'm really sorry.
I think I'm out of my mind.
Please don't do that.
I'm not guilty.
What should I do?
I really don't know.
Oh, Jung-yong.
What should I do?
I really don't know.
No, don't do it!
Don't do it!
No!
Now that I see it,
you're good at taking pictures.
If you want a video, you should have it.
Send it to me.
No.
You two don't have any relationship.
I'll be back.
Take the kids and arrange the underground shooting.
Yes, sir.
Let me ask you something.
Who stabbed Lee Won-joon?
What?
You're the one who stabbed him?
You're my sister, you bastard!
Isn't it me who's your enemy?
Hey, you, bastard.
Do you want to fight?
I'm sorry.
But you're a chauvinist.
It's hot, right?
Should I lower the temperature?
You didn't drink it?
I'm not going to drink it.
I'm going to drink it.
Okay.
Did you eat?
Hey, open your face.
You've made me feel so bad.
Oh, come on.
You're so serious.
This is a video file.
Take this with you or play a game with me.
Choose.
I'm giving you a chance.
A chance to get revenge.
I'm going to kill you.
Who's next?
You have to pay for your choice.
Is your family more stimulating than your friends?
What's the reason for this?
Reason?
It's fun.
I'm going to kill you.