You deserve it.
I'm here.
Hee-hee.
I bought you a new dress.
You little...
Hee-hee.
You didn't even answer.
Hey, hey! Hey, hey!
Hee-hee.
Look at this beautiful dress.
What are you doing?
You cut such a nice dress like this.
Do you know
I asked someone to bring this dress back from abroad.
Why are you so naughty?
Ah.
Get up get up
Scared. Does it hurt?
I don't like dolls.
I don't like skirts.
I like basketball.
What basketball?
Didn't I tell you?
to study hard.
What basketball?
Jung-hee.
What's wrong?
Dormitory.
Time is half an hour earlier.
11:13.
It might be Ji Jinhee.
Hello?
Where are you now?
I'm in the dorm.
It's half an hour earlier.
We have more time to stop the explosion.
Oh.
Okay. Let's talk in person.
Okay.
Hey, Jun.
Are you going to eat in the canteen?
Yes. Do you want one?
I want one too.
Thank you.
I'll send you the money later.
Love you.
If the circulation can stop,
I'll bring you food.
Love you.
Why are you here so soon?
I happened to be nearby.
According to
from Editor Chen
and his chat history with the Psychology teacher.
I think
that scholar named Qin Ze seems very suspicious.
Qin Ze is a scholar.
Maybe he's also good at chemistry.
Hello, where are you?
Luo Yi and I are at the door of the dorm building.
Where are you? When will you arrive?
I'm stuck on the highway.
I can't go down in half an hour.
Okay.
Take care.
Luo Yi and I will go to the psychological consultation room
and ask about Qin Ze.
Okay.
Let's go.
Faster.
No one is here.
Not many people come here at school.
I guess she went to eat.
The door is not locked.
Luo Yi.
I found him.
Looks like Qin Ze's situation
is completely different
in the elevator.
Qin Ze's pressure isn't from his studies.
but not his future life.
Because of his family,
after his parents passed away,
after their parents passed away.
We've been relying on government subsidies.
The school did pay a lot.
But his brother is still young.
he's still in primary school.
I can't stay in elementary school either.
I can only pick her up every day.
I've been taking him back and forth every day.
plus college life,
he barely had time to rest.
But he hasn't received
for a long time.
If it's because of this,
it's not impossible to think of destroying the elevator.
The tuition fee
The education department gave it to the school.
The teacher from the school sponsor center released it.
The school's sponsor center office is under renovation.
so I moved it to the media building.
So,
Qin Ze was probably going to the support center of the media building.
What's his purpose?
With all the information,
Qin Ze is likely to be the murderer now.
We need to find him and test him.
Okay.
This is Qin Ze's phone number I found online at school.
I'll call him now.
Okay.
Hello.
Hello, are you Qin Ze?
I'm a reporter from Advisor Media.
My name is Tang Xiao Zheng.
We're interviewing
of the scholarship.
I need to talk to you about something.
Are you free?
Okay.
I know.
I'll go find you.
Okay.
Qin Ze is working at a cafe outside the school gate.
We'll go there now.
Okay.
Hello.
Welcome.
What do you need?
A cappuccino, please.
Cappuccino.
Three or five?
Sanfen sugar.
Yes.
Okay, wait a moment.
Hello, welcome.
What do you need?
Qin Ze.
Did you call me just now?
Yes.
Let's talk outside.
What do you want to know?
I have to work.
I may not have much time.
I heard you have a younger brother.
Do you live with him now?
Can you take care of him after you go to college?
I rented a single room near the school.
I brought him here
so I brought him here.
and asked him to study
in the west city.
My brother and I
And...
the rent
and daily expenses.
I can't get my scholarship back.
But I heard
because of a new policy.
The poor must stay in school.
A poor student?
If you don't stay in school,
I won't get any subsidies.
But I really can't live in school.
I have to take care of my brother.
What do you think about
what do you think?
I hope it can be released as soon as possible.
Sorry.
Hello
Yes
Your water, sir.
I don't think I can make it now.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'll be there as soon as possible.
The teacher at the school sponsor center
He wants to ask me some questions about the scholarship.
If the school and the Education Bureau want to investigate my situation,
it should be easy to find out.
There's no need to ask again and again.
to expose people's scars, right?
If you have any questions,
you can go to my brother's school.
But please don't disturb him.
I have work to do.
Sorry.
Qin Ze went to the media building
because of the scholarship.
I don't think
he's not the culprit of the elevator explosion.
It's 12:20 now.
It's been over an hour.
We don't have much space to investigate.
We need to confirm Qin Ze's situation.
Why don't we split up?
I'll go to the media building to observe Qin Ze's movements.
Go to his brother's place and find out what's going on.
Qin Ze said his brother will return to the dorm he rented at noon.
There's a detailed address in the psychological consultation room.
I can take a look there.
There should be time.
Okay.
Take care.
You too.
Hello, Lu Zitired.
After you arrive at school,
go to the media building to meet Luo.
Okay.
Be careful.
Okay, bye.
Okay.
If Qin Ze is the murderer,
once there's a conflict,
we can at least defeat him.
Who is it?
Are you Qin Ze's brother, Qin Xiaofeng?
Who are you?
Why haven't I seen you before?
I'm a reporter
who is investigating the drop of your brother's tutor.
I have some questions for you.
Wait a minute.
Hello, brother.
Not only does Qin Xiaofeng look like Qin Ze,
but also his personality.
He's very vigilant.
Come in.
Can I sit here?
Xiaofeng.
How is your brother?
Did you notice
he showed any unstable emotions?
My brother
has been busy lately.
Every time you cook for me,
after cooking for me.
Did you see
at home?
This is a single room.
It's only this big.
Is there anything that you can't see at a glance?
This...
Nothing strange.
Sister.
Do you think my brother did something bad?
What?
Sister.
My brother would never do anything bad.
He's a good man.
I think
Oppa has been busy recently
and anxious
I didn't get the tuition fee this semester.
It's all my fault.
If it weren't for me,
you wouldn't have suffered so much.
Xiaofeng.
It's not your fault.
You are my only family.
Of course he has to take care of you.
and protect you.
When you grow up,
when you grow up, right?
Don't worry.
I'll try to help your brother.
Here are your snacks.
Take it
No sister
I bought it for you.
A reward for you.
Does she really exist?
Or...
It's just my imagination.
What did I get?
What did I lose?
It's as if my life has lost its meaning.
My body is no longer important.
My brother
can't hold me back
My soul
will only be a gift for Lolimas.
Sister.
Is there anything else you want to ask me?
Oh.
No problem.
Today is your birthday.
You have classes in the afternoon.
Have a good rest at noon.
When I have time,
when I have time.
Bye.
There are only two minutes left before the elevator explosion.
It should be too late to meet Luo Yi and the others.
I wonder how they are doing.
Hey.
Did I hit your head with basketball before?
You only cared about Qin Ze.
and forgot Ji Jinxi.
I have something to ask you.
Just now...
Rorymars.
Her name?
In the novel,
in the movie.
Roris means a kind of rose.
means death.
So it's both for the wedding and for depression. [This is the reason why Roris Rose was used to miss death.]
Therefore, it's used for the wedding
It's a huge sadness.
A cracked wound.
Judging from this sentence,
Qin Ze has already thought of killing himself.
But he didn't write in the diary
he was afraid that his brother was in primary school.
He can read.
and discover your disappointment.
You've been staring at Qin Ze.
Did you notice anything unusual?
I've been with Qin Ze for a long time.
He went to the media building after working at the cafe.
Nothing was wrong during that time.
I didn't find
he did something strange to the elevator.
However,
Qin Ze went to the conference room
he went to the conference room on the first floor of the media building.
and stayed there for a few minutes.
I didn't follow him
I didn't follow him.
I don't know what he did inside.
After he left,
after he left.
but I found nothing.
Is he looking for someone in the meeting room?
or something?
You didn't see anything
because he took it.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have entered the conference room for no reason.
There must be something there.
Qin Ze is still in the cafe.
If there's really something in the conference room,
it might still be there.
Let's take a look.
Let's go.
Let's look around.
Luo Yi.
What did I get?
What did I lose?
My life is meaningless.
My body is no longer important.
No one can stop me from running towards death.
Qin Ze wrote this.
It's a suicide note.
Qin Ze wanted to commit suicide.
And he has some relevant knowledge.
Maybe
the breakthrough of the elevator is really with him.
We can look into Qin Ze.
But if it's a suicide note,
the handwriting doesn't look like it.
Hey.
What's going on?
Why do I keep going through the same thing?
Not only you,
We're all circulating.
What?
Because of the explosion in that elevator,
everyone who experienced the explosion in the elevator
can enter the circulation.
Elevator explosion.
Will we
be dead?
I never thought I was dead.
I'm still fighting for my destiny.
Hello?
I'm at the media building.
Where are you?
Oh.
The meeting room on the first floor.
Okay.
He's in the loop too.
Yes.
You know me?
Hum.
Yes.
You may not know me,
but I was in the elevator
I was in the elevator too.
My name is Lu Zitired.
The circulation is real.
When I first entered the circulation,
I only had 30 seconds.
The elevator door was closed.
Every time I woke up, I was already in the elevator.
So I had to escape.
Then it was the second and third time.
Until one time,
I accidentally led Lu Zitired out of the elevator
and dragged him into the circulation.
The time was only 30 minutes.
And Luo Yi.
Every time someone enters the circulation,
time will extend.
And every extended time is related to 30.
The first time is 30 seconds.
The second time is 30 minutes.
Every time after that is the same.
Now our question is
the melody we heard in the elevator.
The anonymous message that Editor Chen received
And Qin Ze.
If you ask me, it must be Qin Ze.
He's been in a bad mood for a long time.
It's highly possible that he did such a thing.
I went to his current place
I went to his current place.
and found nothing dangerous.
If we ask Qin Ze directly,
if we ask Qin Ze directly.
How can we let Qin Ze tell the truth voluntarily?
Maybe
in another way.
What would you like?
A cappuccino, please.
It's cold and hot.
Cold
Hello.
Welcome.
What would you like?
Two lattes.
Okay.
3% sugar, 5% sugar.
5% sugar.
Do you want ice?
Ice.
Okay.
44 in total.
Scan here.
Okay.
I heard
someone installed a bomb in the elevator in the media building.
Ah.
Really?
Someone installed a bomb in the elevator in the media building.
It must be a rumor.
Enjoy.
He's so cold.
He doesn't seem to know about the elevator explosion.
If he's really the culprit,
it would be too good to hide it.
Maybe
we went in the wrong direction from Editor Chen.
We investigated Qin Ze
because he has a tendency to commit suicide.
But he has a tendency to commit suicide.
doesn't mean he has antisocial personality.
Besides,
Qin Ze has a younger brother.
Even if he hates the school for not paying his tuition,
he doesn't have to blow up the elevator.
Yes.
Oh, and that will.
Hey, waiter.
Why is there something dirty in your coffee?
Sorry.
Where is the sorry?
Bing.
It seems that
The sugar hasn't melted, right?
Ah
I see.
I'm sorry.
I didn't see it clearly.
Ah.
It's okay.
Hey.
I spilled the sugar on the table.
Help me clean it up.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I found a suicide note
I found a suicide note.
Who do you think wrote this?
A student from our school?
Is someone trying to commit suicide?
Hey,
Have you seen this suicide note?
Do you know who wrote it?
I don't know. I haven't seen it.
Qin Ze reacted to this letter.
Does Qin Ze really want to die?
to die?
Do you want Qin Xiaofeng
in this world?
You investigated me?
Have you ever thought
if you leave,
Qin Xiaofeng will be alone from now on.
Do you want him to experience
Do you want him to experience it again?
Actor table.
Tang Xiaoma Li Xiyuan
Luo Yi, Xingze.
Qin Ze, Gao Kai.
Lu Zitired.
Ji Jinxi, Miao Yaning.
Song HaoMiao Mo Qinyang
Editor Chen, Shen Bao Ping.
Zhao Zhen, Tian Miao.
Song Liang, Jiao Peng,
Mother of Song, Jia Shu Yi.
Wu Yiren Wang Yanan
Luo Wenli Fu Xiaoming
Little Xiao Meng, Tangyuan
Lu Zitired's father, Guo Yanlang
Luo Yi's father, Chen Dong.
Luo Yi's stepmother, Liu Xiaotian.
Uncle Qin Ze, Xu Ming Zhe.
Agent Han Ming Ming Ming Ming.
Mr. Chen from the supermarket, Ma Qingqi.
Captain of security, Hu Xiaoyuan.
Officer Xia, Zou Gang.
Mr. Lin, Wu Jiliang.
Zhang Chi’s mom, Sui Jia.
Solo, Zhang Jiaqi.
Bar girl, Wang Jiaxin.
Qiao Yuze, Yin Zhi.
Coffee clerk, Marin.
Bartender, Liang Lijun.
The art exhibition staff, Liao Wei.
Female teacher, Zhong Hui.
Police officer Luo, Dingdi Bo.
Lu Ziyao, Chen Yixi.
Lu Zitired (Childhood)
Luo Yi, childhood.
Tang Xiaolu (Childhood) Peng Duer.
My stepmother's son, Niu Yu Rui.
Qin Xiaofeng, Zhou Tianyou.
Jia Yue, a girl from the art center.
Basketball Man, Zhong Zhi.
to perform.
Liu Yaoyao, Cao Yanli, Zhao Mengli, Zhao Mengli, Li Ying, Zhao Jing, Wang Xingjun, Wang Xingjun, from Kaiyue Kong Mengjia
Wang Shengyi, Xiao Di, Qi Yujiao, Gao Zhimiao, Kwok Wong Yifan, Tang Qianxi Commissioner Niu Li, Duan Wenhua
Wang Xu, Zhang Bao, Yue Zhi, Gao Feng Xin Yuan Qingru, Zhang De, Cao Yanli, Zhao Mengli Liu Yaoyao, Li Ying, Oda Qing, Zhao Jing
Shao Na, Yun Yilin, Chen Lian Chi, Zhang Shao Zhang Jiren, Liu Mingkai, Dong Yihu, Wang Xuekang. Qin Jia Wen, Du Linlin, He Wenjing, Ma Luping.
Designer: Yin Bojun
Chief Producer: Xiaoyong.
Producer Director: Shi Yunfeng
[Life Producer: General Choi]
[Live Producer: Mr. Gao]
Director team.
Executive Director: Dingdi-po
Acting director: Yin Shao
Director assistant: Cao Wenqiang
Total: Zhong Hui.
[Note: Zhu Junjun]
According to Mars frequency novel, the melody echoes. [Adapted: Canghai Mirror]
[Photographer]
Photographer: Eun-jo Jiang Chu
Photographer assistant: Yang Gun-woon
Photographer assistant: Wang Ningbo
Drama photo: Chen Yang.
Lighting team.
Lighting guidance: Zhao Yafeng.
Lighting instructor: Wang Hongshan
Lighting Daisuke: Zhang Can.
Lighting Daisuke: Yu Zhihao.
Lighting Suke: Li Dedong.
Lighting assistant: Jia Xingkai.
Lighting assistant: Zhao Di, Geng Xiaoguang Yanlei. Yu Shihuan, Song Zhihao, Zhang Mengwei, Zhu Ruyi. Zhang Shuwang.
styling instructor: Feng Yan.
Makeup artist: Li Rudong.
Art team.
Execute art... Chen Yu.
The prop team leader...... Wang Zhaoqing.
The prop for the play... Fu Wei.
The venue team.
Manager: Liu Xiaofei
Zhang Jianguo, Zhang Hailong, Zhang Hailong, Pan, Yang, Yang, Liang, Liang, Han, Hu Yue, Han Song Luo, Huang Yan Yan, He Yatian, Guo Zhenhai, Gong Peng Cheng
Legal advisor.
Li Zhenning: Cao Zhenfeng. Li Zhenning: Li Zhenning.
Editor: Cho Jin-bong
Zhejiang Tianguang Mei Culture Co., Ltd.
Visual guidance: Zhang Liquan
Special effects director: Tong Zhou
Art Director: Wu Yingmei
[Computer: Zhu Jingwen, Xing Yunpeng, Tian Lu, Ouyang Lei]
Li Yunzhou, Xue Liangyu, Legends of the King, Rong Bing, Zheng Chen, Qi Han, Yang Arrow Shen Lifen.
Special effects engineer: Buyin Hongliang Wang He
Voice team.
Voice production Beijing Lone Voice Production Co., Ltd.
Production: Cheng Yanjun (Sonny)
Mix: Meng Qing Pang Tian Yuhang
Environmental Production: Yu Liu Wei
Foley: Tian Yuhang Fu Bin
Foley recording: Huang Huijie.
Director: Zhu Minyi
Voice Planning: Hu Geng Liang
Recorder: Lu Xiaogang
Recording assistant: Wu Jianguo
Voice assistant: Dong Tongtong
Music Director: Liu Jie
Music composer: Chae Ji-young Chan Karen
Li Wenhan: Li Wenhan.
Additional music: Xu Yifei
Music editor: Chae Ji-young
Music Planning: Fan Janggeun, what poem?
Thank you very much.
Qingdao West Coast New Video Development Center
Qingdao 5G High School Video Experimental Park.
Product.
Qingdao Muzheng Film Co., Ltd.
Dongyang City Yishu Media Co., Ltd.
Control.
Shandong Muzheng Media Co., Ltd.