We're ready for the funeral.
Now…
let's send my father off.
LEE JU-WOON (MICHAEL)
Hey, boss.
If you're running off to Russia,
shouldn't you change your name
from Danny to Alexander or Sergei?
You little shit. Do you think
I'm fucking running away?
I'm setting up a trap, dumbass!
I have it all planned out.
Those fucking bastards.
Just wait and see who survives in the end.
It's been 20 minutes.
Where the hell is that damn captain?
This isn't the fucking time to be late.
- Hey, go check.
- Got it.
Get out of the car now, you bastard!
Right.
Hey.
- Where's the captain of the King Star?
- I don't know.
The King Star. Where's the captain?
I don't know.
I'll go call him.
I'll call the captain.
Hey!
Everyone, get over here.
We've got some new faces.
Let's get a picture.
Yeah, gather around.
It's been a while.
You brats, you know what the elders say?
In the end, only pictures stay!
Get over here.
All right, let's do it.
I'm stuffed. Did I eat too much?
Hey, get over here, you punks!
Hey, newbies, come on.
Stand in the middle. Come on.
All right, guys. Smile, okay? Smile.
Stand over here.
Come on.
Here we go. Move in a little closer.
Everyone, smile. Here we go.
One, two, three.
Who the hell are you?
You son of a bitch. Goddamn it!
Who sent you, motherfucker?
Who was it?
You fucking bastard.
You son of a bitch.
Sim Seong-won will never die, you bastard!
Damn it. Goddamn bastards.
This is just fucking great. Bastards.
Fucking assholes. Where's my money?
My money. These bastards.
I'm not going to die, you bastards.
You son of a bitch.
Sim Seong-won never dies, you bastard!
Go tell them, you son of a bitch!
Yang-sik!
Boss, I'm right here!
You're bleeding!
Where the fuck have you been?
I just got stabbed four times.
Go get a towel or something.
Fuck.
I'll go tell them
this is how you died.
You son of a bitch.
Fucking asshole.
Fucking hell.
Stubborn bastard. Damn it.
I got rid of Sim Seong-won.
Good job.
Sim Seong-won has been taken out.
Well, I guess we're almost done now.
Yes, sir, we're here.
We're heading up now.
Wait.
Where's Cha Yeong-do?
So,
have you made your decision?
Nam Gi-jun.
Bad luck for you.
I was planning to kill Cha Yeong-do first.
You're nothing special, either.
Just like your brother.
So, it was you.
You killed Gi-seok.
Look.
I will build a new plaza.
Unlike my father's time
when we had to stay in the shadows,
I will make the plaza fully legitimate
so that no one dares to touch us.
I may not be able to do that
as Lee Geum-son, son of Lee Ju-woon.
But I can make it happen
as Prosecutor Lee Geum-son.
Fuck.
Don't you think
we're meeting too often?
It's not like we're fucking family.
Let me ask you something.
Did you really know?
You said so in the interrogation room.
You told me you knew
who planned it all with me.
LEE GEUM-SON - LEE JU-WOON
Those idiots.
I told them to be careful. Fuck…
These drives,
do you even know what's on them?
It was Lee Geum-son who said it himself,
"Let's start a war between Juwoon
and Bongsan to take control."
And all the evidence proving that
is on there.
How about this?
You take out Lee Geum-son
and become the new ruler of the plaza.
Lee Ju-woon and Gu Bong-san did it,
so why not you, Gi-jun?
Come on, I'll have your back all the way.
You shouldn't be making offers…
but asking for forgiveness.
This bastard won't even take it
when it's handed to him.
What, you think you're above it all too?
Fuck.
You son of a bitch!
You want to live?
Please don't kill me…
Sorry for your loss.
Is that blood?
Who's that guy?
Sir.
Mr. Choi.
Oh boy.
Looks like Shimane failed.
What about Cha Yeong-do?
He's dead, isn't he?
It's not so bad, then. At least he's dead.
Why did you do it?
And what was your reason, Nam Gi-jun?
My father asked you to take over Juwoon.
Why did you turn him down?
Everyone in the plaza
would kill for that position.
I'm losing my mind not having it
even when it's right there.
So why the fuck do you and your brother
act like it's not worth a damn?
That's it?
That's all it was about?
Have some food before you go.
It's probably the last warm meal
you'll have on the outside.
It's your last one too.
You're the only one left now.
Is the burial tomorrow?
Stay alive until then…
and send him off properly.
JUWOON
I'm sorry it took me so long.
THE LATE NAM GI-SEOK
I'll see you soon.
Here.
LEE GEUM-SON
What's this?
Just hold onto it for now. I'll call you.
Hae-beom.
You should stop now.
What?
Chun-seok and Byeong-ho…
They're gone now.
Somebody has to stay alive
and see this through.
You must've had a hard time finding this.
You found my overseas bank account
to blackmail me.
Really?
Go get some air.
Yes, sir.
JUWOON - BONGSAN
M&A PROPOSAL
So you want me to stay out
of Juwoon's merger with Bongsan?
No one's in charge.
Wouldn't it be easier if we took over?
"We"?
Juwoon Group.
All right. Let's say I go along with it.
What's in it for me?
You'll stay in that chair a little longer.
That's all, right?
Just the Bongsan merger and acquisition.
Yes.
JW DE'CRO
HOTEL
BUSINESS PARTNERSHIP AGREEMENT
JUWOON
LEE GEUM-SON, CEO
BONGSAN
HONG HYEON-SEOK, CEO
LEE GEUM-SON
240407_LEE GEUM-SON REC_18:48
We'll use Gu Jun-mo
to get rid of Nam Gi-seok.
Prosecutor General, that's Lee Geum-son.
Thank you all for coming.
I'm Lee Geum-son.
As you all know, we're here today
to celebrate the merger
between Juwoon and Bongsan.
As of today, I've been appointed
as the new CEO of Juwoon.
And I'm still a prosecutor at the Seoul
Central District Prosecutors' Office.
It's fucking freezing.
I did what you asked,
but are you sure this is okay?
Oh shit.
If anything goes wrong,
I had nothing to do with it.
I plan to create a new system.
But don't worry.
I just want to try a different approach.
We'll keep all the members
and make a few tweaks to the system.
That'll solve all the problems.
I'll make sure
that every illegal benefit you had
will no longer be considered illegal.
The plaza I envision
is a place where the boundary
between the light and shadows
is torn down.
No one will point fingers at you…
I mean, no one will point fingers at us
in the new plaza I build.
Listen, Lee.
The prosecutor general went
to great lengths to make this look good.
You're exaggerating.
So, what can we expect?
Let me ask you this instead.
What kind of positions
are you looking for?
Excuse me, Prosecutor General.
Please take a look.
- What have you got there?
- Check your messages, sir.
LEE ORDERED THE MURDER OF NAM GI-SEOK
What is it?
I enjoyed the food.
We should go.
Very impressive.
Here's a breaking news update.
A sitting prosecutor
has been implicated in a murder,
sparking major controversy.
The prosecutor is Lee Geum-son from
the Seoul Central Prosecutors' Office.
Let's listen to the recording.
We'll use Gu Jun-mo
to get rid of Nam Gi-seok.
I'll say this again.
I want both Juwoon and Bongsan.
What the fuck
is this?
The prosecution has decided to immediately
remove Lee from his position
and has called for a swift…
You messed up big time.
You were all talk
about a new system and shit.
Is this what you wanted to show us?
What's the big deal?
Do you still not get it?
You're done.
All of this is over.
It's not over yet.
Get everyone back here.
Goddamn idiot.
Just so you know…
if you're trying
to drag us down, forget it.
It's already game over. Got it?
Fucking bastard.
What a freaking nutjob.
Fuck you.
Stop.
I'll take care of this.
You should go.
Why would I leave? This is my place.
Go bring everyone back.
- Let go, damn it!
- Knock it off, you fucking bastard!
All of us put our trust in you
and came this far.
If you screw this up, I swear…
You should go, sir.
Sir.
Take the stairs.
Stop him.
You want to come to me?
Or should I come to you?
Stop!
Let him through.
Get out, all of you.
Gi-jun.
Can't you please…
just stop here?
It's been a long time
since you called me that.
As a friend…
and for old times' sake, I'm asking you.
Please stop.
Yeah. Thought so.
Let's go.
I'll show you the way.
I'm just doing my job.
You understand?
It's okay.
Go and finish what you started.
Okay.
I'll see you soon.
So how does it feel sitting in that seat?
You've done all of this
just to get
to where you're sitting, right?
I'm not sure.
It's not as great as I thought it'd be.
I've done all kinds of shit to get here.
If I had known it'd be so pointless…
Everyone feels that way.
They'll do anything to get there.
But when they finally do,
only emptiness is left.
Because they can only go down from there.
For fuck's sake. That's just your opinion.
Me?
I loved the aspect of fighting.
I loved the tension before a fight
and the rush of landing a hit.
But the best part was
what came after I won.
The way my friends looked at me.
My father,
he must've gotten it all his life.
I envied that so much.
The respect. The admiration.
That…
is neither admiration nor respect.
It's fear.
And it becomes a burden.
The chairman…
probably didn't want you
to bear that burden
because he knew the pain.
Fuck, enough talk about my dead father.
Now, I'm genuinely curious
because I really don't get it.
Why go this far? Seriously.
Why are you doing this now
after all this time?
You gave up everything
and just fucking ran.
Because I'm the reason it all started.
I'm the reason Gi-seok…
That's how it works in this business.
Once you're in…
you don't get out alive.
Don't do it.
For fuck's sake!
I told you not to do it!
Go ahead, shoot.
My father was right.
He said
you people live with nightmares every day.
Fuck, I was never cut out for this.
Still…
thank you… for hearing me out.
Fuck!
You
don't get to die like that.
Go…
beg for forgiveness.
Don't tell me what to do,
you fucking bastard.
I wondered who'd come
to a place like this.
But it's actually nice.
Gi-jun.
Maybe I should come work here too.
Leave it all behind.
Sure.
I'd like that. Drop everything and come.
Let's run this campground together.
What's gotten into you?
MERCY FOR NONE
Subtitle translation by: Munhyung Choi