I went to Yumo
Is to pass him a message.
To connect with each other.
And today,
we worked together
to identify the two drug dealers
he did this
to gain time for the CCP
to gain time to escape.
Also,
the four of clubs is me.
Me is the four of clubs.
Old Luo.
Check it out carefully.
You are a bastard if not.
You are so impatient.
Brother,
you're no better than Zhao An.
A narrow-minded person.
Manager Luo,
what should we do with him?
Hang him until he's dead
until he's dead
chief Chen
musket pistol
It weighs about 1100 grams.
The weight after loading is about 1,350 grams.
The weight of the gun
around 1200 grams.
It's neither fully loaded
nor empty.
There's one possibility
several rounds were fired.
But the center of gravity of the pistol seems to be wrong.
So,
several rounds were not fired,
It was filled with blanks.
You must find a way to visit a calligraphy shop.
I will.
The room upstairs
block 7 in the middle of the floor
I hid some documents and data.
Pick something worthless
and give them to Luo Guanqun.
The rest must be dealt with.
Alright.
On the second floor balcony,
I put a pot of yellow chrysanthemums in it.
Which is the safe signal.
Change yellow chrysanthemum into purple chrysanthemum.
It means there is something wrong.
And most importantly,
the four plum blossoms.
Make sure you get to the bottom of Plan Shan
and destroy it completely.
I will.
Alright.
I've told you everything.
Death comes to all.
It is a worthy death
was worth it.
I...
I will find a way...
I will find a way to kill you.
No need.
I can handle it.
I heard
when a man is about to die,
they see the people they want to see
they would see those they want to see the most.
What are you going to do
I'm not afraid of how long it'll take to die.
Because they are with me.
My old path...
No matter where you are in the future,
we will continue to fight together
for the communist faith.
And fight side by side.
Come.
Xiaotao,
sweet porridge and fried wonton are the best.
Hurry to have a try.
I'm really
I'm a little hungry now.
Enjoy yourselves.
What about
I used to eat with him after work
after I was off duty.
You have a younger brother.
But he died before he lived to be 18.
How?
Two years ago at one night,
when he picked me up from work,
he ran into a group of drunk Japanese soldiers.
Flirting with me.
And he was jealous of me.
My younger brother is young.
He's just mad.
So I had to reason with them.
My belly was pricked
with their bayonets.
(Daddy is fond of him.)
Selling candied porridge.
3kg of peach and 4kg of shell.
This ballad was my brother's favorite
liked reciting this ballad the most.
You must hate the Japanese.
What's the use of that?
Can I defeat them?
If you ever fight in a war,
will you give your life for your brother?
Sister Hong Ling.
Why are we taking this road?
It's dark.
This path is short.
Go through it.
My house is ahead.
What dance are we going to learn today?
Let me teach you today
the most popular Fox Trot in Shanghai Beach.
Foxtrot?
I've read a novel once
It's called Shanghai Foxtrot
It's about a murder
In a quiet road.
It's scary.
We don't have that many murders.
But rats are always on this road.
Xiaotao.
I'm afraid of rats.
Can you walk in front of me?
You follow me.
Hong...
Sister Hong Ling.
You
could you
why are you doing this?
You didn't expect this, right?
I poisoned your porridge.
What about
kill her.
How did he do this?
I'll hit the road
taking that path,
shot her twice in the back.
You're not lying
you probably heard gunshots, right?
But I heard gunshot for a long time
why are you back so late?
To deal with the body?
To dispose of the corpse?
Great!
Good job.
Did you take the medicine?
Yes, I have.
Have you changed the gauze?
Not yet.
Let me help you with that.
Alright.
Hongling,
shi Yang was entrusted by Chongqing Military Commission
to hide for a long time.
He got a piece of very important information.
But he didn't hand it in.
He absconded without permission
and threatened the headquarters to redeem the information.
What was the information?
The Japanese Army Ministry's plan to forge legal currency
without this information,
counterfeit money will spread in the areas under the Kuomintang control.
The financial system will collapse.
And the war's supplies will suffer.
Our victory is still in the future.
This is the price for your glorious
and a glorious future.
I just don't want to kill innocent people.
As for what he'd done
and how he got the money,
I don't care about that.
You care about it?
You and Shi Yang are not the same kind of person.
Your conscience?
And justice
have not extinguished
you will help me.
Why did you steal my pendant?
I was wrong.
I'm wrong!
I'm asking why you stole my pendant.
The woman lied to me.
You didn't kill her.
Why didn't you kill her?
The woman told me that
as long as I give her the pendant,
she'll give me half the money.
It's all my fault.
You wretch!
Me?
How could you frame me behind?
I'm sorry.
I owe a gambling debt.
I can't even pay them back.
They'll kill me!
Please.
Please, it's my fault.
Don't kill me.
Where is she?
The old factory.
In the old factory?
Take me to her.
I will take you there.
I'll take you to her.
She's waiting for me.
You can kill her.
I will shoot you
I will shoot you.
She's in that old factory ahead.
Wait for me on the second floor.
Don't forget that
I have the gun at your back.
Got it?
She's very alert.
I'll calm her down.
Don't play tricks.
Xiaotao.
They spotted me.
Shi Yang is outside right now.
There is no information in the pendant.
He's lying to me.
I'm here to tell you that
we can find another clue to him.
Shi Yang has heart disease?
On Thursdays,
ci'an Hospital for a doctor.
To collect some medicine called nitroglycerin.
Ci'an Hospital.
Leave now.
Just go!
How about you?
Don't mind me.
Just do it for my dear brother.
But I can't leave you behind.
Don't worry. He won't hurt me.
Just go. Hurry.
Whore.
Betrayed me?
Get out of the way.
Go to hell!
If one day you fight in a war,
will you give your life for your brother?
Dad is back!
Son.
Father.
Are you well-behaved or not?
Nice.
Father.
Why did you come home so late again?
I have many things to do.
Why are you still up so late?
He asked me to wait
he had to wait for you to finish your story
finish your story.
Alright.
I'll tell you a story.
What do you want to hear?
The tin soldier's story.
The one
a steadfast tin soldier.
The little tin soldier, right?
That's right.
Let me tell you.
Once upon a time,
there was a tin soldier.
Who always had a musket on his shoulder.
Brave and handsome.
Dad, I will have to carry a musket in the future.
Great!
In the future, our Fan Fan
will carry a musket on her shoulder.
Brave and handsome.
And there are many
there are many other toys.
There's a beautiful dancer made of paper.
She is wearing a
with her.
The tin soldier loves her very much.
He looks at her every day
and dreamed that one day
to be his bride.
But there's a little monster
hates Xibing very much.
I threw him into the fire
when he wasn't looking.
Does it hurt, the tin soldier?
Of course it does.
But Xibing is very brave.
Although the fire consumed his body,
and slowly melted his body,
he was still holding on
that Mauser Spear
at that time,
there is a gust of wind.
With the wind,
that beautiful dancer is flying.
He's flying.
So he's next to Xibing.
Brother.
Look at this.
It seems Lao Lu is talking about something.
Come on.
Louder, please.
The dancer, stay.
The rose brooch.
What?
What rose brooch?
Could it be some important information?
He finally confessed.
Listen to more of them.
From now on,
they
be together forever?
Together again?
Which other communist were you with?
Confess.
Did your upline...
Say something.
She's dead.
She just opened her mouth
he died without saying anything.
Come on.
Death comes to all.
It is a worthy death
and worth it.
Place the bet. Keep your hands off.
Place your bet.
It's all in the dealer.
Big and small.
Make your bet. Keep your hands off.
Everyone, stand up and don't move.
Great Lord.
Look at that person.
He looks familiar.
You seem to
somewhat nervous.
Look at that.
You lost all your money.
I can't explain to my wife and kids at home.
It seems
I think I have seen it before.
I remember now.
At Hai Ban Xian Tea House,
she was one of the tea drinkers in the private room on the second floor.
That's right
but I didn't suspect them at the time.
They were all released later
the military police must be looking for him.
Otherwise,
we'll report him
he'll be credited?
Idiot!
If he is taken away by the gendarmerie,
for us to gain any credit?
What can we do
boss Zhang
Is really lucky today.
Luckily,
you said you don't know how to play.
Come with me next time.
Jiaping.
I can't fall asleep.
You can't sleep either?
Do you know how to dance?
I think we've never danced before.
What do you think
what is it?
I can't touch it.
And you can't touch it.
It...
It exists.
Like many great things
great things in this world.
Even if it's gone,
It's still there.
I can feel it.
You are very sad today.
Right?
It means
you also feel sad.
Let's not fight today.
Just stay with me like this, okay?
Alright
chief Chen
you went to work so early today
where's the newspaper?
Have we arrived?
We have arrived.
Come on.
Here are your new application documents and news reports.
Alright.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
The counterfeit money is called Plan Shan.
I heard that in addition to the legal notes,
the Japanese are still trying to forge
the Chinese Communist Party's Border Region.
Two secret agents lurking in Yan'an
they stole the copper plate of the coin
of the copper plate and the formula for the printing paper.
Magpie is from Juntong.
Guoguo has been going to the ballroom these days.
Would it have something to do with this?
Recently, you asked me if there's any case
that is related to the ballroom?
I remembered that.
There was a murder two days ago.
The dead was a dancing girl.
The place of the crime
It's in an abandoned factory.
The victim's name is Cai Hongling.
She was a dancer of Xianle Ballroom
the cause of death is
shot dead
got 3 shots
he fell from the second floor again.
He died instantly.
This man...
Have you found this man?
He hasn't.
I saw traces of men's lives
the traces of a man's life.
But when I asked people nearby,
they didn't know
was staying at her place.
No wonder Guoguo is going to the ballroom these days.
It turns out that he's trying to get close to Magpie through Cai Hongling.
But why would Juntong look for
find one of their own?
Why are you so interested in this case?
I suspect that
my wife is involved in the case.
Your wife?
Has anything to do with the dancing girls?
You were so sad the other night.
Was Cai Hongling killed
for her?
Maybe Guoguo knows where Magpie is.
In this case, we can use Guoguo
through Guoguo.
What are you thinking about with such a frown?
What's wrong with your wife?
Did she fall in love with another man?
I shouldn't have given you the green sofa back then.
Go back to your car.
It's not easy to get married.
Fuck off.
It's good to be single.
On the balcony on the second floor,
I put a pot of yellow chrysanthemums in it.
Which is the safe signal.
Change yellow chrysanthemum into purple chrysanthemum.
It means something bad happens.
I have swapped the yellow chrysanthemum for the purple chrysanthemum.
Who put it back?
What's up
what are you doing?
I'm here
to buy something.
To buy something.
This store is closed.
It's still open.
Hold on.
The boss of this shop, Boss Lu,
he's a Chinese Communist.
He has been captured.
Got it?
Is anyone here
there must be someone pretending to be his old path
and lie in ambush here.
Who didn't know about our sacrifice
but how would this person know
for the safety joint?
You're a new doctor.
Your lipstick looks great.
Where did you buy it?
I bought it at a discount in Yong'an Mall.
I thought the color is too bright.
How come?
It matches your skin tone.
Really?
Oh, right.
The aspirin you want is in counter No.5.
Thanks.
Here is a medicine bag.
Thank you.
Take this.
Please sign here.
I also want to buy lipstick.
Let's go to the mall in a couple of days.
Alright.
You have such a good taste.
Please give me some advice then.
You're so handsome.
You will look good with everything.
It's done.
Alright.
See you later.
Miss, please wait.
What's up
miss.
Your scarf dropped.
Thank you.
Did Ci'an Hospital find a clue to the magpie?
Who is this doctor?
Come on.
Jia Ping.
Lu Fangfang,
It's been a while
I was transferred
the Planning Office of Military Police.
It's so busy
get rid of or get away form duties , pressure , etc
that's an important position!
What important job?
Temporary job.
Because I can speak Japanese,
I have to run between the military police headquarters and the business.
I was exhausted.
You
to do something.
Do you know
these people?
CCP members?
The military police has arrested
the military police have arrested a lot of people.
Then
where are they sent?
I heard they are sent to detention center.
He probably can't come back.
It's so scary.
The...
Working for the Japanese,
we still have to be more careful.
You too.
I'll go in then.
Sir, are you ready?
Thank you.
Alright.
Go back to your work.
Talk to you later.
See you later.
Luo Guanqun caught him.
You caught Huang Jinming?
Recently, your military exploits are so great.
Lu, Luo Guanqun isn't taking the credit from me.
He's a bully!
Luo Guanqun is something he can do.
You're something.
The greatest ability I have
Is to be loyal to Chief Mu Cun.
The greatest ability you have
Is that no matter it's to feed the horses
or the pigs,
you can hide all the things
cover it tightly.
Luo Guanqun couldn't put his fingers in.
I'm guarding your house.
Plan Shan is going well.
Now it's gradually expanding.
The problem now
Is the lack of cash.
Although your previous fund-raising plan
was not adopted,
I'm always optimistic.
Officer Kimura.
I promise that
If we follow my plan,
I'll surely provide endless cash
for the Shan Plan.
Trust me.
Come on.
Officer Kimura.
I've been realizing a truth lately.
What is it?
Actually, people
Is the same as a horse.
What makes a good horse?
But if you look at its skin from afar,
but the feet and legs up close.
Before the chest is wide,
but at the buttocks.
Do you think...
Do I look like your Takeda Shinjunji?
Great.
Alright.
You
you're really talented.
Good morning, Xiucai Qian!
Good morning, Chief Chen
where's the newspaper?
Here it comes.
Here are your new declaration and news report.
Alright
chief Chen
I remember you
the new application forms before.
You always forget about them here.
The new application form
has serialized Wang Dulu's martial arts novels.
He startled Kunlun.
I think you're addicted to it.
Well, I'll check it next time too.
Haven't you read your annals of the Eastern Zhou States?
But how can you read this book?
Of the story.
I like the story
love the story of saving Zhao by stealing the talisman.
You mean the Hou Ying of Wei?
Right.
It's that Hou Ying
he used to be
used to be a janitor.
She's also
but then
he became the follower of Lord Xinling
of Lord Xinling.
It is unexpected that
qian Xiucai also has the same ambition.
What ambition do I have?
I'm just blind and blind.
Your eyes?
Alright.
Got to go.
Director Ding,
I can go home by myself.
That won't do.
Mr. Yamashita specially told you
to get you home safely.
Alright.
Wasn't the light on just now?
Why was it off now?