I knew a Japanese army officer
I knew a Japanese officer.
Called Martial Master Yamashita.
His man Ueda Naoki saved my life.
I've got all the things
when do we leave?
Don't be anxious.
I have something
I want to tell you.
Mr. Jiang,
let me introduce to you.
This is my friend.
Ding Qiu Yang.
Hello, Miss Cold Dew.
Hello
nice to meet you.
I watched a lot of
I've watched many of them.
Now that I see you in person,
the movies
In those films.
What a pity!
Thank you.
He's also a director.
I'm looking forward to working with Miss Han Lu.
I have a friend there.
I won't bother you.
Alright.
When are we leaving?
Don't be anxious.
Come, sit down.
I came to Shanghai this time
things didn't go well.
And then I'm back to Chongqing,
I'm afraid that it won't be easy for me to stay at home.
The nation is in difficulty now.
Successive distresses as caused by continual wars
and I
I also have responsibilities.
Do you think
why would I let you run around
run around here and there
In the city?
That's why
I can't take you away this time.
So it's the same as before?
I made all the high pledges to you
were just to make me happy for the moment.
You'd leave me behind.
I also want to spend my life with you.
Follow shadow
to live and work in peace.
But I'm still the enemy of my country and family.
How dare I expect
will you marry me?
I'm serious this time.
Please give me more time.
I promise you that
I'll come back to get you,
to take you as my bride.
Really
really.
By the way, you're on a mission today.
I followed you to the scene.
I thought
although my gun has been confiscated,
but I will
can I follow her to check it out?
Guess who I saw then?
Who?
Left Pair Tao.
I was thinking
why was she there?
She had a chat with a nun.
Nun?
What? Interested in it?
I know you have a habit of collecting women's clothes.
What's more, you need a nun's gown.
Just go.
I have changed.
I just remembered that
the one who rescued Jiang Zhaoguo
who saved Jiang Zhaoguo this afternoon.
Really?
Why don't you investigate it then?
For nothing? I will.
The nun covered her face
she couldn't see her face at all
moreover, that place is French Concession,
today, there were explosion and shots
we didn't even have time to run away
why bother investigating a nun?
In your opinion,
do you think that nun
who pretended to be me?
Ding Qiuyang will take care of you
ding Qiuyang will take care of you for me.
Also,
he will also help you
your future career development.
Why didn't you mention it before?
I have a friend like this.
He only became a director in the past two years.
Also,
If a spy bothers you again,
you can ask him for help.
Isn't he a director?
Yes
but he has
he has many ways to do it.
How are you going to Chongqing this time?
Is this a secret too?
Will you call me
when you arrive in Chongqing?
Of course I will.
Of course I will contact you.
That's good.
It's good that
even when I'm not around.
All right.
Then you
take care.
This time,
Is it real?
Of course it is.
Of course it is true.
I love you.
Me too.
Let's go now!
I'll beat you to death, anti-Japanese elements!
- Brother Qi! - Seventh Brother!
What happened?
Chief Chen
he was drunk
how could he stab someone with my knife?
You killed this man?
He was anti-Japanese.
What evidence do you have?
He passed by our table
he called us traitors.
Isn't this evidence?
How dare you kill someone
because they scolded you?
Scolding me is scolding Chairman Wang,
and the empire of Japan.
If he should be dead or not.
Calm down, calm down.
Calm down!
Section Chief Chen!
Section Chief Chen?
We are colleagues after all.
How dare you hit me?
Cool down.
Keep calm. Keep cool.
I'll bring him with me.
I'll sober him up.
-Come on. -Let go of me.
Come on.
He beat me with the second best.
Brother Qi!
You jerk! What are you?
How dare you hit me?
Brother Qi!
Don't lose the great for the little.
I'll kill him!
Forget about it.
Second best knife.
- Beat me! - He...
Brother, forget about it.
Don't bother.
How about this?
I'll beat him to death later.
What about
I will beat Chen Jiaping.
Don't argue with him, okay?
How dare you hit me?
Ling Xiao, cool down. Cool down.
Come on.
Wipe your sweat.
What's this?
A woman's thing.
Haven't you changed it?
Why would you steal from a woman?
I did change it.
I used to steal lingerie.
But now you can see.
This sachet is considered elegant.
Have I made progress?
You know what?
I didn't steal this.
I picked this up.
Which girl does he belong to?
It's from the Left Double-peach.
Where did you find it?
Do you remember that some time ago,
the warrior under the mountain pretended to be the Communist Party of China
to identify Chen Jiaping.
Zhao An even hung him on the tree.
When I found him.
After Chen Jia Ping is killed,
his woman is yours.
I can't control that woman.
I smelled her perfume satchel.
To find you.
Look, it's made of yun brocade.
I didn't expect that
you can buy good things at the train station.
How did you know you bought them from the train station?
She said it herself.
On the day she first came to Shanghai,
when Zhao An interrogated her,
It's fragrant.
Where did you get it from?
She was bought at the railway station.
Didn't she come from Wuhan to Shanghai?
That's right.
But this kind of perfume satchel made of yun brocade craftsmanship
Is a unique skill in Nanjing.
And it is only sold in Pukou Station, Nanjing.
What does that mean?
It means Zuo Shuangtao was lying.
You know what?
Zhao An is doomed.
What?
I said that
zhao An is doomed.
Zhao An is going to die.
It's none of my business.
Do you really think I know nothing?
Old Luo.
Those rumors about the company
are just nonsense.
Don't believe them.
I didn't ask you anything.
That there's a rumor.
What rumor?
Shoot.
What exactly is a rumor?
Zhao. Zhao An.
That jerk Zhao An forced me.
He's so powerful.
How would I dare to resist?
Old Luo.
Please forgive me.
We've been married for years,
and I've done so much for you.
Please.
Do you think ordinary men
would forgive such a thing?
Am I an average man?
I don't know.
You should fight for
for yourself.
Does it still hurt?
It's much better after blowing.
You are also one of them.
Aren't you afraid that Zhao An will pick on you?
Why would I be?
It's not like you.
You were quite timid before.
But you can't simply kill people.
I found something.
Ever since we got married,
I have
with great sense of righteousness.
Do you think it's the power of love?
I think
we got married.
You've become more and more slick.
However,
feng Qi is actually
Is the most brutal
and most ambitious man in Zhao An's reign.
Do not mess with him in the future.
By the way,
what did you do in the business today?
Any new task?
A secret mission.
But it doesn't matter to tell you.
You're my wife after all, right?
The Chongqing side
are secretly having peace talks with the Japanese government.
Peace talks?
Are calling a halt?
How is that possible?
Both sides have sent representatives
to Shanghai to exchange their views.
But the Japanese military strongly opposed it.
And also listed the representatives of both sides
are the targets of assassination.
Officer Kimura assigned this task to Zhao An.
And Luo wanted to take the credit,
so he sent me to investigate
I have found out about the time
and the meeting place.
Where is it?
It's in a villa on Yaerpei Road.
I originally wanted to get some scraps
to deal with Luo.
But I didn't expect Zhao An to go
he brought his men to besiege the villa.
Then...
All the negotiators were arrested.
Two of them.
The others ran away.
What happened to the two
what happened?
That must be
why are you so interested in this?
I'm so worried about you.
Worried about me?
Alright.
Then I will tell you
how I survived
and survived in an desperate situation?
Chen Jiaping is
Is as light as a swallow,
she can climb over the wall,
and jumped...
And jumped to the villa.
But Luo told me
I must not let Zhao An
we meddled in this.
So I can't let Zhao An find me.
The situation was
was extremely urgent.
Zhao An shut the front
and the back door
and surrounded.
I'm trapped on the second floor.
You can't fly even if you have wings.
Today I saw that
the extra man
Is Chen Jiaping.
And then?
And
I'll tell you after you sleep.
No, you haven't finished.
You really want to know?
Alright.
But today,
breaking the wall and breaking the tiles,
look at these.
My feet are swollen.
What if I can help?
I might be able to tell you another story.
You wanted me to wash your feet?
What are you thinking?
I was just messing with you.
What about
Is the strength okay?
Are you going to tell me or not?
I will talk. Talk.
At that moment,
a trail of footsteps came from the corridor.
I thought Zhao An was coming up.
What should I do?
I will jump off the building.
If I jump,
or I will fall to my death
or be disabled.
So at this critical moment
when it was a critical moment for me,
I showed my true colors.
I made a prompt decision
and make a leap.
What about
he went under the bed.
I meant that
when Zhao An caught those two,
honey, calm down.
I have to start all over, right?
Tell me about it.
But the one who came up wasn't Zhao An.
It was Jiang Zhaoguo, the representative from Chongqing.
Let me add some water for you.
Don't worry.
Just carry on.
Go on.
Alright.
Jiang Zhaoguo sounds strange.
It was like magic.
And pulled a grenade out of nowhere.
After the explosion,
the villa was completely silent again.
I immediately got out from under the bed
ran to the window and looked out.
To see a car,
was driven by a nun.
A nun?
Have you seen a nun drive?
Neither have I.
I only saw this nun
the gun in left hand
with the right hand holding the grenade,
how could she drive?
That's not important.
Look at the nun raising her pistol
to shoot
zhao An would flee for nothing.
Then she opened the door
and pulled Jiang Zhaoguo into the car.
To be honest,
I thought that
Is this nun disguised as a man?
How can there be such strong women?
Before Zhao An could react,
they drove away.
They disappeared without a trace.
And then?
Then?
I want to know how she will die.
I'll let you sort it out next time.
Alright.
Honey, are you tired?
I'm not tired.
Don't wash it.
Leave it to soak.
Let me knead your shoulders.
Go on.
Give me a massage.
Am I being treated like this?
Go on.
How is it with the two people caught and caught by Zhao An?
Zhao An?
The two of them
then take them away.
Then...
Locking her in the business
being tortured to death, right?
I've never heard that Zhao An brought anyone back to the business.
She must be hiding it somewhere.
Where?
Then how could I know
this is not right.
Left Pair Tao.
Why do you care about these two people
you care more about them than me?
What?
That's not concern.
I just have strong curiosity.
You have to hear the ending of the storytelling.
Alright.
I'll ask around, okay?
I'll tell you when I know.
Alright.
She really wanted to set me up.
If I'm right,
guoguo definitely wants to save the two arrested people.
This girl is desperate
hello, Mrs. Luo.
Where are you going?
Captain Zhao.
I need to deal with something outside.
Great.
Give me a ride.
Where are you going?
Wherever you are.
Today...
What's up
forget about it.
I can't.
I miss you
hello?
Mr. Chen, this is Han Lu.
These are the financial statements for last month.
They've been signed by the manager
okay, I'll go to the finance bureau later.
Miss,
here's a bouquet of lilies.
Welcome to our newly-opened
golden Rose Florist.
I don't like lilies.
I know you will.
And you'll often come here to buy flowers later.
I thought you went to Chongqing.
You saved Jiang Zhaoguo.
Do you want to accuse me of disobeying orders?
You misunderstood me.
I refused this operation before
Is that I couldn't make it.
But you exceeded my expectation.
Zhao An still caught two people.
Our mission is not completed yet.
It becomes
In the future.
That's right.
You must be ready to
to lurk in Taihe Trading House.
Director Guan Yongshan of the Second Military Commission Division
has approved the proposal.
In the market.
You just want that, right?
Right?
Look at these two.
Can you tell which is fake?
There are lots of
a large number of counterfeit money.
As far as I am concerned
the watermark technology was provided by England
It's extremely hard to counterfeit
and most of the legal coins
were printed for us by the Americans.
They have the best printing technology.
The Japanese army
spent nearly two years researching
he also failed to develop
that can fake the real ones.
Then how did they get the counterfeit?
A German submarine
defeated an American warship in the Pacific
and seized a large number of unfinished tokens.
They sold these to the Japanese government
and it has greatly facilitated
to Japanese research.
Our mission is to
to investigate
and destroy this counterfeit plan.
The development of counterfeit money
Is a huge and professional project.
But we don't have any clues now.
But your Taihe Firm
Is directly under the Japanese Military Police Headquarters,
and it has an inseparable relationship
the Japanese Army economically.
This will definitely lead to a breakthrough in our investigation.
I can take your order
but I have a condition.
What's that?
Don't touch Chen Jia Ping again
he is the best cover for you.
I won't touch him.
I wonder what kind of fan association
for your fans.
One who risks life for stars like you.
Is Mr. Jiang safe now?
You saved him.
I just helped a little.
The other person saved Mr. Jiang.
Is that someone you know?
Kind of.
Not really.
I know.
But I still don't know
mr. Jiang just left like that
he left nothing to you.
Kind of a promise.
Then why
ms. Han Lu didn't leave with Mr. Jiang?
You guys should be asking that question.
I'm sure Mr. Jiang
your own reason.
And Du Chun, the translator from Jiang Zhaoguo.
You must save him.
Before he worked for us,
he translated for Iwami,
for the Military Affairs Division of Japan's Army Ministry.
The research and printing of the counterfeit money
was the military lesson.
But two people would be caught.
And the other was up to his fate.
You are still the same.
Do you know where Zhao An has locked him up?
He's not in the business.
Isn't Chen Jia Ping in charge of general affairs?
He's involved in many things.
Try to find some clues from him.
What?
I don't want to drag him into this.
I will come up with something.
Alright.
Also, I have your file.
I've sent it to the headquarters of the Military Statistics Bureau.
Come up with a code name for yourself
chief Guan.
And Boss Dai
they need to know your movements at all times.
Call him five of hearts.
Why not?
I heard that there's an undercover Communist
there's a Communist Party spy in the firm named Four of Clubs
my five of hearts
I'm just one ahead of him.
Four of clubs.
Five of hearts.
Let's see who will win
will win in the end.
I haven't decided
whether I should wear the ring he gave me.
So the promise Mr. Jiang made
It's a ring.
May I take the liberty of asking
Is this a diamond ring?
Miss Han Lu.
Please don't misunderstand.
Here's the thing.
When I married Zuo Shuangtao,
I decorated and bought furniture.
I ordered the banquet and bought a wedding dress.
Basically, I have used up all of my savings.
That's why I didn't buy
when I bought the ring.
That's why she kept complaining
so I want to see
what it's like
what it's really like
I really bring
this box
looks more refined than mine.
What a big diamond ring!
How much is this?
This is two carat.
This is about
around one thousand yuan.
About one thousand yuan?
I'll tell her
let her dream for two more years.
Actually,
the diamond is smaller,
or no diamond,
It doesn't matter.
The most important thing is her mind.
All the matters that matter.
That's right!
Miss Han Lu.
Will Mr. Jiang contact you again?
He said he would call me again.
If that's convenient.
I want to ask Mr. Jiang a favor.
He passed out again.
Splash water.
Forget about it.
Captain Zhao,
let this pass?
It's true that these two people
where Jiang Zhaoguo is.
If you keep doing this,
he'll be dead.
I heard that Officer Kimura will be back tomorrow.
Why don't we
hand them over to Military Police Headquarters
to interrogate them.
That's reasonable.
Mosquitoes are also flesh.
This way, I'll be able to make a report.
Why did Officer Kimura let us
to us?
To help
so that Military Police Command
to clear them of this matter.
Actually, Jiang Zhaoguo and the two negotiators
figured out the truth behind the attack.
But they don't have any evidence.
If we let the two of them know
that this operation
are behind this.
Are behind this.
And then let them go.
And let them spread the news everywhere.
What's the result?
Captain.
You're saying that...
To threaten Officer Kimura with them?
We're going to die.
Don't die.
It's awful.
Now the two of them
are the bargaining chip to save our lives.
Should we continue to lock them
lock them up here, right?
Not only must she be locked up,
but also guard them tightly.
If they run away,
we'll be screwed.
Yes
come on.
What about
I think I know
where Zhao An hides her.
Where do you hide him?
Hong Yun Hotel.
How did you know that?
I told you that
I'll get back to work.
Don't.
You need to tell me the truth.
I won't do anything to you.
He...
He took me there
this is the place where you would meet before.
Right?
In the past,
In the past?
What?
He always took me to Grand Hyatt Hotel.
But this time, he took me there.
Then?
And...
Then I found out
he also knows the owner of Hong Yun Hotel well.
Very well.
What?
And what?
After he asked me to leave,
he stayed there.
It seems very important to him.
I've told you everything,
what more do you want me to do?
Zhao An.
Hongyun Hotel.
Mrs. Luo,
who are you waiting for?
You scared me.
Didn't we agree to get off work together?
Where have you been?
I went out
I went out for a few business.
Come on.
Let's go home.
What's the matter?
I just followed
the Big Spoon.
Why are you following him?
He always reports false accounts.
He said he was on a mission,
but in fact, he was taking them to stroll the streets.
As a result, I incurred a lot of money.
My boss blamed me for not examining him strictly.
I saw him sneaking out again today.
I wanted to catch him in the act.
What's the result?
Finish the book that we finished yesterday
that we didn't finish yesterday.
We have a new one.
Then hurry.
Tell me about it.
Last time we talked about
zhao An arrested two people
captured two men?
But I don't know where it is.
Have a guess
where I followed him.
Where?
Hong Yun Hotel.
Hong Yun Hotel?
I thought it would be
I was wondering why the big spoon went to Hongyun Hotel.
I...
Honey.
I'm hungry now.
How about we eat and talk?
Alright.
Eat.
Boss.
Two oilseeds,
and two eggs.
Alright.
Hurry.
Come on.
Alright.
Go on.
Why did Zhao An go to Hong Yun Hotel?
So I found a hidden corner
I hate it.
I tried to find out what he was doing.
But he didn't go in there
he went to find
who are helping him out.
I have thought it over
you invited others to stay in a hotel,
I'll be the one to blame.
I made a prompt decision
and I followed him.
Then...
Guess who I ran into inside?
Who?
I ran into Zhao An's man.
What double-dealing?
That Chen Shugan
are all there.
However
honey.
Why does the scoop
ends up with Zhao An's men?
You have got it wrong.
Datao works for Luo
they are
are still enemy.
So Diaoyao
Is not with them anymore.
My father arranged it.
Why did Luo arrange that?
Mister.
Egg and oil root.
Please enjoy.
Thanks.
Luo arranged him to
naturally I'm unaware of anything.
Think about it.
Zhao An caught those two
he didn't report the case
you even hid it away.
If they escape,
and Officer Kimura even found out.
Think about
what will happen to Zhao An?
But if Luo is extremely versatile,
to catch these two again,
I'll be able to stand up and win.
Is this perfume satchel sold by you?
You seem to be me.
Have you seen
this woman before?
How can I remember?
Think about it carefully.
Did she buy the perfume satchel from you?
Yes
she came here.
When did she buy the perfume satchel?
More than a month ago.
As for the details,
let me think.
It should be
oh, right.
The 16th of April in the lunar calendar.
I was bought on Xiaoman's day, the 15th of April,
she was sold at the railway station.
She was the first one who came to buy.
So I remember it clearly.
The 16th of April in the lunar calendar.
In the imperial calendar.
Do you want it?
Want it?
Fifty cents.
Hey,
one yuan.
The 16th of April in the lunar calendar.
Is the 22nd of May in the Solar Calendar.
When Colonel Shanxia came to Shanghai
tell me something.
When she bought the perfume satchel,
about what time was it?
It was pretty early.
And it's not even 7: 00 a.m.
The train No. 514 that Colonel Shanxia took
It starts at 7: 45,
great.
They all match.
Don't take it away.
What?
Are you refusing to pay?
I won't return the money.
You know what?
How much is this perfume satchel?
Star anise.
It's not right.
One tael of silver.
I'll give you 50 times of the price.
But you need to go somewhere with me.
Repeat what you just said.
Where are you going?
Shanghai.
It's so far away.
What about my business?
I guarantee that when you go to Shanghai,
that you find everything delicious, delicious and fun
a hundred times as much.
I'll go for that one hundred times.
Great!
Alright.
Only 100 times as much.
I'm used to bad luck.
Everyone knows everyone
how can it be my turn?
How can you prove it?
Write me a letter of guarantee.
Why are you so troublesome?
I won't go if you don't write it down.
Alright.
Write it.
I will write it.
You write it.
What's your name?
Feng Qi.
Just write that I'm Feng Qi and I promise Li Youtian.
My name is Li Youtian.
Go on.
To ensure Li Youtian's safety
when he's in Shanghai.
Also...
Continue the story.
What's the rush?
It's rare for me to go to Shanghai.
I have to bring some specialties for my wife and kid.
Write the code again.
I promise to help Li Youtian
the Three-yellow Chicken from The Hongxiang Story.
The Hongxiang Record?
There are also
the red bean cake of Fu Yun Zhai
and make sure
all the travel expenses
and the expenses of the restaurant.
Are you finished?
You've rushed me.
All right.
If you urge me,
I wrote the name of the hotel wrong.
Even if there's one mistake,
as long as the meaning is right.
Come on.
Give me two more.
Two yuan? What?
The paper and pen.
Here you are.
Alright.
Why are you looking at me?
Interesting.
Look at you.
Where are you going?
Throw cucumber slices.
What happened? You're so nervous.
Go to bed.
Go to bed first.
I'll read a book.
Go to bed early.
You have to work tomorrow.
Goodnight.
Night.
Tonight,
their people
will go to Hong Yun Hotel to save them.
She looks like
I don't think she will join the operation.
But I can't be sure.
Anyway, I can't sleep for the night.
I have to watch her.
Guoguo.
What's wrong with you?
What happened to you?