Contact target appears.
Ready to fire.
Hold on.
That woman doesn't seem to be here for a rendezvous.
Why didn't you retreat when you knew it was dangerous?
You can't retreat if I retreat?
How many snipers you have got?
So far, only one is confirmed.
Understood.
Which side you're from?
Military command or Japanese puppet master?
It's not clear yet.
But when you get into the shooting range,
It's been a while
but he didn't shoot.
He must have known
you will meet your superior here today.
And want to take us all out.
But they are confused.
Because there are no superiors and subordinates.
Would be meeting like this.
Would make it look like we're on a date
or having an affair.
They can think whatever they want.
But they've obviously doubted
their suspicions.
I'm afraid this is only temporary.
Right.
So we must come up with a plan as soon as possible.
The time
the place is all right.
Captain Tao.
Are you going to shoot or not?
Our goal is to eliminate Chen Jia Ping
together with his superior.
Firing now
the real target would be startled.
The real target is here.
You are a parrot.
I didn't expect you
you would be the leader of
so you knew about my identity long ago?
Four of clubs.
Tell me about the current situation.
Have you heard about the matter with the firm?
I don't have an identity to cover myself.
And he got the formula.
I failed the organization's trust in me.
The original plan of the organization
to evacuate Shanghai.
I once watched Mr. Lu compile
about you.
I thought you wouldn't agree to leave.
So, I've already asked for new instructions from the organization.
But now,
I'm at my wits' end too.
There is a clue.
Do you know Xindi?
Xindi?
I heard the conversation between Yamashita and Uchida.
Yamashita said that
hopefully the second phase of Project Shan
will be in Xindi.
Unfortunately, I was interrupted.
I didn't hear the rest of it.
Could new ground
could be the same?
I have checked.
There's no place called Xindi in Shanghai.
What's that?
You must investigate it clearly.
But now the main thing
to get away from here.
Is that the copper plate in the box?
As long as you give me the box,
and it is clear that I am your superior.
They will fire.
We can't take over the copper plating
or act rashly.
Right.
The copper plate is their first target.
Then they want to kill us all.
They still can't confirm my identity.
So they're still hesitating.
But if
make us want to leave,
they don't care about that much
they'll fire directly.
Your three o'clock position
Is Suzhou River.
As long as we can jump into the river,
as long as we can jump into the river,
you mean that I run to the river bank with the box?
No way.
If you touch any boxes,
they'll shoot you.
I have an idea.
What?
Kiss me.
Aren't you scared?
It seems that
this woman isn't here for the rendezvous
and target Chen Jiaping.
Why are you mad at me?
They are trying to escape.
And shoot at Chen Jiaping
aim at the woman.
And block their escape route.
Don't kill me.
My child is only 2-month-old.
Please help us.
It's dangerous to run back.
How are you?
Lu Fangfang,
cover for me!
Jia Ping?
Chen Jia Ping's superior was you.
You are the one who betrayed Chen Jia Ping.
Where is Chen Jia Ping?
What happened to him
what happened to him?
Don't you know
Is he still alive?
I don't know.
I just know that he was saving me.
In fact, you really love him.
Really?
I should be asking you this question.
Do you really love him?
I love him.
But I must kill him.
Inside is the copper plate.
You won't succeed in your conspiracy.
You won't be able to escape.
Your crimes will be known
will be known.
Everyone, back up!
Back up!
Back up.
Okay, stop looking!
Back up!
It's time to go.
Left Pair Tao.
He's back.
You must be disappointed
to see me die.
I'll be more disappointed if you die.
At least you didn't deny that
as a top secret agent in Juntong.
Tao Dachun must not understand
to set the ambush
to set an ambush.
I still couldn't get rid of you.
Why did you do this to me?
You betrayed me.
You betrayed your re-established faith
that has nothing to do with my beliefs.
Then what does it have to do with?
You killed Captain Liu.
I want to avenge him!
Liu Wuchang is dead!
What?
You dare not admit it?
It's not like you.
He saved me.
Why would I kill him?
That's why your crime is even more unforgivable.
I didn't kill him.
I didn't kill Liu Wuchang.
Whoever killed him
to sow dissension between us
and instigated you to betray and kill me.
I see
you killed Lu Fang Fang?
When Lu Fang Fang was dead,
was killed by you?
Captain Tao.
I've got the copper plate.
Good job!
Where is Chen Jiaping?
He's dead.
Are you sure about this?
If he's still alive,
I would find him
and kill him myself.
Alright.
How is this woman now?
She's injured.
I will take her away.
Why not?
I didn't want her to die so easily.
You knew about her affair
she was having an affair with Chen Jiaping.
Alright.
I'll leave her to you.
You'll get rid of your old enemy.
The copper plate
Is finally back to you.
What's in the box just now?
That's none of your business.
I replaced it with something else.
Why?
You first betrayed us
why are you helping us now?
I suddenly understand a truth.
It's personal between me and Chen Jiaping.
I can't be used by people with ulterior motives.
I believe in the justice of the Communist Party.
Only believe that the Communists can bring hope to China.
That's why I won't let Juntong get the copper plate.
And their evil plans will not succeed.
Get off here.
Bring it back to the border.
Thank you.
Comrade.
So what are you going to do next?
I don't know.
I had nowhere else to go.
And nowhere to go.
Why would you choose this path of destruction
than believe Jia Ping is framed?
I believe what I see
jiaping must still be alive
the truth will be known sooner or later.
I want him to be alive too.
He should die in my hands
after that, Lu Fang Fang got out of the car
I won't know
I will never know.
It seems that I misunderstood you.
I also misunderstood you.
We're even now.
Honey.
Remember what I told you at our wedding?
You're not perfect.
I'm not perfect either
but together we
will be perfect.
But now,
so perfect.
Do you still remember
we first met?
Who are you?
Don't.
Three, two, one.
Hold on.
What are you doing?
To think why fried dough sticks with soy milk
you can add an egg.
What's up
nothing.
The egg dropped.
You can add an egg.
They're killing people.
Leave now!
He got himself involved in
to kill me.
Master Yamashita
the four of clubs and the five of hearts are dead.
Are you sure about that?
OK?
I saw it with my own eyes.
It is as expected
as expected, they killed each other.
And eventually perish with the same.
You helped me
you not only found Lu Fangfang,
the hidden CCP,
found the copper engraving of the coin.
And now,
you killed four of clubs and five of hearts for me.
You are talented.
I really admire your talent.
Thank you, Mr. Yamashita.
It seems
you should be the manager
of Taihe Comptoir.
It's you.
Qian Xiucai imprisoned you here.
So it is you who
about Zuo Shuangtao's identity
that Zuo Shuangtao and I
why did you kill Captain Liu?
I didn't kill him.
Isn't it Chen Jiaping?
It's not Chen Jiaping.
Who was it?
Are you going to tell me or not?
It's Director Jiang.
Why did he do that?
Captain Liu is a traitor.
They're leaning against the Communist Party.
Even the Communists' side.
How did Jiang Zhaoguo know about this?
I told you?
So Jiang Zhaoguo asked you to lie
to frame Chen Jiaping?
Right?
If I don't do that,
director Jiang will kill Zhou Qingfang.
That's why Qian Xiucai killed Lu Fangfang
and framed Zuo Shuangtao.
Am I right?
Qian Xiucai,
Is a devil.
And a talent as well.
He has done many things that he is proud of.
But no one told me.
She kept chatting with me.
I know everything.
Promise me one thing.
I'll tell you everything.
What is it?
Unlock it.
What about the letter of Captain Liu?
Captain Liu's handwriting.
It's me.
Who forged it.
I studied graphology before
and I'm good at it
where the letter was?
Director Jiang burned it.
What's in the letter?
Tell me.
Captain Liu said that
I hope you can follow your faith
and dream.
At the end of the letter,
he also sent you a poem.
"Do not listen to the sound of the forest beating the leaves."
Walk slowly despite the noise.
You are badly hurt.
You won't live long.
I know that
you almost killed me today.
Which cut?
The knife.
That cut to you, didn't you?
If I didn't dodge it,
wouldn't you be a widow?
I firmly believe you can avoid it.
Oh my goodness.
It's so scary.
How did you find that?
When I was waiting for you at home,
I kept thinking
all the things that happened.
I thought
to open the window to get some fresh air.
Then I saw the reflection
the reflection from the telescope.
I suddenly realize that
this is not as simple as I thought.
I was too stupid before.
Sure enough,
I went to see Hu Jun
and he also confessed.
It's alright.
Not that stupid.
What about you?
Me?
At the scene,
I saw the knife stabbed in Lu Fangfang's body.
To be honest, for a second,
I did suspect you.
But after I thought about it carefully,
even if you really killed Lu Fang Fang,
you shouldn't have left the knife at the scene, right?
I saw you cutting apples
cutting apples at home.
I was sure that
that you weren't the one who killed Lu Fangfang
didn't you notice it?
Our neighborhood is so quiet.
It's the quietest it's ever been?
It means that someone has set up defences.
You know?
The truth is
when you said we're not perfect at this moment,
I know what you mean.
After all, there are things
to be honest.
What if there's a bug?
A tacit understanding?
One is Scholar Qian,
and the other is Jiang Zhaoguo.
Each set his own trap
so that he could incite us
to kill each other.
Fortunately,
we chose to trust each other.
But now it's still not perfect.
Under the mountain,
sell papers?
The marriage of the movie star Han Lu to a wealthy Japanese businessman
the grand wedding is about to be held.
I suddenly want to drink coffee,
just wait for me in the car.
All right.
If you really marry the warrior under the mountain,
you'll become a notorious traitor.
You'll be branded with shame forever.
Do you know that
I let you down again and again
and heartbroken.
That's because I've been through too much.
I've been through so much.
Now that's different.
Now the mission completely failed.
I can't bring myself to go back to Chongqing.
In my life,
you're my only one now.
Let's forget all these.
Let's find a place where no one knows us
and start a new life.
Alright?
Is this ticket to Hong Kong?
I'll be waiting for you.
I'll be waiting for you all the time.
Comrades.
It's time for the decisive battle.
Welcome the new comrades to join us.
This is Gao Fang.
He intercepted some important information through his radio.
Everyone.
We were misled before.
Xindi is not a place at all.
It's a movie that promotes militarism.
The name of this movie is Xindi,
and the movie
Is going to be released in Luhua Cinema.
And I've already located
the counterfeit factory is underground of Lu Hua Cinema.
Two o'clock tomorrow afternoon.
The warrior and Cold Dew
a traditional Japanese wedding ceremony
at the foot of the mountain in Shanghai.
After that, they'll have an outdoor wedding
for an outdoor wedding.
After the banquet,
commander of Shanghai Dispatch Army, Junliu Hata
will arrive at the scene.
To sign an investment agreement with Yamashita.
Investing in movies is just a cover.
The main content of the agreement
Is about the launch of the second phase of Plan Shan.
So, our goal this time
Is to rescue the kidnapped workers in the counterfeit factory.
And experts
and returned the printed coins
the paper used for the coin
and printing equipment
and destroying the entire planet.
But in fact there are two huge
(and insurmountable difficulties.)
The underground counterfeit factory is divided into two areas,
two areas: the printing shop,
has a built-in safe
has a built-in safe.
Through blasting,
to enter the workers' printing shop,
and the experts' workshops
are separated by an iron gate 5 centimeters thick.
Can it be exploded?
To blow up this iron gate,
we need at least 10 kg
more than 10 kg of TNT
moreover, even if we break the iron gate,
the occupants can't survive
no one inside would have survived.
The only way
Is to get the key to the iron gate.
But the key is in his hand.
Yes
mr. Yamashita,
I don't understand why Jiang Zhaoguo
I don't quite understand.
Why you want to marry Han Lu?
I need a
a Chinese film star
shooting films with the spirit of Japanese empire.
Which will paralyze the Chinese people.
Got it.
There's one thing
I'll only tell you.
What is it?
I like the way
with the scars
with scars.
It turns out that
scars can make a woman
can make a woman more beautiful.
Kimono has no pockets.
That you carry with you.
Usually put it in the Faith Pouch.
Little Pea.
At 4 p.m.,
we must finish it on time.
After we finish today's mission,
I will leave Shanghai.
I'll bring you back to my hometown.
Where is my hometown?
The beautiful Rehe.
My hometown is pretty.
There're prairie,
and lakes.
The grass there is richest.
The water there is the sweetest.
You can have enough to eat
and drank as much as you wanted.
Then I ran.
Until the moon was up.
The prairie will be peaceful.
I can take you to eat roast mutton.
Oh, right.
You don't eat meat,
but you only love grass.
I've been muddle through these years.
But working for a Japanese
and almost caused a huge mistake.
So I'll sit on the grassland in my hometown
watching the bright moon
and reflect on yourself.
What?
And you're looking down on me.
You almost became the Japanese's horse.
So you should reflect on yourself too.
Although Chen Jiaping is mean to me,
he's a good man
I really envy him.
What?
Being a hero?
To be a hero.
Especially when he comes home after being a hero.
And his beautiful wife to keep him warm.
That's right.
I still have you, right?
Little Pea.
In the days to come,
we can live together.
It's broken.
The key is not in the Faith Pouch.
Little Pea.
We're ready to go.
Little Bean!
Action!
What should we do?
Where will the key be?
Little Doudou, come back!
Come back!
Don't shoot.
Be careful
what happened
what's going on?
Little Pea.
Come on.
Mr. Foot the mountain.
Mr. Yamashita.
Miss Cold Dew.
Come here.
What are you doing?
The second best.
Why are you here?
Sorry, guys.
The horse got scared.
Did you hurt everyone?
Let me ask you something.
Why are you here?
I'm working here.
The clogs of
the superstars' clogs.
Mr. Yamashita
both swords
you have a bad habit of stealing things from women.
It's yummy!
Mr. Yamashita,
today is a day with something great.
Please don't shoot.
WEBVTT