♪The glass slipper's tale fades at midnight♪
♪The prince with champagne is hunting his prey♪
♪It's you, it's you, and it's you again♪
♪Let's sing and dance♪
♪Let's go happy♪
♪Love is a crazy game♪
♪Truth or lies, lost in desire♪
♪No way out, sinking deeper♪
♪Who surrenders, and still craves more?♪
[Game of True Love]
[Episode 6]
Want to play a love game with me?
I'll make you concede defeat from the bottom of your heart.
By then,
don't come crying to me.
Why are you laughing?
Xu Nuo, have you ever heard
of "a cover-up only makes things worse"?
You kept saying that you'd defeat me,
but actually, you were thinking
about our deal last night.
Fine.
You have three months left
to be arrogant.
Make the most of it.
Mr. Shen,
don't forget to sign.
[Bai Xia]
I'll transfer the money to you later.
What's more,
speed things up with Xu Mingli.
We don't want any surprises.
What brings you here?
What?
Since you moved,
as your mother, can't I visit?
Nice house!
Look at the decoration,
it must have cost a fortune!
What do you want?
Now that you've got a rich man,
you're ditching your own mother?
I raised you
with so much effort.
What's it all for?
Just tell me what you want.
Give me 300,000 yuan.
What?
Xia,
you're a famous influencer now.
Give me some money.
It's not too much, isn't it?
300,000?
Do you think I'm an ATM?
You're gambling again, aren't you?
That's none of your business.
I know all about your secrets.
You're really bold.
An educated family?
High education?
Aren't you scared
your mask will slip?
What do you mean?
Are you threatening me?
Come on,
I'm your mother.
Giving me money
is your duty.
Nuo,
it's not that I don't want to help.
I promised your mom
I wouldn't interfere in your family matters.
Uncle,
I understand your concern.
My dad has lost his mind,
insisting on bailing out Bai Xia's club
with Yuanfei Group's funds.
You're a major shareholder of Yuanfei,
even if you don't attend meetings often,
you wouldn't want
your interests harmed, right?
What do you want me to do?
I need you to arrange
an internal audit for Yuanfei.
I don't want my dad
making more mistakes,
and I also don't want the shareholders
to suffer losses.
That's easy.
Thanks, Uncle.
Nuo.
Your dad is about to marry Bai Xia!
[Dan]
You know that?
And I heard from Gao Hao'en
that your dad's planning
to transfer your mother's shares to Bai Xia.
He even wants to give my mom's shares away?
Mom.
You should go out more.
They all say
that men at 40 bloom like flowers,
and women at 50 are admired by all.
Really?
You have no idea
how attractive you are right now.
You're elegant and refined.
Now, you are
full of charm.
Nonsense.
Nuo.
Rong.
What a small world!
Although we
had some issues before,
for Mingli's sake,
I'll let it go.
Drop the act, Bai Xia.
You know exactly how much
my dad values you in fact.
You have no right to let it go.
Besides,
my dad
gets bored easily.
You'd better start planning your next move.
Looks like your dad didn't tell you.
For now,
we won't go public,
to protect the company.
But the wedding
is still happening.
Why else would I try on dresses?
Oh,
consider the clothes Rong picked
as my gift to both of you
to celebrate my wedding.
Let's go.
Spending our family's money,
and acting generous in front of me?
Come on,
we will all
be one family soon.
Who's your family?
As long as I'm here,
you'll never marry into the Xu family.
Really?
Mingli already gave me
the family heirloom bracelet.
That's…
That was passed down from your grandma
to me when she was dying.
Oh, really?
Well, sorry about that.
But even if his mother were still alive,
wouldn't the bracelet
still go to the new daughter-in-law?
Besides,
Rong never gave the Xu family
an heir, right?
Shameless!
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
My grandmother made it clear before she passed away
that my mom
was her only daughter-in-law.
Even if they divorce,
the bracelet still belongs to my mom.
Nuo, let's go.
Nuo.
Your hand is bleeding.
I'm fine.
Mom,
Mom, Mom!
Get lost!
Don't hurt Nuo!
I'm here!
I'm Nuo.
I'm here.
Mom.
Don't worry,
with me here,
no one can hurt you.
Sleep well.
[Shen Jiahe]
Nuo, what happened?
What's wrong with your hand?
Shen Jiahe,
do you love me?
Nuo,
tell me
what happened.
What's going on?
Do something for me.
Stop Bai Xia from marrying my dad.
Forget it.
I know you won't
do something that will
offend both sides.
Forget it.
Nuo,
I can do
anything for you.
But I can't stop them
from getting married.
Who are you fooling?
With your relationship with Bai Xia,
you can't make it?
It's not what you think
between me and Bai Xia.
I don't care.
Just tell me, yes or no?
I can't.
Shen Jiahe,
do you love me?
Do something for me.
Stop Bai Xia from marrying my dad.
I went to Yuanfei to see Xu Mingli.
He avoided me again.
That bastard.
These debt collectors are driving me insane.
We did it together,
but when trouble came,
why should I have to
take the fall alone?
Xu Mingli used the Su family's power
to get away clean.
But I have nowhere to run.
My brakes failed on the highway today.
I wonder if it was done
by Xu Mingli's people.
I know too many of his secrets.
Is he trying to kill me?
If he dares harm my family,
I will take him down
with me.
What's Xu Mingli
hiding?
I finally placed Bai Xia
and got a chance for further progress.
Should I really give up now?
Jiahe,
the finance department got some information.
Xu Nuo's uncle, Su Ting,
[Gao Hao'en]
is sending an audit team to check the accounts,
including upcoming investment projects.
I guess it's because
of Bai Xia's club.
It may be shut down.
Right, yes.
About the wedding setup,
you may just contact
Miss Bai's assistant.
Eavesdropping?
What?
Let's make a deal.
What deal?
If I stop the wedding,
you will date me.
Didn't you say you couldn't make it?
How would I know if I don't try?
Deal.
Do something now.
Or they will even be
about to have babies.
What's your plan?
Don't worry about it.
Just prepare for our date.
Hi.
♪I love you, love you, love you♪
♪'Til I forget who I am♪
♪I miss you, miss you, miss you♪