♪The glass slipper's tale fades at midnight♪
♪The prince with champagne is hunting his prey♪
♪It's you, it's you, and it's you again♪
♪Let's sing and dance♪
♪Let's go happy♪
♪Love is a crazy game♪
♪Truth or lies, lost in desire♪
♪No way out, sinking deeper♪
♪Who surrenders, and still craves more?♪
[Game of True Love]
[Episode 49]
Then tell me
how you took liberties with him.
What?
Do you want to avenge him?
Shen Jiahe.
Show me some respect.
I have a fiancé.
Shen Jiahe.
Aren't you going to give up?
What can you do to me?
I...
Chi Ye.
It's a business banquet in Binhai.
Don't be made a laughingstock.
Let's go.
I'm warning you.
Stay away from her.
So ruthless.
[Yuanfei Group board meeting]
Miss Xu.
Thanks to yesterday's banquet,
everyone in Binhai knows
Yuanfei is merging with SJ.
Do you know
our relationship with SJ?
Of course,
but it's not what it used to be.
The market is in a recession,
so I chose to acquire a similar competitor
to increase market share
for the long-term benefit
of the company.
Miss Xu.
Business management is not gambling.
You can marry SJ,
but not Yuanfei.
What if
SJ controls Yuanfei later?
Will shareholders like us
still have a voice?
We trust you
because we think
you can lead Yuanfei
to a breakthrough
instead of cutting off the way back.
Even if we were to merge,
SJ is not the best choice.
Please don't worry.
M&A is not a trivial matter
for a company
of our size.
I'm not a dictator,
so I'll take the opinions of our shareholders
into consideration.
What is it?
I wanted to ask you
if you're pushing for a merger
because you want a chance to investigate Chi Ye.
The M&A was initiated by Chi Ye,
so I'm just going along for the ride,
but Chi Ye has always stayed out
of SJ's business operations,
and the M&A
doesn't do him any favors,
so I'm curious
as to why
he's so aggressively pushing
for this M&A.
He will have access
to SJ's detailed accounts during the M&A process,
so Chi Ye may be doing it
to get at Chi Hao.
Chi Ye doesn't hate his brother
any less than he hates anyone else.
In that case,
we can just watch them
fight.
As for the company,
I'll help you.
Hello?
Miss Xu.
A lady named Bai Xia wants to see you.
OK.
How dare you
use Bai Xia?
She has the best chance
of getting close to Chi Ye
and bringing me
more information.
Aren't you afraid she'll play tricks on you?
Aren't you leaving yet?
Use this cell phone to contact me from now on.
When I can't reach you,
I think you're doing something
with Chi Ye.
Are you trying to spy on me?
Yes,
so you must watch
what you say and do.
Don't feed Chi Ye anymore.
Doesn't he have hands?
Narrow-minded.
Okay.
I'm here to pick up some products
and stop by to visit you.
Thank you.
Are Yuanfei and SJ really going to merge
after all these years of competition?
Why do you suddenly ask about it?
Chi Ye brought in a lot
of SJ shareholders
and planned to take advantage of the merger
to bring down Chi Hao.
Sure enough.
As expected.
This is the performance report that was sent
to the Yuanfei Group.
Turn to the pages about finance.
There are a few accounts
that look fine,
[Asset list]
but if you look at them in conjunction
with the revenue
of your mother's company overseas,
you'll see
that Chi Hao is secretly laundering money.
Give these to the police anonymously.
Okay.
By the way, Mr. Chi.
You should be careful these days too.
The police have been to me several times.
I'm being watched now.
Come in.
Hello, Mr. Chi.
We're from the Binhai City Public Security
Bureau's Economic Investigation Detachment.
Here are my certificates.
Are you Chi Hao?
That's right.
You're suspected of laundering money overseas,
and the amount involved is huge.
Please come with us.
Sir.
There must be some misunderstanding,
but I will assist you in your investigation.
Your cell phone needs
to be kept by us for the time being.
It was you?
You did this?
My brother.
In prison,
please behave yourself.
I'll hire the best lawyer
to defend you.
You stupid ungrateful soul.
Do you think you can beat me like this?
You ungrateful soul.
- I'll kill you. - Calm down.
- Wait and see. - Calm down.
Calm down.
Let's go.
Chi Hao is down,
so Xu Mingli will be next.
We spent more than ten years together,
but at the end of it,
we never really got to know him.
Chi Ye is usually so gentle and kind,
but Lin Yi
is a madman bent on revenge.
If it wasn't for the fact,
it would have been hard for me
to connect the two.
I could understand his hatred,
but I didn't expect him to be so cruel.
No matter how much I hated Xu Mingli,
I never wanted to hurt him.
By the way,
Bai Xia told me
that after Chi Hao's fall,
the various shareholders of SJ began to dispute.
The merger plan
may not be pushed through in a short time.
Okay.
Don't think about these things,
okay?
Just relax.
Let's go.
Have some fruit.
Relax
and don't think so much.
Are you tired?
Your massage was nice.
Sweet.
Isn't it?
Have another one.
Do you miss me?
[Chi Ye]
Miss Xu is not in the office today.
Hello, Chi Ye.
What's up?
I'm downstairs.
I've arranged to go to a concert with her.
Has she packed yet?
Actually,
she has a meeting today
and is working overtime at her company.
I'll pick her up there.
[Chi Ye]
Who is it?
It's me, Chi Ye.
Chi Ye?
He told me he had a meeting today
and that we couldn't meet.
I guess
maybe he saw my car
and made sure I was home.
Go upstairs. I'll meet him.
What are you doing here?
What? Can't I come in and sit down for a while?
You're not welcome.
You put your brother in jail,
and you now can't wait to get at me, right?
He's the one who laundered the money,
and the cops took him.
What's it got to do with me?
Non-biological brothers
can really fall out at any time,
right,
Lin Yi?
I haven't seen you for only a few days,
and you don't even remember
my name,
but Mr. Shen,
don't worry about Chi Hao.
You'd better take care of Uncle Xu first.
Maybe someday,
he'll be there to be my brother's companion.
That's what he deserves,
but I'm warning you.
Don't let this matter involve Nuo.
Nuo is my wife,
so I'll treasure her more than anyone else.
Anything else?
Fine.
Since my master doesn't welcome me,
I'm leaving.
Nuo.
Why did Chi Ye suddenly come over?
Maybe because
I silenced my cell phone
and didn't get his call.
Did he find anything just now?
No, he didn't. Don't worry.
I'm leaving.
Be careful.
Was everything in the past
a lie?
I see it's raining outside.
I bought coupled umbrellas.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Happy birthday, Chi Ye.
Nuo.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
He's my fiancé.
If you have anything against him,
just come at me.
Why
are you in love with my brother?
He's sincere
and persistent.
How can it be fake?
Nuo.
How could you lie to me like that?
♪I love you, love you, love you♪
♪So deep that I forget who I am♪
♪I miss you, miss you, miss you♪