♪The glass slipper's tale fades at midnight♪
♪The prince with champagne is hunting his prey♪
♪It's you, it's you, and it's you again♪
♪Let's sing and dance♪
♪Let's go happy♪
♪Love is a crazy game♪
♪Truth or lies, lost in desire♪
♪No way out, sinking deeper♪
♪Who surrenders, and still craves more?♪
[Game of True Love]
[Episode 44]
Nuo.
Don't go.
Nuo, why are you here?
I left my stuff here.
I called you, but you didn't answer.
I came to get my stuff.
Shen Jiahe.
Don't you know there's a gas leak
in your house?
Are you okay?
Can you be sober
and careful?
You just lost your love.
If someone tries to hurt you,
you won't even know how you died.
Someone tried to hurt me?
So are you here to save me?
You're overthinking it.
I got the stuff.
You obviously care about me,
or why did you come to save me?
I was afraid I'd be thought a murderer
after passing by your house.
Nuo.
After all this time,
surely no one will come.
[Chi Ye]
Chi Ye.
It's Dan.
Nuo is in the shower.
Chi Ye.
Why are you here?
Didn't you say Xu Nuo was at your place?
Where is she?
She...
That's right.
She's in the shower.
Where is he?
Dan.
Dan, why didn't I
find the pajamas you gave me?
Chi Ye?
Why are you here?
Something came up,
and I couldn't get through to you.
I was a little worried, so I came over.
What made you
so anxious?
Tomorrow,
your mom's case has its first trial.
Do you want to attend?
OK.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
Since you're fine, I'll go back.
Nuo.
What happened to you guys?
I've never seen Chi Ye
like that.
That scared me.
Dan.
Remember.
From now on,
don't tell anyone
about my whereabouts,
especially Chi Ye
and Shen Jiahe.
What happened to you guys?
I'll tell you later.
It's safer if you don't know now.
Dong.
And Shen Jiahe?
He's fine
and went to the office yesterday.
Did you find out who saved him?
No.
I hacked the surveillance
before I did that yesterday,
so it didn't catch anything.
Even if Chi Ye can't be arrested,
they could at least
start with Dong.
Why would he want
to hurt Shen Jiahe?
And was that car accident
made because of Xu Mingli?
I'd better call the police first
to give them some clues.
Take your medicine.
Why did you come yesterday?
Dan said she was worried you were taking things too hard
and told me to check on you.
Dan?
I just got a call.
The cops went through
all the security cameras
and said
they were all hacked
last night.
I guess they came prepared.
Luckily, you're okay.
So who do you suspect did it?
I was in danger
as soon as I sent someone
to investigate Chi Ye and Lin Yi.
It's too much of a coincidence.
After Lin Chongshan died
in a fire,
his wife Zhang Lihui
and son Lin Yi
seemed to have totally disappeared,
but before that,
Lin Yi attended a kindergarten
in his neighborhood.
It took me a lot of effort
[Kindergarten graduation photo]
to find a group photo of the students
in their class from one of the teachers.
[Lin Yi]
Mom.
Why are you
gambling again?
Where did you get the money?
Bai Lanhua.
Did you become so love-blind
that some old man tricked you
into taking the fall for him?
Answer me.
Do you know how many years you will be sentenced?
Do you want to stay in jail
until Yuan goes to elementary school?
Leave me alone.
How can I leave you alone?
You're my mom.
What did you do?
And where did you get that half a million
you gave me?
Don't ask.
Raise Yuan properly
with this money.
And that guy,
Wu Tie,
is pretty good to you.
Live well with him from now on.
I can take care of myself.
Mom. You...
My mom was arrested for gambling.
I suspect SJ's people set her up.
They've done it before
with Xiamei's investments.
They'll give you a favor
and then suddenly set you up.
Chi Hao's goal
was to use you to take down Xu Mingli,
but now,
you're divorced from Xu Mingli,
so they probably won't hurt you anymore.
Then who could it be?
If I'm not mistaken,
your mom earlier lied
about Lin Yi's whereabouts.
This matter
is still related to Lin Yi's identity.
Lin Yi?
Lin Chongshan's son?
My
half-brother?
He's Lin Yi,
right?
He's also the one who paid you
to lie to me,
opened a casino for you,
and got you arrested.
Why don't you tell the truth?
Does Bai Xia know you're being threatened?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You don't talk nonsense
in front of Xia.
Calm down.
Sit down.
Thank you.
I've known all about it.
Don't talk nonsense.
I didn't say anything.
Yuanfei's market share
[Yuanfei Harbour City]
has dropped significantly
in the last six months.
[Yuanfei Group Board Meeting]
The market is constantly changing,
so we can all understand that,
but
at this critical time,
we must have someone
at the helm with both experience
and vigor.
Jia.
You're wrong.
I'm not saying
Miss Xu is doing a bad job.
I know we all want
what's best for the group.
Xu Nuo has just come on board,
and the projects she's taken on
haven't come to fruition yet.
What's in this report
you're looking at?
It's all old results
from Mr. Xu.
We can't put it all
on Xu Nuo.
I said
I didn't criticize Miss Xu.
I agree
with what Mr. Su said,
but
right now,
Miss Xu's mother is sick in bed,
so it's hard for her to balance
her career and her family.
I won't let my family
affect my work.
But after all, your influence in Yuanfei
is limited.
In these crucial times,
we still need
a leader who can
calm everyone down.
Her influence is limited?
What do you mean?
Are you looking down
on me?
Mr. Su.
This is not the time for you to defend her.
How about this?
Since this is a shareholders' meeting,
let's vote by a show of hands.
Raise your hand if you agree
to Mr. Shen as CEO.
I don't agree.
Even if the board replaces Miss Xu,
I won't be CEO.
Xu Mingli.
You were framed by Chi Hao,
and Nuo almost lost her life for you,
but now, you're twisting the knife.
Do you have a conscience?
Why do your words
sound so harsh?
Twisting the knife?
It was the board's opinion.
I was just going with the flow.
Stop pretending, okay?
Those directors
don't even read the financial reports,
so would they suddenly
propose the chairman's removal?
I raised Nuo
for so many years,
so can I have no love
for her?
But who are you?
You're my own son.
I was worried that Nuo
would turn against you if you fell out.
That's not necessary.
Mind your own business.
Don't get Yuanfei involved
in the Chi family's revenge.
Do you understand?
Nuo.
Do you have time tonight?
Let's have dinner together.
I have something to tell you.
But I don't want to talk to you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know Xu Mingli
would do this.
People in the workplace seek their own interests.
I'll take what you did today
as your reward for saving you
by mistake the other day.
It wasn't a coincidence that day.
You saved me on purpose,
didn't you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
What are you trying to say?
Nuo.
Do you know Chi Ye
is Lin Chongshan's son?
♪I love you, love you, love you♪
♪So deep that I forget who I am♪
♪I miss you, miss you, miss you♪