♪The glass slipper's tale fades at midnight♪
♪The prince with champagne is hunting his prey♪
♪It's you, it's you, and it's you again♪
♪Let's sing and dance♪
♪Let's go happy♪
♪Love is a crazy game♪
♪Truth or lies, lost in desire♪
♪No way out, sinking deeper♪
♪Who surrenders, and still craves more?♪
[Game of True Love]
[Episode 47]
Hello?
How's it going, Jiahe?
You went to fight Chi Ye.
Did you manage to get
his skin sample?
Hello?
Say something, Shen Jiahe.
What, the fight knocked the words out of you?
It doesn't matter anymore.
Jiahe,
did something happen?
I thought...
I thought if I had the evidence
to prove Chi Ye is Lin Yi,
then he and Nuo
wouldn't have to be together.
But they'll be together anyway.
Nuo's tired of me.
It's all over.
Where are you?
I'm coming to you now.
Nuo.
Dandan...
What do I do?
Come on,
let's get up first.
Nuo...
do you really have to do this?
Back then, he only lied to you
and pushed you away
to protect you.
And now you're using
the same tactic on him?
If the misunderstanding
goes deeper and deeper,
you might never find your way back.
[Love is trust]
This is the one
I gave you before.
Look closely.
Love is trust.
The "trust" is not what it used to be.
Shen Jiahe,
we're the same kind of people,
stubborn and dishonest.
We think we're doing it for love,
but we just keep hiding things.
Can you please wake up
and be more careful?
You came to save me?
Why did you show up yesterday?
Dandan was worried you'd do something stupid.
She told me to check on you.
Dandan?
Nuo still loves me.
Dandan,
what exactly happened
between Xu Nuo and Shen Jiahe?
They completely...
broke things off.
No wonder he said it was all over.
I just called him,
and after hanging up,
he never picked up again.
You think he might do something crazy?
Without you in my life,
I don't see the point in living.
Nuo,
I don't think I can take this much longer.
♪It shines like a star♪
♪It's as bright as light ♪
Even if Chi Ye finds out
and everything falls apart...
I still want to hold you right now.
♪Only you♪
♪Could anchor my drifting heart♪
♪I long to kiss you♪
♪I long to have you♪
♪You are the only love♪
♪Of my life♪
♪I love you, love you, love you♪
♪So deep that I forget who I am♪
♪I miss you, miss you, miss you♪
♪So much in the darkest night♪
♪I cannot♪
♪Help giving you my heart♪
♪My body♪
♪My everything♪
♪I love you 'til the moon sinks♪
♪And the stars fall from sight♪
♪I love you, love you, love you♪
♪So deep that I forget who I am♪
♪I miss you, miss you, miss you♪
♪So much in the darkest night♪
♪I cannot♪
♪Help giving you my heart♪
♪My body♪
♪My everything♪
♪I love you 'til the moon sinks♪
♪And the stars fall from sight♪
Xu,
this batch of scooters
has already been produced.
But Yuanfei Group suddenly shut us down.
They said our quality didn't meet the mark.
Xu,
please think of something fast.
Shut down?
Who gave the order?
Was it Miss Xu?
No, it was Mr. Shen.
Alright then,
go back and apply for a recheck.
I'll give the quality inspection team
a heads-up.
Tweak the numbers a bit.
No big deal.
That's great news,
Xu!
You've really helped us out.
Regarding your bonus,
we'll make sure you get it by the end of the year.
The bonus doesn't matter.
Jiang Tian,
you've really got
to tighten up the quality.
I heard the first batch
didn't sell too well.
If you don't pull your weight,
even I can't help you.
Right?
Right.
Xu,
you're absolutely right.
[Mr. Ao Zhe, you're sincerely invited]
[to the engagement of Groom: Chi Ye & Bride: Xu Nuo]
[Ms. Bai Xia, you're sincerely invited]
[Groom: Chi Ye]
[Virtual number]
It's me, Dong.
What is it?
That electric scooter supplier, Jiang Tian,
[the engagement]
was stirring up trouble with us.
He claimed we didn't ship the batteries
to Yuanfei Group's standard.
I swapped the goods out.
This time,
we're mixing in that batch
with the faulty batteries.
Did Xu Mingli fall for it?
He said he'd give a heads-up
to the relevant departments.
Knew it.
Greedy as ever.
That's just who he is.
The trap's set.
Just waiting for your signal.
By the way...
Looks like we've got no eyes
on Dandan's place.
I'll send someone right away.
We've been short-staffed
handling the scooter factory stuff.
Don't let your guard down.
Got it.
[Mr. Ao Zhe, you're sincerely invited]
[to the engagement of Groom: Chi Ye & Bride: Xu Nuo]
Shen Jiahe...
good thing you know your place.
Since that's the case,
I'll let you off the hook.
Little Mouse says,
"When will spring come?
Will Little Kitty
still be napping by then?"
You think she understands
any of that right now?
Who says Yuan doesn't understand?
Look,
she even tries to talk to me.
My dear Yuan...
Since when
did she become your Yuan?
She's always been mine.
Xia,
when the weather's nice,
let's take her to the park.
Sound good?
Yuan's heart's not well.
She should rest much.
Yuan,
get better soon.
I will take you to the park!
Pinky promise.
Yuan...
Yuan!
[OUTPATIENT]
[Operation Room]
I thought she was better.
I thought...
we could finally live
a normal life.
Yuan will get better.
We made a pinky promise.
I was going to take her to the park.
I really love her...
like she's
my very own daughter.
She really is your daughter.
Thank you.
Actually, from the moment I found out
I couldn't have children,
I really felt hopeless.
You can't have kids?
Yeah.
I had surgery before.
It left long-term issues.
[DURING THE OPERATION]
[THE OPERATION IS OVER]
Doctor.
Doctor,
how is she?
I did everything I could.
Xia...
Xia!
Bai Xia, what are you doing?
Bai Xia!
Where's the paternity test?
What test?
What are you looking for?
You made such a mess.
What are you doing?
Give it to me!
Give you what?
Are you out of your mind?
What do you want?
[Confirmed no blood relation]
[Binhai New Life Private Hospital]
New Life Private Hospital...
Why would they lie to you?
Why would they screw me over?
What do you mean?
Why?
What are you even talking about?
Xu Yuan is your biological daughter.
She's gone...
She's gone!
You think I would...
You really think
I'd believe anything you say now?
Isn't that child
yours and that punk's?
Putting on an act for me again, huh?
I still have Yuan's cord blood.
You can do a hundred,
a thousand paternity tests!
Are you serious?
Xu Mingli...
I hate you!
Yuan really is my child?
She's my child?
My child...
She's my child! My child!
♪I love you, love you, love you♪
♪So deep that I forget who I am♪
♪I miss you, miss you, miss you♪