♪The glass slipper's tale fades at midnight♪
♪The prince with champagne is hunting his prey♪
♪It's you, it's you, and it's you again♪
♪Let's sing and dance♪
♪Let's go happy♪
♪Love is a crazy game♪
♪Truth or lies, lost in desire♪
♪No way out, sinking deeper♪
♪Who surrenders, and still craves more?♪
[Game of True Love]
[Episode 8]
Shen Jiahe!
What are you doing here
in the middle of the night?
Why didn't you answer my calls?
I didn't want to.
What were you doing?
None of your business.
Last night you were in my bed,
and today you're dating someone else,
right?
I already told you.
Last night was an accident.
One that lasted all night?
That's too long for an accident.
You...
Happy boys, happy time.
You should just admit defeat
if you can't play the game.
I'm telling you, Xu Nuo,
you can mess around with anyone
but Chi Ye.
So you're allowed
to mess around with your ex,
but I can't reunite with mine?
Oh, I forgot.
Chi Ye is your good brother, right?
You're really bothered, huh?
Since the moment
you came home with me
the night before last,
you've already lost.
Shen Jiahe,
it's all just an act. Don't you get it?
But my relationship with Chi Ye
is different.
Have you ever watched the stars
with me at the Grand Canyon?
Or basked in the sun
with me in Hawaii?
Or roamed the grasslands...
Who do you think you are?
to just kiss me whenever you want?
How boring.
The game has just begun.
You should just admit defeat
if you can't play the game.
Mr. Shen.
Mr. Shen?
What's wrong?
Well,
it's about Miss Bai Xia's live commerce.
Coordinating the live commerce is a small matter
that the Marketing and PR departments
can handle.
Do I need to give direct orders?
Everyone knows
it's a thankless job
with a big responsibility.
No one wants to do it.
Right, the future Mrs. Boss
is hard to please.
If she whispers in his ear,
we'll be packing our bags and leaving.
You're right.
Since you're so eager to fight injustice,
then this case
will be handled by you, Assistant Xu.
Me?
Ao Zhe,
this case will be handled by Xu Nuo.
Report to Susan of the Marketing Department.
Okay.
I won't do it.
Then don't come to work.
Shen Jiahe,
what else can you do
except threaten me?
What else I can do to you,
you know best.
Do I need to say it out?
Fine.
I'll do it.
Can I get off work now?
Mr. Shen,
I have a date.
With whom?
With whom, you know best, don't you?
Do I need to say it out?
I'm sorry, Mr. Shen.
Mr. Shen,
is this Miss Xu's first love
as is said?
What first love?
She was with Chi Ye back then
just to provoke me.
She's still doing this after all these years.
Because it still works.
Boss,
I'll get back to work if there's nothing else.
By the way, Susan just returned from abroad.
She doesn't know who Miss Xu is.
Should I give her a heads-up?
No.
Okay.
[Susan, Marketing Department]
Hello, Susan.
What?
The live stream starts tomorrow.
I don't care if you have excuses.
If anything goes wrong with the merchandise,
you take full responsibility.
Hello!
Open the door, please!
Please open the door!
Sir,
why is the warehouse leaking?
The roof might have been damaged
by the strong wind.
Get someone
to cover them up now.
But it's so late.
Who can I get?
Then find some waterproof cloths.
Okay.
Ao Zhe,
tell the Engineering Department to fix the roof.
What about Miss Xu Nuo?
She doesn't want anyone to see her
when she's in a mess.
Let's go.
If it rains all night,
I'm afraid most of the goods
will be damaged.
Mei,
get someone to the warehouse
to keep an eye on the shipment.
Don't let damp cotton pads
reach the live stream.
Have a quick check.
Don't let anything go wrong
during the live stream.
Okay.
What's wrong with you?
Can't you
check the weather forecast in advance?
The weather forecast doesn't predict
warehouse leaks.
You...
Mind today's live stream.
Don't mess it up!
Oh, Miss Bai,
you've become even more beautiful.
I'll tell you
the features of our product.
Well,
it is individually packaged.
This cotton pad
is the new domestic brand
we highly recommend in this live.
It's made of natural, biodegradable materials.
Each cotton pad
is individually packaged.
Clean and hygienic.
And today,
our brand representative is here too.
The discounts are also very generous.
Here!
Let me open one for everyone to see.
Sorry, I dropped it.
It's done for.
It's over.
You dare sell moldy products!
Call the complaints hotline!
I'm sorry, everyone.
We have to pause the live
for a while now.
[Live stream has ended.]
Do you know how many fans
there are in my channel?
And you gave me moldy goods
to sell!
The humidity shouldn't be like this.
Xu Nuo,
how did you do it?
You obviously didn't deal with them properly
last night
so they got damp and moldy.
They got moldy overnight?
This isn't even
our product.
Xu Nuo,
you did this to me on purpose!
Despicable.
I wouldn't ruin our brand's reputation
just to fight against you.
There's definitely something going on.
I'll get to the bottom of it.
You're still trying to get rid of this even now?
I can't escape the responsibility on this.
I'll pay for the financial losses
of your channel personally.
As for your reputation,
I'll try to make it up.
Fine.
Start the live stream now.
Kneel and apologize to my fans.
Then it will be over.
Kneel?
Are you dreaming?
Okay.
Then settle it yourself.
You're really something.
As for the matter,
explain it to the boss yourself.
Take a good look at this.
Take it and look!
[Eco-friendly skincare live stream data]
Was this your performance
after getting the opportunity?
The brand was just launched,
and it's already being boycotted online.
Now Bai Xia
doesn't want any association with me
even on business.
Dad,
about this,
I was clearly set up.
Set up?
By whom?
Are you delusional?
You were saying Bai Xia set you up,
weren't you?
Why would she do it?
If she set you up,
she would damage
her own reputation.
I didn't say it was her.
But I'll investigate.
Investigate what?
Don't investigate anything now.
Just go back home!
Don't come back to the company
and embarrass me again!
Leave now!
[Description of the Event]
[Investigation Report]
Mr. Xu,
[Analysis of the Event]
that's the Investigation Report
on the fake cotton pads incident.
Nuo was indeed framed.
It seems the goods were indeed switched.
Did you find out who did it?
We've identified Susan as the suspect for now.
She's a commercial espionage sent by SJ.
We've already handed over the relevant materials
to the police.
Chi Hao from SJ
is always doing these shady things.
But even so,
if Nuo hadn't been careless,
they wouldn't
have had the chance
to do it.
About this event, tell Nuo
that she still needs to apologize
to Bai Xia publicly.
Mr. Xu,
if a public apology is needed,
I'll do it.
The HR Department didn't do a thorough background investigation.
The system on product safety is flawed.
These are all my mistakes.
Jiahe,
if the people under
keep messing things up
and the boss has to make up for their mistakes,
what's the point
of having them?
I know you're always meticulous,
serious, and principled.
But why do I feel
you're prioritizing Xu Nuo
over the company's interests.
Well,
deal with it yourself.
[Xiamei Beauty Club]
You volunteered to do this.
Don't play innocent
if Jiahe or your dad asks about it.
I told you,
I'll take responsibility if something goes wrong.
Fine. Let's start.
Three, two, one.
Start.
As the brand representative,
I apologize to the customers and fans
of Bai Xia's channel.
My personal negligence
has caused a negative impact.
Look,
Miss Xu is apologizing publicly
on Bai Xia's live stream.
What's going on?
To make it up to the customers,
today, I...
today Miss Bai Xia and I
will jointly
provide free gifts for everyone.
You deceived the customers.
Do you think we're stupid?
We won't take them even they are free.
Boycott them!
I heard this woman
is the brand owner's daughter.
She's good at nothing
but causing trouble.
Get out of the live stream!
Why are they talking like this?
These cyber bullies
are going too far.
Speak! Are you dumb?
To show my apology,
I will resign
from the position of Brand Manager
and take full responsibility for this incident.
Kneel and apologize!
Apologize now!
Right. Kneel and apologize!
- Apologize now! - Apologize!
Just kneel and apologize.
Don't forget
what you said:
You will do whatever
my fans ask you to do.
♪I love you, love you, love you♪
♪'Til I forget who I am♪
♪I miss you, miss you, miss you♪