♪The glass slipper's tale fades at midnight♪
♪The prince with champagne is hunting his prey♪
♪It's you, it's you, and it's you again♪
♪Let's sing and dance♪
♪Let's go happy♪
♪Love is a crazy game♪
♪Truth or lies, lost in desire♪
♪No way out, sinking deeper♪
♪Who surrenders, and still craves more?♪
[Game of True Love]
[Episode 38]
[President Room]
You really think that'll work?
The public only cares
whether our relationship
will impact Yuanfei Group's
long-term interests.
They don't actually care
if we're really divorced.
So,
as long as you two
record a video together,
telling everyone
you never got married
and parted on good terms,
this issue will be settled.
Hurry up.
You two are oddly in sync,
even wearing matching outfits.
Alright, ready?
Three, two, one, go!
Hello, everyone.
I'm Xu Nuo, Chair of Yuanfei Group.
I'm the current...
Cut!
You're clearing up rumors.
But look at you two,
anyone with eyes
can tell there's tension between you.
Move a little closer
to Mr. Shen.
A bit more closer.
Good.
Alright, ready?
Three, two, one...
Action!
Hello, everyone.
I'm Xu Nuo, Chair of Yuanfei Group.
Hello...
Xu Nuo,
could you soften
your expression a little?
Look at that smile,
you'd be better off not smiling at all.
Come on, bosses,
I'm begging you.
If you keep this up,
Yuanfei Group might really go under.
And I don't want to lose my job!
Smile a bit!
Imagine how you felt
the night before your wedding.
Look at you two,
the second you touch,
it's like a jolt of electricity.
You still claim there's no love?
Shut up!
Are we filming or not?
Filming!
Last take, okay?
Get in the zone.
You need to show some energy,
alright?
Okay, let's go!
This darn chemistry...
Last one, seriously.
Come on!
Ready?
Three, two, one...
Action!
Hello, everyone.
I'm Xu Nuo, Chair of Yuanfei Group.
I'm Shen Jiahe, current CEO
of Yuanfei Group.
Thanks for your continued interest
in our relationship...
Okay!
Hello?
Critical condition?
I'm on my way!
Nuo!
[Outpatient Clinic]
[Operating Room]
Don't panic yet.
Let's wait and see
what the doctor says
after the surgery.
Just sit for a bit.
Doctor...
how's my mom?
We've stabilized her for now,
but she's still
in critical condition.
As for what happens next,
it's hard to say.
You need to be prepared.
Ms. Su
may remain
in a vegetative state.
She was totally fine
just a couple of days ago.
How...
how did things get this bad today?
It's hard to say.
Her condition
was never really stable.
It's okay. Thank you, doctor.
It's alright.
Okay.
[Operating Room]
[Outpatient Clinic]
Lawyer Xiao.
Why are you here?
Miss Xu,
your mother entrusted me with something.
If she ever fell
into a coma
or became critically ill,
I'm to deliver this will
to you and Mr. Shen.
[Will]
[If I fall into critical condition,]
[the right to end treatment]
[will be given to Shen Jiahe.]
Mr. Shen,
please read
the will...
especailly the line
about Shen Jiahe has the right to decide
whether to continue treatment.
Ms. Su believed
it would be too painful
for Miss Xu
to make that choice.
And you, Mr. Shen,
are more rational,
better able to judge
what's best for her.
I'll take my leave now.
Call me if you need anything.
Shen Jiahe,
take a good look
at how my mom treated you,
and how everything you've done
has repaid her.
[Will]
Shen Jiahe,
leave.
I never want to see you again.
[Outpatient Clinic]
You look
just like someone.
Who?
Me, the night before your wedding.
Nuo,
there's this cheesy line,
but it's true:
"Ever since I met you,
it feels like I've been heartbroken every single day."
We've known each other for years.
Whether or not you were around,
I always knew
where your heart was.
That's why I envy Shen Jiahe.
He always had a hold on your heart.
But I hate him even more.
Because even though he could
stir up your emotions,
he always made you cry.
So,
when the wedding fell through,
I was happy.
Nuo,
on the day you were supposed to marry him,
it felt like my soul
died inside.
So yes,
I was glad
it didn't happen.
I know that's not right,
but I really cherish this chance...
to stay...
by your side,
to take care of you.
Chi Ye...
I...
I know.
I'm asking for anything.
Right now,
let's just focus on taking care of Aunt Rong.
We'll deal with everything else later.
I'll always be here for you,
by your side.
Thank you, Chi Ye.
[Outpatient Clinic]
♪Dark and lightless♪
♪That's my bitter, fleeting life♪
♪Disappointed and heartbroken♪
♪That's your empty vow of forever♪
♪Chasing a happiness out of reach♪
♪I became a slave to love♪
Do you still remember the rules of the game?
♪I stopped caring about holding on♪
And that game you suggested,
gave me the perfect chance
to use you.
The truth is, I never loved you!
How could I possibly fall
for the daughter of my enemy?
Could you? Would you?
♪Now this broken heart is only tormented by hate♪
♪Love's temptation♪
Shen Jiahe,
I hate you.
♪Your cruel betrayal cuts like a whip♪
I hate Xu Mingli too.
♪Your solemn promises...♪
All you two ever brought me
was pain.
Shen Jiahe,
take a good look
at how my mom treated you,
and how everything
you've done
has repaid her.
♪Regretful, tear-streaked♪
♪That's my twisted journey of life♪
Jiahe,
I'm trusting you with Nuo now.
Don't worry, Aunt Rong.
You two really are in sync.
♪No regrets as I fall into the void♪
♪Better the heartbreak than holding on♪
♪Still, I chose to let you go♪
♪Love's temptation, fate's chains♪
♪They're blades of wind that cut me deep inside♪
♪You once gave me warmth and love♪
♪Now this broken heart is only tormented by hate♪
♪I love you, love you, love you♪
♪So deep that I forget who I am♪
♪I miss you, miss you, miss you♪