♪The glass slipper's tale fades at midnight♪
♪The prince with champagne is hunting his prey♪
♪It's you, it's you, and it's you again♪
♪Let's sing and dance♪
♪Let's go happy♪
♪Love is a crazy game♪
♪Truth or lies, lost in desire♪
♪No way out, sinking deeper♪
♪Who surrenders, and still craves more?♪
[Game of True Love]
[Episode 37]
You're here.
You're awake.
Where's Dandan?
She went to work.
Eat something first. You're getting skinny.
Chi Ye,
I want to visit my mom at the hospital.
Aren't you afraid of running into Shen Jiahe?
What's there to be afraid of?
It's over between us.
Then why won't he let you out?
He said something's not finished.
Let's not talk about him.
Did you find the driver
who caused my mom's accident?
Yes.
It was Jiang Yuan.
He's in the same hospital as your mom.
[Outpatient Clinic]
It really was an accident.
Look,
I had a heart attack.
How could I plan that?
Why won't you believe me?
We just wanted
to understand the situation.
Ever since the crash,
I've been answering
the same questions every day.
Besides us,
who else came?
The police,
a lawyer,
and...
Mr. Shen from Yuanfei Group.
I used to work at Yuanfei Group.
But six months ago,
I left.
My family
is not doing well financially.
Now,
I mostly rely
on driving ride-hailing to make money.
This car is how I make a living.
Why would I mess around with it?
Since you left Yuanfei Group
half a year ago,
then why was Shen Jiahe
in your call history
before the crash?
Was he?
My head... It's hurting.
My head really hurts.
I don't remember.
I honestly can't recall.
This couldn't have been an accident.
You think Jiang Yuan
was working for someone?
Chi Ye,
you took Nuo away, didn't you?
Didn't you say
I was just a former boyfriend in name?
Well now I'm not.
It's just easier with her staying at my place.
Tell her,
if she comes back,
I won't care about anything else.
But Nuo told me
she never wants
to see you again.
She wants you out of her life.
Fine.
Then take good care of her.
I'll disappear myself.
Nuo.
What's wrong?
I was just thinking...
why did that driver
suddenly dodge the question
when we mentioned the call records
with Shen Jiahe?
Could that mean
Shen Jiahe is the one behind all this?
I don't know.
But his reaction was way too suspicious.
Nuo,
if you want to know anything,
just ask me.
But don't go
to the hospital on your own.
Shen Jiahe
will definitely be around there.
[President Room]
Shen Jiahe,
can't you handle
such a simple task yourself?
I'm your assistant,
not your maid.
Take a break.
Don't overwork yourself.
Mr. Shen,
we had the tech team
analyze that video.
It's just a snippet.
Miss Xu
pushed Chi Ye away soon after.
Mr. Shen,
are you okay?
Want to take some time off?
I'm fine.
Get back to work.
So revenge only means
pulling petty tricks now?
Mr. Shen.
Uncle Zhou!
When did you get back?
Have a seat, please.
With Xu Mingli under investigation,
I'm finally safe.
I just came to check on you.
Someone at the company reported him
for embezzlement and abuse of power,
but we're still waiting
on the investigation results.
Have some tea.
So...
this wasn't your doing?
No.
I didn't plant anyone
in the unmanned supermarket project.
Could it be Su Ting?
I have no idea.
Let's put that aside for now.
I'm here to inform you
Miss Xu is secretly mobilizing
the board
to get you removed.
Jiahe,
you've been at Yuanfei Group for years.
Your abilities are well recognized.
To be honest,
up to now,
no one's a better fit
for the CEO role
than you.
So of course,
we'll support whoever brings real value
to the company.
But...
Miss Xu's side
has support too,
a few Su family-in-law shareholders.
They're not to be underestimated.
Thank you, Uncle Zhou.
Jiahe,
don't blame me for saying this.
Though we don't know
the full story yet,
the bottom line is,
you and Xu Nuo
are family, after all.
You should talk to her.
Think about what's best for Yuanfei Group.
Of course.
Right,
this Friday.
You'll back me up, right, Uncle?
Then I'm relieved.
You're back already?
Did I allow you to come in?
Nuo, I need to talk to you.
I've got nothing to say.
Please leave.
You're calling a board meeting
to kick me out, right?
That's right.
What are you going to do about it?
Nuo,
the CEO position at Yuanfei Group
isn't up to you or me.
To the shareholders,
only with me in charge
can Yuanfei Group stay stable.
If you fire me,
you're the one who'll be out.
Cut the act, Shen Jiahe.
You ignored the fact
my mom raised you for over twenty years.
You used family as leverage,
treated marriage like a game...
and now you suddenly care
about Yuanfei Group's reputation?
You took down my parents.
Is your next move
to come after me?
Nuo,
I know you suspect me right now,
but I swear I had nothing to do
with Aunt Rong's accident.
Then why did the driver
have your number
in his call history?
And who reported Uncle Xu?
Hurting Nuo wasn't enough,
now you're going after her whole family?
Shut up!
This is between Nuo and me.
None of your business.
He's someone
who truly cares about me.
He's also the one
who pulled me out of your grasp.
Can you go now?
Fine.
Nuo,
just like you ordered,
I sounded out the board members.
And honestly, our chances aren't great.
[Uncle]
Is there another way
to get rid of Shen Jiahe?
[Uncle]
That depends
on what you're willing to sacrifice.
If that price means
halting Yuanfei Group's growth,
would you still do it?
What's wrong?
The plan to remove him didn't go well?
I kind of expected it.
Shen Jiahe's been at Yuanfei Group for years.
His roots run deep.
It won't be easy to bring him down.
But just now, my uncle told me,
before my dad was taken away,
he talked to the shareholders
as a personal favor.
He asked them to support Shen Jiahe.
Shen Jiahe reported Uncle Xu,
yet Uncle Xu still helped him?
I never imagined
they were that close.
Maybe to my dad,
a son will always matter more
than a daughter.
But you're the real one,
and he's not.
Nuo,
the news
[Chairman and CEO]
about your divorce
[of Yuanfei Group announce divorce]
is all over the internet now.
Divorce?
We didn't even have a wedding!
The news also says
Yuanfei Group's stock
is dropping like crazy.
Could it be Shen Jiahe
manipulating things behind the scenes?
No way.
Why not?
He threatened you just yesterday.
Yuanfei Group is already
in the palm of his hand.
He knows exactly
where the shareholders stand.
He's aware I can't touch him.
So announcing the divorce now
doesn't benefit him at all.
Then...
who else could it be?
Not many people even knew
you two split up.
Could it be Chi Ye?
Chi Ye's not that kind of person.
But his brother, Chi Hao...
maybe.
[Xu Nuo]
Nuo...
[Add friend to message]
Maybe from the start,
we were doomed to fail.
[Nuo]
[Maybe from the start,]
[we were doomed to fail.]
[Yuanfei Harbour City]
Give me a few minutes.
No time.
About the divorce rumors
going around...
What happened?
Why?
They got divorced?
♪I love you, love you, love you♪
♪So deep that I forget who I am♪
♪I miss you, miss you, miss you♪