(Dream Garden)
(This story is purely fictitious. Any similarity is purely coincidental. Hypnosis must be performed under the guidance of a professional. Please do not imitate.)
In the modern day commercial market,
online sales platforms of different kinds have already become a Red Ocean market.
It is within this Red Ocean, that our team,
our company has discovered a new territory.
- It is from within the global–  - Alright, alright.
Problems regarding quality has arisen on your platform.
We will reconsider this cooperation project.
(Zheyan Corporation)
We'll talk another time, okay? We'll talk another time.
Okay, okay.
- Secretary Zhang. Has the manager seen it?  - Mr. Sun.
Our manager has read your project plan.
That's great. This project of ours about selling medical equipment online,
if the manager is interested, I've brought along a whole bunch of information
about the plan of our app development.
If time allows, I can give him a demonstration.
There's no need.
If there are any updates, we will notify you immediately.
That will be all for today, okay?
(Funding Plan)
- Hello, who is this?  - Is this Mr. Sun Dongsun?
I am.
I'm calling from Shaolin's Psychological Counseling Centre. My name is Zuo Yan.
- Are you satisfied with the recent session you had with Dr. Xiao Xiao?  - Extremely.
That's great, thank you.
It's like this, from next week onwards, Dr. Lin
has an empty slot in his schedule.
I wanted to ask if you wanted to
have your session be transferred to Dr. Lin Shen?
I don't need to. Although I look up to Dr. Lin Shen's expertise,
Dr. Xiao is not bad, she's quite good.
I feel much better after a few session with her.
Please keep the appointment with Dr. Xiao for me.
Mr. Sun! Please stop there.
(Xiao Xiao  Pschologist Intern)
Dr. Xiao.
There's something that I wanted to discuss with you.
Go ahead.
Your customer service department called me.
They said that your senior psychologist, Lin Shen, has some free time.
I think my current situation is a bit complicated.
How about you transfer my sessions over to him?
(Episode 12)
(Shaolin's Psychological Counseling Center)
(Lin Shen  Psychologist)
Imagine this, you're standing alone in the dorm room.
There's nobody inside.
You can see all of the furnishings in the dorm.
What can you hear?
I can hear the sound of water dripping from the tap.
Very good. You can hear the dripping of water.
Every time you hear a drip,
you will feel...more relaxed.
What can you see?
Student, please let us through.
Hello, Teacher. My name is Li Yixin.
I'm here to be an assistant for Dr. Lin Shen in Sun Xiaoxue's place.
Li Yixin, right? Xiaoxue has already told me.
Here are the student information for Xiaoxue's class.
Thank you, Teacher.
(Psychology Practical Class Student Information  Xiao Xiao)
Okay. I'm heading off, Teacher.
Dr. Lin is very strict. You should be more attentive.
Don't worry.
Li Yixin!
Li Yixin, how could you be so shameless?! Li Yixin!
Casually seducing someone else's boyfriend!
Do you think anyone will fall in love with this fake face of yours?!
I'm telling you, you're seriously shameless!
Do you hear me?! You're shameless, Li Yixin!
I didn't seduce your boyfriend.
- You're still saying that you didn't?!  - You've misunderstand, I didn't seduce your boyfriend.
Dr. Lin, your hypnosis really does have some effect.
I feel like my whole body is relaxed,
as if I've just had some deep sleep.
But you suddenly woke up,
you must have seen or heard something during the hypnosis.
The things you have seen and the sounds you heard,
they all have meaning. They might be the real reason for your insomnia.
I recommend you going to a psychologist whom you have a pure counseling relationship with.
Dr. Lin, time is up.
I should go back to schoo, I still have class in the afternoon.
I'm leaving first.
Xiao Xiao.
Why are you here?
You thought that your disguise was seamless,
that you hid from the surveillance cameras in the lift and corridor.
But you didn't know that my neighbor's front door had surveillance cameras too.
(Xiaotong) I have a video of you fighting with Li Yixin that day.
(Sun Rui)  Thank you. I'll buy you lunch tomorrow.
What does it have to do with you? Dissolve those ten injections of hyaluronic acid in your face first!
You–!
The teachers at school found razor blades on Sun Rui's desk.
She was immediately suspended and went home.
Right now, everyone in the dorms believe that
I was the cause of this whole situation.
Teacher Lin, I...
Soon, I'm going to be pressured; pressured so much that I can't catch my breath.
Right now, I truly feel
suffocated.
It's exactly the same. So this razor blade is yours too? Come to the Student Affairs division.
- Dorm Manager, This...  - Let's go.
Don't loiter around.
Quit looking. Go on. Go about your business.
Xiao Xiao, I know I did wrong. Forgive me, okay?
- I really know I did wrong.  - Yizin, go to the school to confess your mistake.
Sun Rui has already been punished for that video that was issued without any context.
You need to take your responsibility of your behaviour.
Maybe because you've lacked attention, lacked love that you've felt lonely
and used this kind of vicious method to get others to pay attention to you.
But you should not lie, cheat and hurt people.
The more you do that kind of thing, the more you won't gain other people's trust.
And you won't get the friendship and affection that you want.
I came to see you today about another situation.
I want a chin similar to hers.
In order to reach an objective, there are those who will choose to change themselves; disguise themselves;
even go so far as to imitate or impersonate someone else.
Xiao Xiao.
You're my only friend in the school.
To me, you're the most extraordinary person.
But in the end, what this brings you and others along with you,
is only pain and suffering.
To get the approval we want from others, we can only be our true selves.
We want to win true friendship and affection.
We can only get that with sincerity towards another person.
(Love is mutual sincerity.)
Hey, good morning.
- Good morning. - Good morning.  - What's going on?
You're all together here so early.
We just here discussing going to Boss Shao's house after work to have hotpot.
Hey, Teacher Lin, will you go?
I am not joining.
Are you coming?
I have something tonight, I am not going then.
Don't be like that, Xiao Xiao. Without you, it won't be lively.
You both are not coming.
it won't be lively; we might as well cancel it.
- Do something another day. You have to clean up afterwards anyway. - Don't, don't.
Cleaning up is no trouble.
I'm booking a cleaner right now. You book them and they come.
Hey, Xiao Xiao.
What date have you made for this evening so you can't come?
How do I have dating, I
I have a little puppy, I need to look after it.
Little puppy.
Male or female?
You should have asked to whom it belongs to
Wow, you are buying so much meat
Let's go over there and look
What do you want to eat?
I think this crab looks good.
Miss, Miss, come look at this. This Zhibai hair curler is great.
The low temperature model doesn't damage hairstyles.
It has 2 curling styles, right?
- Okay, then. Give me a new one.  - Okay.
Thank you.
Ms. Zhou Yun. Ms. Zhou Yun.
Mr. Lin Shen. Mr. Lin Shen.
Your granny is waiting for you at the information desk.
Mr. Lin Shen, your granny is waiting for you at the information desk.
Please come to the information desk.
- Lin Shen? It couldn't be Teacher Lin, could it?  -  Mr. Lin Shen.
Your granny is waiting for you at the information desk.  - No way. How could there be such a coincidence?
Teacher Lin, you're at the supermarket too?
You came on your own to buy groceries.
We are going to the hot pot restaurant, are you coming to join?
If you do, leave me a text.
Your granny is here.
Come on, get in.
- What are you doing?  - Excuse me, can we use your office? It's an emergency.
- I'll get an invoice.  - Okay.
That Teacher Lin didn't return my text.
Wait for me at the exit. I'll give him a call.
Please get me an invoice.
They're all here too.
- Hello.  - Hello.
Was there a granny just here looking for someone?
Yes.
Did she find him?
She has already gone.
She has gone.Yes.
That is fine, thanks.
No problem. Is there something else I can help you with?
There's nothing else you can help me with.
Then, I wish you happy shopping.
I am leaving.
The invoice?
He's gone.
He knew.
What could we do?
Keep it, I will handle it.
Alright.
- It's all bagged up.  - Done.
Let's go.
Teacher Lin, it really is you.
It really is you, Teacher Lin.
I just heard from the announcement, granny is looking for you, she found you?
She is back for resting.
So sorry.
Then, will you come eat hotpot with us tonight?
Right. come have hotpot with us.
Come eat hotpot together.
He has to go to spend time with his elders.
That's true.
Why don't I ask her for advice?
I have her Weixin account number.
Hey, Granny, we've commandeered Lin Shen.
Uh, don't be mad.
Cheers.
- Thank you, Boss Shao.  - Thanks for treating us, Boss Shao.
Thanks for coming to my home.
Come more often in future.
Has something come up, Teacher Lin?
Nothing much.  - Maybe Granny sent some news.
News? She can't even use a cell phone. Send news?
Granny hasn't eaten yet, should we go to get her here to have a meal together?
No need, she has eaten at home already.
I go to washroom.
Washroom? Sit down.
Grab some duck. It's fun with 5 people. It's no fun with 4.
♫  Many stars are twinkling in the sky  ♫
♫  Who's tossing and turning late in the night?  ♫
♫  At that moment, fountains, fireworks, and shadows  ♫  - You keep going. I really need to use the bathroom.
Do you want to run?
What do you want?
Your granny is here.
I'm the cleaner from 58 Home.
Auntie, please come in.
Okay.
Come on in.
What's the matter between you two?
Which two?
Do you really thought that I wouldn't know who was the person behind the broadcast room door
in the supermarket?
I'm telling you, Lin Shen. As your partner,
as Xiao Xiao's boss, I have the right to know about the office romance.
It's not what you think.
It's not what I think?
Then tell me where you are now?
We live together.
We are very patient, you guys are living together?
I'm begging you, please let me go.
You just move in together, and she is setting a certain time for you to return?
Thank you! Please forgive me.
Counselor Lin is taking off?
It's pretty late,
he has to turn his granny in bed.
The above is Miss Li violated the riles. The truth has been verified and it is against the school rules.
Her act has brought negative effect on regular school education.
In order to reinforce straight school guidelines based on Education from itself.
According to Shen Jiang University school rules,
after taking careful consideration, she will remain at the university under observation as the punishment.
♫  I know you want to go ♫
♫  I know you want me gone  ♫
That's right. ♫ But I just want you to stay ♫
I haven't picked up two boxes of masks in the fridge.♫  I'm try to say  ♫
♫  Cause love is blind ♫
Also, my vanity bag in the bathroom.
♫  My heart will always stay No matter what you say oh my ♫
What's the matter?♫ I know you want to go
Can you not go?
♫  I know you want me gone ♫
The weather forecast said it will rain tonight, why don't you leave another day?♫  I know you want you to say ♫
♫  I'm try to say ♫
Perhaps you in another person's eyes,
is polite and distanced. She is someone who can only seen from afar.
But for me, you are the loveliest person in the world.
Every look and every smile, it lingers in my heart for a long time.
Perhaps you like someone tender, mature and humorous.
But in front of you, I want to be an overbearing monster.
Rely on you and tell you you are the only one I like.
Anyways, self sentimental is my forte.
What is this, Sun Kele? You are such a douchebag. Overbearing Monster?
Hello. I couldn't hear you. I'm still here.
Counselor Lin is here.
You are on the phone?
Sun Kele wants to confess to Sister Yan.
This is his confession statement.
Look at this? It won't work.
Okay, you two carry on. I'm not going to interrupt you.
Don't be! Counselor Lin! Counselor Lin!
Can you help me out here?
If you haven't shown any nice gestures to Zuo Yan and rush to confess,
she will only find it awkward.
No matter how beautiful your statement is, she be embarrassed.
I agree. Talking about how to create fondness to your love interest,
this is the biggest question in love psychology.
You need to do something to move her.
Then, as the psychology specialists, can you tell me what to do.
Let me explain it with neuroscience, our brain generates the feeling of love.
When people encounter love, their brain will generate this chemical substance
that stimulate the happiness area.
It will create the illusion of love.
This chemical can release through psychology hints to the opposite person.
It's the darkness effect, cross bridge effect, including intermittent reinforcement
can also stimulate the love adrenaline.
But Sister Yan studied psychology and she was a top student.
She can easily tell by the small tricks.
That's why I suggest you to go with the flow.
Am I right?
Let's go get a coffee.
Let's me go with you.
Hello? No sound again? Hello? I'm still listening. Hello?
First, you need to create opportunities.
Pop up in front of her under different scenarios.
When she sees you more, she will know you more.
This one is good.
In psychology, this is called Frequency effect.
When she sees you more often, the chance of her liking you will be increased.
- However, you need to come up with a good First Impression Effect. - First Impression Effect?
That's her first impression toward you.
People typically determined their like and dislike based on their first impression.
That's it. I don't think I have any advantage.
You have to keep sending Sister Yan your love signals.
When you received those signals, it will be easier for her to like you.
How to send her signals?
Talk to her with the topics she is interested in.
Give her the feeling of love. Create this habits and sense of security.
Also the affection of missing each other.
People can in fact easier to fall in love to the person they like.
This is a Love Compensation Effect. But the actual case study need actual analysis.
If you use hints and ways to cater her interests,
and create this love illusion.
In fact, you are doing it to cater her but not the real you.
When the real you show up in front of her,
she might no longer interested in you.
If that's the case, love will become an illusion and then an imagination.
Just like bubbles. When you touch it, it bursts.
Counselor Lin, can you explain to me in plain language?
It means don't put up an act for too long, it will reveal your true intension.
Why don't we set up one or two incidents,
and let Sister Yan realized that you might leave her and stimulate her.
In this case, she will realize
that she has been deeply in love with Sun Kele.
G.K. Chesterton has said before, the fastest way to fall for anything
is let the person realized that they might lose them.
To my understanding on Zuo Yan, if you did that,
she might give up on you right away.
Let's set up couple of scenarios,
and let Sister Yan realized that Sun Kele is also very popular.
But you need to show your heart can only accommodate Zuo Yan.
What Xiao Xiao said is the Veblen Effect. It means when the price
of a product costs higher, the demand for it will be higher.
Let me set an example, just like property prices.
If the price of the property drops, people will hold on and wait.
When the property price increased, people will start grabbing it.
But Sun Kele, do you think you are the property price in the eye of Zuo Yan?
What do you mean? You mean Sun Kele is no chance on Sister Yan?
In the contrast, Zuo Yan might have studied psychology,
but she can still fall into these
psychology traps.
Even you, so call Love Expert.
How can I be trapped?
When people interact, our brain uses seven to sixteen areas.
When they are in love, only four to five areas are more active.
Meaning,
when people is in a relationship,
their thinking ability is worsen compare to other situations.
It will let people sunken into unconsciousness
similar to hypnotization.
Based on this theory, you can find a private location
where people won't find it alarming.
For example, while you are waiting for a coffee. Give it a try.
Eye look at each other. Pay attention, you need to control the timing.
You need to stay two seconds longer than you typically do.
You only need two additional seconds.
More than two seconds, the person might ask you
"What's wrong? Do I have something on my face?".
When you ask her in her conscious status, then you can no longer lure her into the unconscious stage.
However, if that person doesn't ask,
meaning she might like you as well.
It might not be the case. What if that person has a stern mind?
Xiao, give this a taste.
It's a new product I discovered, it's very good.
Come.
What happened to you two?
Something wrong between you and Counselor Lin.
There is nothing wrong.
Are you guys in a fight?
Tell me about it.
They must have fought.
A few days ago, you looked like you were about to move into his house.
You said you were moving the moment I came back.
You even told me that you were moving in the morning and didn't want to waste one moment.
Xiao.
Actually, Dr. Lin isn't the kind of guy to please girls with sweet words.
But, it's always this type of guys
- who are the most reliable and practical.  - Who said he's not good with words?
I've noted that. And then?
Hello?
What were we talking about just now?
He had the mind to ask Sun Kele what they were talking about just now.
Then? Then?
Then...
Then, there's no "then".
- No way.  - It's true!
Some guys are more passive and like girls to be more assertive.
I'm already assertive enough. Am I supposed to confess to him?
In the push-and-pull war of love, confession
is the most important key point. Whoever says it first loses.
I've read that article too.
This is how I teach my fans too.
Could it be that my kissing technique is terrible?
- Let me be the one to cook.  - Really?
But you need to wash the dishes.
Deal.
Eat your food.
♫  It's all related to you  ♫
♫  It's all hidden inside the wind  ♫
♫  It's an unspoken secret  ♫
♫  Some things that happened in the past is like a city  ♫
♫  Surrounding us are  ♫
♫  thorns that won't disappear  ♫
♫  Some feelings are like a city  ♫
♫  I am so paranoid, but I'm missing a key  ♫
(Confession)
♫  You are the jacket that blocks the wind  ♫
♫  Which warms my homeless and desperate plight.  ♫
♫  The memories that don't fade  ♫
♫  is always clear  ♫
♫  Not in the eyes, at the bottom of the heart  ♫
(Dream Garden by Luo Luo Jiang)
(Dream Garden)
What would you like?
- I want your heart.  - My heart?
- Thank you. - Thank you.
When are you releasing your next new book?
- I'm still preparing it. Once I'm done, I'll let you all know. - Okay.
That's really good. Okay, that's fine.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Luo Luo Jiang, I really like you. Can we take a photo together?
I've been following you since your first manhua released online three years ago.
Can you give me a chance?
No.
- No!  - No, we want one too!
We want a picture too!
Are you done taking photos?
I'm done.
Quickly leave.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Give me an autograph too.
I want a designated autograph. I am a cultured fan.
You still haven't returned my glasses yet.
- I–  - I'll let you keep it as a souvenir.
Okay.
Looks nice. Thank you.
(Shaolin's Psychological Counseling Center)
(Xiao Xiao  Psychologist Intern)
Imagine this, you're currently on a spacious grassland.
You're feeling the light wind.
You feel like your body is becoming lighter and lighter.
Mr. Sun.
Try to remove yourself from the tight space.
Imagine yourself being back in a spacious area.
Mr. Sun, because there were problems with your most recent batch of medical equipment,
this project of yours didn't pass our risk assessment.
Why did you borrow so much money?
Now the lender is knocking at our door.
Do you think I want it to be like this? I can sit and wait around after all.
As a man, I need to make a gamble!
But, I'm really sorry, Mr. Sun.
You had a physical store before.
Your medical machines have problems.
We used to sell medical machines.
The concept of an online medical app caught in a recall turmoil
- did not pass our risk assessment.  - Stop bothering me!
How do you feel, Mr. Sun? Are you still feeling okay?
Did I wake up prematurely?
I don't know what happened to me today.
It was quite successful the previous few times.
Today...why can't I relax?
Actually, I just saw that part of you were already relaxed,
yet the other part of you were still stiff and nervous.
Did something happen recently that made you stressed?
Dr. Xiao.
You...are you feeling unwell?
No, no.
Dr. Xiao, there is something that I wanted to discuss with you.
Go ahead.
Your customer service department called me.
They said that your senior psychologist, Lin Shen, has some free time.
I think my current situation is a bit complicated.
How about you transfer my sessions over to him?
Mr. Sun, your situation is not as serious as you think.
How about we stop here today? I'll inquire about your situation with Dr. Lin later
to see if you should continue with the current session plan
or to transfer you over, okay?
I'll call you to notify you, if you would like.
Okay.
We'll end it here today.
Xiao Xiao moved from your house?
I saw you two going around like a couple just a while ago.
You went to work together and went home together. Your relationship fell apart in just a short time?
No.
- "No" to the relationship or "no" to it falling apart?  - The former.
No way. I saw you two in the tea room.
I didn't mean to watch on purpose, I was passing by.
I didn't expect you
to only take advantage of the situation without taking responsibilities.
- Do I look like someone like that?  - Let me have a look to see if you are.
You do.
- What? - It's not that I'm not taking responsibility.
I just haven't thought about how to confess.
You've already kissed her. How else do you want to confess?
She has already said on her public account.
To a girl, a ceremonial confession is very important.
It means that the other person places a lot of importance on this relationship.
Friendly advice from Xiao Bei Bei:
Boys, you mustn't think that just a hug or a kiss means that you're now dating the girl.
Girls needs a ceremonious feeling.
Ceremonious represents the importance you place on the beginning of a relationship.
There's logic in her words.
- Have a good think then.  - Do you have any advice?
Advice...I don't have any.
But, I have create opportunities for you.
Didn't Yan Luo just come back from a signing tour?
Yeah. She helped Xiao Xiao with moving house last week.
When I invited Xiao Xiao to dinner last time, she didn't come. This time,
we will invite the both of them and no one else, so it's just the four of us.
We'll say that it's for celebrating the sellout of Yan Luo's "Dream Garden".
Are you really trying to create opportunities for me?
I am.
Why do I feel like you're not the more I listen?
Tell me honestly.
One shouldn't verbally reveal it even if they have seen through it.
Give it to me.
If your stomach is unwell, don't drink cold water.
I have no appetite.
You need to take some food even no appetite, it is late for meal already.
When did you start having stomachae?
I pulled a few allnighters recently because of Sundong's situation.
I didn't eat breakfast in the morning either.
Is his case that complicated?
Tell me the general situation.
This Mr. Sun works as a medical agent.
He used to be Lejian's national agent.
- Lejian? - Yeah.
Even though he started off with nothing from that,
because a recent batch of medical machines had problems,
on top of the recent bad reputation of Lejian,
nobody is willing to invest in him.
Anybody would feel difficult in this situation.
His condition was improving after a few sessions,
but I don't know what happened lately,
his condition has become worse again. He even displayed behaviours of self-harm today.
I really want to help him.
But, I haven't thought of a better idea.
After all, I've only just started as a psychology intern.
You've already finished your clinical psychology class.
His condition has also previously improved,
which means that you're doing exceptionally.
I'm thinking, could he have encountered something unexpected lately?
How about this,
you and your supervisor should investigate his case again.
But, this visitor of mine thinks that I don't have enough experience.
He said he wanted to be transferred to you today.
- Really?  - Yeah.
Let's not talk about this, let's talk about something lighter.
Boss Shao is inviting us to dinner tomorrow night, let's invite Yan Luo too.
- Invite Luo Luo? - You don't know this,
but Shao Ning is now Yan Luo's...
biggest fan.
Alright. I didn't go to dinner when the three of you went last time.
When she came back, Xiao Rui said Boss Shao's house had many bottles of good wine.
I'll be the decider of that this time.
Master.
Thank you.
No. You can't drink.
Why?
Your stomach hasn't gotten better yet, listen to me.
Why should I listen to you?
Because I am your–
Your master.
It's great to be having this gathering today.
It's to celebrate the publishing of Yan Luo's "Dream Garden".
Let's hope it can sell better and better in the future.
Let's cheers to this wine.
- Cheers!  - Cheers.  - Cheers.
Xiao Xiao, you can't drink. Hey–!
The last glass. We shouldn't waste wine.
Enough, enough. I brought the thing you like to drink.
Don't leave any wine.
- Is your stomach okay?  - I'm fine.
(Saturday menu:)
(Saturday menu:  Pasta, burger)
I'll clean these things up.
The two of you, sit. Keep talking.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'll clean up with you too.
- Thank you. - Me too.  - I'll clean up too.
No, no. The two of you don't need to.
Xiao Xiao's stomach isn't well. If you need to, the two of you can go home first.
I'll clean up with Yan Luo.
We don't have any plans. I'll clean up with you.
You really don't need to.
- You really don't need to. Who asks their guests to clean up? - Okay.
Then, you clean up with Yan Luo.
Let's go.
- We're leaving.  - We'll take our leave then, Boss Shao.
Bye bye.
- Drink more warm water since your stomach is unwell.  - Got it!
- Where are they? - They have plans, they left first.
- I'll clean up with you.  - No, no. Just let me clean up.
Luo Luo, you're a guest in my home.
You really don't need to tidy up, just let me do it.
I came to your home because you wanted to celebrate with me.
You even made a whole table of tasty dishes.
In the end, you even washed the dishes. How unsuitable of me.
These are things I should do.
And Xiao Xiao too,
they left without telling me.
Mr. Shao.
Are you creating opportunities for them to be alone?
Yeah.
Let me do it.
- I'm sorry, Yan Luo.  - Let me clean up.
I'll do it, I'll do it. No, no, I'll do it. Don't hurt your hands.
- I should do it.  - I should do it, really.
Mr. Shao, I'm sorry.
It's getting late, I'm heading home.
Luo Luo.
Young man, buy a bouquet.
Buy a bouquet.
Young man, your friend is quite pretty. Buy her a bouquet.
There's no need, Auntie. Thank you.
Buy one, young lady. It's a token from your boyfriend, take it.
Auntie, you've misunderstood. I'm not his girlfriend.
Right, Auntie. She's not my girlfriend.
- Auntie, I'm going to buy all of these. How much are they?  - You, you...
She's not my girlfriend now, it doesn't mean she won't be in the future.
I'll scan your code. How much are they?
I'll give you a discount since you're buying all of them. It's ¥105.
Okay, ¥105.
I've finished scanning. Thank you.
Come in.
Boss Shao.
Dr. Lin, this is your schedule for next week.
Okay, thank you.
Let's eat lunch together later.
I'm sorry, I have plans at midday.
I'm sorry, I was asking Shao Ning.
I'm sorry, I have paid leave in the afternoon.
If there's anything you need, ask Sister Yan. Don't ask me.
What a blatant office romance.
It's even filled with tension. I want to fire the both of you.
What office romance? Let's continue.
You talk first. What did you do to her last night?
What do you mean?
Xiao Xiao never wears rings.
Today, not only did she wear a ring, she has one on each finger.
She is announcing that she is single. What do you think?
We do not discuss private matters in the office. Let's continue.
But mine is private matter too.
Okay, okay. I won't scatter salt on your wound.
Let's get back on track.
I'm now suspecting that Yan Luo has attachment issues.
Mr. Shao, I'm sorry.
It's getting late, I'm heading home.
I probably need you and Xiao Xiao's help.
Yan Luo!
Yan Luo.
Stop hiding from me, Yan Luo.
Yan Luo. Don't hide from me, Yan Luo.
Luo Luo, give me another chance. Luo Luo. Yan Luo.
Yan Luo. Yan Luo, don't hide from me anymore, okay?
Luo Luo. Where are you going? Don't hide from me anymore, okay?
Yan Luo. Stop hiding from me, Yan Luo. Yan Luo!
Don't hide from me anymore, okay? Yan Luo!
Yan Luo! Yan Luo!
Where are you going? Yan Luo, I'm begging you. Okay? Yan Luo.
- Yan Luo!  - Leave! Stop following me!
Brother...
Who?
Coming, coming!
Who is it?
- Why are you here?  - Didn't we agree to get lunch together?
You don't pick up my call nor reply my text.
I come to see what happens.
I am sorry, I just overslept.
I was rushing for the deadline last night.
I slept until just now.
Wait for me, I just get changed and can go.
No problem. Let me do it.
Didn't you cut out reliance on sleeping pills after breaking up with Wang Su?
When did you start again?
It's nothing.
Yan Luo, I'd be even more worried about you if you don't tell me.
I'm so tired.
What's wrong?
Every time I want to start a new relationship,
or if I have any new ideas,
he will definitely appear in my dreams.
In the dream, no matter where I go,
wherever I escape to, he'll always find me.
He doesn't want me to start over again.
Luo Luo,
I think I don't deserve love.
Nonsense! You're so talented.
I know Wang Su hurt you really badly.
But it doesn't mean that all the men in the world are like that.
We're fine.
Don't go into self denial.
Don't think too hard.
We're fine.
It'll get better.
Come in.
- Boss Shao.  - Yes.
I thought you were adjusting your schedule? How comes you're here?
Boss Shao, I remember you received an attachment injury case before.
Could you tell me more about it?
Why are you suddenly interested in attachment injury?
I have a potential patient who has been struggling with this.
You're talking about Yan Luo, right?
How do you know?
I can interpret.
Yan Luo condition hasn't been great recently.
It might be because she has the intention to start a new relationship.
That's why she's been experiencing frequent nightmares.
She dreams that Wang Su wants to hurt her.
To stop her from starting her new life.
These symptoms you mention are quite present.
Boss Shao, since you have so much experience, how about you take it on?
I can't help you with this.
Why?
You should know that in this line of work there is a rule.
A consultant cannot have any feelings
- with the consultee.  - Yes.
What does this have to do with Yan Luo?
Unless you want to break off the relationship between the two of us–
No need. No need. Just giving me some tips will be fine.
Oh right, I think you can watch a movie called,
'The Heart is a Lonely Hunter'. That should help with Yan Luo's case.
The main characters in the movie have fearful avoidant attachment and dismissive avoidant attachment respectively.
The psychologist's trauma therapy is strongly rejected by the main character's main consciousness.
The obstacles that come from the subconsciousness shields consciousness
from directly facing the hurt and emotional stress.
Okay, I won't give you any more spoilers. You should watch it yourself.
- Two tickets?  - Go with Lin Shen.
We'll also need everyone's strength after that.
This is about Yan Luo.
I will definitely go.
(Tengqing Road Station)
(Teng Yuan Movie City)  - It should be this place.
- Hello.  - Hello, is this Mr. Lin?
This is from Jia Ren Nursing Home.
Why isn't he picking up?
Hello?
The situation with the nursing home is done.
It is going according to plan.
I will leave to rest to you.
Okay. Got it!
Be careful.
Don't take any rash actions before the next move.
Wait for my call.
I'll be responsible for Xiao Xiao's side. Don't interfere.
Okay.
She's an important part of our plan.
Don't fall too deep and ruin the bigger picture.
Otherwise, I won't hold back.
He didn't even turn up. How can I fulfill my dream?
It's all rigged, how could there be plane tickets to Bali?
Don't torture it any more. If you have any wish, I'll make it come true.
Brother Qi?
♫  The more passersby there are in my life  ♫
♫  Tthe more inexplicable I feel lonely  ♫
♫  The cool eye of a bystander hides in secret watching  ♫
♫  The truth is hard to comprehend  ♫
♫  It's very easy to see through someone's secrets  ♫
♫  And at the same time, I'm used to my feelings being passive  ♫
♫  In this maze of chaos,  ♫
♫  My self-hypnotism comes around full circle  ♫
♫  There are many blocked paths in the direction I want to find  ♫
♫  With many hindrances, I feel at a loss  ♫
♫  I'm afraid of losing again what I cherished most  ♫
♫  It turns out that I'm still waiting for my true love  with whom I can share everything  ♫
♫  I'll accept my fate and unpredictable future  ♫
♫  Until I can look deep in my heart  ♫
♫  If someday I find love, will it be heart-felt and fluttering?  ♫
♫  I'll accept the reality of life being a long, long journey  ♫
♫  Through all the ups and downs, I've experienced  and seen many things  ♫
♫  Will I have the courage to overcome the  obsession in my heart?  ♫
♫  So that I can understand that simplicity is  the warmest feeling  ♫
♫  In this maze of chaos  ♫
♫  My self-hypnotism comes around full circle  ♫
♫  There are many blocked paths in the direction I want to find  ♫
♫  With many hindrances, I feel at a loss  ♫
♫  I'm afraid of losing again what I cherished most  ♫
♫  It turns out that I'm still waiting for my true love  with whom I can share everything  ♫
♫  I'll accept my fate and unpredictable future  ♫
♫  until I can look deep in my heart  ♫
♫  If someday I find love, will it be heart-felt and fluttering?  ♫
♫  I'll accept the reality of life being a long, long journey  ♫
♫  Through all the ups and downs, I've experienced  and seen many things  ♫
♫  Will I have the courage to overcome the  obsession in my heart?  ♫
♫  So that I can understand that simplicity  is the warmest feeling  ♫
♫  In this maze of chaos  ♫
♫  My self-hypnotism comes around full circle  ♫
♫  There are many blocked paths in the direction I want to find  ♫
♫  With many hindrances, I feel at a loss  ♫
♫  I'm afraid of losing again what I cherished most  ♫
♫  It turns out my true love is within my grasp  ♫
♫  I'll accept my fate and unpredictable future  ♫
♫  until I can look deep in my heart  ♫
♫  If someday I find love, will it be heart-felt and fluttering?  ♫
♫  I'll accept the reality of life being a long, long journey  ♫"
♫  Through all the ups and downs,  I've experienced and seen many things  ♫
♫  Will I have the courage to overcome the  obsession in my heart?  ♫
♫  So I'll understand that simplicity is not out of the ordinary  ♫
♫  How can I live life without any regrets?  ♫
♫  May I bravely confess with my sincere heart?  ♫
♫  Then naturally, there must be an answer  ♫