=The Prisoner of Love=
=Episode 4=
I'll make sure you live a luxury life!
Who allowed you to lay hands
on my woman?
Uncle,
that is out of line.
We cannot explain this to Chu.
If Chu wants to start something,
tell them to come
to the General's Mansion.
No one can touch
what's mine.
Not even if it is just an ant.
Uncle, you intrigue me.
Move again and I won't hesitate to add
another broken bone to your tally.
Why the pretense of kindness?
Dare you say
you didn't arrange the show today?
Still so presumptuous.
Who can match you
when it comes to that?
And on top of that,
you've got a persecution complex.
You think everyone's out to get you.
Halt right there.
(The Xiao family's guard)
What do you think you're doing?
How dare you snoop
around the Xiao Mansion?
You look like a spy up to no good.
If you're set on accusing someone,
you'll never be short of excuses.
Then, I'll make sure you confess.
You're quite tough.
Let's see how many whips you can take!
Stop!
Miss Xiao.
All of you, stand down.
I will interrogate him myself.
Yes, Miss Xiao. Let's go.
Chen Fengxue.
It's you again.
Didn't expect you
to be tough
and tight-lipped.
I like that about you.
Our families have never gotten along.
I am hardly worthy of your affection.
I don't like
things I like being imperfect.
Let's go.
Yes.
(Why doesn't he remember)
(how I once treated him?)
You keep staring at me.
Are you trying to seduce me?
I wouldn't mind
satisfying you.
You're right.
I am trying to seduce you.
But are you even up for it?
Don't touch me
with that filthy hand
that Chu's grubby envoy has touched.
Disgusting.
Men.
Present.
Lock Xiao Ningyun in the woodshed
for three days
and give her no food.
Give her all of the most
degrading chores in the mansion.
Yes, sir.
Sir, I heard you actually locked her
in the woodshed and made her a slave.
You... You always let your anger
get the best of you.
You really shouldn't...
If you break the medicine mule
we worked so hard to find,
it'll be your life on the line.
There's no beast that can't be tamed.
If there is,
it just means
you weren't ruthless enough.
I worry you're being too ruthless.
You could lose
everything
in the process.
If my mule dies,
I die.
You should worry about your own life.
Talking to someone
as cold-hearted as you
is pointless.
Forget it.
As long as she's still alive,
I can save her.
Sir, they've taken the bait.
Miss Xiao.
(Xu Yunze, the Xiao family's guard)
Why are you here?
I received Zhao Yan's report
and found out you were being held
as a slave in the General's Mansion.
It's nothing too bad.
But what about you and Zijin?
How is he?
Mr. Xiao has been rescued.
I'll get you out of here tonight.
Who's there?
Come on!
Madam Liu.
You wretch!
How dare you have an affair!
So desperate?
Then I'll let you have your fill of men!
That might not be a good idea.
What's wrong with it?
General Chen is already tired of her.
She's nothing
but a lowly servant now!
I see.
Then I won't hold back.
Don't come any closer...
Stay away!
Don't come near me!
Go away!
What's going on?
You were lucky I was there.
Listen,
General Chen yields to softness,
not force.
If you keep resisting,
next time you won't be so lucky
for me to save you.
You don't know him.
If he wanted to torment me,
he wouldn't need me to provoke him.
You still don't see it.
He's already been good to you.
There, all fixed.
He allowed you
to heal my hand?
Of course.
How can I draw blood otherwise?
Are you trying to kill me?
You're overthinking it.
I just wanted
to tuck you in.
Looks like dislocating your arm that day
didn't teach you a lesson.
Is my blood
not enough for you?
Of course not.
Why?
Why can't I still stand up?
Why? Why?
Are you mocking me?
Get out!
Get lost
before I kill you!
(I will leave.)
(Far, far away.)
(And we will never meet again.)
Put this on.
We're leaving.
Let's go.
Miss Xiao.
Where do you think you're going?