=The Antidote to Love=
=Episode 15=
I didn't expect you to come.
Have you found Zhe's body?
Zhe's body is at the Office.
The Chief Diviner did all that.
You...
What have you found out?
I've gotten back
the memory of your clan's tragedy.
(How should I tell him)
(that Zhao Zhe caused all of this?)
Actually...
It was me.
I led the attack on the Moon Clan
on the wedding day.
Since you say so,
prove it.
On the wedding day,
the entire Moon Clan
was celebrating the Saintess's marriage.
I led the North Army's elite inside.
That day,
the place was decked in flowers.
It was very lively.
When they saw me,
the Moon Clan welcomed me warmly.
Right then, I gave my order
to kill everyone there.
Every single member of the Moon Clan
would follow the wedding
into the afterlife.
I hadn't even dismounted
before I struck someone down
with my sword.
Ms. Li didn't even have time to cry out
before she got slain.
Blood splattered
across the wedding scene.
It stained everything crimson.
Blood dripped from the tip of my sword,
leaving long streaks on the ground.
The screams of terror...
The frantic rush to escape...
You can't imagine how thrilling it was.
Then there was Wang
who tried to ambush me from behind.
But he was no match for me.
With one swing,
I parted his head from his body.
Blood surged in a crimson wave.
One by one, they all fell before me.
Enough.
Stop it.
Why did you do all this?
Because the blood of Moon Clan women
cures all illnesses.
Though you saved me in the Moon Valley,
I came with the task
of the massacre of the clan.
This was all my plan from the start.
Shut up.
This was all your plan, huh?
Very well.
Then I want you
to kneel before the Sacred Pool
and repent.
I will kill you myself.
Your blood will be offered
to honor every soul lost
from the Moon Clan.
Let's eat.
How nice.
Your Highness, you're back.
I've been looking for you
since yesterday.
I found the true survivor
of the North Army.
Come on.
Sit down.
Your Highness.
Since you lost your memory,
you haven't joined us for a drink.
Is there something to celebrate?
It's been a while since we've talked.
Tonight,
let's drink till dawn.
- Cheers.
- Sure.
Let's drink till dawn.
- Cheers.
- Come on.
I've seen each of you grow
with my own eyes.
Zhen Hu.
I remember you used to be timid.
Now you've become a true leader.
- Good.
- Not really.
It's all thanks
to your helpful guidance.
- Xiu Feng.
- Yes.
Do you recall this scar?
It happened when you slipped up.
I took a blow for you.
So, on the battlefield,
never let your guard down.
Your Highness, with you here,
when danger comes,
you'll always shield us first.
Isn't that right, everyone?
Yes.
What if one day I'm gone?
Your Highness.
Is something troubling you?
It's nothing, just a jest.
Wushuang.
You're the only female general
in the North Army.
If not for me,
you wouldn't have joined in two years.
(Recruitment Office)
The first year,
you won the contest,
but they said you weren't strong enough.
They claimed you'd be at a disadvantage
on the battlefield.
Then came the second year.
You stood by the Conscription Notice
in front of my mansion,
(North Army Conscription Notice)
searching,
but your name was nowhere to be found.
Stop looking. Leave.
Your name's not there.
Do you want to join the North Army?
Can I?
Come with me.
When the battle began,
you fought just like men.
You are braver and wiser than most.
Wushuang,
I was right about you.
Everyone here today
is the pride of the North Army.
In my heart, you are all heroes.
We have fought side by side
to defend the nation.
Every drop of our blood
and every act of loyalty
have built the North Army's name.
Your Highness,
what do you want to say?
North Army, hear my command.
- Yes.
From this day forward,
Shen Wushuang
will be your new commander.
Your Highness,
I am unworthy
of such a heavy duty.
Your Highness, are you leaving us?
Your Highness, you are our general.
We swore to follow.
- That's right.
- Yes, Your Highness.
We can't do this without you.
Are you ignoring my orders now?
This is the North Army's command token.
It commands all our troops.
It stands for our army's honor.
Take it.
Soldiers of the North Army,
one day,
Wushuang will lead you into battle
to defend our home and country.
Please remember this:
Wherever I may be,
my heart
will always be with the North Army.
(All of this)
(happened because of me.)
(Let me)
(bear all the consequences.)
Give me a little more time.
I promise to find the truth for you.
Do you believe me?
♪Before the flowers bloom
and fill the earth♪
♪When snow falls, I sing alone,
yet you're long gone♪
♪The past is never marked with a word♪
♪Alas, fate makes all the decisions♪
♪We're destined to meet
yet not meant to be♪
♪Yet my heart still belongs to you♪
♪Leaving me with wounds that never heal♪
Let's go.
♪Turn us into strangers♪
♪Candlelight flickers,
haunting my quiet mind♪
♪Words by the window
lock in the midnight hush♪
♪The beautiful dream feels so real♪
♪So I follow where the dream may lead♪
♪Spring rushes past;
silent rain soaks us both♪
♪Time drifts on; I can't bear to let go♪
♪Melancholy lingers♪
Who is better for her,
the one beside her or me?
It's definitely him.
What a poor judgment.
Come on, let's get to work.
Here.
(Wanted Notice)
Have you heard this?
The God of War of Dawei fell
for a demoness.
He handed over his military power
and fled with her.
I heard the demoness's blood
carries the Gu poison.
Anyone who drinks it
obeys her every word.
The God of War must've been bewitched.
♪Autumn wind stirs gentle ripples♪
♪Before the flowers bloom
and fill the earth♪
♪When snow falls, I sing alone,
yet you're long gone♪
♪The past is never marked with a word♪
♪Alas, fate makes all the decisions♪
♪We're destined to meet
yet not meant to be♪
♪Yet my heart still belongs to you♪
♪Leaving me with wounds that never heal♪
♪Years leave the past behind
and turn us into strangers♪
♪Candlelight flickers,
haunting my quiet mind♪
♪Words by the window
lock in the midnight hush♪
♪The beautiful dream feels so real♪
♪So I follow where the dream may lead♪
♪Spring rushes past;
silent rain soaks us both♪
♪Time drifts on; I can't bear to let go♪
♪Melancholy lingers♪
♪Yet my heart still belongs to you♪
♪Leaving me with wounds that never heal♪
♪Years leave the past behind
and turn us into strangers♪
♪Candlelight flickers,
haunting my quiet mind♪
♪Words by the window
lock in the midnight hush♪
♪The beautiful dream feels so real♪
♪So I follow where the dream may lead♪
♪Spring rushes past;
silent rain soaks us both♪
♪Time drifts on; I can't bear to let go♪
♪Melancholy lingers♪
♪The beautiful dream fades to dust♪
♪Leaving us in the past♪