=The Antidote to Love=
=Episode 9=
On the 15th day of the 4th month,
Year of Ding Mao,
I woke up from a dream.
Gazing up at the bright moon,
I seemed to hear
an old friend's whisper,
yet the words slipped through my grasp.
How frustrating.
On the 8th day of the 10th month,
Year of Jia Wei, I walked the streets.
In the bustling crowd,
a sense of déjà vu struck me,
yet old memories stayed out of reach.
I couldn't help but feel sad.
You wrote down
everything?
Whenever something comes to mind,
I make sure to write it down.
Yun Yao.
Give me a little more time.
I promise to find the truth for you.
I've heard
he's told you everything.
This comb here
seems unfamiliar to me.
It seems to be bought
at the Lantern Festival.
Your Highness.
These are the daily things
you asked me to get for Miss Yi Jiu.
Everything has been bought.
I believe
she can help me regain my memories.
There were so many doubts
about the past.
I've investigated
as you ordered for so long
but still found nothing useful.
I thought I'd know the truth
if I regained my memory.
If it wasn't me
who destroyed the Moon Clan,
then who could it be?
If we never find a clue,
there will always be a rift
between you and the Consort.
Keeping her close by your side
might bring...
No matter what plot lies behind this,
I must uncover the truth
for Yun Yao
and the Moon Clan.
General Wushuang, what's this for?
His Highness has not slept all night
in the study.
So, I brought him some food.
(Gathering herbs in the hills;
stones pile high, vines winding long)
Set the food over there.
Yun Yao.
Didn't you say you'd give me an answer?
Can you tell me
what truly happened that year
when I went to the Moon Clan?
On the 5th day of the 8th month,
Year of Fenggu,
I received your letter.
In it, you said
your father agreed to our union,
and you'd come to marry me.
In truth,
Father first refused our marriage.
That girl has bewitched you.
I sent you to investigate the Moon Clan
not to be swept up in romance.
When I was wounded,
it was the Saintess of the Moon Clan
who saved me with her blood.
So what?
They've practiced sorcery for years
to beguile and deceive the minds.
That's not true.
The Moon Clan is honest and kind,
not at all as the rumors claim.
Enough.
But three days later,
Father suddenly decreed
to approve our marriage.
On the wedding day,
I did wear my armor,
led the North Army,
and left for the Moon Clan to marry you,
but we were ambushed on the road.
I remember nothing else
after that.
That day, I saw
that you destroyed my clan in armor.
If that wasn't you,
who could it be?
That's what I've been trying
to find out.
All these years,
I've searched for survivors
of the North Army,
but there's no news so far.
Yun Yao,
do you believe me?
I've seen the bamboo scrolls
in this room
and the writings on them.
I've heard your scattered memories.
Every word
leads back to my clan.
I'd rather believe the truth
than believe you.
Don't worry.
The truth
will come to light soon enough.
If I truly have erred,
you can punish me however you want.
Yun Yao.
This is from General Wushuang.
It will rain heavily tonight.
Warm yourself by the fire.
Got it.
Thank you.
Yun Yao.
The floor is cold.
Go rest on the bed.
(Prince Ning's Mansion)
There have been many thefts
in the city lately.
Tell the men to stay alert.
Strengthen the patrols.
Yes, General Wushuang.
Wushuang.
Your Highness.
I haven't seen Zhe lately.
Where is he?
His Highness...
He hasn't appeared for days.
I heard you haven't been eating well.
What's going on?
You're too old
to have me feed you now.
He,
why did you bring back
the woman who hurt you?
She's from another clan.
Many things
aren't as simple as you think.
She's my wife now.
I have my reasons
for doing this.
What reasons?
She is tied to my memories.
He,
did something come back to you?
Not yet.
Since you
can't let her go,
I'll treat her as my sister-in-law.
But if she tries to hurt you again,
I won't let her off.
Alright, alright.
I understand.
Remember to drink your congee.
(Office of Divination)
I beg you.
Please, let me go.
I'm begging you.
Beg me?
If you wish to beg someone,
beg your dear friend.
She's now risen to glory.
This medicine
can only be made using you all.
Milord.
Seems we must try something stronger.
♪Autumn wind stirs gentle ripples♪
♪Before the flowers bloom
and fill the earth♪
♪When snow falls, I sing alone,
yet you're long gone♪
♪The past is never marked with a word♪
♪Alas, fate makes all the decisions♪
♪We're destined to meet
yet not meant to be♪
♪Yet my heart still belongs to you♪
♪Leaving me with wounds that never heal♪
♪Years leave the past behind
and turn us into strangers♪
♪Candlelight flickers,
haunting my quiet mind♪
♪Words by the window
lock in the midnight hush♪
♪The beautiful dream feels so real♪
♪So I follow where the dream may lead♪
♪Spring rushes past;
silent rain soaks us both♪
♪Time drifts on; I can't bear to let go♪
♪Melancholy lingers♪
♪Yet my heart still belongs to you♪
♪Leaving me with wounds that never heal♪
♪Years leave the past behind
and turn us into strangers♪
♪Candlelight flickers,
haunting my quiet mind♪
♪Words by the window
lock in the midnight hush♪
♪The beautiful dream feels so real♪
♪So I follow where the dream may lead♪
♪Spring rushes past;
silent rain soaks us both♪
♪Time drifts on; I can't bear to let go♪
♪Melancholy lingers♪
♪The beautiful dream fades to dust♪
♪Leaving us in the past♪