♪You're the one who
makes me fall in love♪
♪My mind is composing a melody♪
♪Play a magical encounter♪
♪I walk into the trap slowly♪
♪Abandon the unimportant questions♪
♪It might make♪
♪The magical relationship closer♪
♪Your smile is like a summer view♪
♪It slowly grows in my heart♪
♪When I open up my heart♪
♪I realize I don't mean what I say♪
♪I realize you're getting ready, too♪
♪To say I do♪
♪I'll hold your palm with all my might♪
♪Experience the definition of love♪
♪A magical encounter♪
♪Becomes sweet♪
♪So we're meant to be♪
♪Instead of pondering reasons♪
♪Why don't we bravely
approach each other♪
♪It might turn into a dream♪
♪You're the one who
makes me fall in love♪
♪My mind is composing a melody♪
♪Play a magical encounter♪
♪Our gazes approach each other♪
=Hello Mr. Gu=
=Episode 12=
(Beyond the obligation...)
Gu Nanzhou,
why are you
being so mean to me lately?
Is it because I split
water on your book?
Is it because
I washed your pants
together with bed sheets?
Are you angry that
I barged into the bathroom
and saw you taking a bath?
Product placement
in an animation
is a common method nowadays.
(Product Placement)
We get paid for advertising
and get to lower the risk.
When the animation is released,
the sponsor will help us
to promote it.
Sorry.
We can't accept it.
I can accept partial product placement
in the scenes about real life,
but after the characters
enter Lake Xingling,
I want the sense of
reality to be minimized.
There can't be any product placement.
The scene of real life
only covers 10% of the animation.
We can't slot in
so many advertisements,
unless you lengthen this part.
Lake Xingling's structure
can't be changed.
I'm sorry.
We can't accept
Yingqi's proposal.
Mr. Gu,
according to our agreement,
as the investor, Yingqi
can request Xingyun
to have reasonable amendment.
If Xingyun doesn't do that,
Yingqi can pull out from
the project anytime.
I got you.
However, this project
is what I've been wanting to do
for ten years.
I know exactly how
to present it at its best.
Okay.
I'll let Mr. He know
your stand.
We need to amend these four parts.
The atmosphere in this chapter
has to be refreshing.
Okay.
Mr. Gu,
Mr. He of Yingqi called.
What did he say?
Mr. He said that
after comprehensive consideration,
he thought investing
in Xingyun was risky.
So he decided to
withdraw the investment.
However, we're going
to pay Bule Ray soon.
If they withdraw it now,
Xingyun will face an issue of cash flow.
According to the agreement,
when do we need to make
the first payment to Bule Ray?
We need to do it on 13th.
I heard that
Mr. He of Yingqi and Lu Ziming
are good friends.
Do you think
it's Lu Ziming's conspiracy
to make us sign an agreement
with Bule Ray
before Yingqi withdrew the investment
to ruin us once and for all?
Qingqing meant well but
she landed us in trouble.
She got Yingqi to invest in us,
but we didn't expect
Xingyun to be in big trouble.
It's my decision
to collaborate with Yingqi.
It has nothing to do with her.
Just discuss with Bule Ray
first.
Ask if we can postpone the first payment
to a few days later.
Okay.
(Jiang Jingxuan)
Hello.
Bule Ray
called and asked
about the first payment.
Following what you said,
we discussed it
and it's postponed for a week.
Thank you.
Even though we have one more week,
our company doesn't have enough money.
Don't worry about the money.
I'll figure it out.
Haven't you found the right company?
Those companies that offered me jobs
are not the ones I want.
Those I want to join didn't look for me.
Here you go.
Listen.
Stop torturing yourself.
Instead of working in
our family's company,
you want to suffer out there.
Mother,
I told you...
Got it.
You're not interested in
your father's business.
I just want to do something on my own.
Everyone around me has a goal,
but I don't even have a direction.
You're a girl.
Why do you have to exhaust yourself?
You should make more new friends.
Expand your social circle
and you won't be isolated.
You're always like this.
You don't like being nagged.
Are you free at noon?
The son of Antai's Uncle Liu
came back from overseas.
He invited us for lunch.
Mother,
I told you no more blind date.
It's not a blind date.
It's just a meal.
You're young adults.
Maybe you can talk to him
and befriend him.
Your social circle is small.
Where else can you get
to know new friends?
I don't need so many friends.
The more friends, the more options.
Finish the fruits.
The vitamin is good for your complexion.
Remember. 12PM.
Your restaurant serves great dishes.
It's exactly the same as what I had
in Provence.
Thank you, sir.
I had a chance to learn it overseas.
I hope you like the dishes.
Waiter! Come here.
Please enjoy.
Sure.
It's diverse.
Not bad.
Let's order Ratatouille
and blanquette de veau.
Xiaxia.
Help yourselves. Come on.
Come on.
Well,
anything will do.
Waiter,
Ratatouille
and blanquette de veau.
Please hold on, sir.
Come on, Xiaxia.
Come on, try the fish.
It's really delicious.
It's good for the complexion, too.
We'll be a family.
I know, right?
Come on.
Excuse me,
I want to go to the bathroom.
Xuan,
I didn't want to come here.
His parents did.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm happy
that you came to our restaurant.
Then the chefs,
can get more bonus.
About just now...
Did your family bring you out
for a social gathering again?
It's good.
Getting in touch with others
is good for you.
Xiaxia,
I saw you walking this way.
I thought the bathroom was over here.
Do you know each other?
He's...
Look,
Ms. Su is our restaurant's VIP.
I serve her regularly.
Of course we know each other.
You suggested another restaurant.
I thought
you didn't like the food here.
I like it here,
but
I didn't want your parents
to spend too much.
It's all right.
It's time for us to go back.
Our parents are waiting.
I'll play host to you next time.
Sure.
(Yuebaiwei Restaurant)
Uncle, aunt
and Xiaxia,
I'll send you home.
It's all right.
Just take care of Xiaxia.
All right.
We'll go back first.
Okay.
We'll make a move first.
Uncle and aunt, bye.
We're leaving.
Mother!
Bye.
Your son is great.
How is he? Not bad, right?
Xiaxia,
I know a great bar around here.
Why don't we go there?
Not today,
I have something on.
You...
Mr. Gu.
-Good morning.
We're only left
with one investor, Jialuo.
However, there's a problem
with their company this year.
They might not agree to invest.
What about Qihe Capital?
In our last meeting,
didn't Mr. Sun say it's almost done?
They're singing a different tune now.
After risk assessment,
they're reconsidering it.
(Lake Xingling Project)
It's okay.
Have a meeting with
the original draft team first.
I'll figure out the investment.
Okay.
Your background
is getting better.
I should call you
Zhang the Expert now.
Stop flattering me.
Just send me
whatever that's needed to be done
or we might not make it two days later.
That's all.
Thank you.
Maintain the quality and quantity.
No problem, don't worry.
Hello, Yan.
Qingqing, come to the company now.
Now?
I'm rushing my work.
The deadline is approaching.
You may delay it for a day.
You must attend this meeting.
There's a big good news.
What is it?
Your Romantic Starry Sky
is chosen by a big company.
Come and talk to them.
If it goes well,
who knows
it might be made into an animation.
Seriously, Yan?
All right, I'll be right there.
I...
Half an hour.
No,
I'll be there in 20 minutes.
Thank you, Yan!
You're welcome.
Where are you going?
Yan just told me
that our Romantic Starry Sky
might be turned into an animation.
You're awesome, Qingqing.
Is it confirmed?
Not yet.
Yan wants me
to talk to them.
Your senior is eloquent.
It's a piece of cake.
If we secure the deal,
seeing how you went all out to help me,
we'll split the bonus.
I'll leave now.
(Yingqi Investment)
Hello.
Who are you looking for?
I'm looking for Mr. He.
Mr. He has something on.
Please wait at the lounge.
Okay.
This way, please.
I watched Gu Nanzhou
growing up.
Forget about his minor flaws,
the worst thing is
he's willful and arrogant.
He lost most of the Gus' fortune
that was entrusted to him.
Thanks to your reminder, Mr. Lu,
Yingqi withdrew our investment in time
instead of walking into the trap.
I think he's simply inexperienced.
He even wants
to work with top special
effects team overseas.
He's digging
his own grave.
That's why Gu Group
needs to be led
by someone like you, Mr. Lu.
If Gu Nanzhou
was half as smart as you, Mr. He,
I wouldn't have been so anxious.
As the saying goes,
a family's fortune can't last for
more than three generations.
Licheng and I
worked so hard to establish this.
When it's handed to the kid...
Ms. Zhou.
Mr. He, you still remember me.
Of course,
you're memorable.
I would like to discuss
something with you, Mr. He
and Mr. Lu.
Me as well?
I'm all ears.
Although I'm new in the industry,
I have basic aesthetic sense.
If you ask me,
Lake Xingling is one
of the few best works in recent years.
It may not be perfect,
but each penny Gu Nanzhou
invests in it
is absolutely worth it.
If that's the case,
do you think it's my mistake
for Yingqi to withdraw
from Lake Xingling?
It's a grave mistake.
Enlighten me.
What did I do wrong?
Gu Nanzhou knows
how good this project is.
That's why he spent a lot of money
to make it.
However, you only care
about the risks and cost.
Gu Nanzhou's obsession
is seen as a spendthrift's ways.
One who only cares about the profit
can be a good businessman,
but he or she can never
produce good work.
I've been in the industry for years
and produced so many good works.
Young lady,
you're the first one
who spoke to me like that.
Am I wrong?
The Legend of the Valley
was eight years ago, right?
Did Yingqi produce
any reputable work after that?
I think you're
inexperienced.
That's why you're
brainwashed by Gu Nanzhou.
How well do you know about him?
Why are you defending him?
I might not know Gu Nanzhou well,
but I know Lake Xingling well.
If you give up a piece of great work,
in which Gu Nanzhou poured his heart,
over a personal grudge,
then you're
the stupid ones.
I don't know
how good Lake Xingling is,
but I know Gu Nanzhou
perfectly well.
You'd better ask him this.
15 years ago,
how did his brother
die in a stampede?
Obsession?
His obsession
is about having his own way for decades
and disregarding others' lives.
Ms. Zhou,
you're a great distance
away from our standard
for collaboration.
Therefore, there's no point
discussing this collaboration.
Wait till
you are more mature.
Ms. Li.
Ms. Zhou.
(Romantic Starry Sky)
(2004 Stampede)
(November 22 Chunyu Square Stampede)
(November 22)
It's his brother's death
anniversary today.
Gu Nanzhou.
Gu Nanzhou!
Hello, Xiaochuan.
Hello, Qingqing.
Is Mr. Gu in?
I don't think so.
What's the matter?
Mr. Gu was absent
for an internal meeting
this afternoon.
I saw that his pill box was empty.
He's not picking up my calls either.
I don't know where he went.
Is he suffering from anxiety again?
Did
anything bad happen again?
Mr. Gu negotiated
with several investment companies today,
but none went well.
According to Xuan,
Lu Ziming intentionally spread
news about a problem
with Xingyun's capital.
As a result, many companies
are reluctant to work with us.
Lu Ziming
is evil.
If I knew, I should've
scolded him even more today.
Did you see Lu Ziming?
Forget it.
It's pointless to scold him anyway.
Let's look for Gu Nanzhou first.
Where could he possibly go?
So you're here.
What a great night view.
I should've worked at
the balcony back then.
Who allowed you to come here?
Go out.
I pay my rental.
If you can be here,
why can't I be?
Just stay here
without making a noise.
Fine.
I'll lower my voice.
One needs to suck when eating crayfish.
Do you want to try one?
Don't miss it.
I'm not lying.
How is it?
It's so-so.
You're boring.
You can't even appreciate
crayfish.
You've been peeling it for so long
and there's so little flesh.
Isn't it troublesome?
It's really simple.
Do you want to give it a try?
You're indeed from a rich family.
You look so stiff peeling it.
That's it.
Eat it.
It's not so difficult.
What's wrong?
Did I do it wrong?
No.
You peeled it quite well.
It's been a while
since someone peeled it for me.
I'm not used to it.
Well,
you can have the rest.
I need to rush for my work.
Why can't I open the door?
Where's your key?
I think I forgot to bring it.
My phone is dead.
What about yours?
Mine...
Mine is dead, too.
You...
The cleaner will come tomorrow.
She'll open the door for us.
Just take a break.
What's so nice about stargazing?
I think it's interesting.
For example, the Milky Way
will be dimmer in winter than summer.
The Big Dipper
will be pointing to the north.
Also, Orion
is the shiniest in winter.
How do you know?
My brother taught me when I was young.
He'd been bright since young.
Astronomy, geography, music and arts.
You name it and he knew it.
If he didn't die,
my father wouldn't
have been disappointed.
Look,
what's that?
That's Cassiopeia.
What about that?
The constellation
is Draco.
Meteor!
That's a plane.
It's just a plane.
♪The daily bickering♪
♪Is like meteor across the balcony♪
♪The moment I lift my head♪
♪My vulnerable heart is healed♪
♪Not afraid of drowning in a crowd♪
♪Even if I remain silent♪
♪The soft spot in my heart♪
♪Can only be touched by you♪
♪Put my life♪
♪In your life♪
♪When I see you in the rain♪
♪I just want to hold you♪
Thank you for your clothes.
Girls feel cold easily.
Wear it.
♪Allow me to face the world♪
I didn't expect you
to be so considerate.
You're indeed the best Party A in China.
♪It's solved by time, too♪
♪Someday♪
♪I understand what's worthier♪
♪I anticipate♪
Didn't you say you didn't bring the key?
What is this?
It's the key to my office drawer.
It's actually the balcony's key.
No drawer has such a big key.
Zhou Jianqing!
This guy
wanted me to accompany him,
but he told a lame lie.
He's childish.
(Although I don't know)
(why you're mad,)
(well,)
(seeing how you're)
(a great Party A,)
(I'll still apologize to you.)
(Lavender scent and flowering
tea help one to sleep well.)
(Sweet dreams.)
(Don't get all stressed out.)
(Keep it up.)
Come here to eat.
The dishes are ready.
What are you doing?
What do you want?
What on earth do you want?
I'm thirsty.
♪You're the one who
makes me fall in love♪
♪My mind is composing a melody♪
♪Play a magical encounter♪
♪The tears secretly cooperate♪
♪Like misunderstanding,
it drives the gap♪
♪Into a corner♪
♪I don't understand
what's wrong with us♪
♪Because it's still blinking♪
♪For your promise♪
♪I'm reluctant to part♪
♪The feeling of missing is more bitter♪
♪We slowly familiarize with each other♪
♪Hopefully love will make
the dream warm♪
♪I care deeply for you♪
♪Even if there's a distance♪
♪I care for you and protect you♪
♪Perhaps there's a sense of longing♪
♪It surpasses time♪
♪I go through the crowd to find you♪
♪As my heart beats, I gain courage♪
♪I want to become better for you♪
♪End the shivering♪
♪I care deeply about you♪
♪I still care deeply about you♪
♪I need your company♪
♪We go back to the same way♪
♪To be reunited♪
♪In each other's arms and be healed♪