=Hello Mr. Gu Theatre=
(I once made a wish)
(that my other-half)
(would be tall, handsome,)
(gentle, understanding)
(and polite, with a sense of humor.)
(If he can't be all these,)
(he should at least be handsome.)
(Who'd have thought)
(I'd encounter)
(someone like Mr. Gu.)
♪You're the one who
makes me fall in love♪
♪My mind is composing a melody♪
♪Play a magical encounter♪
♪I walk into the trap slowly♪
♪Abandon the unimportant questions♪
♪It might make♪
♪The magical relationship closer♪
♪Your smile is like a summer view♪
♪It slowly grows in my heart♪
♪When I open up my heart♪
♪I realize I don't mean what I say♪
♪I realize you're getting ready, too♪
♪To say I do♪
♪I'll hold your palm with all my might♪
♪Experience the definition of love♪
♪A magical encounter♪
♪Becomes sweet♪
♪So we're meant to be♪
♪Instead of pondering reasons♪
♪Why don't we bravely
approach each other♪
♪It might turn into a dream♪
♪You're the one who
makes me fall in love♪
♪My mind is composing a melody♪
♪Play a magical encounter♪
♪Our gazes approach each other♪
=Hello Mr. Gu=
=Episode 5=
(The never-ending cycle of
lying and covering up the lie)
Mr. Gu.
Is anyone in?
Zhou Jianqing.
Brother.
Brother,
drink a glass of water first.
What did you do to my sister?
Why don't you ask her
what she did to me?
Brother,
don't get the wrong idea.
We only drank together.
You drank?
Why did you
get a girl drunk?
Brother,
it has nothing to do with him.
I offered to drink.
You did?
What if he took advantage
of you when you're drunk?
Brother,
you misunderstood.
What happened?
I...
We're engaged.
Engaged?
Are you Gu Nanzhou?
Don't tell me you're dating him
to settle my debt?
Brother,
don't get the wrong idea.
We're each other's true love.
I really love him
and he loves me, too.
I guarantee that
our relationship is the purest
and no interest is involved.
It's love.
Fine.
Let me ask you.
When did you get to know each other?
-At childhood.
-Last year.
How well do you know her?
What does she love?
She loves to eat.
She's a drama queen.
When eating Stir-fried egg with tomato,
does she prefer the tomato
or the egg?
Tomato.
Egg.
When is his birthday?
Which university did he graduate from?
Where has he ever worked?
Brother,
a relationship is about the present.
What's the point of knowing this?
This information can be found
on Xingyun's homepage
within three minutes,
yet you don't even know.
How dare you claim that it's true love.
Come on, let me ask you.
What do you see in him?
I
love him
for his nice appearance and figure.
I care about one's appearance.
Appearance.
What about you?
What do you see in my sister?
I don't...
He means there's no
answer to this question.
He's been telling me
loving someone is not about reasons.
Nanzhou is less superficial than me.
He has substance.
He loves
my carefree soul.
He's unlike me.
I'm so shallow
and I'm into his appearance.
I'll never approve of your relationship.
Why?
You don't have a chemistry together.
You don't know each other at all.
You got together hastily.
You won't be happy together.
I agree with you in this,
but don't worry.
In the first place,
I only want to get married.
He means
he wanted to marry me
the first time he saw me.
Dear,
please leave us alone.
I want to talk to my brother.
Go.
Are you sure Gu Nanzhou
sincerely wants to marry you?
Of course.
He already proposed.
There's a big diamond ring.
Where is it?
It's too expensive.
So I'm not wearing it.
Brother,
Gu Nanzhou and I
genuinely love each other.
It's 100% true love.
The moment he appeared,
I thought,
I'm doomed.
Maybe
this is love.
I've never been courted
in such a passionate manner.
No one else
has ever cared for me like this.
He stood among the roses
and popped the question
in front of so many people.
You have no idea
how romantic
it was.
You even said yes to such
an old-fashioned proposal?
What kind of proposal do you want?
Did you expect him to be on a hot air
balloon of the altitude of 20,000m,
facing rapeseed plants
and telling me,
it's all yours?
So you disappeared earlier on
to be with him.
Yes.
Since we're engaged,
it's necessary to spend some time
to get to know each other.
If not,
how do I know whether he has a problem?
Come to think of it,
on the surface,
there's a huge gap
between you two.
How did you charm him?
You even fooled him into
paying my RMB2 million debt.
I'm after all
a pretty girl in University of Nancheng.
In a year,
I have around 50 or 60 suitors.
30 freaks and 20 weirdos, you mean?
I'm telling you.
Anyway, we have our family rules.
We must pay the money we owe others.
Don't make your relationship
complicated
over this matter.
Got it.
I have a feeling that Gu Nanzhou
is kind of weird.
He must be a psycho
or maybe he's traumatized
in childhood...
You're
just jealous that he's better-looking
and more brilliant than you.
Stop teasing me.
Let's get down to business.
If you find any problem
during this period,
just end the relationship.
All right.
I'll report to you if there's a problem.
Fine.
I'm leaving.
All right.
Have a safe trip.
Remember what I told you.
Yes.
I'll visit you again tomorrow.
Not again.
What's the matter?
Can't I visit you?
Of course you can.
Have a safe trip.
Bye.
Is he still coming tomorrow?
I'm sorry.
My brother worries a lot.
He's smart and paranoid.
I might have to stay here
for a few more days.
Can you do me a favor?
According to the agreement,
Party B won't create
trouble for Party A.
Party A can request Party B
to do something beyond
the scope of the agreement
in exchange.
What can you exchange?
Just tell me what you want.
I'll do it if it's within my means.
You'll surely need me somehow.
Please.
Just treat it as charity
and helping the needy.
You will get good karma.
At home, you aren't allowed
to make any sound that is
more than 30 decibel.
If Party B destroys any item at home,
you must compensate me
based on the original price.
Party B must protect
Party A's image at all times.
You can't simply bring
anyone to the house.
No pet is allowed.
All cleaning
will be done by Party B.
Waste sorting has to be done
individually by Party B.
This is too harsh.
Penalty for a violation.
You're required to leave if there're
more than three violations.
Party A...
No,
Mr. Gu.
Can we discuss this?
The door is over there.
Gu Nanzhou.
You're being too much.
Forget about the first 19 terms.
For the 20th term,
I don't stay here alone.
You can choose not to stay here.
Continue.
Let me ask you.
How long have they been together?
I seriously have no idea.
You're her best friend.
How can you not know?
She didn't tell me, seriously.
Zhou Jianqing is not a secretive person.
She neither told you nor
posted it on her social media.
Gu Nanzhou is kind of weird, too.
There're flaws in the way
he speaks and acts.
I think he's keeping something from me.
There must be a problem with him.
I'll make a move first.
Qingqing,
Xuan looked for me yesterday.
He didn't seem to
believe you're engaged.
You should figure out a way.
He'll surely get to the bottom of this.
How's your life at Gu Nanzhou's home?
Did he
make life difficult for you?
He
is a psycho.
The books at home
must be sorted alphabetically.
Why didn't you
return the books to the spots?
Didn't I put them back?
Transformation
should be put behind Light-Year Stories.
Why is it in front?
Peruvian Traditions
should be put in E category.
Why is it in C category?
What are you waiting for?
I'm not allowed to
keep unfinished beverage.
I have to discard it.
What is this?
Beverage.
Why don't you discard it if it's opened?
There's still half left.
It's a pity to discard it.
I'll continue to drink it later.
Discard it.
It's an eyesore.
When I'm sitting on the sofa,
I can't flatten the pillows.
From now on,
I'll never sit on the sofa anymore.
You'd better
remember the terms in the agreement.
Last night...
You came out of nowhere.
I told you
after 12 o'clock,
you're not allowed to make any sound.
It's not 12 o'clock yet.
Look at that.
It's only past a minute.
Also,
strawberry mousse has high calorie.
Drinking cola in midnight
is bad for your teeth.
The grapes
are rich in sugar.
Bananas
are all right.
Gu Nanzhou,
you're so nosy.
Follow my rules when
you're staying here.
He lectured me for half an hour.
Tell me.
Isn't he crazy?
Oh, Qingqing,
why is Gu Nanzhou like this?
It must be harsh for you.
However, Qingqing,
you should think twice.
Your brother
is not easy to fool.
If you don't show him concrete proof,
he won't believe it.
What should I do?
This is too difficult.
Mr. Gu,
our team spent a long time
working on this.
It's the best version
with our existing resources.
For this part,
actually I want to present
Lake Xingling as an ethereal fantasy,
like the reference effect I showed you.
However, your work
does not live up to my expectations.
Mr. Gu, to be frank,
your desired effect
can't be achieved
with the existing technology in China.
If you turn to an overseas company,
Xingyun's budget
can't cover it at all.
You're right.
The technology overseas
is indeed more mature.
Mr. Gu, what I mean is
we will
try our best to fulfill
your requirement.
What are you doing here?
I know you've been working overtime.
So I specially cooked
chicken soup for you.
It's for your nourishment.
I spent two hours on it.
It smells really great.
I'm not hungry.
Smell it.
It tastes as good as it looks.
Put it down.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I did this
just to thank you for taking me in.
If you like the soup,
I'll deliver it to you tomorrow,
the day after tomorrow
and the following days
There's no need for that.
Do you have anything else?
If not, just go back.
I'll leave after you
take the chicken soup.
I have to
bring the lunch box back for washing.
What are you doing?
I just want to take
a photo with you, Mr. Gu.
No photo is allowed.
All right.
I told you no photo was allowed.
Don't delete it.
I need the photo to convince my brother.
It's none of my concern.
If he doesn't believe
that we're dating,
he'll think
I'm dating you for the money.
If he disturbs you everyday,
you will be bothered.
I don't have to cooperate
with you to take the photos.
You can use it to convince your mother.
She called me last night.
I told her
about our engagement.
You...
You also don't want her to know
we're putting on an act, right?
Just treat it as fulfilling
your filial piety,
so that your mother will be relieved.
We're helping each other.
Don't be calculative.
Just take a few photos with me.
It won't take long.
Otherwise,
your mother will call me again.
I'm only free at noon.
Thank you.
You're really kind.
Come on, drink the soup.
Hurry up.
Just drink it.
♪It's like a signal of love♪
♪As we watch a horror flick♪
♪You hold your breath♪♪
Come on.
♪I pretend to stretch♪
♪Who will be enraged and
have sleepless nights?♪
♪The sunlight is perfect♪
Try it.
Hurry up.
Come on.
♪That's how far our footsteps are♪
Pull the trigger.
Over there.
♪I can't help but steal a glance at you♪
Yes.
That one.
The one over there.
There's also that.
That one.
Look, over there.
♪Answer♪
♪I'll answer more bravely
than love first♪
♪You're the steps I pursue♪
♪I'm fearless as long as you're around♪
♪Do you see it? Tick-tock♪
♪Blossom in the heart♪
♪Answer♪
♪I want to express my
feelings before love does♪
♪I'm the fairy tale where you begin♪
♪Hand-in-hand, we answer the sweetness♪
♪My mood is perfect♪
♪It's like a signal of love♪
♪As we watch a horror flick♪
♪You hold your breath♪
♪My heart is pounding♪
♪I pretend to stretch♪
♪Who will be enraged and
have sleepless nights♪
♪The sunlight is perfect♪
♪We're surrounded by romance♪
♪Our shadows rub shoulders♪
♪That's how far our footsteps are♪
♪That's how sweet the air is♪
♪I can't help but steal a glance at you♪
♪I'm in love with
the detail given by you♪
Can't you give in to a girl?
♪Do you see it? Tick-tock♪
♪Blossom in the heart♪
♪Answer♪
♪I want to express my
feelings before love does♪
Do you want to play this?
I'll demonstrate it to you.
♪Hand-in-hand, we answer the sweetness♪
Yes.
♪You're arrogant♪
Look. How is it?
Am I awesome?
♪You make me cry and laugh,
yet I care the most about you♪
Let's go.
Let's take photo stickers.
This is just the merchant's tactic.
You can't get one.
No,
it surely has a pattern.
I want to do it again.
We got it.
(Here's a token of appreciation.)
(Please enjoy.)
Mr. Gu,
if we continue to
increase the investment,
for Fengchi, this project
will be too risky.
Xingyun can't afford the consequences
of increasing investment.
If Mr. Gu insists on
increasing the investment,
Mr. Jin
will never follow suit.
Mr. Gu,
Lake Xingling's current investment
is reaching the budget limit.
If we turn to foreign companies
for special effects,
the investment will increase
by at least two times.
The risk will be unpredictable.
Moreover...
Stop talking.
Mr. Gu,
did you even finish this
box of medicine, too?
Bring me the report of Lake Xingling's
investment increase.
Why did you simply
look at others' stuff?
It's just some couple photos.
Why can't I look at them?
You're done.
Just go.
I only came here for two minutes,
yet you're chasing me away.
Are you even my sister?
You've been here for
more than half an hour.
-No.
-Just leave.
Dear, you're back.
Please do me a favor.
You're back, brother-in-law.
Just nice,
I want to talk to you.
Here's RMB10,000.
I'll
return the rest to you gradually.
I've already planned it.
In the first year, I'll return
you RMB10,000 monthly.
In the following year, I'll
increase the payment
by 50% every year.
As for the interests,
I'll pay based on
bank loan interests.
Don't worry.
I won't take advantage of you.
I don't need you
to return the money.
By rights,
my sister is marrying you.
You should call me brother-in-law.
However, come to think of it,
even siblings should
make transactions clear.
I've already told you.
You don't have to return the money.
I've already told you, too.
You must take it.
We're done talking about money.
Let's talk about my sister.
This recorded my years of experience
in taking care of Qingqing.
Please read it carefully.
(Handbook on caring for Zhou Jianqing)
Since our parents passed away,
I've been caring for Qingqing.
Although my sister
is flawed,
she's my sister after all.
I can't bear to see her being wronged.
Am I right?
This is too troublesome.
I've been caring for Qingqing for years.
Did I complain?
I finally raised her up
and now she's with you.
Did I ever think it's unfair?
You've cared for her for years,
but you've also
created troubles for her.
How does that count?
Those are different matters.
(Yinshan Animation)
Not bad.
The response for the comic is great.
It's even ranked among the top 15
most searched comic in the website.
The platform thinks highly of you.
Thank you, boss.
I'll continue to work hard.
Therefore,
I think you should strike
while the iron is hot.
Update it this week.
Update it again?
Mr. Gu is rich.
Why do you have
to make your own living?
What do you know?
Anytime,
a woman should have her own career.
If I have a girlfriend,
as long as she's happy,
I don't mind providing for her.
You're lame.
Things are different now.
Your mindset is outdated.
Ladies
should be independent.
You're
still young.
You don't understand.
I'll leave if you don't get in now.
Coming.
I'll make a move first.
See you tomorrow.
Junk food.
Hello, your food delivery.
What is it?
Snail rice noodle.
It's yours.
Where's my food delivery?
I discarded it.
I ordered the food.
Why did you discard it?
Don't you know what time it is?
Why do you want to
eat such a smelly food?
I'm eating it in my own room.
How does it concern you?
Your room?
That's part of my house.
Fine.
Your house.
Everything is yours.
Can't you be understanding?
I'm rushing for work at night.
Do you want me to starve?
The rules are long set.
Moreover, according to the agreement,
even you are mine.
Do you have to go so far?
Every day, when I'm here,
I have to be cautious
even when I'm drinking water
or in the bathroom.
I ordered food delivery.
You wouldn't smell anything
if I closed the door,
yet you discarded it.
Do you want everyone
to follow your lifestyle?
If you are reluctant,
you can leave immediately.
You...
Luckily I have smelly tofu.
Stupid guy.
Forget it if he stopped me
from having snail rice noodle
in the room,
he even discarded my smelly tofu.
I don't mind skipping supper.
Just treat it as going on a diet.
Was I
being too harsh just now?
Zhou Jianqing.
♪You're the one that
makes me fall in love♪
♪My mind is composing a melody♪
♪Play a magical encounter♪
♪The tears secretly cooperate♪
♪Like misunderstanding,
it drives the gap♪
♪Into a corner♪
♪I don't understand
what's wrong with us♪
♪Because it's still blinking♪
♪For your promise♪
♪I'm reluctant to part♪
♪The feeling of missing is more bitter♪
♪We slowly familiarize with each other♪
♪Hopefully love will make
the dream warm♪
♪I care deeply for you♪
♪Even if there's a distance♪
♪I care for you and protect you♪
♪Perhaps there's a sense of longing♪
♪It surpasses time♪
♪I go through the crowd to find you♪
♪As my heart beats, I gain courage♪
♪I want to become better for you♪
♪End the shivering♪
♪I care deeply about you♪
♪I still care deeply about you♪
♪I need your company♪
♪We go back to the same way♪
♪To be reunited♪
♪In each other's arms and be healed♪