♪You're the one who
makes me fall in love♪
♪My mind is composing a melody♪
♪Play a magical encounter♪
♪I walk into the trap slowly♪
♪Abandon the unimportant questions♪
♪It might make♪
♪The magical relationship closer♪
♪Your smile is like a summer view♪
♪It slowly grows in my heart♪
♪When I open up my heart♪
♪I realize I don't mean what I say♪
♪I realize you're getting ready, too♪
♪To say I do♪
♪I'll hold your palm with all my might♪
♪Experience the definition of love♪
♪A magical encounter♪
♪Becomes sweet♪
♪So we're meant to be♪
♪Instead of pondering reasons♪
♪Why don't we bravely
approach each other♪
♪It might turn into a dream♪
♪You're the one that
makes me fall in love♪
♪My mind is composing a melody♪
♪Play a magical encounter♪
♪Our gazes approach each other♪
=Hello Mr. Gu=
=Episode 8=
(Party B's Obligation)
Mr. Gu,
your coffee.
No sugar, remember?
Sorry, I forgot.
I'll make another cup for you.
The format is wrong.
Font face of Song 4.
1.5-spacing.
Didn't you see the remark?
All right, I'll redo it.
I asked you to categorise them
according to time and
production companies.
How could you mess up
something as simple as this?
Redo it.
All right.
You can't even button my shirt right.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it again for you.
Can't you match the colors well?
Got it.
You don't know how to tie a tie either?
I'll be done right away.
Enough.
You don't have to tie it.
Show me the amended draft.
There isn't a problem.
Just edit the fighting scene
based on what's been discussed
in the meeting yesterday.
All right.
Mr. Gu,
at 11.30 a.m,
you have a meeting
with Mr. Wu from T2 Entertainment.
Bring along the files
in the brown folder.
Start the car first.
Okay.
Nanzhou,
why don't I go for the meeting today?
I'm rather close to Mr. Wu.
Okay.
Jingxuan will go with me today.
As for you,
just stay in the office.
Mr. Gu, thank you for
your hard work today.
Goodbye.
Mr. Gu,
your suit...
I'm so sorry.
Goodbye.
I only asked you
to buy a suit for me.
Why did you even
mess that up?
Did I not give you enough money
or did you not understand what I said?
I just wanted to save
some money for you.
What did you say?
I mean
you're right.
It's my fault.
You're fast in admitting your fault.
You admit you're wrong
but you never change.
I wake you up every day now
and you never prepare breakfast.
I told you to depart early
to avoid the morning peak.
Have you ever obeyed me?
You've never been late because of me.
So you think you're right?
I didn't expect
my brother-in-law to be bad-tempered.
You're indeed a boss.
You're even bossing
your girlfriend around.
Brother,
we're talking about work.
Are you his maid?
Why are you carrying so much stuff?
You used to do this to me, too.
What's the matter?
Why do you think it's inappropriate now?
I'm your brother.
Who
does he think he is?
You...
Brother,
why are you here?
I'm here to send you food,
that's why.
All right.
I'll take the food.
Go back.
I came all the way to send food to you.
Are you keeping me out?
Brother,
later Nanzhou will try
to get me to sleep
and act intimately with me.
What's the matter?
Do you want to take a tour?
Zhou Jianqing, you...
Enough.
Hurry up.
Go.
I...
Just go.
Your brother is not
allowed to visit again.
If he does,
I'll double the rental.
No,
I'll try my best.
The special effects companies you picked
are great,
but the cost will multiply.
A few years ago,
Tuxing wanted to make
an animation that transcended the era.
You saw the outcome.
I think Tuxing failed
because they cared
more about special effects
than the script
and the details.
I have the confidence
that Lake Xingling
will not repeat the same mistake.
It's not that I don't trust your work,
but a broken chain is
every investor's nightmare.
We can't possibly invest in a project
that might cause us to
lose money anytime.
Investing more in special effects
will undoubtedly increase the cost,
but the enhanced quality of the work
will be another protection
for the investor.
We understand what you mean.
Our company might need
to reconsider Lake Xingling.
Please understand that.
Nanzhou,
eat something.
Avocado, surf clams
and low-calorie sauce.
They're all your favorites.
Thank you.
Lately,
you've been having the takeaway
bought by Qingqing.
Are you not used to it?
Little girls are like that.
They do
whatever they want.
If you don't want to tell her off,
I can bring you food.
It's okay.
You mentioned something on WeChat.
What is it?
I almost forgot.
Ant Paradise is nominated
(Award Ceremony)
for the top prize of children category
in Golden Apple Animation Festival.
The committee contacted me
and said you're required
to give a three-minute speech.
I know
you might not like
this kind of occasion.
However, many companies
in the industry
will attend this ceremony.
I think
this is a great opportunity
to promote Lake Xingling.
Also, the committee
said
you could ask your date to
collect the award on your behalf.
All right,
I'll leave
the communication to you.
We're here.
Come on, uncles and aunts. This way.
Watch out.
It looks great.
Look, it's awesome.
Let's line up here.
-This is not bad.
-What's wrong
with this car?
I know, right?
Why did he simply park it?
Young man,
why did you park the car so close?
How can we get off?
That's right, move it.
Yes. Why did you park it here?
Just move the car.
Don't park it here.
We can't even get off.
Move it.
Young man.
He's leaving.
Young man, where are you going?
Young man.
What's going on?
What should we do if you leave?
(Dear)
(Jiang Jingxuan)
Nanzhou,
do you want to eat anything?
I'll cook for you.
It's all right,
you may go back to office.
You're unwell.
I'm worried.
Also,
I can handle
the company's affairs here.
Get Zhou Jianqing
to handle the stuff here.
(Dear)
Why isn't he picking up?
Nanzhou,
you need to rest now.
Why don't you transfer your calls
to my phone first?
I'll handle the work for you.
All right.
By the way,
text Zhou Jianqing
and tell her to come back soon.
Sure.
What's wrong?
Are you done with the storyboard?
I'll give it to you tonight.
I've been tortured by Gu Nanzhou
in the past two days.
I have no time to draw.
How about this?
Let's draw in the library.
We'll go home after you're done.
I don't want you to stay up again.
However, Gu Nanzhou...
If he needs you,
he'll look for you.
Let's go.
The deadline is approaching.
Take your stuff.
Come on, hurry up.
Aren't you asleep yet?
So you did come back.
I was rushing to submit the comic.
You've been calling me.
What's so urgent?
Even if it was urgent,
could I count on you?
Jiang Jingxuan never forgets
what I tell her to do.
Did she tell you?
What is it?
There's an awarding ceremony tomorrow.
Ask her about the details.
What's the awarding ceremony about?
Call her to ask her.
Why did he turn moody all of a sudden?
It's not like he's having period.
You look elegant.
Very few can carry this gown.
It's customized
for someone like you
who has a great figure
and an air of elegance.
(Zhou Jianqing)
Hello, Qingqing.
What's the matter?
Xuan,
Mr. Gu wants me to ask you
about the awarding ceremony.
He wants me to get ready.
How should I get ready?
Look,
Xingyun's Ant Paradise
is nominated for the best
animation for children
at an animation festival.
Mr. Gu needs a date
to attend the event with him.
What should I wear
for that kind of occasion?
I don't even have a proper dress.
Don't care too much about it.
Those who are attending
it tomorrow are animators.
They're very casual.
Just wear
something that's comfortable.
You mean I don't have to dress formally?
I'll simply pick one then.
How about a T-shirt
of One Piece theme?
It matches the theme of
the anime and manga festival.
How about this?
Just pick
the most comfortable
outfit that fits you.
Nanzhou and I will meet up
with the committee at tomorrow noon.
Just come over at noon.
I'll send you the address later.
All right, thank you, Xuan.
Goodbye.
Hi.
Miss.
Pack this for me.
All right.
(I'm already at the venue.)
(Don't be late.)
(Okay, I'll depart right away.)
(Golden Apple Animation Festival)
(DAAF)
Okay.
This way, please.
Where are you?
I'm at the entrance.
On your left.
You...
I'm here.
Why are you dressed like this?
I...
Isn't this an anime and manga festival?
My attire matches the theme.
Qingqing,
you're dressed too casually.
Jingxuan,
didn't you tell me
to wear something that fits me?
Yes,
I meant something that fits you
and your demeanor,
but
this is too plain.
Do you think you're going on an outing?
(You're wearing a dress)
(yet you asked me to wear a T-shirt.)
(Forget it.)
(I volunteered to work for him.)
(I shouldn't be mad.)
Nanzhou,
it's Qingqing's first time
participating in such an event.
It's inevitable.
Why don't...
Go in her place.
Gu Nanzhou.
I didn't even finish drawing my comic.
I came all the way
to attend this
awarding ceremony with him,
yet he pulled a long face.
Who cares about it?
Jiang Jingxuan never forgets
what I tell her to do.
Don't care too much about it.
Those who are attending
it tomorrow are animators.
They'll dress casually.
Just pick
the most comfortable
outfit that fits you.
(So you're into Gu Nanzhou.)
(Why did you have to plot against me?)
(Do you think I'm a pushover?)
Golden Apple Animation Festival
begins now.
The nominees for best
animation for children
include
Tom's Morning.
The award of the best animation
for children goes to
Xingyun's production,
Ant Paradise.
Let's invite
Xingyun's CEO
Mr. Gu Nanzhou's fiancée
to collect the prize for him.
(Why isn't the introduction amended?)
♪You're the one who
makes me fall in love♪
I think that's Mr. Gu's fiancée instead.
How do you know?
I bumped into them at the entrance.
Let's go.
Come on.
♪My mind is composing a melody♪
♪Play a magical encounter♪
♪I walk into the trap slowly♪
♪I'm not used to such
weird frequency yet♪
♪But my mind is occupied by you♪
♪You're eccentric and willful♪
♪You're so captivating♪
The beautiful and elegant goddess
is always fashionably late.
A round of applause
for her speech, please.
♪Your smile is like a summer view♪
Do you know what to say on the stage?
If not, bring the speech.
♪When I open up my heart♪
It's unnecessary.
I used to earn a living
by memorising text.
Moreover,
even without it,
I can make a brilliant one, too.
♪I'll hold your palm with all my might♪
♪Experience the definition of love♪
♪You're the one who
makes me fall in love♪
Everyone must be curious
about why I'm collecting the prize
on behalf of my fiancé,
Mr. Gu Nanzhou.
Actually he's gone bald
as he's been staying up.
That's why
he's asking me to be here
to maintain his image.
♪I like you anyway♪
Actually,
I was just kidding.
My fiancé
still has a lot of hair.
However,
animators are leading a tough life.
This is true.
Although I didn't participate
in the making of Ant Paradise,
his devotion, hard work
and obsession and pursuit of art
were evident to me.
♪To say I do♪
♪I'll hold your palm with all my might♪
Ant Paradise
was already in the making
when Xingyun was founded.
Everyone told him
that creating original
work was challenging
and that it's safer
to use imported work.
However, he thought
certain things
must be done.
♪When I open up my heart♪
Actually, as part of the industry,
I have churned out many
pieces of illogical works
that had nothing but hype.
Many people in this industry know
what makes quick cash
and high return.
Those
who want to focus on doing great work
are eliminated instead.
However, my fiancé
chose to tread the seemingly
impossible path they took
♪Experience the definition of love♪
Although companies
who focus on the craft failed
and people are saying that
the animation industry is dying,
regardless
of others' objection,
he insisted on making
the moving animation.
That's Lake Xingling.
I can tell that
his passion and initial resolution
is as resilient as his hair.
♪I realize I don't mean what I say♪
Lastly,
I sincerely wish that
he and Lake Xingling
will go further in the future.
Thank you, everyone.
♪To say I do♪
♪I'll hold your palm with all my might♪
♪Experience the definition of love♪
♪You're the one who
makes me fall in love♪
Ms. Zhou,
what's the progress
of Lake Xingling?
Lake Xingling
is in production according to the plan.
Please look forward to it.
Ms. Zhou,
when will Lake Xingling
be shown?
Lake Xingling's actual show time...
Mr. Gu.
Depends on Xingyun's progress.
Can we talk?
What's your expectation
for the box office?
Please tell us.
(Yingqi Investment President)
Yes, tell us.
As long as Xingyun makes
what the audience loves,
we won't fare too badly
-at the box office.
-Of course.
What are you doing?
Qingqing,
you're careless.
You didn't even remove the label.
If others see this,
they might think
you're returning the dress
after wearing it.
Thank you, Ms. Jiang.
Don't mention it.
You've done Mr. Gu a huge favor.
I'm really happy for you.
If you're the one
who went on the stage today,
perhaps you would be even happier.
I'm
actually fairly approachable.
If you want anything,
I can give it to you.
It's just that...
What happened today
was due to miscommunication.
If you don't know anything,
you can ask me in advance.
After all,
I'm more knowledgeable than you.
Why is she pretending?
My label.
Why should I even try?
If she wanted to go,
I should've just let her go.
Why are you staying in the room?
Are you happy
with my performance today, Mr. Gu?
Mr. He from Yingqi Investment
approached me.
He said you did well.
Because of what you said,
he's interested in Xingyun
and Lake Xingling now.
Seriously?
Do you mean
Yingqi which produced
The Legend of the Valley?
I told you I am awesome, right?
If they really invest in you,
shouldn't you
pay me commission?
Your performance tonight
was indeed great.
Mr. He said
judging from your aura,
those who aren't familiar with you
might think you're a celebrity.
Of course.
Don't you know?
I used to be
a little princess in Nancheng.
Whenever I celebrated my birthday,
my father
would invite all famous people
in the city.
It's
even grander than this.
Such an awarding ceremony
is nothing to me.
Is this your label?
I accidentally ruined it.
Are you planning to
return it after wearing it?
Of course not.
It's just a dress.
It's not like I can't afford it.
Good.
I thought
of getting the company to reimburse it.
Okay,
please reimburse it, boss.
Didn't you say...
I really can't afford it.
Also, I came
to participate in Xingyun's event,
and pretend as your fiancée.
According to the agreement,
Party A should bear the cost, right?
What about Party B's professionalism?
I'm sorry.
Well,
the dress...
Look for Jiang Xiaochuan.
Thank you, boss.
Thank you.
For these problems,
fix them according to what I said.
Okay.
Zhou Jianqing.
Follow up with him.
Mr. Gu,
I think Qingqing went to the bathroom.
All right,
you may leave first.
Okay, Mr. Gu.
I can't even finish it.
How to submit it?
Hello.
How are things at your side?
The part you assigned to me
is basically done.
I'll adjust the details
before sending it to you.
You're indeed fast.
Can I assign you one more part?
I can't make it.
Qingqing,
you're being too much.
Please.
I'll pay you
an additional 20% in payment.
Today, my psychotic boss
has been monitoring me
for an unknown reason.
I tried to sneak away
and I almost had a heart attack.
I can't even slack at all.
Zhou Jianqing.
Are you in there?
I'm in.
Are you all right?
Mr. Gu is asking about you again.
Coming.
I'm really unwell today.
Hurry up.
Did you hear that?
I'll leave it to you.
Mr. He,
I'm flattered.
After listening to your
fiancée's speech yesterday,
I'm impressed by you,
who stay true to yourself
in producing good work.
Is it convenient for you
to send me information
of Lake Xingling?
Sure.
I'll let my assistant
send it to you now.
Yingqi ranks the top in the industry.
If we can work with Yingqi,
it'll surely enhance
Lake Xingling.
Don't worry.
Yingqi
would never miss a good story.
Thank you, Mr. He.
May we have a pleasant cooperation.
Goodbye.
Qingqing has been in the bathroom
the entire morning.
I wonder how she's doing.
Is she crying?
Her eyes were red just now.
I have no idea.
She looked tired
in the past two days.
She seemed troubled.
Is she...
(This girl)
(has been away and distracted all day.)
(Is it because)
(she can't bear to leave me?)
Nanzhou.
Mr. He read
the introduction of Lake Xingling.
He loves it.
He wants to talk to us face-to-face.
All right.
I didn't expect Qingqing's speech
had done us a huge favor.
She's quite capable.
Why don't you keep her in the company?
I'll consider it.
If you think it'll be troublesome,
you don't have to force it.
I'm just saying.
Nanzhou,
I know everything.
You two have been pretending
as an engaged couple.
You must have your own reasons.
How did you find out?
You don't have to lie to me.
You should've
told me about it.
Who knows
I could've given you suggestions.
It's my own matter.
I can handle it myself.
Why
did you pick her?
It's working hour now.
Let's not discuss personal matters.
You two...
Our relationship isn't real.
Xiaochuan,
you'll be discharged in two days?
Don't worry.
Now I'm really good
at making coffee now.
Okay.
That's all for now.
Bye.
(Nebula Carton)
Jiang Xiaochuan
is coming back in two days, right?
Yes.
We agreed on this.
As soon as he's discharged,
he'll replace me in work.
Do the handover with him then.
Yes, sir. Mr. Gu.
Jianqing,
the boss of the female leading character
is so lame.
Add some characteristics.
Characteristics.
How about Dugu Nanzhou.
Art indeed imitates life.
♪You're the one who
makes me fall in love♪
♪My mind is composing a melody♪
♪Play a magical encounter♪
♪The tears secretly cooperate♪
♪Like misunderstanding,
it drives the gap♪
♪Into a corner♪
♪I don't understand
what's wrong with us♪
♪Because it's still blinking♪
♪For your promise♪
♪I'm reluctant to part♪
♪The feeling of missing is more bitter♪
♪We slowly familiarize with each other♪
♪Hopefully love will make
the dream warm♪
♪I care deeply for you♪
♪Even if there's a distance♪
♪I care for you and protect you♪
♪Perhaps there's a sense of longing♪
♪It surpasses time♪
♪I go through the crowd to find you♪
♪As my heart beats, I gain courage♪
♪I want to become better for you♪
♪End the shivering♪
♪I care deeply about you♪
♪I still care deeply about you♪
♪I need your company♪
♪We go back to the same way♪
♪To be reunited♪
♪In each other's arms and be healed♪