(Hello Mr. Gu Theatre)
Hello. I've arrived. Where are you?
I'm behind you.
Move forward.
What are you doing?
Go on.
It's beautiful.
(Ways to confess your love in 10 dramas.
Confess your feelings now.)
I love you.
Zhou Jianqing.
I repeat.
I love you.
We've just met.
It has nothing to do with
how long we've known each other.
As soon as I first met you,
I confirmed that I fell for you.
I loved you deeply before you knew me.
♪You're the one who
makes me fall in love♪
♪My mind is composing a melody♪
♪Play a magical encounter♪
♪I walk into the trap slowly♪
♪Abandon the unimportant questions♪
♪It might make♪
♪The magical relationship closer♪
♪Your smile is like a summer view♪
♪It slowly grows in my heart♪
♪When I open up my heart♪
♪I realize I don't mean what I say♪
♪I realize you're getting ready, too♪
♪To say I do♪
♪I'll hold your palm with all my might♪
♪Experience the definition of love♪
♪A magical encounter♪
♪Becomes sweet♪
♪So we're meant to be♪
♪Instead of pondering reasons♪
♪Why don't we bravely
approach each other♪
♪It might turn into a dream♪
♪You're the one that
makes me fall in love♪
♪My mind is composing a melody♪
♪Play a magical encounter♪
♪Our gazes approach each other♪
=Hello Mr. Gu=
=Episode 19=
(You will never fail as long as
you never confess your love.)
Hello.
Gu Nanzhou.
I've arrived. Where are you?
I'm behind you.
I don't see you.
Where are you?
Move forward.
Gu Nanzhou.
What are you trying to do this time?
Go on.
♪The daily bickering♪
♪Is like meteor across the balcony♪
♪The moment I lift my head♪
♪My vulnerable heart is healed♪
Oh, no.
You...
Are you okay?
Did you ask me to come here for this?
It's purely an accident.
An accident?
You have the remote control.
How can you call it an accident?
I don't want you to catch a cold.
I don't want this!
Are you okay?
Do I look okay?
It's purely an accident.
Could it possibly be a coincidence?
I didn't want that to happen.
I thought you came to apologize.
You don't even know how to apologize.
Go away!
Sorry, it's my fault!
Tell me.
What did you want to say at the park?
I can't say it under such a circumstance.
You spilled water on me!
Sorry.
Where are you touching?
I didn't mean it.
Coming.
You've arrived. Come on in.
Why did you come here
early in the morning?
I...
I can't wait to tell you
a piece of good news.
Tell me now.
My oil painting won the first prize.
Isn't it a good news?
Is it true? First prize?
Congratulations.
Here comes a new oil painting master.
Sit.
I've won a prize, right?
There's a big amount of cash prize.
Why don't we travel?
Treat it as celebration.
Sure.
I haven't travelled for long.
What a great friend you are, junior.
Don't you need to rush your work?
Are you free to travel?
Forget it.
I'll go next time.
Wait until I finish my work.
Also,
a judge of the contest
has introduced a job to draw
comic for advertisements.
Do you want to work with me?
It can make money.
Sure, no problem.
I have an appointment
with the company later.
Shall we meet them later?
Sure.
Do you want to skip breakfast?
Also,
there is a restaurant selling
nice pan fried buns below their office.
Shall we try it?
Sure. Let's go.
Enjoy the breakfast yourself. Let's go.
Meeting in the big meeting room
in 10 minutes.
Sure, Mr. Gu.
You should treat the problem
I said seriously.
You'll get more than a scolding
if you make another mistake.
Okay, Mr. Gu.
I said I want creativity
and a sense of design.
What is the point of
sending old ideas with new names to me?
Is punctuation mark a minor mistake?
This document has shown
your work attitude.
-Redo it!
-Yes, Mr. Gu.
The scene has collapsed completely.
Don't think you can slack off,
though it only takes a few frames.
-Redo it!
-Yes, Mr. Gu.
Meetings for three consecutive days.
My eye wrinkles are coming out.
I don't think we're allowed
to get off from work.
Xiaochuan,
is something bothering Mr. Gu lately?
He has suddenly become so aggressive.
As the saying goes,
frustration in love
can only be healed with work.
He and Zhou Jianqing?
Have they broken up?
This explains why he is torturing us.
He wants to heal
a broken heart using work.
At first, they...
Mr. Gu,
I've made coffee for you.
Do you want to drink it here
or in your office?
Mr. Gu,
this is a love amulet I
brought back from Japan.
It's efficacious.
Wish you good luck in love.
Well,
Mr. Gu, I...
Mr. Gu, I wish you well in love.
Get ready for a meeting
in the big meeting room
in 10 minutes.
Nanzhou,
your work schedule is too full lately.
It's said that the new interns
intend to quit due to the high workload.
There're many problems to solve.
We need to work overtime.
You might be exhausted and collapse.
Those interns are
Zhou Jianqing's schoolmates.
Are you upset
by their conversations?
What did they say?
Don't you know?
I heard it randomly.
They said Zhou Jianqing
got quite close to a junior lately.
I think they're about to go steady.
Students love gossip.
Do you love gossip, too?
I'm just worried
it may affect the agreement
between you two.
You don't need to worry about that.
Nanzhou,
there is a new pub below our office.
Do you want to drink tonight to relax?
Have you compiled the documents
I gave you this morning?
Not yet.
Work overtime on it tonight.
Submit it tomorrow morning.
Mr. Chen of Jiangcheng will
come over this weekend.
You shall meet him.
You could talk about the new plan
of Lake Xingling.
Okay.
Camping at Mount Lumen?
It sounds interesting.
I have to check if I can make it
on the day after tomorrow.
I've checked it for you.
You don't need to go to school
nor meet any clients that day.
If you're okay,
we'll meet at Mount Lumen
on the day after tomorrow.
We'll come back after
spending a night there.
All right.
Let's do it.
See you in two days.
They will be alone.
They will even be camping.
In the real world,
bothered by his family and studies,
he is also estranged from
friends due to various reasons.
A'Ming gradually becomes dispirited.
Till one day,
he enters a bizarre world of stars
after a meteor shower.
Mr. Gu.
That's all for the adjustments.
Is it okay?
I heard all of you are
complaining about workload.
No.
Thanks for the hard work.
Tomorrow will be the company's holiday.
All of us will camp at Mount Lumen
to relax and get fresh air.
Do I hear it correctly?
-Is it true?
-That's wonderful.
Long live Mr. Gu!
Yes!
Isn't that the comic
club from our school?
That's right.
(It turns out they aren't alone.)
Mr. Gu,
it's Zhou Jianqing.
-She is there.
-I see her.
Go for it!
What a coincidence.
You two are here.
My club came to
Mount Lumen for inspiration.
Can I join you?
Mr. Gu, you're here.
Yes.
Are you...
Are you going to camp here as well?
We do have the plan.
Does it happen to be
a day and a night, too?
-That's right.
-What a coincidence.
Indeed.
So the team building is fake.
He came to monitor his wife.
Mr. Gu is really smart.
A man in love is scary.
That's certainly Mr. Gu.
Is there chocolate flavor?
How to open this?
Who wants chopsticks?
-Chopsticks.
-I want it.
There you go.
-Here.
-Move over.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
What should I get?
I...
Here is the extra portion.
Do you want it?
Not bad.
Your staff meal is sumptuous.
No.
I don't think you can eat
seafood when you have a cold.
A little should be fine.
No, Qingqing.
Seafood is stimulating food.
Your flu might get worse.
Why don't we settle it for you?
Let's eat.
It smells so good.
Qingqing.
Try my pork knuckles in
fermented black beans.
It's very delicious.
It smells so good.
It contains fermented black beans.
I suppose it's spicy.
You mustn't take spicy
food when you're sick.
It doesn't taste spicy at all.
It's spicy anyway.
Let us settle it for you.
-Hurry up.
-Give it to me.
It smells great.
Nice food.
It smells so great.
Try this grilled beef.
No beef steak.
Beef steak is oily.
A sick person shouldn't take oily food.
Give it to us.
That's right. Give it here.
We'll take it instead.
Qingqing,
I made this nuts tart.
Try it now.
I like it very much too.
It looks really good.
It's sweet.
You should take less sugar
when you are coughing.
I am not coughing.
Okay.
It's delicious.
Let me try that.
You're so mean.
Give me that.
Here you go.
Grilled mutton fresh from the stove!
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Let's drink.
-Come on!
-Cheers!
Let's play a game.
Sure.
How about omitting the multiples
of seven, the figure?
Sure.
Are you in, Mr. Gu?
-Mr. Gu.
-Join us.
You don't drink anyway.
I don't think you'll join us.
Don't provoke him.
He's really competitive.
What are you murmuring?
Why don't you rest if you're tired?
Who says I won't play?
Here.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Mr. Gu.
He lost.
Drink, Mr. Gu.
Carry on.
Okay.
-It's Mr. Gu again.
-He lost again.
It's Mr. Gu again.
Mr. Gu, I'll drink for you.
It's fine.
I'll drink it.
Good drinker!
Fantastic.
Mr. Gu.
We'll make a move first.
Bye.
Roaming in the world of martial arts,
getting injured is unavoidable.
Four stabs to kill you.
One stab to kill you.
Three stabs to kill you.
Drink it!
Drink it.
Go on.
Gu Nanzhou,
what were you thinking?
You're even so competitive in a game.
You took it seriously with Zhang Yin.
I love you.
Gu Nanzhou, wake up.
What did you say?
Do you really love me?
Listen.
I'll take it seriously
if you say it again.
Zhou Jianqing,
come to your senses.
He is drunk.
He might not even know who I am.
It means nothing.
I'm not drunk.
I told you I loved you.
I love you.
♪Even if there's a distance♪
♪I care for you and protect you♪
Gu Nanzhou!
Don't you love
Jiang Jingxuan all this while?
Why did you say you love me?
Wake up, Gu Nanzhou.
Gu Nanzhou.
Gu Nanzhou!
Make it clear.
Who do you really love?
♪End the shivering♪
Qingqing!
Qingqing, where did you
go the whole night?
I woke up twice, but I never saw you.
You have deep dark circles.
Did you stay up the whole night?
I think so.
I can only sleep on my own bed.
I went out to enjoy the breeze.
Qingqing.
(Shasha Camp)
Mr. Gu, we may leave now.
You must be thirsty, Qingqing.
How nice.
There're bubbles.
Let's go.
Get close. I'll take a picture.
Say cheese.
What a coincidence.
You came to refill water, too.
Yes.
There.
There, right?
I'll make a move first.
What a pleasant weather.
Isn't it cloudy?
Look at that beautiful tree.
It has withered.
Look at the grass.
It's dying.
Why do you have deep dark circles?
Your skin is dull.
Your hair is messy.
What happened to you last night?
Mr. Gu.
Yes, you know what?
-It's a nice trip.
-Yes, indeed.
I like that very much.
We're leaving.
Bye.
See you.
-Bye.
-Bye. I'll treat you next time.
-Okay, bye.
Bye.
Be careful.
-Give me the bag.
-Come here.
Give it to me.
Let go of me!
Aren't you going to take my car?
I'll take the school bus.
Do you want to go back by school bus
and walk home?
I can chat more with my classmates.
Why do I feel like you're avoiding me?
Last night you...
You finished a carton of beer
with Zhang Yin yesterday.
I was the one who sent
you back to the camp.
Thank you.
Is that all?
How should I thank you then?
Just tell me what happened.
Qingqing, let's go.
Our classmates are waiting.
Mr. Gu.
Shall I beat Zhang Yin up?
Go.
I'm outnumbered.
Next time then.
Nothing happened between you
and Zhou Jianqing last night, right?
Nothing happened.
Are you sure?
What are you trying to say?
After she sent you back to the camp,
I went to check on you
in case she couldn't handle it alone.
I saw her coming out and blushing.
-I thought...
-What were you thinking?
Aren't you busy with work?
I must have seen it wrongly.
I thought
maybe she did something wrong
when she took care of you.
You scolded her.
I'm not drunk.
I said I love you.
If...
It's just an assumption.
I have a friend.
He kissed a girl
while they didn't go steady.
-Did you kiss her?
-Not me.
I said it's my friend.
In this situation,
that's a forced kiss.
He is a terrible person.
What if he was drunk?
That can't be an excuse.
If you kiss a girl
before she agrees to date you,
she can sue you for sexual harassment.
Speaking of that,
it makes sense that she's angry.
I suppose your...
I mean your friend's
image in the girl's heart
has collapsed overnight.
Can it be restored?
Clarify it with her.
Tell her it's purely a drunken incident.
You had no intention to
take advantage of her.
After what happened,
you should display how calm
and polite you are as a gentleman.
Work hard to restore
your tainted image.
What else?
If it doesn't work,
bear responsibility for it.
Do you mean getting married?
You've made a deal with her anyway that
you two will get married
after her graduation.
It's just a ceremony.
We're not talking about me.
Yes. My bad.
Tell your friend to think about it.
Otherwise,
that girl might not want
to see him anymore.
♪You're the one who
makes me fall in love♪
♪My mind is composing a melody♪
♪Play a magical encounter♪
♪The tears secretly cooperate♪
♪Like misunderstanding,
it drives the gap♪
♪Into a corner♪
♪I don't understand
what's wrong with us♪
♪Because it's still blinking♪
♪For your promise♪
♪I'm reluctant to part♪
♪The feeling of missing is more bitter♪
♪We slowly familiarize with each other♪
♪Hopefully love will make
the dream warm♪
♪I care deeply for you♪
♪Even if there's a distance♪
♪I care for you and protect you♪
♪Perhaps there's a sense of longing♪
♪It surpasses time♪
♪I go through the crowd to find you♪
♪As my heart beats, I gain courage♪
♪I want to become better for you♪
♪End the shivering♪
♪I care deeply about you♪
♪I still care deeply about you♪
♪I need your company♪
♪We go back to the same way♪
♪To be reunited♪
♪In each other's arms and be healed♪