This program was created with the support of the Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, Korea's Creative Content Agency, and Media Content.
Episode 7
No. It's not the time for you to worry about a woman, Moo Hyul!
Ip Shin Yang Myeong.
(To succeed and gain world recognition)
That's right. Just think of Grandma.
Grandma.
Warrior-nim.
Do you want to go with me?
Where are you going?
Ham Joo. I'm on my way to Ham Joo
Ham Joo?
Yes.
To Ham Joo where General Lee Seong Gye is.
If you join General Lee Seong Gye's forces and fight the Japanese pirates,
you will immediately be acknowledged by General Lee Seong Gye and your name will be widely known.
My name will be known?
Yes. It's doing Ip Shin Yang Myeong.
Among the warriors I have seen so far, you are the best.
Yes, let's go.
Ham Joo.
That person
is where Father is. Ham Joo.
Then, the owner of the cave is gathering people at Ham Joo?
This no ordinary matter.
It's an organization trying to destroy Goryeo. They are even using a secret code.
Am Eo: A secret code only select people can decipher
That kind of organization is hiding at the General's base...
- Let's go.
- Yes!
I will get the horses running to Ham Joo right away.
No. To Gaegyeong.
Pardon?
We need to go to Gaegyeong first.
G-Gaegyeong?
What is going on? Is everything connected to Sam Bong?
Why did the Bi Guk Temple monks do that, and who was the warrior who saved the woman?
I think Hong In Bang is the mastermind.
What do you mean by Hong In Bang?
Hong In Bang came out of the monk's room.
(Gab Boon)
Enter.
Did you hear back from the boys that are tracking the kids?
Yes.
Where are they headed?
Their destination is still unknown but we have been informed that they're going north.
North, you say?
What could this person be doing in Ham Joo?
Jeong Do Jeon's book about building the stronghold of the revolution
Jin
Chae
(Jin Chae: A base where military troops gather)
Gye
(Gye: Strategy/Plan)
What's the matter?
Jo Young Gyu
Why didn't you tell Young Master Bang Woo?
If it's something concerning Ham Joo, then your eldest brother, Young Master Bang Woo—
You must never tell him.
Surely not to Bang Woo Hyung-nim. Also not to those in Ham Joo, General Lee Ji Ran, Bang Gwa Hyung-nim, Father...
We cannot tell anyone about what has happened up to now.
Then, I cannot go with you.
I was born and raised in Ham Joo.
I have always thought proudly of my parents and the whole military troop.
In that Ham Joo, in that military troop, unknown people have infiltrated.
No! We're not even sure if a lot of people have already gone in there, but
you're telling me to just shut my mouth? That's betrayal!
It's not betrayal!
Ham Joo is...
a base.
Base?
What is that?
It's the base of a revolution.
The stronghold for a revolution.
That person
has chosen Father's Ham Joo as a revolutionary base.
Who is that person?
That's what I'm also trying to find out.
It doesn't make sense! To betray because of a person we don't even know—
We don't know who he is but I know what he's going to do!
What is it?
What is he going to do?
This won't do. I have to tell Young Master Bang Woo.
Goryeo...
This rotten Goryeo...
What?
That person is going to end this rotten Goryeo and establish a new country.
And I
will make sure to do that with him
Goryeo has disappointed me,
frustrated me,
and left me sapped of my strength.
Then, we can just tell the General.
Don't you know Father?
That person has made a perfect plan to establish a new country but has left out one thing.
What is it?
That person I call Father.
He left out that person, Lee Seong Gye.
If Father finds out about the truth,
that person will die.
Then this revolution will also end.
Please help me. I beg of you.
Ham Joo, Lee Seong Gye's military troop barracks
Soldiers were reading this in the barracks, so brought it.
Please take a look.
Isn't it impressive?
If it goes this way, wouldn't it be really good for us?
Who wrote this?
That, I do not know.
Soldiers were looking at it one day.
Still, whoever wrote this, the content is really good.
How about if we submit this to the government.
This is not going to happen.
Lee Seong Gye
It won't work and it will bring suspicion from the government.
But—
Did you not consider this might have been written by a spy?
Based on what I'm hearing I agree, Brother.
Just discussing it would cause the government to suspect us of treason.
Lee Ji Ran
Bang Gwa, find the person who wrote this.
Didn't you hear your uncle?
Yes. I understand.
Assign it to 1st class military officer Lee Shin Jeok.
He's the most trustworthy and he'll surely do it well.
Sir, thank you very much.
- Follow me.
- Yes.
Next!
Lady, it seems that they don't accept just anyone here.
That's because in the whole land of Goryeo, this a place that tries to feed people.
That's why homeless people gather here. Even people from the North come here.
How do you pass?
That, I don't know...
You bastard! This is not a place where you can enter after committing a crime!
It's not that. It's something that I couldn't control.
Please—
Arrest this person and let the Ham Joo government office know.
Yes!
Then, at least let my children in!
Please at least let my children in!
Sir, Sir!
Next!
Who are you and where are you from? What's your reason for coming here?
Slowly explain it.
Even the slightest lie and you will be severely punished. Do you understand?
I am Boon Yi from Yi Seo Geun (Western district).
This is Ham Joo!
Ah! After coming to Ham Joo, I now feel good.
Hurry and let's go! Let's meet Young Master Bang Gwa and the General.
No.
What is it again?
Before meeting them, we need to figure out what's going on in Ham Joo.
So what are you going to do?
You know a lot of people from here, right?
Are you going to say it like that? Of course, I know everyone from Ham Joo!
Fine. I'll go to an inn first and you secretly infiltrate and
try to find out what Father has been doing these days. Don't let yourself get caught.
We,
from a 5-year-old child to a 80-year-old man,
daily visited that wasteland by removing one rock at a time,
planting the crops and watering them.
I've spent three years like that.
Then, on that day,
the day we'd been hoping for,
was the first harvest, but...
Did you get that taken away from you as well?
I just
said that they can take it.
For something like that,
they can take it and we will just start over.
Like an idiot, it wasn't worth it, it was just food,
and they died while protecting it?
How can they can just kill them for that?
That's why I...
All of the stolen crops,
I burned them.
What? What did you say?
Memorial Service to go with them in paradise.
No.
Although they may wonder for 9000 years,
at least they will be full.
What should we do?
Send her to 13 base.
Let's go.
This is unbelievable, unbelievable!
They raised the tax last time as well. Now with tax going up to 90%, what are the people supposed to do?
Shouldn't we just kill them all?
After hearing all those shocking stories I'm not surprised any more.
These bastards!
Brother!
After winning back Ssang Sseong Colonial Office,
After I was born... A lifetime!
Stuck out here at the border and fighting foreign enemies.
In the mean time all my soldiers died.
All my people who have died thus far, what has spilling their blood accomplished?
The people are becoming increasingly impoverished.
Lee In Gyeom! Gil Tae Mi!
Hong In Bang! These three ministers!
Day by day.
Brother...
This nation,
doesn't get better even by just a bit.
We have fought for so long.
We have endured! But this nation
has not improved. Not even in the slightest.
Not even by a bit.
Come over here.
You should stop crying now.
Father Pal Bong, just wait for a little bit.
I have passed one obstacle now.
Bang Gwa brought a document from military camp, and suggested submitting it to the government.
General said it might be a spy, so he gave the order to capture the author of the document.
What's in it?
That, I don't know either.
The General, General Lee Ji Ran, and Young Master Bang Gwa—only these three saw it.
I think the content must be extraordinary.
Where is it? I have to see it.
That's probably with the person investigating it.
If they're going to look for the person who wrote it, wouldn't they be comparing and checking handwriting?
Who is investigating it?
Lee Shin... Lee Shin Jeok? They said he's the Jin Mu Bu Ui.
- Lee Shin Jeok?
- Yes.
It's been three years since he came here. It's my first time hearing that name.
I have brought everyone.
It's here.
Okay, everyone. Write the character "An" for peace.
That person is Lee Shin Jeok.
Looking at his clothes, it has got to be him. That person has the documents.
Next, write the character "Bang" for country.
But Bang Won, you must not do anything reckless.
Brother Heo Gang?
Contrast handwriting
Among these people, there is nobody with the same handwriting.
Tomorrow we will broaden the scope of the investigation. Go deliver the message to Lee Bang Gwa.
Yes.
Three.
Why? Did you forget something?
Brother Heo Gang.
I was worried about you, Brother Heo Gang.
After I came here, I knew I would see you someday.
It's a relief that you're looking good. How have you been all this time?
I have abandoned that name, Heo Gang.
Anyway, I am no longer Heo Gang. I am Lee Seong Gye's troop's 1st military officer, Lee Shin Jeok.
- Still, Brother—
- So I'm definitely not your brother anymore.
I just want to follow General to war and start a new life.
- He uses his left hand.
- Who? That Heo Gang person?
No. Lee Shin Jeok.
Heo Gang uses his right hand.
So what?
In all of Ham Joo, about a hundred or so people can write.
But out of those investigated they didn't find the writer.
Could it be?
Could it be what?
We'll know once we get there.
Go? Where?
Let's go in.
What is that? We have to get out soon.
"Prepare the people for military training in peacetime
to prepare for foreign aggression."
That's just an obvious thing. Let's go out and talk. Let's go!
New furnishing number one.
"Combine 100 units in to 1 section"
All of the people
belong to General's military camp."
Ah, putting together the military and agriculture? It's easy to say but that one is difficult!
Let's get out.
Using the tax collected from the northeast region
to create a self-sufficient governing nation.
Ah! Provisions from taxes?
What? To be independent?
If it's like this..
If it's the Northeast, either the military or the administrative part
will be independent.
Sure, so it was that all along.
Bang.
a country. (Bi Bang)
Bang(a country) Bi Bang(area not a country)
A region that's not part of the country, the Northeast,
will become an independent region.
It will become the base of a revolution!
Let me take a look.
To be able to do this, there are two plans.
An. Byeon. Chaek.
That's right. This is the An Byeon Chaek!
It sounds good but will this be accepted by the government?
There must have been a plan make this happen. That's why it was submitted to my father.
The problem is...
More than the government office,
it will be harder to go through the General. Is that it?
That's right. That's why he needs me.
You've worked hard.
We have to follow him.
Why?
That An Byeon Chaek... Lee Shin Jeok put it out.
Brother Heo Gang is right-handed.
Did you say you are Boon Yi from the Western district?
Yes, that's correct.
However, why are you like this? How—
What is this?
That... It was made by my mother's friend--
Shut up!
We have intelligence information that there have been spies sneaking into camp as migrants
and this figurine is proof.
Just tell the truth.
No, I...
I really do not know what you're saying.
What is that organization? What is it about spies?
I don't do things such as torture.
I can just catch the spies.
I'm going to ask you one more time, with what motive
did you go into Ham Joo?
I've been suspicious of you since the homeless people inspection.
Don't even think about getting away. Just answer my questions.
Before entering, my belongings were searched.
Of course you would have discovered the wooden soldier.
But why didn't you arrest me right then?
- That's because I have to observe you and—
- Yes.
You could release me first and ask me who I'm in contact with. After identifying me, you could just arrested me.
I still haven't contacted anyone and yet you arrested me in the middle of the night!
Also, not in the barracks but deep in the forest.
What is this woman saying?
Also, after looking at it, this person
is surely from General Lee Seong Gye's 3rd barracks.
But how is it that you brought soldiers who belong to the 3rd barracks and are doing investigation?
Elder Military Officer.
If I'm correct,
I am not being investigated.
Currently, right here,
I am being tested for something.
Am I wrong?
You have the same necklace as mine.
I will put my life on the line.
I don't have time.
I have village people waiting for me.
I have things to tell him and things I need to ask.
Please tell that person that Boon Yi from Lee So Geun has come and he should keep his promise!
This is the secret order.
"Close down the seven strongholds and gather into Ham Joo.
Be one of Lee Seong Gye's people."
Coming to Ham Joo,
I welcome you.
Young Master, now...
Aigoo. Please stop! You said you have something important to do.
I have to do it. That important thing.
With those people.
It's that bastard.
We just have to take that bastard to Head Monk Jeok Ryong at Bi Guk Temple.
Who is this? If it isn't the fake monk Jeok Ryong?
Seriously, what in the world.
A monk going into the gisaeng house during the day.
This is really tasty. It's fits my taste buds.
I heard you can buy few houses with few baskets of these.
We're not close enough to be joking around like this.
Why? What's the matter?
Jeok Ryong.
What do you think I came to buy from an information merchant?
Obviously to buy information.
The head of Bi Guk Temple came to Hwa Sa Dan to buy information?
Who killed Baek Yoon?
Give me the info and swallow that.
We're both doing business.
People in Songak say this ...
Hong In Bang probably killed Baek Yoon.
Why?
Because Hong In Bang gained the most after Baek Yoon was killed.
Hong In Bang is your best customer, but that Jeok Ryong of Bi Guk Temple
came to me, of all people,
to ask about who killed Baek Yoon.
You don't know?
Yahhhh...I'm really disappointed.
It's something that happened in Gaegyeong so the Hwa Sa Dan should know about it.
When are you going to use your trick?
The legendary girls, the most beautiful ones.
Does she really exist?
Stop talking nonsense.
The reason why you suddenly became curious about me,
I want to buy that information.
Something came up in connection to Baek Yoon's killer, right?
If it't not that, then you wouldn't be curious about something that's already on trial.
How is it? Are you going to sell it?
Fine. There is some kind of organization.
We caught a person involved with that organization and were doing an investigation.
A swordsman possessing skills that are unheard of came and rescued that person.
Where? Right in front of my eyes.
What kind of organization is it?
I don't know. She was taken away before we could investigate. But originally there's no sword skill like that.
No matter how much I looked, I couldn't figure out who it was.
So wouldn't that swordsman be Baek Yoon's killer?
I thought about this.
We weren't originally chasing after a secret organization, but
someone asked me to look for someone, and
while doing so, things got more complicated. That's everything. We're done, right?
The person you were looking for... Who is it?
Jeong Do Jeon.
There will be movement soon. Watch carefully.
Yes.
Since I've already thrown the bait, Cho Yeong, that wench, won't be able to stay still.
Find out about what happened in Bi Guk Temple during the past days.
Go to the center of your assigned identity and region.
Grab ahold of all information and report it.
Investigate Baek Yoon's death from the start and report it.
Yes!
Should we also communicate with Ja Il Saek?
No. Until Ja Il Saek contacts us personally,
never interfere.
Yes, I understand.
Elder Hong In Bang is here.
It's been a long time since we've met..
Where are you returning from?
We've been looking for you for a long time.
Why?
Choi Yeong came and made a commotion.
(Gil Tae Mi)
It's because of the Western district. He said that if the taxes are not rolled back, the alliance will be broken.
So? are you scared?
Scared? It's just that I thought it might be a problem.
There's a misunderstanding regarding Elder Baek Yoon's death.
Firstly, I would like to apologize.
Well, I'll accept your apology.
Sit.
I wanted to ask you once.
Since we met like this, I'll just ask anyway.
Yes, of course. Say what you have to, please.
About that land which reached it's limit. Taxes at 90%.
Yes.
Because of that, Lee In Gyeom is suffering from Choi Yeong.
You don't have to worry about that.
Don't worry? But what if, with one blow...
They won't be able to do it anyway.
How?
To run a country, a lot of things need to be included.
Where would the soldiers we need to fight off Japanese pirates come from?
If not for us, this country wouldn't function.
Could it be that the reason why you didn't go to Lee In Gyeom, although he called for you, is...
I am not rebelling against Lee In Gyeom.
But we have to arrange the rankings according to the level that fits us.
We can decrease the taxes to 70%.
Lee In Gyeom should also consult us about the country,
and, in all, should earn our consent. That's what I'm saying.
Yes. Instead of giving us orders, he should consult with us.
In that way, we will also gain power.
Yes. Is there anything that you can't do more than Yi Ui Min?
Garnering strength, you should be 'a man under one but above many.'
Okay, let's drink to Elder Gil Tae Mi joining
the Mun Ha Shi Jung in the future.
(Mun Ha Shi Jung: Goryeo's highest government office)
Cheers.
Do you really not know?
That man, Hong In Bang, is checking you out right now.
Without them, the country cannot function,
but I'm saying that they shouldn't just do as they please.
[Choi Yeong]
I.
I'll take care of it and restrain it, General.
Do you have a plan?
I'm asking if you have an alternative for those people.
An alternative...
Lee In Gyeom
There has to be an alternative.
If it's Lee Seong Gye,
it is a possibility.
But...
Should I call Lord Hong In Bang back to Do Hwa Jeon?
Stop it, it's enough.
What's that commotion?
Didn't they finish the morning ceremony of placing Buddha's statue?
Yes. It has ended but there was an astrologer from the west with them.
It appears that the woman is looking at people's fortunes.
They said she came from the West.
Are you reading constellations?
I'm trying to match the movements of Cheon Gi to human affairs.
I was word in January of the year of 1318.
I have been pondering on something these days.
What should I do?
It is the Cheon Gi Seong.
(Cheon Gi Seong: name of the star)
Fire penetrated the wood and couldn't reach Tae Baek.
(She's explaining his constellation)
At the moment, there is no visible path, whether to the front or to the back.
There is no way?
You're saying one who originally has concerns cannot do anything.
In that note, it could be described as Hok Se Mu Min.
(Hok Se Mu Min: A ploy to disturb the world and deceive people)
Enjoy that as a form of entertainment.
There is a path for you upward.
Upward, you say?
The top of Cheon Goong is the north.
Yeon Hee
If the Buk Nak Sa Mun can be seen in the sky, it will bring good luck.
Buk Nak Sa Mun?
(Could mean the fish constellation or the military force at the northern border)
It's a star protecting the northern sky.
In this land, it would be the northeast.
Seeing the look on your face, it seems that you have figured out the answer.
If you follow your heart
fortune will come from the star of the Shepherd.
Star of the Shepherd in the northeast?
A surname that has Wood Mok in it...
Surname Lee. Lee Seong Gye.
(Mok Character: meaning of Lee Seong Gye's surname)
Surely,
is that person the only alternative?
Ham Joo
Is the work not tiring?
Indeed, there are a lot of clothes to wash.
But if you compare it to farming, then it's nothing much.
If you don't have anything else to say, then I'll leave now.
I see. You may leave.
Bon Won wants to see you. Look ahead.
Following the stream where you do laundry, if you go down about five units, there will be a trail.
If you follow that path, there will be a stone tower. Wait there.
How did that girl know Bon Won?
From Western district,
Boon Yi.
Meddlesome, mannerless, and reckless.
She can lie really well and will bite when she's angry.
You should be careful too, Brother.
As I told you, I am not your brother.
Let's have a talk.
I've nothing to say to you.
"Break down the seven walls
and gather in Ham Joo."
Lady.
Lady. I'm up here.
Oh, sir! What are you doing up there?!
I'm doing first level training.
First level. As you may know, I'm not someone who should be doing first level training, right?
Right?
Still, you have to start from the bottom and slowly take your chances.
Hurry and go back to your position. Understand?
Then.
Lady— Lady!
This isn't it...
You said I was best....
I almost fell off.
Ahjussi.
Even though I'm not sure,
you already know that much. Now, you called me out here, defenseless, to a quiet place. What's next?
Who is it?
Who is on top of this and leading your organization?
Lee Shin Jeok
If I get caught, I would bite my tongue off here and die.
Whatever you try, that person is-—
Father wants to meet that person.
For what that organization is doing, don't they need Father?
Then why didn't they pass the An Byeon Chaek?
An Byeon Chaek: A plan to stabilize the border
General knows about it too?
Yes and he wants to meet that person.
Tonight at Ja Shi, the place is at the memorial shrine of Hong Yoon Myo.
(Ja Shi: Between 11pm and 1am)
You and that person. My father and I. Just four people. Everyone should be unarmed.
Please keep that promise.
Pardon?!
You said General really wants to meet that person?
Yes! Finally, the General is getting involved!
I'm lying.
Father never said that.
Young Master, are you insane?
Why would you do that?
Father is like a mountain,
and this is something that requires moving a mountain.
I'll meet that person before him.
Then, with that person, I will move a mountain.
I'll do that, for sure.
I've met him.
Thank you for helping me out.
Okay. What did he decide to do?
Ajussi said to use me as a messenger.
'Ajussi'?
Never mind.
Read it.
It's okay for me read to you?
Bon Won said that
he trusts you, so I guess I will do that too from now on.
If General Lee Seong Gye's reaction to the An Byeon Chaek is like that, then I will personally—
I'll meet Lee Seong Gye in person.
It's difficult but make it possible.
Does Bon Won think that way as well?
But will the General meet him?
Actually, it's already been arranged.
I heard that General Lee Seong Gye wants to meet that person himself.
Oh. That's good then even if I'm not sure.
That side proposed it first?
They know about our organization?
That's why they asked to arranged this meeting.
Sure, I'll get going now.
But what if it's a trap?
General Lee is not someone who would do that.
Yes.
I know it isn't my place,
but in this world I grew up in, there's no such thing
as "that kind of person, not that kind of person".
Right there.
We decided to meet there.
I'll wait right here.
If General Lee Seong Gye shows up, I'll go to Ajussi and let him know.
If anything strange happens outside, immediately blow on this thing.
Yes.
Are you really alright?
Will he really come out?
What if it's a trap?
Stay here and watch. If needed, you must come running right away.
I would be running, but...
Ah, really, can he really do this without the General's permission?
Please, please be there, you must be there.
Why are you alone?
Why did you come alone then?
He will come soon.
That person will come soon too.
It's past the promised time, how?
You didn't lie to me so that I would bring him to you?
It was a trap!
It isn't a lie.
We decided that I would greet him first and then meet my father.
If you wait a bit more...
So it was a trap. Lee Bang Won.
Darn it. I knew this would happen.
Young Master.
Ahjussi!
Ahjussi, there's a huge problem!
General, General, General!
Wait, what's the ruckus?
Just now, Young Master Bang Won got kidnapped.
What are you talking about?
How did he get kidnapped?
Bang Won? How is that he is here?
Um, that..
Just spit it out!
I'll tell you everything.
Aiyo. Was it wrong to come here?
Shouldn't I just have caught the Viper?
What should I do with this person?
He is injured. It's too much to drag two people with us.
Just kill him.
What are you guys?
Hurry and escape. It's Bon Won's order.
What are you talking about?
Please come out for a little bit. I have something to tell you.
I have a servant protecting me.
I saved you again.
It must be our fate.
Please be quiet.
My servant has probably reported everything.
He probably misunderstood that I got kidnapped.
The soldiers have probably already been mobilized.
Leave me, go ahead and block it.
Tell them that I am safe and it's all a misunderstanding.
If he's already reported everything, then my identity must have already been found out. Do you think they will believe me?
You should be the one to stop it. Go!
You. Can you run while carrying me on your back?
Me? Why?
Bang Won!
Young Master!
I will slit this wench's throat.
Between you wenches, I already know that there is a secret organization.
I also know that those bastards kidnapped our young master.
It's not me. It's really not me!
Confess.
Where is he?
Tell me!
If not, your neck will be separated from your head.
You guys are going to stay quiet?
Then, I will cut this wench's head off first and ask again.
Stop, stop!
He wasn't kidnapped.
We've found Bang Won!
He's safe.
But!
It is true that you have bad intentions for coming into Ham Joo.
General.
I will take this opportunity to fish out that organization
so it doesn't happen again.
All the things you told me, are they all just lies?
About your village's people dying and about that young girl, Uh Nyeon's death,
and the tears you have shed.
No, It isn't a lie.
It's not just me. The homeless people who gathered here in Ham Joo for the past years
are all the same.
In this whole land of Goryeo, I only have my small self.
That's why I came here. It's the truth.
If not for you taking us in, all of us
are just people who would be corpses rotting on the walkways.
The reason why that person
sent us to you, General, is because our despair, hopes,
and dreams will be accepted.
I think that is the meaning of being saved in this world.
Then who is it?
Reveal everything. General is asking.
That person...
Right here.
I am that person.
Ahjussi..
Ahjussi?
That, that person..!
War should not be decided by those who have power!
It's not something that can be decided by old people.
That man is the Jantgar.
Jantgar: Strongest man
The owner of the New Joseon is Jangpyeong Gate's Jantgar.
It's me. Jeong Do Jeon.
Six Flying Dragons
Do you think I will waver because of one word from a scholar I just met?
- He's a person we can trust.
- I will not do it.
I'm asking you why you called Lee Seong Gye to block my path.
I'm thinking of helping you.
What exactly are you saying?
I need you, Brother, and you also need me.
What are you? What are you doing?
- Why is it me?
- I'm going to defeat those three people and establish a new country.
I chose you.