This program was created with the support of the Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, Korea's Creative Content Agency, and Media Content.
Did the General
Episode 36
agree to this?
Young Master! I asked if the General agreed to this.
No.
I am the one doing it.
I, Lee Bang Won.
What about his bodyguard?
Does it matter? You're the best swordsman in the Three Kingdoms.
One servant and another petite person who looks like a girl
were waiting while holding swords.
Could it be...
Before Teacher Po Eun goes into the palace,
he has to die.
Sam Bong: Jeong Do Jeon
Sam Bong, it's better for you to resent me
but I have to do this to protect the country.
Will all the fighting end by tomorrow?
Why are you asking that?
I just want it to end as soon as possible.
It will. We have to quickly end it.
You're also having a hard time, right?
Aren't you?
It pains me but it's something that I have to do, so I have no choice.
Fighting is also hard on me.
Blood thirst...
Is something wrong?
You should make haste and go back to the palace.
Is someone following us?
I will be there soon.
Lady! Is Young Master inside?
No matter how I look, I couldn't find him. Young Gyu Hyung-nim and Bang Ji weren't there either.
It seems that Young Master didn't tell you.
About what?
Did Young Master go somewhere?
Are you following Lord Po Eun?
Because Cheok Sa Gwang is a woman.
Are you perhaps...
So you're Lee Bang Ji, the best swordsman of the Three Kingdoms.
Why are you following Lord Po Eun?
Are you going to kill Lord Po Eun?
I have a long-time dream buried in my heart that I couldn't fulfill.
A dream?
It's to end Goryeo.
Perhaps... Did he go to kill Lord Po Eun?
Please be quiet.
Tell me! Young Master, Bang Ji, and Young Gyu Hyung-nim. Did they really go to kill Lord Po Eun?
Yes.
Damn it. Where is it? Where did they go?
Why are you being like that?
- They will all die.
- What?
Young Master Bang Won, Bang Ji, and Young Gyu Hyung-nim. They will all die.
What does that mean?
Cheok Sa Gwang is there. Where is it? Hurry!
It's probably on the way to the palace.
Palace.
But I couldn't send you to Lord Po Eun before you kill me.
Are you Cheok Sa Gwang?
Yes.
I've wanted to fight you at least once anyway.
That's what I despise the most. That kind of warrior's competitiveness.
Fortunately, you have a long life.
Is that so?
That's right. A really long life. As long as you don't meet the reaper.
Reaper? What is that?
In the life of a swordsman, there's a time when you will meet it.
A reaper can just be your luck on that day, the weather,
or at other times, it could even be the sudden urge to poop.
It could also be an amazing master (swordsman).
What if I meet it?
You have to hope that you won't meet it.
Teacher, I think I've met the reaper.
For a warrior, it is a very common thing
for his corpse to be left lying there in the mountains forever unfound.
Warrior-nim, you are very strong so
I can't fight while being careful of your life.
I'm sorry.
Dying is not the problem. If we can't catch Po Eun tonight, it will be the end.
Lee Bang Won, you're doing it properly, right?
He blocked this. Let's finish it quickly.
So you're out of breath, Cheok Sa Gwang.
It seems that Lee Bang Won will attack Po Eun.
Lee Bang Ji went out with the Ga Byeol Cho. Moo Hyul also followed them.
Mugeuk!
Then, will Po Eun die?
But Lord Po Eun's side has Cheok Sa Gwang.
If Lee Bang Ji and
Cheok Sa Gwang fight, what will happen?
If I consider my experiences of fighting each of them,
Lee Bang Ji will die.
So you don't have to worry.
The Goksan swordsmanship can look impressive but it's actually simple.
This swordsmanship is familiar.
Could it be...
And she's become slower than when we started.
What's your relationship with the leader of the Wudang Clan?
He's my Teacher.
Our ill-fated relationship is deeper than I thought it was.
I have to make him run.
I have better stamina than her. I mustn't let her rest.
It wasn't a deep cut so why?
You...
It's your first time getting cut by a sword since you were born, right?
I didn't think this would take so long.
If someone else followed Lord Po Eun's side...
Let's quickly end this.
He's still alive.
Bang Ji. Cheok Sa Gwang.
This warrior is confident with his defense.
He'll definitely block it instead of avoiding. Let's end this.
Maincham.
No.
Don't block it! Move!
It can't be like this.
The thing about weakness is
that it doesn't just apply on swordsmanship, but to people as well.
People?
I actually
don't have much experience in fighting.
No matter how good the swordsmanship is, if she lacks fighting experience, it would be hard for her to respond to an unexpected situation.
Unexpected situation.
He threw away his sword.
Hesitating in an unknown situation.
I terribly hate to kill.
Hesitate, Cheok Sa Gwang.
Moo Hyul!
- What's with you?
- When morning comes,
are you going to execute Teacher Sam Bong and our people?
Since you guys tried to overthrow the country, your punishments won't be taken lightly.
Can't you really give up on this country?
This is the country where I was born and grew up.
This land where my family and I
and my colleagues grew up.
If I turn my back on this country, how can I call myself a Confucian scholar?
Country...
Country, you say?
You bastard. Are you going to use the people as an excuse?
You told me before to not sell the people out,
so I took another good look at the people.
But the thing about the people is
they don't care what happens to the country.
So are you saying that those pitiful people want a new country?
To those people, whether it happens this or that way,
what does it matter to them?
Whether you protect the country or Teacher Sam Bong establishes a new country,
it doesn't matter to those people.
The people are fine as long as they have food and are happy with life.
You're selling the people out again.
Even if the kudzu vines on Mansu Mountain are all intertwined,
what is wrong with that?
Teacher Sam Bong and you were intertwined like that, so
if you could hold hands and make the people enjoy life,
who would dare disgrace you with his petty brush in the history that you so cherish?
The people, you say?
The people enjoying life...
Listen well.
A Confucius scholar does not chase after the people.
It's about embracing the people and guiding them.
To embrace them, a country and system are needed.
And a Confucian scholar's heart towards that is called patriotism.
If he abandons that patriotism, then the people in his heart will disappear as well.
Whatever
happens tonight,
are you still not going to change your mind?
Can we really not get you to our side no matter what we do?
That's such a petty threat.
Look here.
General Lee Seong Gye and Sam Bong.
Whatever they do, the only thing that they can gain
are Goryeo and this body just over a 100 geuns (unit of weight).
Try to kill me over and over again.
Try to kill me a hundred times over. Even if my bones rot
and my body become the soil
and become dust,
this one piece in my body, the unwavering and passionate heart I had towards this country,
you will not be able to get it.
That heart is indeed admirable.
Yes.
I understand what you mean,
Teacher.
Ah! There's actually one thing that you will get.
A thousand years of bad reputation.
Starting tomorrow, you will be entangled with my name, Jeong Mong Joo, for a thousand years,
and it will be recorded and be the talk of the town.
Try hard to endure it!
Yes! I will!
If I can't be entangled with you in this life,
I will at least try to be entangled with you after death
and enjoy it for thousands of years.
Young Gyu!
Sam Bong, it went according to you.
I tried to serve with my life for the thousand year history of Goryeo.
But this country has come to an end,
and I ended up living the thousand years.
Isn't this just ridiculous?
Was Cheok Sa Gwang defeated?
Fate is indeed capricious.
What happened here?
I think he's someone with a high position.
Isn't that Teacher Po Eun? Look.
Aigoo! You're right! What's going on here?
Aigoo! Lord Jeong Mong Joo! What's happening?
Come out.
Why are you doing this?
Isn't the execution at myoshi (5am-7am)?
Hyung.
It's okay. Are you okay?
Yes. Well, I've done even worse things than this.
But why am I trembling like this?
You've done a great thing. A great thing.
What will happen now?
A lot of things will probably change. Immediately, by tomorrow, a lot will change.
What?
Tell me again.
What are you saying?
Lord Po Eun was murdered at Seonjuk Bridge.
It was done by Lee Seong Gye's fifth son, Lee Bang Won.
Po Eun...
How did this happen...
How?
But Your Majesty, you need to control your emotions and be steadfast.
Po Eun!
Po Eun? What did you say happened?
Was he really murdered?
Yes.
Yes, Teacher.
This cannot happen.
How can Po Eun...
How can Po Eun end up like that?
Teacher...
It's probably done by Lee Seong Gye's people.
Just what are we going to do with these traitorous crooks!
Hyung-nim.
Don't be so surprised when you listen to what I say.
Lord Po Eun, when he was returning to the palace from here last night,
he was murdered.
He was murdered? Just who would...?
I think Bang Won did it.
Okay. Let's go!
Ah! You startled me.
Why are you all here like this?
What happened to my brother?
What happened to my Moo Hyul? My Moo Hyul?
Ddang Sae and Moo Hyul never came back.
They haven't come back?
Yes. Weren't you all together?
What could've happened? We split in two groups.
Then did Bang Ji follow after Cheok Sa Gwang?
Cheok-cheok Sa Gwang? Who's Cheok Sa Gwang?
Oh right. We were going to draw that warrior away.
Could they have...? Damn it!
Brother!
Moo Hyul. Where's Moo Hyul?
He hasn't come back yet?
What are you talking about? Were you not with him?
Last night, Moo Hyul fell off the cliff with Cheok Sa Gwang.
I haven't been able to find him yet.
Oh no... Oh Moo Hyul.
Ohhh nooo....
Did she use the falling technique while holding on to me?
Aigoo. What happened to my Moo Hyul...
How could this happen to my Moo Hyul...
Since everyone is all looking for him, please don't worry.
Boon Yi is using the help of the whole marketplace organization
I even told Moo Hyul not to go out like that...
Moo Hyul isn't someone who will die that easily. Please don't get yourself worked up so much and just wait.
Moo Hyul! Where are you!
Have you found anything?
Where are you!
Daeseong Shrine (Shrine of Confucius)
Was it something that couldn't be done no matter what?
Was it really something that couldn't be forgiven?
As a Confucian scholar, all I did was follow your teachings.
After following your teachings to put the people above the country, this is the path I've taken, so why?
Why did Po Eun and I have to end up this way?
Why? Just why?
If I really work hard, can I really make a world described in this literature?
You can! Let's make it.
We can make it.
What do you mean we can do it?
This useless crap. This useless crap that couldn't even convince Po Eun!
What's the use of all these plans?
Sahyung! Why are you acting like this?
What? Our great cause has already been ruined anyway. Can't you see?
Sahyung!
Husband, Father-in-law is calling for you.
I might die by my father today.
He won't be able to kill you.
So don't avoid it and go confidently.
Okay. I will go.
Husband.
I'm sure no one has yet told you this.
You did well.
Lee Seong Gye
Father. It's Bang Won.
Father.
I'm sorry. I did wrong.
Take your life as punishment for you sins.
Die!
Bang Won!
I definitely told you not to mess with Po Eun.
What's your reason for disobeying that order, but only obeying the order to kill yourself?
You are probably trying to say that even if you have to die you are still right.
"You, Father, are wrong! I am right!"
"That's why I did everything according to what I think!"
Even if it is against your own father,
even when you secretly stamped my seal on the Ahn Byeon Book,
even when you hit Po Eun to your heart's content until he died,
it's because of your temperament that you wanted to do everything according to your will!
I also don't like your temperament!
Even when the path you needed to take was obviously in front of you, you still looked somewhere else.
Why do you have to make it so complicated?
So then was turning all the Sadaebu following Po Eun
into your enemies all that easy for you?
Then, what is the right thing to do?
Teacher Sam Bong, Teacher Nam Eun, and everyone else.
Should we just let them be executed?
You have made our great cause into a usurpation!
And the little respect and sentiment the people had for is is going to disappear!
Are those really needed in the way to the great cause?
- Being king—
- I will not
be the king of the country!
Yes! If you don't want to, then just forget it!
If you're afraid of taking responsibility, if you're scared of being criticized,
if you hate getting your hands dirty that much, then just quit.
Bang Won, you bastard!
Hyung-nim! Don't do this!
You bastard! You killed Teacher Po Eun!
That's right. You probably made up your mind to die when you did it.
Hyung-nim!
Bang Gwa, immediately arrest this criminal!
Hyung-nim! Please calm down!
If you can't do it, I will do it!
Hyung-nim!
Bang Won! Run! Hurry and run!
Let me go! Let go!
Even the little kids know the fact that Teacher Po Eun was a loyal subject!
If His Majesty doesn't punish the man who killed such a loyal subject,
then who would ever be loyal to this country?
That's right! We need to sentence to Lee Bang Won, who killed Teacher Po Eun, to death.
That's right! We need to all stand together and put these notices up all over Gaegyeong.
We also have to make a petition to His Highness!
- Of course!
- We must do that!
Let's go!
- Let's do that!
- Let's go!
Isn't this a petition for resignation? What is this?
Until the criminal who killed Teacher Po Eun is punished,
we will not come back.
This is something that shouldn't have happened!
It's not that I don't know about your pain and tears.
But I'm scared that even you would get hurt if we acted recklessly.
We're already prepared to die!
Seriously, this bastard Bang Won...
Please, you need to support us!
We are prepared to die!
We are prepared to die! We are prepared to die!
Lee Bang Won Death Penalty
Bang Won will be executed?
How did this happen?
What does that mean?
Warrior-nim!
What happened?
What should we do about your face? Aigoo. Your handsome face...
Ah, whatever. Still, I knew nothing bad will happen to our Moo Hyul.
You said so yourself that I have the greatest luck in Goryeo.
Of course! That's why I didn't worry at all last night. I slept soundly all night long.
No, you couldn't sleep at all, so you were whimpering and scratching the wall.
Aigoo. When did I do that?
Is it true that Teacher Po Eun has passed away?
While we were fighting, Young Gyu Hyung-nim...
I see.
What happened to you?
When I woke up, Cheok Sa Gwang was gone.
That's a relief.
Hey! Were you worried?
You planned to jump, right? You could've died.
That's right. If you meet a strong person, you have to avoid them in the first place.
It's not like you made up your mind to die.
I don't know why Cheok Sa Gwang was protecting Teacher Po Eun, but
if she's still alive, don't you think she'll want revenge?
By the way, what's with the notices put up in the marketplace?
That's because there are a lot of Confucian scholars who respect Teacher Po Eun.
It will all pass. Honestly, Teacher Po Eun's side was the one who started it anyway.
Would they think like that? People just side with the person who died.
Centering on the Seonggyungwan, it seems like the inclination to execute Young Master Bang Won is spreading.
Bon Won, in whatever situation—
In the end, I am the one who killed Po Eun.
He died because of me.
Are you still lamenting that the great cause is ruined?
Because I wanted to remain a Confucian scholar, at the last moment, I acted in a spoiled manner.
It was something that I shouldn't have done and something that shouldn't be done to Po Eun.
And so? What do you think you should have done?
Rather, what are you planning to do?
I have two options now.
Live brutally, or die brutally.
Bon Won.
The justification we lost in the beginning of our great cause,
can only be recovered by establishing a new country.
I have to leave; I need to go see the General.
I definitely told you not to mess with Po Eun.
Bang Gwa, immediately arrest this criminal!
Oh! Lee Bang Won!
Don't get close.
That murderer!
It's from things like this that people talk about "betraying someone's gratitude".
Look, it's Lee Bang Won. He must have no shame.
Isn't he the guy that killed Teacher Po Eun?
Aigoo. Just look at him.
Aigoo.
One more. Aren't you hestitating because you are afraid you will be shunned by the world and become lonely?
Just don't even pay attention to him. Aigoo.
Let's go. Aigoo.
Look here.
Look here!
I told you to lay low and not do anything rash. Why did you cause this trouble?
Do you think you would have had a different method?
I do.
Assassination. You should've assassinated him.
Of course, you would have been suspected,
but you could just deny it. What could they do?
The Jeon Joo Lee family has all the power right now. People will talk about it for a while and it will just pass.
I am fair!
Why do I have to assassinate?
I simply stopped someone who was trying to hurt Father
and got rid of the person who was preventing history from moving forward, in the name of Lee Bang Won.
Always so quick-tempered.
He doesn't even know what kind of weakness it can be to him.
You are okay, right?
What would I do even if I wasn't okay.
The General will eventually calm down.
Even if he doesn't, there's nothing we can do about it.
I have to see Teacher Sam Bong.
He's just entered the Gaegyeong residence.
Okay. Let's go.
Has your health gotten better?
Sam Bong...
How did...
How did things end up like this?
I think I can tell the public sentiment without even stepping outside.
How the world is thinking of me, of us.
I think I know it all.
What can we do now...
General.
Tell me.
Po Eun...
We have to denounce Po Eun as a criminal, and hang his decapitated head in the marketplace.
Wha-What?
We need to hang Po Eun's head at the commonplace and denounce him as a rebel.
Look here, Sam Bong.
Are you out of your mind?
Is this...
Is this the great cause that you wanted?
Killing General Choi Yeong, exiling Lord Lee Saek,
and beating to death the person who came to visit the sick. And now that's not enough,
so you want to hang his head and frame him as a rebel?
Even though I have killed countless numbers of enemies on the battlefield,
I've never killed them in this way.
Even though I've cut off the head of an enemy general running away
after abandoning his army to save only himself,
for the enemy general that fought till the end with his soldiers—
Yes. You've always held a grand funeral for them.
But,
but that Lee Seong Gye is going to frame Jeong Mong Joo as a rebel?
Then should we set up a memorial stone for him as the greatest loyal subject and serve him in a shrine?
General, we need to take responsibility.
In whatever situation, we need to take responsibility.
That's what politics is and is what a politician should at least do.
Since the beginning of history, the essence of politics has never changed.
Politics is responsibility.
Po Eun opposed our plans
and took political responsibility by dying.
And for us, on this road we chose to take, even by killing Po Eun in the process, we must achieve our great cause no matter what.
If we don't, we all have to die.
Is Teacher Sam Bong truly the only person capable of pushing Father forward?
If Po Eun hadn't died, I probably would've died.
Woo Jae, Nam Eun, Lee Shin Jeok,
and all the talented people that we raised and needed for our cause would have died.
It's my fault.
The first was when I thought Po Eun would agree with me, because what I was thinking (about the new country) was correct.
The second was when, even though I knew attacking those who are close
is much more difficult than attacking my enemies, I wanted to ignore it.
And at least to Po Eun,
at least to Po Eun,
my desire to be acknowledged.
That's my third fault.
I fully realize the responsibility. But
if we are alive, if we can't die,
then we have to take responsibility.
What happened?
Teacher!
There was no other way.
I am not reproaching you.
I did it fully determined to face the consequences.
What kind of consequences were you determined to face?
Now, in this great cause, there is no place for you.
You must have have been prepared to face this kind of consequence, right?
From the beginning...
From the beginning, there was no place for me, isn't that right?