This program was created with the support of the Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, Korea's Creative Content Agency, and Media Content.
Do you think you can take me down with just this?
Because I know I can't, I will be even more prepared from here on.
What are you doing? Hurry and arrest him.
Episode 41
Hurry and confess. When did you join hands with Nameless?
I don't know anything.
Late last night, you urgently met up with Prince Jeong An (Lee Bang Won)
and that wench, Cho Young.
Are you saying it's just coincidence?
You're not going to say anything?
What are you doing? Continue.
Yes!
Father appearing at that time and place...
It means that everything had been planned all along.
There is no actual evidence.
But Sam Bong will not let go of this pretext.
What are you going to do, Lee Bang Won?
Then, is Prince Jeong An allied with Nameless?
It is true that he was meeting Cho Young who's been exposed as a Nameless.
But how can Prince Jeong An be with those people...
Do you have definite evidence?
Why is there a need for evidence?
The fact that the prince of a country would do something like that is already a big problem.
His Highness is blocking Prince Jeong An's path.
He's trying to put in order everything that may be a threat to the Crown Prince's safety.
If that's the case, is there really nothing we can do?
His Highness is also trying to sort out the problem that you are worried about as well.
Don't be too upset.
What are you talking about?
It's something related to the Wang family.
Left Minister had a lot of worries from the start.
His Highness has put it to the side until now while thinking of the public's opinion.
The whole country is in chaos because of this and that.
All are big problems that can't be just covered up.
So we'll have to settle things as soon as possible.
We'd have to start wrapping up things with Prince Jeong An. He's a formidable person.
(Shim Hyo Saeng: Lee Bang Seok's Father-in-law)
Lee Shin Jeok also joined them.
Just when did that person follow Prince Jeong An?
Honestly, isn't he disgraceful?
Dying here is not the problem.
If Prince Jeong An gets different intentions, Bi Guk Temple will be wiped away.
I have to let them know. I have to tell the organization no matter what.
Yes. I will deliver your words.
You were the head of the investigation office until last night,
but you've become so helpless,
even though you still have subordinates like that following you.
Shut up! You ruined everything! What are you planning?
Yes. I also got fooled by the child I raised.
That's right.
That wench. That Yeon Hee is the problem.
That wench stuck to Lord Sam Bong and planned this nonsense.
How could I have been pushed aside by such a lowly wench!
Yes. I know full well that you have no connection to Nameless,
but who would believe in my words in this situation?
Since I was caught with Prince Jeong Ahn in the middle of the night, Lord Sam Bong will try to end me here.
Should I help you?
How can you help me?
It's simple.
You just have to send a short letter outside.
Teacher Ho Jeong!
I came because I have something to consult with you about concerning Prince Jeong An.
It's happening to Prince Jeong An but it's something that can happen to both of you as well.
What are you talking about?
Right now, Sam Bong is trying to subdue the royal family members who have many soldiers.
Then do you have any good plans?
Immediately meet with General Lee Ji Ran.
Together with General Lee Ji Ran, you have to petition to His Highness to deal with Prince Jeong Ahn by public discussion of the Court.
How should I do it?
If Prince Jeong An is conspiring with Nameless, they'd have to do an investigation.
Say that it must be dealt with by investigation and public discussion.
If we do that and find evidence, what do we do?
No. Right now, His Highness
will find it burdensome to make this official and investigate.
- Uncle!
- Aigoo. Get a hold of your temper.
For now, we also don't have evidence that he's not allied to them.
There is no evidence.
If Bang Won is really that suspicious, aren't we supposed to do a cross-examination?
That's right. Just because he's a prince, it's not right to settle it without a fair investigation.
Please interrogate Cho Young.
So you really want to take it to the investigation bureau?
I have to prove my innocence.
Cho Young received your letter and ran all the way to Gyeongdeok Jeon.
That alone is a problem for a country's prince.
But ignoring your father's face in front of all the ministers,
You want to do an interrogation?
Why? For what?
Lord Sam Bong's and your thoughts,
I just can't act according to them.
Do you want to be the crown prince?
I have already decided on a crown prince.
If you want to be crown prince, you'd have to attack your brother, me, and Sam Bong.
Can you do that?
Father.
How can you...
That is an impossible greed.
While I still have a little bit of love for you,
stop that greed.
Greed?
Why do you call my dream greed?
Becoming the king wasn't your dream.
Prince Ui An (Lee Bang Seok)
also never dreamed of it but he became the crown prince.
But I've been dreaming of it.
So why is it that only my dream is greed?
I couldn't do anything anymore.
If you still believe that I am a part of Nameless
you are going to have to prove it.
Is Prince Bang Won really
working with Nameless?
That's not it. This is called a struggle for power.
It's even more brutal than fighting with swords.
Boon Yi's organization has decided to leave.
Was it Banchon?
At any rate, they said that they will be able to at least eat and live without doing this kind of work.
Boon Yi made the right decision about that.
Gab Boon, you should just go with them.
You are kind of part of that group.
Still, would it be alright for me to do that?
I will
try to open a Tavern in Banchon
Let's just try to squeeze our way in.
Let's try to squeeze our way in together.
Whatever happens to Prince Bang Won, it doesn't have anything to do with you anymore.
How can it have nothing to do with me?
I heard you are leaving for Banchon.
You made the right decision. You're going to do well there.
And the people from your group are going to do well too.
- But Yeon Hee, Prince Bang Won--
- Although it's unfortunate
his greed brought this upon him.
Greed?
Why is only Prince Bang Won's greed a bad thing?
When there is just greed, it is not a bad thing.
Even for people who commit theft, greed is just
wanting to be full, wanting good things
That's all. It's something everyone has.
How is this in any way similar?
So, what's going to happen to Prince Bang Won?
Yes, what's going to happen?
It will probably be difficult for him to return to politics.
Lord Sambong is going to make it that way.
As we said before,
stay away from their issue.
It doesn't seem like this problem will change even if we do something
I don't think this is something that we can help with.
Probably, right? Obviously.
I heard you made a tough decision.
Yes, I did. A tough one.
- You're upset, aren't you?
- More than that,
I just don't like it. I hate this situation terribly.
But there's one thing I know. Now
is the time to make a choice.
What will your choice be?
I will go with Prince Jeong An.
Believe in your decision.
I'm not upset at all.
Prince Jeong An will probably be the same.
What do you want me to do?
Ask a favor from that soldier who follows you
and let our organization know about this situation.
Why are you hesitating?
We're just riding the same boat
out of a difficult situation for a short time.
Please have some water.
Can you risk your life for me?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
Deliver a letter.
For now, I'm satisfied with what happened to Prince Jeong An.
Why are you laughing?
Look here, Lord Shim.
Yes, Lord.
Actually, my plan
hasn't started yet.
No. It has probably started now.
What does that mean?
Bon Won, he's here.
I will never join hands with Nameless.
Yes. Don't worry.
I did as told.
Aren't you from the investigation office?
I think Lee Shin Jeok
has succeeded.
This time,
your body will eventually get hurt.
I am prepared.
To eradicate Nameless,
I think this is the only way.
It's not just Nameless.
You have to become Prince Jeong An's person now.
-Start.
-That's too much!
What's the matter? Calm down.
Lord Sam Bong is wrong.
Right now, Prince Jeong An
is probably really upset because he wasn't selected as a meritorious contributor.
Try to approach him.
This isn't fair treatment.
Do you really think so?
Bon Won, this time you must
expose Nameless' true identity.
What? Lee Shin Jeok resorted to desperate measures?
Even if we arrested Nameless,
one problem was that we couldn't get a grasp of their leaders.
The second one is preparation for Prince Jeong An.
Preparation? Prince Jeong An will be chased out soon.
But he's a prince.
He's also an amazing and wise prince at that, so
it's highly possible that he will make a comeback.
Lee Shin Jeok is now under Prince Jeong An because of this.
Anyway, we have to start the next step.
Yeon Hee, organize Hwa Sa Dan's data.
- It's all organized.
- Is that so?
Then we will be able to utilize it soon.
Yes. I will get it ready.
Because of this incident, the Wang family that has a chance to restore Goryeo, the Nameless,
and Prince Jeong An.
We can catch all three of them.
We have to.
Take Bang Ji and start the operation to arrest Nameless.
Yes.
Slowly turn around.
So you're from Hwa Sa Dan.
Why are you following that person?
Why is Hwa Sa Dan...
White soil mark?
Is the army following you?
Mugeuk!
I think this place has been exposed.
We have to get out of here.
This is the fourth white soil mark.
Let's go.
Yes!
This place has been exposed?
Just how?
I think the communication line has been broken.
Then...
Cho Young probably got arrested.
If not, she was betrayed or fooled by a plan.
Tell all the members to lie low for three months.
Yes. I will do so.
What about the Ming work that Cho Young was supposed to do?
I will personally do that one.
Teacher Yook San, after three months,
inspect the Hwado Inn in Tamra first and go north.
Yes. I understand.
Let's go.
I think Lee Bang Ji came as well.
The traces were cut.
It's that way.
She was found out.
Divide and spread out.
Arrest those who are suspicious. If they resist, you can kill them.
- Do you understand?
- Yes!
Mother.
That's right.
I was dying to see you.
For a long time, I went around looking for you
but I get to meet you here.
Ddang Sae.
Did you really...
Did you really abandon us?
That's what you told Boon Yi.
You didn't look for us. You didn't even want to look for us.
Our poor Boon Yi
said that you have always been like that.
So she told me to not look for you and just forget.
Without giving her a warm hug,
without even saying sorry,
that's what you told her.
Please answer.
I told you to answer.
That's what I said.
Everything.
Everything was your fault!
While looking for you, I met Sam Bong.
While looking for you, I learned how to use a sword.
But you never looked for us.
You didn't leave.
You abandoned us.
That's right.
So why did you appear?
If there's something I feel sorry to you about,
I can only do this to make up for it.
Leave Jeong Do Jeon. I came to tell you that.
If you want to keep your life, leave Jeong Do Jeon.
That person has amazing ideals.
And rarely seen in history,
That person, who has amazing ideals, also has great power.
That has never happened before.
But...
A country like that is impossible, Ddang Sae.
It seems that you believe in that country, like Boon Yi—
No.
I'm different from Boon Yi.
I don't believe it and I don't even dream of it.
Boon Yi, whom you've abandoned...
The dream Boon Yi has...
Protecting that is everything to me.
I will protect it no matter what.
So in the end,
you will
be going against me.
That's how it ended up.
Ddang Sae.
The real identity of your mother who lived poor in the Western district for ten years
is Mugeuk,
Nameless' leader.
Boon Yi's dream, the world she believes in.
If you want to protect them,
kill me now.
You can't always protect everything in the world
so you have to choose.
If you can't choose to leave Sam Bong,
you'd have to kill me, Ddang Sae.
I will let you
kill me any time.
If you ever want to kill me
post up a notice any time.
Your once foolish
and innocent
heart. The sin of putting hell in that heart.
That's the only sin I can admit to.
Also, tell Sam Bong
that Nameless will not disappear with just catching everyone.
We
are the people's hearts.
A few of the lower ranks have killed themselves.
Then the leading figures have escaped again?
I apologize.
But since they lost two of their main bases, their activity will be reduced.
Has Cho Young confessed?
Why would her confession be important?
We have records that can prove her charges.
The assassination attempt of His Highness in 1392.
The materials used for the operation you guys called "Kill the ash tree flower"
were bought by you. This is true, no?
Confirm it.
Yes. That is Cho Young's handwriting.
Is it also true that you made a deal
with the merchant group operated by the dethroned king, Wang Yo?
The entries under Myeongun merchant group are all
transactions with dethroned king, Wang Yo.
What are you going to do?
I am trying to prove that Nameless tried to enthrone Wang Yo.
If you think like that,
then to you it will happen soon.
I will talk to her for a moment.
Go ahead.
I have gotten Cho Young's confession.
It is true that Nameless was involved in the plot to assassinate the King.
It is also true that Nameless continuously made deals with the dethroned king, Wang Yo.
Good.
I am going to tell this to His Highness
and get royal permission to execute the dethroned king Wang Yo and the Wang family.
What are we going to do?
By saying that during the process of your enthronement the Nameless was part of it,
public opinion of the Court is leaning towards executing Your Highness.
Your Highness, if you decide to escape,
I will help you.
Your Majesty, what are you thinking about?
You should go inside.
Do you
have something to say to me?
A long time ago
you saved me.
That's right.
Tired from ceaselessly walking,
you were dying from hunger in the streets.
Just skin and bones.
Your legs were so bruised, they were about to explode.
I
washed, clothed,
fed and raised you.
Yes.
You did.
Then how
could you betray me?
I wanted to live.
Selling my smile to countless men,
pretending to give them my heart while obtaining information,
killing.
It was a time when I didn't feel like I was living.
The one who saved me
was Lord Sambong.
Have you not thought about
how you might be being taken advantage of?
Even if I am being taken advantage of,
since this is my dream now,
I do not care.
That dream
will never be fulfilled.
At the end of life is death.
You said this.
Yes.
Even if it is not fulfilled
how great is it that we can dream
while we are alive?
Leave.
Do not ever again
talk to your enemy about such innermost thoughts.
I am sincerely grateful for everything.
Good—
Good-bye.
Take it away!
Until I am allowed to talk with Cho Young
I will not drink a drop of water.
Father, do you not think that Prince Bang Won should cross-examine Cho Young as he wishes
and conduct an exact investigation?
That's right. Father, Bang Won...
I mean, Prince Jeong An. Even if he is kicked out,
shouldn't he leave without being wronged?
I also
think so.
Isn't he this country's prince?
Exile or whatever.
If we just handle it like this...
Fine.
Let him cross-examine her.
But there will be no interrogation.
Just a cross-examination.
It was very touching.
Yeon Hee, that wench.
A traitor.
In this turbulent time,
believing someone is a bigger crime.
How can betrayal be a sin?
Well,
whether it's you or that wench Yeon Hee,
are not even Sadaebu or men so whether you betray or not,
you won't care about hurting your honor.
Though we are not women of a noble family,
we have honor as women
and honor as spies.
It's like that for people like you, so what do you think it will be like for someone like me?
Someone like me... Falsely accused of secretly communicating with Nameless.
I just can't stand that.
I am only joining hands with you for a short time.
Yes. I am aware of that.
There will be communication soon...
What's wrong?
What happened?
Yes. I put it on that place you told me about.
Please untie me for a bit.
Yes.
But Prince Jeong An will be cross-examining that wench.
He's on his way.
Is that so?
When did you deliver it?
I left it there as soon as I left earlier.
I opened it after a while and it wasn't there.
Lee Shin Jeok.
As a person who thinks so preciously of honor
and is terribly scared of being connected to Nameless,
how can you
escape with me?
If you escape with me, you
will be confirmed as Nameless, so why?
What are you saying?
Furthermore,
if my organization took that letter,
to leave a mark, they will open that roof tile and never use that one again.
But...
You
opened that place again?
Lee Shin Jeok, so you're Sam Bong's
desperate measure.
Prince Jeong An will be here soon.
You bastards planned to use me as your spy!
Go out
and buy more time.
Hurry.
Yes!
Wait!
Please wait for a little bit.
What's taking so long?
What happened?
I'm sorry.
Cho Young found out my real intention.
Prince Jeong An is almost here
If this were known, the next plan would be ruined, so
I had no choice.
Damn.
What should we do?
Prince Jeong An is waiting right now.
Move her to a prison.
Pardon?
Cho Young committed suicide in prison. Do you understand?
Cho Young killed herself in the prison.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Do you want to check?
Will you believe it then?
How did you kill Cho Young?
Nothing like that happened.
Are you going to kill me too?
Aren't you already planning that anyway?
Your Highness.
After Po Eun died,
I erased all the hesitation in my heart.
Exercising tolerance,
endurance, patience, and persuasion.
I have realized that things like this will eventually
disturb everyone and bring misfortune.
That's fortunate.
Although you are too late.
Yes.
That's why I am gravely blaming myself,
so I hope that I won't make the same mistake with you.
Five years.
Please go to Geoje for just five years.
I was thinking of issuing you a government post in Geoje.
Within five years, I
will make this country stable in many ways and make its foundation strong.
Five years?
It's the time
when Bang Seok becomes an adult.
Yes. Please come back then.
What if I won't go?
You have to go.
If Po Eun had also
done this earlier, he could have been saved.
You wouldn't have done such a terrible thing.
So I have to save you even if I do it like this.
Yes.
Try it.
Jeong Do Jeon is going in.
Is it true that Cho Young committed suicide?
I apologize, Your Highness.
So you weren't able to cross-examine her?
Then, Prince Jeong An won't surrender again.
So instead of an exile,
what about issuing him a government post in a province?
That's right. Keep him away for just five years.
Just five years.
Your Highness.
I have decided.
Let's send Bang Won
to Geoje.
Your Highness, it's not that.
A message has come from the Mings.
And?
A while ago, they captured Japanese pirates that invaded the frontiers of the Ming's country.
And the pirates confessed that on the orders of the Joseon's Court,
they were spies observing the Mings.
What?
So one of our princes has to go in to Ming.
and give explanations on this matter.
Won't they be hostages anyway?
And what do they mean spies? They are just nitpicking.
And looking at Ming Emperor Zhu Yuanzhang's recent actions,
it can't be any more atrocious!
He massacred 20,000 subjects!
It's a place of death.
How can we send our princes to Ming in this hopeless situation?
But if we don't send them,
they'll just make bigger excuses.
Your Highness, I will be in charge of being the villain.
Don't lose strength.
You are a smart person so you will understand what I'm saying.
Please choose between two options.
There's no other way.
One is
to go to Geoje and stay there for five years
and the other one is...
Perhaps, me?
Yes. That's right.
Go to Ming as an envoy?
That's right.
You might die due to the Ming emperor's anger
or you might go into exile in Ming.
Did Father
really approve this?
Because he knows that the only person
who can go to Ming and persuade the emperor is you.
So he eventually acknowledges me at times like this.
No.
He acknowledges you and he deeply knows that
and you have become dangerous
to His Highness and to the Crown Prince.
Thank you.
I didn't even know that both of you acknowledge me.
I will go.
I can't stay for five years
in a place like Geoje.
I knew it.
I'd rather go to Ming as an envoy.
Whether I die as an envoy while doing work for the country
or
I persuade the emperor of Ming
and return home in glory
within a year.
Father.
Come back
in glory.
Your Highness.
You
make sure to go to Banchon.
Like you said,
whatever happens,
you must not be swept away by Sam Bong or me.
Why, all of a sudden?
You must not be swept away.
What's the matter?
If you don't get swept away,
if you make it so...
You are going to be relieved
and live like a beast?
Comfortably.
Don't say that.
Please don't say that.
If you don't, how can I comfortably leave for Banchon?
Still,
you have to leave.
Whether as a beast or whatever...
Whatever happens to me somewhere,
even if I die,
still...
You'll be somewhere smiling.
Please let me think that way.
During the time when we were friends back then,
the reason why I liked you,
do you remember?
Because I don't look like I will die.
♫ In the middle of this painful world ♫
♫ I breathe and live even though it's difficult ♫
♫ I try to endure the day ♫
♫ Even if destiny blocks ♫
♫ and abandon me, ♫
♫ I have to protect ♫
Liaodong Fortress
Why are you here?
We are envoys from Joseon.
We're on our way to accept the emperor's summons.
Arrest these people!
No.
What happened here?
It has started.
What is?
Being an envoy going to the mainland is always like this.
It's not like we came here for something good,
so we won't know what will happen from here.
I've had a bad feeling since we departed.
Ah, my legs are stiff.
You're in trouble now.
What did he say?
He said we're in trouble.
Your country got caught
accepting Yeojin (Jurchen) tribes.
He said they know about us accepting Yeojin (Jurchen) tribes.
Well, you are all the same. Uncivilized bastards.
He said we're all the same, uncivilized bastards.
What?
Translate what I'm going to say
from here on.
Yes.
Listen well.
You.
Do you want to die?
Translate it.
You.
Who are you?
He asked for your name.
I am Lee Bang Won.
Who are you?
I
I am Ju Che (Zhu Di)!
Ju Che (Zhu Di)...
What did he say his name was?
(Ju Che (Zhu Di): Later 3rd emperor of the Ming dynasty, Yeong Rak Emperor (Yongle Emperor))
Six Flying Dragons
Go back. I never allowed envoys to pass.
The result can be war.
Is that what you want?
Don't you know that you could die because of what you say?
It's tonight. Is everything prepared?
Tonight, everyone will be gathered at Jeongyeonam.
Is there still no news about Prince Jeong An who went to Ming?
Nothing yet.
You're probably alive, right, Bang Won?
Please let us pass through Yodong (Liaodong).
How arrogant and foolish.
You bastard will either live or die today.
Then please let me die fighting.