This program was created with the support of the Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, Korea's Creative Content Agency, and Media Content.
The Heavens never change
[Episode 35]
so how come Po Eun changed?
Even though we are the ones who plan for domination, we are still lost in our thoughts.
Ruthless domination...
Po Eun, on the other hand... Even though he was trying to stop this domination,
he already knew about all of that.
Father.
The General fell off his horse?
(Jeong Do Jeon's place of exile)
That's not all.
Lord Po Eun sent all of General's followers into exile, including Lord Jo Joon and Lord Nam Eun.
P-Po Eun did?
And so?
Bang Won hurriedly went to Byeokrando to escort General back.
There's no one to lead us in Gaegyeong right now.
If you want, I will get you out.
There are only a few soldiers outside.
If we wanted, from the beginning we could've just gathered forces and attacked the royal palace to claim the throne.
Did you say that true power is only the sword?
But this is definitely not fake power.
It's because justification and great cause can become power that people trust and follow.
Now, it depends on Heaven's will.
First is General's life and death situation.
Second, will Bang Won be able to escort him back to Gaegyeong as soon as possible?
Criminal Jeong Do Jeon, accept the royal command!
It is an order for criminal Jeong Do Jeon to be transferred to Gaegyeong.
Calm down and put your sword down. It only said to transfer him.
They won't be able to get off of this mountain with an injured man.
We have to find them!
Let's go.
Why is the palanquin like this?
Someone appeared and made it like this an instant before leaving.
What?
Young Master Bang Won was right.
If we hadn't done this, General might have died.
We also got attacked.
Those bastard who were targeting General will be searching the mountain.
We should also hurry and find General and Young Master Bang Won.
Everyone, disperse and find General and Bang Won!
Yes!
Thank you, Warrior-nim.
I will escort you.
You don't have to.
What are you doing there?
Can't you figure it out just by looking?
I was pulling up the cart again after dropping it down the slope.
Who are you and where are you from?
I'm a farmer from the village at the foot of the mountain.
You don't look like a farmer.
Pardon?
The criminal, Jeong Do Jeon, and his followers are being transferred to Gaegyeong.
Now, if Rang comes back after safely completing her task,
(King Gong Yang, the last king of Goryeo)
proceed with the execution according to this royal command.
Yes, Your Highness.
Being agile in one's duty, and knowing to spare one's words,
I think I've learned—
Who are you?
Please help me.
How did this happen?
Actually, we're being chased by our landlord's soldiers.
For what crime?
I wasn't able to pay tax because I was taking care of my sick father.
I will be back with some medicine.
Are there some people hiding in here?
Pardon?
They are a father and a son.
Why would there be people like that at this time of the night?
May we have a look?
I already said that no one came here so why are you going to search?
I already said they're not here.
Nothing.
Let's go.
Excuse us.
Just where did they go?
Let's look again. Even if he's Lee Seong Gye, he won't be able to get away.
You can come out now.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Do you think I don't know anything because I'm a Confucian scholar from the rural countryside?
I am from the Jo family of Yangjoo, and my teacher is one of Teacher Po Eun's scholars.
As someone who respects Teacher Lee Saek, do you think I wouldn't know Lee Seong Gye who sent him to exile?
Do you think I wouldn't know of the plans to ruin Goryeo's Confucianism with the rebellious Sam Bong?
Your plans to start another period of military regime in Goryeo's history,
do you think that I didn't know that?
Are you crazy?
No. It's just funny.
What?
Think about it.
A person who has been on a horse all his life, as he went to war,
has fallen off his horse.
Being chased by Lord Po Eun, who's always been old-fashioned all his life.
And now, by some countryside scholar who no one's ever heard of,
his life is being threatened.
Father really has an interesting fate even in his end.
Kill him.
What?
If you have the nerve to kill a hero of Goryeo who has spent all his life serving the country,
and have firm faith and belief in Lords Lee Saek and Po Eun, then kill him!
I will go to Ham Joo right away.
I will then bring the Ga Byeol Cho and kill you.
I don't even have to know your name.
I can just kill all the Jo family of Yang Joo.
Your second and even third generation. All of them!
Your respected Teacher Lee Saek?
Why do you respect him anyway?
He's against the land reform. He's also against the reform of Buddhism!
So why are you following Lee Saek?
The country that Father is going to establish
is not a military regime.
is a Confucian country.
If it weren't for that,
why else would he go so far as to do the land reform and the Buddhist temple reform
despite all the opposition from Gwon Moon Sae Jeok .
You... You! You said you're a Confucian scholar.
We
- are going to make a Confucian country.
- I'll follow you.
- What?
I was just curious.
Everyone just talks a lot,
but they don't know what General Lee Seong Gye has been doing.
I wanted to know but you answered right away.
I think it would be good if you didn't do this.
You can get off of this mountain with my help, even with people wandering around here.
What did you say? You failed?
Yes.
General Lee Seong Gye was not in the palanquin the army told us about.
He was not in the palanquin taken by General Lee Ji Ran either.
Then, where did he go?
The royal army stayed and searched around the mountain, but
they couldn't find him until now.
- You didn't meet with Bang Won?
- No.
I sent men to the path from Byeokrando to Gaegyeong but they didn't go through there.
- Where do you think they went?
- At that time,
one of us should have followed Bang Won.
If we had, then those people wouldn't have been tricked the way Young Master Bang Won said.
Young Master!
Please stop for a bit.
Don't make a big fuss about it. Father
is safe inside there.
That scared me.
- Hurry and move him to the Gaegyeong residence.
- Yes. Let's go.
Let's go.
Thank you, everyone.
I will not forget this favor.
I am indebted to you. I'll pay you back.
The General has to be alive for you to pay me back, right?
I wish you good fortune.
- Let's go.
- What is your name?
Mal Saeng. Jo Mal Saeng.
Mal Saeng...
What's with your name?
What about my name?
- What happened?
- Minister Lee Seong Gye went through Soongin Gate
He just entered his Gaegyeong residence.
Lee Seong Gye eventually got back.
Then now the important point is what condition he is in.
General. General!
Is he still unconscious?
Wife, the doctor. Quickly.
- Assassination?
Who would order an assassination?
- I don't know but couldn't it be Lord Po Eun?
- Is he crazy?
He's someone who comes here every day. Why would he do that all of a sudden?
I knew something was up, when he sent Elder Sam Bong into exile.
Hey! Even so, why would he...
Go bring a doctor.
Yes. Come. Let's go.
Your Highness, I think
- that we must not stop here.
- But what if
Minister Lee's situation is not critical? What are you going to do?
I will go out.
- Wouldn't it be dangerous?
- Please don't worry.
Lee Seong Gye won't be able to do anything to me.
Follow Po Eun. You must protect him.
Let's go. Hey! Moo Hyul! Let's go.
Grandmother, I have somewhere to go to.
You can go first.
Excuse me. By any chance,
do you know whose residence this is?
This is Lord Woo Hak Joo's residence.
Lord Woo Hak Joo.
Warrior-nim!
Why are you following me?
I... Lady.
Last night,
it was you, right?
Right?
Could you be...
Because Cheok Sa Gwang is a woman.
Cheok Sa Gwang...
Is it you?
Your identity must not be exposed.
Are you?
Why are you going to kill our General?
That... It's the same for you.
Lord Po Eun was the first one to attack Elder Sam Bong and the others.
To do it as soon as General fell off his horse, that's a cheap shot.
Who is right or just,
let's not talk about that.
It doesn't mean anything.
Do I have to kill him here?
But actually,
you don't look like a person who would kill just anyone.
It doesn't suit you.
I actually don't have that much real fighting experience,
and I have no idea how the warrior world works.
But I am sure of one thing.
If you fight me,
you will die.
That's why—
But you don't like it, right?
Why did you only hit the warriors with the back of your blade at Byeokrando?
I also don't have much experience, but
it was my first time seeing that. I've never even heard of it.
Everyone is fighting while putting their lives on the line,
but why did you do that?
You also don't like killing people, right? It's terrible, right?
I'm actually like that too, but
it seems that you hate it more than I do.
That's right.
I really hate to kill,
so...
Let's not meet again.
What is his condition?
How is it that he still hasn't regained consciousness?
The external shock has greatly injured his organs and blood vessels.
So when is he going to wake up?
I also cannot tell right now.
I've done everything I can, so
we can only wait.
In this extremely important situation,
can we just leave it to the heavens?
Your Majesty, I've told Lord Woo Hak Joo to find out about Lee Seong Gye's condition, so
there will be news soon.
In a little bit, Jeong Do Jeon and the others will be transferred to Gaegyeong.
This country's fate lies on Lee Seong Gye's condition.
Yes.
We have to prepare for the different possible outcomes.
What happened?
Yes. We have confirmed it. It will be here soon.
The doctor must not go outside.
Look here!
Can you stay here
until Father wakes up?
Pardon?
Please stay.
Yes.
Get a room for this doctor to stay in.
Please follow me.
You must listen carefully to what I'm going to say.
Right now, Father's condition is what everyone is interested in.
so we must fool everyone until Father wakes up.
Then, what do we have to do?
First, go visit a doctor and as shown on this prescription,
ask for medicine that is good for internal bleeding from bruises and a tonic good for overall recovery.
Yes.
After that, go to the market and buy Father's favorite wine and dried persimmon
along with tea that has a good scent.
It's important to do it so that people will notice.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
- Yes. We understand.
Let's go.
Hello.
This...
For a man who is 58 years old.
He fell off his horse
- and he was hurt a little bit.
- Yes. A little bit.
I will then give you medicine for blood extravasation (effusion).
Yes.
Oh and also make something that's good for recovery
and throw in everything that gives energy.
I understand.
Blood extravasation? Are you sure?
Yes.
I personally heard what that house's servants said at the doctor's.
I understand. You may leave.
If it's only blood extravasation, then that means Lee Seong Gye's injuries are minor.
But Your Highness, they could have also purposely planned to do that to trick us.
We cannot completely believe in that just yet.
Even so, we cannot execute Jeong Do Jeon and the others without any assurance.
Your Highness, Lord Woo Hak Joo is here.
Let him in!
Right. What happened?
About that... The doctor who went into the Gaegyeong residence still hasn't come out.
The doctor didn't go out? How come?
In my opinion, Minister Lee's condition is not good so they are trying to hide that fact.
(Woo Hak Joo)
However, this is only another speculation.
We need more assurance.
You don't have to be scared.
You just have to properly answer our simple questions and you will be compensated.
Y-Yes.
You treated Lee Seong Gye who fell from his horse, right?
Yes. I did that.
How was Lee Seong Gye's condition?
Yes. When I first saw him, he was unconscious and he was in a critical condition.
He couldn't even lift himself.
If he hurriedly came to Gaegyeong in that condition,
on a funeral palanquin, what would his condition be by now?
If he had kept on moving like that, it would have become even worse.
It might even be dangerous.
Lee Seong Gye
Who is right or just,
let's not talk about that.
It doesn't matter anyway.
Why doesn't it matter?
I'm fighting for the world that I believe in.
Lady!
We are just, right?
That man called Po Eun backstabbed us, right?
Why are you like that? Did something happen?
Just that... It seems that I saw it as something really simple.
At first, it's because of success. I wanted to take care of my family.
But as I have gone along, I have come to like the things that we are doing and the world we are establishing,
so with my life on the line, I fought those bad people who were blocking that world.
But why?
But the people we have to fight from here on
might not all be bad
or evil people, after all.
My thinking must have been incorrect, right?
Are you following Jeong Do Jeon and Lee Seong Gye without that kind of resolve?
Abandoning the people who are important to you
and making an enemy out of those people, if you don't have that kind of resolve, then forget it.
Someone said that
the people we have to fight from now on
could be people who are not only not bad, but who are important to us.
If you don't have that kind of resolve, then you should not get involved.
Do you have that kind of resolve?
I'm not sure.
I still have to do it anyway if I don't want to run away.
You have to be more prepared.
Fighting with a sword means that if you don't kill, you will die.
Let's not die.
If you fight me, you will die.
Your grandfather and your father both died in the war.
Aigoo! You scared me. I almost got hurt!
What's with your face? It's not the usual you. Do you need to go to the bathroom?
Teacher.
Teacher? What's with you?
How strong is the Goksan swordsmanship?
It's very overwhelming.
If I fight with Cheok Sa Gwang, will I lose?
Of course, you will lose.
Will I die?
You probably will.
Then, I'll probably die soon.
What are you saying?
I met her. Cheok Sa Gwang.
When?
On our way to escort General at Byeokrando.
When Cheok Sa Gwang swung just one strike, the whole palanquin split in half.
Maincham.
I couldn't even believe it.
It's called Maincham.
Maincham?
There was a story that when General Cheok Joon Gyung was at his peak, he cut the enemy general in half along with the horse the enemy general was riding on.
It's that technique.
Teacher.
I am going to meet Cheok Sa Gwang again.
If I meet her again, we will fight. And when we fight, I won't be able to win.
Bang Ji probably cannot do it either.
Run.
What?
You can just run so why are you worried?
Cheok Sa Gwang is targeting the General and not you.
If you run, she won't chase you.
That is true. That's right.
I guess you have matured a little bit.
But I don't think I can run away.
Why?
I don't know. I just can't do that.
Please tell me the weakness of the Goksan swordsmanship.
You probably have a reason why you went into their house as a servant.
It's because you wanted to know something.
That is right.
Please tell me its weakness.
About the Goksan swordsmaship...
Yes.
There's no weakness.
No matter how much I looked, I couldn't find it.
So there's no way then.
But Moo Hyul,
a weakness
not only applies to the swordsmanship but also to the person.
Elder Bon Won, General Nam Eun, and Lord Jo Joon are all being summoned to Gaegyeong.
How come? It hasn't been long since their exile.
Young Master, isn't this better?
I don't think so.
I think this is an impending execution.
And so?
I think this is the only chance.
We have to execute all of them.
What if Lee Seong Gye is okay?
What about the army?
There' are no strange movements.
What about the marketplaces in Gaegyeong?
Patrols have been strengthened.
A lot more of Investigation Bureau's soldiers are on the move than usual.
They disguise themselves, but we could tell because we memorized their faces.
Shouldn't we get the Ga Byeol Cho ready?
The new commanders of the left and the right armies are all Lord Po Eun's people.
Even Lee Bang Gwa has been removed from the investigation bureau, so we are at a disadvantage.
Whether it be the left and right armies or the investigation bureau, do you know how many of our people are stationed there?
If something happens, they will be all on our side.
That was when General Lee Seong Gye was still around.
Lord Po Eun spread a rumor throughout the whole army that General Lee Seong Gye is in a critical condition.
We don't know for sure what will happen.
Young Master, what do we have to do?
Yes.
You have to make a decision now.
We cannot just leave Elder Bon Won like this.
Yes, Young Master.
If you make a decision, we will follow it no matter what.
Perhaps, the answer might have been there all along, from a long time ago.
Where is Jeong Mong Joo right now?
His Highness cannot make the decision.
Before he finds out Lee Seong Gye's condition, he can't make any decisions.
I will go to His Highness.
General!
Is anyone out there?
Come here!
Lord Po Eun is in the palace.
Palace. He probably is there.
He will need to be inside the palace...along with the protection from the 5000 royal army.
But...
There's a different sword to use in turbulent times?
No. That's just the bug that's growing in your heart.
If it's turbulent times now,
then it would be sweetly whispering to you that you have no choice but to survive the turbulent times.
Po Eun. It's so that I won't lose Po Eun.
Since I said that I will persuade Po Eun until the day I die, then I'd have to do it.
Please give me the royal command.
What will you do with it?
Are you going to do the execution?
Whatever condition Lee Seong Gye is in, we must not waste time like this.
So?
Please give me the royal command for the executions,
and if things go wrong, please push all the fault on me.
Say that I forcibly stole the royal seal
and it all happened because of my own decision.
Po Eun.
King Gong Yang, Goryeo's Last King
If something happens to you, Po Eun,
I can't do anything by myself anyway.
Your Highness, Lee Seong Gye can never do anything to me.
Please don't worry.
Please give me the royal command.
Why are you pretending to look like you're in agony?
What do you mean?
Then, are you really in agony?
(Hong In Bang)
Then does it look I'm all excited?
Goryeo's lifeline is now Po Eun's life.
Isn't thinking of ending that making your heart flutter?
Don't talk nonsense to me.
The person who ends Goryeo will be the one to open Joseon.
Also, you will be the person who killed Po Eun, who is a great Confucian scholar and the great teacher of Sadaebu.
What do you think? Are you scared or is your heart fluttering?
Accept yourself.
You're actually caught up in something.
The things that will happen to you after you kill Po Eun.
"What if my position (in the organization and society) becomes smaller?"
"What if, because of this incident, something happens to laying a foundation for my successors?"
Also, aren't you scared and hesitant because you might become lonely after the world turns away from you?
Young Master, how...
How come you're like that?
Are you on my side?
I am asking you if you're on my side.
Of course, I am on your side.
Tomorrow, and
no matter what happens tonight...
If you can't answer me, then just forget it.
Are you going to kill him?
Lord Po Eun.
I don't understand political relationships and things like that,
but I know that Lord Po Eun is an important person to the General and Elder Bon Won
so I also know that it's a difficult task.
But as for myself,
in order to fight against someone even more important than that
I am fighting through gritted teeth.
That's why right now, I am on your side.
That's right. I will kill Po Eun.
It's a plan from here on. We need to drag Po Eun out of the palace.
I...
I haven't told you the reason why I urgently came here.
What is it?
That person has come.
How is the General?
I came to visit since he seemed okay.
Visiting the sick?
Po Eun... This man is truly bold.
Yes.
Are you going to keep someone who came to visit out here?
No. Please go inside for now.
Go out and wait.
I must not.
Please do so. Hurry.
Visiting the sick?
I know that you sent assasins to Byeokrando.
How many lives do you think you have?
Even General Lee Seong Gye has put his sword on my neck.
He couldn't do it.
Can you do it?
What did you say?
As I said, I only came to visit the sick.
Please let me see General Lee.
Teacher Po Eun.
I also tried to kill Hyung-nim.
I had bloody fights with Hyung-nim in the Northeast.
That's how I got caught.
I thought I would die right away
Even more fiercely than when he was fighting me, he persuaded me and soothed me.
He took me in as a younger brother.
He promised to protect our tribe and all our people.
Our Hyung-nim is that kind of person.
Even though you did something terrible to Hyung-nim,
if only you would change your mind, he would forget everything.
He's someone who would take you in as a brother,
Teacher Po Eun.
Can't you think about it one more time?
Please let me see the General.
Teacher!
Could he be
still unconscious?
Father! Are you okay?
Po Eun came?
Yes. He came and said he's here to visit you.
He couldn't be more shameless.
Father, this is a chance from heaven.
I will plot a scheme on Po Eun.
You bastard!
Don't say nonsense.
Nonsense? He wanted to kill you.
I killed General Choi Yeong who I've served my whole life
I plotted a scheme on Teacher Lee Saek, who is a great teacher of this country,
and dethroned and killed two kings.
Do you want me to kill Po Eun, who has come to my house, as well?
Father.
If you want the great cause to happen, then stop saying nonsense.
Let Po Eun in.
General.
How can you meet with a schemer like that?
Let him in!
I asked if he is unconscious.
What are you saying?
Let me meet him before I go.
Teacher Po Eun, Father wants to meet you.
You tried to kill me to protect Goryeo.
If I have to choose between you and Goryeo,
there is only a clear answer for me.
If I die,
will Goryeo survive?
It's hard but I have to try.
Why do you even have to do that?
Yes. I didn't want to do it.
That's why I tried to make you change your mind.
I clearly told you that we shouldn't meet again.
You are the one that came to me.
What I said was for you to run far away.
I've thought about it a lot, but
I am not going to run away.
King Woo's rule... During that 14 years
the country couldn't protect the people from the invasion of Japanese pirates.
If the country cannot protect its people, then how can you call it a country?
What the country cannot do, I, Lee Seong Gye, have accomplished.
Actually, whether it is Choi Yeong or Lee In Gyeom,
they could have attacked the powerful Gwon Moon Sae Jeok if they'd set their minds to it.
If they'd focused on national defense, anyone could've done it.
But no one did it.
That's why I eventually got rid of them
and protected the country and the people.
Yes! You did it, General.
So even in the future, as a general,
you can just protect the country and the people, right?
After establishing a new country, we can live better
and I can protect it even better.
That's what you call a rationalization, a self-justification.
Do you think Choi Choong Heon and Lee In Gyeom didn't have any justification? (Choi Choong Heon, a figure in Goryeo era who took over the government and enforced military rule.)
But even they didn't say that they would make a new country.
Look here, Po Eun.
They didn't have any ideas or ambitions for the future.
I am different from Choi Choong Heon.
I have the idea and the ambition called Sam Bong and Po Eun.
Po Eun, do you think I'm doing this because I want to become king?
You know full well that it's something that I have to do because I have no other choice.
I still don't understand politics.
You can just practice politics yourself.
Not too long ago, as we all shared wine at Do Hwa Jeon,
we talked about each other's dreams.
My dream...
My dream is
your and Sam Bong's will to come true. I am protecting that.
Po Eun, please give it another thought.
Please. Please think about it again, Po Eun.
General! General!
Father! Father! Are you okay?
I hope you get better, General.
Let's go.
Tomorrow, at myoshi (5-7am),
proceed with Sam Bong's execution.
Yes. I understand.
Teacher Sam Bong was immediately imprisoned as soon as he arrived in Gaegyeong. There is also word going around that he will be executed soon.
Are you just going to stay like this?
Whether you take him out of prison or assemble the soldiers and cause a coup, aren't you supposed to save Teacher Sam Bong?
Right now, whether it's breaking out of prison or a coup, it's impossible.
- So? Are you giving up?
- No.
Po Eun.
I'm going to have to kill him.
Isn't it going the way you want it to?
Lee Seong Gye going out on a hunt at an out of the ordinary time. An unexpected assassination attempt.
And falling off of a horse. To think that such small coincidences have led everything to this point.
Now, this is the end of Lee Seong Gye and his followers.
I'm not sure. Will they really end?
Each side's will, determination, desire, coincidence, and luck
Or some clever plot or the overwhelming difference in power.
If everything is decided based on these factors, how easy would it be to figure out the world?
Fate can be affected by such trivial things.
Fate is like that of an ill-tempered three-year-old child.
To what will his mind change again?
When morning breaks, it will be scary and heart fluttering.
This will be the longest night in Goryeo's history.
Six Flying Dragons
For the people, whether this or that happens, what matters to them?
Even if the kudzu vines on Mansu Mountain are all intertwined, there's no one who would blame them.
By killing me again and again, try killing me a hundred times.
Even if all my bones rot away and my body becomes soil and the dust,
the one part of my body, the unwavering and passionate heart I have towards this country,
you won't be able to kill my loyal heart.