This program was created with the support of the Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, Korea's Creative Content Agency, and Media Content.
I am Lee Bang Won.
Episode 42
Who are you?
I am Ju Che (Zhu Di)!
Ju Che (Zhu Di)...
What did he say his name was?
He said he's called Ju Che.
Ju Che?
(Ju Che (Zhu Di): Later 3rd Ming Emperor Yeong Rak Emperor, also Yongle Emperor)
Who the hell is Ju Che?
He's the fourth son of Zhu Yuanzhang and was appointed king of Yuan areas.
Your Highness, what's going on?
This kid asked me if I wanted to die.
Cut one of his arms first!
Moo Hyul, no! Stop it! That person is the king.
I don't know about that.
King or not, if I stab him, the sword would still go in.
Teacher Ha Ryun, please translate Moo Hyul's words.
Why are you doing this, Your Highness?
Translate it!
I understood it.
So you know our language.
I do.
Then, I will tell you myself.
That ignorant guy who doesn't even know how to write his own name
obviously doesn't know who the king is.
If I tell him to cut you down, he will do so.
Moo Hyul, count to ten in your head then you can cut him if you want.
Yes, Your Highness.
This guy is totally a crazy bastard.
Because of you, all of us are going to die.
Beat him up.
Because he put a sword to my neck, that guy will die.
Your Highness.
Since he risked his life to protect his lord's life,
I will return the corpse.
We were not the first ones who were disrespectful.
We are Joseon's envoy group who came to answer the emperor's summons.
But you arrested us in Liaodong fortress without any explanation
and Your Highness hid your identity and insulted us.
His country
and his master is in danger while being insulted,
how can a bodyguard just stay still?
That's right.
Tell his family
that he died a loyal death.
He was a good subordinate for a barbarian.
"Only the wise can deal with those who have more than they."
"Only the kind-hearted can work with those who have less than they."
Only a good person can serve a small country despite his great country."
Only a wise person can take a small country and serve a great country.
Therefore, the great country has to act with kindness and virtue
so that the small country can serve with courtesy.
Virtue and courtesy are exchangeable.
But since you did not treat us with virtue,
our rudeness was caused by you.
Mencius. Book of King Yang Hye, third chapter of the last volume.
I also like Mencius. There are some things to nitpick but he's an interesting person.
How did you know our language?
Manchurian, Mongolian, Timurid, Tartar, Goryeo language. I can speak them all.
My Father is His Majesty the Emperor.
Do you know how many of his royal concubines are Goryeo women?
My nursemaid was also from Goryeo.
It's not Goryeo anymore.
It's Joseon, Your Highness.
That's right. A new country was created, right?
Your Highness,
please spare my bodyguard's life.
That man cannot live whatever he does.
Since a sword was put on my neck,
I will also kill all of my bodyguards. They have to take responsibility.
So how would I be able to spare just his life?
Whatever you say—
Yes, that's right.
You must kill all of them. Of course.
Then, please let him die while fighting.
Are you saying that you're confident?
It's not because I'm confident.
That man's dream as a warrior...
He came to me with just that dream alone.
Even if he dies, it shouldn't be like this.
Let him die fighting as a warrior, Your Highness.
This will be interesting.
Moo Hyul...
It's alright.
You tried to protect me
but I don't have the power to protect you.
The only thing that I can do
is give you an opportunity to fight.
You mean...
Staying alive is your part.
That is all I need.
That is all....
Let's stay alive.
I'll live
only if you live.
The 25th move of The Twin Dragons of the East. Moo Hyul.
The 25th move that I developed while watching Bang Ji copying Cheok Sa Gwang
You've practiced it a lot all this time.
Although it's not that good to try it out in a real match
I believe it's definitely going to work.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not afraid.
Since I can fight
I feel rather at peace.
Right. That's right.
Peace within tension.
The best condition.
You... You can beat anyone.
You can do it. I believe in you.
But, Teacher.
Yes, what?
If something goes wrong, my grandmother—
No!
I... I can't take responsibility.
Stay alive and take responsibility yourself.
Twin Dragons of the East!
Moo Hyul.
Don't be afraid. You can't be afraid.
Don't be afraid.
Take a deep breath.
Think about a still lake.
You are water. It's so calm and still.
It's so calm and still.
Teacher.
It seems like you are more nervous than I am.
Oh, right.
Start!
Moo Hyul! Dodge!
Step one of the 25th move!
Don't rush! Dodge!
Avoid and attack. Avoid and hit once!
Stop!
Moo Hyul, stop!
It is your victory.
Tell me your wish.
Because of what I did today,
I heard that
your guards may die.
Please spare
their lives.
Why?
There's a connection
among people who protect others.
They will want to protect again
and
they will protect even better.
This man is telling me to forgive you all.
I will!
The benevolence of the king is great!
As even the 5th prince has such a talented guard,
Joseon is indeed a dangerous country.
And so, I can't let you pass.
Go back.
Your Majesty.
I have never let one of your envoys pass.
But we have received orders to come from the Emperor.
That is your circumstance.
Namgyeong: Ming's capital in the beginning
Did you see it?
The maps in the barracks.
Maps?
Ju Che (Zhu Di) is saying that there is a war brewing between Yeojin (Jurchen) and Joseon,
and he even came all the way here to train soldiers.
But...
All of his maps are maps of the Central Plain.
Do you know what they are?
You do, right?
In what state are Mainland's internal affairs right now?
We have to pass. Let's make a bet.
Why do you keep
on creating a tense relationship with Joseon?
What?
Your Highness
fabricated a case that never existed
and kept nitpicking at it.
You sent a fake report to the emperor.
You bastard!
How dare you speak such imprecations!
Why do you think
that I lied about something like that?
Because you want to steal
the throne from your nephew.
Continue.
The next in throne will be
the emperor's eldest grandson, your young nephew.
His Majesty the Emperor will obviously
be anxious of Your Highness' power.
So...
Didn't you do it
because you were scared of the emperor's suspicions?
Just what are you saying?
Because of the unstable political tension between Joseon and Yeojin (Jurchen), you have no interest in the imperial throne.
Even just protecting this place is too much.
Aren't you trying to present yourself this way to the emperor?
So?
Your Highness
reported to the emperor that Joseon is dangerous.
His Majesty the Emperor
will be coming up with an uncompromising policy for Joseon.
The result of that
can really be war.
Is that what you want?
A cornered mouse
can do nothing but bite the cat.
But that is not
what you wanted, right?
Who says that I don't want that?
Then,
in this headquarters that was made for defense against Joseon and Yeojin (Jurchen),
why is it that there are only maps of the central plain?
Isn't it that your great ambition
is pointed towards Namgyeong (Nanjing) in the central plain?
Namgyeong (Nanjing): Ming's capital in the beginning
What is it that you want to say?
On the day that you head towards the central plain,
you probably don't want a hostile relationship with Joseon
to be an obstacle.
The enemy, with no path for retreat,
has no choice but to be desperate.
In military tactics,
it is said to fight the enemy only after giving them a path to retreat.
So in order to make sure Joseon doesn't think of starting a war,
create a way out.
Is that it?
Yes. That's right.
So that the hardliners in Joseon who are in favor of a war do not gain power,
I'm telling you that you should take hold of a good hand.
A good hand?
It's
me. I, Lee Bang Won.
To make sure that Joseon doesn't fight back in desperation,
through me
please open a way out.
Please let us
pass through Liaodong.
You are really
wise
and bold.
But
you're also arrogant and foolish!
Don't you know that you could die because of what you said?
You can also be found dead
all of a sudden tomorrow.
I
bet I won't be.
Today, you
either die
or live.
What happened?
It seems that we'll either die...
Pardon?
or pass through Liaodong.
That is true.
What a smart person I'm serving...
Tell His Highness that I want to see him.
Untie him.
You must be surprised.
There's still something shocking left though.
Come in.
I heard that you know each other.
Your Highness, it's amazing that we meet here.
How could you...
As I was pondering whether I should kill you or make you a way out,
I found out a lot about you.
She's the leader of a group that's also famous in the Mainland.
I saw her when she brought Goryeo women
to the imperial family.
Have a seat.
You're more amazing than I thought.
I didn't do anything.
I just
shared with His Majesty the things I knew about you.
Your situation in Joseon
is also the same as mine.
You got it stolen by the youngest child, right?
So,
have you made your decision?
Fine.
For my way out,
I'll use you.
Also, I personally will
write a letter to His Highness the Emperor.
Your Highness, I am extremely grateful.
But I have a condition.
What is it?
Your bodyguard, Moo Hyul.
Give him to me.
His Highness
wants you.
So I decided to give you away.
Pardon?
How could Your Highness...
On our way back from Namgyeong (Nanjing), we have to pass through here again.
At that time, I will risk my life and take you back.
But
you must not stay here wasting your time.
Fight and fight some more and learn here.
Your Highness.
Ju Che's bodyguards
are quite skilled, you say?
Ah, yes. Especially that one short guy is really amazing.
An expert knows other experts.
Earlier, he came to me and asked about Twin Dragons of the East and stuff.
That one short guy...
Master Hong, stay here as well and watch over Moo Hyul.
Can I do that?
I don't know what it's like in Goryeo's time
but the best swordsman in the new country, Joseon,
has to be this guy, Moo Hyul.
Can you do it?
The warriors here,
I will completely defeat them all.
Lee Seong Gye eventually
ordered your execution.
Tomorrow,
an officer will come here.
I
put a dot in the character for Wang
and changed my last name to Oak.
You will also go, right?
If I say that I want to live,
she will have to keep fighting
and will die in the end.
Your Highness, come eat.
It was cooked deliciously.
If you're going to the market, I have a favor to ask.
Please bring me that.
Sure.
Then, please eat while I'm away.
I will make you a really good dinner.
Yoon Rang.
Thank you.
You were keeping something for His Highness, right?
Yes.
It's this.
Isn't this a letter?
Yes.
Please read it.
Meeting the beautiful you...
Before I became king, I spent time as if in a dream.
My farewell to you really
hurts, but
Rang,
even if it's just you, you have to live.
Prince Jeong Chan, Wang Yo acted against the law
and many people have left you due to your incapability to manage the country,
so you were dethroned by the heavens. Also,
since the heavens have changed, for the stability of the country and safety of the royal family,
Receive your punishment.
Rang, like that time when you said you'll fight by my side,
I would have told you to run away.
But
in any case, I am
the last king of Goryeo which was passed down through the Wang family for 500 years.
In the end of the last king,
he shouldn't run, right?
If you go to the paper goods shop in Daerim Marketplace at Gaegyeong, Mr. Oak will be there.
I already told them so you can stay there.
You must not have bad thoughts
like ending your own life.
Go find your life now.
You have to do that for me to also
comfortably rest in the afterlife.
Hanyang (after transfer of capital)
It's a petition for impeachment.
Leave out Lord Hong Ak Joon.
Pardon?
He is a close member to Lord Sam Bong.
There will be promotions soon, in the Office of Inspector General.
If you do that, I will put in a good word to him for you.
Yes. I will do so.
Go out the back door.
Pardon? The back door?
What is the inspector general?
While inspecting the officials' corruption and illegal activities,
even if there was a royal command, if you think of it as the right thing to do
you must be prepared to exchange your life for that righteousness.
But you can't even withstand my authority, so you just succumb to it?
Also, all of you
are the first ever government officials of the new country Joseon.
The principles and discipline you guys set will have an effect for hundreds of years to come.
If we are not able to set those things right,
this country's officials will also be like Goryeo's officials,
who were vampires that sucked the blood out of the people.
Are you going to be like that?
Will it really be that kind of country again?
You became like this while trying to stop His Majesty from seeing the king's historical record?
I'm sorry, Lord.
I will make you
a rank 3 official.
Pardon?
If you're not this much prepared, all of you can resign.
Even if you have to wear a diaper to withstand it,
the Office of Historical Records
has to record every little detail of the king's words and actions.
Yes, yes.
It's said that the king is only afraid of the writer of the historical records.
the historical records, that you guys write with your lives,
will become the discipline of the future generations. Do not ever forget that.
Yes, my Lord.
Leader.
We're back.
Today is the first day of students in Seonggyeonggwan. Do you all know that?
Of course.
We helped with washing up and organization and also checked attendance.
We have also checked on where they would stay after classes.
You've worked hard.
Then, eat your meal and I will see you later.
Yes, Leader.
Banchon (Village assisting Seonggyungwan scholars)
Hello.
The preparations are going well, right?
You're not experiencing any difficulties, right?
The civil service examination is coming up. You are going to have to prepare ahead of time
Yes, leader.
To be honest, as we are commoners,
- to be working with people who used to be slaves in Gaegyeong—
- Gab Boon
We are all just Banchon people. Keep that in mind.
I understand, Boon Yi. I mean, Leader.
Ajussi.
Hello.
Is the work alright?
It has been worth the wait to come. I like it.
Oh my. Your handiwork is amazing. Look at that, Leader.
You merchandised with brushes before this, right?
Maeng Soon, you shouldn't ask such questions here.
This tongue. I forgot
But, I don't see your younger sibling again.
Yes. My younger sibling is inside doing needlework.
I see.
You're here.
You always seem to eat your lunch here.
No matter where I go, there's no place better than our grandmother's.
But you seem to be doing well too.
Is that so?
There is nothing much going on, right?
Of course not. Why would I have anything going on?
But, Leader. Have you received any news about the prince who went to Ming?
No, I haven't heard anything either.
Lord Sam Bong is coming. Ask him for me.
Are you on the way to Seonggyungwan?
Yes. I see you're doing inspection.
I heard that all you do is work all day and all night.
It's a blessing.
I...
Has there been news about the prince who went to Ming?
Not yet.
Do not worry too much. He is a talented person.
Yes, yes.
You're alive, right? Right, Bang Won?
Seonggyungwan
It's tonight. Are you all prepared?
Yes. We will all gather at Jeongryunam tonight.
We're taking the first step today so I'm really filled with emotions.
At last, we are finally having our first gathering. My heart is very eager, but everything is going so slowly.
They say that starting means you're halfway there, my Lord.
This is our doctrine. Can you copy these?
Yes. I understand.
You told me everything that happened and things that you heard today, right?
Yes. I've told you everything, Leader.
Yes. Then, you can forget everything now.
Forget everything you told me about.
So are you well now after having used the bathroom?
Give it back.
What are you saying?
The thing that you stole from Seonggyungwan.
What are you talking about? I'm doing a night shift, so I was checking on the lights in Seonggyungwan.
I guess words won't work on you.
Brother!
I see you're in the middle of a conversation.
Everyone, you can go out and tend to your jobs.
Yes.
Baek Jin was caught?
It seems that he went into Seonggyungwan and stole a document. He's currently being held in Banchon.
The investigation bureau has gone too, it seems.
What was the document he stole?
He infiltrated Banchon because Sam Bong has been frequently going to Seonggyungwan.
It's probably something related to Sam Bong.
This place, Banchon, has the shrine of Moon Seong Gong and the Daeseong Shrine.
You know that the royal forces are not allowed in unless it's a royal command.
Isn't the criminal inside Banchon?
We have already caught a suspicious person.
Is that so? Then hurry and hand him over to us.
When we caught him, we realized that he's from Banchon.
As long as it's not the royal command, as the leader, I have the right to deal with it.
You can only arrest him, after I expel him.
So?
He's being interrogated so please wait for a bit.
You wench! Do you think we will just wait here?
If you come in here, to His Majesty and Lord Sam Bong who declared this country will only be ruled with laws and ordinances,
you will become troublesome.
Ajusshi, did you assault the senior scholar, Lord Park Chan Hyun,
and steal a document?
Leader. Why would I do that? I never did that.
Then why did you run?
This man followed me so how can I not run?
No, Boon Yi. That's a lie. I'm sure it's him.
Can I look through your clothes?
Of course. Go ahead.
Brother. If he was hiding something, he wouldn't let me check.
Instead of his clothes, I want to look at his body for a tattoo that we know of.
What kind of suspicions do you have?
From here on, I am asking you as your leader who has power over your life and death.
If you lie about what I'm asking you,
you will be kicked out of Banchon and all of us will forget you.
You will become a dead person to us.
Are you a part of Nameless?
Hold him.
Leader! Leader!
Leader!
All of you, take cover!
Really... Do you think you can fight me with that?
Why did you appear again? No, you Nameless.
What are you planning by entering Banchon?
It's not just Banchon. We are everywhere.
Are you okay?
He threw beef jerky?
Beef jerky? Huh?
That person is clearly Gil Seon Mi.
Nameless has appeared again.
In Banchon, at that.
Excuse me, Leader!
See me for a bit.
This was found by coincidence.
Is that so?
So it was this.
A man was hiding it at a pharmacy and he was suspicious.
Thank you. There was quite an uproar today because of this.
Do you think the royal forces will come here because of this?
No. It won't happen unless it's a royal command.
But why don't you go outside?
Do you feel uncomfortable with people?
No. I'll go out more often.
Yes. Please do so.
I'll take my leave.
Take care, Leader.
Lady, the royal forces can't go in here
so we came here as a last resort. But if you don't like it—
No. This is the best place.
The late king left these children in my care.
You don't have to feel responsible.
They're that person's children.
I'm doing it because I like it.
Jeongryunam?
Bon Won is here.
Jeongryunam
You did well on coming.
It is a pleasure to meet you and I am overwhelmed.
About 2300 years ago, after the Zhou dynasty,
a true Confucian country that practices land reform and equal land division,
it's already been a few years since that country, Joseon, has been founded.
This is hard. Your shoulders.
Though you have a large build,
As light as a butterfly.
- Master Hong!
- Why? Master Hong is here.
Your country's prince.
What about the prince?
The prince
came back alive.
What? He's here?
Moo Hyul!
You heard that, right?
He came back alive?
Moo Hyul!
But this big tree called Joseon's roots
is still weak and pitiful.
The scholars, officials, and Sadaebu.
We who are here
must become this country's healthy and strong roots.
We must become this tree called Joseon's roots among roots for a thousand years.
Hidden but alive.
Can't be seen, but breathes life itto the tree, the leaves, and the flowers.
The hidden root that extends deep and hard in the earth called history.
We are this land's Milbon (hidden root)!
Milbon?
Milbon guides the king.
Milbon corrects the king.
Milbon takes care of the people who are in the lowest place in this land.
Milbon thinks preciously of the people. Milbon respects the people.
Milbon keeps the people safe. Milbon raises the people.
Milbon only has to be and can't ever be different than the following two things.
It's Minbon (the people are the basis and the roots).
It's Minbon!
Minbon.
The people... The people...
are the roots.
Jeong Do Jeon
Milbon's first Bon Won (original root)
Six Flying Dragons
You came back alive. You are really lucky.
It's the royal command to arrest the envoy group.
Transfer them? Just why?
Lord Sam Bong is surely planning something again.
I haven't yet made my vicious move.
Take my vicious move.