This program was created with the support of the Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, Korea's Creative Content Agency, and Media Content.
Episode 37
From the beginning... From the start of this great cause,
I didn't have any place in it, did I?
That's right. From the start, there was no place for you in this great cause,
but you eventually made one for yourself.
Killing Po Eun. That will become your place.
What about Lord Po Eun? What happened to him?
Lord Po Eun died.
Then, what about His Highness?
He's probably not in a good situation.
Is he alive?
He is probably alive.
He will soon step down from the throne.
That went well.
Why didn't you kill me?
You didn't kill me either.
Last time at Byeokrando and at the market,
you were more than capable of killing me.
Why do you live wielding a sword?
I want to protect the people I love.
I want to protect my dream.
I am the same. The person I love,
dream...
Are you going to avenge Lord Po Eun?
I won't avenge.
My dream is to go back to the time before His Highness went up to the throne.
If it's not for Lord Po Eun, he probably wouldn't have taken the throne, right?
Just living a quiet life with His Highness,
it's only that.
If nobody hurts him, I won't fight anyone.
Lady!
Now, Po Eun's head will be hung in the market,
and it must be officially announced that he's a traitor.
Sam Bong.
I tried to change the country through the support of the people,
but the people's hearts, that we barely got a hold of through the land reform,
are now impossible to get back again due to Po Eun's death.
But to hang Po Eun's head—
What use is there to try turning back something that is irreversible?
We have to quickly and strongly proceed with this.
Dethroning the current king and as well as founding a new country.
Do you all understand?
Po Eun left like that and I don't even know if Yoon Rang is still alive.
This is the end.
Your Highness! Jo Joon, Nam Eun, and Jeong Do Jeon are entering.
Let them in.
Your Highness, Po Eun Jeong Mong Joo used sly tricks to falsely charge people with crimes, and
he planned a conspiracy and received Your Highness' royal command to execute innocent people.
The reason why General Lee Seong Gye's fifth son, Lee Bang Won, attacked Jeong Mong Joo
was to stop a conspiracy.
So please hang Jeong Mong Joo's head in the commons
and give us the decree that denounces him as a traitor.
Please give us the command.
Your grace is immeasurable.
When are you going to take the royal seal?
There's an order for everything so please wait.
I didn't want to become the king.
Arrest all those people who are putting up false posters.
Yes!
Move aside!
His Highness has ordered for Traitor Jeong Mong Joo to be hanged.
Those who will go against it
will also be treated as traitors and will be killed.
Do you understand?
I can become even stronger.
Bang Ji's movements have changed.
He's following the Goksan swordsmanship.
Ah. Goksan swordsmanship.
That's right. It's that.
What are you doing here? Elder Sam Bong told everyone to gather.
I think it's because of what Young Master Bang Won did.
The market is going crazy wanting to execute Young Master Bang Won.
Then, are they telling him to just sit down and die? They're too much.
They're waiting so hurry and go.
Master Hong, what are you doing? Hurry. Moo Hyul, go.
Let's not drag time now. We have to make haste.
Yeon Hee, you have to spread rumors among the Sadaebu through Hwa Sa Dan.
Please speak.
After the General heard about Po Eun's death from Bang Won,
he threw an inkstone at Bang Won and cracked his head.
You said that wound came from your older brother, right?
Spread a rumor that it was done by the General.
Say that after doing that, the General cried for three days and nights.
The whole family was unable to sleep because of the General's sorrowful wailing. Do you understand?
Yes. I understand.
Boon Yi, you should also spread it through the market organization.
Emphasize that it was solely done by Lee Bang Won.
What do you mean?
We will now establish the new country.
Bang Won has be to excluded from this process.
The General, who will be leading the new country,
has to be innocent of kiling Po Eun. It needs to be justified like that.
I don't really know much, but wasn't it done so that we can live?
He did it to survive. Isn't that justification?
If we could do it using strength, then we could've just seized the palace on the day we attacked Jo Min Soo.
Until now, even though it took time,
we put in so much effort in order to persuade, to debate and to embrace.
But...
It has all become nothing now.
Even if it pains the heart, the new country was started with the sword.
Bang Won has to take responsibility for this in his own way and
we have to proceed and endure it in our own way.
But Elder—
Bang Won, you understand, right?
Yes. Of course.
That doesn't make sense!
It's right though. I was the one who killed Po Eun.
I mean, did you kill him to gain fame and money?
Did you kill him to succeed?
Teacher Sam Bong didn't say to spread the rumor that, in order to gain fame and money,
I killed Teacher Po Eun. It wasn't worded like this.
I independently killed Po Eun.
I, Lee Bang Won, killed Goryeo's last remaining loyalist, Jeong Mong Joo.
It is not connected in any way to General Lee Seong Gye.
He said to spread it like this. There is nothing wrong with it.
Still, Young Master...
If I have to take responsibility for this, then let it be.
That's what makes me different from Sam Bong and Father. I will not avoid it.
I'm okay. You don't have to worry.
I heard about it.
A scandal and disgrace like that, you can just ignore it.
Just think of the future.
I am thinking of doing so.
Boon, look into who put up posters asking for me to be executed.
What?
What will you do? You must not.
Yes, Young Master. You have to be careful.
I was just asking you to look into it.
From now on, I have to know who my enemies are.
Young Master, how long has it been?
Young Gyu, I heard that you used your hand this time.
(Lee Bang Gan: Lee Seong Gye's fourth son)
Pardon?
Jeong Mong Joo.
Ah, yes.
You did well. Good job!
When you were hitting his head, it felt good, right?
Ah, yes.
Where is Bang Won?
What is this? Does this make sense?
How can Po Eun's end be like this?
Yes, Teacher. How, under the heavens, can something like this happen?
If you do that in a place like this, everyone will misunderstand.
You bastard!
Do you think you will be safe after doing this to Po Eun?
I don't think I will be safe.
Also, I've never wished for a safe life.
You will face a more merciless fate than Po Eun.
Your end will be more horrendous than Po Eun's.
Yes. It might be that way
but you won't see it, Teacher.
You don't have much time left.
Tell the person who is writing the impeachment list to include Woo Hak Joo.
Woo Hak Joo is already on it.
Yesterday, you told me to add Lee Jung Hak, Ho Hong Soo, Lee Sung In, Kim Jin Yang, and Woo Hak Joo.
Is that so? Then there are 56 people.
They cannot be allowed to stay in Gaegyeong before the coronation--
It must not happen.
Are you okay? What's the matter?
It's nothing. I'm okay.
Do you think you'll be able to eat your meal?
I have to eat. Even through gritted teeth, I have to eat.
He's probably having a hard time even if he acts like he's not.
Go ahead.
Please give us rice porridge here.
Yes. Go inside.
Let's go in.
I'm fine.
Okay.
Elder Sam Bong.
It's been a while.
Yeon Hyang! The little court lady!
Just like how you are not just a young scholar anymore, I am no longer a little court lady.
Just what happened?
You have changed a lot.
What's going on?
Are you... Nameless?
That's right.
Do you know that your children are looking for you? Outside... Your child is outside.
I know. Please don't call him.
How?
I came here today to only talk to you.
Calm down. We only came for a talk
with your elder.
Who?
Our side's Elder.
You became faster.
It must be great to be young. You're developing like this.
If you do anything to Elder...
I won't, so relax.
If you fight me here,
it might get even more dangerous. I'm not the only one you will be fighting.
What was that sound from outside?
It seems like my bodyguard said hi.
Nothing will happen.
I guess the new country will be revealed soon.
Are you against it?
No.
Then why are you blocking us?
We weren't, in the beginning.
When we heard about your plan, we were excited and cheered you on.
We even tried to help, before we found out about that truth.
Are you talking about the land reform?
The equal land division, the land distribution.
Whatever the name, in the end the problem is the land reform.
Didn't you already burn the land registers?
Stop the process and forget about equally sharing lands, Elder.
Your organization must have a lot of land.
So you probably suffered some losses from it.
Since there are a lot of people, a few of them have a lot of land, but the majority do not.
Then why?
It's because of principle.
A person chases after work, and the generation chases after the person. That is our principle.
But the new country denies this great desire.
You say that it's great?
The land reform fundamentally seals people off from any desire to have more land.
That desire has brought Goryeo to this state. That personal land ownership.
And so you are going to proceed with the land reform?
Equally distributing land for every person,
and not being able to increase this amount a little bit. This is what the land distribution does.
Since no one is able to increase their land by even a little bit,
no one will ever have their land taken by even a little bit.
We are the ones who first created the concept of personal land ownership.
A few hundred years ago, when it seemed only right that land belonged solely to king and country,
we cultivated the wasteland and created the system of personal land ownership.
And?
As a result of the people's desire to have their own land,
they crazily ran to the wasteland and dug.
After that the farmlands grew rapidly,
and the Three Kingdoms became more prosperous than ever before.
Desire paved a way and achieved prosperity.
And what happened to that prosperity? Who are the ones that became prosperous?
In the end, more than 70% of the country's land was taken by the Gwon Moon Sae Jok.
The people didn't even have the land to place a single nail, so they were kicked out from their homes
and slowly died away from starvation or slavery.
So is it really great? The desire for all this?
A person perseveres through many hardships in order to expand their work.
As a result, in the past the world advanced and could have gone forward.
The world from now on will be different.
In the place of the desire to chase after work,
Neo-Confucianist ideals will take precedent.
A country where every person becomes a wise man.
Therefore, a country will be made where no one groans for having theirs taken,
and no one takes another's in order to fill his own belly.
It seems you aren't going to give up.
Of course. From the trade and commerce on the outside to the marketplace on the inside,
this desire will be controlled and managed by the nation so that
the poison from desire will never cause us to hurt each other.
I have heard you well.
Then although we don't have much power,
we will use what little we have to stop you.
It looks like they are done. I hope the talk went well.
See you again.
What happened? Are you alright?
Gil Seon Mi was outside.
We will use what little we have to stop you.
Yes. Nameless was here.
I will try to be more careful in guarding you from now on.
Bang Ji.
Your mother is Nameless's—
Boon Yi told me she met our mother.
She said that Mom told us that she abandoned us and to forget her stop looking for her.
So I'm going to forget her too.
♫ Cry, cry, bird ♫
♫ Sleep and wake up, bird ♫
♫ I, who am more sorrowful than you,  ♫
What happened?
It's war now.
Keep a good watch on Lee Bang Won.
I understand.
Look for the missing Cheok Sa Gwang as well.
What's the use of looking at it. I can't even read anyway.
How did it go?
We got it.
Okay. Now let's change the heavens.
Of course. Starting with the heavens,
the earth and humans will all begin anew.
Yes. Today has finally come. You worked hard.
Our work has only just begun. Let's begin.
Yes.
Prince Jeong Chang, Yo. By acting against the law and putting the state in confusion,
he has betrayed many people and deserted his relatives. Due to his inability to maintain the country,
he is henceforth dethroned by the heavens.
It is the wish of all the countless numbers of people.
Please become the father of all the people.
The country must go to a person of virtue
The throne cannot be vacant for too long.
Please rise to the throne and calm the people of this land.
♫ Is there any difference between politics and swords? ♫
♫ You, the nameless bird in the sky ♫
♫ Why are you wailing so sadly? ♫
♫ You can’t find where ♫
♫ Wildflowers have fallen anyway ♫
♫ You, the nameless bird in the sky ♫
♫ Why are you wailing so sadly? ♫
♫ You can’t find where ♫
♫ Wildflowers have fallen anyway ♫
Long live!
Long live the King and Queen! Long live the King and Queen!
Long live the King and Queen!
Lee Seong Gye, Joseon's first King
♫ Sword dance and flower-viewing ♫
♫ The melody of Do Hwa Jeon is shivery cheerful ♫
♫ All the great works for the past 500 years ♫
♫ were all for nothing ♫
The king was chased out.
The king, you say?
By the way, that Cheok Sa Gwang, or whatever, has been pretty quiet.
Everyone was so nervous thinking she would seek revenge.
Then again, what would she able to do by herself.
That seems so.
I won't seek revenge.
If nobody hurts him, I won't fight anyone.
I just want His Highness to live a quiet life.
What does Cheok Sa Gwang look like?
Does she look like some terrifying witch?
No. That's not the case.
As the Chief Officer of the Royal Guard, and the Chief Commander of the National Army, Nam Eun.
As the Chief Minister of State Affairs, and the Chief Commander of the Five Regional Armies, Jo Joon.
As the Second Minister of State Affairs, Lee Ji Ran. As the Junior Second Minister of State Affairs, Min Jae.
And as the Chief Minister of the Personnel Affairs, the Chief Minister of Finance,
the Chief Minister of Regional Administration, and the Second Minister of State Affairs, Jeong Do Jeon.
I am afraid of not being able to take responsibility with my lack of virtue.
But due to the people's wishes,
I have taken the crown by heaven's command.
From now on, I will find a way to make all the people's lives better no matter the circumstances.
Your grace is immeasurable.
I heard that there are a lot of empty positions because many officials have resigned.
Yes, Your Majesty.
It will already be very burdensome for you to take on all those positions, but
please fill them up, Sam Bong.
Yes. I will create the country's name, and organize the government.
When are you going to start the civil exams?
Out of your system to establish a new nation,
I really liked the idea of choosing all government officials through the civil exam.
Is that so?
Without the skills,
all the Gwon Moon Sae Jok and military officials that took positions through nepotism,
aren't we supposed to start all over again?
Your command is right in every way.
If it gets known that without caring about family backgrounds,
all people will be given the opportunity to obtain government positions fairly,
we can recover the public opinion. It will be a big help.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I will make haste to proceed.
The harvest being collected from the farm lands cannot go above 30 doos per 1 gyeol (units of measurement).
Try to calculate the tax revenue with that in mind.
- Yes.
The key point of the government reform lies in how we can control the officials' desires and raise interest of the public.
Do not ever forget that while you think of a system that has a clear distinction of different roles and authority.
Yes.
How is the civil exam coming along?
I've sent the message to the local government offices in every area.
Also, I've sent the message to Seonggyungwan, Daehaksa,
and all schools in every region.
That's right. Let more people know.
We have to make sure that as many people as possible can take the exam.
Also make sure to let people know about the new military exams.
Yes, please do not worry about it.
Are these it?
Yes. For now, I brought these.
Are these the historical records of Silla?
I got them from the Royal Library.
I will provide you with some people, so investigate these very confidentially.
Will we really find traces of Nameless from these?
Yeom Jong, who started the rebellion with Bi Dam,
was a very successful merchant at that time
who traded with not only Baekjae and Goguryeo, but also the Sui and the Tang.
And during his later years, he was deeply involved in politics as well.
There are probably traces left in history.
Also keep an eye on Yeon Hyang as well.
Yes, I understand.
- Oh, is this it?
- Ah, yes.
As you've instructed, by reviewing education, character,
acquaintances, reputation and so on, I am narrowing down the candidates.
They will be the supporting pillars of our new organization.
The important thing is the strong will to resist succumbing to any power,
and the integrity to resist corruption.
Yes.
I am closely reviewing by considering those points.
Also from now on, make sure to assist the Queen well.
The Queen?
I already told His Majesty.
And prepare Hwa Sa Dan to be ready to accompany her,
as well as being someone that she can talk to.
Someone that she can talk to...?
I understand. Please do not worry.
But Bon Won...
What are thinking of doing with your connection to Bang Won?
His soldiers have increased, and the marketplace messengers have expanded as well.
He is receiving funds from the Min family as well.
Furthermore, His Highness would not see Bang Won.
His Highness is someone much more upright than me.
That is why I am even more worried.
Do you think you could embrace it?
You are probably trying to say that you are still right even if you have to die.
It's your temperament of wanting to do things the way you want!
Killing Po Eun. That will be your place.
That's not bad.
Husband, Lord Ha Ryun is here.
Don't look at me like that.
I had a hard time thinking of how I should serve only one king since I am a Confucian scholar.
That's not it.
I'm surprised that Lord Sam Bong allowed you to take a government office.
Well that's because you stabbed Po Eun to death,
the officials all resigned and the positions were all empty.
Isn't it right?
And because of that incident, His Majesty hasn't yet forgiven you.
On the other hand, I heard that Lord Sam Bong's government offices grew to four positions
He got one more today so there are probably five.
Today as well?
Since he took over the Dodang, the legislative branch, and personnel affairs,
now if he takes over the military,
that will surely be Sam Bong's world.
He's put himself in the position that he was going to put Po Eun in.
It can't be.
Once the Sadaebu who resigned comes back, His Majesty will distribute the political power.
Well, everyone is thinking the same thing, but...
That will not happen.
What do you mean it won't happen?
I can read Teacher Sam Bong's thoughts.
What?
Of the scholars you told me to investigate, seven out of ten are missing.
What do you mean they are missing?
Even their families don't know where they are.
Isn't it just that they went back to their homelands?
They weren't in their homelands either.
Then where could those scholars have gone?
Those scholars?
They were the scholars who put up posters about executing His Highness Bang Won, right?
Yes. So I followed after them, and they were looking at these.
This is a map...
Tongsung Village...?
Is there one of our people out in Tongsung Village?
There's barely anyone living there, so there's nothing to report.
Doesn't it seem like there's going to be some kind of gathering?
Boss! The assembly of the inspector general officials just ended.
These are the names of the attendees.
Okay.
You can write pretty well now.
That's because you're teaching me well.
Please have a look at this, Your Highness.
The scholars who wanted to execute Your Highness have been passing this to each other every night.
Tongsong Village.
It's outside the palace but it's not that far.
Should I go there once?
I don't know why I'm so nervous about the scholars' examination.
Since you are like that, I feel the same.
It's the first civil examination of this new country, so it's normal to be excited.
It will all go well because Lord Sam Bong has prepared it while even skipping meals.
Yes, anyhow I wanted to meet and talk with you.
Please tell me your orders, Your Majesty.
I heard that you skip meals, don't even go home, and just work all the time.
You are now a person who is in charge of an important position in the country.
It's only natural for you to wear good clothes and live comfortably.
You should get out of that shabby house now too.
Being an official means that I'm eating food and wearing clothes made by others.
We must not be affluent.
Are you saying that to me?
I'm not living that affluently.
How can it be?
Okay, let's go.
From here, it's Tongsong village.
There's nothing much though.
Warrior-nim, what's wrong?
Your Highness, there's a small disturbance.
Yes. We'll resolve it soon, so please come back afterwards.
What happened for you to do this?
It's nothing, so if you will go back to the palace we will...
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Hey... Come and have a look from here.
Just what is that?
What is that?
That... on tree...
It's Gwaegwan.
What is that?
Taking their hats off and hanging them on a castle gate means that they are resigning.
This was done by people who are against this country.
Moo Hyul, go and chase them.
Yes!
First look into what's actually going on.
A number of scholars you were looking for are missing.
Missing?
Don't you think it's related to the civil examination?
They're gathered and living there?
Yes. We followed that scholar
and there's a big village in the mountain.
I think there are approximately 300-400 people there and more are coming.
The people who are against this country are gathered and living right in front of Gaegyeong.
Boon, go and tell everything to teacher Sam Bong.
I think it was done by the scholars who followed Teachers Mok Eun and Po Eun to reject the civil examination.
Do you think they've been threatened?
There was no need to threaten them since everyone's already in rage.
They must be determined to ruin this country's name and its legitimacy.
The missing scholars didn't go back to their hometowns either.
They could be gathered somewhere planning something.
What do you mean?
There's no way of knowing that, but such a large number of people has disappeared in such a short time.
Just what are they doing and where?
I found out where they are and what they are doing.
Where was it?
They're on Mount Gwangdeok, West of Gaegyeong.
What are they doing there?
They gathered and are building a village.
What are you saying? Say it in details
There was a map being passed around between the scholars, so we chased after them.
And when we went to Tongsung Village in Mount Gwangdeok,
everyone took off their traditional hats and scholar hoods,
and went to the village after donning straw hats.
Gwaegwan.
This is their demonstration that they do not approve the government and the king.
We can't just let this be.
We can only stay still.
It's not illegal so we can't reprimand them,
but such movements can be critical at a time like this.
When the news spreads, more people will join them, and as you saw at the civil exam,
we won't be able to tell what kind of group actions they will take.
What?
It's not even enough that no one turned up for the examination. Now they are gathered to live there?
Yes.
The people call it Doomundong.
Doomundong?
It must mean a village outside the gate.
I've never seen such bastards before!
We can't just leave them alone like that, right outside the capital.
Yes that is so. If they try to create some kind of conspiracy
there's no telling what might happen.
Let's send the troops.
I'm saying we should bring them all in.
For what crime?
What do you mean what crime? The crime for despising the royal family, and disturbing the country.
It's not like they caused a commotion, or sent petitions.
Since we even declared rule by law, system and ordinance,
it's not right for us to do that.
But if we leave them be, more people will gather in Doomundong.
That by itself will become a representation of denying the new dynasty.
Doomundong... Doomundong...
We are moved to tears with gratitude for giving everyone in our family a royal nickname.
What happened to Bang Woo and Bang Ui?
Bang Ui is still in Ham Joo while Bang Woo Hyung-nim is not feeling well
He is staying at Jebyeokdo.
Is he still like that?
I will make a visit to Hyung-nim.
Okay.
It's been a while, Bang Gan.
How was the situation in Ham Joo?
Yes. There's nothing wrong in Ham Joo.
The North is also quiet.
Okay. You have worked hard instead of your father and older brothers.
What hard work did I do when Father, you...
I heard that you are very concerned because the of civil exam incident and Doomundong.
(Lee Bang Gan - Prince Hwae Ahn, Lee Seong Gye's fourth son)
I've been in discussions with the Do Dang for days
but it's not an easy decision.
Those people who do not fear the heavens,
(Lee Bang Gwa - Prince Yeon Ahn, second son)
how could they just do that in front of the capital?
Because their respected teacher became like that,
they are probably saying they'll do something.
It's been a while.
Yes, Your Highness.
It seems that His Majesty is deeply worried about the problem with Doomundong.
Yes. Since they are people who should be the country's support,
he must be feeling great regret.
Is there something I can do to help?
Your Highness would?
Yes.
I don't mean anything else.
No matter how you look at it, my immature actions were the cause of it, so
I'm thinking of helping out.
I am very grateful that you would like to help out.
But why do you want to help?
I will persuade those people
to come back. What do you think?
I will persuade them.
You, who killed Po Eun, will persuade the scholars and officials who resigned?
Just what are you thinking?
How will you persuade them?
I will give it a try.
Can you really do it, Your Highness?
If I do my best with sincerity, wouldn't it lead to a good result?
Yes. Since you've decided to fix what you did yourself,
I think it would be good to step up and do it yourself.
At a time when a new country has just been established, a place like Doomundong must not exist.
Yes.
But I won't be able to persuade all of the hundreds of scholars who are there.
I will persuade those I can.
As for those who I cannot persuade, I will at least not let them stay at Doomundong.
If you can do that, it will be a big help to the nation.
Then, I beg of you.
What are you going to do?
The people who are in Doomundong think of you as an enemy.
How will you persuade those people?
With hard work and sincerity.
Husband.
Are you trying to change His Majesty's cold feelings towards you?
If the person who killed Po Eun can change those people's hearts,
this will become a symbolic event
But how?
Do you have a plan?
An intelligent Prince wouldn't be acting like this without a plan in mind.
Well since it seems like there will soon be a crown prince proclamation,
before that you'll have to calm His Majesty's heart, right?
It's western wind.
Bang Won will persuade them?
Yes.
If we can persuade them, nothing could be better than that.
Even if he can't, in showing his sincerity
there will be no harm.
Prince Jeong An (Lee Bang Won) already left for today so please wait.
We will be going to the West Gate of Doomundong so go to the East Gate.
Yes!
Let's go!
Since Prince Jeong An is not scared of difficult and complicated things,
it's worth expecting something from it.
Is he trying to gain merit to earn my forgiveness?
Do that. If you do...
You bastard!
Hey!
You killed Teacher Po Eun. What nerve do you have to come here?
We don't feel like listening to even a word of your excuse.
I don't make any excuses.
Then, why are you here?!
Set it on fire!
What? Set it on fire?
What was that? Didn't you say you'll persuade them?
I will persuade them when they come out.
There will be those who come out and those who'll be burned in the fire.
I will only take and persuade those who come out.
Your Highness!
This is my way and my place.
How would I rise up without touching this field of shit when it's a field of shit I've fallen in?
Father, and also teacher Sam Bong,
you'll see.
I will build power in my own way.
Even if I were to die and live again, I believe I'm right.
I might find my way by doing this.
What are you doing?!
Set it on fire! Right now!
Six Flying Dragons
You bastard! Do you not even fear the heavens?
They're still overflowing with strength.
Your Highness, Prince Jeong An has disappeared.
The rule of primogeniture has been broken!
Come in.
He has to become the king no matter what.
What about making Prince Ui An the Crown Prince?
(Prince Ui An: Lee Bang Seok)
Crown Prince. Crown Prince, you say?