This program was created with the support of the Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, Korea's Creative Content Agency, and Media Content.
The person I'm going to serve as my lord
is linked to him by blood, that Pok Doo that's hard to control.
According to military strategies,
if you want the commander to collapse, then aim for his horse first.
Teacher Sam Bong, my place in that cave,
please take care of it well. I will surely come back to it.
The An Byeon Chaek wasn't sent by Lee Seong Gye.
His son, Lee Bang Won, stamped it with his father's seal and forged it.
Lee Bang Won?
So, things have become more difficult.
Now, Lee In Gyeom will counterattack.
Lee Bang Won, Lee Bang Won!
Did you suddenly think of a good idea?
Have you thought about the thing that is the hardest to understand in this whole palace?
How is it that Lee Seong Gye's An Byeon Book
was favored by Hong In Bang and Gil Tae M? It was this.
You've pinpointed it.
Now, I will make people understand that.
What is that?
I-It's nothing.
Nothing? You're face suddenly went pale. What is it that you're being like that?
Through the An Byeon Book, the tax revenue of the now secured Northeastern side
will be divided between Hong In Bang, Gil Tae Mi, and Lee Seong Gye
in a secret agreement?
It's only an anonymous letter. There isn't any basis for it, either.
No, no. It couldn't be.
Lee Seong Gye is not that kind of person. Certainly.
Pan Yi Bu Sa,
(Pan Yi Bu Sa: a government post name)
I need to ask for a favor.
Yes. Please speak.
General!
I... have something I want to consult with you about.
What is it, Pan Yi Bu Sa?
Have you heard about the stories going around now?
Are you talking about the anonymous letter that nobody can confirm?
(Choi Yeong)
You have to read this.
I want to tell you that a series of letters like this shouldn't be overlooked.
Isn't it strange?
If the contents of that letter aren't true, then just why
would you, Gil Tae Mi and Hong In Bang, vote in favor of the An Byeon Book when you have a really bad relationship with Lee Seong Gye?
That's definitely because,after stabilizing the Northeastern side (Woo Hak Joo),
there will be a strong defense.
Ah, so that was it.
For the stability of the Northeastern side?
But during the last Do Dang meeting, what did you say?
"Is Lee Seong Gye the only one protecting the country?" Didn't you say that?
That is...
Look here. Seung Rok Dae Bu!
(Seung Rok Dae Bu: a government official during the Goryeo era)
Kwa Jeuk...Mul Tan Gae?
(Kwa Jeuk Mul Tan Gae: Not hesitating to immediately fix what you did wrong)
(Gil Tae Mi)
There's a saying like this!
According to Jung Yong! Jung Yong!
(Jung Yong: Doctrine of the Mean, one of the 4 Books of Confucian texts)
Non Eo.
(Non Eo: Analects, one of the four books)
Non Eo. According to Non Eo!
It means that a superior person should not be afraid of fixing what he did wrong.
But right now, I am showing you my image as a superior person.
What is wrong with that?
Ah, seriously.
Did I really say that?
Anyway, there was an uproar at the royal palace because of this so we need to investigate.
Investigate? What investigation do you need?
What?
(He spoke informally to someone older than him.)
What? You bastard!
-Bastard? Bastard?
-What, you bastard?
- I ought to just--
- Bastard? Why?
Hey, you bastard!
Stop!
Prime Minister.
Me?
A few days ago, your son got nominated as a Gam Chang Gwan in the Northeastern region.
Gam Chang Gwan: an official rank given to someone who inspects tax and warehouses
What are you saying? It's something that I didn't know.
There's a written certification like this and you're still denying it?
Go Gong Chong Rang Gil Yoo has been appointed as a Northeastern region tax and warehouse inspector.
If it's the Gam Chang Gwan, then isn't that the one who inspects taxes in the Northeaster region?
How could this be!
Even with this, are you still going to say that you didn't have a secret agreement with Lee Seong Gye?
Then, it is true...
- It's true?
- How could this be?
It's that position too.
Okay, okay, okay.
Although it is anonymous,
since some of the Do Dang members have spoken up about their will,
I'm thinking of going through with the investigation...
(Lee In Gyeom)
My Lord!
If Gil Yoo has really been appointed as a tax inspector,
this series of circumstances is enough to be suspicious.
Do you really think that General Lee Seong Gye is that kind of person...
(Po Eun: Jeong Mong Joo)
No. Do you think he's someone who would do that?
Lord.
Didn't we already witness the unpleasant crumbling of heroes many times?
It's just a groundless rumor.
It's a rumor, just a rumor. But in that rumor, General Lee Seong Gye
will get the most fatal blow.
It is indeed fatal. Integrity...
He is attacking Lee Seong Gye's biggest weapon, his integrity.
Yes. As is expected of Lee In Gyeom.
I need to go to Ham Joo. I need to meet General Lee Seong Gye.
A report came in saying that Lee Shin Jeok is coming to Gaegyeong by Lee Seong Gye's order.
Please decide after meeting him first. He'll be here soon.
Just what are you saying?
It's as you heard, Hyung-nim.
So, at a time like this when the war with Ho Bal Do has started, you came here to Gaegyeong?
(Lee Bang Woo)
Yes. I already relayed the message and was about to go back immediately, but you were scolding me.
(Lee Bang Gwa)
Then immediately withdraw the An Byeon Book, give the documents to the Do Dang, and go back to Ham Joo.
But Hyung-nim.
Is withdrawing the An Byeon Book right, or...
Whether it is right or wrong, Father has already decided. We can just follow him.
He is our father but he is also the leader of the Ga Byeol Cho.
(Ga Byeol Cho: Lee Seong Gye's secret private army.)
It's what we have to do according to our military discipline.
How could you also be played by Bang Won's lies?
Where are you going? Where are you going that you're packing you're stuff?
Ham Joo.
Ham Joo?
To take responsibility.
You said that being an adult is taking responsibility.
(Lee Bang Won)
Withdrawing the An Byeon Book?
Lee Bang Gwa has the documents to withdraw the An Byeon Book and he has arrived in Gaegyeong.
Where is Lee Bang Won's house? Lead me there.
What are you going to do?
Gyo Ui Lee is going to Lee Bang Won's house, right? First, we have to stop him.
In the end, there's a sequence to giving up. It has to be that way to allow the next move.
Hey, I'm fine with you going wherever, but you have to tell me where ajussi is before you go.
Young Master!
Did you come from Ham Joo?
Ah, there's a big problem. The general told me to catch you immediately.
(Jo Young Gyu)
Like your legs will get clubbed... Like, really! Well, it's that kind of atmosphere.
I'm already on my way to Ham Joo anyway.
I'll go and settle things.
Aigoo, I should've stopped him back then. What kind of hard work is this when the An Byeon Book will be withdrawn anyway...
What did you say?
Young Master Bang Gwa came with me.
He has the documents to withdraw the An Byeon Book.
You bastard!
No matter how young and foolish you are, how could you behave in such an immature manner?
Everything is my fault. Still, how could you withdraw the An Byeon Book?
That will not do.
I will go to Ham Joo and receive my punishment, whatever it is.
You must not withdraw it, Hyung-nim!
This bastard still cannot clear his head.
There's an execution in this mountain-like work.
Did you see the Ga Byeol Cho and Northeastern region that you rattled?
Go to Ham Joo and accept your punishment. You will be on detention.
Hurry and go to the Do Dang. Hand over the documents of withdrawal to them.
Yes, Hyung-nim.
Hyung-nim! You must not do this.
Please hold on to it for just a bit. I will meet Father and I can persuade him.
Please wait.
Bang Won, you bastard!
What are the police doing here?
Is General Lee Seong Gye's fifth son, Lee Bang Won here?
He is but why are you looking for him?
He is being charged of having illegal dealings with Head of Seonggyungwan, Hong In Bang, to get the An Byeon Book approved.
Arrest him!
Yes!
It is you, Hap Ha.
In thinking of your next step regarding Head of Seonggyungwan, Hong In Bang,
(Cho Young: Hwa Sa Dan Owner)
you must be busy.
That's why you called on to your Jang Goon.
(Jang Goon: General, a chess piece)
I...
I didn't call my General for Hong In Bang.
What?
Then for whom?
I think Hong In Bang is just being controlled.
Then, is Lee Seong Gye standing behind Hong In Bang?
No.
A glimmering shadow behind Lee Seong Gye and Hong In Bang...
I've sent the General to that shadow.
Even if you meet with Gyo Ui Lee, how will you block the documents?
Isn't that Bang Won?
The shadow behind Lee Seong Gye.
Can you see and receive it this time?
We can gain four things from just this one happening.
First, if the arrested Bang Won, in the middle of being tortured,
has something bad happen to him,
the forging of the An Byeon Book documents will be buried.
What?
Second, if that happens, Lee Seong Gye and Lee In Gyeom
will have already crossed a river of no return.
Lee Seong Gye will be standing in the position you wanted him in.
Then, third. The thing you are worried about, Bon Won,
that serious Pok Doo,
will be naturally solved.
So are you just going to watch over this situation?
(Lee Shin Jeok)
Are you just going to let a person without sin be tortured to death?
Sin and death have never been related to begin with.
You don't die because you have sinned
and you don't live because you have no sins.
In this country, has any death
been related to sin?
What? This wench is wholeheartedly wishing ill upon others!
We are all gathered to change that kind of country!
Elder Bon Won, this must never happen.
Let's say that Bang Won did something wrong.
Even so, you can't sacrifice him to this kind of conspiracy.
I only follow Elder Bon Won's will.
I will follow your decision.
Bug. A bug.
A bug has finally started crawling in my mind.
No, it was from the moment I saw Lee Bang Won arrested.
What Yeon Hee said was right.
If I let Lee Bang Won be tortured to death,
the many things that came to be might get easily and swiftly be resolved.
I can just turn my head away for a bit.
In that smooth-sailing process,
how many people need to die?
That's a process we need to go through.
Every great cause is followed by hardship.
Taking responsibility.
I've already prepared myself for that.
It's a bug. A bug.
(Sam Bong: Jeong Do Jeon)
But...
We have to save Young Master Bang Won!
We need to do something, whatever it is.
Hurry and send the documents to cancel everything, okay?
Give them to me.
What are you going to do?
I will not send this.
- Hyung-nim!
- This is how Lee In Gyeom
is proclaiming war against our family.
The Ga Byeol Cho doesn't avoid war!
Hyung-nim.
You two command the Gaegyeong Ga Byeol Cho
and be ready and in position.
- Yes, Hyung-nim.
- Yes!
I will go to Ham Joo, report the situation to Father,
and receive a strict military command.
He is being charged with illegal dealing with Head of Seonggyungwan Hong In Bang to get the An Byeon Book approved.
Hong In Bang...
You met?
Yes. That night when I got attacked,
it is true that Lee Bang Won came to me.
(Hong In Bang)
We didn't have a secret agreement but there's also no evidence of that.
What's the use of evidence?
If Lee Bang Won confesses, then that would be the evidence.
How can such a young kid endure police torture?
Let's kill him.
Lee Bang Won...
If he dies,
we might be suspected, but
so what?
Let's kill him!
Elder Hong In Bang!
It's an important matter. You have to see me, Elder!
Father!
Un Nyeon, no!
You!
Crazy wench, you came here on your own!
After meeting with the Elder, what will you do?
Let go of this! Let go!
Follow me.
- Follow me.
- What's going on?
Elder, this wench is the mastermind of the Western district village.
She came here on her own.
Transfer her to the government office.
Young Master Lee Bang Won...
I was sent here by Young Master Lee Bang Won.
What happened on that night... I knew about it.
(Boon Yi)
Bang Won sent you?
Actually, I wasn't sent by Young Master Bang Won.
I came here to meet you.
That night, there wasn't a secret agreement,
but I know that you said that you will join hands with General Lee Seong Gye.
So?
Then, you should have prevented it!
That's...
what Young Master Bang Won would probably think.
I came instead of him.
If something bad happens to Young Master Bang Won while he's being tortured,
can't you to predict what General Lee Seong Gye will do?
The time is limited!
You have to save Young Master Bang Won fast!
There's no reason for Lee In Gyeom to kill Bang Won.
He only wants to hear Lee Seong Gye's confession.
Even so,
in the investigation office,
we don't know what might happen in the middle of torture.
How can you be calm like this?
You're passionate.
What's you're relationship with Bang Won?
What relationship do you have with him that you, a girl from the Western district,
would come running here on your own when you could be caught and killed?
So what is your reason for passionately asking that Bang Won be saved?
Could it be
that you and Bang Won...
He bought shoes
- for me.
- What?
A certain nobleman kills us
but Young Master bought me shoes.
I will do something
so meet Bang Won and tell him this.
You know, I
am someone who renounced my belief as soon as I entered the investigation office.
But that bastard, Bang Won,
always said that is different than I am.
But he must never mention my name
or his father's name in a confession.
If our names come up,
everything that you are worried about will happen.
Is it Ap Seul?
Ap Seul: a method of torture that presses the knees using a heavy object.
Is it fire torture? Or torturing by hitting my body?
If they hit me, the bones in my knees will be broken
and I won't be able to walk again.
If I get out of here alive,
how will I look?
You are here because of the charge against you saying you had illegal dealings with Hong In Bang.
The torture will continue until you confess to that.
There was no secret agreement of any kind.
Let's start.
Yes.
Before flying,
there's no way of knowing if I am a chicken or a bird
Lee Bang Won, you punk.
This time, you have to withstand it! Endure!
I am not a chicken.
You have to come out fast!
Yes, I understand.
This way.
Hey, Lee Bang Won!
Hey!
How did you...
Are you okay?
Do you think I'm okay?
How did you get in here?
First, eat.
How did you get in?
Hong In Bang sent me in.
You met Hong In Bang?
He asked me to give you a message.
Say it.
He said that as soon as he went to the investigation office he renounced his belief,
but you always said that you are different from him.
So?
"So,
never mention
my name or you father's name."
Of course not.
I shouldn't become like Hong In Bang.
That's right, Hang in there.
Enduring it will be the wisest thing to do.
Ajussi will quickly make a way.
Teacher Sam Bong
wishes
me to die.
What nonsense are you saying?
If I die,
the forging of the An Byeon Book will be naturally covered up.
Then, Father will be Lee In Gyeom's opponent.
A big nuisance like me will also be taken care of.
Impossible.
You are being like that because ajussi scolded you.
Ajussi will save you and resolve this situation and everything else.
He will find a way to do that.
Will he really do that?
Will that person really do that?
You have to hurry and come out now.
Yes, I understand.
I'm going.
Don't lose hope.
Also, smile.
You should smile first.
Do you know why I like you?
Because I don't think you will die.
I don't think you will leave me.
You like me?
I won't die.
I will definitely live and get out.
Just wait.
Don't die.
I don't want to see someone leaving me again.
I won't even think about it.
Brother and mother.
I forgot about them.
Don't you forget.
Did you meet Bang Won?
- Yes.
- What did he say?
Where is ajussi?
I have to see him. I have something to say.
You're not a contact anymore.
How can a member act like that without permission?
Please let me see him for the last time.
- Grandmother!
- Aigoo, this guy!
Moo Hyul! Hey! What happened?
(Myo Sang: Moo Hyul's Grandmother)
Have you already caught the Viper?
I caught a better one!
A better one?
Could it be that you
caught Gil Tae Mi?
No.
(Moo Hyul)
I got General Lee Seong Gye.
You crazy bastard. This rotten bastard!
Hey, you bastard. Goryeo's hero,
General Lee Seong Gye. Are you saying you killed him?
This ridiculous bastard! Hey, get me the broom!
He's going on with this nonsense...
No, no.
I saved General Lee Seong Gye's son's life twice.
That's why I am now a second rank Buk Doo body guard.
Second rank Buk Doo body guard?
What is Buk Doo body guard? Why is it second rank?
Oh? Why is that swindler here?
Hyung, our household got a servant!
What servant!
What happened? Why is that person here?
That person...
Do you think I would just let that person who swindled our family leave unscathed?
So I went and gave him trouble!
I told him to take out everything that he has taken from our family.
That's why he's cutting costs with manual labor like that, every day.
Ah, Noonim! What cutting costs.
To a dignified person... He's deducting it! That's how you say it.
Noonim?
Ah, right. Now that we are living in the same house, while thinking of the age order,
I arranged a title for her.
- That's why...
- Ah! Forget it! Forget it! Anyway!
Grandmother, our hardship has ended now.
General Lee Seong Gye's eldest son told me to bring my whole family to Gaegyeong.
We have all become part of the Ga Byeol Cho!
(Ga Byeol Cho: Lee Seong Gye's secret private army.)
Ga Byeol Cho?
Our whole family to Gaegyeong?
So, our whole family. So what you're saying is we became part of the Ga Byeol Cho and we're going to Gaegyeong? Finally?
That's what I said!
Aigoo! Our Moo Hyul!
Hey!
Our Moo Hyul did it!
Our family is going but why are you the one who's happy?
(Hong Dae Hong: Moo Hyul's Master)
This Noonim said I am a swindler and spread the rumor in the neighborhood.
I don't have a way to survive in this neighborhood!
That's why you have to take responsibility for me.
Responsibility? Responsibility, my foot.
You swindled our family for a long time. What are you saying?
I've never swindled you!
Hong Ryun, Gil Tae Mi, Gil Sun Mi, I trained them all!
In that cold winter, with my hands trembling.
Why are you holding on to that again?
Moo Hyul.
Noonim! I'm... in pain.
You have to be responsible for me.
Servant Hong! Move.
(Gab Boon)
♫ I lived, I have lived
♫ In Cheong San, I have lived
(Ddang Sae: future Lee Bang Ji)
♫ Eating wild grapes and gooseberries,
♫ in Cheong San, I have lived
♫ Cry, cry, bird
♫ Wake up after sleeping and cry, bird
♫ More than you, I have a lot of sorrow
♫ but I wake up and cry
I did it according to your plan but this country has become more chaotic.
♫ Yalli yalli yallasyeong
♫ Yallari Yalla
♫ Yalli Yalli Yallasyeong
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
♫ Yallari Yalla
♫ At whom was the stone thrown
Look at the forest instead of the tree?
To wild grass that gets stepped on inside the forest,
♫ Who was hit by that stone?
you didn't give any consideration, right?
It's not that. It's not that.
In that smooth-sailing process, how many people need to die?
In that damn strategy to alleviate the world, how many more needs to die
for Goryeo to end?
So, are you going to stop?
♫ Yalli Yalli Yallasyeong
Or without much thinking, are you going to kill everyone now?
♫ Yallari Yalla
Will it do to listen to the crawling bug inside my mind? Will it work by doing that?
♫ Yalli Yalli Yallasyeong
♫ Yallari Yalla
This is not the time to be like this.
Have you found out anything about the Viper?
Yes. When he was young, he lost his mother to the nobles
and it appears that he was enraged by that.
He's not someone who would go under your control.
Just end your relationship with him like this.
He's a pitiful child.
Please let him go so that he doesn't get carried away anymore.
Elder! The situation has become urgent.
If he can't endure the torture, Lee Bang Won's mouth
will mention his father's or Hong In Bang's name.
If even your name is mentioned, Elder Bon Won,
everything that you have planned all this time will become nothing by morning.
If you allow me, I will infiltrate the investigation office.
A person being tortured in the investigation office and dying inside the prison is a common thing.
You don't have to do anything.
You just have to turn away for a bit.
That girl from the Western district wants to meet you, Elder Bon Won.
- Boon Yi has come to Gaegyeong?
- That's right.
She helped Lee Bang Won in Ham Joo and she followed him.
So I kept her out last night.
A person came into an organization and acted independently. You need to remove her.
Why are you being like that?
Have I ever told you that girl's name?
I have told you about my connection to that girl, but
I don't think I mentioned her name.
Actually,
I know her.
How?
When I was young, I also came from the Western district.
I hope that you don't say anything to Boon Yi.
Also, please do not ask me about the story behind it.
My brother left then and there was also no news regarding Unni Yeon Hee.
Could that Yeon Hee have been you?
Where in Goryeo can you find a person without a story? I will not ask you.
Where is Boon Yi?
At a time when the people are dying of hunger, there was a secret agreement regarding tax revenues!
We will clearly expose what is true and what is not.
We will clearly expose it!
Even the students are like this, I
cannot reject an investigation.
But you already caught and tortured an innocent Lee Bang Won, so that should do. What else do you want? You can't even make him confess!
If that young child is innocent to that extent, don't you think he would confess in that scary place?
Yes. It's either that he can't trust his conviction
or that he trusts Lee Seong Gye with everything.
Is Lee Seong Gye someone who would accept an offer like that?
I only voted in favor of the An Byeon Book because it will be a great help to Goryeo's defense.
Of course, it's also because I wanted to be in a higher position than you in this political war.
But there was no such thing as a secret agreement.
That's why I am going to do an investigation.
What's the use of saying whether there was a secret agreement or not here?
But how can we trust that investigation?
There's one person in the investigation office, like a Byek Chang Ho.
(Byeok Chang Ho: A stubborn person who you can't communicate with)
Ah, you're talking about the dumb-head stranger, right?
Ah, that person? Fine.
That person previously
raised an appeal to kick me out.
It will be okay if we assign that person to investigate.
- I was wrong, ajussi.
- Why did you do it?
Why did you help that person without saying a word to me or to Lee Shin Jeok?
I was wrong.
He only has a temper but he doesn't think before doing something.
For the goal in front of him, he couldn't distinguish between fire and water.
Why did you help him?
Didn't I ask you?
Because we are similar.
The people of my village
only have quick tempers and don't think twice when doing things.
They can't distinguish whether what's in front of them is fire or water.
That's why the people of your village died.
Yes, I know.
But we...
the people...
are like that—because we are suffering in hope.
We gain hope and lose it.
We gain hope again only to lose it. Yet again, we gain hope and lose it.
Because we keep on being like that, we get quick tempers and don't think twice.
We don't even know how to distinguish methods.
That's how we became like that.
I was wrong, Ajussi. I am really sorry, but
just like I went to Ham Joo to find you,
to Bang Won your plan
is probably his only hope for survival.
You and Lee Bang Won are different.
No. We are not different.
I first met Lee Bang Won when I was young and went to Gaegyeong to find my mom.
At that time, to help those of us who were in a difficult situation, that child
was the one who led us.
Also, that Lee Bang Won that I met again after growing up
risked himself in order to help us, like always.
Among the powerful people I have seen,
they were all people who have taken things from us.
But that person
was the first nobleman to help us.
Also, that person, more than anyone else...
No. More than myself.
He wishes for your plan to succeed.
That's why I,
more than anyone else, wish for Teacher Sam Bong's plan to succeed.
To defeat the Do Dang officials, turn the tables, and proudly,
proudly live with strength in my guts!
I wish to live like that.
That's why
he waited, waited, and waited some more, in that room,
for you to quickly come.
Ajussi, you have to quickly come back.
We will be waiting.
I know that both Bang Won and I are wrong, Ajussi.
Still, to Bang Won and I,
please give us a chance to make up for our wrongdoings.
Please save Bang Won, Ajussi.
Ham Joo
Shin-dong, Im-dong, Yang-dong.
(Lee Ji Ran)
If we strike these three strongholds, Ho Bal Do's incoming troops
(Ho Bal Do: Yeojin tribe's Chief)
will all be defeated by our Ga Byeol Cho.
As I said, they will be in a situation where they cannot move or back out! If we launch a surprise attack at daybreak,
Ho Bal Do's main force cannot organize their battle line
and we can annihilate them.
Lee Seong Gye
Between five and seven o'clock in the morning,
we will launch a full-scale attack.
Yes, General!
What happened to Bang Won, and why did you come alone?
Did you send the documents to withdraw the An Byeon Book?
Why are you not saying anything?
I didn't send the documents.
What are you saying right now?
Bang Won was arrested by the investigation office.
For what?
As a condition for approving the An Byeon Book, Hong In Bang and Father
will divide the Northeastern region tax revenue between yourselves. He was charged for illegally negotiating that.
Lee In Gyeom has proclaimed war against our family.
So, as the eldest son of the Jeon Joo Lee Family,
I decided in your stead.
We have never avoided a fight when our family's name was on the line, Father.
Shouldn't we save Bang Won?
If Bang Won has to die for what he did wrong,
it has to be by our hands,
not Lee In Gyeom's.
In a situation where we have an upcoming huge battle,
I am sorry for saying this.
No.
We have another reason to win.
Let's take Ho Bal Do's head
and discuss the next case.
Daronggarongjoorong... Daronggarongjoorong...
This really doesn't get loose.
That's right!
(Jukryong: Bi Guk Temple's Head Monk)
Who am I? I am Bi Guk Temple's Jukryong!
How could you treat a person like this?
The situation outside has become urgent so we have been busy.
I will explain our stand while we go.
Go?
Where are we going?
You have to go to Gaegyeong with me.
I will relay to Head of Seonggyungwan Hong In Bang the Ga Byeol Cho's stance.
- You're going to release me?
- Yes.
- Right now?
Damn it. They should've released me earlier.
If something bad happens to Lee Bang Won,
you said we would gain four things from that.
What's the last one?
I
find your hesitation a pity, Bon Won.
I became like that the more I understood.
"Am I right?"
"Am I also
becoming like other politicians?"
It's because I was scared like that.
By it,
at the moment of the great cause's desperation,
I feared that I am wrong like this.
You are right, Bon Won.
Don't be scared.
Yes,
I am scared.
But I
am me because I am always scared.
So,
I will not use your scheme.
Watch Lee In Gyeom's movements.
What kind of movement are you talking about?
It will be hard to accuse Lee Seong Gye just on a letter and some rumors.
He will fabricate some sort of evidence next.
Watch him while keeping that in mind.
That's right.
This is totally Hong In Bang's handwriting!
Yes.
Since three years ago, I have been training one of my staff to imitate writing.
Great, great.
Now, this...
You can just put it in Lee Bang Won's residence.
Tomorrow, the investigation office
will conduct a search there.
Yes.
Since, the secret agreement is written in detail, it will become confirmed evidence.
Now, Lee Seong Gye's moral integrity will collapse.
With that, to prove his innocence,
he will have no choice but to withdraw the An Byeon Book.
His alliance with Hong In Bang will also be broken.
I will be going.
I have placed it there according to your orders.
Let's go.
Now, Lee In Gyeom's desire is confirmed.
(Through An Byeon Book, the tax revenue of Northeastern region to be split between Hong In Bang, Gil Tae Mi and Lee Seong Gye.)
After fabricating evidence like this, General Lee Seong Gye's reputation will fall to the ground
(Through Go Gong Chong Rang Gil Yoo being appointed as Northeastern region tax inspector, Lee Seong Gye and Gil Tae Mi's connection is confirmed.)
while Hong In Bang and Gil Tae Mi will be driven into a corner.
Fortunately, I was able to remove it today.
But what are we going to do in the future?
Change the letter to this and put it in that place.
I will turn the tables with this.
Everyone scatter and search thoroughly!
Yes!
Search thoroughly!
- Search!
- Yes!
Sir, we found something strange.
They say that Lee Seong Gye's residence in Gaegyeong has been searched.
Finally, he's making this issue bigger?
They said that the dumb head in charge of the investigation is upright
so we can believe in him.
Using whatever method he can, Hap Ha
will stop the An Byeon Book and break off our alliance.
Whatever comes out of the investigation today is only to push us out.
What can we do now?
There will be something.
Something...
But at this crucial moment, where is Sam Bong?
He said he will be going to Ham Joo...
Today,
regarding the investigation of related materials to the An Byeon Book,
with the many members of the Do Dang,
I want to have a consultation.
Today, at the investigation office,
we heard that there was a search conducted at General Lee Seong Gye's residence.
Have you received the report?
No.
He will come to the Do Dang himself and report.
That way, there will be no unnecessary misunderstanding.
Open it!
I am an officer of the investigation office.
So that there will be no doubts regarding this investigation,
to personally inform you about it
I came to this place.
Have you found anything worthy of being evidence?
Today, from the hours of Jin to Mi, we conducted a search.
(hours of Jin: 7-9 AM, hours of Mi: 1-3 PM)
This was found.
Then, read the contents of that letter to everyone.
Yes.
This was found in Lee Bang Won's room.
No matter how long I wait, you don't appear.
According to your plan,
I killed Baek Yoon first.
Who is the next person?
What?
Weren't you going to save Lee Bang Won?
But mentioning Baek Yoon's murder?
Why did you place the letter the Viper left behind in Lee Bang Won's residence?
Don't you get it?
I don't. This is a different matter than the illegal dealings regarding the An Byeon Book.
Lee Bang Won can die with just this accusation.
Really? Will he die?
Bon Won!
An intelligent snake will not swallow a boar.
Yes?
If it does, it will break its jaw and its stomach will explode.
Lee In Gyeom is an intelligent and sensible snake.
Also, the current Do Dang can't handle a problem of this level.
What exactly are you talking about?
All of this
is possible because Lee Bang Won is Lee Seong Gye's son.
The letter got changed.
The Elder is crazy. Even if he's just manipulating, how can he put in something that enormous?
He's going to corner Lee Seong Gye as Baek Yoon's killer?
This was forged. It's impossible.
What reason would Lee Seong Gye have to kill Baek Yoon?
The one who ordered Baek Yoon to be killed was Lee Seong Gye?
Is he saying that he will go into war with Lee Seong Gye?
There's no way Lee Seong Gye will just sit back while this happens.
Whether it is true or not, if he finds out about this,
20,000 soldiers of the Ga Byeol Cho will be heading to Gaegyeong.
Po Eun, you're thinking of the same thing as me.
This is not Lee In Gyeom's work.
That's right. This is not Lee In Gyeom's forgery.
If Lee In Gyeom corners Lee Seong Gye as Baek Yoon's killer,
naturally, after calling him into Gaegyeong, he will have a plan.
There's no way he'd do it to the commander of 20,000 men now.
This is Sam Bong's plan.
We won!
Great victory! Great victory!
That is such a great victory!
Please, don't say that Lee Seong Gye had a great victory.
General Lee Seong Gye shot an arrow into Ho Bal Do's horse
and Ho Bal Do fell straight to the ground!
From then on the great military force just went jwang jwang kal pang jil pang
(He is making the sounds of the fighting.)
They lost most of their troops and they just escaped far, far away to the North.
General Lee Seong Gye is truly good at fighting.
But why is the atmosphere like this?
Hyung-nim, let's now go to save Bang Won.
Who changed the letter?
Who would do this?
Could it be... the shadow?
Was it you, shadow?
Hap Ha Lee In Gyeom,
will you accept
my move this time?
Six Flying Dragons
He'll try to deny the letter himself.
That person keeps on being fishy.
Is this the end? Can I only last until now?
Do you have a plan to save Bang Won?
Of course, I do.
Before the night is over, Lee Bang Won has to confess.
I don't know anything.
To save his son,
he'll probably come to me to negotiate.
Lee In Gyeom! You did something you shouldn't have done.