This program was created with the support of the Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism, Korea's Creative Content Agency, and Media Content.
Episode 32
What's wrong?
Why are you being like that? Did something happen?
Boon.
Speak.
Now... I'm done playing now.
I don't think I can have fun with you like this anymore.
Boon Yi
Excuse me.
I tried asking Cho Young about your mother.
What did she say?
If Yeon Hyang is your mother, it seems that Cho Young knows her.
So just wait a little bit more.
If my words go through, there will be a reply from there.
I will make sure to keep my promise. It's the same for the land problem
and I will surely find your mother.
But why did you do it?
What?
Why are you suddenly bringing out talks about your promises?
Also, we can't play any more. What do you mean by that?
Why? Do you want to play some more? It's too bad we can't play anymore, right?
That's not what I'm talking about.
Something happened, right?
- Boon.
- Go ahead and speak.
Say my name.
I'm asking you to say my name.
- Bang Won.
- One more time.
Bang Won. Lee Bang Won.
That's good.
What was that?
- Boon.
- Yes?
Don't call me by my name from now on.
Don't use informal speech either.
Now. Now...
I get it.
I understand. (formal)
If you call my name...
I think it will be hard on me. I think I'll feel weak.
If you use informal speech to me...
You don't have to tell me the reason.
It doesn't matter to me.
If the plan works out, you'll be part of the royal family. Of course, I'd have to use respectful words.
Letting me speak informally is something I am grateful for. It's also something that I didn't deserve.
I really liked it. You were really like my friend.
People enjoying life.
So that the people will feel happiness in their lives every day,
become an amazing royal and please practice good politics.
♫ I recognized you a few times. Because of you, ♫
♫ I am alive. ♫
♫ I restlessly follow your voice. ♫
♫ Even if you push me out a thousand times, I go to you.  ♫
♫ I shine in your eyes. ♫
There's no place for me?
No. All of this will be my place.
Now... I'm done playing now.
Are you Young Master Lee Bang Won?
Who are you?
I heard from Hwa Sa Dan's elder owner.
Nameless.
We are curious about you and you probably feel the same.
Let's have a talk.
Will you come with me?
I came because you wanted to talk about the things we are curious about each other. But this feels like a civil service exam.
Are you trying to see if I am someone who is capable of sitting on the throne?
The elders only want to confirm if Cho Young was telling the truth.
So they've come in person... Are they trying get more information about the land reform from me?
Who is your leader?
That person didn't come.
What? Jeong Ya personally went to meet Lee Bang Won?
Yes.
Who accompanied her?
I think she was accompanied by the woman who was always with her.
- Do you know where they went?
- Yes.
Show me the way.
According to Cho Young's words, you were angered because of Jeong Do Jeon's plan to give the prime minister complete control.
Why were you angered?
I already told Cho Young everything about that. I don't have anything more to say.
Do you not like the king's Five Rules that much?
Why are you curious about that?
We're judging whether or not the king's Five Rules are enough of a reason for you to make the decision to abandon Sam Bong.
You probably made that judgement before coming here. Why else would you show yourselves in front of me?
I already told you that I will not be used and abandoned like Hong Ryun.
Aren't you also supposed to give me answers to things I'm curious about?
So the two of you are bodyguards.
So you're the highest person here.
What about asking and answering three things we want to know about each other?
If not, I'll just go. What are you going to do?
I will do that.
Then, I will ask a question first.
What is this organization's goal?
Stability. Until this country becomes stable, we're managing it.
You put a person like Lee In Gyeom in a high position
and made the country into this pitiful state and you're saying it's for stability?
That's right.
After Lee In Gyeom stepped down, how many political upheavals happened?
Two kings have abdicated and there has been bloodshed between men of power.
I roughly understand what stability you are talking about.
Though it's pretty pathetic.
I will ask a question.
What are the king's Five Rules?
Why are they curious about the king's Five Rules?
Lee Bang Won couldn't have talked about that, right?
Who are you?
Where are the children of this house?
They went to Gaegyeong looking for their mom.
At that time, the children disappeared
and you were in a tight situation to be going around Gaegyeong looking for the children. Don't you know?
We were all at war with the factions.
It's probably not that. You're not someone who can be that hard on Yeon Hyang.
Isn't your heart different from other people's?
Of course, I also cannot understand
how she could have married and had kids with such a country guy.
Fifth Rule: The royal family cannot participate in politics.
That's all five. Don't you think it's enough reason for me to not continue with Sam Bong?
Now, I will ask. When did your organization start?
It's during the Silla Dynasty.
Under Queen Seon Duk's rule,
it started with a person called Yeom Jong.
Yeom Jong? The traitor who was with Bidam, Yeom Jong?
I will ask you.
Regarding the national system of the king asking the high priest for advice when making important decisions for the country's future,
what are you going to do?
I will get rid of it, of course.
How can such a system exist in a country of Sadaebu?
I will ask my last question now.
In your Nameless organization,
is there a person called Yeon Hyang?
Aren't you going to answer?
That's...
There is.
We will also ask our last question.
Why are you looking for Yeon Hyang?
Her son and daughter are looking for their mother.
Did they already meet? Could he have already...
He must not say it yet. Not yet.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Where is she?
Tell me where she is!
Gil Seon Mi! How can you do such a thing?
Did Lee Bang Won say something?
(Gil Seon Mi)
I will not be used and abandoned like Hong Ryun.
They definitely guarded the servant woman.
Just why? Damn it.
I will explain. Where is she?
What? They're alive? The children are alive?
Master Gil told me to keep it a secret, but it's something that will be exposed anyway.
Gil Seon Mi, this man...
From the beginning, you did something irrational.
What do you want to say?
"Let's disguise it as if the opposing faction murdered Yeon Hyang's kids."
That's how Yeon Hyang changed her mind and joined our organization.
It was a plan that you would think of.
Where are the children?
They're with Lee Bang Won.
There's a high possibility that they're in the Ga Byeol Cho.
Yeon Hyang also has a pitiful fate.
Yeon Hyang and I grew up here together as war orphans.
Here, we ate, studied, trained, and were raised as Mugeuk candidates together.
I wasn't able to become a Mugeuk but Yeon Hyang
became that person, Mugeuk.
Gil Seon Mi is meeting Mugeuk.
What... are you doing? To a servant...
Gil Seon Mi, I have a lot of things to hear from you.
She's Mugeuk. Keep your manners.
Bi Guk Temple's Jeok Ryeong is meeting Mugeuk.
In 1375, pressed by the opposing faction, we were near destruction.
At that time, you told me that the opposing faction killed my children.
If I hadn't said that, you would have probably run off to the Western district
and we would've been annihilated.
Did you receive orders from Yook San?
You probably did.
Yook San, you are going to have to pay the price.
Getting into another war among ourselves
is something that must not happen now.
Where are my children?
They are somewhere very close.
Where are they?
Lee Bang Ji.
The best swordsman of the Three Kingdoms, Lee Bang Ji, is your son.
Boon Yi is at the Ga Byeol Cho.
For the assassination of Lee Seong Gye, I told you to trick the best swordsman.
But...
That's right.
Even when you knew that...
Do you think it's just that?
What do you think I told Lee Bang Ji to lure him away?
If he wanted to meet his mother, I told him to come to Yeoamjeong.
That's what I said.
Continue.
All of this misfortune
started when you betrayed the organization,
abandoned me, and ran off to the Western district.
That's right.
Continue to rattle on.
The reason why abandoned His Majesty and joined this organization was you. Don't you know that?
Keep it a secret from Yook San.
How can there be such dismay? Gil Seon Mi
How are we going to endure this once Muguek finds out?
I personally met Lee Bang Won today.
Sam Bong's country is dangerous.
Lee Bang Won having different thoughts from Sam Bong looked sincere to me.
Did she not hear about her children?
Whether we're going to use Lee Bang Won as a sword, like Hong Ryun,
or to use him as poison, like Lee In Gyeom, we still need to think about that.
- Teacher Yook San.
- Yes?
You will be in charge of everything regarding Lee Bang Won.
You will have to find out more thoroughly about the plans of Sam Bong.
Giving me the authority? Looks like she did not hear about it.
Teacher, Muguek is giving you an order.
Yes. I will follow your orders.
As you all know, everything is a mess.
Like this we were found out by others, gathered together, and comrades that should have not known about each other now do.This is miserable.
Land survey.
I will go and give a report tomorrow.
Where is Cho Young? I need to personally meet her.
- You can't meet her now.
- Why?
- I released her.
- What?
Nameless came to me.
Did you talk about our mom?
Yes. I did ask,
but they all just looked shocked at the mention of your mother.
From my perspective, I do not think you can separate the matter of things between your mother and Nameless.
It must be frustrating but wait a little bit more.
Do you think that our mother is deeply connected to Nameless?
I don't know yet. If that is true, there's probably a reason for it.
That's right, Gil Seon Mi. So you didn't tell her.
If Yeon Hyang attacks me now, it will be another war. How can you not know about that?
Right. Did you find out anything about the one who killed Baek Geun Soo?
Yes, that night the one that killed Baek Geun Soo and the assassins next to the king, was not Jung Eun Gwang.
From what I heard from the police bureau, at about that time he was already dead.
Then? Are you saying the king knows martial arts?
If not, did his servant do it?
It was definitely Goksan's swordsmanship.
Was there any message from the servant we put next to the king?
Yes. I heard that there's a woman who is a contact between His Majesty and Po Eun.
Right.
They say she's someone he treasured when the king was at his house.
(Jeok Ryong)
It seems like the king trusts her a lot and gave her that duty.
This is the antidote.
If it was that woman from back then...
If we catch her and make her speak, we will probably be able to find out the plans of the king and Po Eun.
Capture her.
- You met Nameless?
- Yes. Those people came to me.
It's going according to your plan as expected. What did you talk about?
Their organization's goal is this country's stability.
What? Stability?
Yes. Also, it started during Silla Dynasty with a person called Yeom Jong.
Yeom Jong?
I understand. I will look into it too. Was there anything else?
No.
It is indeed strange that those people wanted to know about the Five Rules, but...
It was our first meeting so I think they did it to have a look at me.
Did they believe you?
Yes. Since I'm even training soldiers, they will believe me.
We have to have a hold of the truth. The truth.
Yes. I understand.
- Bang Won.
- Yes, Teacher.
If you want to fool your enemy, you'd have to fool those around you including yourself.
However, after fooling yourself too long...
Does he know something?
you can also become the fake self you're portraying. Be careful.
Yes.
- You there!
- Yes!
What is that movement? Why can't you do it?
Put all your heart to it and like this "heung"!
Don't we just have to pretend to raise soldiers.
I think he's trying too hard.
No. Young Master told us to work hard. Since we are doing it, we should try hard.
Moo Hyul!
Yes? Me?
There will be a example from an already-trained warrior.
Show them. Fifth move of the Twin Dragons of the East!
The pit of the stomach, you have to hit in the pit of the stomach, the pit of the stomach. "Heung!"
The side, do you understand?
We have to do the land survey again.
- Do it again?
- We already knew that the officers that are under the Gunmoon Saejok from each part of the lands were interfering with the land survey.
That is not the only problem. Even while doing the land survey,
the Gwon Moon Sae Jeok secretly hoard an enormous amount of land by donating it to the temples.
Yes. We cannot do it like this.
Then, are you saying that we should delay the land reform now?
If the land survey continues in this way, there are only 60 mangyul.
If we take out some for the country for this and that, then there are only 17 mangyul left for the people.
The land that will be divided among the people is absolutely lacking.
After retreat from the Wihwa Island, I've already
promised the people that I will return the lands that were stolen from them.
But what is my image right now?
I killed Choi Yeong, attacked Jo Min Soo and the Gwon Moon Sae Jeok and made King Woo and King Ja kill themselves.
I am a person in power who even sent Lee Saek, who the people honored as a scholar, into exile. That is my image right now.
But now you're telling me to do the land survey again?
What will happen to the promise I made to the people?
Yes. We have to think of the public opinion now more than anything.
The people's sentiment does not look good after we just sent lord Mok Eun into exile.
(Mok Eun- Lee Saek's name)
We have to continue even if it's lacking.
It is not that we do not know that.
But if we do not equally divide the land to the people, the people will highly disappointed.
Sam Bong, how come you're not saying anything?
It's a really difficult problem.
If we proceed right away, it won't be an equal division of land.
But the taxes will lower to ten percent, and
- it will be a big help to the people.
- Of course.
Let's enforce it right away.
But if we continue the land survey this clumsily,
the dream we had of really wanting to equally divide the land and give it to the people...
That promise won't exist.
We can just do it again in the future.
When, in the future?
(Jo Joon)
Equal division of land is done by looking ahead for a hundred years.
Do you think we can change the equal division of land every five or ten years?
What should we do?
In every part of the land, all of our men were involved with and interfered with the land survey.
The land survey wasn't properly done.
But, will they still do it?
Jeong Do Jeon.
Is it because of your mother?
Why do you look like you have a lot of problems?
Well,
the way I see it, I think you have more problems.
Is it because of the land survey?
I cannot decided whether I have to
continue with the survey we have right now
or wait endlessly until we have enough survey results.
When you are in a sword fight.
how do you judge between when to attack and when to defend?
For a swordsmen like me, we have to judge in a split second.
How do you choose?
It's not important what choice you make.
What's important is to believe in that choice.
The trust that
(Lee Bang Ji)
my attack and my defense will work, no matter what.
But what if you were wrong to trust it?
You die for sure.
Wow.
For me, whatever happens, now I just wish something would happen.
Still, if they do it now,
the people won't be getting more land.
Is that so?
Hey, Gab Boon,
you also heard about that rumor going around the market about the general, right?
What rumor?
No, well, it's not anything special.
(Myo Sang-Myuhyul's grandmother)
It's okay. You can say it comfortably.
Well, what was it again? About the general,
that if he retreated from Wihwa Island
just to become the king.
Only the dead General Choi Yeong is pitiful.
They say things like this.
Not everyone thinks like that.
Just the servants of the Gwon Moon Sae Jeok.
(Gab Boon)
Yes, that's right. Most of the people
think that things are so much better than before.
Did you come? My husband just now went out.
- Yes.
- Should I bring him?
If it's like this, the equal land distribution that we were doing can't be enforced.
Not all the people will get to share land.
Have you talked to your organization members?
Our members ask me every time they see me.
When are they going to own their land
and when can they go back to their hometowns.
We are not accustomed to
looking at the future.
It's because the people who are here today
might not be here tomorrow.
Even if it's not an equal land distribution,
they will probably be happy with just that.
But if we lose this chance,
we might not be able to do the equal land distribution again.
The people who got their lands stolen
will get their lands back but the equal divisions of land
might end by just lowering the taxes.
If our members hear that,
they will probably say this:
"Please don't let it end."
"Please give us land too."
It's not easy to do.
Yes, but
you do not just do easy things, right?
You will do something.
You will not look away and you will not forget about the people.
Then you will at least do something.
Then what should I do? Should I just die like this?
I have to at least do something to live.
As long as I'm alive. Is that what you're saying?
Yes. I believe in you.
We'll proceed with the land reform like this.
- Brother!
- Then do you mean to give up on the equal divisions of land?
We're not giving up on it. We will keep on preparing it.
I ordered Lee Shin Jeok to secretly do something.
It's been a while since Lee Shin Jeok was away. What was he doing?
I will talk to you separately.
Please allow us to move forward.
I have to.
Go ahead.
- Brother!
- Please trust me.
For now, we'll have to step forward.
There is a big problem in the market.
♫ Going away! Our general is going away!
♫ General Choi Yeong is pitiful.
♫ Because we are vexed...
We can't just stay still
while our land is taken.
We have to disrupt public opinion and stop Sam Bong.
Jeong Do Jeon. That man,
his teacher, our teacher.
He put him in a cell.
How can he do that to his teacher?
How can an educated person be like that?
Because of that person,
I went into exile and just got back.
Something like that was done to me
by someone I was close to for my entire life.
The plan that Jeong Do Jeon is working on right now
is just for him to gain power.
By using General Lee Seong Gye,
he's trying to get ahold of power! That's what it is!
How can a reform from such an immoral and evil man
be a proper reform?
He attacked his own teacher
and threw out his own friends for his reform.
In the end, he will ruin the country.
Did you not see the Gaegyeong market street just now?
How many days have they marching been for?
Is that all? Because of Lord Lee Saek's impeachment,
even the Sadaebu resent me.
(King Gong Yang, Goryeo's last king)
But Your Highness,
from this reform
the people will be in rich and
the public opinion will be taken care of.
Look at the public opinion now.
Who are the people on the streets blaming?
- Your Highness.
- I am tired.
Let's stop here.
Go and tell Po Eun everything that you heard.
Your Highness.
You look very worn out.
Please gain strength.
(Cheok Sa Gwang)
Everything will go according to Your Highness' plan.
Are you going to Lord Po Eun's house?
Who are you?
We have something to ask you so come with us.
Why are you doing this?
Hey!
What are you doing?
Don't bother us and just go on your way. We're just fixing a misunderstanding.
Let go of her hand before you talk.
What are you doing disturbing a woman this late at night?
Get rid of him.
T-T-That guy. He's Moo Hyul from Do Hwa Jeon.
Ya Cha?
Let's go.
Thank you, Warrior-nim.
It's nothing.
It's been chaotic these days. It's dangerous at night, Lady.
Where are you going?
I will take you there.
You don't have to.
It's okay. I will accompany you there.
(Moo Hyul)
You really don't have to.
My grandmother said that I should always protect women and children.
You dance?
Yes. I also play musical instruments.
Wow. You're a person of many talents.
I don't even know any of those.
Ah, among my friends, there's one who sings really well.
So it's not like I'm completely clueless when it comes to music.
Seeing you earlier, it seems that you're quite skilled in martial arts.
I almost got hurt there. Thank you.
Where do you stay?
I'm from Ga Byeol Cho.
Ah, Ga Byeol Cho.
By any chance, can I watch you dance?
I haven't seen one like that before.
I don't know if I will have a chance to show you but if there is, I will.
I will go now.
Ah, yes.
Take care.
Yes, Warrior-nim.
Why did you follow me?
Your senses are good.
You shouldn't have sent that warrior away.
We're not here to harm you.
Just come with us for a bit and answer our questions. Let's go quietly.
I will not go with you.
Then, we have no choice. Get her.
What is that? Just what is it?
This woman is not my match.
Are you Nameless?
If not...
Well, it doesn't matter.
Don't do this ever again.
Don't bother His Highness or Lord Po Eun.
What?
That way of speaking that doesn't suit her...
If you do this again, at that time, it won't be the back of the sword
but the blade.
The servant that survived wasn't someone who does martial arts.
He was not?
Yes. I hired a warrior and confirmed it.
Then, what is it?
Wang Yo couldn't have done it.
Was there another person?
It was that woman.
I think that woman killed the assassins and Baek Geun Soo.
The woman Wang Yo was going to marry?
I lost.
No, I was no match to her.
What?
What are you saying?
That woman was using amazing swordsmanship.
Then, that woman killed the assassins and Baek Geun Soo?
Didn't you say it was Goksan swordsmanship?
Perhaps that woman...
Cheok Sa Gwang?
While the market is this disordered, how can we go ahead with such a big event for a country, and
he said isn't it the right thing and to set it aside for now.
Did he say to tell me that?
Yes, My Lord.
If the king is also against it, like this, it will be hard for us to continue on as we wished.
Sam Bong, what are you thinking? What are you going to do?
Many places in the market are in chaos.
I know.
It is their last revilement. Do not be hindered by it.
If it were you, what would you do?
In the end, it will be done.
Land reform.
Yes.
It will not stop here.
Our goal is to end it at a reasonable reform.
What are you going to do with Yook San?
I'm thinking about it.
Right now, Jeong Do Jeon.
We met a really absurd opponent.
I don't know.
You don't know?
This uproar will disappear in a bit anyway.
But after this time passes, these same steps we were late by, we won't know how many steps it will take in the future.
Why are you laughing?
You have really become an adult now.
What?
What are you saying all of a sudden?
Saying that you don't know is very adult-like.
Is that so?
The moment I ask you a question,
if it were the insufficient and hot tempered old you, and not you right now, I was able to imagine right away what you would have done in this situation.
Meanwhile with your absurd actions that put others in shock several times,
you did not care what happened before or after, or look ahead because of your childish short judgement. What did you do?
At that time, you did something that you could never turn back.
Let's go to Pandosa.
Do you mean Pandosa?
Tell all your message people to gather up at Pandosa as well.
I will have the Pandosa door open.
Everyone, go in.
Can we really go into a place like that?
Then let's go in quickly.
The front mountain looks that way and
- also the back mountain looks...
- Aigo!
Our phoenix, General Choi Yeong, who has saved our country Goryeo many times.
- Aigoo!
- How could you die?
Aigoo!
Everyone look here. Something happened.
Hey there!
Hurry up and come.
- Where are you going?
- Let's go together.
Jeong Do Jeon. That man, for these past years...
Something big happened at Ganhan gate.
I am Jeong Do Jeon.
I, Jeong Do Jeon, impeached my teacher, colleagues, and seniors and sent them into exile.
It was all because of this.
Everything in here are Goryeo's land deeds.
In other words, these are
the lists of land that was taken away from the people and
the lists of land you guys have to get back.
Just because of some words written on these land deeds.
You guys have lost the land you worked hard for, for years, and
you were out of your hometowns and are wondering around in an unfamiliar place.
Now, in here,
there are documents of land deeds the country has harshly taken away from the people through huge taxes.
Also in Do Hwa Jeon, there's this much new data from the land survey.
It is 60,000 mangyul of land information. Of course that is not everything, but.
we came all the way here after difficulties.
With the land survey information as the base, and an informed plan for equal division of land,
we can get back most of the land that was taken away from you and
you'll only have to pay 10% in taxes.
Perhaps, this is...
But, as you have seen in the market,
the people who took and exploited the land have brought up complicated political logic and are going against it.
Just what is that person trying to do?
Politics. What is politics?
Politics might look complicated but it's actually simple.
Politics. Politics.
Politics is sharing and distribution.
The problem of politics, in the end, is who do we gather from and give to?
Who do we take away from and who do we fill up?
You guys! Who have you taken away from and whose greed have you filled up?
I, Jeong Do Jeon,
will practice politics from now on.
This country's land is a rotten land that has been exploited and cheated for the past 500 years.
How can everyone divide a rotten land?
Don't you guys think it is the right thing to set it on fire and do a slash-and-burn field?
- Slash-and-burn?
(an agricultural technique that requires cutting and burning plants to create fields)
What?
What is that person saying right now?
Set it on fire!
Burn them all!
Burn it! Burn it!
This is what you cannot turn back from.
If all these land deeds are burned,
there's no other choice but to divide and distribute the land.
Land.
Who's going to burn this? I'm a Sadaebu so I haven't done slash-and-burn.
What about someone who has done slash-and-burn step up and do it?
It's also good for someone who has done slash-and-burn to do it but it's about setting something on fire.
Don't you think someone who has set something on fire before can do it well?
I have set something on fire. When I got chased out of my village's land,
the land was stolen but the house was mine.
I don't have any way to make a living.
So I just set everything on fire and came here.
I also have done that, I'm someone who has burned some hay stacks.
Let's all burn it!
No! What are you doing, Jeong Do Jeon?
You bastard! Don't do it! No! Put out the fire!
No. This. What is this...
Now, this country's land will be reborn!
In September 1390, Goryeo's land deeds were set on fire in Gaegyeong and the fire did not die down for many days.
He was able to do it.
You are amazing.
But I will make you step down and rest soon.
That man... That man...
I still like him. Damn it.
Six Flying Dragons
Ajussi said that it won't end here.
This person...
Isn't he really trying to change the entire world?
Now he will be a direct threat to us as well.
Mom, are you being threatened? Brother can save you.
Nameless is me. Don't try to look for me anymore.
We need to help Po Eun.
We need to kill Lee Seong Gye. Sam Bong will get the backlash from this.