Episode 1
The outskirts of Geogyeong
And to see a person that actually shares his food with another
in this day and age...
What is life anyway? Live and share.
Do you come to Gaeseong often?
(Goryeo’s capital)
Well, about once every ten days.
For me it's been eight years. Were there many changes?
Eight years? A lot has changed. It's operating like a dog house.
Those three crazy bastards sitting in Do Dang are exploiting the middle class,
Do Dang: Highest institute of state affairs during late Goryeo era.
And the ones in the middle are exploiting the commoners.
As a result, common people are taking from beggars to live.
So don't just go around giving food away.
Then you will draw all the beggars in Gaeseong.
That's why (I prepared this) to eat before I entered Gaeseong...
By chance...
Was that my food?
Oh!
What's this?
Later on, if you come find me, I will give you ten times the amoun—
- Look you crazy bast—
- I'm serious!
Why, you....
Ai! Ai!
Just come find me later.
- Hey, you bastard!
- I will see you again.
Hey!
Who are you?
I've waited a long time to see you.
Me?
Yes!
Teacher.
A disciple I don't know about.
Then the person behind me is waiting for me too?
What?
I've waited a really long time...
Sam Bong.
You...
You are...
You came too.
You know me?
Of course I do.
I know you very well.
I don't know you. Who are you?
Then you? Who are you?
I am the one who was cheated of life by you.
Someone I've never seen or known... I cheated you?
Who are you?
I... know both of you.
I know you... very well.
Who are you?
So... Who are you?
I am...
Lee Bang Won (son of General Lee Seong Gye).
8 years ago, Hamjoo
Bang Won! It's dangerous. Do not come!
Never you mind, Hyungnim (older brother).
I'm going to catch him.
Ya! Ya!
Damn it.
Let's run quickly!
Fall backwards, Hyungnim!
Lee Bang Won (later King Tae Jong)
Lee Bang Gwa
Lee Seong Gye
Father, father I caught him.
(Joseon’s first three kings)
I said to learn the Gaegyeong language.
Yes!
Tie him up and bring him.
How nice!
Boy, our father sure is a Jantgar!
Jantgar: The strongest man, in Mongolian.
Again, again... That's Mongolian language.
He says to use neither Mongolian nor Chinese (Beijing dialect), so why do you keep on doing so?
What else should I use to call a Jantgar
but exactly that?
Doesn't that fit his description the best? Jantgar!
You're right.
If a man like that isn't a Jantgar, then who else would be?
The traitor started to run away.
I ran really hard!
What about Young Master Bang Gwa?
Hyungnim was following me from behind.
Little by little,
I caught up to him like the wind, and then suddenly like this—
Bang Won.
Are you going to neglect your studies? Are you?
I don't like to study.
I want to be like you, Father.
Like me? What is that?
Someone good at archery, riding horses and who wins every battle.
Isn't that why people are cheering for you?
Isn't that why all the people of this land respect you?
That is why I want to go to battle with you.
Do you have any idea what a war is like?
A war?
War is...
Come with me!
Who ordered you to commit this disloyalty?
Are you deaf? ANSWER ME!
(Lee Ji Ran)
This is the letter you tried to give to the spy within our group.
(Ga Byeol Cho: Lee Seong Gye's secret private army)
Lee In Gyeom sent this. Right?
I'm asking if Prime Minister Lee In Gyeom is the one watching your back?
Su Shi Joong: the highest ranking political figure in Goryeo
- Beat him up.
- Yes sir!
Enough!
You... You've already betrayed me.
If you reveal who is behind this act then you will be betraying for a second time.
Don't betray anymore.
In this spot,
let's sever our connection right here.
This is what war is about. No matter what words I use,
war is killing people.
Aigoo. Were you shocked? Was it scary?
I wasn't scared. It was just shocking.
Our General is a generous man, but he does not forgive betrayal.
Of course. Since that bastard, Jeong Nam Jo So Saeng,
he never allows (betrayal).
(Jo So Saeng: one who betrayed Goryeo)
Are you referring to that Jo So Saeng?
That bastard put all of his comrades-in-arms and soldiers, who he lived with and shared joy with,
into a deadly situation and tried to run away.
As he tried to do that (run away),
General caught him. Ah!!! The heartbreak!
Betrayal by someone as close as a brother.
Then what? What did he do after?
What else? Jo So Saeng pleads, "Brother, spare my life," as he runs away.
Right then, what he said as he placed the arrow in position was
"Don't call me brother." With that, Jo So Saeng!
Oh!
-He met his end.
-Wow...
Father is indeed awesome. "Don't call me brother."
No matter what, I'm going to become just like Father.
There will be no mercy toward traitors.
Move! Move out of the way!
Move! Where did you spring from?!
Lee In Gyeom
Ahh... why is Gil Tae Mi making such a fuss?
(Baek Yoon)
Elder. Elder! Move!
What did I tell you? Since you announced that you'd invite the envoy from Yuan,
(Gil Tae-Mi)
I told you that Jeong Mong Joo was suspicious, right? Did I tell you he was going to cause trouble or not?
What do you mean trouble?
He made visits to the Dowager Empress and whispered away. Now Lee Seong Gye is being called into the government!
The royal command already went to Hamjoo!
Huh?
I believe it was Lee In Gyeom. The spy most likely would be the one sent by Su Shi Joong (Prime Minister) Lee In Gyeom.
Why would that bastard Lee In Gyeom send a spy to this border area? To gain what?
General! General!
General! General... We have been instructed to return to Gaegyeong.
To Gaegyeong?
Yes, Young Master.
It's a royal command.
Royal command?
Is that true?
Of course! His Highness has given His approval. Po Eun: Jeong Mong Joo (Shinjin scholar, poet and scientist.)
General Lee Seong Gye will become the Jae Choo of Do Dang.
(Jae Choo: the highest level to participate in legislative organization.)
As I have sent a separate message to him, he will arrive around the first five days of the month, when the Do Dang meeting is assembled.
That's good! (Hong In Bang - nobleman)
Now we can prevent the establishment of diplomatic ties with Yuan and prevent the war.
This is not because Lee Seong Gye is great.
If Lee Seong Gye comes back, there is a big possibility that Choi Yeong will cross over.
Then Gyoung Bok Heung could back out!
That's what I mean. How many times do I have say it?
At this rate, if the Dowager Empress, who was shoved back behind the scenes, were to reemerge,
it wouldn't matter if you're the one occupying Dohwajeon, Prime Minister. That's what I'm saying!
Additionally, what if they join the noblemen? Then what will you do?
Sam Bong Jeong Do Jeon
Sam Bong!
Sam Bong... Did you hear? General Lee Seong Gye is coming.
This is because you detected and prevented Lee In Gyeom from carrying out his plot.
When General Lee Seong Gye arrives, the (effort to establish) diplomacy will end and we can avoid war.
Hmmm... General Lee Seong Gye... Don't trust him too much
What? What are you saying now?
Doesn't he appear to be jealous of you, Chief, who have achieved a great feat?
- Sam Bong wouldn't do that.
- Don't protect him.
Since you keep on protecting him, he steps above his station!
The one who saw through Su Shi Joong's (Lee Yin Gyeom's) plan was Sam Bong.
Sam Bong never said anything wrong before.
This time it's not true. It's only because Sam Bong has never seen General Lee Seong Gye.
Send your man to make a secret delivery to the border.
The border?
Yes.
What are you planning to do?
We should at least prevent the war.
We will be prepared to depart in three days.
Go to Gaeseong (Goryeo’s capital) and deliver my message to Teacher Po Eun (Jeong Mong Joo).
Tell Bang Woo to be ready.
(Lee Bang Woo - 1st son)
I'm going. I will be going too!
We will all be going together in few days anyway.
No, no! I won't go with everyone.
The oldest brother went alone, and the second oldest brother also went alone.
Bang Gwan Hyungnim, Bang Wi Hyungnim, everyone has gone alone.
Why do I have to be left out just because I didn't learn the Gaegyeong language?
I know you're trying to leave me.
If you'd let me go, then I will learn the entire Gaegyeong speak!
Well, in that case I will be the guardian.
(Jo Young Gyu)
If I went with Father there wouldn't be any sightseeing.
Of course. It worked out well!
But why do you look so dressed up?
You don't look so bad yourself.
I did it because I didn't want the Gaegyeong folks to put me down as a country bumpkin from the border.
You did well! Let's go!
Go!
Gaegyeong
Everyone get paired up!
The work you must do from now on is to walk around in pairs
and find the country bumpkins who have come to visit the capital, without fail.
Country bumpkins on a capital visit?
Aigo! Aigo! Aigo!
I'm talking right now!
Hey Gab Boon, where did your mother run off to
when she gave birth only few days ago?
My mom did not run away!
Leader.
It's okay. Okay! Okay!
Gab Boon, you can just beg for the baby's milk today.
You have to feed the baby so that the baby won't cry.
- What was I saying before?
- Country bumpkins coming to the capital.
But what is a country bumpkin coming to the capital?
You mean someone like us who has just come to Gaegyeong?
You're not a country bumpkin coming to the capital.
You are country beggars!
-Hahahaha!
-Don't laugh!
What kind of people are they then?
Listen carefully. From now on I will tell you who to look for.
I will tell you exactly.
First, they are wearing flashy clothes.
Flashy clothes?
- But they're totally over the top.
- Over the top?
They are wearing over-the-top flashy clothes.
And they look around too much.
They are always looking around, like this.
We joined the beggar's den just like you said.
How are we suppose to find Mother here?
We have to eat something.
Have you had a proper meal since coming here to look for Mom?
Did you just come for a free meal then?
(Ddang Sae - later Lee Bang Ji)
You said that Mom was dragged to Gaegyeong
(Boon Yi)
so we came to Gaegyeong and searched for her for a month
asking if anyone has seen our mom, Gan Nan Yi, alright?
(Gan Nan Yi is a typical country name given to women.)
The whole world is filled with Gan Nan Yi.
We can't find her just with her name.
Even so, we have that song she sang that night.
If we find the person who knows the song then we would find a clue...
Listen.
Do you know this song?
What's that? What kind of song is that?
Look at this. Just look at this, huh?
We haven't found a single person who knows this song.
There is nobody who knows this song.
Since not a single person knows this song, when we find even a single person who knows the song,
then that person will know Mom.
There is more.
That night, the person who dragged mom away, on his wrist
I saw this picture.
Gab Boon, go find someone to feed the baby.
I will find a visiting country person and get you some food.
- Okay!
- Go!
How are we supposed find people donning over-the-top clothes that are looking around too much?
Over there!
It's a little overboard, right?
- It is.
- A lot.
I'll be back after I inform our leader.
Keep a close eye on them.
Okay...
I'll be back after feeding the horses.
It's a taffy!
Everyone, here are some interesting items from the Western region!
Please come take a look.
Master! Master! Come look at this!
These... Aren't these corpses?
Do people in Gaegyeong not collect their family's corpses?
They don't have any family either.
Who is there?
Master, do you know how much this is?
Master! Master! Master!
What? What about the Young Master?
Nothing. He was just with me here.
You should have kept a close eye on him. I'll look here, you look there.
Yes!
Master!
You! Do you know who I am?!
You punk! Take it!
Do you know who I am?!
I don't know.
We know you have a loud voice, though.
You're laughing?!
That's right! Have your fill of laughs now. You have to laugh now, so...
Master! Master!
What did I tell you? I told you to laugh when you had the chance, didn't I?
You rascals. Move aside now!
If you don't step aside, you will die.
Young Master, come over here.
Where is my mom?
You are the one that dragged my mom away.
Me?
You are the one who hid this over there.
This picture in this letter!
The person with this picture took our mom.
This letter is meant to be sent to a spy in our army.
This was sent by Lee In Gyeom, right?
Ajussi, you're a traitor?
Chase him!
Get him!
Boon Yi!
What are you doing? Go after him too!
Are you okay? Are you hurt somewhere?
What are you doing? We have go after him too!
I should at least put clothes on.
So frustrating! You two are so frustrating!
And there is no need to chase him.
Why?
Doesn't the fact that he hid a letter mean that he's trying to send it to someone?
But now that you took the letter,
where do you think he would go?
I don't know.
Don't you think he went to see the person the letter was intended for?
Who would that be then?
Lee In Gyeom.
Is that so? Then let's go to Lee In Gyeom's house.
Lead the way.
Me? I don't know the way.
You kids acted like you knew where to go.
When did we?
I know where it is.
It is the biggest house in this city.
You know where?
Yes, I know. I go there sometimes to steal food.
Are you that worried about a country bumpkin from the North entering the Dodang?
If you give me the order, I will go and bring back his head.
Gil Tae Mi
Oh my gosh, what's this? It's way too delicious!
Really, what is this?
Oh my gosh, how can a taste so good (exist)...?
Of course, it would be tasty
(Lee In Gyeom)
since it is a piglet fed on human milk.
Anyhow, how can you, who control the Dowager Empress' Gyeongbok Palace
and even General Choi Yeong, be worried about a mere Lee Seong Gye? That's what I'm saying.
Since I do not know.
What do you not know?
There are two ways to put a person in the palm of your hands
—by fulfilling their ambitions and making them into my people,
or by utilizing their fears and weaknesses,
making them tremble in fear.
But I don't know Lee Seong Gye's ambitions
or his fears.
He hasn't shown ambition or fear.
That is why I find Lee Seong Gye difficult.
Here. If you go in this way, you'll see the kitchen right away. It's really big.
I said we should just go to the police...
If you heed my words, you can get a rice cake while sleeping.
(Good things happen when you listen to me.)
There really are rice cakes?!
What is that delicious smell?
Hey, now is not the time to be eating this food.
Hey, what is this? How come it's this tasty?
Let's go. Come on!
Come on. Let's go now.
Follow me now.
Go that way!
Isn't that Gab Boon's mom?
Is anyone out there?
While I was seeing my guest off, someone entered here.
Lock all the doors and find them. Hurry!
Yes!
What is that?
Oppa. What is that?
Why are people breastfeeding piglets?
Could it be that the meat from earlier...
This...
To make pork dishes, they make women feed pigs.
Is this why Gab Boon's mother has been dragged over here?
Just wait. If I tell my father about this,
this place can be wiped out with one attack.
Everyone engage to find them. Quickly!
Yes!
Run!
You! Come here!
How did you get in here?
Let go. Let me go!
Come here!
Search.
Come over here.
Those little rats. How dare you come here!
We found them!
Prime Minister!
I found the culprit!
Aren't you just a beggar who came to steal some food?
There weren't any other trespassers.
Forget it.
Just scold him and send him away.
Yes!
Bastard.
Why did this beggar learn to steal?
What do we do? It's locked.
Butler Song!
Yes!
You...
Do you know the story about Lee Seong Gye and Jo So Saeng?
Well, they pledged to be brothers.
It's said that Jo So Saeng betrayed Lee Seong Gye during the reclamation of the Ssang Seong colonial office.
(Sssang Seong colonial office: Yuan's governing office in northern Goryeo.)
That's right. That's what this world believes.
Tell them to perform what's written here.
Bastard. Bastard!
Young Master!
- Where are you—
- Move!
Boon Yi, when my father arrives, I will...
What happened?
What else? The baby died. Someone can just breastfeed the baby for a day or two.
How can a newborn baby endure?
Just how can Gab Boon's mom abandon her baby?
Look at this.
To make pork dishes, they are breastfeeding pigs.
Young Master! Young Master!
Young Master!
Is that a man or a woman?
Let me down.
Aren't you General Gil Tae Mi, Goryeo’s best swordsman?
That's what people call me since I defeated Hong Ryoon.
I am also pleased that I got to meet you, General Lee Seong Gye.
I heard that you're a shingoong.
(a person with outstanding archery skills)
But what brings you here?
Lord Lee In Gyeom prepared a big banquet, when he heard that General Lee was coming,
tonight at Dohwajeon.
You will be coming, right?
You must come.
Anyway, I have delivered the invitation.
What?
Baek Geun Soo was a spy?
That's not all.
To take young mothers and use them as piglets' wet nurses?
Then what happens to infants without their nursing mothers?
My friends witnessed it with me.
They are still being held at that place. We have to save them.
Father!
General. Lord Po Eun is here!
Hurry up and bring him in here.
- Lord Po Eun
- General.
It's been a long time.
What is it that I have to do in the Do Dang?
You have to block the diplomatic relations with Yuan and stop the war.
People with their limbs cut off are all over Gaeseong.
(Jeong Mong Joo)
And the bodies of people who die of starvation are overflowing in the streams.
At this juncture, how could he promote a positive relationship with Yuan?
And to go to war with Ming?
As the nation's Su Shi Joong,
he's accepting war to protect himself. Does this make sense?
Your thoughts and my thoughts are not different.
Although I'm not talented,
I will defeat Lee In Gyeom and stop this war from happening.
General.
I have yet to be defeated in any battle.
Dohwajeon: Lee In Gyeom's residence
Aigoo! General Lee, how long has it been?
Thank you
for hosting a banquet for such a lowly humble military man.
General Lee is the main pillar of Goryeo!
This feast is no big deal.
Ah, you are...
Is this your son?
I heard about my son's rude behavior.
You little brat! A son of Great General of Goryeo shouldn't be stealing meat.
I'm here to catch the spy.
Spy?
I've heard that a spy within Ga Byeol Cho snuck into this house.
(Ga Byeol Cho: Lee Seong Gye's secret private army)
Have you seen him?
Oh, is that so?
I'm hearing this for the first time.
I see.
Then...
I also heard that his friends and new mothers
are held against their will in this house. Do you know anything about it?
How could that be?
I've witnessed it!
You were mistaken.
Come, come, come. Let's go inside.
For our General Lee Seong Gye who's returning to Gaegyeong,
let's have a congratulatory drink.
Congratulations!
Now, now.
Now it seems it's becoming more fun.
Let's watch an interesting play.
Go ahead and start.
Ah...
The time was the 86th year after Goryeo surrendered to Yuan.
Nice!
Our King Gongmin finally crushed the thief, Yuan!
Great!
Take off pigtail.
Push out Gi Cheol's people too!
He wanted to reclaim the land that was taken away,
but the land was owned by traitors
who sold the country to build their own wealth.
To tell you more about the traitor's land,
it was den of bastards who mooched off of Yuan
for a hundred years!
However,
King Gongmin gathered soldiers and attacked them.
The ruler of the land was...
Who was he?
He was, he was, he was
a shameless and audacious traitor! Red wolf! Jung Nang!
Jung Nang?
Brother.
It's too high.
Hey! Hurry up and come down!
Hey!
That's the sound of a dog.
This wolf had a real son of a bitch.
It was traitor Shepherd!
The word shepherd implies Lee Seong Gye's last name, Lee.
Brother Wolf, the tide has already turned. Surrender now!
Surrender now!!
If you don't surrender, you will die.
You will die.
But if you surrender...
You will die!
I. I am Jung Nang!
Father, what do you mean get rid of Brother Jung Nang?
(1356, Ssang Seong Colonial Office)
At Ja Shi (between 11pm - 1am), Goryeo troops will attack us at the Ssang Seong colonial office tomorrow.
You will have to open the gate.
Father!
Yuan will collapse soon.
(Lee Ja Choon, Lee Seong Gye's father)
Then, even now we can persuade Jung Nang.
Don't say the name Jung Nang!
Now he is only an enemy of Goryeo, traitor Jo So Saeng.
If Jo So Saeng is a traitor, then we are too.
Shut your mouth!
Can't you understand?
If we contribute to Goryeo now,
then all of Jo So Saeng's assets will be ours.
I... cannot do it.
As a soldier, I will fight with the Jo family.
Will you really destroy my family line here?
Father!
Our relationship with Jo So Saeng is insignificant. Look at the big goal, Seong Gye
There was a traitor! Some bastard opened the gate!
Since the northern gate is the weakest, we must go through there now!
Jung Nang Jo So Saeng: head of Ssang Seong colonial office, traitor of Goryeo.
You can't go.
Was it you?
Did you open the gate, Brother?
Don't call me brother.
I did not raise a brother, but a dog.
Your family's lineage is that of a dog who bites its owner.
Goryeo.
What has Goryeo done for your family?
I gave you everything you have.
In the end, you bastards
will also betray Goryeo.
That is...
That is the dirty fate of the dog who betrays his owner.
You dogs of Goryeo.
Your family of dogs that bite their owner's hand will eventually
end up looking like this.
Give me my sword.
Hey! What are you doing? Why aren't you cutting his head off?
Take my sword!
I got rid of my enemy!
I got rid of him!
Did you enjoy the play?
Gaegyeong people are good at laughing about nothing.
Since you betrayed Jo So Saeng, someone like your own brother,
it must be painful for you.
We prepared in a hurry so we used swords.
Originally it was an arrow, wasn't it? Since you are a god-sent archer.
It's alright, General Lee.
You must have had a good reason for what you did.
Of course General Choi Young, and nobles who value loyalty over life,
might think differently.
In order to play out this hand, did you plant a mole in Hamjoo?
I never planted any spies in Hamjoo.
LOOK HERE, Prime Minister!
Now I understand
why you throw yourself into countless battles, risking your life.
You're generous to people, without limit.
So, why didn't you have a goal to enter Gaegyeong?
Why?
What ambition does he have to live that way?
Now, I understand.
It was because, more than anyone else, you can't forgive yourself.
But...
Why, now, are you trying to forgive yourself?
Why, now, are you getting involved in politics?
Why right at this moment?
Why are you blocking my path?
Why!
Does anyone else
know about this?
Nobody else knows
whether it will be secret between us or not.
What are you going to do?
Please
look the other way this time.
I beg you.
The First Dragon
The First Dragon: Lee Seong Gye, Joseon’s founder
25th anniversary special production
Six Flying Dragons
Preview
Episode 2
General Lee Seong Gye is returning to Hamjoo.
Father, why aren't you saving my pitiful friends?
We can't push this country into hell anymore.
What on earth are you trying to do?
No matter what method I use, I have to stop the war.
All the nobles could be in danger.
Lee In Gyeom's trap!
Are you going to do it yourself?
Only by going there myself will stop Lee In Gyeom, who is in cahoots with Yuan, and stop the war!
Man to man, can you promise me?
I promise.