Did you get it?
This move is way too big.
What do you mean?
I'm going to meet Jin Fei.
There's constant infighting at the quarry.
It's too chaotic.
Come back first.
Whatever happens, we'll handle it together.
Stop being so fussy.
And also,
about this,
don't tell Ran Yue.
You go first.
Where are we going?
I'll take you back to the clinic first.
In four hours,
call me.
If I don't answer,
call Cheng Feng.
Captain Ran.
It was Tang Jun who called, right?
The phone.
It's him.
Did something happen to him?
No.
If nothing's wrong, why are you so nervous?
Captain Ran,
This is about a case from eight years ago.
He doesn't want to drag you into it.
Tang Jun has his own ideas.
What we can do now
is to trust him.
Eight years.
It's been eight years.
All these years,
to find my father's killer,
he's endured so much.
He's suffered a lot.
I don't want him to keep going on like this.
For these eight years, not a moment has passed
without me wanting to catch my father's killer.
To bring peace to my father's soul.
But whatever problems there are, we can face them together.
Right?
He doesn't want you involved.
Because you matter to him.
Captain Ran,
Let me give you some advice.
You can be his armor,
but don't become his weakness.
Let's all take a break.
Have some late-night snacks to recharge.
Yours.
Little Fatty.
Thank you.
That's right.
Yan Zi is right.
You need to eat to have energy to work.
How about this—
Let me show you something cool.
Watch closely.
Isn't it funny?
Don't overthink it.
There must be some misunderstanding in this matter.
Jun would never join that organization.
Yes, yes, exactly.
This must be Erinius
casting an illusion on us.
As long as we can solve this mystery,
we'll be able to clear Jun's name.
Captain Ran,
Let me say a few words.
Everyone has been working hard lately.
I'm just like all of you.
I believe
there's more to Tang Jun's situation than meets the eye.
The mystery of the 909 major case hasn't cleared yet.
We all need to work together.
Let's catch the culprit together.
That's right.
United as one,
we are unstoppable.
Yes.
United as one,
we are unstoppable.
Are you okay?
Me? I'm fine.
By the way,
it's already so late.
Why don't you
go upstairs
and have some supper?
How about it?
Maybe next time.
Alright.
Then let's do it next time.
Well,
Old man
I
I'm hungry
I knew you were hungry
And you said you weren't hungry
Comrades
I'm taking my daughter upstairs for a late-night snack
Let's go together
No need, no need
Thank you
Alright, alright
Let's go
Xiao Qiu
Come
Come in
Hey, daughter
You, you, you
You
Make yourself at home
There's food on the table
Have a bite first
Dad
I'll make something delicious for you
Xiao Qiu
Sweet and sour ribs
Here it comes
Come
Eat
Mom
Why isn't Dad back yet?
Dad
He went to catch the bad guys
Once he's done
He'll be back soon
My dad is a police officer
That's right
Come eat
Here it comes.
This is the last dish.
Take a look.
Dad made this for you.
Your favorite sweet and sour ribs.
Old man.
When did you learn to cook sweet and sour ribs?
I learned it from your mom.
I was busy with work before.
I never had the chance to make it.
Try it.
How is it?
Does it suit your taste?
Here.
You have one too.
Dear,
Let me report to you.
Our daughter came home today.
I’m so happy.
I made for her
your signature dish.
Sweet and sour ribs.
Eat up.
What’s wrong?
Is Dad’s cooking not good?
It’s delicious.
Daughter,
In this life,
I’ve let you and your mom down.
I’ve let down my identity as a police officer even more.
Old man.
Stop drinking.
It’s fine.
Let me finish what I have to say.
In my whole life,
the mistakes I've made
can't be changed.
Every wrong has its source, every debt its debtor.
What I've done
I have to take responsibility for.
No one can escape that.
Actually, in my life,
the one I worry about most is you.
You're not a kid anymore.
When
I see you
married to Cheng Feng,
I'll feel like I've fulfilled my duty.
It would also be
an answer to your mother.
Old man,
you're drunk.
I'm not drunk.
I'm just too cowardly.
Dad.
Why are you still here?
I can't leave.
My brother is dead.
Give me an explanation.
What exactly do you want?
I want to see Jin Fei.
Your boss.
Wait a moment.
Brother.
Mao Xie's body was dug up by his brother.
He insists on seeing you.
Let's bury them together.
Sun Ruhai sent me.
Bring him over.
Okay.
Mr. Jin
Hope you've been well.
Thanks to you.
I heard
that Gao Ang's missing gun
has fired again.
It's caused quite a stir in the city.
The police in Luzhou are watching you.
They should have found you by now.
You said that person was a cop.
Mr. Jin,
if you walk the dark path too often,
you'll eventually run into ghosts.
You should admit what needs to be admitted.
Once you admit it, keep completely silent.
Don't let the ghosts haunt you.
It's bad for everyone.
Will you handle it yourself,
or do you want me to help you?
You choose.
Can you spare my life?
Mr. Jin,
your daughter is doing well overseas.
All these years,
the brothers have taken good care of her.
Rest assured.
Mr. Sun
Don't worry.
Everything abroad
has been arranged by me.
Thank you, Mr. Sun.
You sending my daughter abroad
is the greatest favor you could give me.
I will repay your kindness.
That's right.
This day has finally come.
Sorry, the number you have dialed
is temporarily unavailable.
Officer Cheng
This is Chu Hong.
Lawyer Chu
Why are you calling?
Did something happen to Tang Jun?
Tang Jun
He went to Yuanshan Gravel Quarry
to find that boss named Jin Fei.
He told me
if he doesn't come back in four hours,
I should come to you.
But I'm really worried.
So I'm calling you now.
Tang Jun went to see Jin Fei.
By himself?
Yes.
He went alone.
He wouldn't let me go with him.
What do you think—
Alright.
I understand.
Brother
You should go back first.
This—
Go on.
You came for this, didn't you?
Why do you have this gun?
Eight years ago, you, Sun Ruhai, and Gao Ang—
What did you all do?
Sit.
Since you've come to me,
I'll tell you about it.
Eight years ago, Shisong Demolition Company
killed five villagers in Xishan Village.
But Sun Ruhai got away unscathed.
Do you know why?
It was Shisong
who took the fall with his life.
Shisong died.
The protection from above could cover you.
We thought
we could get away with calling it a suicide.
But that cop named Ran wouldn't let it go.
If this matter got exposed,
everything hidden behind it
would all be revealed.
There was no other way.
Those above had no choice but to have him killed.
We found Gao Ang.
We gave him a sum of money.
He took this gun.
When I found Officer Ran,
he was eating noodles.
He didn't even swallow his last bite.
You killed my mentor.
That's right.
With this very gun.
Now, a life for a life.
I should settle the score now, right?
Put the gun down, put the gun down!
Who?
The car's been stolen.
Catch him, don't let him get away!
Officer Tang!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Tang Jun!
Give me the car keys.
Hurry!
Stop chasing.
I've already notified the Tongde Police Department.
We can't do anything.
It's out of our jurisdiction.
Leave it to them.
I'm going to find Gao Ang.
I'll go with you.
What are you doing?
It's for your own good.
Thank you.
Lawyer Chu.
Take this thing off me.
I've already gotten in your car.
And I agreed to go back with you.
I've been handcuffed for hours.
Are you afraid I'll jump out of the car?
I don't know how crafty you are.
Until we get to the station,
I won't take them off.
Let me ask you,
Why do you have black preserved flowers at home?
You suspect me too?
During the interrogation,
Zhao Lingjing said it himself.
You're the last link in the serial murder case.
I don't know either.
Why I was chosen to join their organization.
Two nights ago,
I received a package.
After I opened it,
there was a black preserved flower and an invitation inside.
According to their
rules for exchanging murders,
a new round of murder plans has just begun.
The Erinyes Plan
is very likely
still ongoing.
I
am definitely not the last link.
I think so too.
Zhao Lingjing's testimony
is probably half false.
So, in that case,
Jin Fei's death
has another cause.
Jin Fei shot himself.
I saw it with my own eyes.
I can testify to that.
I'm certain
he was also involved in Shi Song's death eight years ago
and was one of the killers in my master's murder.
In the whole incident,
he played a role in fueling the situation
and was a key figure.
But afterwards,
he disappeared without a trace.
He hid the expensive gun
for a full eight years.
If it weren't for Crab's murder,
he might have kept hiding it.
But because of Crab's death,
he was forced into the spotlight.
Behind him,
there must be a
darker force
pressuring him,
making it impossible for him to survive.
As for the source of this force,
I believe
it's not Erinius.
So you're saying
Jin Fei's death
was an accident in this plan.
It's possible.
I think you're right.
Erinyes never fights unprepared.
And right now, there's no direct evidence
to prove
that Jin Fei had an enemy for a revenge killing.
And you've also proven
that Jin Fei committed suicide.
So
he really wasn't
a target of Erinyes' revenge.
Officer,
I really wasn't the one who called the police.
I just went upstairs to deliver food,
and when I came back down,
my bike was gone.
What's your phone number?
One nine one
three three four two
eight nine zero one.
When you were delivering food just now,
did you see anyone suspicious?
Suspicious people?
Oh, right.
When I was coming downstairs just now,
I did see two men
coming down from this building.
I deliver food in this neighborhood a lot,
so I'm really familiar with it.
When I saw those two,
their faces looked unfamiliar.
And then
so I paid extra attention to them.
One of them
seemed to call the other one by the name...
Officer Tang
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Tang Jun
What's his name, Tang...?
Tang what?
I can't remember.
Oh, right.
That man with the surname Tang,
he was holding a gun.
I'm going to find Gao Ang.
I'll go with you.
Check the neighborhood surveillance.
Let's see who these two are.
Sign your name here.
You can leave now.
Officer,
About my car...
Can you help me get it back?
Don't worry.
We'll do our best.
Okay, thank you, thank you.
Nanyang Criminal Investigation Team
Cheng Feng
Escort
I need to use the bathroom.
I'm warning you,
don't try anything funny.
Officer Cheng
Officer Cheng, wake up!
Hello, Lawyer Chu.
There's a new case.
I'd like to report it to you.
The Luzhou police
just sent us a message.
Zhao Lingjing wants to hire you
as his defense lawyer.
Professor Zhao
Yes, that's him.
The perpetrator of the 909 major case.
Alright, I understand.
I'll come over as soon as possible.
Are you crazy?
Do you even know how to drive?
It was mainly because of that delivery guy.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have hit you.
But what if you had hit me?
But I didn't hit you, did I?
What if you did hit me?
Don't pull me.
Now they're arguing.
Wasn't it because of the delivery guy just now?
Should we try to stop them?
They said it was all about the crash, none of your business.
What are you doing? What do you want?
What do you want?
Stop fighting.
Let's go check it out.
Let's go take a look, come on.
Stop fighting.
What are you doing?
Let go.
What are you doing? Let go.
What are you two doing?
What are you two up to?
He hit my girlfriend.
I didn't hit her.
He didn't hit her.
We all saw it.
We saw it.
Let's go, let's go.
Everyone's leaving, everyone's leaving.
Let him go back.
Tang Jun
Tang Jun is here.
Go.
Tang Jun
Over there, over there.
Chase him.
Split up and chase.
Shout for him to stop.
Why are you running?
My food delivery is about to be late.
Who are you guys?
Who?
Food delivery.
Tang Jun.
You.
Cuff yourself.
Tang Jun.
You.
What are you doing?
Go.
This is kidnapping.
Tang Jun.