♪If not for you♪
♪I wouldn't have wanted
to make a name for myself♪
♪Only when I have your love♪
♪Is my invincibility not in vain♪
♪The towering peaks I've conquered♪
♪Leave me♪
♪Feeling empty♪
♪I've given everything♪
♪Just to follow you♪
♪Through life and death♪
♪Could it be that love♪
♪Is the true end of this life♪
♪Why does every battle♪
♪Bring deeper pain♪
♪I never got it♪
♪You once promised me♪
♪You'd give me ordinary days♪
♪Then I'd rather♪
♪Face blades and fall♪
♪Into your arms instead of the clouds♪
♪I'll pass through layers of fog♪
♪And barriers♪
♪The world's rights and wrongs,
wins and losses♪
♪Who's to weigh their worth♪
♪Only love♪
♪Gives me a sky as wide as the sea♪
♪I only want to be your hero♪
=The Prisoner of Beauty=
=Episode 9=
You're home early today.
(Wise Kashyapa Who Governs Eternally)
I am.
To congratulate you.
Why is that?
Do you know
who the Commander of Boya Forces is?
Who is it?
Your brother-in-law.
Bi Zhi.
You must be joking, My Lord.
My brother-in-law is just a stableman.
You really don't know?
Your brother-in-law
is quite remarkable.
He not only
defeated Xue Tai,
but did so more than once.
Really?
I can't believe he pulled that off.
That means Cousin's days ahead
could finally be peaceful.
But then again,
how peaceful can it really be?
He claimed Boya all on his own.
Different factions
will go after him.
But he's just one man, not much power.
My uncle,
wary of your reputation,
won't accept him easily.
Neither of them can go home now.
Typical Qiao. Always defiant.
Were you copying sutras just now?
Yes.
Do you like the armrest I gave you?
I do.
It's made from fresh southern bamboo.
It never feels sticky.
I treasured it too much,
so I hardly dared use it.
It's all right.
It's not that rare, anyway.
This bamboo, though,
it's truly quite fine.
My Lord.
You work so hard every day
and often suffer headaches.
I thought perhaps,
your pillow wasn't comfortable.
So I made you a new one.
(That pattern…)
(What's she trying to imply?)
Did you embroider it?
No.
I asked Chunniang to sew it,
but I picked the fabric myself.
And this pattern…
I…
I just thought
the fabric was so soft.
It must be comfortable for sleep.
Thank you.
Why is he acting so odd today?
He insisted you read and write here.
Wait.
The fabric is
of Flourishing Descendants pattern.
Why didn't you tell me?
Flourishing Descendants?
You said it was just soft fabric.
And,
that armrest's jade.
You didn't say that either.
My Lord.
Rest assured, sir.
I've already asked her.
As for this matter,
no matter how bold the Qiao Clan is,
they wouldn't dare raise a flag in Boya.
What did Mrs. Wei say?
You can rest assured.
Bi Zhi may have some skills
and defeated Xue Tai several times,
but the Qiao Clan won't accept him.
He's just
looking for a foothold.
As long as there's no flag,
Boya remains unclaimed.
And since he's fighting Xue Tai,
he poses no threat to us.
Just keep things as they are.
Only a few hundred men?
General,
those hunting in the woods
were very agile.
Not mere servants.
Wei Shao
has intervened in Boya,
dressing his soldiers in plain clothes.
What's his intention?
Luckily, we didn't rush to attack.
He was once Qiao's stableman,
and is Qiao Yue's son-in-law now.
In truth,
he's family to the Wei traitors.
Yanzhou has two such sons-in-law now,
and they're both carving out territory.
We won't engage.
Withdraw the troops.
- Yes.
Xue Tai has withdrawn?
That's right.
He left just like that?
My friend,
we owe this to you.
General, you flatter me.
I didn't do much.
Even though Xue Tai has retreated,
we declared ourselves
commander here.
There will be trouble again.
So what should we do?
You drove off the bandits
and have won the people's trust.
Find a hilltop
and raise a command flag.
It'll look like you're asking
for the people's support.
If you do this,
more will follow you,
and fewer will cause trouble.
But what kind of flag?
I only know horses.
That's easy.
I've seen plenty of flags.
Bring a plain piece of cloth.
Xing.
Yes.
But what should we write on it?
We can't write "Zhi" (swine).
A command flag
declares ownership.
If it bears the character "Wei,"
it means this place belongs to Wei.
If trouble arises later,
Wei will have to step in.
If it becomes Wei territory,
wouldn't that cause problems
for the Lord of Wei?
Xue Tai is stationed at Xiaogang,
across the river from Boya and Panyi.
This trip
is not for battle,
but to probe.
We can't let others think
that Wei plans to occupy Boya.
Dear, what if
we write your surname,
Qiao?
That's a good idea.
Xing, bring more liquor.
We must thank General Wei Qu.
Yes.
(Qiao)
Ma'am.
General Bi Zhi.
Don't bother.
Take care, General.
Take care.
Hyah.
(Qiao)
You raised the flag for Qiao.
You handled such a big matter
and only brought back some wild game
and sacks of rice?
It was my oversight.
You ordered me
to ensure no one thought
Wei intervened.
But everything was ruined by hesitation.
Looks like all you do is hunt and drink.
After a few drinks,
you've forgotten who you are.
My Lord,
Wei Qu can't be blamed for this.
Who would've thought
Qiao was so bold?
They challenged you
over Boya.
Yong.
Sir.
- Speak.
- My voice...
My Lord,
if anyone's to blame, it's Bi Zhi.
All brawn,
no brains.
Fought so hard for a piece of land,
only to fly
his wife's surname on the flag.
Sounds like a kept man.
Who are you mocking?
My Lord.
We haven't seen it coming.
It's a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding?
How could things line up so perfectly?
No need for you to tell me.
I know who's behind this.
My Lord,
could it truly be as the advisor said,
that this is Mrs. Wei's doing?
I underestimated her.
You all remember this:
Stay away from the Qiao Clan.
Or you'll be dumb.
- Yes.
Yes.
You may all rise.
I can
give up Boya,
but I won't just hand it to Yanzhou.
It was a losing game,
yet she managed to turn it around.
(Xiaogang, Boya)
Send the order:
Attack Xiaogang immediately.
My Lord,
Liangya's army guards Xiaogang.
That land belonged to Wei.
But 14 years ago,
it was taken while we were weak.
Lady Qiao
(Panyi)
gave me Panyi without fuss,
(Boya)
but secretly let Bi Zhi take Boya.
That gives Yanzhou a new gateway.
So,
keeping troops in Panyi
will be pointless.
To strike back,
we must open
a new front.
Boya and Xiaogang face each other.
(Xiaogang)
From there,
we can monitor Bi Zhi closely.
You four,
gather the troops.
Set out for Xiaogang.
- Yes.
Wei Qu,
this is your chance to redeem yourself.
Don't waste it.
Understood.
Any other orders?
From today on,
all correspondence from the Qiao Clan
comes through me.
Got it.
I don't think
any of us should get married.
Marriage just turns
into mind games.
Don't count me in.
Only you
could be outwitted by your own kin.
And My Lord, too.
Enough.
My Lady.
What's this?
You're home early today.
These are wild game from Boya.
And this rice too.
Come.
Specially prepared for you.
Cousin sent these?
Yes.
You two share a deep bond,
looking out for each other.
It's truly moving.
But it's not even mealtime yet.
I can't eat these.
You made me shoes,
pillows,
and meals.
This meal
is to thank you.
Dig in.
Try this.
The meat is good.
- My Lord.
- It's tasty.
I can't eat that much.
The kitchen made this just for you.
Eat more.
Eat.
He said not to associate with Qiao.
Does that include Xiaotao?
Probably.
Duang,
I heard General Wei Qu is back.
How is Miss Daqiao doing in Boya?
I'm talking to you here.
Duang.
Xiaotao,
can you leave me alone?
My Lord said
to stay away from you people.
Said we might turn dumb.
How does your dumbness
have anything to do with us?
Duang, how is she?
Xiaotao,
I'm truly on official duty now.
We messed up in Boya,
and now we're making up for it.
My Lord is sending troops to Xiaogang.
So please, stop bothering me.
Xiaogang?
I really can't eat more.
Just a bit more.
Look.
The rice is from Boya.
Have some more.
Did you
come here for something?
Not really.
I just wanted to ask you,
what have you been busy with lately?
Needlework and copying sutras.
Besides that?
Studying "The Analects"
and "The Book of Songs."
For example, letters to your cousin?
Just some
daily reminders.
Daily reminders?
Does that include
raising the Qiao flag in Boya?
I only heard him defeated the bandits,
so I gave a few reminders.
Lady Qiao,
how cunning you are.
I don't understand
what you're saying.
Really?
You pretended to care,
made me drop my guard,
then used the box incident
to make me feel guilty.
I couldn't
have planned guilt.
You had to be wrong first
for me to use it.
Exactly. You used that guilt.
Faked deep sibling affection.
Used the konghou to draw my concern.
Right?
Missing my cousin is real.
But your love for music is fake, right?
After all these days,
why does it still sound awful?
Besides,
if you want Boya,
you could've just told me.
Why manipulate my men
to send your letters?
Act all high and mighty
in front of Xue Tai?
No battle fought,
yet the Qiao flag flew over Boya.
My brother-in-law succeeded, huh?
Look at your smug face.
Look in a mirror.
Turns out, I was too naive.
You're a Wei wife in name,
but still a Qiao woman at heart.
He defeated Xue Tai
and helped Wei
get rid of a threat.
Raising the Qiao flag
shouldn't be a big deal.
Qiao and Wei are one family.
You won't attack
the Qiao Clan, will you?
Or,
the marriage between us
was all for show?
Is that why
you stationed troops in Panyi?
I can't out-talk you.
You always win with your words.
Words are all I have here.
Your words drive me mad.
I'm done arguing.
However,
don't think holding a key position
means you can act reckless.
I'll always keep a knife
at Qiao's throat.
Mrs. Wei,
Wei Liang got all mad when he saw me.
Said his lord told him
not to go near the Qiao clan,
or he'd turn dumb.
Can you believe
how ridiculous he was?
But he's not entirely wrong.
Now they're so angry,
they're sending out troops.
Where to?
Xiaogang.
Chunniang.
When will Zhang Pu return to Kangjun?
My Lady.
He was ill
after coming to Yujun.
He likely hasn't recovered yet.
Have him come see me.
Yes.
Sir, when you return to Yanzhou,
could you take a detour to Boya
and deliver a message
to my cousin?
I'm still sick.
Can't you just write a letter?
It's of great importance.
You must explain it in person.
Break it down for them.
I see.
Please tell me.
Wei Shao
is attacking Xiaogang today
to pin down Boya.
But in Yanzhou, there's a place
called Liancheng
close to Xiaogang.
If you take the mountain path,
it's a three-day trip.
Tell my cousin,
to have her husband start mining there.
I've marked
the exact spot on this map.
(Yanzhou, Panyi, Liangya,
Wei State, Bianzhou)
(Boya)
Mining?
(Wei)
(Wei Shao set his sights on Xiaogang)
(as it's easy to defend
and hard to attack.)
(It could be used to pin down Boya.)
(But if we dig)
(a secret tunnel here,)
(Yanzhou's troops)
(could reach Xiaogang
within half a day.)
(In that case,)
(Xiaogang would be firmly
in Yanzhou's grasp.)
Lady Xu,
Mrs. Wei is here.
Grandmother.
Did you see him off?
I did.
Have a seat.
Do you play Go?
Yes.
But I'm not skilled.
It's an art to be learned.
Beginners often focus
on capturing more pieces,
trying to wipe out the opponent.
And they lose because of it.
To win,
you have to yield a little.
But knowing how much to yield
takes judgment.
If both sides press too hard,
it ends
in a stalemate.
There may still be a winner,
but the board
looks ugly.
I will remember your words.
Do you think
I was talking about the game?
It was about marriage.
My Lord and I are not enemies,
but allies.
Still, maybe
I'm not good at Go.
I used to see him off to war.
Now you do.
That's a wife's duty.
I'm pleased.
But what I really hope is:
From now on,
Zhonglin will
no longer go to war.
Do you know
what that means?
I understand.
Back then,
when your grandfather proposed,
he wrote me a letter,
confessing his past wrongs.
I resented your grandfather.
His betrayal
cost me my husband,
my son,
and my grandson.
But the dead can't come back.
Even if I wipe out the Qiao Clan,
would it ease our scars from the past
and the pain in our hearts
even a little?
But if
your marriage with Zhonglin
could resolve this hatred
and help him
let go of his obsessions,
so he no longer
spends his life in mourning,
what more
could I ask for?
Grandmother,
I've let you down.
It's all right.
Everything takes time.
Let's take it slow.
(Two Months Later)
(Government Office)
The Lord has returned.
My Lord, we claimed
a great victory at Xiaogang.
We gave Liu Yan of Liangya
a strong warning.
It truly lifts everyone's spirits.
How many times must I tell you?
Never judge by appearances alone.
Stationing troops at Xiaogang
isn't only about intimidating Liangya.
Besides reinforcing Xiaogang,
I have four more
tasks for you.
Yes.
First:
Increase patrols
along the Xiaogang-Liangya border.
You are wise and decisive.
Liangya has always eyed us.
Second:
Keep close watch
on military movements
between Yanzhou and Boya.
You're thorough and careful.
We must guard against an attack
from Boya.
Third:
Reinforce all frontier outposts.
Your foresight's unmatched.
We must watch every state's moves.
Fourth…
My Lord,
what's the fourth thing?
The fourth one.
Get my bedding back
to the main chamber.
I'm going to battle Lady Qiao
over every inch of ground.
Howe can you just barge in?
Do you have no respect?
This is the Lord and Lady's bedchamber.
No matter how often
you used to come,
from now on,
without being summoned,
no one may enter.
If we aren't moving in ourselves,
will you do it?
Didn't you just say
this is the Lord and Lady's bedchamber?
My Lord is moving back in.
Excuse me.
Careful.
Don't crush the Lady's quilt.
Get down.
Stop it. That's Mrs. Wei's books.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
Don't touch the Lady's books.
Wait. She's just a woman,
she reads too?
My Lady could read at three,
recite poems at five.
Of course she reads.
Fine, fine.
Put those useless books
on the dressing table.
He won't use it anyway.
What?
You say it like he doesn't have a face.
The sword. I think it's best here.
It fits well right here.
You're leaving a sword here?
Does he practice it?
He's not just a swordsman.
He kills with ease.
Where should his clothes go?
This one
and those ones are My Lady's.
Well,
he can use that one.
So small?
Wait.
Why does she take up so much space?
Did she move all of Yanzhou in?
None of you four are married, right?
Anywhere, the woman's wardrobe
is always bigger.
Really?
Makes sense.
With Xiaotao's temper, honestly,
who'd marry her?
What's she to you?
Why worry about that?
Come on.
Don't forget,
she's meant to marry into our family.
Well, just one of us.
Not it.
Me neither.
I'm not marrying her.
You…
Let's draw lots.
Alright. Fine.
Didn't we agree to draw lots?
Where is everyone?
My Lady, you should've seen them.
It was like they were
dividing up territory,
arguing over every inch.
Insisting on which part belonged to him,
and which to you.
But the two of you share a room,
how can it be split so neatly?
People say, easy with the ruler,
tough with the servants.
Just like Grandmother said.
When someone pushes,
another must yield.
I've raised the Qiao flag at Boya.
If he wants to get back elsewhere,
so be it.
Let's organize his things.
As for his bedding?
Just leave it for now.
All right.
What are you doing?
I saw you sleeping uneasily.
Maybe the candlelight was too bright.
So I wanted to put it out.
Don't.
Just wear more clothes
at night.
Don't try to seduce me.
I am the Lord of Wei.
I won't be swayed by beauty.
I had no such intent.
You speak in opposites.
You say no,
then it's yes.
If you say so,
then so be it.
Sir, please sit.
My Lord,
my cough hasn't healed yet,
so I dare not
drink with you.
Then,
just sit here
and keep me company.
My Lord,
there are many things
that can be shared with dearest ones.
No need to bear it all alone.
But I have no one to talk to.
No one understands.
It's all because he kills in dreams.
He made you lose sleep.
Even said you tried to seduce him.
How unfair.
He only said it to ease my worries.
You're always defending him.
He just talks, that's all.
He never hurt me.
Forget it. Go make some red bean soup.
My Lord?
Why is it so dark in here?
My…
They say the Lord of Wei kills
in his sleep,
never lets anyone near him
when sleeping.
My Lord.
Xiaozao…
Don't go.
Stay.
What's wrong?
Are you afraid of the dark?
It's okay.
It's all right.
I'm here for you.
Don't be afraid.
I'm right here.
As the saying goes,
"A wise one knows when
to advance and when to retreat."
But this requires careful judgment.
A slight error,
and one crosses the line.
Bear insults
without flinching,
and see faults
without exposing.
My Lady, you should know
the art of wise companionship
better than I do.
You're talking about noble friendships.
But what about marriage?
It's the same
for you and My Lord.
I thought
he'd resent me over Boya.
But these past days,
I've realized he doesn't.
And now I don't know how to face him.
The Lord grew up in hatred,
inherited leadership young.
If he's sometimes cold,
it's only natural.
Please try to understand.
But I've served him in war for years.
I know him
better than anyone.
Then,
what's his true nature?
Tough on the outside,
soft on the inside.
Big-hearted.
Otherwise,
he wouldn't have allowed you
to stay in Yujun.
If that's the case,
I've misjudged him.
Thank you for your advice.
♪The moonlight is as silent
as the deep sea♪
♪From afar♪
♪It once lit up dreams with a breath♪
♪But vanished with a sigh♪
♪Brushing past my fingertips♪
♪My heartstrings were stirred quietly♪
♪As if we once met before♪
♪Holding back a love so deep♪
♪Love asks for nothing in the end♪
♪Leaving only obsessions♪
♪I've wandered in the world♪
♪Yet cannot have it all♪
♪We meet and part in the fires of war♪
♪Embracing,
leaving tender marks of love♪
♪With one breathtaking glance♪
♪How could I ever forget♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪