♪If not for you♪
♪I wouldn't have wanted
to make a name for myself♪
♪Only when I have your love♪
♪Is my invincibility not in vain♪
♪The towering peaks I've conquered♪
♪Leave me♪
♪Feeling empty♪
♪I've given everything♪
♪Just to follow you♪
♪Through life and death♪
♪Could it be that love♪
♪Is the true end of this life♪
♪Why does every battle♪
♪Bring deeper pain♪
♪I never got it♪
♪You once promised me♪
♪You'd give me ordinary days♪
♪Then I'd rather♪
♪Face blades and fall♪
♪Into your arms instead of the clouds♪
♪I'll pass through layers of fog♪
♪And barriers♪
♪The world's rights and wrongs,
wins and losses♪
♪Who's to weigh their worth♪
♪Only love♪
♪Gives me a sky as wide as the sea♪
♪I only want to be your hero♪
=The Prisoner of Beauty=
=Episode 34=
I...
It's you?
My Lord.
It's been a long while.
So, he's the one you spoke of?
Do you know, months ago,
he attacked Yanzhou,
causing us tens of thousands of casualties?
I offended you before.
But may I now have
the chance to redeem myself?
If we join hands this time,
we could help you reclaim true authority,
and take back Panyi for Yanzhou.
Panyi?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Governor, you're a man of great talent,
wise and formidable in battle,
much like the late Lord Qiao.
But Prefect
has long coveted your position.
He has plotted carefully.
Now he controls the troops,
and has Wei Shao as his son-in-law.
As the Lord of Yanzhou,
do you truly accept being beneath him?
What's the point of these words?
If Wei Shao falls,
Yanzhou will be the strongest force.
Qiao Ping will be left without support.
If you will not submit to him,
why not take a chance?
You want to kill the Lord of Wei?
Wei State now draws strength
from regions to build the canal.
Soon, their strength will be unstoppable.
If we do not act now,
there may never be another chance.
Over the past months,
I've reached out to many forces,
rallied troops to resist Wei State.
Xue Tai, a valiant warrior,
has also pledged support.
We'll strike from two fronts.
Everything is ready,
except your resolve
to cast off Wei State's yoke.
So, you've come to persuade me?
I have come today,
only seeking a powerful alliance with you
to crush Wei State
and divide its lands.
Ping, my brother.
It's been a long time
since we had an evening like this,
just sitting and drinking together.
Let me take this chance
to toast you first.
Bottoms up.
I know I'm mediocre.
All these years,
it's you who held everything together.
I'm proud of you,
but also ashamed that I've done so little.
Here's a second cup
to show my respect.
Yue,
please don't put me on a pedestal.
If not for you,
who always showed such grace,
what could I
have done alone?
I should be the one
to toast you.
Very well.
As long as we stand united,
there's nothing we can't overcome.
Cheers.
I have something
to tell you, Ping.
Please go on.
I've decided
to lead Yanzhou
in allegiance to Liu Yan, Lord of Liangya,
and sever all ties
with Wei Shao of Wei State.
Why?
No...
wait.
Why didn't you
say a word of this beforehand?
Ping, what do you mean?
Must I seek your permission
for every decision?
That's not what I meant.
Right now,
the realm is in turmoil
and its future uncertain.
Yanzhou, for the moment,
can still hold its own.
In my view,
we should wait and observe.
It's unwise to turn to Liangya so hastily.
Yue,
have you ever considered
our Qiao Clan has an in-law relationship
with the Wei Clan.
If one is in trouble,
the other should come to its aid.
Even if not,
we shouldn't betray them.
So in the end,
you just want to tie Yanzhou's fate
and the Qiao Clan's
to Wei Shao?
Am I right?
Back then,
when our families allied by marriage,
Yue,
you supported it too.
But now,
at the first sign of trouble,
you're ready to turn your back!
How is this
any different
from being a turncoat?
How dare you speak to me this way.
Do you still see me as your elder brother?
Remember, I am the Lord of Yanzhou!
I have no sons.
I treat Ci as my own.
Why do you think I'm doing this?
Do you really believe it's for myself?
I'm doing this for Yanzhou's future!
Know this,
my alliance with Liangya
is not open to your objections!
You...
You drugged my wine!
No, I didn't.
- I didn't.
- My eyes...
You traitor!
Traitor...
Is he dead?
He's still breathing.
What did you give him?
Why can't he see anything?
I don't know.
Liu Shan gave me the drug.
He said it's much stronger
than ordinary knockout drops.
It must be
his rage.
It triggered temporary blindness.
He might recover in a few days.
My Lord,
our top priority must be
to seize control of Prefect,
take back command of the troops,
and take charge of the situation.
How is Ci right now?
Wait.
Only restrain him. Do not harm him.
Rest assured, My Lord.
I've sent trusted men to guard him closely.
(Boya)
Look over here,
Li.
Ma'am,
here's a letter from Kangjun.
Is it from Ci?
(I heard you had a son.)
What does it say?
(I hope you and Bi Zhi return to Kangjun
to enjoy family time.)
It's from Father.
He heard
I have a son
and wants to meet Li.
He hopes we bring him back
to Kangjun for a while.
I know grandparents have a special bond
with their grandkids.
Father must be so happy
to be a grandfather now.
He must have forgotten past arguments.
I hope so.
But Father
really does love children.
When we were young,
he treated us so well.
He's fallen asleep.
I'll go find some fast horses.
We'll set out at once.
No rush.
We're going back to Kangjun.
(Kangjun)
There they are.
Whoa.
Fan, get down.
- Father.
We've waited so long for you.
Where are Mother, Uncle, and Ci?
They're all waiting in the mansion.
I heard you've been good to Fan.
You often pick sour plums for her?
Yes.
I learned the recipe
to pickle them from a kitchen maid.
She loves them.
What a coincidence.
The plums in Kangjun are ripe now.
They're in the West Hill.
Go pick some for her.
Let's have a taste as well.
- Yes.
- Father.
We've only just arrived.
Don't send Bi Zhi
off on errands right away.
Besides,
back when Mother was in Boya,
I stopped him from picking sour plums.
He's a respected leader now.
Since he's my son-in-law,
he ought to show some filial piety.
Earlier,
I acted rashly driven by
anger toward Wei Shao.
I did something inappropriate.
You and I share the same blood.
I should treat Bi Zhi well.
The two of you should hold
a proper wedding ceremony.
Now that you have a son,
it's time to make it official.
Father, I'll be right back.
Good, don't be long.
- Bi Zhi...
- Don't worry.
I'll be right back.
Come to the mansion with me.
Li is still in the carriage.
We'll fetch him in a moment.
Bi Zhi! Come back!
Father, what are you doing?
- Gag her.
- Let me go!
What are you doing?
Bi Zhi!
Bi Zhi,
stop right now,
or she'll get hurt.
So, you're Bi Zhi, the green-eyed stableman.
Just as Xue Tai said, you're hard to handle,
but you love your wife deeply.
All the better.
You'll make a fine weapon
against Wei Shao.
I once swore an oath.
I will never harm Lord of Wei
or Her Ladyship.
In that case,
she'll get hurt.
Stop!
Kneel.
Kneel!
From this day forth,
be you a stableman
or my slave,
stay by my side,
and obey my command.
If not...
Well then,
you can try and see
whether you're faster
than my blade.
(Kangjun, Yanzhou)
- Whoa.
- Stop.
State your name and purpose.
I'm Wei Liang from Wei State,
here on Lord of Wei's orders
to invite Prefect of Kangjun.
General Wei, please wait a moment.
General, Wei Liang has arrived.
Shall we let him in?
General Wei,
you may enter.
Giddy-up.
(Kangjun Wharf)
Shopkeeper,
do you have any fine orchids from Yanzhou?
The fine ones are back at my home.
They're costly, though.
Still want them?
Price is no issue.
Give me the best.
Sure. Follow me.
Move aside!
Out of the way!
Move it!
Shopkeeper,
has Kangjun been peaceful lately?
Thanks to Prefect,
every home sleeps with their doors wide open.
But why are there
so many patrols on the street?
I don't know why.
There are more patrols lately. That's true.
Let's go.
Governor.
General, your arrival is sudden.
May I ask what brings you here?
Her Ladyship misses her father,
so His Lordship sent me here
to invite Prefect Qiao
to stay in Yujun for a while
until Her Ladyship gives birth.
They can enjoy some family time.
To invite Prefect?
Manman is about to give birth.
He is a man, after all.
He can't help much there.
He'd only cause trouble for the Lord of Wei.
How about this?
Once Manman gives birth safely,
I'll visit them with Ci.
Governor, you're overthinking.
It's no trouble at all.
How about we ask Prefect
and hear his thoughts?
My brother hasn't been well lately.
He's resting at home now,
not seeing guests.
Prefect is sick?
Then I should visit him
to show His Lordship's filial piety.
I'll go right now...
He just took some herbal soup and is asleep.
I'll send someone to check if he's awake.
Mr. Zhang,
go and take a look.
Yes.
This kind of small thing
should be left to servants.
Why trouble Advisor
with such things?
Zhang Pu is more thoughtful.
Where's Young Master Ci?
I haven't seen him in a while.
I truly miss him.
Ci went hunting in the hills.
It's getting late,
and he's not back yet?
He's still a kid
and really playful.
By the way,
I heard in Boya
that General Bi Zhi and Ma'am
were invited here in Kangjun too.
Did they bring their child?
May I visit them?
General, must you ask about
every single member of my family?
General,
was Ma'am's delivery smooth?
you...
Governor,
you want to side with Liu Yan?
Since Wei Shao's lackey is here,
there's no way you'll make it back alive.
Bi Zhi,
you green-eyed scum!
You'd betray Lord of Wei too?
Bi Zhi,
what are you waiting for?
Don't you care about your wife and son?
Go get him!
Hurry! Go get him!
My Lady.
I've prepared some food for Ci.
By His Lordship's order,
no one is allowed inside.
Insolence!
How dare you speak to me like this?
Am I not the Lady of Yanzhou?
I need to
check the food box, My Lady.
Do you need to search me as well?
I wouldn't dare.
Let her in.
- Aunt.
- Ci.
What happened out there?
How is my father?
Why did Uncle lock me up?
Don't call him Uncle anymore.
He's allied himself with Liu Yan
and is plotting against the Lord of Wei.
Your father and Cousin are locked away too.
Even Bi Zhi is being forced
to serve them now.
General Wei Liang came unexpectedly,
and they attacked him.
We don't even know if he's still alive.
Ci, your top priority now
is to get out of here,
rescue General Wei Liang,
and inform Lord of Wei.
My Lady!
Step aside!
Young Master Ci, calm down.
Step back!
- Step back!
- Make...
Make way!
Ci! Ci!
Get out of the way, you all!
If anything happens to Ci,
how will you explain to Governor?
Move!
Ci?
Move aside!
Young Master Ci, please stay calm.
Don't follow me.
Aunt,
take care.
- Go get him!
- Ci!
Ci! Ci!
Are you alright, My Lady?
Ci...
My Lady.
Stop right there!
Go after him!
Don't run!
Stop!
- Don't run.
Go get him!
Bring the orchids to Wei and tell them,
Boya has rebelled!
Kangjun has rebelled!
General!
Tell Xiaotao
not to wait for me!
Xiaotao,
don't wait for me.
My Lord, be careful.
Where is Ci?
He escaped.
I've sent men after him.
He escaped?
Whatever happens, don't take his life.
My Lord.
In this case,
our secret plans
will likely be exposed.
Then we don't hide it.
Let's start the war.
Attack Panyi
and catch them off guard.
If we control the Yongning Canal,
we control the lifeline of every region.
Seriously?
Panyi is heavily guarded.
It's not so easy to take.
Exactly.
That's up to you, Governor.
Can you find a way
to knock the gates of Panyi open?
Well...
Yang Feng, Mayor of Panyi,
once served my father closely.
He's a slippery one, though.
Let's hope he doesn't stop us.
(Panyi City, Wei State)
(Panyi)
(Wei)
Open the gates!
Open the gates now!
Open the gates.
What's going on, General?
Lord Yang, look.
Why would they suddenly show up like this?
Both Governor of Yanzhou
and Commander of Boya Forces
come here together.
General, let me ask them.
Governor,
why have you
brought troops here?
Yang Feng,
Liu Yan attacked Kangjun.
Luckily, Bi Zhi saved us.
Open the gates quickly. I seek refuge.
Please wait a moment, Governor.
General,
Wei State and Yanzhou are bound
by both marriage
and alliance.
Please allow the family of the late Lord Qiao
to take shelter in the city,
and send a message to Yujun
without delay.
Well...
Thank you very much, General.
Alright.
Open the gates!
Open the gates now!
Governor,
please enter quickly.
General... General Bi Zhi,
what are you doing?
Yang Feng,
I've allied with Liangya
to resist Wei State.
From this day on,
Panyi returns to Yanzhou's rule.
You once served my father closely
and are a man of wit.
I trust you know
what must be done,
don't you?
Yes, I do.
Governor,
your march here with so many troops.
Has Xindu noticed?
Xindu?
In this realm,
who could possibly rival Bi Zhi?
True.
And what about Zhen Zhi?
Bi Zhi.
He lacked your subtlety
and tried to stop us.
He fell in the line of duty.
Governor.
My Lord.
Mayor Yang, please
inform all regions.
The watergate at Yongning Canal
is now under my control.
All forces and nobles must reconsider
where their loyalties lie.
Yes,
I understand.
(Panyi, Wei)
(Qiao)
You fell in the line of duty?
If I had known sooner,
I would've had a drink with you
back in Rongjun.
Liu Yan's evil heart never dies.
If such a warmonger gains control of
(Governor of Yenzhou)
the water source,
how can the realm ever find peace?
Want me to join him?
Never!
I told them to follow the Lord of Liangya,
(Governor of Taozhou)
but they wouldn't listen.
Luckily, we chose our side early.
We might yet claim
a share of the spoils.
Wei State is too strong.
(Governor of Yaozhou)
I agreed to help build the canal
only as a temporary move.
If Liangya State
really defeats Wei State,
that will be a good thing.
Let's wait and see.
(Proclamation: Liangya now
accepts Panyi's surrender.)
My Lord, your asthma is acting up again.
Shall I call for the physician?
Liu Yan...
He is dead set on mutual destruction.
We cannot let Shiyuan
get dragged into this mess.
Yes.
Young Master.
Shiyuan, you're back.
Son, you've been
guarding the border for a while.
You've done well.
It's time you came home.
You've been away too long.
I do miss you.
Governor, I'd like to request command
of a military unit.
Is there any unrest at the border?
Are you hurt, son?
No, it's fine.
So,
you want to reinforce Yujun?
Liu Yan caught us off guard.
I just need to help out for a few days
to ease Zhonglin's troubles.
Shiyuan!
Given the current situation,
I've held back from attacking Wei State
out of respect for your ties with the Weis!
As for the rest,
don't bring it up again.
Governor!
- Guards.
- Yes, My Lord.
Escort Young Master to his chambers.
You must be tired from the journey.
Rest in your chambers for the next few days.
Young master,
this way, please.
(Zhongzhou Post House, Zhongzhou)
My Lady, General Xue Tai has arrived.
My Lady,
the Lord of Liangya has announced
he has taken Panyi.
Our plan has succeeded.
Very well.
In that case,
I need Governor of Zhongzhou to meet me.
Zhongzhou is
a thousand li from Panyi.
Even if they gather troops,
their aid would be slow.
Who said I plan to attack Panyi?
What's your plan, My Lady?
Since Liu Yan took Panyi
and the Yongning Canal,
Wei Shao surely won't sit still.
The moment he moves,
I'll strike straight for Yujun
and wipe out the Wei Clan.
I didn't expect that to be your plan.
The Lord of Liangya attacks Panyi
to rule the realm,
but what I seek
is so much more than that.
I will walk over the bones of the Wei Clan,
wade through their blood,
and rise to the top, step by step.
The humiliation the Weis inflicted on me,
I shall return it in full.
Who's there?
(Yujun, Wei State)
Who are you?
My brother-in-law...
Young Master Ci!
Inform His Lordship!
Ci.
- You're awake.
- Manman.
My Lord.
I sent Wei Liang
to invite you and Father.
Why are you the only one back?
Xiaotao.
General Wei Liang
asked me to give the orchids to you.
General Wei Liang...
He died fighting.
Are you out of your mind?
Did you hurt your head or something?
He's a stand-up man.
You say he's dead and that's it?
We waited all night for you to wake up.
What do you do?
The first thing you say is
that Wei Liang's dead?
Can you think before you speak?
He has that huge shield.
How could he die just like that?
You're still alive,
but why isn't he?
Believe whatever you want.
I'm going to do the laundry.
Ci,
what exactly
do you mean by that?
Just say it.
Say it!
General Wei Liang
died fighting.
Uncle was incited by Zhang Pu
to ally with Liu Yan
and rebel against His Lordship.
Zhang Pu even drugged Father.
Now, Father is blind.
Uncle imprisoned me, Cousin,
and my nephew, and forced Bi Zhi
to turn against us.
I don't know why
General Wei Liang came to Kangjun
to see me and Father.
Out of fear that the truth
would come out,
Liu Yan ordered a siege.
We couldn't hold them off.
General Wei Liang fought to
get me out of there,
but he...
He...
It should've been me.
Qiao Ci,
look at me.
Wei Liang went to fetch you, right?
Where is he now?
Look at me. Where is Wei Liang?
He went to Yujun.
Answer me. Where is he now?
Look at me. Where is Wei Liang?
Where is Wei Liang?
Where is he?
It should've been you.
Why did it have to be him?
Why not a Qiao?
Wei Xiao!
My Lord!
Reporting!
Liu Yan has taken Panyi with his troops.
Pass down my orders:
All troops, stay on alert.
Tomorrow,
we march on Panyi!
♪The moonlight is as silent
as the deep sea♪
♪From afar♪
♪It once lit up dreams with a breath♪
♪But vanished with a sigh♪
♪Brushing past my fingertips♪
♪My heartstrings were stirred quietly♪
♪As if we once met before♪
♪Holding back a love so deep♪
♪Love asks for nothing in the end♪
♪Leaving only obsessions♪
♪I've wandered in the world♪
♪Yet cannot have it all♪
♪We meet and part in the fires of war♪
♪Embracing,
leaving tender marks of love♪
♪With one breathtaking glance♪
♪How could I ever forget♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪