♪If not for you♪
♪I wouldn't have wanted
to make a name for myself♪
♪Only when I have your love♪
♪Is my invincibility not in vain♪
♪The towering peaks I've conquered♪
♪Leave me♪
♪Feeling empty♪
♪I've given everything♪
♪Just to follow you♪
♪Through life and death♪
♪Could it be that love♪
♪Is the true end of this life♪
♪Why does every battle♪
♪Bring deeper pain♪
♪I never got it♪
♪You once promised me♪
♪You'd give me ordinary days♪
♪Then I'd rather♪
♪Face blades and fall♪
♪Into your arms instead of the clouds♪
♪I'll pass through layers of fog♪
♪And barriers♪
♪The world's rights and wrongs,
wins and losses♪
♪Who's to weigh their worth♪
♪Only love♪
♪Gives me a sky as wide as the sea♪
♪I only want to be your hero♪
=The Prisoner of Beauty=
=Episode 10=
Then,
what's his true nature?
Tough on the outside,
soft on the inside.
Big-hearted.
Otherwise,
he wouldn't have allowed you
to stay in Yujun.
If that's the case,
I've misjudged him.
Thank you for your advice.
Your Go skills are truly remarkable.
I gladly admit defeat.
Greetings, Mother.
Mother, you asked for me.
What would you like me to do?
I heard from the accountant
that you changed the candle expenses.
We're using yellow candles now.
I'd prefer beeswax candles.
They burn brighter
and produce less smoke.
Nonsense!
Zhonglin works tirelessly out there,
while you lounge around in here?
You don't care for him, fine.
But now you're making
all kinds of demands?
Clearly,
no daughter-in-law can ever match a mother.
Only a mother
can truly love her son.
Mother,
I've checked the household accounts.
We're under budget
on candles every month.
No extra costs.
My Lord!
Her Ladyship wrote to Yanzhou again.
She didn't ask you.
I held it back.
Have a look.
Aunt, I've been scared of the dark lately
and having trouble sleeping.
Could you please copy me
the calming and mind-clearing
remedy from Yanzhou?
That's it?
All for nothing.
Wait.
There's a hidden message.
You all are way out of line.
Do what you gotta do.
A hidden message.
Only a few shops in Yujun sell candles.
Big, small, thick, thin,
we've got them all here.
My Lady, we have plenty of
candles here already.
Why do you have to do this?
This candle won't do.
It smokes too much.
Try this one.
Careful, it's hot.
But this one flickers too much.
Can't sleep well at night.
Well,
it could be.
- You're back home.
- My Lord.
What are you doing?
The candles we have give off thick smoke,
harsh on the nose,
and strain the eyes when reading at night.
So I wanted to replace them.
We are not an ordinary couple.
Just keep up appearances.
Don't play clever tricks,
trying to snoop into my affairs
and cause a stir in the whole household.
I only changed the candles.
I wasn't trying to snoop into your affairs.
That's for the best.
Her Ladyship
paid for the candles herself.
She didn't cost you a coin.
I'll have the accountant
send some silver tomorrow.
I rule Wei, a great state.
Do I lack money for a few candles?
I've heard Boya
used to be part of Wei's holdings.
But because of Qiao's tricks,
the Qiao flag now flies there.
Lady Xu is furious.
She lectured Lady Qiao
for quite a while.
That's right.
Since she acted without
considering the household,
Mother certainly
won't let her off easily.
Besides,
it's been over three months
since Zhonglin and she got married.
They're no longer newlyweds.
Taking a concubine now
is definitely not
seen as disobedience.
Actually, Shao approved
taking a concubine.
Aunt, why not
go straight to Lady Qiao
and get her to agree to the match?
If she refuses, go tell Lady Xu herself.
Lady Qiao is clearly in the wrong.
I guess
she doesn't even dare to refuse.
(Betrothal Letter)
This is Zhonglin and Chuyu's
Betrothal Letter.
The 5th of next month is an auspicious day.
Hurry
and prepare for the betrothal.
This matter is of great importance.
I need to ask His Lordship first.
I can't decide on my own.
Is it that you can't decide,
or that you don't want him
to take a concubine?
Zhonglin is
the last of the Wei line.
Everyone in this family is waiting his heir.
But you are still in mourning.
How is our Wei family
supposed to carry on?
Then I'll be direct.
I already asked His Lordship
about taking a concubine.
Neither he
nor Grandmother
agreed to it.
You...
You're using them to pressure me again?
Fine.
I'll speak plainly today.
Don't think I don't know
it was you who egged Zhonglin
on not to take a concubine.
I won't argue with you
over all your little schemes.
As long as Zhonglin
takes Chuyu as his concubine,
you can take charge of
everything else.
You're clever, Mother.
That's true. I did try to
dissuade His Lordship.
When I first met him,
I was struck by his masculinity.
He set aside our families' old feud
and treated me kindly in Xindu.
From then on, I saw that
he carried the world in his heart.
He's a truly broad-minded man.
Later, in Panyi,
he saved me from danger.
From that moment,
I swore to myself
I would stay by his side forever.
Enough, stop it.
No one wants to hear
your sentimental rambling.
Mother,
it's all my fault.
I love His Lordship too deeply.
I can't bear to share him with other women.
You can call me jealous,
or say I'm harsh,
but what new bride,
just months into marriage,
can bear watching
her mother-in-law arrange
a concubine for her husband?
Punish me if you must.
Even if it costs me my life,
I will never accept
Zheng Shu as a concubine in my home.
Enough. That's enough.
You want to see me, My Lord?
I heard you told Mother
you have feelings for me.
Is that true?
I only said that
to go along with your wish.
I had no other choice.
You needn't take it seriously.
My wish?
Aren't you afraid Mother will blame you?
I just don't want you
to do anything you don't want to.
As the master of this household
and ruler of Wei,
you should make your own decisions.
If you want to take Zheng Shu
as your concubine,
I won't stop you.
But if you don't want to,
I won't let anyone else
force you into it.
Your words can cut deep,
but sometimes they're comforting.
I'll take that as a compliment.
But remember this.
We are not an ordinary couple.
From now on, never...
Never try to seduce you with my beauty.
I know that.
Very well.
Well, you should head back.
Alright.
Lady Qiao truly has no shame,
using that excuse to brush me off.
Aunt, please,
marry me off to someone else.
Chuyu...
I'll never forget you,
and I'll come visit you often.
Chuyu!
Once you're gone, I'm left alone.
It's bad enough dealing with
my mother-in-law,
and now I have to face Qiao too.
How can I handle all this?
Tell me, how am I supposed to live like this?
Now that it's come to this,
do you have any ideas left, Aunt?
No, we can't do that.
Chuyu,
I know
this
is hard for you.
But now,
there's no other way.
If you refuse,
even I can't help you anymore.
Well, Aunt,
I'll do as you say.
Let me propose a toast first.
Son,
I was born clumsy
and reckless.
I've caused you much trouble.
I'm sorry for that.
Let me have three cups to apologize.
No need, Mother.
Please take it easy.
Drink up.
How many cups have I had?
Three.
Three, huh?
No problem.
Here, I'll top off your cup, son.
Eat and drink up.
- Thank you, Mother.
- Shall we?
Sure.
Ma'am, it's time for your decoction.
What's wrong, Mother?
I've had headaches recently.
I asked the physician for some decoction.
I was too happy today
and forgot to take it. Let's go.
Shall I come with you?
No, you stay.
Watch your step.
My Lord.
Lady Zhu
was planning to come
after taking her decoction,
but somehow,
her headache got worse.
Even the decoction didn't help.
Please, go check on her.
- Lead the way.
- Yes, My Lord.
My Lady?
His Lordship is here to visit you.
Mother?
Shao.
How does my dress look?
Does it look good?
I'm sorry.
Shao.
Are you not feeling well?
Shall I
help you rest inside?
Go away.
I said go away.
- Shao...
- Put on your robe.
Shao,
I have no choice.
Now, I just want
to ease your pain.
Shao, please don't go.
Go away!
Shao!
- My Lord!
- Zhonglin.
- Where are you going?
Go away!
Zhonglin! Zhonglin!
I...
You plotted with an outsider
against your own son?
Zhonglin.
Zhonglin, please.
I can explain.
Look away!
His Lordship is just angry.
Say one word and I'll tear your mouths apart!
Chuyu.
My Lord?
Are you alright?
Shall I call the physician?
No.
Don't let anyone see me like this.
Get me more water!
Water.
So the one closest to you
should be someone
who sees what you see,
and feels what you feel.
I just don't want you
to do anything you don't want to.
If you want to take Zheng Shu
as your concubine,
I won't stop you.
But if you don't want to,
I won't let anyone else
- force you into it.
- My Lord?
Things you don't want to tell others,
you can tell her.
- Leave what you don't want others
- My Lord,
- to handle to her.
- are you alright?
Shall we call the physician?
And you can show
your vulnerability to her.
No need.
Your robe is soaked.
Go change it, or you'll catch cold.
I've told you before,
whatever happens with the Qiao family,
I will never let you be without a home.
Do you remember?
Yes.
You said so, My Lord.
My Lord, let go of me.
Let go of me!
Your Lordship!
What's wrong?
Are you drunk?
I'm still in mourning.
If I've done something wrong,
just tell me directly.
My Lord, you promised me
on our wedding day in Panyi
that I could mourn Grandfather for a year.
I'm sorry.
I had something dirty at Mother's.
Bring me some ice.
Mother...
Bring me some ice!
Here's the ice.
Is that enough?
Yes.
My Lord,
I'll stay right here.
If you need anything,
just say the word.
Alright.
I want some water.
Water.
Here's your water.
I'll get you another cup.
Here.
Bring me my clothes.
Did you get those wounds
in Xiaogang?
Just minor injuries.
Nothing serious.
Are you feeling better now, My Lord?
If you are,
I... I'll take my leave.
Thank you.
His Lordship caught a chill last night.
He's not feeling well.
Keep it down while you're working.
Don't wake him up.
- Yes.
My Lord, are you feeling better?
No idea what you're talking about.
Last night,
your old wound flared up, so you used
crushed ice to ease the pain.
I've already ordered the maids
to make ginger tea for you
to drive out the cold.
Thank you, My Lady.
Zhonglin,
it was my fault
for what happened last night.
How could I have been so foolish
to do that?
After you left last night,
I thought you'd never accept me
as your mother again.
Zhonglin.
I suppose
your grandmother knows about it now.
Yes, it's all my fault.
I'll go to Mother
and ask her to punish me.
Mother, don't worry.
Grandmother knows nothing of this.
I'm not going to tell her
and make her worry.
However,
there's one thing I hope you'll agree to.
Zhonglin,
go on and tell me.
Send Zheng Shu away.
She is never to set foot
in the Wei household again.
But...
I...
I understand. I understand.
It's just that
Chuyu has been
with me all these years.
She has no one else to rely on.
If I suddenly send her away,
where else would she go?
Zhonglin,
over these years
you've been busy with state affairs,
and it was Chuyu who stayed by my side
and took care of me.
I don't mean anything else.
I just want
to prepare more for her
and find her a good husband.
It's my way
of thanking her
for the filial care
she's given on your behalf.
No, I...
Please, son.
Three days.
I'll give you three days.
I just hope
you learn your lesson
and never act so foolishly again.
That would be
the greatest blessing for me, as your son.
Zhonglin!
Are you speaking the truth?
I dare not lie, Ma'am.
Ma'am, Her Ladyship is here.
Greetings, Grandmother.
I'm sorry I got up late today
and kept you waiting.
I deserve punishment.
You may all leave.
Come here.
Sit.
I called you here
to ask about something.
I heard last night
Zhonglin got angry at Lady Zhu
and Zheng Shu in the east wing
and even kicked down the doors.
I honestly don't know
what happened in the east wing.
You're a sensible girl.
Zhonglin finds it hard
to speak openly with me now,
so I'm asking you.
What exactly happened
last night?
Grandmother,
I really don't know.
What about him asking
for ice in the middle of the night?
You don't know that either?
Lately, while caring for His Lordship,
I noticed new wounds on his back,
probably from the Xiaogang battle.
They haven't fully healed yet.
I presume
he used ice to ease the pain.
But please don't worry, Grandmother.
I've asked the maids
to prepare more ginger tea
for him to drive out the cold.
He should be fine.
Alright,
I see.
You've stayed up all night tending to him.
You must be tired.
Go back and have some rest.
Then I'll take my leave.
Very well.
Ma'am,
it seems Her Ladyship
doesn't know about this.
Luckily,
we got the truth
from the east wing maids.
That's some clever talk.
She's usually sharp-tongued,
witty and eloquent.
She knows how to say nothing
when things get sensitive.
If you push her too hard,
she'll just make something up to fool you.
She's so tight-lipped.
So,
Her Ladyship deceived you, Ma'am.
Yet somehow I feel
you're not angry with her.
She was preserving Zhonglin's dignity
by covering for his mother.
Ma'am,
just admit it.
At this point,
no matter how you look at it,
you've grown fond of Her Ladyship,
haven't you?
I only care because she cares for Zhonglin.
Since she holds him dear,
I can't help but care for her too.
I truly hope she and Zhonglin
can be a loving couple.
Indeed.
That foolish Zhu
isn't even a match for a young girl.
She is utterly ignorant!
Aunt.
If Lady Qiao
had even half your thoughtfulness,
I wouldn't have been
humiliated in front of my own son.
You two make such a devoted aunt
and niece.
Mother.
Mother...
Ma... Ma'am.
What brings you here?
If you need anything,
have a servant call me.
I'll be right away.
- Maids.
- Yes, Ma'am.
Send Zheng Shu away immediately.
I don't want to see her again.
Mother!
- Ma'am...
- Please, show mercy.
- Aunt!
- Mother!
Ma'am!
- Aunt!
- Mother!
- I know you and your niece are close.
- Aunt!
- I won't let her suffer.
- Ma'am, I admit my fault!
Though Zheng Shu
is an orphan,
she still has uncles.
Ma'am has
prepared a dowry for her
and will find her a good husband.
Lady Zhu,
are you satisfied?
Mother, I will
follow your arrangements.
My Lord, let go of me.
Let go of me!
What is it?
Her Ladyship worried
the chill might make you sick,
so she sent some decoction.
She hopes you feel better.
Anything happened
in the household today?
Her Ladyship visited Lady Xu,
and then Lady Xu went to see Lady Zhu.
That's all I know.
I heard Lady Xu scolded Lady Zhu
in the east wing today
and sent her to meditate
at the ancestral hall.
But I don't know what really happened.
What could it be?
Mother must've upset Grandmother again.
That's not unusual.
I hope she learns her lesson this time.
But it won't be easy.
- My Lord.
My Lord, please have a seat.
I heard
Grandmother called for you early
this morning.
Yes.
But don't worry, My Lord.
I didn't tell Grandmother a single word
about what happened last night.
No one else knows either,
not even Chunniang.
Let's eat.
(Healing Powder)
My Lord.
Are you afraid of me?
I just...
I'm just worried about your wound.
(Healing Powder)
Don't worry.
What happened yesterday
won't happen again. I promise.
We need to supervise
the Yongning Canal in a few days.
Whose turn is it?
I'm too young. I'm not going.
I can't leave the tavern maid
at Luozhong Tavern.
Wei Xiao, you should go.
Let's draw straws.
What? Again? No way.
You only draw straws when no one wants to go.
I'm not drawing.
Just get it over with, so we...
What are you mumbling? So annoying!
My Lord,
what's wrong?
He said he's staying at
the Government Office for now.
Probably had another fight with Her Ladyship.
Finished the military embezzlement case?
Yes, the ringleader's caught.
He'll be executed soon.
Then you're just idling around here?
No, we're not.
The Yongning Canal is almost finished.
We were talking about
who should go inspect it in a few days.
It's not a big deal.
Advisor said
it doesn't matter who goes.
Just bring a few men and make it official.
Since it's not a big deal, why's it
taking so long?
I'll go myself.
It's just a routine check to Panyi.
You don't have to go...
Enough!
I said I'm going. That's final.
Yes, My Lord.
♪The moonlight is as silent
as the deep sea♪
♪From afar♪
♪It once lit up dreams with a breath♪
♪But vanished with a sigh♪
♪We meet and part in the fires of war♪
♪Embracing,
leaving tender marks of love♪
♪With one breathtaking glance♪
♪How could I ever forget♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
(Execution)
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
His Lordship said he caught a chill.
But why hasn't he come back for days?
Hiding from me, I guess.
He's hiding from you, My Lady?
Afraid I'll catch his illness.
That's rather considerate of him.
Quite the planner.
Planner?
What plan?
Nothing.
I just think he's trying to balance
his mother's dignity and his filial duty.
I feel a bit sorry for him.
Go tell him
to come home later.
I'm not afraid of chills.
Greetings, My Lady.
Why are you packing so much?
His Lordship has official duties?
In two days, His Lordship will go to Panyi.
He asked us to get his things packed.
What's the trip to Panyi about?
The Yongning Canal project is almost done.
Someone needs to inspect it.
His Lordship insists on
going himself.
Just a routine inspection?
Why not let Wei Liang go?
Now he's going to Panyi to hide from me?
Any other orders, My Lady?
There you are, My Lady.
I've been looking everywhere.
Lady Zhu said
since she went to meditate
at the ancestral hall,
she hasn't seen you for days.
She asks you to come, My Lady.
I should visit Mother.
Chuyu's been
by my side all these years.
Now that I'm sending her away,
it should be done with dignity.
If you hadn't tattled,
why would Lady Xu
have ordered Chuyu
to leave with no delay?
Is stealing my Zhonglin not enough?
Now you're driving away
my only niece, aren't you?
You're being way too cruel.
Did your father teach you of this?
Grandmother ordered you
to kneel in the ancestral hall.
You must be exhausted.
I shall take my leave.
Stop right there!
Did I say you could leave?
If it weren't for your meddling,
Zhonglin would've married Chuyu long ago.
But now, he's lost face
with both his family
and ancestors.
Seems like your time kneeling
in the ancestral hall
hasn't taught you Grandmother's wishes.
Insolence!
How dare you talk back?
Of course you're the enemy's daughter.
You don't even come close to my Chuyu.
True.
You've always wanted Zheng Shu
to marry His Lordship.
Despite all his refusals,
you still pushed on.
You even schemed just to make it happen.
Now that everything's come to light,
all you care about is Zheng Shu.
What about His Lordship's dignity?
Everyone says you love your son,
but do you really?
You want Zheng Shu to be his concubine.
You tampered with the box
for her sake.
You even drugged His Lordship,
all for Zheng Shu.
His Lordship is the ruler of Wei.
His marriage should serve the greater good.
The marriage alliance is taking effect,
but you keep interfering.
I'm afraid you don't want His Lordship
to truly take the throne!
How dare you!
♪The moonlight is as silent
as the deep sea♪
♪From afar♪
♪It once lit up dreams with a breath♪
♪But vanished with a sigh♪
♪Brushing past my fingertips♪
♪My heartstrings were stirred quietly♪
♪As if we once met before♪
♪Holding back a love so deep♪
♪Love asks for nothing in the end♪
♪Leaving only obsessions♪
♪I've wandered in the world♪
♪Yet cannot have it all♪
♪We meet and part in the fires of war♪
♪Embracing,
leaving tender marks of love♪
♪With one breathtaking glance♪
♪How could I ever forget♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪