♪If not for you♪
♪I wouldn't have wanted
to make a name for myself♪
♪Only when I have your love♪
♪Is my invincibility not in vain♪
♪The towering peaks I've conquered♪
♪Leave me♪
♪Feeling empty♪
♪I've given everything♪
♪Just to follow you♪
♪Through life and death♪
♪Could it be that love♪
♪Is the true end of this life♪
♪Why does every battle♪
♪Bring deeper pain♪
♪I never got it♪
♪You once promised me♪
♪You'd give me ordinary days♪
♪Then I'd rather♪
♪Face blades and fall♪
♪Into your arms instead of the clouds♪
♪I'll pass through layers of fog♪
♪And barriers♪
♪The world's rights and wrongs,
wins and losses♪
♪Who's to weigh their worth♪
♪Only love♪
♪Gives me a sky as wide as the sea♪
♪I only want to be your hero♪
=The Prisoner of Beauty=
=Episode 35=
Out of fear that the truth
would come out,
Liu Yan ordered a siege.
We couldn't hold them off.
General Wei Liang fought to
get me out of there,
but he...
He...
I...
It should've been me.
Qiao Ci,
look at me.
Wei Liang went to fetch you, right?
Where is he now?
Look at me.
Where is Wei Liang?
He went to Yujun.
Answer me. Where is he now?
Look at me. Where is Wei Liang?
Where is Wei Liang?
Where is he?
It should've been you.
Why did it have to be him?
Why not a Qiao?
Wei Xiao!
My Lord!
Reporting!
Liu Yan has taken Panyi with his troops.
Pass down my orders:
All troops, stay on alert.
Tomorrow,
we march on Panyi!
Yes.
My Lord.
My Lord, My Lord.
Let me lead a team to bring him back.
I asked Wei Liang to go. He'll be fine.
He just didn't see him.
- Wei Qu.
- I'll get him back.
Wei Qu, calm down!
Wei Qu!
Let me bring him back!
Get up.
My Lord, let me bring him back.
Wei Liang will be okay.
I'll go now. I'll bring him back!
Wei Qu, hear my command.
Tomorrow, take a cavalry unit
to Kangjun.
Find Qiao Ping.
Bring
Wei Liang back.
I will bring him back.
Yes, My Lord.
- My Lady.
- Manman. Manman.
- Manman.
- My Lady.
Lie down.
My Lord.
Don't blame yourself.
I just hate
that I can't take this pain for you.
You grew up with Wei Liang.
You weren't real brothers,
but he was like a real brother to you.
Now, he was killed because of my family.
Even if we paid with our lives,
it wouldn't ease your pain.
I once promised you
that I'd give you more kids
and restore the past glory.
But now I've made you lose Wei Liang.
And Xiaotao...
She's still...
She's still waiting for Wei Liang.
This isn't your fault.
You've tried to balance both clans.
It's been exhausting.
Besides,
Qiao Yue and Liu Yan
did this.
You had nothing to do with it.
I will never blame you
for this.
But from now on,
I may...
I understand.
Whether it's to avenge Wei Liang,
take back Panyi for the people,
seek justice for General Wei Liang,
or punish my uncle's betrayal,
you must go to war at once.
Don't worry.
I don't blame you.
Thank you, Manman.
You've never failed me,
and I will never fail you.
I promise.
This matter
will not implicate others.
I give you my word.
After I leave,
take care of this family for me.
Take care of yourself
and Feifei.
I may not be back
in time for Feifei's birth.
That's okay.
This time,
I won't see you off.
Be careful on your journey.
Don't worry.
(Yujun)
My Lord, don't worry.
Wei Xiao and I will protect Yujun.
We'll patrol day and night.
Nothing will happen.
Lady Xu and Lady Zhu
will take care of the Lady.
You have nothing to worry about.
Good.
- Depart!
- Yes!
Hyah!
My Lady, take care of yourself.
Don't strain yourself or harm the baby.
How's Xiaotao?
Xiaotao...
You're really going to Yanzhou?
I'll go and pick a real Yanzhou orchid
to marry you.
Are you asking me to serve you?
No need for that.
Just marry me.
Once I've saved enough wages,
I'll have the Lord ask
for your mother's approval on my behalf.
He values you.
He's afraid he's not worthy of you,
so he wants to do more.
Only then will he feel at ease.
You...
Come back safe, okay?
I've got your safety charm.
Even if I get injured,
I'll come back and ask
for your mother's approval.
Pah, pah, pah.
You won't get injured.
Mine is a little gold dart.
Every time we head to battle,
we leave these little weapons behind.
I want to give this to you.
Seeing it
will be like seeing me.
Before General Wei Liang died,
he asked me
to bring this orchid to you.
He must not have wanted you
to grieve like this.
He said
he'd bring the orchid
and propose to me.
Tell Xiaotao
not to wait for me!
This is from him.
My mother said
he was afraid I'd suffer
and I'd look down on him one day
so he made the betrothal gifts
so complex.
She asked me to let him.
She said it was more festive.
(Panyi City, Yanzhou)
Lord Yang.
What's the situation in the city?
The defenses are weak.
We can't hold against Liangya.
Panyi has completely fallen
into Liu Yan's hands.
Lord Yang,
we once helped Lord Qiao
knock at the gate.
So now...
Should we have
to turn to Liangya now?
Listen.
(Zhongzhou has defected)
Lady Yulou has swayed Zhongzhou,
dealing a major blow to Wei.
Now, Wei Shao's allies
are turning to me.
I wonder how he defies me now.
But the Wei cavalry is still strong.
Even without allies,
they're hard to defeat.
Last time at Panyi,
Liangya lost to them.
Things are different now.
Wei Shao must pass this way
(Yongning City)
to reach us.
Yongning City?
He once built a dam here
to divert floods.
If the upper course breaks
and the lower course is blocked,
what do you think will happen
when he passes through?
Brilliant.
If it works,
this place will become Wei Shao's grave.
That day,
Lady Qiao scared off my reinforcements.
Today, I shall return that disgrace
in full.
Who's there?
Come in.
I'm here to deliver a report.
The Wei army is on the move.
My Lords,
(Zhongzhou has defected)
what to do?
Just as expected.
Lord Yang, guard the Panyi dam.
Be ready to release the water.
Yes. I'll prepare to open the gate.
Not to open it.
Destroy it.
Destroy the dam?
That can't be.
I've observed the clouds.
Heavy rains are coming.
If we break the dam now,
the flood downstream
will be catastrophic.
If the rain intensifies,
the people will be doomed.
The Lord of Wei...
Wei Shao deserves it,
but the people along the way
are innocent.
To achieve greatness,
one can't fuss over trifles.
Lord Yang, my late father trusted you.
Surely you understand that.
You call this a trifle?
Fine.
I understand.
Governor, My Lord,
I'll do as you command.
But the dam of the Yongning Canal
is made of giant stones.
It's hard to destroy.
If we use sulfur as an explosive,
it must be placed
beneath the load-bearing wooden beams.
Without the right method,
it won't work.
My Lord,
he makes a point.
Then please wait here.
I'll fetch the engineering diagram.
With that, it'll be more effective.
Very well.
Be quick.
Yes.
The Yongning Canal project
is very complex,
especially the section
from Panyi to Xindu.
It took years to build.
Now,
it links two major rivers.
I can't even tell if we're standing
above the Yang River
or the Pei River.
Lord Yang,
you took Wei's salary for years.
Do you see yourself as from Yanzhou
or Wei?
Does it matter?
Lord Qiao devoted years to this dam
to unify the land.
He hoped
for good traffic and trade
so the people no longer needed
to travel long
for water, food, and minerals.
I've seen
that same ambition
not only in Lord Qiao
but in the Lord of Wei, too.
They say you built canals in Panyi
and even in Rongjun.
Panyi wasn't always
a water town.
It used to be a flood zone.
Thanks to Lord Qiao's water management,
it became what it is today.
I just followed him around,
digging trenches.
That's how I gained a little experience
to fight back against the floods
of the Yang River.
That must've been hard.
When this is over,
you'll be rewarded.
I'm just
following orders.
There's no hardship in that.
But today,
I'll have to fail Lord Qiao.
Father built the canal for Yanzhou.
Destroying it now
is to eliminate a threat to Yanzhou.
You won't fail him.
Hurry and unroll the diagram.
Let's get started.
Sure.
An assassin!
Someone help!
Don't move!
What are you doing?
I couldn't kill Liu Yan,
but I can kill you!
However,
I'll have to fail Lord Qiao.
Yang Feng, are you insane?
How can you live after killing me?
Without the dam
and Panyi,
what's the point
of surviving alone?
Let him go.
I'll spare your life.
If Zhen Zhi could die for the cause,
so can I.
My Lord,
don't push him.
Fine.
I'm sorry, Lord Qiao.
(Hydraulic Engineering Diagram)
You...
My Lord...
Even a minor mayor dared defy me?
Wei Shao,
I'll kill you myself.
(Hydraulic Engineering Diagram)
Don't worry too much
about Qiao and Liu.
It had nothing to do
with you or Ci.
Zhonglin will handle it.
Has your appetite
become better?
Yes.
My Lady.
General Wei Xiao requests an audience.
Let him in.
Yes.
My Ladies,
news from the border.
Su Ehuang and Xue Tai
are leading the Zhongzhou army
to attack Yujun.
Zhongzhou has defected too?
How many troops are in Yujun now?
My Lady,
our troops
are fewer than 60,000.
Besides the border garrisons,
the Lord also left 5,000 each
in Yunzhong and Rongjun.
Grandmother,
I believe we should dispatch couriers
to warn the Lord,
so he'll be more careful.
They can also alert the border generals
to support one another
in case they're attacked.
Approved.
Let's do as you suggest.
Though the enemy comes strong,
the men of the Wei Clan
are battle-tested.
Heaven favors Wei.
We will overcome this.
- Yes.
General, please wait.
Grandmother,
Yujun is in grave danger.
We should post a notice
to call on the people
to defend Yujun with us.
Anyone who volunteers
can get armor and weapons in the office.
Also, we should open the gates
for two days
to let those who wish to go
leave Yujun.
When peace returns,
they can come back.
The Wei Clan
always puts the people first.
Do as you say.
- General Wei Xiao.
- Yes.
Escort Lady Zhu and the Lady
out of the city.
- Be quick.
- Yes.
Grandmother,
I can't leave.
I must stay in Yujun.
Before the Lord left,
I promised him
that...
- Lady Qiao.
- She's about to give birth.
Summon the physician!
Hurry!
Breathe. Breathe.
My Lady, please wait outside.
My Lady.
My Lady, push!
Come on, wipe her sweat.
Don't panic, My Lady.
Just relax.
Inhale. Push.
My Lady.
Don't panic. Hurry.
Relax.
Whoa.
Watch out!
- Inhale.
Exhale.
Not yet.
Push again.
Exhale.
- Push!
Push!
Push, My Lady!
Bear with it.
Come on, one, two.
Push!
Hurry!
Lift!
We can see the head.
Push!
The baby is here!
- The baby is here.
- It's born.
Alright.
Congratulations, My Lady.
You have a child now.
My Lady,
look.
It's a little girl.
Feifei.
This is wonderful.
Wonderful.
Both of you are safe.
Mother.
Thank you.
She looks adorable.
How are you?
It must've been so hard.
Not at all.
You're soaked in sweat.
Report!
Yunzhong, Rongjun,
and Hanjun have fallen.
A force of 100,000 is marching on Yujun.
What do we do?
My Lady!
- What to do?
- Pack now.
Let's bring the Lady back to Yanzhou.
- What should we do?
- What to do?
Where do we go?
- What should we do?
- What to do?
Where can we go?
Stop panicking.
Grandmother,
the Lord left 60,000 men here.
How many troops does he have?
Building the Yongning Canal
cost Wei dearly.
We don't have many left.
How is he
supposed to fight?
What to do?
Good child.
Since Zhonglin has arranged it,
he must have a plan to win.
Get some rest.
I'll arrange for guards
to escort you
and Lady Zhu out.
I can't leave.
Grandmother.
Before the Lord left,
I promised him
to take care of everything at home
with no mistakes.
Grandmother, you are my family.
Yujun is my home.
I am the Lady of Wei.
I will stand with the people of Yujun.
I won't leave either.
Stop making more trouble.
In my whole life,
I've only wanted
to make you happy,
but I'm foolish
and often fail.
If you can see me differently
when I choose to stay,
then I won't leave.
Yes.
Though I'm
afraid of death,
my sons
and my husband
would never be deserters.
I will never
shame them
because of me.
Mother,
please let me stay.
I beg you.
Look.
These are
the Ladies of Wei.
She's smiling.
My Lord,
just as expected,
Liu Yan took Panyi
and destroyed the dam.
The Yang River broke free,
flooding everything.
He wants to trap us here
to miss our chance.
Anything else?
The couriers report
that Lord Zhen and Lord Yang
died for the cause.
Qiao Yue is dead.
How many of our men are left?
Fewer than 70%.
(Yujun)
(Panyi)
We can't delay anymore.
We must hurry to Panyi
and retake the Yongning Canal.
Report!
My Lord,
Lady Yulou and General Xue Tai
are leading 100,000 troops
to besiege Yujun.
They'll break through the gates soon.
Please come back to defend.
My Lord,
Lady Xu, Lady Zhu, and the Lady
are still in Yujun.
If the enemy breaches the city,
their lives will be at risk.
Fifteen years ago in Xindu,
the Wei Clan lost three generations.
Must we face
the same today?
My Lord,
shall we march on Panyi
or fall back to defend Yujun?
Grandfather wants to keep
the people of Yanzhou
out of this war.
Whether to fail one person
or fail the people...
If it were me,
I wouldn't know how to choose either.
(Panyi)
Pass on my orders:
Let's march on Panyi
and retake the Yongning Canal.
Yes.
(Government Office)
Those seeking shelter
with nowhere else to go,
regardless of age,
may take refuge in the hall.
My Lady,
I want to enlist.
The enemy
is at our doorstep.
Though I am a woman,
I refuse to be bullied.
- I want to protect my home.
- Yes.
I once followed the late lord
to fight across the land.
Now the enemy's children
have reached our homes.
Yes.
We must show them
the power of Wei.
- Yes.
- Drive the enemy away!
Defend Wei!
Drive the enemy away! Defend Wei!
I know you want to protect our home.
Thank you all.
Count us in.
We may fail
in the battle today.
But we stand here
to tell everyone
the Wei Clan
hasn't betrayed the Wei State
and never will.
Yes.
As long as the Wei Clan stands,
the Wei State stands.
The Wei Clan
will stand with you.
Defend Yujun!
Protect the Wei State!
Defend Yujun! Protect the Wei State!
(Kangjun, Yanzhou)
Cheers! Come on!
We're on duty. Drink less.
What's there to fear?
The battle is at Panyi.
Who'd come here?
Cheers!
Come on!
If you go to Kangjun,
you can bring back
the Lord's father-in-law
and pick up an orchid on the way.
Then you can marry Xiaotao
when you're back.
Come on.
Let me fill your bowl.
Your face wasn't harmed.
We're not staying here.
I'm here to get you, Liang.
I'm bringing you home.
Aren't you Wei's greatest warrior?
Why did you die here?
How could you die here?
Come on, come with me.
I won't draw
grass straws anymore, Liang.
I won't.
Get up. Come home with me.
Get up!
Get up. I can't carry you.
We won't draw grass straws anymore.
Xiaotao's waiting to marry you.
Liang, let's go home.
Let's go.
You must be cold.
Liang,
we're not staying here.
I'll bring you home.
(Kangjun Wharf)
(Wei)
The Wei Clan
still has to fight for the Qiao Clan.
The Lord sent me to rescue a Qiao.
Come with me.
Enemy! Reinforce the defense!
Yes.
Liang.
I lost an arm.
Go to Kangjun
and bring
Wei Liang back.
Who's there?
Wei Qu, General of Wei.
I'm here to rescue you.
Thanks, General Wei.
Can you see anything?
Though I can't see,
I still have some basic fighting skills.
I won't hold you back.
Just give me
some instructions, General.
Hold on to me tight.
General,
who's on your back?
Wei Liang, General of Wei.
You two,
I suggest you surrender.
This is Yanzhou.
How can a Liangya man be in charge?
Soldiers, you might not know,
but your governor
was killed in Panyi
by the Lord of Liangya.
Liangya is hiding this
to divide Yanzhou later.
My brother is dead?
Qiao Yue is dead.
So, the prefect is
the governor now.
Are you sure
you want to fight him now?
Don't listen to him.
Seize these two immediately.
The Lord of Liangya
offers a heavy reward.
The Wei army will soon crush Panyi.
The Lord of Liangya
can barely protect himself,
let alone you.
- Well.
- Think carefully.
Will you listen to a Liangya man
or your prefect?
♪The moonlight is as silent
as the deep sea♪
♪From afar♪
♪It once lit up dreams with a breath♪
♪But vanished with a sigh♪
♪Brushing past my fingertips♪
♪My heartstrings were stirred quietly♪
♪As if we once met before♪
♪Holding back a love so deep♪
♪Love asks for nothing in the end♪
♪Leaving only obsessions♪
♪I've wandered in the world♪
♪Yet cannot have it all♪
♪We meet and part in the fires of war♪
♪Embracing,
leaving tender marks of love♪
♪With one breathtaking glance♪
♪How could I ever forget♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪