♪If not for you♪
♪I wouldn't have wanted
to make a name for myself♪
♪Only when I have your love♪
♪Is my invincibility not in vain♪
♪The towering peaks I've conquered♪
♪Leave me♪
♪Feeling empty♪
♪I've given everything♪
♪Just to follow you♪
♪Through life and death♪
♪Could it be that love♪
♪Is the true end of this life♪
♪Why does every battle♪
♪Bring deeper pain♪
♪I never got it♪
♪You once promised me♪
♪You'd give me ordinary days♪
♪Then I'd rather♪
♪Face blades and fall♪
♪Into your arms instead of the clouds♪
♪I'll pass through layers of fog♪
♪And barriers♪
♪The world's rights and wrongs,
wins and losses♪
♪Who's to weigh their worth♪
♪Only love♪
♪Gives me a sky as wide as the sea♪
♪I only want to be your hero♪
=The Prisoner of Beauty=
=Episode 21=
Go tell Zhonglin
that I've entrusted Lady Qiao
with the Deer Hunt Venue.
Let's see how can he can avoid her now.
Who said I can't live without her?
I think the Government Office
is far better than home.
At least here, I feel free.
My Lord,
have some hot ginger soup before bed
to warm you up.
How thoughtful. Everything's better now.
I'm glad the Lord slept well last night.
The dishes tonight
have been prepared in the kitchen.
Bring them to him later.
If anything is missing, go buy it
or come back to get it.
If you're short on money,
ask Xiaotao for more.
Thank you for caring for the Lord.
I will make sure he is looked after
as if he were at home.
Are you trying to make him
never want to come back?
I don't have such deep thoughts.
I just want him to live comfortably.
Come with me to Deer Hunt Venue.
If you feel tired or have a headache,
use this cooling balm
to refresh yourself.
♪The moonlight is as silent
as the deep sea♪
♪From afar♪
♪I've wandered in the world♪
♪Yet cannot have it all♪
♪We meet and part in the fires of war♪
(Qiao)
♪Embracing,
leaving tender marks of love♪
♪With one breathtaking glance♪
♪How could I ever forget♪
The hand warmer is ready.
Hold it, so you won't get cold.
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪No matter the trials♪
(Government Office)
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪
My Lord, are you hungry?
What makes you become
so thoughtful suddenly?
It's made in the kitchen at home.
You'll definitely like it.
This...
Who prepared it?
Of course, it was the Lady.
The Lady?
What about this balm?
Also the Lady.
- The hand warmer?
- Also the Lady.
Why did you smile yesterday
when I praised you?
Weren't you praising the Lady?
Though I'm at the office,
I'm still caught in the web.
If you don't like it,
I'll prepare something else.
No need.
I'll just make do.
What has the Lady
been doing these days?
Besides instructing me every day
to care for you,
she's been busy with the renovation
of Deer Hunt Venue.
I heard
she's anxious to find someone
to write poetic exposition to boost
the popularity of the Deer Hunt.
Do you know there's a scholar
skilled in poetic expositions
and full of talent,
named Gao Heng?
Master Zhenshi, Gao Heng,
is famed across the states,
admired by many.
The weather changed so fast.
It suddenly turned cold.
Yes.
Since the Lord is staying at the office,
hurry and prepare more clothes
to send to him.
Yes, yes.
I know you care deeply for the Lord.
Your hands are busy,
but your mouth isn't idle either.
Send him
another hand warmer.
Be careful.
That's his beloved item.
You can't touch this box.
Lady Yulou and the Lord
were almost betrothed.
Xiaozao,
about the jade pendant the Lord wears,
Lady Yulou seems to have one too.
Didn't Xiaotao say
Lady Yulou almost married
into the Wei Clan?
But don't worry, My Lady.
That's all in the past.
I'm afraid it's not in the past.
This is the dessert from Danjun?
Yes.
Why did you prepare this for me?
The Lady arranged it.
She said you'd surely like it.
I'd surely like it?
Take it away.
I don't like it.
Yes.
Where's my hand warmer?
It was taken back
to the mansion.
Back to the mansion?
The Lady said
the office is for working hard.
It shouldn't be made
as comfortable as home.
It would hinder your diligence.
What happened?
I even praised her today
in front of others
for her meticulous care.
She asked you to take it away,
so you did?
Whose side are you on?
Go get it back for me.
I'm on it.
Wait.
It's already late.
Don't disturb her rest.
Do it tomorrow.
Yes.
Why is this box here?
The Lady sent it.
She said it's your cherished item
and should be kept close.
You may leave now.
Yes.
Shao,
promise me two things.
Don't trust anyone from the Qiao Clan.
And take care of her for me.
You
have fallen in love
but still care about filial duty.
That will only
bring you pain.
Tomorrow, find some tavern maids
who resemble this goddess
in figure and charm.
Yes.
Why are you back?
The office is damp.
My headache flared up.
So tonight,
I'll sleep in the bedchamber.
As you wish.
What are you doing?
Fixing the pillow.
Perfect timing. Let me try it.
I have
a headache.
- Listen.
Let me go first.
My Lord...
This box holds the belongings
of my grandfather,
father,
and elder brother.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have taken the liberty.
It was my fault.
I should've told you earlier.
This jade pendant
is actually one half.
Before my brother died,
he split it in two
and asked me to give the other half
to Lady Yulou
because they were
almost betrothed.
My brother had excelled
in martial arts since he was a child.
He was known as the destined patriarch.
He followed Grandfather
into battle
and never lost a fight
until the Xindu Battle.
Then he became a scar
of Mother and me
that never healed.
So, from a young age,
I've told myself
to grow up to be brave,
kind,
and responsible
like him.
I still wonder if I can ever
measure up to him in Mother's eyes.
You're the best patriarch
the Wei Clan has ever had.
Before my brother died,
he asked two things of me.
The first was
to take care of Lady Yulou
on his behalf.
The second...
I failed to fulfill.
Do you
have a style name?
It's Manman.
Manman.
(Boya)
General,
there's been another raid
from Bianzhou today.
Thankfully,
they only took some livestock.
A few commoners were injured.
General, please come up with a solution.
Alright. I understand.
You may go.
- Yes.
Darling, is something troubling you?
Fan.
(Qiao)
Did I wake you just now?
It's still early.
Why don't you go back to sleep?
Why won't you tell me what's going on?
There was another raid
from Bianzhou.
No major losses were caused,
but this is the third time
this month.
Why didn't you tell me
something so serious?
Lady Ding and Ci are here.
I didn't want them to worry,
so I kept quiet.
I sought help from Father,
but he remained silent.
He won't send reinforcements.
He must have his reasons
for not doing that.
But I won't show weakness,
or he'll look down on me,
and you might not
be welcomed home again.
Bi Zhi.
Fan.
I know you worry for me,
but the Lady is right.
If I don't make something of myself,
how could I be worthy of you?
I've followed her instructions
and started to build roads
from Liancheng to Xiaogang.
That is what truly matters.
As for the rest,
they don't.
Since Father refuses to help,
I'll write to Manman
and ask if she can help.
But in the end,
the Qiao Clan's banner
is still flying in Boya.
Why would the Lord of Wei
vouch for me?
You fool.
I'll say
since the Deer Hunt is coming,
we'd like to visit them for the event.
Yeah.
If I attend,
the world will know
the Lord of Wei sees me as an in-law,
and if anyone dares invade Boya later,
they'll think twice.
We'll have to take a risk
and see if the Lord of Wei
has a place in his heart for Manman.
(To Manman)
Why didn't I see you
in the tavern before?
I'm a Yu.
I've admired you for a long time.
Good.
I'll come by another time.
I'll be waiting.
Lower
your head.
Zhu Quan,
send them back.
Yes.
My Lord,
Master Zhenshi, who was invited
for the poetic exposition,
has arrived in Yujun.
He said
he wanted to explore the scenery
before he could begin writing.
Let him be.
Treat him well.
Yes.
Chunniang sent these
honeyed drinks and cakes
on the Lady's orders.
Why didn't she
bring it herself?
She's at Deer Hunt Venue,
overseeing the renovations.
Any other orders, My Lord?
Pick out a few hairpins
in the latest
and finest styles for me.
Yes.
What a rare gathering.
Let's raise our glass.
- Mother.
- To grandmother.
Though it's late now,
the room feels
particularly radiant.
It must be because of Grandmother
and Aunt's beautiful new jewelry,
so you look much more stunning.
During the day, Zhonglin
noticed my hairpin was worn,
so he brought a new one tonight.
He also got one for Mother
and Lady Qiao too.
He's mainly trying to be filial to you.
I just benefited from that.
Shiyuan,
what's wrong with you?
Three of us have new jewelry,
but you only complimented two.
Can't you see the hairpin
on Lady Qiao's head?
Grandmother,
Zhonglin should be the one
complimenting Lady Qiao,
while I can focus
on cheering up you two.
Of course, we're happy.
I really like the hairpin from you.
The craftsman had
some material left
so he made yours
with it.
Still,
I'm glad you like it.
Zhonglin,
you meant well.
Why say such things?
Is it so hard
to say something nice?
You're right.
Let's drink.
To Grandmother.
Mr. Wei really is something.
That girl is completely obsessed
with him now.
She's driven off every suitor.
She'll marry no one but him.
Really?
Where did you hear that gossip?
The whole city's talking about it.
She says
she sees him every day
and spends every night
with him.
She even has a keepsake from him.
She's a girl, after all.
With that much detail,
it's gotta be true.
Is Mr. Wei getting married?
I don't think so.
We know him.
He's engaged with half the girls here.
He's always been a flirt.
It's not likely that he'll tie himself
to one woman.
So, he gave her affection
but no promise.
That'll ruin her life.
You're too naive.
Who is this good girl?
A Yu in the east of the city.
I've never heard of her.
Why are you here gossiping
instead of being on duty?
Mr. Wei, we're waiting for the Lord.
- Close the door.
- Sure.
We're waiting for the Lord to head
to the office.
You shouldn't have asked.
You mentioned it first.
Shiyuan
has always been messy
with women.
I'm not surprised
that he's messing
with a good girl.
Mr. Wei never mentioned this.
We don't know if it's true yet.
I've seen plenty of girls claiming
to hold his keepsakes.
Some have a rouge box,
and some have a wooden comb.
I wonder
what it is this time.
My Lady,
this time
it's a flute.
A flute?
Then it might be true.
If she's someone
Shiyuan really likes,
I'd like to meet her.
What's all the chatter about?
- It's about you.
- Let me hear it.
Grandmother.
Aunt.
It's your flirtatious debts.
There's gossip all over the city.
A girl claimed to have your keepsake,
said she was engaged to you,
and swore she'd marry no one else.
She said you invited her home to paint.
Mr. Wei, do you know anything
about this?
Painting?
Was it a tavern maid surnamed Yu?
What tavern maid?
She's a girl from a decent family.
You found her?
If you keep this up,
I won't help you
find anyone next time.
So, you do know she's a Yu.
Then she does exist.
Grandmother,
it's a misunderstanding.
That day...
If she's truly the one you want,
we don't care about her background.
Shall I arrange
the betrothal?
It was just one meeting.
If I truly care for someone,
I'll ask you to arrange it for me.
I'm tired.
I'm leaving.
Mr. Wei.
What's wrong?
I have an appointment.
Would you like to join me?
Who is it?
I've sent someone to fetch her.
Miss Yu, I invited you here today
to hear your thoughts
and to settle
all the rumors.
My Lady,
I was once intimate
with Mr. Wei.
I've rejected all other suitors for him.
I'd gladly be his wife or concubine.
I will marry
no one else.
I've given him my heart.
Just last night,
he treated me tenderly,
smiled at me,
gave me a keepsake,
held me close, and kissed me.
You mean last night?
We've been together every night.
Last night was no exception.
There was a family banquet last night.
Was it later last night?
Yes.
It was later than usual.
Last night,
Mr. Wei got drunk at the banquet.
He rested at the mansion as arranged.
He didn't go out again.
How did you
meet him?
Perhaps I remembered wrong.
He didn't come last night.
But usually,
he comes every day.
If you can't recall
what happened last night,
how can we trust
what you said about before?
I have his keepsake.
Everything I said is true.
Mr. Wei and I truly love each other.
I must marry him.
We don't know
whether what you have
is proof or a stolen item.
Being a weak woman doesn't mean
you can use it to oppress Mr. Wei.
My Lady,
she just
admired Mr. Wei deeply,
so she was momentarily confused
and disguised herself as a tavern maid
to sneak into the mansion.
She just wanted to see him,
yet he treated her so gently.
That's how she wanted something more.
My Lady,
please show mercy
for her sincere love.
How unfair.
Love has now become
an excuse to make false accusations.
Take Miss Yu home.
Watch her closely.
Thank you, My Lady.
My Lady.
Chunniang,
spread the word:
This must not be talked about again.
A woman's reputation matters.
Don't ruin her future.
Yes, My Lady.
Rest assured.
Why did you do that?
I am the Lady of the Wei Clan,
so I should get to decide
everything about women.
I just don't understand.
Since you were wrongly accused,
why didn't you defend yourself?
I'm a man.
Why care about reputation?
Besides, I've had affairs with many.
What's one more?
Still, I didn't expect you
to defend me like this.
Reputation, good or bad,
should come
from what you've actually done,
not from false accusations.
I'm your family.
Of course,
I won't let you suffer injustice.
Everyone thinks I'm a rake
and it's no surprise for me to do this.
Why do you
see me
differently?
Perhaps it's because I believe
I understand your character.
Even if your words
are sometimes flirtatious,
you would never
deceive and abandon a woman.
Grandmother protects me,
and Zhonglin defends me,
even when they think
I'm wrong.
Thank you.
Miss Yu loved Mr. Wei,
so
she picked up his flute,
hoping it would lead to marriage.
Unexpectedly,
Mr. Wei had no such intentions.
Fate
can't be forced.
Yes.
Seeing
how Zhonglin and his wife
live so harmoniously,
I just hope Shiyuan
can get married soon
so he won't end up alone
like his mother.
Don't worry, My Lady.
Mr. Wei
will definitely find someone he loves.
(I was like that poor scholar,)
(lost and weary,)
(wandering into the wrong path,)
(until I finally came)
(to an open land)
(and saw the goddess.)
♪If my endless longing for you
can bring you to me♪
(With one move, flowers bloomed,
and grass withered.)
(Tiger and hare lived in harmony.
The sun and moon rose together.)
(I admired her)
(and wanted to approach)
(but feared she was out of reach.)
(I was)
(caught)
(in a dilemma.)
♪I stayed true to my heart♪
♪So what if we part again and again♪
(Matters of love fear hesitation)
(and overthinking.)
(That won't be spontaneous,)
(free,)
(simple,)
(or joyful.)
♪Leaving no regrets♪
♪I'll always remember you
in the years to come♪
(Wei Yan's Mansion, Wei)
♪Bravery won't fail me♪
♪Even in extreme danger♪
Is the goddess
that Mr. Wei loves
me?
Alright.
If you have nothing else to say,
you may leave.
My Lord,
this is a letter from Boya to the Lady.
What does it say?
Not much.
Just the same praise about how good
the general is to his wife.
She's bragging about her husband.
Nothing new.
Bi Zhi listens to his wife
in everything.
I've never seen a man
so devoted to his wife.
How can a man
be controlled like this?
You don't get it.
I heard it from Wei Qu.
He said
the general and his wife
went through a lot
to be together, right?
I saw that myself in Boya.
Their bond is truly
beyond ordinary couples.
The Lord and the Lady
have been through a lot too,
but I don't see the Lady
controlling the Lord.
Wait, Wei Liang.
Why are you suddenly talking
about love today?
Are you thinking of getting married?
With whom?
Alright, you may leave.
My Lord.
I have a report.
Speak.
Master Zhenshi has finished
the poetic exposition.
Already?
Didn't he say earlier
he had no inspiration
even after touring all of Wei?
He just suddenly got inspired?
It's said that he strolled
around the drill ground for two hours
and started writing on the spot.
That old man
is quite interesting.
My Lord,
Master Zhenshi is no elder.
He is a young and handsome man.
Young
and handsome?
I'll head to the drill ground.
My Lord,
he's a rare talent.
Please treat him with respect.
(Yujun, Wei)
(Shi)
(Bian)
(Xi)
(Gao Heng, a famous scholar)
How brilliant.
To compose like that on the spot
is truly beyond us.
Indeed.
It was only by coming here
that I finally found inspiration.
Master Zhenshi,
with such striking features,
is not only good-looking
but also talented in literature.
You have finally finished.
Let's read it.
- Yes.
- Right.
Such elegant writing.
Every word is a gem.
His diction and structure
are far beyond our reach.
- Truly.
- Yeah.
When all states prosper,
the world will have peace.
The water from the Yang River
is accessible
thanks to the Yongning Canal,
which runs over 700 li,
chasing the sun across the sky.
The walls of legacy are painted
with the contributions
of Lady Qiao.
Once I entered Xindu,
I saw the people living in harmony,
and the Lady, as pretty as a lotus,
walking like the drifting wind,
like a goddess among clouds
wherever she goes.
My Lord, you invited him
to praise Wei and the Deer Hunt,
yet he spoke of the Lady endlessly.
Master Zhenshi.
My Lord.
Master Zhenshi,
your talent is exceptional.
But with your strong build,
you don't look like a scholar,
more like a soldier.
You flatter me.
I've never practiced martial arts.
I'm as weak as a scholar should be.
Weak?
Really.
Each has their own path.
In combat,
you're unmatched.
In words and verse,
I won't yield
to anyone.
Indeed.
Master Zhenshi's exposition
is brilliant.
What a vivid portrait
you painted of the Lady.
"As pretty as a lotus,"
"walking like the drifting wind,"
"like a goddess among clouds"
"wherever she goes."
Once carved into a wall,
her beauty will echo
- through the ages.
- Exactly.
Carved into a wall?
Had I known that,
I wouldn't have read it so soon.
So,
you admit the piece is good?
Don't rush, My Lord.
I have one more line
to praise the Lady's handwriting.
With strokes like dragons
and strength like bamboo,
each motion
gleams with grace.
I've heard
the Lady's calligraphy
is refined and elegant.
If carved into a wall,
it'd rival
the famed Moya Inscriptions in Yunzhong,
leaving a legacy for future generations.
You're flattering me.
I've always wanted
to see the Moya Inscriptions
but never found the chance.
What's inscriptional?
It's not that.
It's the Moya Inscriptions.
Speaking of which, my top choice
is the Ode to Yunmen.
Its brushwork is wild,
and its structure is unbound.
It combined the large
and small seal scripts.
Its strokes are
like the clerical script.
Its writing
is free and ethereal,
full of imagination.
With changes
in the weather and light,
the inscriptions
seem
to have also changed.
My Lady,
if you want to view them,
I'd gladly be
your guide.
Why should you be her guide?
How could I trouble you?
I'm still new in Yujun.
I must care for Grandmother and Mother.
It's not convenient to travel.
That's right.
If you ever wish to go,
just tell me,
and I'll take you.
Actually,
there's no rush.
The Lady's visit to the inscriptions
is for later.
Today,
My Lady,
please write this for me.
A masterpiece
should be matched
with your calligraphy.
I think that won't be necessary.
Sir, I wasn't finished just now.
Your exposition is brilliant,
but it's off-topic.
I invited you here
to praise
the great land of Wei,
not the Lady.
Sir, your vision
is limited.
You're absolutely right.
I'll revise it.
I'll revise it at once.
However,
the Lady
truly is
a rare
and talented woman
in this world.
Every word I spoke
came from my heart.
Then let this piece
be a gift to you, My Lady,
to show
my admiration to you.
Your words are too precious.
I dare not accept.
Yes.
We must decline your offer.
Of course,
it won't be carved into any wall.
Master Zhenshi,
please rewrite
the whole thing.
You'd better
compose a song.
Don't go wandering off
until it's done.
Let's go.
Tan, escort Master Zhenshi back.
Yes.
My Lord.
Wait, that's a dead end.
You need to go this way.
One day,
I hope to invite the Lady
to see the Moya Inscriptions.
She has no time.
You're always busy with state affairs.
What
brings you here today?
Master Zhenshi
truly is gifted
and handsome.
No wonder so many women
admire him.
If so many admire him,
he must have met real beauties,
yet he stays above it all,
with a heart set on scenery.
Why aren't you wearing
the hairpin I gave you?
You said you made it casually.
I figured you didn't like it,
so I didn't wear it.
How could I have had it made casually?
I put a lot of thought into that gift.
Thank you, My Lord.
♪The moonlight is as silent
as the deep sea♪
♪From afar♪
♪It once lit up dreams with a breath♪
♪But vanished with a sigh♪
♪Brushing past my fingertips♪
♪My heartstrings were stirred quietly♪
♪As if we once met before♪
♪Holding back a love so deep♪
♪Love asks for nothing in the end♪
♪Leaving only obsessions♪
♪I've wandered in the world♪
♪Yet cannot have it all♪
♪We meet and part in the fires of war♪
♪Embracing,
leaving tender marks of love♪
♪With one breathtaking glance♪
♪How could I ever forget♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪