♪If not for you♪
♪I wouldn't have wanted
to make a name for myself♪
♪Only when I have your love♪
♪Is my invincibility not in vain♪
♪The towering peaks I've conquered♪
♪Leave me♪
♪Feeling empty♪
♪I've given everything♪
♪Just to follow you♪
♪Through life and death♪
♪Could it be that love♪
♪Is the true end of this life♪
♪Why does every battle♪
♪Bring deeper pain♪
♪I never got it♪
♪You once promised me♪
♪You'd give me ordinary days♪
♪Then I'd rather♪
♪Face blades and fall♪
♪Into your arms instead of the clouds♪
♪I'll pass through layers of fog♪
♪And barriers♪
♪The world's rights and wrongs,
wins and losses♪
♪Who's to weigh their worth♪
♪Only love♪
♪Gives me a sky as wide as the sea♪
♪I only want to be your hero♪
=The Prisoner of Beauty=
=Episode 32=
Do you blame me?
Why would you say that?
When you were at home,
you were treasured like a jewel.
But in the Wei State,
you're cautious everywhere.
The Wei State
is not a cage,
but for you,
it's no different.
And I've never seen you
so at ease before.
It's my fault.
You treat me well.
The days with you
are comfortable and happy.
Then it's settled.
Kangjun is your home,
and Yujun
is also your home.
Let's go.
This used to be my favorite place.
In summer, the trees grow thick and full.
I would dance
as Cousin played the zither.
Those days
seem far away now.
Maybe,
some still linger.
You're really lucky today.
Cousin feels like playing again.
Her zither is of exquisite craftsmanship.
How about this?
I'll play a piece for you.
No need today.
I've heard you play before.
Spend some time
with your cousin today.
I'll go for a stroll.
Manman!
Don't get up.
You're with child now.
How could you come
all the way out here alone?
Do you still see yourself as a young miss?
Soon, you'll be a mother.
We've been apart for so long.
Meeting here in Kangjun is a rare chance,
so I came early to wait for you.
Cousin, if ever you miss me,
just come back anytime you want.
When I left,
I didn't bring this zither with me.
But now,
my fingers itch to play.
It's perfect.
I would be delighted to hear you play.
I would be glad if you don't mind.
♪I travel alone to the moon♪
♪Against the stars♪
♪Looking back on each step♪
♪I'm coming♪
♪Fate's fickle♪
♪The journey's long♪
♪Mixed feelings♪
♪Intertwine♪
♪Tearful eyes♪
♪Meet at the sharp edge♪
♪Who'll surrender first♪
♪Looking back♪
♪I see the old moon♪
♪Longing that never fades is♪
♪The hardest to quit♪
♪Sacrifice one♪
♪For a ceasefire♪
♪Peace will last♪
♪Fate's fickle♪
♪The journey's long♪
♪Mixed feelings♪
♪Intertwine♪
♪Tearful eyes♪
♪Meet at the sharp edge♪
♪Who'll surrender first♪
♪Looking back♪
♪I see the old moon♪
♪Longing that never fades is♪
♪The hardest to quit♪
What's wrong?
Manman and I
feel distant now.
It'll be alright.
Why do you
look so downcast?
I just feel
Cousin and I are no longer as we once were.
That day in Xindu,
when Yanzhou was under siege,
I went to her for help.
She told me...
You know it's dangerous up ahead.
Are you going to send him to die?
You are capable and responsible.
You can save the people of the realm,
but I'm different.
I'm just an ordinary woman
with no ambition and no grand vision.
Even if I give it my all,
I can only protect one person.
I'm not like you,
who pushes her husband
fight and die
for the Qiao Clan,
and for the people of Yanzhou!
But I...
I can't do it.
Did I make a mistake?
Even Cousin knew
not to let her husband take such risks.
But I pushed you, pressured you,
even calculated you.
In those days, I was so afraid
you would think the same,
that I cared nothing for your safety.
In that situation,
you had no other choice.
Besides, I know
my Manman
is not like other women.
She loves me,
her family,
and all the people even more.
So you did nothing wrong.
Also,
I'd love to be your spear and shield,
to fight for you,
to guard your path,
to make your every wish
come true.
I have one more wish.
What is it?
"May you be safe and sound."
You just said
all my wishes would come true.
All I wish is for you to be safe and sound.
Don't worry.
I will be.
You startled me.
Over there.
Feel free to have a look.
Thank you.
It's beautiful.
Isn't it?
Does it good?
It does.
It really does.
See? It looks just like you.
This one?
Like me?
This chubby little thing is you exactly.
What's wrong?
I'll keep my distance.
I'm chubby. I don't want to crowd you.
It's cheerful and bright.
Everyone,
you've fled far
and suffered much.
For now,
please settle here,
stay warm and well-fed.
Prefect, that's so kind of you!
Prefect, that's so kind of you.
I never thought
- he'd gave us shelter.
- Exactly.
Prefect, you're so kind.
He doesn't look down on us Liangya people.
Exactly.
In the days ahead,
we'll do what we can for you, Prefect.
Thank you, Prefect.
No need for formality.
Please rise.
Distribute the food.
Mother,
this is for you.
You eat that.
Prefect,
our food was already scarce after the war.
Now I fear we won't hold out much longer.
Pass my order.
Stop all wine brewing.
We should
save the grain first.
Yes.
(Grain)
Lord of Wei.
May I ask why you are here?
And what's this for?
These are military supplies
I brought to Kangjun.
I hope they will be helpful.
Also, grain from Xindu
will arrive in a few days.
Lord of Wei,
you've lifted a great burden from us!
On behalf of the people,
I thank you, Lord of Wei.
Please rise.
No need for formality.
Although you thank me,
there's something
I want to ask you.
Because of Liangya,
Yanzhou lies in ruins now.
Why do you shelter
these stragglers and refugees?
Moreover,
some of them may have fought
against you in Liancheng.
These common folks
are war-torn innocents.
They are pitiful souls with nowhere to go.
Does it really matter where they come from?
Who among them
ever wished for war?
They had no choice.
Lord of Wei,
you built canals for the realm
and gave up troops.
You never asked who helped
or opposed you,
nor cared about
past kindness or grudges.
You did it for the people, and so do I.
That's true.
If peace ever comes
one day,
I'll guard it with all my heart
and ensure it
lasts for generations.
Even if peace lasts only for a moment,
a sincere heart can make
its echo last for generations.
If every region
followed your example, Lord of Wei,
then true sincerity
could dissolve hatred
and
bring peace to the land.
I'm willing to assist you
in completing the canal construction.
Let's face difficulties together.
Let water flow in all directions.
Let war be quelled.
Let sincerity dispel hatred
and win peace for the realm.
I hope that day will come.
At the end of the day,
since they've come to Yanzhou,
I can't simply
watch them starve.
But, I'm sorry
for causing you trouble.
You shouldn't have burdened
Wei State because of this.
You're welcome.
In chaotic times,
the people are the most innocent.
Father, we share the same intention,
so I wish to help.
What did you call me?
I called you Father.
It's been a while
since I married Her Ladyship,
but the journey's been rough.
Only now do I get to speak with you.
Your heart is with the people,
just like Her Ladyship's.
Father, I hope
you don't mind
my being late.
Lord of Wei,
I don't deserve this.
This gesture
is not from the Lord of Wei
to the Yanzhou Prefect.
It's from a son-in-law
to his father-in-law.
Zhonglin, you show such respect.
I feel
all the more
uneasy and ashamed.
We're family, no need to be so formal.
The night banquet is about to begin.
Let's go together,
Father.
Of course.
This way, please.
(Zhonglin bears no grudge.)
(But our Qiao Clan)
(still owes the Wei Clan a great debt.)
Father,
I'd like to offer you a toast
on behalf of Her Ladyship.
Thank you for raising her.
Speaking of raising her...
Right,
Yue and Lady Ding
have treated Manman as their own,
especially Lady Ding.
She deserves
this toast from Zhonglin.
Mother,
I'd like to offer you a toast.
Thank you
for raising Fan.
Lord of...
Zhonglin,
here's to the rebuilding of Yongning Canal.
Everyone,
raise your cups.
To the canal.
Although
Governor is Manman's uncle,
Yanzhou and Wei State
lie between us.
You'd better
call me Lord of Wei.
Lord of Wei...
Zhonglin means to speak
to me as family,
and to you as an official.
It doesn't conflict.
Um, well,
Bi Zhi.
Governor.
You should call me Father.
Father.
I've heard
you repeatedly defeated Xue Tai.
You're pretty talented.
We're short on generals in Yanzhou.
Seems you're destined
to join the Qiao family.
Governor, you flatter me.
Call me Father.
Father.
Though I've fought Xue Tai a few times,
I'm just a stableman.
I know little beyond that.
I merely scraped by.
Fan once said
Xue Tai feared
Lord of Wei and Her Ladyship,
so he never attacked me head-on.
To Lord of Wei.
Cheers.
Now that
you and Fan have both returned home,
settle in properly.
I'll send someone to take over Boya.
Thank you, Father.
Do you truly
accept Fan and me now?
Boya is just a small place.
Bi Zhi can still manage it well.
Besides,
I've grown used to it.
We will return someday.
That's our real home.
Manman asked for your help, but you refused.
No wonder Wei Shao keeps his distance
from me.
Father, don't worry.
Lord of Wei holds no grudge.
He's still willing to be Bi Zhi's in-law.
You're too naive.
He's only being polite
because Bi Zhi is useful.
I've explained
the pros and cons to Manman.
I didn't want Bi Zhi
risking his life to help them.
Manman understands.
Daughters often grow distant after marriage.
Daughters of others
know to stand with their kin.
Mine ran off with a stable hand.
At the crucial moment,
you turn your back on your family for him!
Father,
Bi Zhi is no longer
a stableman.
I know.
He's now Commander of Boya Forces.
The so-called forces
are just a ragtag army.
And you think it's a fine title?
Go tell Bi Zhi,
I'll take over Boya.
He will train my cavalry
and raise my steeds.
He should back up Ci,
so no one dares trample on me.
I refuse.
What did you say?
Father, since you still
see Bi Zhi as a stableman,
I suppose
you'll never accept him as your son-in-law.
I'll live in seclusion with Bi Zhi at Boya.
Let's not interfere with each other.
Wouldn't that be better?
You...
Do you even hear yourself?
To you, I'm just a daughter
who ran off with a stableman.
When Bi Zhi and I were in real danger,
you didn't send a single soldier to help us.
But now that Bi Zhi's gaining power,
you want to use me to control him?
I won't let that happen.
Also,
Bi Zhi didn't come
to fight against Liu Yan.
That decision was mine alone.
The Qiaos never lent him aid.
I could not let him
risk his life for my family.
Manman never blamed me for this.
Governor, you have even less right to!
I am
unfilial to Mother,
and I may have wronged my cousins.
But, Father,
I owe you nothing.
- You...
- Governor!
If you wish to claim Boya as your own,
send your troops and take it by force.
My Lord.
Mr. Zhang,
look at me now.
Do I look like a patriarch to you?
Both ladies are now backed
by powerful husbands.
They're no longer easy to control.
But I believe
both of them still hold loyalty
toward Yanzhou.
Loyalty to Yanzhou,
but not to me!
Tell me,
what caused all of this?
My Lord,
refugees have been flooding
into Kangjun lately.
Prefect's reputation
may now outshine your own.
What's wrong?
Fan,
you'd defy
your father for me.
That saddens me,
but also makes me happy.
You fool,
I'm not defying him.
Father has always
bullied the weak and feared the strong.
I won't blindly follow him
just because he raised me.
Remember this.
In this realm,
no one can
use me to control you.
Fan,
I'm not scared.
Everything I've done
was for your happiness.
Being with you makes me happiest.
I only hate myself
for not giving you the honor
that the Lord of Wei can.
If I cared about that,
I wouldn't have left with you.
What I care about
is your honest heart.
Sour plums.
That's exactly what I wanted.
It's cold outside.
Let's go into the room.
I love this room.
It's filled with your scent.
It just smells like your wine now.
Does it?
Can you still smell it?
You cheeky rogue.
We're returning to Wei State tomorrow.
Is there anything else
you'd still like to do?
Tell me.
I'll go with you
at first light.
I have nothing else.
I never imagined a day like this
before I married you.
You weren't just pretending to be happy
for my sake, were you?
If I said I was,
you wouldn't believe me.
Then
if you want to make it up to me,
how about
we strike a deal?
Whatever you want, say it now.
If it's something I can do,
I'll give it my all.
How about
giving me a child?
You want a child from me?
What do you mean, from you?
It would be our child.
And
I want it now.
I promise I'll give you a new home,
one filled with children and joy.
(Kangjun)
There's not much time.
You still need to hurry back to Yujun.
I won't insist on keeping you.
I only hope that next time,
you'll stay a little longer.
Governor, you're so kind.
Father,
we'll take our leave.
Please take care of
your health.
May I have
a word with you?
Of course.
Is this the direction to Wei State?
That's right.
- Father...
- Father.
On behalf of the Qiao Clan,
I bow from afar
to the spirits of
the late Lord of Wei,
your late father and brother.
I don't dare to seek forgiveness,
only to express my deepest gratitude.
I'm grateful to Lady Xu
and Lord of Wei
for your magnanimity.
Back then,
at the battle of Xindu,
it was the Qiao Clan's fault.
We brought disaster upon your kin.
I feel deep remorse.
My guilt is beyond words.
The grudge between our families
was settled long ago
by my grandmother.
You bear no resentment,
but I cannot pretend to forget.
All I ever wanted
was for Manman
to marry
someone she loved,
a man who would cherish her,
and live a peaceful life with her.
But fate had other plans.
On my late father's deathbed,
he took advantage of the situation
and arranged this marriage with you.
If the Qiaos and the Weis
had traded places,
I must admit
I wouldn't have treated
an enemy's daughter kindly.
But Lady Xu
has been gracious and generous.
She has cared deeply for my daughter.
You didn't turn her away.
You've shown her great care.
Even for her single request,
you dropped everything
to personally escort her home
and stepped into Yanzhou.
That made me all the more ashamed.
Now I see,
all my doubts
came from judging you
by my own narrow heart.
Father,
I'm ashamed as well.
I, too,
once made things difficult
and treated Her Ladyship harshly.
When did you ever treat me harshly?
I'm just a man of little worth.
Life and death, honor and shame,
they're fleeting to me.
All I care about
is my daughter.
Today,
I'd like to take this chance
to entrust Manman you, Lord of Wei.
Please protect her
and let her live a life of joy.
Here and now,
I offer you my sincere gratitude.
Father,
you have my word.
From now on,
I will cherish Manman even more.
Please,
trust me.
I trust you.
I really do.
(Yujun, Wei State)
(Wei Mansion, Wei State)
My Lady,
these are the ceremonial items prepared for
tomorrow's memorial rite.
Please take a look.
(Gift List of the Memorial Rite)
His Lordship won a great battle
and honors his father and brother.
You've worked so hard for this,
but will you be allowed to attend
and step into the ancestral hall?
Forget it.
Back when we first arrived in Yujun,
we were left outside of the city gates
just to avoid taking part in this very rite.
According to tradition,
a new wife who hasn't paid her respects
at her husband's ancestral hall
is not accepted nor recognized by the family.
Whether they accept me or not
depends on His Lordship's attitude.
Besides,
to ask Grandmother, Mother, and His Lordship
to let me into the ancestral hall
is asking too much, isn't it?
Why do I bring trouble upon myself?
My Lady,
this was rushed by His Lordship's orders.
He reminded them again and again,
worried it might delay
tomorrow's memorial rite.
My Lady,
this is the ceremonial robe.
My Lord.
Let's get inside.
♪In this realm, loneliness reigns supreme♪
♪It pushes me into♪
♪A prison shut out from every soul♪
♪The towering peaks I've conquered♪
♪Leave me feeling empty♪
(Spirit Tablet of the Late Lord Wei Shang)
♪I've given everything just
to follow you through life and death♪
Cleanse your hands.
Offer incense to the spirits.
♪I never got the ordinary days
you once promised me♪
(Spirit Tablet of the Late Lord Wei Lun)
♪Into your arms♪
♪Not distant misty peaks♪
♪Why does every battle bring deeper pain♪
♪I never got the ordinary days
you once promised me♪
Grandfather.
Father.
Brother.
♪Instead of the clouds♪
This is Lady Qiao,
my wife.
♪The world's rights and wrongs,
wins and losses♪
♪Who's to weigh their worth♪
♪Only love♪
♪Gives me a sky as wide as the sea♪
(Spirit Tablet of the Late Lord Wei Lun)
♪I only want to be your hero♪
♪The moonlight is as silent
as the deep sea♪
♪From afar♪
♪It once lit up dreams with a breath♪
♪But vanished with a sigh♪
♪Brushing past my fingertips♪
♪My heartstrings were stirred quietly♪
♪As if we once met before♪
♪Holding back a love so deep♪
♪Love asks for nothing in the end♪
♪Leaving only obsessions♪
♪I've wandered in the world♪
♪Yet cannot have it all♪
♪We meet and part in the fires of war♪
♪Embracing,
leaving tender marks of love♪
♪With one breathtaking glance♪
♪How could I ever forget♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪