♪If not for you♪
♪I wouldn't have wanted
to make a name for myself♪
♪Only when I have your love♪
♪Is my invincibility not in vain♪
♪The towering peaks I've conquered♪
♪Leave me♪
♪Feeling empty♪
♪I've given everything♪
♪Just to follow you♪
♪Through life and death♪
♪Could it be that love♪
♪Is the true end of this life♪
♪Why does every battle♪
♪Bring deeper pain♪
♪I never got it♪
♪You once promised me♪
♪You'd give me ordinary days♪
♪Then I'd rather♪
♪Face blades and fall♪
♪Into your arms instead of the clouds♪
♪I'll pass through layers of fog♪
♪And barriers♪
♪The world's rights and wrongs,
wins and losses♪
♪Who's to weigh their worth♪
♪Only love♪
♪Gives me a sky as wide as the sea♪
♪I only want to be your hero♪
=The Prisoner of Beauty=
=Episode 16=
Grandmother...
Grandmother.
Grandmother?
Shiyuan.
Grandmother.
Are you feeling better now?
When was I ever unwell?
Lady Qiao said you were…
I understand now.
I'm glad that you're fine.
I'll take my leave.
Shiyuan.
Are you never going
to see me again?
I've been unfilial
and caused you worry.
Please scold me
and punish me.
I hold no complaints at all.
This is not your fault.
Stand up.
No, it is my fault.
It's my fault losing my mind.
I nearly did something...
that would bring shame to the Wei family.
How did you learn
the truth about your birth?
While I was traveling,
a man approached me.
He claimed to have served Chen Pang.
He told me everything.
Shiyuan,
though you know your origins,
you may not know the whole story.
Your mother, Qingyun,
was my only daughter.
I cherished her
like a pearl in my palm.
But she was abducted by Chen Pang
and violated.
Three years later, she returned,
bearing you in her womb.
She died after
giving birth to you.
What did you say?
She was abducted? Violated?
When you were a child,
I kept this hidden from you.
Later,
when you were about 14 or 15,
we clashed with Bianzhou
in the battle of Xindu.
At that time,
you swore to defeat Bianzhou.
Had I told you the truth,
what would you have done?
I've always urged Zhonglin
to let go of the Qiao family grudge.
But deep down,
I could never let go
of my hatred for Chen Pang.
I shouldn't have misled you
into thinking you were from the Wei State.
Everything that happened
was my fault.
Grandmother,
did you truly see me as your grandson?
All these years,
you've always treated me like Zhonglin,
and at times,
showed me
even more affection.
But whenever
it came to military command,
you always left me out. Why?
Because you carry
the blood of
the Chen family.
Shiyuan,
since your grandfather passed away,
I've carried the Wei family on my shoulders.
I could never
fully trust you.
And Chen Pang wants the two
of you to reunite as father
and son in Bianzhou.
If Bianzhou changes hands,
you'll become the heir.
Now that it's out in the open,
you need to make a choice.
If you wish to stay by my side,
you will
still be my grandson.
I'll care for you as I always have.
But
I will never entrust you with power.
If you choose Bianzhou,
I won't stop you.
Before you leave,
kneel and bow to me three times,
as thanks
for my raising you all these years.
Then you leave this mansion,
and never come back.
A lost soul
is like a stray hound.
Grandmother,
I bow three times
to thank you for raising me.
I know you've always worried for me,
which is why you hesitated
to tell me the truth
about who I really am.
From this day on,
I belong only to the Wei family,
because I can't bear to leave you.
My Lord, now you're reassured?
Yes, My Lady.
You're so wise.
Since you praised me,
I shall do all I can to help.
Let me do one more thing for you.
What is it?
Ma'am.
What are you doing here?
You...
Are you here to enjoy the show?
It's cold at night.
The ancestral hall is colder.
I made some soup for you, Mother.
Take it away.
Drop the act. You're no saint.
If it weren't for you,
would Mother even punish me like this?
I've never wanted to harm you,
but you're using
the wheat seed matter to hold it
over me, aren't you?
Even though
you're now part of the Wei family,
I still don't like you.
Mother has never
liked me. That's fine.
Now, even you are
making things harder for me.
I've been in this family for 20 years.
Maybe no great deeds, but I gave it my all.
And now, my place in this house
even worse more than an enemy's.
I never expected you to like me.
All I want is for His Lordship
to have peace of mind.
And I believe that's what you want too.
This time, because of the wheat seeds,
he's been torn between me and Mr. Wei.
I don't want him
caught between his mother
and his wife.
What happened with the seeds
was my fault.
Zhonglin hasn't
come to see me since.
He must still resent me.
Indeed, he's angry about it.
But it wasn't you
who steamed the seeds.
You confessed
out of care about His Lordship.
It shows you've changed.
You truly care for him now.
He cares for you, too.
He's not good with words,
so he asked me
to visit you.
Really?
Is that truly what Zhonglin thinks?
Even if he doesn't blame me,
Mother
will surely do.
This punishment
is harsher than usual.
I don't know how long
it'll take to finish copying.
Mother, please don't worry.
This time,
it's different.
The punishment is for outsiders to see.
Once you're done kneeling,
you and Grandmother
will truly be family.
(Danjun, Bianzhou)
Xiang.
Xiang!
Xiang...
Xiang.
You've held on long in illness.
That's not easy.
Now,
you may rest.
My Lord,
Bianzhou can't go a day without a leader.
Please take up the role of Governor.
From now on,
Uncle will watch over Bianzhou for you.
I heard
you've been with my father
since you were young.
So, you must have
known my mother as well.
Yes.
Let me ask you something.
How did
my mother
and father first meet?
Say it.
His Lordship and Her Ladyship...
They were deeply in love.
Deeply in love?
Young Master.
You're still lying.
My mother was abducted
and violated by Chen Pang.
She died because of him.
Isn't that the truth?
Do you think
you'd still be alive if I move
this dagger just a little closer?
Go back and tell him,
I'll burn everything
he ever gave me.
And
he's not my father. He is my enemy.
If I see him on the battlefield,
I'll take his life.
Chen Lie sent word.
The heir refused
to return to Bianzhou.
That's fine.
Let him have some fun in Wei for now.
I rule Bianzhou now.
The power is in my hands.
Sooner or later, he'll come back.
My Lord, you're far-sighted.
The heir will understand one day.
What about Lady Su?
She should be arriving in Danjun soon.
What's wrong?
She escaped?
Her nephew
is troublesome.
But our guards are searching thoroughly.
Please rest assured.
The peony huadian on her forehead
makes her easy to spot.
She won't get far.
She's too well known
to fall into the wrong hands.
It'll only make her bolder.
Pass down my command.
My nephew's dying wish
was for Lady Su to remain chaste.
Find her at all costs.
Confine her in the Yulou Pavilion
as a tribute to their bond
as husband and wife.
Yes.
Thank you for visiting, Sir.
We are from the same clan.
No need to say that.
Lady Qiao.
Mr. Wei.
This courtyard is usually so quiet.
But ever since
Grandmother fell ill,
people keep coming to visit.
Lady Xu had always been in good health.
This illness was brought on by the Qiaos.
Are you Qiaos here
just to curse the Wei family?
She had nothing to do with the wheat seeds.
Sir,
please don't twist the truth.
She's innocent.
She's innocent?
Since when the Qiaos are innocent?
You know what?
Fourteen years ago...
Let the past rest.
True,
the Qiaos betrayed us 14 years ago,
but it had nothing to do with her.
Besides,
she is now a daughter-in-law of this family,
the Lady of Wei.
Sir,
would you turn against your own?
You are all being fooled by the Qiaos.
Thank you for standing up for me.
You're welcome.
Would I ever side with some bitter old man
to bully a defenseless lady?
My Lord,
these wheat seeds from Yanzhou
arrived so quickly.
We should thank Her Ladyship.
But she always looks out for the Qiaos.
Now that the wheat seeds are here,
it's time to begin digging
the canal to Rongjun.
Do you have a plan, My Lord?
- Wei Xiao.
- Yes.
Go to Panyi,
pick up Yang Feng,
and escort him to Rongjun.
Yes.
But he is
a former officer of Qiao Gui,
known for two-faced loyalty.
We can't let him run
the whole canal construction.
We must stay cautious.
Yes.
Fourteen years ago,
Panyi and Xindu built
the Yongning Canal together.
Now, we have
Yang Feng working with us.
If we could add one of our own,
wouldn't that be better?
Wei Xiao, when you
pass through Xindu,
deliver a letter to Zhen Zhi.
Tell him to take office in Rongjun.
Yes.
But I'm still worried about it.
Rongjun is far from Yujun,
and it borders Bianzhou.
It's always been difficult to govern.
The current prefect, Yuan Wang,
has strong local support
and close ties to Wei Dian.
They're discussing marriage alliance.
In my view,
we need someone with more influence.
I'll go myself.
Delivering wheat seeds is the pretext.
It'll demonstrate your authority,
secure the canal construction,
and put pressure on Wei Dian and Yuan Wang.
That would be perfect.
Besides, this can't be delayed.
I'll depart in two days.
(Bianzhou Border, Bianzhou)
Ehuang,
soon after we went to Wei,
the Lord grew weaker by the day.
Soon...
Soon after,
he...
He what?
He passed away.
My empress's fate...
He was too weak to bear it.
He couldn't even wait...
He didn't live to see
his foster child.
Who's in charge now?
Chen Pang.
He still got his way.
Things have changed in Bianzhou.
Chen Pang
has ordered a citywide search for you.
They're looking for a woman with a huadian.
He's declared that you'll be imprisoned
for life in the Yulou Pavilion.
Shameless!
My husband isn't even cold yet,
and he dares to
covet my empress's fate.
But this wasn't
Chen Pang's idea.
It was the Lord's last wish.
What?
He feared that
your empress's fate might
bring danger to Bianzhou.
So, before he died,
he instructed Chen Pang
to confine you in the Yulou Pavilion
until your final days.
I know his decision
truly broke your heart.
But please, take care of yourself.
We both married for politics.
Lady Qiao found true love,
while I ended up in a cage
built by Chen Xiang.
Don't let this weigh on you, Ehuang.
There's no true love greater
than political interest.
If I had
a family like Lady Qiao's,
I wouldn't be in this position.
Ehuang,
now isn't the time to dwell on this.
Let's figure out how to get out of here.
Who would've thought that
my empress's fate became a curse?
This board
is set.
I won't surrender.
We can't count on anyone in Danjun.
Take me
out of the city, alone.
Then we'll make a plan.
Ehuang,
Chen Pang's men are everywhere.
How am I supposed to get you out?
Find a woman with a huadian on her forehead!
- Yes.
- Stop right there.
- Stop!
Officer, what's wrong?
Don't arrest me.
Keep searching.
Yes.
Ehuang,
those are Chen Pang's men.
Ehuang?
Aren't they looking for
a woman with a huadian?
Now,
I don't have it anymore.
The canal reaches Rongjun.
Planting winter wheat there
could make Rongjun
the largest grain supplier for Wei.
So, this journey is crucial.
I must go there myself.
Rongjun has always been
aligned with Wei Dian,
yet he continues to provoke us
and challenge your authority.
Use this opportunity
to put him in his place.
Yes.
That's what I'm thinking too.
Then you'd best set out soon.
Alright.
Zhonglin,
stay and chat with Grandmother a bit longer.
I'll go tell them to prepare the meal.
Yan, wait.
There's something
I want to ask of you.
You don't have to be so formal with me.
But you know what I'm like.
Fun, I can handle. Business? Not so much.
I'll be away in Rongjun for a while,
but someone has to keep an eye on Yujun.
You're here,
so help me watch over it.
I'm hungry.
Since Zhonglin entrusted you,
just give him a hand.
You'll be by my side anyway.
There's nothing to worry about.
Yan,
may I ask for your help?
I'll do my best.
I won't let you down.
Go have the meal prepared.
We'll dine at my place tonight.
Yes.
Zhonglin,
this time, Shiyuan and I
were able to make peace
all thanks to Lady Qiao,
who stepped in to mediate.
You knew that, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Lady Qiao
is a thoughtful, well-mannered young woman.
You flatter her, Grandmother.
Zhonglin.
Some things
are better left in the past.
I hope that on this journey to Rongjun,
you will finally be able to
let go of what's behind you.
You know what?
I've sent Wei Xiao
to Panyi.
He's bringing Yang Feng to Rongjun.
Since you trust him,
I'll write him a letter
to remind him not to be careless.
No need.
Stay seated.
I need to make this clear.
Even though I know Yang Feng
cares about Yanzhou,
I'm still choosing to use him.
It's entirely my decision,
so there's no need to
thank the advisor.
I know.
You trust me,
so I should write to him
to make sure he doesn't let you down.
You don't have to do that.
I will go there myself.
Let's eat.
My Lord, you've spent years
traveling far and wide.
You must've seen all kinds of scenery.
Sadly, I'm not.
I came to Yujun from Kangjun when I married.
That's the only journey I've ever taken.
So I wanted to go out and see the world,
just like you.
See the place where you grew up.
Yujun is
where I grew up.
I heard Rongjun is mountainous,
so different from the waterways of Yanzhou.
I've always wanted to see it for myself.
Do you want
to come with me?
I can take care of your meals
and daily needs.
You don't need to worry about that.
Tan can handle everything.
This isn't the kind of trip
I can bring you on.
It's all work.
But winter wheat
requires special planting methods.
Seeds alone won't grow
if you don't plant them right.
What do you mean?
I could teach the farm officers,
and they could pass it on to the people.
But I'm afraid
some things might
get lost in between.
If the harvest fails next year,
it could cause serious trouble.
Or, do you just
not trust me,
My Lord?
It's not about trust.
It's just that
this journey will be dangerous.
I don't mind.
You will protect me, won't you?
Alright then.
Well,
go get packed.
We leave the day after tomorrow.
Okay.
There's nothing special about planting wheat.
Yeah.
There's really nothing special here.
Could it be
that Her Ladyship just wants to
keep you company?
No way. Absolutely not.
Her Ladyship
is smart and always puts the people first.
She takes her duties seriously.
Maybe
she really does have
a unique method she can't share openly.
Or maybe
she just really cares and wants
to see it through.
That must be it.
Fine.
I'll take her with me
on this trip.
Fine.
(Hope to meet again in Rongjun.
Wishing you well.)
My Lady, you really
do care about His Lordship.
But My Lady,
why do we have to go
with His Lordship?
Silly girl.
(Wei Mansion, Wei State)
My Lord,
the troops have been counted,
and the grain carts are on their way.
When are we heading out?
Give it a moment.
Yes, My Lord.
Told her not to come, but she insisted.
Such a hassle.
This one's ugly. Give me another one.
But it looks good.
Where's the green one?
Here it is.
His Lordship said
it looked good on me last time.
And that jingling hairpin.
- This one?
- Yes, that one.
Who said it looked good?
Wearing a
jingling hairpin in the carriage
would be so annoying.
My Lord, I'll go hurry her.
Give it a moment.
It's natural for a young lady
to dress up.
No need to rush.
My Lord,
I have a little idea
about this journey.
How about we
take a detour this time?
My Lord?
Take a detour?
We'll talk about it later.
Yes.
My Lady.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's go.
The way His Lordship looks at you today
is different.
Yan.
Grandmother's worried you might feel
lonely on the trip,
so she asked me to see you off.
After all, I've got nothing better to do.
I'm just a lonely man.
Then marry early
if you're lonely.
Spare me, please.
It's a long trip ahead.
Mr. Gongsun,
Yan, please
keep an eye on Yujun.
Just leave it to us.
You focus on taking care of your wife.
Lady Qiao,
with your beauty, even if
you were thin and worn out,
you'd still shine.
Remember to eat more, okay?
Don't go using your
flirting tricks on the tavern girls
of your own family.
Let's go!
Go!
Giddy-up!
(Wei Mansion)
This way, please.
After you, Mr. Wei.
It's windy. Close the window.
He's so bossy.
His Lordship just doesn't get
Her Ladyship good intentions.
It's alright.
After this, he'll understand.
Xiaotao? Xiaotao!
Xiaotao!
- What's up?
- The road is rough.
If Her Ladyship's not feeling well,
tell me at once.
We can stop anytime.
No worries, Her Ladyship is fine.
Are you okay? Need anything?
Something to eat or drink?
Just say the word.
Me?
Just do your job.
Xiaotao?
Back then,
when we were heading to Yujun,
they rushed like crazy
and didn't care about Her Ladyship.
But now,
they're much more
considerate of Her Ladyship.
Exactly, My Lady.
Do you need anything to eat or any supplies?
Get me some water.
Here you are.
Here.
Come here. Sit.
This is rough fare. You can't eat it.
You can,
why can't I?
If you like it,
have another one.
Here.
Want some water?
It's good.
I told you
this journey wouldn't be easy.
Told you not to come, but you insisted.
So what?
To see what you've seen,
walk where you've walked,
and stand by your side,
that's all been worth it.
The view's nice here.
Enjoy.
Still, there's one thing I can't figure out.
Even though Rongjun
is suffering from drought,
does delivering wheat seeds
really require you to go in person?
You've always made wise decisions.
Could you tell me why?
You don't always get it, huh?
I guess I was just
trying to be a bit clever before,
but mostly it was dumb luck.
My Lord, you've ruled Wei for years.
There's no way I can compare,
just a woman who's only read a few books.
If you don't tell me,
I might never get it.
Alright.
Since you want to know,
I'll tell you.
Bring me the panorama.
Come on.
Give it to me.
Take a look.
Rongjun's east of Yujun
(Liangya, Panyi, Wei State, Bianzhou)
and
borders Bianzhou.
Fifty years ago,
Rongjun wasn't part of Wei State.
When my great-grandfather ruled Wei State...
Those who surrendered after persuasion
were countless…
Why are you looking at me?
Look at the panorama.
The land rises and falls,
but it's nothing like your strong features.
The mountains and rivers are lovely,
but they still can't match your spirit.
You're weird today.
Look at the panorama.
If you want to know why, stay focused.
The prefect of Rongjun
is nearly fifty,
born into
a noble local family.
However,
the canal construction
and farming
take a lot of manpower.
It could weaken his future standing.
He may not go for it.
That makes things tricky.
Yes, it does.
When the time comes,
we'll still need a proper plan
to persuade him.
Xiaotao.
Let me tell you something.
What is it?
There's a great place nearby.
The delicacies there
are absolutely delicious.
If only we can go and eat there.
How do you know that?
A good buddy of mine
gave me a guide.
The guide says it.
Don't you also wish
the Lord and the Lady
could grow a little closer?
Of course.
Look at them now.
It's so awkward.
The guide says
if we follow it on this journey,
their relationship
will definitely improve.
♪The moonlight is as silent
as the deep sea♪
♪From afar♪
♪It once lit up dreams with a breath♪
♪But vanished with a sigh♪
♪Brushing past my fingertips♪
♪My heartstrings were stirred quietly♪
♪As if we once met before♪
♪Holding back a love so deep♪
♪Love asks for nothing in the end♪
♪Leaving only obsessions♪
♪I've wandered in the world♪
♪Yet cannot have it all♪
♪We meet and part in the fires of war♪
♪Embracing,
leaving tender marks of love♪
♪With one breathtaking glance♪
♪How could I ever forget♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪