♪If not for you♪
♪I wouldn't have wanted
to make a name for myself♪
♪Only when I have your love♪
♪Is my invincibility not in vain♪
♪The towering peaks I've conquered♪
♪Leave me♪
♪Feeling empty♪
♪I've given everything♪
♪Just to follow you♪
♪Through life and death♪
♪Could it be that love♪
♪Is the true end of this life♪
♪Why does every battle♪
♪Bring deeper pain♪
♪I never got it♪
♪You once promised me♪
♪You'd give me ordinary days♪
♪Then I'd rather♪
♪Face blades and fall♪
♪Into your arms instead of the clouds♪
♪I'll pass through layers of fog♪
♪And barriers♪
♪The world's rights and wrongs,
wins and losses♪
♪Who's to weigh their worth♪
♪Only love♪
♪Gives me a sky as wide as the sea♪
♪I only want to be your hero♪
=The Prisoner of Beauty=
=Episode 14=
There is Lady Yulou.
So noble.
(Yujun)
- Lady Yulou.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is my cousin, Su Xin,
whose style name is Zixin.
These are generals Wei Liang and Wei Qu.
Say hi to both generals.
Nice to meet you.
To make it in time
for Great-aunt's 60th birthday,
I came in a hurry
lest I might cause trouble.
I didn't expect
the Lord of Wei to send you two
to receive me outside the city.
I don't deserve this.
Lady Yulou,
you're too kind.
It's getting late.
Let me escort you into the city.
What a beautiful carriage.
Who's inside?
That's Lady Yulou's carriage.
The legendary Lady Yulou?
The one with the peony mark?
Lady Su of Wushan.
Her fate is exceptional.
She was born noble.
No wonder the generals
came to welcome her.
She really is a belle.
So beautiful.
They try to imitate you,
but they can never succeed.
So many believe in fate,
but how many understand
that nothing comes easily
in this world?
Even gifts from heaven
require one's own effort.
What I have today
was not easily earned.
The foolish believe
that they can obtain
your empress's fate
by wearing a huadian.
But they don't know
that fate is hard to change.
You've borne the destiny
of the Su Clan of Wushan
since childhood.
Guided by great scholars,
your vision is extraordinary.
How could common women ever compare?
That's not entirely fair.
If I fail to break the Qiao-Wei alliance
on this trip,
then in my husband's eyes,
I'm no different
from those common women.
Is this the place
the Lord of Wei
has arranged for us to stay?
Yes.
This is the best post house in Yujun.
(Yujun Post House, Wei State)
Lady Yulou,
are you dissatisfied?
Not at all.
This place,
peaceful amidst the bustle,
is just what I wanted.
The Lord of Wei is thoughtful.
Lady Xu said you've had a long journey
and may rest here first.
No need to rush to the mansion.
This...
Didn't you say the Lord of Wei
would have us stay at the mansion?
Why is it the post house instead?
It must be Lady Qiao's idea.
Gorgeous huadian!
Once you put it on,
you'll meet a man in one day
(Rouge)
get married in three days,
and find a devoted man in ten days.
Gentlemen,
buy one for the lady at home.
This is the hottest trend
in Yujun right now.
I don't need that to win a girl's heart.
Let's go.
Give me
- the most popular one.
- Sure.
- How much?
- Three wen.
Do you really believe
what that seller says?
Xiaotao surely doesn't want
something like that.
She won't like it.
Don't talk nonsense.
It's not for Xiaotao.
Can't I wear it myself?
What's wrong, Duang?
Here, take this.
This...
Why do you have one too?
Girls in Yujun now
love this huadian.
After I escorted Lady Yulou,
I picked one up for you on my way back.
Why do girls like
this kind of thing now?
Who says we do?
Whoever wants this cheap stuff
can have it.
Alright, alright.
Don't pick it up.
Okay, I won't.
I get it. You don't want it.
Why are you angry?
What do you know?
Let me ask you something.
Answer me honestly.
I heard Lady Yulou
was almost betrothed to the Wei family.
Is it true?
Yes.
Does she like it
or not?
My Lady,
Lady Yulou has come to pay her respects.
Let her in.
- Yes.
- Ask Lady Zhu
to come and meet our guest.
Yes.
Grandmother, you have a guest.
I'll take my leave.
You stay.
It's fine.
By seniority,
she should call me
Great-aunt.
When she was young,
we were very close.
Sure.
Greetings,
Great-aunt.
Get up.
Take a seat.
Thank you, Great-aunt.
I heard your husband is gravely ill.
I'm only celebrating a birthday,
yet you came all this way.
Great-aunt,
though I am
the Lady of Bianzhou,
I'm bound by many constraints,
walking on thin ice.
I often recall my childhood
when you were always
so kind to me.
This year, I missed you too much,
so I came in haste.
I only hope
I haven't disturbed your peace.
If you're here to unwind,
then stay and relax.
Thank you, Great-aunt.
This is Lady Qiao,
Zhonglin's wife.
She's excellent
at managing the household.
I've long heard
the Lady of Wei
is as radiant as the sun.
Now that I've met you,
you're truly captivating.
I was caught up
chatting with Great-aunt.
Sorry for neglecting you.
Please
accept my apology.
I hope we can
spend more time together
so today's meeting won't be in vain.
You're too kind, Lady Yulou.
I feel the same.
No need to be so formal.
I grew up with the Lord of Wei.
You can just call me Ehuang.
You're now
the Lady of Bianzhou.
I'm still young.
I dare not lose decorum.
It's only proper to address you
as Lady Yulou.
You're a Qiao,
even more noble than I am.
Lord Qiao's reputation for benevolence
is known throughout the land.
I spoke out of turn.
Great-aunt, please forgive me.
My Lady,
Lady Zhu is here.
Greetings, Mother.
Ehuang,
long time no see.
You look more and more blessed.
As expected of the Lady of Bianzhou.
You flatter me.
Since we parted ways in Yujun,
I didn't expect
to only see you again now.
You always treated me
like your daughter.
In Bianzhou,
I often thought back
and couldn't help but weep.
Back then, I had no choice.
Look at me,
chatting on and almost forgetting
the main reason I came.
Great-aunt,
I heard Rongjun is suffering famine
so I brought some grain
along with me
as a gift for your birthday.
I hope
you won't find it unworthy.
Grain
is no trivial matter.
This must be decided
by Zhonglin.
He'll accept it.
They grew up together
after all.
Ehuang,
you're so thoughtful toward Zhonglin.
How touching.
This is what family means.
Enough with the chatter.
Grandmother, you must be tired.
I'll take my leave
and serve you another day.
You're thoughtful.
Everyone
should go rest now.
Yes.
My Lady,
Lady Yulou looks
much fuller than before.
Yet she claimed
she was constrained and had a hard time
in Bianzhou.
She used
to care for the Lord
meticulously.
I once thought she had feelings for him.
Who would've thought
she'd marry the Lord of Bianzhou
just a couple of years
after the Xindu incident?
She was planning for her future.
Nothing's wrong with that.
I guess she and I
just weren't fated.
I find
the Lady of Wei
quite clever and capable.
You've worked hard for years.
You can finally enjoy some peace.
Peace?
That's not in my fate.
I only hope Lady Qiao
lets me
live a quiet life.
Why do you say that?
Just now,
I saw how much Great-aunt
favored her.
I thought...
If you saw it in one day,
you can imagine
how things usually are for me.
Mother is always overbearing.
Lady Qiao acts all delicate.
She even fooled Zhonglin
into driving Chuyu
out of the house.
Now,
the two of them stand united.
I'm the only outsider left
in this home.
Why doesn't Zhonglin
speak up for you?
He's busy.
He was fixing the Yongning Canal,
and now he's working
on the canal for Rongjun.
I can't help with those things.
I just try not to add to his burden.
Only a mother
thinks this way for her son.
No one else would.
That's true.
You understand me best.
If only you could stay longer this time,
so we could have
a proper talk.
You just said the Lord of Wei
was working on the canal for Rongjun.
Didn't the canal for Xindu and Panyi
just get completed?
Why the rush to divert water to Rongjun?
Are there some problems?
Maybe I can help.
I heard Rongjun suffered from drought.
Yanzhou
is sending wheat seeds,
so they need the canal.
What can we women do
about these things?
I once suggested to Lady Yulou
that she meet you at the office,
but she insisted
on coming here.
It's fine.
Lady Yulou.
Long time no see.
You're now the Lord of Wei.
Do you remember?
Back then, we and Bogong
used to play in this very courtyard.
How carefree and happy.
After so many years,
this place has fallen into dilapidation,
yet standing here
feels like just yesterday.
Yes.
It truly does.
Though I was born in Wushan,
my happiest childhood days
were spent with you guys.
Now returning to Wei
feels almost like coming home.
Indeed,
Wei can be considered
your second home.
The day I arrived at the mansion,
I learned the Lady of Wei
has been taking care of Great-aunt
and managing the household meticulously.
Lady Qiao
is gentle and considerate,
kind and wise.
She must've given so much.
Yes.
She has worked hard.
More than just hard.
It pains me to think of it.
I heard
Lady Qiao was much loved at home,
never having to worry about anything.
Yet she's here now,
handling so much.
Zhonglin,
here's a piece of advice.
Managing the household is hard enough.
Don't let Lady Qiao worry
about the grudges
and political affairs
between the Qiaos and Weis anymore.
(Birthday Banquet Guest List)
I keep wondering these days:
Why did Lady Yulou
suddenly show up
after all these years of absence?
Could you explain further?
She came with grain.
She must have a purpose.
I've already asked Uncle for seeds.
If the Lord
accepts her grain now,
it'll be a shame to Yanzhou.
I know Rongjun is in drought,
and Yanzhou offering seeds
was Lady Qiao's way
of easing the tension
between the two clans.
Still, we can't rule out
the ill intent
of the Qiao Clan.
This time I came
not just to celebrate
Great-aunt's birthday
but also to do my part
to help Wei.
I brought grain
to aid Rongjun
through the drought.
This batch of grain
is not from Wushan
or Bianzhou.
It's simply a gift from me personally.
Please don't feel pressured.
If Yanzhou and Wei join hands
to open the canal in Rongjun,
they'll be
surrounding Bianzhou.
How can Bianzhou stand by and watch?
That's why Chen Xiang
sent Lady Yulou as a mediator
to stop Wei
from building the canal in Rongjun.
Canal work is Wei's state affair.
Now that you are
the Lady of Bianzhou,
it's no longer appropriate
for us to discuss politics.
So, I can't accept
your grain.
Rongjun's drought
has drawn support from many prefectures.
Besides,
I can't betray
the Qiao-Wei alliance.
Yes.
I didn't consider it thoroughly.
I'll take my leave.
Zhonglin.
Wei Liang
humiliated me
with such a cheap gift.
Stop laughing.
My Lady,
Lady Yulou and the Lord
were almost betrothed.
So what?
So what? Well...
We just got rid of Zheng Shu,
and now Lady Yulou shows up.
How are you supposed to live in peace?
If I spend every day
dwelling on his old flings,
then life will truly become unlivable.
Anyway,
I heard that Lady Yulou
asked to see the Lord.
Who knows what it'll be like
when old lovers reunite?
After Bogong passed,
I married the Lord of Bianzhou.
Do you still resent me for it?
I was just a girl back then.
It wasn't what I wanted.
I was forced into it.
Let's not speak of the past anymore.
Now,
I only wish you
endless good fortune.
My Lord.
Oh, you like this kind of thing?
Then
I'll take you to the streets later
and buy you more in other styles.
You're busy with affairs of state.
How could I trouble you
with my concerns?
Besides,
I've hated
flashy things like this
since I was a child.
Help the Lord change.
No need.
You may leave.
- Yes.
What happened?
The Lord of Wei rejected
free grain?
He's distancing himself from me
because I'm the Lady of Bianzhou.
The Qiao Clan of Yanzhou
sent wheat seeds to celebrate
(Qiao)
Lady Xu's birthday.
(Grain)
If the Lord of Wei is wary of you,
Ehuang,
how will you make your next move?
If I can't act freely,
then Lady Qiao,
as the daughter of his enemy,
is in an even worse position.
The Lord of Wei remembers the past
and holds grudges.
When my betrothal was on the table,
if the Qiao Clan
hadn't broken their word,
and if tragedy hadn't struck the Weis,
Bogong wouldn't have...
The Su Clan wouldn't have sent me
to Bianzhou.
I've never forgotten that grudge.
The Lord of Wei wouldn't forget either.
In that case,
Ehuang,
what should we do now?
The canal is for the seeds,
and the Lord of Wei rejected my grain
because of the seeds.
If something happens to the seeds...
Don't forget.
We still have one hidden piece to play.
(Granary, Qiao)
(Grain)
Then I'll trouble you, Mr. Wei.
There's no need for such formality.
I should be the one
thanking Yanzhou for aiding Rongjun.
It's what we should do.
Mr. Wei, the wheat has been weighed.
Please take a look.
Make sure it's well-guarded.
Yes.
As expected of someone from Wei Mansion.
If she had better clothes,
her bearing and looks
would match any noble lady.
What a pity.
To help you, I must do this.
I didn't mean to offend you.
I'm new to Yujun
and not yet familiar with the area.
May I ask you
for directions?
Where do you want to go?
Do you know the way
to Wei Mansion?
Wei Mansion?
You're going to see the Lord of Wei?
Yes.
Who are you?
Ma'am,
this gentleman is
the young master
of the Su Clan from Wushan.
He came to offer birthday wishes
to Lady Xu.
Oh, you're a noble guest.
I'm Su Xin.
My style name is Zixin.
You look so lovely.
Which heartless husband
would let you
labor out here alone?
The route to the mansion isn't far,
but it is a bit tricky.
If you don't mind,
I'll go home and get changed
and then guide you there.
I would
love that.
Here.
Take this umbrella.
Thank you, sir.
Ehuang,
I've got her.
Chuyu was beaten by her in-laws?
Hurry and bring her here.
I need to ask about it.
But Lady Xu said
she wasn't allowed in the house.
Bring her to the outer courtyard.
Just don't let Lady Xu find out.
You...
I'm going now.
Where
is Mother going so early?
My Lady.
The guest list is ready.
No need to consult Lady Zhu.
My Lady.
Here are ritual records
of birthday banquets in Yujun,
family genealogy, guest list records,
and family gathering records.
They're all for your reference.
Thank you.
Can I take these back with me?
Of course.
But there's no need to carry them.
The Lord said you could use the study.
If you need any books or records,
just ask me.
The Lord prepared these?
Yes.
(Guest List)
What does the Lord mean?
Maybe he's afraid I'll ruin the banquet
and embarrass him.
Or maybe he genuinely
cares about you.
Chuyu.
Let me look.
Aunt,
please save me.
Come on, get up.
What happened to your face?
Get up now.
They accused me of being indecent
with another man
but the truth is that gambler
squandered my dowry
and wanted more money from you.
Aunt,
the marriage Lady Xu arranged for me
has put me in great misery.
My life hasn't been easy either.
If it weren't for Lady Qiao,
you would've had everything you wanted.
It looks like
to make this work,
we need Lady Qiao to slip up
so you can have the upper hand.
Mother supports her now.
What can I do?
There
might be a way,
but it depends on you.
(Granary)
Greetings, Mr. Wei.
Anything unusual in the granary today?
All is as usual.
Please rest assured.
(Granary)
Ehuang, it's done.
A grand birthday celebration
needs to be livelier.
I heard
Lady Yulou is gifted in music.
Would I
be lucky enough
to enjoy a performance today?
The Lord of Wei has heard me sing.
You may ask him.
Shiyuan,
Lady Yulou is noble now.
She's no longer someone
you can joke with like before.
I only hope
her singing can entertain you
on this special day.
How do you plan
to entertain me yourself?
Shiyuan,
why not perform a sword dance?
I can sing along.
What do you think?
That'll be wonderful.
It'll be great.
Sounds good.
♪The graceful grass♪
♪Stands alone yet captivating♪
♪My longing for it♪
♪Twists into the night♪
♪The graceful grass♪
♪Carries my distant yearning♪
♪My honest husband♪
♪Truly worries me♪
Bravo!
How beautiful!
Beautiful!
Mr. Wei is truly charming.
You're hiding such talent.
If you were on the battlefield,
you'd be a mighty warrior for sure.
Indeed.
Your voice is like that of a goddess.
Thank you, Great-aunt.
Grandmother,
may you
live long with endless blessings
and everlasting health
and peace.
Mother, you must be
in high spirits today.
Shiyuan performed.
Lady Qiao gave a thoughtful gift.
I heard Yanzhou
also sent a generous gift.
Grandmother has seen it.
Yanzhou sent winter wheat seeds.
Just seeds?
Winter wheat is the foundation
of Yanzhou's prosperity.
Giving this
shows great sincerity.
It's the best birthday gift
I could receive.
It's just winter wheat.
Is it really that special?
You didn't seem interested
in this before.
Zhonglin, what are you doing?
I...
Want to use the restroom?
Go on then.
This child...
Mother, I mean no offense.
I'm just curious.
Since we're all here,
why not have Lady Qiao
bring out the seeds
for everyone to see?
Right?
- Yes.
- Great.
Let's see them.
We want to see
what winter wheat is like.
Grandmother.
Mother.
These are the wheat seeds from Yanzhou.
Please have a look.
This winter wheat
is an improved strain.
It's planted in the autumn equinox
and harvested in the fifth month
of the next year.
It's perfect for easing food shortages
in early summer.
But winter wheat
has always been exclusive to Yanzhou.
Yanzhou produces and sells them,
but it never gives away seeds.
This time,
on Grandmother's birthday,
Yanzhou shares them
in hopes
of standing together with Wei
through thick and thin.
What's that smell?
Could it
be mold?
Yes.
How dare you!
I want to ask you today.
What exactly is your family up to?
Fourteen years ago,
you broke your word
on the battlefield
and caused enough misery to our family.
How dare you present
these rotten seeds as a gift?
Take them away!
Mother,
I personally inspected
these seeds.
Every single one was carefully selected.
This concerns an alliance
between our families
and the lives of our people.
The Qiao Clan would never
treat it lightly.
From what I see,
each grain is full and intact.
They're not rotten.
Though the seeds
aren't rotten,
they're floating.
They're cooked!
Cooked!
How could they be cooked?
They're truly cooked.
Cooked seeds.
How can cooked seeds be planted?
Let me see.
It's hard to tell if they're raw seeds.
If the people plant them
and they don't sprout,
they'll blame themselves
for not tending the fields properly.
Then they'll miss the planting season,
and the famine will be even worse
than this year.
People live on food.
Everyone, they must hate us deeply.
Exactly.
What were they thinking?
The seeds that won't grow.
What a malicious scheme.
It looks like Yanzhou's seeds are here
to cause havoc.
We demand an explanation today.
What's going on?
The seeds are the foundation of a state.
We need an explanation.
Everyone says
Yanzhou's seeds are the best.
If they send us duds,
the farmers will suffer.
If the seeds are steamed and dried,
it'll be hard to tell if they're cooked
without careful examination.
We can test them
to find out.
Look. Some are floating.
Look, look.
They're cooked.
That's right.
They're all cooked.
The seeds are all cooked.
That can't be.
My Lady,
I swear I didn't know.
Grandmother.
Everyone.
My uncle may be foolish,
but this is serious.
He would never risk
the lives of Wei's people.
There must be a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding?
Good thing there's no war now.
Grain is extremely important in wars.
How would we feed the soldiers
and the people without grain?
The Qiao Clan
- is so vile.
- Indeed.
There will be famine every year.
My Lady, what should we do?
Shall I go beg the Lord?
He might not help us.
It's a plot against our people.
We must get to the bottom of this today.
We demand an explanation.
We need an answer.
The Lady has always been cautious here
just like me.
How can you gang up on a woman?
How can a lady of inner chambers
get involved
in political affairs?
In my opinion,
it was Qiao Yue who did this.
Grandmother,
perhaps someone plotted to frame us.
Please look into it fairly.
Look into it?
The truth is right before us.
Stop trying to deny it.
They might not be seeds from Yanzhou.
They're definitely from Yanzhou.
- Stop denying it.
- Exactly.
Yanzhou's envoy presented them.
They must be from Yanzhou.
How wicked.
You try to use steamed seeds
to fool the people.
What are you up to?
This is Grandmother's birthday banquet,
not a place for shouting.
Silence!
Shao, they're all cooked.
I already know.
In that case,
punish the Lady now.
At Grandmother's birthday banquet,
what a surprise to see a mystery
instead of a puppet show.
Clearly,
someone wanted to disgrace our family.
What mystery?
Lady Qiao clearly plotted this.
With bad seeds,
she wants our people to starve.
She ignores the people's suffering.
She's pure evil.
Why are you laughing?
I'm laughing
because I'd believe you
if you told me Lady Qiao wanted
to poison my whole family,
but I'd never believe
she'd harm the people.
Get up.
Grandmother,
back in Xindu,
Lady Qiao risked her reputation
to help me win back the people's trust.
The people of Xindu
volunteered for labor.
Then in Panyi,
she risked her life
to fight off the Liangya army
with me.
Afterward,
using her identity as a Qiao,
she persuaded local experts
to help repair the canal.
The Yongning Canal
revived after 14 years
because of her.
All of you here
drink from your cups
yet forget who made it possible.
♪Sing a song of longing♪
If she wants to harm the people,
she doesn't need to go this far.
She just needs to refuse to help me
with the canal.
So,
this must be a setup.
♪The memories can't be retrieved♪
♪I went through a lot
just to understand you♪
♪White wings♪
♪Fall into my hands♪
Before entering Yujun,
the seeds must've been weighed.
Dried seeds
are lighter than the raw ones.
So if there was a switch,
we'd know by weighing.
Guards!
- Yes!
Weigh the seeds.
The Lady and the Lord are of one heart.
She wouldn't betray him.
If the seeds weren't tampered with
before storage,
then the problem lies after.
May I ask
who manages the granary?
Could it be
someone else is plotting
against the Lord?
According to Lady Yulou,
if it wasn't
Lady Qiao,
then it must be Wei Yan.
How interesting.
My Lord.
Should we continue weighing?
Shao,
if neither Lady Qiao
nor Wei Yan is behind this,
you owe us
an explanation.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
- We must have an answer.
How can our people be treated this way?
My Lord,
one is your wife,
and the other is your cousin.
Who will you choose?
Mr. Wei is just the Lord's cousin,
not his real brother.
You mustn't show favoritism.
♪The moonlight is as silent
as the deep sea♪
♪From afar♪
♪It once lit up dreams with a breath♪
♪But vanished with a sigh♪
♪Brushing past my fingertips♪
♪My heartstrings were stirred quietly♪
♪As if we once met before♪
♪Holding back a love so deep♪
♪Love asks for nothing in the end♪
♪Leaving only obsessions♪
♪I've wandered in the world♪
♪Yet cannot have it all♪
♪We meet and part in the fires of war♪
♪Embracing,
leaving tender marks of love♪
♪With one breathtaking glance♪
♪How could I ever forget♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪
♪I would cross mountains and seas♪
♪To spend time with you♪
♪When we grow old♪
♪Nothing will change♪
♪The misty rains never cease♪
♪Falling gently on your brow♪
♪Lingering in my heart♪
♪I would sever fate's ties♪
♪To protect your smiling eyes♪
♪Even if behind me lies a storm♪
♪No matter the trials♪
♪I carry this longing for the journey♪
♪This life♪
♪Will not be in vain♪