Beat spirit
I will be with you forever.
Is love the only thing that can last me for the rest of my life?
Why do I feel more and more pained when I'm fighting?
I didn't get your ordinary care.
If you don't get my ordinary care,
I will be afraid.
play Zhao Yongqi in Detective Conan when in FUKIAN
and also play the role of X sweets
if you get it right this time
i'm gonna forget everything
if you can restaurant
you can learn the life of being a self-study
framework
the people
My mockery
because when you lost all your research
you all thought you were brave
Mr. Gra propriety
Every time in a battle
I'll take these
castaxia
we would leave these weapons behind.
Although we were not born on the same day,
I don't think we would die on the same day.
But in the future,
even if we four leave,
and bury these weapons together,
we will always be brothers.
So,
I want to give this to you.
What?
Why are you giving it to me?
This is my most precious thing.
At least I can give it to you.
Then,
why do you want to give it to me?
You should take care of her for me.
Seeing her
is like seeing me.
Who wants to see you?
What?
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
Let's talk.
No, no, no.
Let's go home.
What are you doing?
No, no.
Let me go.
You little...
What are you doing?
Some people say that
there is a deep blood feud with Yanzhou.
They are not on the same side.
But what happened?
They said they were willing to work for the master
and didn't want to marry.
But what happened?
Some people...
Enough.
Don't say that.
I didn't tell you about this.
It's my fault.
You can kill me or kill me.
I'll tell you.
Stop talking.
Well,
I'll give you all my belongings and money.
Is that okay?
What are you talking about?
We are brothers.
We are born to be together.
How can I take your money?
Besides, who cares about your silly things?
Get up.
Give me your little gold watch.
I'll help you.
Enough.
Between me and Xiao Tou...
Who said that?
I will never marry a woman from the Qiao family.
She doesn't believe in Qiao.
You said you wouldn't marry a woman from Yanzhou.
I...
Didn't the master marry someone else?
You are comparing with the master.
The master married someone back to Yu Jun Lai.
You want to marry yourself to Tong Jun.
Can you do that?
Good.
So you want to do the training.
What are you doing?
No.
Be gentle.
Nan Jun.
Ning Jun.
Isn't what you are holding
the thing I gave Wei Lian?
Why is it with you?
No.
Nan Jun is wrong.
Your hand...
Ning Jun.
Mr. Saifu is closing the door.
So you knew
Wei Lian likes Xiao Tao.
Just a little bit earlier than Nan Jun.
I mean...
Why would Wei Lian not
marry the daughter of the master?
What do you think?
What do I think?
If Wei Lian wants to marry Xiao Tao,
can you agree?
Xiao Tao is from the Qiao family.
Why can't I agree?
No matter who she is,
she is from the Wei family.
You are.
Nan Jun.
What?
Am I wrong?
We were suspecting each other.
Now,
you are helping me to marry her.
Let me go!
Pu Xiaohui!
Stir-fried mushrooms are ready.
Baked meat!
Oui Lian ordered them.
No awful food
could match my fattness.
I can't eat it.
We just eat it.
Unrusual, right?
Fattish?
We just eat it.
P configurations.
I can eat something completely.
Let's go.
We should change it.
We should make the Mar sings too.
Yeah.
I'll take you to the door of the wrong side
and embrace the sunset
Madam, please
What kind of jewelry do you want to choose today?
You may not know
The jewelry store is full of them
Jade hairpin
White pearl hairpin
Crispy hairpin
This time
Take care of your mother
and keep your eyes on her
You like these things?
No woman doesn't like jewelry
I'm not afraid of anything
This and this
Do you like it?
So Nanjun knows my hobby
I don't understand these
This was chosen by Wei Xu
I thought you weren't that stubborn
Why did the female army come back so soon?
Did Nanjun make the female army angry again?
I'm telling you
Don't talk to Wei Jialang again
What do you mean?
Only know how to fight
and not know how to fight
I'm telling you
Don't talk to Wei Jialang again
What do you mean?
Only know how to fight
and not know how to fight
Hmm
Where are my Garden of Youth Whenever I Come
What do you mean?
Forget it
Wei Jialang?
I can't understand
According toèsame
I've seen according to Wei Jialang
I've heard from outside
to his Miss
Eunuch Yuan
why
Wei Jialang
Didn't receive rewards for his grandfather
He didn't accept any System of War
I'm not sure.
He's thoughtful.
Yujuan, be careful.
Don't drop it.
He gave it to you.
I dare not drop it.
You promise.
No.
It's mainly from Nanjun.
I dare not drop it.
Nanjun?
Wei Liang said
each of them
has a small weapon.
Wei Qu is a pair of long and short swords.
Wei Xiao is a small bow.
Wei Duo is a small sword.
Nanjun made it
according to everyone's preference.
So it's not that Wei Jialang
doesn't know how to deliver things.
It's not that Nanjun doesn't know how to deliver things.
It's Nanjun who doesn't know how to deliver things.
I have no problem with it.
Nanjun...
Nanjun.
Wait for me.
I'm walking so fast.
Come on.
Nanjun has been a soldier for many years.
He walks very fast.
I have to walk faster
to catch up.
You don't have to.
These are all your favorite
combat weapons.
I knew it.
You must like combat weapons too.
We'll go back to the army tomorrow morning.
You should rest for a while.
I have to tell you something
before you go to bed.
I'll go now.
All these
were chosen for grandparents.
Then I'll
pick this for you.
Your advice is Sun Xiao's latest?
Works as a
Name simply.
But I have to work harder.
But you said
you would go back to Yujin tomorrow.
Why?
Doesn't Yujin want to go back?
Not that.
I don't want to leave halfway.
Go find Yang Feng.
Yes.
This one.
Sir,
such a dress should be there.
It's better to wear it when you go out.
Pill Galaxy.
What are you thinking?
驯
It looks like Because I only wanna be your superior,
and leave no guest behind.
Here,
Yue Liao.
Come.
Master.
Tell me.
Why did you give the gold watch
to someone else?
Master.
You don't agree to marry my daughter
because you like Xiaotao.
Why didn't you tell me?
I was afraid you wouldn't agree.
I was afraid you'd like it if I didn't.
I really can't control myself.
When we took over Yun Zhongjun five years ago,
you were burned to death
for the sake of the operation.
Now you're telling me you can't control yourself.
I really can't control myself.
Every time I was working in the office,
I was thinking about him all the time.
What's so fun and delicious?
I thought of him at first sight.
When he was angry,
I couldn't sleep all night.
I was happy when he was happy.
I was happy when he was sad.
I was sad when I was sad too.
I really can't control myself.
It's said that
heroes are sadder than beauties.
So you're sad too.
Master.
Love is complicated.
You don't like someone.
You don't understand.
Master.
Love is complicated.
Yes.
You're right. I don't understand.
We didn't leave.
Where's Junsheng?
I'll tell him now.
I'm sure his daughter's birthday is on me.
Don't worry.
No, no, no.
Master, you're wrong.
You're wrong.
Nanjun.
Since you've packed up,
let's go.
Everyone.
Please take care of the rest of the Yongning Qu's.
We'll do our best.
Let's go.
Oh no.
This is bad.
What's wrong?
Just tell me what's wrong.
I have a book of water
You can remember to bring yourself
It's not easy.
I shouldn't have bothered you.
But this book is related to the progress of the project.
So, please go there for me.
You're just pretending.
If you really want to help us,
how can you forget this?
Shut up.
Are you serious?
Marquis Wei.
It's okay.
It's not a big deal.
I'll send someone to send someone to get you a book.
How about Lanjun take us to go together?
That's the best.
Marquis Wei can handle this matter himself.
There will be no mistake.
Wait.
Marquis Wei is willing to go to Panye for you.
Just for a book?
Don't worry.
The process of Panye
goes along the water.
First, we can go to see
the progress of the project.
Second, we can go there alone.
And we can help the county magistrate get the crystal back.
It's a one-off.
Just as the queen said,
I dare to ask Marquis Wei to go there.
What do you think, Lanjun?
We did a lot of things in Panye last time.
I want to go back and have a look.
Okay.
Do as you want.
Let's go to Panye.
Thank you, Marquis Wei.
Let's go.
Get in the car first.
Yijuan, did you see that?
Just now, Lanjun looked at you.
His eyes were straight.
See you.
Madam.
Yuchi.
Can you hear me?
Xing, go find the doctor.
Yes.
Are you going to give my family some plum?
General asked me where I got plum two days ago.
I told him that I had it.
I didn't expect to fall at the gate.
Who knew it would fall?
It's a fall.
It's obviously a fall of the air.
It must be Xue Tai.
The mountain is at the border of the Boya.
Xue Tai is always there.
When General Lai wakes up, he'll be there.
Hurry, take him in.
Yes, hurry.
You're awake.
Fan.
Don't move.
Fan, I'm getting up.
Does your wound still hurt?
Is the plum delicious?
It's okay if it's not.
Next time, I'll get you another tree.
I haven't eaten yet.
Then try it.
Try it.
Is it not delicious?
If it's not delicious,
then I won't eat it.
Delicious?
Delicious.
I don't want to eat plum anymore.
I just want to live a good life with you.
Fan.
Aren't we living a good life?
This time, it's just an accident.
I promise you.
I'll be careful in the future.
I won't be found by Xue Tai again.
If you were an ordinary citizen,
you wouldn't have to pay attention to Xue Tai.
But you're the commander of the State of Boya.
That's why you're in danger.
Let's leave, Yizhi.
Fan.
I don't want to be the commander of the State of Boya.
I just want to give you a stable place
in this chaotic world.
A happy life.
A place where others are,
is never as safe as your own.
Moreover,
the most important thing is
I want to get the approval of the female king
and your family.
I think that's how you'll be happy.
I'm sorry.
Fine.
Since there's a conflict,
let them not interfere.
If you can get the approval of the Qiao family and Wei family,
and make an announcement that you're the son-in-law of the Qiao family
and the father-in-law of the Marquis Wei,
they won't interfere.
Fine.
Don't cry.
Nan Jun.
Don't be so formal.
I'm used to eating with the soldiers.
I just want to share my thoughts with you.
We're just eating.
You want this?
Master.
The road ahead is blocked.
Please make a decision.
Okay, I'll go and have a look.
You can use it yourself.
It's too cold outside.
Get in the car and take it.
Tao, I'll get in the car with you.
You like this cake?
Eat more.
Are you moving to the mansion first?
Okay, let's go.
Tao.
Take this.
But eat it first.
If Tao can't avoid this cake,
there'll be a seperation,
You eat first.
Don't wait for me.
Who's waiting for you?
Why are you holding this for me?
Master said you wanted to eat it.
You and him,
what can you learn?
You don't understand anything.
What's wrong?
Did I annoy you again?
Go, go, go.
You didn't annoy me.
You offended the Queen, didn't you know?
You can't tell at all.
The Queen wants to be closer to the King.
The road is so big.
Why do you have to call the King away at this time?
I don't care.
You're responsible for your own trouble.
Fine.
I'll take care of it.
You'll take care of it.
I'm leaving.
Come back.
It's on you,
not on us.
You're so fast.
You can handle it yourself.
Go.
Come back.
Master's stupid brain.
You want him to understand the Queen's mind.
What do you think?
Are we brothers?
Did we say
we have both good and bad.
What happened to him?
He's scared.
It's not about life and death.
You have your own way.
Go.
Come back.
One month off.
Three months is enough.
Kids don't listen to this kind of things.
Go.
Go play on the road.
Don't move.
Come here.
Go.
I can't hear you
saying such bad things.
When I went to the bar,
there were always those drunkards
who were jealous of me.
There's a gap between
the female soldiers and the main workers.
You
are jealous of the main workers?
Do you want me to die?
What do you mean?
I'll tell you the truth.
I'm in love with her.
The best way to make a person
realize his feelings
is to make him lose his feelings first.
Think about it.
If Xiao Tao disappears now,
what will you feel?
Will you be in a hurry to get her?
You are so sweet.
Do you have any orders?
The main worker only asked me
to ask you to wait here.
We'll protect you.
Please.
Wait here.
Wait.
Master.
The female soldiers...
What's wrong with the female soldiers?
The female soldiers said
they were sitting on the carriage for too long.
They were bored.
They insisted on going out.
Can someone guard them?
Wei Liang and Wei Duo are both here.
They are all here.
That's fine.
The female soldiers haven't returned for a long time.
I guess they are bored
on the carriage.
And the march is really boring.
Now that the food is ready,
the big event is over.
Let him play for a while.
Why are you back?
Didn't I ask you to guard the female soldiers?
Master.
The female soldiers said they wanted to get some water.
They asked me to ask if they wanted to get water from the river.
You are so muddled.
It's a wild place.
How can you keep the female soldiers alone?
Wei Duo.
Wei Duo?
Wei Duo is not as tall as Tao Zi.
Tell me about Wei Duo.
It's a complicated place.
It's a wild place.
If the beasts come out,
the female soldiers will be in danger.
They will be in danger.
If they encounter bandits,
and they are afraid of the beauty of the female soldiers,
or if they encounter refugees,
they will be in danger.
The hungry women in the belly will be treated as food.
They will be like a woman in the belly.
Haven't you heard of this kind of story?
If there is something wrong with the female soldiers,
you will be punished.
You will be punished.
Master.
I will teach her a lesson for you.
What's wrong with you today?
You just went for a walk.
Wei Duo is following us.
I mainly see the sun.
The female soldiers...
Okay.
I will go to welcome her.
Master, please.
You were so scary just now.
I'm serious.
Do you know that you are anxious?
You can't always
come to see me.
The female soldiers won't really be in danger.
Wei Duo is here.
That's right.
What are you two arguing about?
Wei Duo.
Where are the female soldiers?
Female soldiers?
Aren't they with you?
Oh, no.
I didn't clean my ears.
Wei Duo.
Yes.
Where are the female soldiers?
Oh, no.
Find them!
Yes.
This way!
Stop!
Are you okay, Master?
Take them down!
Yes.
Master, please spare us!
Xiao De, are you okay?
Who are you taking?
What's wrong?
Master.
I'm fine.
You're useful.
Take these people
to see the doctor.
Some of them are sick.
How did you know I was here?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I saw these refugees
wandering in the woods.
They were walking around
when they came out to find food with their fellow villagers.
It was late at night.
I asked the guards to lead us to find the way.
Then we arrived here.
Didn't you get caught by them?
No.
Let's go.
Go.
Where are you from?
Where are you going?
General,
we're from Yanzhou.
Because the rain water this year
is less than last year.
In order to fight against the flood,
Yanzhou and Yaozhou
fought tirelessly.
Hundreds of people in the village
were forced to leave home.
All the way here,
only these people are left.
General.
Yanzhou is thousands of miles away from here.
You people
just walked out like this.
There's no other way.
We went to Liangya.
He didn't take us.
We went to Yanzhou.
Yanzhou didn't take us either.
Yes, General.
We really couldn't walk.
Even if we found a sheltered place
to hide from the rain,
we couldn't go there.
We could only go there
when the weather gets better.
Please forgive us.
Don't drive us away.
Yes, General.
We didn't mean to drive you away.
The soil here
is really not a good place.
Where are we going?
General.
Please save us, General.
Please save us.
General.
Save us.
General, please save us.
There's a place 20 miles north of here.
It's near the Panyi,
the new capital of the East Street.
It's suitable for building houses.
And it's near the Yongning District.
It's also convenient to water the fields.
You can open up a big field there
and cultivate your life.
But from today on,
you have to promise to follow the law of the country
and not offend the people.
The Wey Kingdom will take you in.
You can drink the water of the Wey Kingdom,
eat the rice of the Wey Kingdom,
and be with ordinary people.
Thank you, General.
Thank you.
But when we passed the Panyi County,
the county magistrate happened to be out on business.
Without the county magistrate's approval,
we wouldn't dare to stop outside the city.
It's not easy to build houses.
The one in front of you
is not an ordinary general.
He's the master of the Wey Kingdom.
They're all so kind.
Marquis.
Thank you, Marquis.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Marquis.
You're awake, Dad.
Come back to the camp with us.
Eat some dry grains with the wind.
Let's set out to Panyi County tomorrow.
Thank you.
Congratulations, Marquis.
Congratulations.
Where are you going?
There's no water.
I'll get some water.
No need.
Guards.
Yes.
Get some water.
Drink it.
Yes.
Where are you going?
It's cold at night.
I'll get some clothes from the carriage.
No need.
Here, cover it.
You can wear it.
It's okay. Cover it.
Here, cover it.
Here.
Change clothes.
No.
Sit down.
But what's wrong with you today?
You're always against me.
I don't care. I'm going to change now.
No.
Listen.
From today on,
you must tell me where you want to go.
Don't make me worry like today.
Guards.
Guards, it's okay.
Chunniang did make me worried today.
She has been nagging me for a long time.
The one who worries you the most today
is not Chunniang.
Good.
Good job.
The eldest daughter of Yao family
is very beautiful,
but she's old now.
It's not convenient to write to the lord.
Yes.
Although the eldest daughter of the Li family
is good at singing and dancing,
she's a famous
stupid mouth and a snake.
Yes.
Lord.
What do you think of the daughter of Xu Gong?
This daughter is beautiful
and has a clear smile.
And the daughter of the Lv family
is good at playing the zither and painting.
She's famous all over the country.
If you can find this daughter,
it's a great gift.
It's not easy to find this daughter.
Isn't it a little hard?
Lord.
Lord, this is for the country.
If you have no children,
you can find a woman who is not a woman
and be a concubine.
So what?
What concubine?
Brother.
I'll order someone to find a beautiful girl
and make a zither for you.
I'll ask someone to find a beautiful girl
What concubine?
I'm old.
I...
I want to find a good-aged woman
to raise her
and marry her to the Marquis of the World.
You married two daughters
and you've tasted the sweetness?
I'm doing this for the country.
In the world,
there's no such thing as the country.
Don't talk nonsense.
Sister-in-law.
Brother, you've gone too far.
You asked A-Ci and Manman to get married.
All these years,
you've been the only one who's been over the edge.
You've raised these three children.
Even your father
respects you.
How could you be so cold to him?
I've said it.
It's not about the concubine.
I didn't say that.
It's just that...
It's just that he said it.
Brother.
I'm doing this for our family
and for the country.
Since Manman got married to Wei,
the relationship between the two families has improved significantly.
It's clear that the marriage is going well.
Brother.
Now,
Liangya, Zhongzhou, and Juejun
are all expanding.
The world is in chaos.
I can't wait for the Qiao family
to have more daughters.
You're doing this?
Aren't you afraid of being laughed at?
If I, Yanzhou,
please other people with my daughter,
it'll be a shame for me.
If I really do this,
how can I have the face
to do this to the young master of Yanzhou?
Brother.
You're not going to die here.
But you'll be bewitched by this bitch.
Brother.
I'll kick you out of the house.
Master.
I...
Mr. Zhang is a man of no value.
You'll have to rely on him in the future.
He's a man of no value.
Master.
Since you don't believe me,
I'll go back to clean up.
I'm going to go back to my hometown.
You don't have to go.
I'll go back to clean up now.
Leave this dirty place.
What are you talking about?
Zi.
Master.
Enough, sir.
Don't make trouble.
I...
Don't be afraid.
Tell me if you want to live.
Tell me if you want to die,
but they'll kill you,
or you'll never say goodbye to me.
I've needed so much time to approach you.
Just ignore my family.
And live the dream.
Yes.
white as an enjoyed dark good wine, faithless lovers Hooking premises with my finger.
I'm willing to be the smile that makes you smile
Even if the wind and snow are behind me
No matter how much I don't want to be, I only think about you
I won't forget you in this life
I'm willing to cross the sea of mountains to follow your wind
Waiting for the white hand to enter the bow
Jiangnan words are not落在你眉睫
The heart is sad and the tears flow
I'm willing to be the smile that makes you smile
Even if the wind and snow are behind me
No matter how much I don't want to be, I only think about you
I won't forget you in this life
优优独播剧场——YoYo Television Series Exclusive