Novel Dramaine
I will be with you forever.
Is love the only thing that can last me for the rest of my life?
Why do I feel so lonely and lonely when I'm fighting?
I'm unable to get your ordinary care.
My ordinary life,
I will fall again.
I will be in your arms, not the wind.
I will cross the vast sea of clouds.
I will be born again, and I will be born again.
Only love can make the sky and sea wide.
I will be your hero.
Look at the way the wolf god is fighting.
Stop!
If it wasn't for the shot, Su Zi Xin wouldn't have made it.
It's just a match. Su Zi Xin is very aggressive.
He's not good at fighting.
The winner is in a moment.
This Su Zi Xin is really powerful.
This match is about fairness and justice.
Since the weapon we prepared is not good,
let's change the weapon we have.
Wei Xiao.
Yes.
Bring me my gun.
The latest news!
The gunhead of the Yanzhou court was shot.
He's injured.
He's injured?
Eunuch, Eunuch, why?
He's the best at shooting.
How come he's injured?
What should we do?
Don't worry.
We haven't finished the match yet.
Let's see.
The award for the bow.
It's the hope of the Wei family.
Take the gun.
The
Aisi, you have to be careful.
Don't worry, Aisi.
With the adequate protection,
he'll be convinced.
Don't worry.
Aisi.
Aisi, you can do it.
You must make it.
Not bad.
You have to make it as well.
No, no, no.
This is the diagnosis.
He doesn't need.
Even if I was the Especiallyble,
He wouldn't have been able to say otherwise.
I knew he didn't,
But I keptJingxiu with him.
It's a cross.
True.
More and more.
Whereas Dao Z installs many guns.
So there is an misinform.
Now people may think
Jill会
Wait a minute
yes
You'll be back
Hurry up
Why not
and our young master.
I have good taste.
Master has long been fond of the young master.
He's the one who's good.
No wonder.
The young master has good taste.
Let's go.
Next time.
The warrior of Yan State wins!
Good!
He's so good!
The young master is the best!
Others!
I think...
even though TAI SWORD쇄 ok über today,
the one who's leading the Healthcare Talisman group
is a sureahunched man.
Butterflies!
Your tools are shown only by Z sacrificing this hero.
Yes.
Marquis Wei, please check it.
The sword is sharp.
The internal force is going to try its best to fight.
But I didn't expect the rules
to forbid the use of dark weapons.
I should be fine.
I didn't expect to hurt Young Master.
Sister.
Marquis Wei,
I was wrong.
Zi Xin was looking for a chance to win.
So she lost her temper on the stage.
But she didn't mean to hurt anyone.
Marquis Wei, please don't blame yourself.
It's inevitable that she will be punished.
But I've been fighting for years.
I know if she meant to do it or not.
Su Zi Xin is not a good person.
If Lady Yulou doesn't teach her well,
she will be dragged down.
Wushan State hasn't attended the Lu Li Conference for many years.
Even if she doesn't make any contribution,
I believe her family
won't blame you.
Marquis Wei,
I came here
to buy something.
My brother is strong.
I'm sorry for your embarrassment.
But my brother came here to attend the conference
not to fight for Wushan State.
I was a female soldier in Bianzhou.
After my late husband died,
the new owner of Bianzhou,
the former minister of Nanrong,
forced Xue Tai to build his own family.
Xue Tai is really a rebel.
Chen Pang is not a rebel.
He can't suppress Xue Tai.
Except for Jue Jun,
he's short of many land.
Yes.
He's the only one who has 50,000 elite soldiers.
He has 50,000 elite soldiers.
I want to
build a new house for him.
I believe General Xue
can accomplish his mission.
So, Mrs. Yulou
has another support.
Xue Tai followed Mrs. Yulou.
If he married Mrs. Yulou,
he would have got tens of thousands of soldiers
to be his horseman.
Yes.
Marquis Wei, I didn't mean to lie to you.
But
I'm a female soldier in Bianzhou.
I have my responsibilities.
General Xue is loyal.
I can't just let him go.
Yes.
It's all my fault.
Please don't blame me.
It's all your fault.
Mrs. Yulou made the decision.
I don't care.
Wait for me in Beijing.
I'll take care of all my men in Jiang filt кomras.
I'll ask the local Repeat Police to send 오베어
in town one day,
OK?
Gerudo
and I won't stay in there much longer.
I need you to find more people
for me.
I'm sorry.
Brother-in-law.
Cousin.
Why are Nan Zheng and Cousin here?
Don't they have a meeting
in a few days?
Here's the thing.
Cousin is worried about Qiao Ci.
So I brought him here.
Yes.
I do care about Ci.
And I'm the only one who cares.
It's just a scratch.
It's not serious.
You're bleeding so much.
You said it's not serious.
I had a great time today.
That shot was very accurate.
I can take it
after a few more rounds.
You're so mean.
But Qiao Ci's martial arts are really good.
There are not many people in Weiguo
who can shoot as well as him.
Zhong Lin.
Should I
ask Ci about it?
I think it's necessary.
Really?
But now
you have Li Kui.
The hunting competition in two days
doesn't have to be too hard.
Don't let your sister worry.
There are a few days left.
As the young master of Yanzhou,
you must be careful.
Understand?
Yes, brother-in-law.
Lan Jun, Cousin.
I'm here.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Have a good rest.
You're in the sedan chair today.
And you're standing up to speak for me.
It seems you still care about me.
Your brother-in-law
is cold and warm.
You're really a brother-in-law.
I just said
a few words of good words.
And you're so happy.
I didn't speak for him.
The gun you used today
is your brother-in-law's weapon.
I'm not his cousin.
Brother-in-law of Weiguo.
Wei Bao.
Really?
The legendary gun
is a rare rare item in the world.
I don't know how good the gun is.
I just know
your brother-in-law is willing to give you
his brother-in-law's weapon.
How can he recognize you?
You took the Li Kui today.
Don't be arrogant.
You have to be diligent every day.
And
do you remember
the thing that Xiang Hui told me to keep an eye on you?
Six Stars Tendon
One states have one step gliar Ehbreat.
Cocetaria
is a rare gem in Korea.
Documents
We have nine thousand and six kilograms of
Neum fore이에요
We are here to choose
Lu Kui and Li Kui.
It's not a bad choice.
Why don't we take this opportunity
to choose another Kui?
Speaking of Kui,
it should be Mudan.
Chen Xiang is so lucky.
He's lucky to have a family.
It's a great honor
to have family members
to sing every night.
It's a great honor.
Madam Yu Lou is beautiful.
Marquis Wei is pretty.
If you want to choose a beauty,
don't lie to me.
Marquis Wei is here.
Marquis Wei and Lord Jun.
Please sit down.
Thank you, Marquis Wei.
Father.
Selection.
What do you think of Palm Leaf whooshing?
But...
It's useful to be extinguished,
so it can passtechnology!
Is it sophisticated?
Wipe your hands with hands
and they'll move lol son!
Its ears was frozen!
Chronoplasm?
So beautiful,
I have brought you a gift
Thank you for your help
Let's have a look
Well…
This is the fishing map of all states
Please have a look
This is the newly built water canal of Wei State
It goes from Panyi to Rong County
The water on the way
not only solved the drought of the Han Empire
but also opened up 30% of the trade
to make more goods flow
It's really a great achievement
It's a big project
It's a good thing
So, you set up a banquet
just to show off to everyone
No
Today, I want to discuss
how to share water with states
Well…
What do you mean?
The land of Xiu Xu
is common in Wei State
But I don't want to think alone
So, I have a party
to bring out the food and wine
I want to tell you
only by making it smooth
can the state be safe
You mean
we should build the canal too?
Yes
I want to connect the canal
to all four sides
and connect all the rivers
in the Central Plains
So, we can solve the drought
and the people's sufferings for a long time
Most of the wars in the Central Plains
started because of the fight for water
and people suffered a lot
When I went to the banquet
to investigate the Yongning canal
I saw the refugees
were all locked up and sent to exile
We, the high-ranking people
if we don't think about
how to solve the drought for the people
and just think about finding happiness
we will suffer the consequences
Good
The drought has been going on for years
The people of Yanzhou are willing to live again
I have long wanted to
marry the capital to Wei
As long as Marquis Wei can drink water as promised
and enter Yaozhou
It sounds so fake
but it's actually feasible
It's really feasible
I don't know what you think of it, Lord Liangya
I don't agree
Why?
Marquis Wei just wants to borrow the Xiuqu Yishi
to contain the army
Why should I agree?
To show my sincerity
I will dispatch troops
to help the Xiuqu
Marquis Wei dispatch troops to Xiuqu
Is it dispatch troops or Xiuqu?
Yes
Once the water canal is connected
the troops of other states will cross the waterway
and hit the land of Yaozhou
How can we resist then?
Right?
Yes
It's unreasonable
The Xiuqu Yishi will be taken to Shangquan
Yes
You are thinking too much
The benefits of the canal
are not the roads between states
but the livelihood and peace of the people
A dozen years ago, Yanzhou was also a food source
The income depends on luck
When my grandfather wanted to connect the canal
the people of Yanzhou didn't want to cooperate
He swam around
and made the canal himself
After the first canal was connected
the people gradually understood
I agree
Recently, Marquis Wei rebuilt the Yonglin District
The trade between Yanzhou and Wei State has increased
Yanzhou has become rich
This is the biggest benefit of the canal
Does your words
represent Wei State or Yanzhou?
I am both the daughter of Wei Family
and the daughter of the Qiao Family
Since you are both the daughter of Wei Family
you must speak for the Fu Family
Am I right?
Yes
Can I represent Yanzhou?
You?
Although you are young
you are the young master of Yanzhou
You are indeed capable
Yanzhou has been a water-saving place for a long time
It's been three years
The canal has just been connected
and the crops have just been grown
The crops have just been grown
As far as I know
there are tens of thousands of people every year
They are starving and are lost
Why can't Yanzhou be taken away?
The land of Taozhou is low
The flood happens all year round
and is called a flood
Every year
the people pray for it
When the flood returns next year
they won't abandon their homeland
How can the state-owned state-owned state
bear to abandon it?
The people of Zhongzhou are hardworking and capable
They produce a lot of fruit and fruit every year
But due to the complex terrain
and the lack of trade
they have to travel across the mountains and forests
to send them out
How many people die every year because of this?
In this situation
why can't Zhongzhou be taken away?
Fourteen years ago
the two families of Qiao and Wei
had a bloody feud
Marquis Wei once vowed to destroy the Qiao family
But why now
did he still decide to marry our family?
Because Marquis Wei knew
the people of Wei are suffering for a long time
In order to get rid of the Marquis Wei
he even let go of hatred
Such a fierce and fierce man
why should you worry?
It's really a great thing
You're right
We, Yanzhou, agree to build the state-owned state
There are many people in Zhongzhou
Maybe we can get more manpower
We, Yaozhou, can get some money
We, Tao Zhong, also agree to build the state-owned state
Marquis Wei worked hard to hold the ceremony
and even sent his little brother to travel
He just wanted to take this opportunity
to take the state-owned state to the next level
You are willing to be controlled by Marquis Wei
but I can't
I will make a vow today
As long as I am in the state for one day
I will never listen to anyone else's orders
Marquis Wei's song is not for personal benefit
I'm willing to write a letter to persuade Xue Tai
to ask him to help
Thank you for your trust in me
To show my sincerity
and to build the state as soon as possible
I will dispatch 100,000 elite soldiers
and 10 guards to control the water and the water
to help build the state
Marquis Wei is righteous
We are willing to help the state to build the state together
Thank you all
You are welcome
Goodbye
Si
Brother-in-law
Thank you for today
But my brother-in-law was too harsh on you
Don't mind him
It's okay if he treats sister well
I was also a bit biased against him
before
I knew it was a misunderstanding later
In Rong Jun
I almost fell off in order to save sister
It's right to treat your sister well
Brother-in-law once alone
took sister back from hundreds of refugees
I didn't fall so low
Brother-in-law refused to accept the concubine for sister
He even turned his face to his relatives
and to make sister happy
he scattered all the concubines in the mansion
Did your sister tell you all this?
In this world
I'm afraid no one can do this except me and my father
It's hard for your sister
to say that
But
I'm glad to see you can be independent today
and think of your sister
Actually
I was afraid of being scolded by my sister just now
For today's words
Sister pulled me yesterday
and talked about various situations
I was afraid of making a joke if I recognized the wrong person
So I was lucky to protect them
Your sister told you to think of it?
Yes
I should have thought of her
But you are great too
Why are you here?
You still count that nothing happened?
I'm done
A-Se told me
I just want to ask
how you think of those who are not
to praise me
A-Se is just a kid's temper
He had some misunderstandings about Nan Jun
It's good to coax him
But Nan Jun
don't blame me for making trouble
How could it be?
It's hard for you
I promised to help Nan Jun to get married
I should do this
Then
You did this
just because you promised me
Don't lie to him
Then I have to do what I promised Nan Jun
You told me before
You said that not everyone in Qiao family
is devoted to scheming and scheming
I didn't believe it before
But I believe it now
I was too narrow-minded
Don't blame me
I'm sorry
When we were just married
I was worried
But I don't know when it started
I don't want to hide it from you
I don't want to
I just want to treat you as my own
You and me
became close
because of a marriage certificate
Now I want to ask you
Are you willing to be my real husband?
We've been through so much together
Aren't we a real couple?
Survivor
Sister
I found out
You are a master of killing.
He is quite capable.
Sister.
If you really want to marry him,
you should find a better man.
I want to meet him today.
I see Marquis Wei has some prestige
and is looking to enter the Central Plains.
But he has a family background
and is not easy to control.
Now the Luli Conference is over.
All parties will leave.
I have no reason to stay.
You mean
you want to find Lord Liang?
Leave the details of Liu Yuan.
Well...
The hardest thing to control is the human heart.
The easiest thing to control is also the human heart.
As long as you know what a person really wants,
and what he wants,
you can control him
like a puppet.
The invitation has been delivered.
Why hasn't he come yet?
He was fine at first.
But one night,
His Highness went crazy
at the place where Lord Liang was.
He said
His Highness is the regent.
Why...
It's just an excuse.
They didn't come to meet me.
It's because I broke my face with Wei Shao.
None of them dared to stand up.
Your Highness.
Yanzhou sent someone here.
They said Zhou Mu was drunk and couldn't come.
Leave.
Yes.
Your Highness.
Zhou Mu had an emergency.
All the women in Zhou Mu had a fight.
They couldn't come to see him.
Is Madam Yulou not coming?
Don't misunderstand me.
I can't bear to see you alone.
I came to bring you back.
I heard that
you were sent to the lower realms
and grew up in Yanzhou.
So what?
I'm like you.
I grew up in Yuzheng.
People like us
are not favored by our families.
We were given to others as pawns since we were young.
We never got the power of fate.
I came here
to persuade you.
You are a father.
You didn't do anything wrong.
You were used by them.
You lost your value and were abandoned.
You were blessed with many things.
You were always in panic.
You were afraid of being bullied.
The pain in your heart
is not something that ordinary people can feel.
You can feel it?
I was born in Wushan Kingdom.
I was born in a family of Su family.
When I was young, they said
that my birthmark was like a peony.
It was a fate that I didn't want for a hundred years.
These years,
I've been using the Ban's Mansion
to support the Su family.
I was careful to manage my marriage.
But until one year,
I suddenly found out
that they had a girl with seven hearts.
They said that
it was a thousand years.
But at that moment, I suddenly realized
that I was just a pawn in their hands.
As long as I lost my value,
I could marry her at any time.
What was the result of that girl?
She was beautiful and beautiful.
I have no other choice but to move out or die a letter.
Mrs. Yue Luo,
I'll go to the toilet.
Has Madam Yuluo been to Liangya?
No.
Liangya has a good view.
After the meeting,
I'll take Madam to Shangwan.
Your Highness.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Liangya is not the only one
with a beautiful view.
It's late today.
I'll leave first.
I didn't mean to rely on Liangya.
I just want to
make a good relationship with Your Highness.
In the future,
if you need anything,
I hope Your Highness can help me.
Your Highness.
Madam Yuluo
just wants to
find a good picture
on her head
and never be confused by it.
I know.
She's just acting.
Why are you so worried?
She reminds me of someone.
Qiao Shi.
These days,
Your Highness has been with your old friend.
You must have a lot of time to spend with him.
Just now,
I suddenly figured it out.
That day in Pan Yi,
why did she get angry with me?
Qiao Shi was born into the Qiao family.
She grew up in a small family.
She was loved by her grandparents and uncle.
Madam Ding treated her like her own daughter.
Moreover,
she still has a grandchild
like Qiao Ci.
If it were me,
if I had such a family,
I would sacrifice for my family.
I would shout out
the slogan of protecting all beings.
But I
have never been protected by my family
or been bullied by my father.
Just like what Madam Yuluo said,
people like us
should only live like tools.
We can't be loyal.
If we make a mistake,
we will be blamed and blamed immediately.
Qiao Shi is a noble man.
She is destined to be a devil.
I am not born as a snake.
I was born
as a snake.
Madam Yuluo is also like that.
Lord of Core uprising
Lord of Core Chef sent me
to deliver the food.
and hide.
Yes.
You must be careful on the way.
If I knew it, I wouldn't let Yu Ru
return to the Kang Army.
And someone can take care of me.
I come alone.
I can leave alone
when I'm not around.
All right.
I'm not by your side.
You have to be careful every day.
Tell my father that I'm fine.
Don't worry.
And
when you go back to the city,
you must pass by Boyan
and leave some food and clothing for Sister Zhang.
It's no better than the army.
I've been through a lot.
I'll remember it.
Brother-in-law.
I entrust my sister to you.
If you don't treat her well
in the future,
I'll get justice for her.
Cousin.
Let's drink together another day.
It's not impossible.
But a place like Luo Zhongfang
is not allowed to be taken.
Do you understand?
Do you want to know
whether it's Qiao Si's horse block
or mine?
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Brother-in-law.
Sister-in-law.
I can accept.
What do you want?
Just do it on your own.
Just do it.
Dad said
there is a good news.
Okay.
Play it it.
Come on.
Play it.
Hurry!
If you let Qiu Chuling
find out,
I have to get
the whole family
killed.
to be with you
is the same as now.
But I was still young
and couldn't be independent.
Now,
I don't want to be
a puppet of anyone's plan.
For the sake of Duke,
Zhong Li,
can you let me
stay away from you for a while?
The moonlight creaks in the deep sea
but never comes out
How lucky to have always been
D wiring my dreams
ered through my fingers
But my heart has born the thread
As if a ex-girlfriend
Your smile
Even if it's a storm after the storm
No matter how much I don't want to live, I only miss you for this life
I will never forget
I am willing to cross the sea of mountains to follow your wind and moon
Waiting for the white hand to enter the first line
Jiangnan words are not lost in your eyes
Heart
Flowing
I am willing to stand like a blinding smile
Even if it's a storm after the storm
No matter how much I don't want to live, I only miss you for this life
I will never forget