(Undercover High School)
(A Good Friend to Meet)
(All places, organizations, characters,)
(incidents, and backstories in this drama are fictitious.)
(Episode 2)
Don't move.
Oh Su A the teacher?
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
What is she doing here?
Stop! Just don't!
Your hand.
Does this look like a toy?
This is a real tear gas gun, okay?
(Patrol)
I told you not to move.
Darn it.
Remove your cap and mask.
Hey, you!
Hey!
Shoot.
(Keep Out)
Why are you so fast?
I was on the track and field team in high school!
Stop right there!
- Oh, dear. - Mister.
- My gosh. - That weird guy...
- A weird guy? - Where'd he go?
You didn't see a masked man in a cap?
No.
I'm sorry, sir.
Tell me if you're in pain tomorrow.
Okay?
Darn it.
He got away.
I'll kill him next time.
What?
Were you caught?
You should've been more careful.
You can't get caught by your own teacher.
Okay. I'll be more careful.
Who'd have thought someone would patrol the place?
What about your face?
Did she see it?
Fortunately not.
She's weird, though.
She runs like she's a machine.
Like a real Terminator.
What?
So what happened? Did you get him?
No.
I lost him, but I almost had him.
Should I have just shot him?
My gosh.
What if you didn't have the tear gas gun?
I told you...
it was dangerous out there and you'd need it.
Yes.
I listened to you and got out alive.
You must be so proud of yourself.
If I saved your life,
why don't you help me close up?
I must've had the shock of my life.
I need to go home and rest.
Bye.
It's my fault.
I raised her.
It's such a shame.
If I'd caught him,
I'd have gotten a citizen's award and become a full-time teacher.
Please show up once more.
She's so weird. We won't get along.
(Keep Out)
(Byeongmun High School)
Last night, someone broke into the old building.
Ms. Oh came across the intruder...
on the first floor and gave chase,
but lost him.
She didn't see his face.
See if there were other witnesses.
I will.
Okay.
What should N be if these are to be equal?
It should be nine.
That's it for today.
Well done. See you next time.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Why the heck am I studying math at my age?
What's wrong with your age?
You have no idea what you're asking.
Here's your first mission, Hae Seong.
Ta-da.
Dong Min's fingers are way too slow.
You have three days.
Get him to max level.
- You can do it, right? - Wait.
I don't know this game.
Learn how to play, then.
It's three days. Get to it.
Okay.
Good.
Three days. Good luck.
I know the game.
- Want me to teach you? - How can you say that?
Where's your pride?
You want to do this because they say so?
Aren't you a man?
- What? - Max level in a game.
Don't tell sir or Yeong Hun.
Hae Seong, this is the NIS.
Asking me to hack a game to get you to max level...
is crossing the line.
Pretend it's part of the mission.
I'm having the worst time here.
Goodbye.
Hello? Mi Jeong.
Park Mi Jeong.
I see you're having a rough time.
You make it max level for me, then.
No, thank you.
You're really impatient.
Even before I told you to stay away from Park Tae Soo,
you two got involved.
I don't know what I'm doing here.
What's the guy like?
He's a typical jerk and bully.
He harasses kids because his dad's an assemblyman.
What about you, Yu Jeong? Are you okay?
Me? I'm...
I'm, well... We're both on the student council.
What? You too?
What? You think it's weird?
I heard it was really hard to join.
I'm impressed.
Well, I happened to get accepted.
Anyway, beware of Park Tae Soo.
He's a jerk, but he's on the student council.
If you get on their bad side, even I can't help you.
Watch your language.
I smell a nagging old guy.
See you. Stay another five minutes.
What? I'm a nag?
Ms. Oh.
- Do you think little of me? - No.
Whom did you see last night?
I told you to patrol with an extra dose...
of a sense of duty.
Why did you take extra care to lose him?
I apologize.
I promise...
to get him next time.
Are you praying for him to reappear?
Enough with the nonsense.
Those reports.
Go through them all and submit a summary.
- All of that? - Is there too many?
I'll do it, then. Let's see.
The job posting for a vacancy at our school...
No, sir.
I'll do it.
I love this kind of work.
Good.
It's fine.
Ms. Oh was the only witness.
The CCTV cameras didn't catch anything.
I see.
However, there was some interference in the footage.
An expert says...
it looks like a video jammer was used.
A jammer?
What an interesting toy.
If they fled from the first floor,
they didn't get to the basement.
The person will be back.
Let's see...
what they get up to.
It's that, isn't it?
"Workplace bullying."
Discrimination against temporary teachers.
We're to put up with it or become a full-time teacher.
The bullying could be because of...
the toupee incident.
Things are already rough. The darn intruder...
I wonder.
What was the intruder doing there?
You have a point. There's nothing there.
Only he'd know that.
There are spooky stories and now an intruder too?
Why won't they just tear down the old building?
"Spooky stories?"
There's a ballet studio in the basement over there.
Something happened there years ago.
What are you three doing?
Oh, no.
I'm so sorry.
Play or you lose. Rock-paper-scissors.
- There. - Okay.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Nice one. - Come on.
- No. - Please?
- Pay up. - Seriously?
- You lost. - But still.
- Why do you need it? - To play games.
Hand it over.
Be quiet!
Let's start. Turn to page 125.
Did Dong Min go somewhere?
Ms. Oh.
He left early saying he felt sick.
Was it Park Tae Soo?
- Who else would it be? - Darn him.
He never mentioned that to me.
He said you weren't in the teachers' office...
and asked me to tell you, but I forgot.
Sorry.
Okay. Let's start the lesson.
What did we learn last time?
- The Russo-Japanese War. - The Russo-Japanese War.
Right. Today we'll touch on the 1905 Protectorate Treaty.
As you all know,
the 1905 Protectorate Treaty...
isn't exactly a "treaty" because we were unwilling.
The call cannot be connected.
After the beep, you'll be transferred to...
(Grade 11 Class 1 Lee Dong Min)
I don't have his number so I can't even call.
I'm bothered.
(You are dead.)
Darn it...
(Keep Out)
(Byeongmun High School)
(Park Jae Mun, 54, Byeongmun High principal)
(Seo Myeong Ju's loyal henchman)
(Seo Myeong Ju, 48, 4th chair, took office in 2001)
(Byeongmun High School)
You there.
Hurry over here.
You could get into huge trouble.
Weren't you told students were to stay away from the building?
Some crazy guy was in there last night,
and the principal's on edge.
You could get chewed out.
I'll be careful.
Just wait until I set eyes on the fool.
Stay away from the old building.
You could get into trouble if you're caught.
Did they hide gold and jewels under the floor?
They make such a fuss of the place.
The eyesore is a headache.
I'll go on my way.
Okay. Study hard.
- I will. - Good.
(Jeong Hae Seong)
Byeongmun High's principal?
Yes. He went into the basement.
Did you find out what he went there for?
Not exactly.
Something's definitely in the basement.
I doubt...
the principal went down there to take a poop.
Don't talk about food when we're eating poop.
It's the other way around.
The school knows of the intruder.
- Move with caution. - Yes, sir.
Thanks.
Don't you hate how they treat you?
I do.
But there's nothing I can do...
other than bear with it.
Don't tell the teacher.
It'll make things worse.
You mentioned your grandma's ID.
Is that why Tae Soo's bullying you?
That too...
and some other stuff.
But it'll mostly be for fun.
I'm an orphan...
and a parasite of sorts who lives with my grandma.
They think it's okay.
Thank you for this. I'll wash it for you.
Okay.
Dong Min.
What happened?
You left early but didn't answer your phone.
I went to see a doctor and just got back.
Without a word to me?
Why are your clothes dirty?
I was throwing out the trash.
- See you later. - Okay.
I'm off too.
Stop where you are.
Follow me.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Ms. Oh?
You said you wanted to talk to me about something.
Be honest with me.
Have you been bullying Dong Min?
Gosh, I'm getting a headache.
Fine. Considering the situation earlier,
I understand why you got the wrong idea.
But you see,
I'm not a bully.
Then explain what happened.
He left early, so why was he with you?
And what happened to his uniform?
You can't even answer these questions.
I knew you'd be trouble when I saw you drinking.
How dare you try to fool me?
Don't move.
Oh, what are you doing?
- Come closer. - Why?
- Come here. - What? Why?
- Why... - Hey, come here for a second.
- But why... - Come here!
You little punk, are you out of your mind?
Hey, am I a virus or something?
Why do you keep dodging me?
I'm sorry. Blame my reflexes.
Shut it. I should use my reflexes and smack you.
You really don't get it, do you?
I'll be watching you.
You'd better stay out of trouble.
Sure thing. I want that more than anyone else. I'm off.
(Counselling Office)
Goodness.
(Serving in the shadows to light the way forward)
Sir.
You need to see this.
(Senior Agent An Seok Ho)
"Chairwoman Seo Myeong Ju of Byeongmun Foundation..."
"launches a large-scale project to make Seongju..."
"the global mecca for education."
"This integrated elite program will cover..."
"all curriculums from grade school to postgraduate education."
"It's estimated to cost around 800 million dollars..."
Eight hundred million dollars?
That rings a bell.
Emperor Gojong's gold?
You said it was valued at 800 million dollars.
What is this, then?
They'll sneak it out of the country to launder the money...
and fund this project with that money?
She'll use the country's assets as if it's her money...
I hear many students...
are seriously addicted to online gambling these days.
Do you know if any of our students are struggling with such addiction?
My gosh, Chairwoman Seo.
You truly love the school and our students.
Put your worries to rest. As the vice-principal of the school,
I swear on my career that I'll make sure...
our students can't even dare to get into gambling.
Mr. Baek.
I suggest you remove Solitaire from your computer first.
Oh, I only play it to prevent Alzheimer's...
As you all know,
the construction of our Edu-City project will be completed soon.
I don't want anything...
to taint the foundation's image or the school's reputation,
so please be very careful.
Understood, ma'am. You can count on us.
Next, we have to talk about the demerit point system.
They want to increase the demerit points?
Don't complain to me.
It came up during the teachers' meeting.
The vice-principal wants us to decide.
Darn it. The vice-principal drives me nuts.
Hey, Ye Na. Can't you tell Chairwoman Seo...
to fire Baek Kwang Du?
Then my mom will expel you first.
Let's decide on the demerit points for each category.
What's up?
- Goodness. - Hey, you reek of cigarettes.
You said you quit smoking.
Many smokers quit only to smoke again, you fool.
The transfer student is getting on my nerves.
- Why? What did he do? - Well, he's a weirdo.
He went ahead and let Dong Min go without my permission.
Go easy on him. Don't you feel bad for him?
Did you lock him up or something?
Yes, in the recycling bin.
You're crazy.
My gosh. He bawled his eyes out as he refused to go in there.
- Do you want to watch the video? - Yes, show me.
Hold on.
Did you really have to do that?
What did you say?
I mean, I'll be honest.
There's a line you should never cross.
Also, the others really hate it when you do stuff like this.
This could negatively impact the student council...
My, you're something else.
Who are you to lecture me and tell me what not to do?
You're in the student council too, so we let you talk to us.
And you think you're it?
Do you think you're on the same level as us?
Hey, what's with you? Don't be so delusional.
We let you join because you're Ye Na's friend, you loser.
- Tae Soo. - What?
- You're out of line. - Why? Am I wrong?
She was an outcast and had no friends until last year.
Ye Na saved her. Am I wrong?
Hey.
You should thank Dong Min.
I'd be picking on you if he weren't around.
We heard you, so that's enough.
You're starting to get on my nerves.
Hey, stop defending her.
What is this? You're ruining the morale here.
Says the one who's actually ruining the morale here.
I agree with everything Yu Jeong said earlier.
Apologize to Yu Jeong.
Hey.
Isn't your dad seeking a fourth term in the National Assembly?
The party leader dropped by my house yesterday.
I think he and my mom discussed who to nominate.
The minute your dad loses his job, you become a loser too.
So, you need to apologize before that happens.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Hey, Ye Na.
Thanks for doing that earlier.
I had been vying for a chance to tell him off.
Tae Soo is a total scumbag, you know.
Yu Jeong, but don't step in like that from now on.
How you told Tae Soo to stop being a bully.
Let me say those things. It shouldn't come from you.
Right, I'm sorry. I'll be careful from now on.
Let's go.
(Grade 11)
This is the cut off line.
That's our top one percent.
Assemble them...
and create a special class for our top students.
We already have a special class. Do you want to split them up?
Create the best environment for them to study.
Get ready to manage their extracurricular activities...
on top of offering college admissions consultations.
Anyway, they should get more perks than those in the special class.
Ma'am.
Many students are complaining about the school's policies.
Especially those who aren't in the top ten percent.
They don't care about winning the competition.
No wonder they aren't in the top ten percent.
If we split up the class again...
in the current situation,
more people will complain.
Back when black slavery...
was a key part of the economy and society in America,
many slaves killed their masters and ran away,
so someone wrote a book called...
"How to Make a Slave."
It's very simple.
Create a caste system within the slave community,
clearly differentiate the groups in the slave caste system,
and treat them differently based on their caste.
In other words, drive a wedge...
between the slaves to...
So they'd look at...
who's at their level...
instead of who's above them when they have complaints.
We should split up the 90 percent too.
Give it a name that's similar to the special class.
Thirty percent in each class. We'll have three classes in total.
Yes, ma'am. Got it.
(Bulletin Board)
Are you skipping lunch?
I'll eat in a bit.
It's embarrassing to eat alone, you know.
Okay, suit yourself.
I hate crowds.
Wake me up when you're heading out.
Why did you ask me about the old building the other day?
Hey, kid. I'm going to sleep.
We're the same age.
I'm warning you just in case.
You'd be better off staying away.
Especially from the basement.
I know because I've been inside.
If you're curious, I could tell you more...
while we have lunch together.
Let's go. I'm hungry.
Come on. Let's go.
Are you not eating?
Well, just go ahead and tell me...
why I should stay away from the old building.
Before that, if you're not eating...
Here, it's all yours.
All yours.
Eat up.
Hae Seong, you're new here, so you probably don't know about...
the spooky stories about that building.
Years ago, there were classrooms in the building,
and this happened in the ballet studio.
There was a girl who dreamed of becoming a ballerina.
She practised there every night.
Oh, no. That must hurt.
She was being bullied by her classmates.
One night...
- Hey! - Hey!
Hey, where are you going?
- Stop! - Stop right there!
Get her!
Stop right there!
- Stop! - We'll catch you!
- Oh, no. - What do we do now?
- Darn it. - What should we do?
(Byeongmun High School)
She felt that she'd lost all hopes and dreams and chose to...
- For real. - What are you saying?
What do you mean? It's...
The girls decided to hide her body...
somewhere in the old building...
so that no one...
would ever find out what they did.
Hey.
What are you doing here? You should go home.
Sir.
I have no legs.
That was when...
rumours started to spread that she'd appear every night...
in the studio at the time of her death.
That's an interesting story.
I hope you don't expect me to believe it, though.
You see, I don't believe that stuff.
Come on.
I mean, in this day and age... Give me a break.
But I saw her.
I told you. I've been inside the building.
You actually saw a ghost?
(Dance Studio)
I swear, I wasn't mistaken.
I'm sure it was the ghost people talk about.
Do you want to hear the other spooky stories too?
The four spooky stories about Byeongmun High.
There are four scary stories about our school.
The first one is about the old building,
and the second one is...
Look, the losers are having lunch together!
- What? - What's going on?
- Are they talking about Dong Min? - Goodness.
(Lee Dong Min)
What if Dong Min is...
What if he's going through something?
School violence, perhaps?
Could he be being bullied?
What if he is being bullied?
But who'd bully Dong Min?
The transfer student, perhaps?
That's my guess.
But then again,
the look on his face tells me that he may not be a bully.
If you're not sure, just observe them for now.
And if you get a chance,
try talking to Dong Min.
I put in some honey to help boost your appetite.
- Eat up. - Nice, that looks delicious.
Eyes down.
Put your phones away.
And you, Dong Min.
Why did you crawl out without your master's permission...
to be embarrassed like this?
You think you can act out now that you've got a friend?
All right, go on and eat.
Hey, if you keep this up, I'll make you drop your pants.
Eat it!
Don't eat it.
What did you just say?
You keep crossing the line.
You three are disgusting.
He's out of his mind.
Say that again.
I dare you to say it again.
Hae Seong.
Repeat yourself, you punk.
Sorry. I guess I overreacted.
My bad. I apologize.
This won't ever happen again, so...
- What the... - No way.
Did you see that?
- Darn it. - Unbelievable.
- Are they insane? - What's going on?
Shouldn't we get someone?
What gives?
- No way. - This is bad.
Ms. Oh, it's bad!
Hey.
Jeong Hae Seong, was it?
- Come with me. - No, don't do this.
Hey.
Come on. I can't get into fights.
You've clearly lost your mind.
- I said that was enough. - Let go.
Let go of me, you punk.
Everyone's watching, so let's cut this short.
Let go, you prick.
Let go of me, darn it!
Get over here.
You...
Did you see that?
This is insane.
- No way. - My gosh.
That was crazy.
I can't believe it.
Stop right there!
Darn it.
What are you two doing?
Both of you, wait for me at the counselling office!
No way. The stream is going viral.
I've never seen Park Tae Soo get his butt kicked before.
That will cause quite the commotion.
He's an amusing one.
Let's eat.
(Student Counselling Office)
Are you that stupid?
How can you cause problems in less than a day?
I bet you have no idea what you've done.
You messed with the wrong guy.
You're in for a painful lesson.
Tae Soo, what are you doing here? Come on out.
Getting into fights when you just transferred?
I'm curious to know what will become of you.
I hope we can get along.
These schools are still pretty much the same.
Why is it just you? Where's the class monitor?
The vice-principal came by.
Why did you and Tae Soo fight?
Because he started it.
As in Tae Soo?
What could the two of you get into it about?
A physical altercation of this level isn't something I can take lightly.
So answer me.
Why did you two fight?
You should've come to me if an argument had started.
Are you a common thug?
A bully?
How can you get into fights only just after transferring?
You really are clueless.
What?
Are you knowingly turning a blind eye...
or are you just dense?
Ms. Oh, do you even care about your students?
I'll think that Tae Soo's a fine actor.
Because I'll be disappointed...
if you've knowingly been turning a blind eye.
I have nothing more to say.
This is up to you now.
Darn.
I bought another while getting mine.
I'm the reason you couldn't finish your lunch.
Thanks.
What did Ms. Oh say?
You know, the usual.
Don't get into fights and whatnot.
Sorry I made it hard on you.
Why would you need to apologize?
It's this world that's the issue.
Why did you hold back the other time?
You seem to pack a punch.
What was it again?
Hiding your true powers or something like that.
- HTP? - Yes, it's something like that.
I see.
Dong Min.
Hang in there.
You too.
(Have a Drink With Su A)
Darn.
Who does he think he is?
Of course, I care about my students.
Why do you think I want to be a full-time teacher?
Why? Just why? Darn it!
- Goodness. - My gosh.
- Darn! - I'm so sorry.
This is what I should've said to him.
She's not in her right mind.
Oh Su A,
you idiot.
You wait and see, Jeong Hae Seong.
I'll get rid of you.
Shouldn't the line be...
"I'll crush you?"
Potato, po-tah-to.
Darn.
I have students talking down to me now.
What a life this is.
It's the path you chose.
Hang in there.
What about that first student you taught?
Min Ji, was it?
You want to be a full-time teacher for her sake.
To guide other students since you failed her.
Is that something I said?
Yes, while crying your eyes out.
Drink in silence and go home.
Sir,
it's about Hae Seong.
- Will he be all right? - Don't.
Don't you dare say you want to be in a school uniform.
We're short-staffed as is.
Also, you look like...
you can pass for a disciplinary teacher.
Why are you hung up on school uniforms?
That's not it. I'm seriously worried.
You know how Hae Seong gets easily worked up.
You can worry about everyone else but not Hae Seong.
I know him better than anyone.
I heard you two had a long history.
You've known him since he was young.
Tell me about it.
My gosh.
Time sure does fly.
I can't believe that tiny thing is already...
Goodness.
Anyway,
he's not someone who'd easily cause trouble.
I trust him.
Let's eat before the noodles go mushy.
Director, my gosh.
Eat for now.
See for yourselves.
Eat while you watch.
Let go.
Let go of me, darn it!
You...
The transfer student has balls.
He messed with you of all people.
Here.
I'm not in the mood to laugh.
How can I end that punk?
You're not one to let this slide.
Tell me.
Should I come to your aid?
Forget it. He's not even worth it.
If that's what you say.
By the way, when are you going to pay me back?
If you're having trouble with it,
get me IDs instead like last time.
(Spark Golf)
I enjoyed the video.
What have you been getting yourself into?
Senior Agent An, didn't you warn him?
He's to lead a quiet school life...
to keep it from interfering with the mission.
I'm sorry.
I'll keep it brief, Agent Jeong.
If anything like this happens again,
the mission will be called off,
and you'll be investigated on the charge...
of damaging national treasure.
That'll definitely be the end of the idiotic Domestic Team Four.
You.
You joined the NIS to follow in your father's footsteps.
What will you say to him when you finally locate him?
That you got fired for botching a mission?
That'd be humiliating if you ask me.
Don't just look at me and get going.
Darn, I have an important game tomorrow.
Was it necessary to put it like that?
Don't be bothered about that comment about your father.
Just behave from here on out.
What about what I requested?
It'll be able to crack any door lock out there.
You said there was likely to be a storage room.
Anyway, let's wrap up this operation today.
Sure.
Ta-da!
What's this?
A gift for Parents' Day.
Really?
This is incredible.
I should wear this forever.
Dad.
Job shadowing is required for homework.
You said you worked for the government.
What should I say under job description?
Say I'm like a compass.
A compass?
A nameless compass that guides the nation...
to prosper and into the future.
When will you get home if you leave this late?
It's my birthday tomorrow.
As if I would've forgotten that.
I'll be home before you know it and wake you up.
We'll go to your favourite observatory.
Keep your promise this time.
Or I won't ever talk to you again.
I promise.
This won't take long.
Bye.
Dad!
- Yes? - You forgot this.
Your notepad.
Thanks, Son.
Bye.
I'll be back before you know it.
- Who is it? - Hello, ma'am.
I'm Dong Min's friend Jeong Hae Seong.
Why would Dong Min's friend come by at this hour?
He's at his part-time job.
He asked me for a favour, that's all.
- A favour? - I guess he didn't tell you yet.
He's receiving the encouragement scholarship,
but your ID is needed to complete the process.
He asked me to get it for him.
How sweet of you.
- Just a second. - Sure.
Goodness me.
My gosh.
- Hello. - Delivery!
Over here.
I'll leave it here. Please enjoy.
Sure.
(365 Pool)
Hae Seong.
What are you doing here?
What about you?
I saw you while out working my part-time delivery job.
Why did you jump over the wall?
Could you be after what I think you're after?
You are.
That's why you're here. To see if the story is true.
What?
No wonder you sneaked in here.
The place is out of bounds,
and you didn't want your name written down on the visitors' log.
Yes, that's it.
- Can I come with you? - No way.
Getting in here wasn't an easy feat for you.
Nothing good will come out of you being disciplined.
It'll only upset your grandma.
So head home already.
Be on your way.
You'd be disciplined as well.
Darn.
For the record, I told you to leave.
I didn't follow you in here. I'm going my own way.
You're more stubborn than you seem.
Whatever. Come back tomorrow, then.
Go your own way tomorrow.
Wait.
Do you hear that?
Senior Agent An.
I'm afraid this mission will take a while.
What do you mean?
My guess is that the chairwoman...
is also looking for the gold bars.
(Retired to the countryside after the 1905 Protectorate Treaty)
(The emperor's lost gold funding Byeongmun Foundation?)
Dong Min, let's go.
Let's go. It's dangerous here.
That was when...
rumours started to spread that she'd appear every night...
in the studio at the time of her death.
Hey.
What are you doing here? You should go home.
Sir.
I have no legs.
The story was true.
About the school ghost.
(Undercover High School)
(Sending back to desk)
(Where did the 800 million dollars from the national coffer go?)
(He was appointed as the first chairman...)
(of the school board.)
Who's there?
Seo Byeong Mun who hid the gold bars...
set up the ghost story as a riddle.
You must be interested in ghost stories.
Jeong Hae Seong did what?
Darn!
You're busted.
Jeong Hae Seong, get your act together.
Young man, you can't go in there.
This is a serious issue.
What will happen to Hae Seong, then?
Will he really be expelled?