(Celestial Duchy)
(1999)
(Changqingtai City)
(Here's a breaking story.)
(Deep In The Bustle
in the heart of Chinatown)
(is now renowned far and wide.)
(Although newly established,)
(Tu Jiasheng, Nie Feng, Zhao Lu)
(backed by the powerful connections)
(Deep In The Bustle)
(of its three founders,)
(it rapidly claimed)
(the top spot
in the city's entertainment industry.)
(But now, with the key founder)
(Nie Feng's father)
(Anti-corruption Investigation Team)
(caught in a political storm,)
(the future of Deep In The Bustle
may be at risk.)
(After all,)
(a business this profitable)
(attracts many greedy eyes.)
(It's said that Chief Phachai)
(has publicly declared more than once)
(to take over Deep In The Bustle.)
(How this will end)
(remains to be seen.)
(Chinatown)
(Welcome to Deep In The Bustle.)
Congratulations to Director Jimiya
for taking two beauties.
Next, let's welcome
the chief of Changqingtai City Police,
Phachai
to the Losha Pavilion.
At Losha Pavilion,
each token costs 100,000.
The girls whose tokens are taken
tonight
belong to Chief Phachai.
Chief Phachai is spending big tonight.
Looks like he is taking
all the beauties home!
Congratulations to Chief Phachai
for winning a bevy of beauties.
=The Glory Fades=
=Episode 1=
(No Causing Trouble, But Not Afraid of It)
Is this a scam?
(Qin Wei, GM of Deep In The Bustle)
I prepaid 500,000 dollars as a deposit,
and you tell me it's not enough?
Chief Phachai.
The entry fee for Losha Pavilion,
top beauties' chamber,
is 188,000 per person.
(Phachai, Police Chief)
You flipped eleven tokens tonight.
That totals 1.1 million.
Our prices
are clearly marked.
Refund me!
Wipe the bill!
Let me tell you.
I can shut this place down right now
on prostitution charges.
Chief Phachai.
That would be
against the rules.
Qin Wei.
I make the rules here.
Your Fifth Brother Tu Jiasheng
is nothing!
He's just a puppet.
And your Sixth Brother,
Zhao Lu.
What's the use
of having a government official father?
I'm the same rank as him!
He still relies on Governor Nie
to cover for him.
Now everyone knows
the Nie family
is hanging by a thread.
Where are the three brothers now?
Which one of you
dares talk to me?
(Tu Jiasheng,
Founder of Deep In The Bustle)
I'm letting you stay open.
I'm already doing you a favor.
Don't push it.
Smash it up!
Hello, Feng.
Are you handling this?
Phachai's going crazy.
Lu.
Behave.
(Zhao Lu, Founder of Deep In The Bustle)
Don't you know my family's situation?
Put Jiasheng on.
Hello, Feng.
Tu Jiasheng, are you useless?
Can't you even handle Phachai?
I'm telling you.
If he wrecks it today,
you'll answer for it.
Do we make a move?
No fatalities.
The thugs he brought are easy.
But if he calls men
from the police station,
then what...
I'll handle it.
All officers!
Surround Deep In The Bustle completely.
Not a single fly gets out.
Tu Jiasheng.
If you've got guts, open the door!
Kneel and call me grandpa,
and I might spare your lives.
I want Deep In The Bustle,
not your worthless lives.
Come out!
(Grand Princess Manor, Celestial Duchy)
Hello?
Your Highness.
What?
I guessed right.
(Grand Princess of Celestial Duchy)
I knew you'd come to me.
(Raja Kalina)
I just didn't expect
it to come so soon.
I'm starting the countdown now.
In thirty minutes,
you three
get out of Deep In The Bustle.
Fine.
In twenty minutes,
my Royal Guards will arrive.
And I'll keep my promise
and break up with Paria.
Remember your promise.
As expected,
my Paria was nothing
more than your stepping stone.
Last ten minutes.
One last chance to live.
All units, stand ready.
Jiasheng.
I've got this.
You should leave.
Nine minutes left.
Open the door.
Chief Phachai.
I never expected
the real backbone here
is you, the so-called puppet.
To be used by Nie Feng,
you really have guts.
Come on.
Kneel and beg me.
Being my dog
is much better
than being the Nie family's dog.
Chief Phachai.
You've deployed so many policemen.
I should agree to anything.
But just this one thing, I can't.
My knees are bad.
I can't kneel.
Ungrateful!
Get him!
Attention!
We are the Royal Palm Guard.
The Grand Princess commanded
all of you lay down your weapons
and submit.
Repeat.
Lay down your weapons
and submit.
Repeat.
Lay down your weapons and submit.
No!
Nobody move!
You punk.
You called the Royal Guards?
Darn it!
Nobody lives!
Feeling better now?
Chief Phachai.
Let me go!
Tu Jiasheng!
What's so funny?
You owe me a life.
Alright.
(In the third year
after Deep In The Bustle's founded,)
(used the Grand Princess' power,)
(I had Phachai, who intended
to annex Deep In The Bustle,)
(thrown in prison.)
(The price was breaking up
with her daughter.)
(Half a year later,)
(I met An Ruoxi.)
(In the two years that followed,)
(both my career
and love life flourished.)
(However, I didn't know)
(that the thing that'd change my life)
(was already approaching.)
(It was Deep In The Bustle's
fifth anniversary)
(when an uninvited guest arrived.)
(Vice leader
of the notorious Yanyue Gang,)
(Huang Weide.)
Hello, Mr. Huang.
It's such a wonderful day.
Mind if I show up uninvited?
Are you...
Call Tu Jiasheng out.
Tu Jiasheng.
(Huang Weide,
Vice Leader of Yanyue Gang)
Getting arrogant now?
You don't even greet me?
Tu Jiasheng!
Come out!
Mr. Huang?
(Deep In The Bustle)
Rolling in money now, huh?
- What brings you?
- You dare not come out to greet me?
I didn't know you were coming.
Wei.
Arrange a private bath.
Got it.
This way, Mr. Huang.
Private bath?
You think I'm that easy to fool?
Mr. Huang.
Not just a private bath.
You'll see.
Here, please.
Everything you want is inside.
Jiasheng.
Don't worry.
(An Ruoxi, Tu Jiasheng's fiancée)
I've arranged for the guests over there.
Okay, got it.
You go ahead.
Wait.
Who's she?
Mr. Huang.
She's our boss' wife.
Right.
Your woman?
You lucky man.
No wonder you ditched
the Grand Princess' daughter.
I want her tonight.
Mr. Huang.
Well.
We have better ones
inside.
I'll arrange for you.
Just go inside.
Rest assured.
Come on.
I only want her.
Her.
Or I'll shut this place down.
No problem.
I'll change and wait.
This way.
Jiasheng, I couldn't stop Huang Weide.
He rushed upstairs looking for An Ruoxi.
Ruoxi.
Listen to me.
Go upstairs. It'll be fine.
What about you?
It's okay.
Go to bed first.
Wait for me.
Be obedient.
Trust me.
Which room?
999, right?
Tu Jiasheng.
Where's your woman?
Tu Jiasheng!
Get out.
Hand her over.
Tu Jiasheng!
Mr. Huang.
Weren't the girls good?
Why did you come up?
You've got some nerve.
Tu Jiasheng!
I'm already changed.
Where's she?
- Calm down.
- Where?
Where is she?
You think you're hot stuff now?
Daring to mess with me, huh?
Calm down, Mr. Huang.
Calm down?
I'll kill you!
You believe it?
- Believe it?
- Jiasheng.
Get lost.
Let go! Let go!
Let go!
No!
Sweetheart.
Mr. Huang.
She's my woman.
- Do me a favor.
- Piss off!
Jiasheng!
Come on.
Tu Jiasheng!
Let go!
Let go of me!
Tu Jiasheng, you see it?
Your woman?
Help!
Here's Deep In The Bustle.
Stop playing coy.
Serve me well
and Tu Jiasheng can answer to Nie Feng.
Jiasheng.
♪If the heart can't hear the sorrow♪
♪It only makes everything look so fake♪
♪Your eyes resemble hers too much♪
♪Who makes me forget whom♪
♪The warmth in my heart is fading♪
♪Every glance feels like atonement♪
♪Ambiguity hidden in the night breeze♪
♪Blows away the chance to explain♪
♪I feel guilty♪
♪I'll have no regrets
even I leave quietly♪
♪Even in tears♪
♪It doesn't matter♪
♪We embrace in dreams♪
♪I let down all my defenses♪
♪Though the story has its end♪
♪I'll journey with you all my life♪