(Anonymous Email
A new email. Please check.)
(Don't ask who I am. I don't want
Ruoxi to die unjustly.)
Jiasheng,
Mr. Tang considers us insiders.
If we were outsiders
standing him up twice,
we'd never get another meeting.
Mr. Tang,
you're magnanimous,
so we toast you.
Mr. Tu,
Mr. Zhao,
what happened
last time did anger Mr. Tang.
They say third time's the charm,
yet we keep coming with sincerity.
You should at least
offer something real.
Jiasheng,
they're demanding something real.
Mr. Tang,
I hear you're interested
in joining ASEAN.
=The Glory Fades=
=Episode 20=
(Tamed)
I received
a mysterious email.
Wearing lipstick now.
Mr. Tu,
don't mock me.
I'm merely
a deputy governor.
ASEAN membership
is light-years away.
Bottoms up.
Mr. Tang,
good evening.
Today
I've brought two familiar faces.
Miss Yingwan
composed poetry with you last time.
Remember her?
And this,
Su Yunian,
last beauty contest's champion.
Good evening, Mr. Tang.
Two drinkers facing mountain blooms,
cup after cup.
Pleased to meet again.
Good.
Li Bai's poetry.
Excellent.
Mr. Tang, good evening.
We first met
at your inauguration.
Every word you spoke
made me realize
the weight behind
your rise to power
and your limitless potential.
Hope you enjoy tonight.
What happened to your hand?
Got hurt opening wine recently.
I was off-duty today,
but hearing you'd come,
and Mr. Tu values me
and especially you,
so I reported despite injury.
Hope you don't mind.
Not at all.
Miss Su, please sit.
You
should sit by Mr. Tu.
Since you're here,
I'll attend to you.
Mr. Tu won't mind.
Right, Mr. Tu?
Mr. Tang,
a toast to you.
But...
You're injured.
Don't drink.
Tang, see?
How considerate Mr. Tu is.
He truly cares for us.
I'll empty
my glass. Help yourself.
Yunian,
with this wine,
I toast Mr. Tang.
Mr. Tang,
welcome once more
to Deep In The Bustle.
(That night rescuing Su Yunian,)
(what did Mr. Tu's words really mean?)
Bai Manni,
I have a new shirt.
Change her into it.
Okay.
Chu Bai, step out first.
Leave this to me.
Mr. Tu,
it's inconvenient to leave her here.
And it disturbs your rest.
- Otherwise I should...
- Worried it's another trap?
No.
Room 999 is the safest.
I just...
You like her.
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of her.
Thank you, Mr. Tu.
Chu Bai.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Hello.
You're Chu Bai, right?
Who are you?
You don't need to know who I am.
I just want to ask you,
if you see the girl you love
holding someone else's arm,
how would you feel?
Are you crazy?
I'll hang up.
You can hang up on me,
but I want to tell you
that your beloved Su Yunian
has moved into Tu Jiasheng's Room 999
on the second floor.
And I
have a way
to make her leave Tu Jiasheng,
as long as you do what I say.
I've emailed you
the time and place.
I'll be waiting.
Mr. Tang,
this is my sincerity.
It's also
Deep In The Bustle's sincerity.
Bottoms up!
Now you see what a heroine looks like.
You
need more training.
Yes, Mr. Tang.
Um...
I need to use the restroom.
Mr. Tang,
we'll drink with you.
Come on.
Tang,
excuse me.
Where are you going, Mr. Tu?
Don't mind him.
Let's keep drinking.
Okay.
I brought you back to work
to keep you within my sight,
not for you to show off.
Show off?
I don't need to show off.
Besides,
I'm Madam now.
I can't exactly
embarrass you.
When I need to puke,
I even use another VIP room.
I made you Madam
to uncover the truth,
not to degrade yourself.
The truth?
Really want me to find the truth?
That day,
was what you said on the rooftop
really the whole truth?
I'm afraid
you're hiding a lot.
Forget it.
Let's go back to Room 999 first.
Room 999?
No need.
Stop!
Back to Room 999 first.
I'm going back to Mr. Tang.
Tu Jiasheng,
what are you doing?
Let go!
Tu Jiasheng,
let go!
let me go!
Hurry up!
Are you crazy, Tu Jiasheng?
I'm dizzy.
I'm going to throw up.
Enough, stop pretending.
How do you know that?
Because I
asked the waiter to switch your wine
to a soft drink.
Thank you.
Well,
aren't you overacting?
Throwing up is fine.
But you flailed around wildly.
And,
you even bit me.
You deserved that bite.
Tu Jiasheng,
after so many days here,
I've finally realized.
Those you wine and dine
outranks the last,
like mayors, governors,
Cabinet members, ASEAN officials,
each more influential than the other.
Yet when it comes
to the police's
so-called scapegoat theory,
you're indifferent. Silent and passive.
I've been waiting
for a reasonable explanation.
I told you I have my reasons.
Yes, you have your reasons.
The reason is you
can't exactly send yourself to prison.
Will you ever stop?
No, I won't.
I won't rest until I uncover the truth
and avenge Ruoxi.
Childish.
Correct.
I'm childish,
not as shrewd as you
with many connections.
At worst, I'll die and join her.
Otherwise, nothing will stop me.
No one's stopping you.
But we need coordination.
Fine.
Tell me.
How do we coordinate?
Remember what we said on the rooftop?
We must work together.
You,
play Madam.
- Good evening, Mr. Tu, Madam.
Chu Bai,
what are you doing here?
Waiting for you.
Here.
Same old thing.
Alright.
Say it.
Say what?
Say whatever you want.
You are dating
Tu Jiasheng?
You're about to become
the new Madam?
Is it true?
Do you wish it were true?
No.
Remember what we said on the rooftop?
We must work together.
You,
play Madam.
Su Yunian!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What did you say?
I asked
if you're really dating Tu Jiasheng.
Yes.
Just last night.
Why?
For money.
He's wealthy, powerful
and handsome.
Though he's over a decade older,
that's hardly an issue.
Satisfied with my answer?
Yes.
Brutally honest.
I...
I didn't expect this.
Neither did I.
Alright.
If nothing else,
I'll leave.
Su Yunian.
Take care.
♪Even the starlight has dimmed♪
♪Leaving only me behind♪
♪Awake alone♪
♪What will tomorrow bring♪
♪Perhaps I was wrong♪
♪Finally saying it out loud brings
some relief♪
♪I only wanted to play♪
♪The role you loved♪
♪Even if the ending is too bitter♪
♪Turns out I would cry♪
♪Turns out you would hurt♪
♪Those rights and wrongs from the past
don't matter anymore♪
♪How much I miss the joy
we once shared together♪
♪If only we could go back to the past♪
♪Perhaps at this very moment♪
♪I can finally understand♪
♪What to love and hate
are all my choices♪
♪Some words I don't say♪
♪Doesn't mean I no longer care♪
♪I just wish to hear 'I love you'
one more time♪
Hello, this is Chu Bai.
Tell me what to do.
♪If the heart can't hear the sorrow♪
♪It only makes everything look so fake♪
♪Your eyes resemble hers too much♪
♪Who makes me forget whom♪
♪The warmth in my heart is fading♪
♪Every glance feels like atonement♪
♪Ambiguity hidden in the night breeze♪
♪Blows away the chance to explain♪
♪I feel guilty♪
♪I'll have no regrets
even I leave quietly♪
♪Even in tears♪
♪It doesn't matter♪
♪We embrace in dreams♪
♪I let down all my defenses♪
♪Though the story has its end♪
♪I'll journey with you all my life♪