(2005: One Week Before An Ruoxi's Death)
Look.
Jiasheng,
I want to go out to clear my head.
Clear your head?
Where do you want to go?
I haven't decided yet.
I just want to go out for a walk.
No.
Wait for me.
The reconciliation is
the day after tomorrow.
You can go after that.
I'll go with you.
I just want to be alone.
It's dangerous to go alone.
So you do know
the current situation is dangerous.
Ruoxi,
as long as I promised you something,
I will definitely do it.
But
you have to give me time.
Is that so?
When Qin Wei wanted to do that business,
you also promised me
you wouldn't touch it.
But what happened?
Got roped into that mess anyway.
I know you had no choice.
Feng forced it,
so you had no choice.
Right?
I'm just a little tired,
sinking deeper
into this world of debauchery.
Just let me go out for a few days.
I'll adjust on my own.
Maybe I'll feel better.
Okay?
=The Glory Fades=
=Episode 5=
(The Ice Ball Game)
(2006: Su Yunian's Second Day at Work)
Mr. He.
Yunyan.
I've missed you so much!
You've become prettier.
Come on, girls!
Let's begin!
Hello, Mr. He.
Distinguished guests,
I'm Jing from the Ren Class
and from Luosen City.
Hello, Mr. He.
Hello, distinguished guests.
Okay.
No more hello.
Yunyan,
what's going on?
Why are they all
newcomers of the Ren Class?
Forget about the Tian Class.
At least,
you should arrange those from Yun Class.
Mr. He,
you're wronging Yunyan.
These are all newcomers.
They're very fresh.
Get lost!
How dare an assistant talk to me!
Don't block my view!
Yunyan,
do you think I'm stupid?
Let me tell you.
Stop messing around here.
They're still fresh?
If I wanted fresh ones,
would I need to come here?
Among these girls,
tell me
who has connections.
You?
Who has?
Do you have any?
Not to mention higher-ups,
which of them has connections
higher than my father's?
Mr. He,
just calm down.
In Deep In The Bustle,
we climb up step by step.
Cut the nonsense.
Peter.
Yunyan,
let me tell you,
either find me some girls
with high status,
or promote me to the Tian Level.
Do you hear me?
Don't be in such a hurry.
I'll go apply right now.
I'm going now.
Mr. He,
look at that waitress over there.
Her resources are unimaginably vast.
You few, stay here.
Keep Mr. He and the guests
happy with drinks.
Go.
The rest of you, come with me.
Hello, Feng.
Let me say this one more time.
Call me
"Boss".
Yes, Boss.
Go ahead.
That's more like it.
Unless Lu and the others are present,
always use this title,
"Boss".
Yes, Boss.
Stay away from
He Mike's project.
I'll have someone take over from you.
I've taken over the project.
What comes next is...
Do I need to repeat myself?
No, Boss.
What a pity for my string of beads.
Tu Jiasheng...
(Nie Feng,
Founder of Deep In The Bustle Nightclub)
Book the tickets.
It's time to return home.
Come on,
sit here and drink with me.
This is for you.
No need, sir.
I don't drink.
I'll focus on providing you
with the best service.
Interesting.
Mr. He,
her name is Su Yunian.
She's new, a top student.
Most importantly,
she's a newbie,
but a little quick-tempered.
A newbie with quick temper.
Not bad.
I like that.
Come on,
sit here and drink with me.
Don't push your luck.
I have plenty of money.
I'm sorry, Mr. He.
As a VIP room attendant,
I'll provide the service I should.
You're pushing it.
Mr. He,
she's just a waitress.
Please don't stoop to her level.
Let's play a new game, Mr. He.
Mr. He.
Okay.
Let's
play a new game.
Lu, are you busy?
No.
What's up, Jiasheng?
Come with me for a patrol downstairs.
You sound like something's wrong.
See you there.
Ms. Bai.
Ms. Bai,
today
all VIP rooms are booked.
Two rooms are occupied.
Mr. Peter from Haiwei,
and Allens from Swire Group.
Oh, right,
a Victoria's Secret show starts
after midnight.
Okay.
Ms. Bai,
Ruoxi is gone ages ago.
I'd like to go see...
Get out!
Su Yunian, what's wrong with you?
No, Yunyan.
Inside just now...
How many days have you
even been working?
On your very first day,
you argued with a guest,
and now you get kicked out?
Do you even want this job?
Listen to me.
Inside just now, they...
They what?
The customer is God!
Got it?
So what if they're God?
They're human.
Shouldn't act like beasts.
You
- Yunyan.
- are talking back?
Who's in the Earl room today?
So brazen?
It's Peter from Haiwei
and Mr. He.
You don't know.
Since his father
got promoted,
he's downright outrageous!
But what can we do?
He has a powerful father backing him.
I heard he went to ring the bell
at NASDAQ this time.
And even came back with a private jet.
So you see,
for such a big spender,
we have to serve him well.
Right?
Tell me
what exactly happened inside?
This is our GM, Ms. Bai.
She's asking you a question.
Hello, Ms. Bai.
(According to Ruoxi's diary,)
(this must be Bai Manni,)
(the GM at Deep In The Bustle,
her counterpart.)
She's asking you a question.
Ms. Bai,
inside just now,
Mr. He forced me
to stuff ice balls in there.
I'm here to be a waitress,
not to be
their crazy outlet toy.
Go fix your hair.
I'll go check.
(Earl)
Enough?
Enough? Enough?
Are all the girls here so feisty?
Calm down, Mr. He.
Ms. Bai,
you came at the perfect time.
Look at your girls here.
Is putting some ice in her chest
so hard?
Fine, skip it.
Just upgrade me
to the top-floor VIP room.
My dad and Mr. Tu are deep partners.
Is upgrading a room this difficult too?
Mr. He,
let's discuss it later.
As you know,
girls at Deep In The Bustle
are exceptionally talented
and beautiful.
What's that got to do
with me?
I think her chest is too small
with bad visual appeal.
Why wouldn't I put it here?
Why?
Besides,
I prefer things ice-cold.
Like this whiskey,
no matter how fine
your winery's vintage,
no matter how rare the year,
if it's not chilled,
I don't want to drink it. Okay?
Okay.
Ms. Bai,
no wonder you're the GM.
Actually,
there's a simpler solution.
Why don't you
sit down and have a drink with me?
I'd be deeply honored.
She's our GM. I'll drink with you.
Get lost!
What's it to you?
Having me accompany you
would cost a lot.
Come on,
don't talk about money.
I've got plenty of money.
Money's no object for me.
Ms. Bai,
please.
Let go!
Bai Manni, are you insane?
Know what you're doing?
Go.
Get up.
Ten ice balls, one million.
It's premium ice, so add 50,000 each.
A total of 1.5 million.
Here's the money.
All on the card.
A small penalty for a big lesson.
Not exactly bone-chilling, is it?
Remember this.
The top floor of Deep In The Bustle
isn't somewhere for anyone.
Today, yours are bigger than mine.
Bai Manni!
♪If the heart can't hear the sorrow♪
♪It only makes everything look so fake♪
♪Your eyes resemble hers too much♪
♪Who makes me forget whom♪
♪The warmth in my heart is fading♪
♪Every glance feels like atonement♪
♪Ambiguity hidden in the night breeze♪
♪Blows away the chance to explain♪
♪I feel guilty♪
♪I'll have no regrets
even I leave quietly♪
♪Even in tears♪
♪It doesn't matter♪
♪We embrace in dreams♪
♪I let down all my defenses♪
♪Though the story has its end♪
♪I'll journey with you all my life♪