Look.
Yours looks better.
Mine looks good, huh?
I tried to talk you out of it,
but you insisted on this one.
Regretting it now.
I'm always like this.
Never hold onto the best.
It's okay.
Just a manicure.
At worst, remove and redo it.
I'll go with you.
So good to have you,
Ruoxi.
What?
Why so serious?
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Alright.
Let me tell you some good news.
He promised me.
He promised you?
To leave Deep In The Bustle
and live an ordinary life with you?
But regarding Feng,
he's still a bit worried.
He'll figure something out.
Let me show you this.
What is this?
Well.
I planned one for you, one for me,
so we could make two necklaces later.
Now that I see how happy
you are with Mr. Tu,
I'll step aside.
Here, press it.
I'll make you a necklace.
You're a bit jealous?
Let's do it together.
He's just a man.
Doesn't know about female bonding.
I'll go first.
Done.
=The Glory Fades=
=Episode 33=
(Truth and Lies)
I want to hear it from you directly.
Did you kill An Ruoxi?
Yes.
Why?
Because she wanted too much.
Because she became
an obstacle for the Grand Princess.
Tu Jiasheng could never leave
Deep In The Bustle.
Yet she stubbornly tried to change it
using her own strength.
Then the only result is her death.
Meng Yin,
I never thought
it would be you.
I never imagined
you served the Grand Princess.
Ruoxi,
I was sent to Deep In The Bustle
to watch Tu Jiasheng
to sever his tie with young lady.
After you appeared,
seemed he might keep his promise.
I never expected
that I was merely Tu Jiasheng's
tool to appease the Grand Princess.
The second time
he begged the Grand Princess
was for Nie Feng's father 's case.
The Grand Princess set one condition:
He had to work for her from then on.
How dare you try to influence him
at such a time
to betray the Grand Princess?
Betrayal
is not permitted.
I never intended
to disrupt the Grand Princess' plans.
I just
wanted him
to commit fewer evil deeds
and live with me
a simple, ordinary life.
How naive.
How utterly naive you are!
Has he ever done fewer evil deeds?
To climb the ladder,
he has done any dirty deed back then.
You just don't know
how many lives he has taken.
You think refusing a few deals
for the Grand Princess
will spare him a few levels in hell?
No way, listen, An Ruoxi!
You're too naive.
He built Deep In The Bustle.
He can't just abandon it
for a simple life with you.
Don't you understand?
I understand now.
But it's too late.
Right?
I fall in love with Tu Jiasheng,
but I don't regret it.
Whether I'm a tool,
a puppet
or just a passerby in his life,
it doesn't matter.
After all,
love is beautiful.
Meng Yin,
you've never loved.
You wouldn't understand.
I've never loved?
Is the person you love
worth dying for?
Ruoxi,
if you weren't you,
and I weren't me,
we'd surely have more time.
Meng Yin,
I don't blame you.
But you know
I have a sister.
She might track you down.
Promise me.
Protect her.
Okay?
Pah!
Meng Yin,
Tu Jiasheng used Ruoxi.
What did that have to do with her?
I was truly blind.
Ruoxi was blind too
to be friends with someone like you.
I promised Ruoxi
to protect you.
But if you still investigate,
you'll end up like her.
Understand?
No need.
Just kill me.
Meng Yin,
you're pathetic.
No one loves you.
In this world,
you only live for yourself.
Su Yunian,
I'll say it again.
Ruoxi asked me to protect you.
Protect me?
Have a murderer protect me?
Ridiculous.
Believe it or not.
Kill me.
I'm not like you.
Someone loves me.
At least,
Ruoxi loved me.
You'll get what you deserve.
You deserve it.
- Pah!
- Su Yunian,
calm down.
Listen to me,
from now on...
Are you okay?
Chu Bai.
Feng,
we're both men.
No more nonsense.
Speak.
What do you plan to do?
That's more like it.
Jiasheng,
attitude
matters a lot.
I always say,
my left hand
can lift you up,
but my right hand
is even stronger.
Come on,
Jiasheng.
Let me
tell you my plan.
But before that,
let's first pay respects
to eldest brother.
Let's go.
That's right.
Worship Liu Bei more.
After all, he aimed for the world,
while Guan Yu only guarded Jingzhou.
Feng,
I admire Guan Yu.
Then I'll have to make you
hit the rough patch.
♪If the heart can't hear the sorrow♪
♪It only makes everything look so fake♪
♪Your eyes resemble hers too much♪
♪Who makes me forget whom♪
♪The warmth in my heart is fading♪
♪Every glance feels like atonement♪
♪Ambiguity hidden in the night breeze♪
♪Blows away the chance to explain♪
♪I feel guilty♪
♪I'll have no regrets
even I leave quietly♪
♪Even in tears♪
♪It doesn't matter♪
♪We embrace in dreams♪
♪I let down all my defenses♪
♪Though the story has its end♪
♪I'll journey with you all my life♪