Fine.
I'll have them make you something.
It won't take long.
No need.
It's fine.
Your noodles are the best.
The sweet talker.
Yunian.
Here, put this on.
You should head back.
I can manage myself.
Absolutely not.
It's so late.
You're a young woman.
I'm taking you home.
Tell me where you live.
It's okay.
I'll call a ride later.
You've got lots of guests waiting.
Go on back.
Tell you what, Yunian.
I'll arrange a car.
Tell the driver your address
to take you home.
- Alright?
- No need.
Let's go, Yunian.
You've had too much.
Come with me.
Thank you.
You made me believe
that a place like this
still have genuine feelings.
You gave me the confidence to stay.
Thank you, Ruxue.
Thank you.
Take it easy.
Haven't you noticed
that Feng and Jiasheng
seem a bit off lately?
It'd be weird if they get along.
Feng's autocratic.
Jiasheng's tough.
Have they ever got along?
You men are so oblivious.
Don't you think
they talk less and less these days?
Other than when
you three reconcile
monthly,
do they ever talk privately?
We're guys.
Why would we chat for no reason?
No.
Ever since An Ruoxi's death,
they've been off.
After Ruoxi's death,
Jiasheng has changed.
Su Yunian
looks so much like An Ruoxi.
Why's Jiasheng so hung up on one woman?
Not like you,
through all the beauties,
not a trace left on you.
That's only because a certain someone
isn't in that garden.
If she were there,
I'd never leave her.
Easy, Yunian.
Slow down.
Steps ahead.
Steps!
Watch your step!
Steady!
Slow down!
The car's here.
Up front.
Come on.
Let's go.
Stop the car!
Stop!
Ruxue, whose car is that?
Chu Bai, why are you running out?
Where are you taking Su Yunian?
She's drunk.
I'm getting her a ride home.
Don't worry.
Get back to work.
Thank you, Lu.
What are you thanking me for?
I know.
If you hadn't
protected me,
I might have
made the same mistake as Yunyan did.
Don't even know
if I'd still be alive.
Haiwei East Road.
Thanks.
Don't worry.
I'll get you there.
Mr. Lin,
why is it you?
=The Glory Fades=
=Episode 14=
(A Sheep in Tiger's Den)
I thought
maybe I was not good enough.
Compared to the girls we selected,
I just had an ordinary
undergraduate degree.
So then I
studied hard,
took advanced courses,
and prepared for grad school.
Later I felt
maybe I was not pretty enough.
Compared to our girls,
I'm just average.
So then I
spent money
on treatments and upkeep,
learned dance and practiced yoga.
Later I felt
I didn't understand him.
Like that kind
of care and love for him
couldn't reach his heart.
So I would
find ways
to try to
understand him better.
But it didn't work.
No.
Wrong is just wrong.
An Ruoxi was the right one.
You really dosed her heavily.
From Deep In The Bustle
to the hotel shortly,
Su Yunian
hasn't regained consciousness yet.
Don't worry.
This girl
will be handled perfectly.
(Chu Bai)
The right person
can do no wrong.
That's why the noodles
you make are the best.
Lu,
I understand your feelings,
but we're not from the same world.
Tell me.
Since Su Yunian looks
so much like An Ruoxi,
why did Jiasheng drive her away?
Couldn't they just be together?
Perhaps for Jiasheng,
there's only one An Ruoxi.
True.
There's only one An Ruoxi.
No one can replace her.
Come in.
(LXR Hotel, Changqingtai City)
Sleep with you and get paid?
Is there such a good deal?
It'll be a fun night.
(Three days later)
(Deep In The Bustle)
(Dragon Soars, Phoenix Sings
Beauty Contest)
Ms. Bai, I didn't expect
Lin Shen would seize...
Bai Ruxue!
A sheep in tiger's den.
Don't you understand that?
Considering you once helped me,
I'll remind you one more time.
At Deep In The Bustle,
Jiasheng is in charge.
Remember that.
I know I was wrong.
I'll apologize to her now.
Something like this
can't be fixed with an apology.
Where's Su Yunian?
Su Yu...
She
is getting makeup done.
Should be ready soon.
You still look a bit pale today.
I'm fine.
Thanks for your concern.
Not good to be a server?
Why insist on joining
the Beauty Contest?
Since I'm here,
I have to climb step by step.
This path
isn't easy.
If you can't climb up
or accidentally fall,
it'll hurt a lot.
Just tell me.
Make me look as much like An Ruoxi
as possible.
Okay?
There's only one An Ruoxi.
Even if her own sister
couldn't take her place.
By the way,
can you make friendship bracelets?
I have a really nice bracelet cord.
It's broken.
Can you show it to me?
I might be able to fix it.
Find it yourself.
You and Meng Yin became good friends,
because you're both incredibly genuine.
People in our family
are sincere right down to the bone.
Just look at you.
Being at Deep In The Bustle for so long,
you haven't changed.
Look at these stones we just picked up.
They lay at the bottom of the sea long,
washed ashore,
and now under the sunlight,
they shine even brighter
and more translucent.
I want to be like these stones.
The deeper in the dye vat,
the clearer I must be.
Drill a hole in them,
and they could probably
be strung into a lovely bracelet.
I'll braid you a decorative cord for it.
Ruoxi,
trust my craftsmanship and taste.
I do.
I absolutely do.
Once done, I'll give it to Meng Yin.
She'll love it.
Just a few stones?
Isn't that a bit half-hearted?
It's the thought that counts.
She understands me.
Help me pick one.
Which one looks best?
Well then,
this one.
Let me tell you something.
You
are Ms. Bai's top recommendation.
Later,
go with whoever
takes charge of you.
Do not wander off.
Do you understand?
Exactly!
Especially Room 999 on the top floor.
You should never enter it.
Did you hear?
That girl days ago...
Yanzi,
wash my makeup sponge.
Can't hold her tongue,
so I sent her out to reflect.
(Meng Yin was Ruoxi's best friend)
(at Deep In The Bustle.)
(She always said)
(they were more like
each other's shadow.)
(They rarely needed many words)
(to share a silent understanding.)
(Look at it now.)
(Meng Yin)
(is incredibly cautious)
(and treads carefully.)
(If I confess my relationship
with An Ruoxi,)
(will she help me?)
Ms. Bai.
That's enough.
Almost there.
Not bad.
You look more like her now.
Go downstairs.
Alright, let's go.
Follow me.
I'll take you down.
The Beauty Contest
officially begins now.
Let's welcome all the beauties
to make their dazzling entrance.
Dear guests,
tonight's moon glows softly
for our beauties,
and the stage shines bright
with their elegance.
After rounds of competition,
we finally arrive
at the most anticipated moment.
The final group, six peerless stunners,
are taking the stage for the finale.
Chosen from...
Mr. Tu,
Mr. Zhao,
I carry little weight
and my words are insignificant.
Being stood up
is hardly worth mentioning.
But I do not come alone.
I stand here representing
the trust of 5,300,000 people
in Danding State to negotiate
this cooperation!
Deep In The Bustle
is powerful.
I know that.
Whether this deal succeeds
or fails is one thing,
but
the very first step between people
should be
sincerity and trust, right?
Yes.
Tang.
Mr. Tang,
I got a last-minute notice from home.
They told us something happened at home.
We absolutely didn't mean
to stand you up
or cancel on you.
Right, Mr. Tu?
Tang,
in this world,
sometimes we're driven by circumstances.
To be honest with you,
I came back suddenly that day
for the Grand Princess.
I wanted to explain,
but it is classified.
So
please understand.
Since that's the case,
let's not dwell on it.
Let's share this drink.
Tang,
please take a look
at these beauties tonight,
appraise their spirit,
and guide us.
Deep In The Bustle
has no shortage of talent.
Especially that female literature major,
reciting poetry effortlessly.
As for classics and histories,
she speaks them fluently.
Oh,
especially Miss Su,
a mere waitress
with such literary refinement.
Impressive.
Truly impressive.
Lu,
what's going on?
Where's that talent?
My fault.
That's on me.
Tang,
I'll arrange for her right now.
But Miss Su...
I understand this.
Miss Su
is Mr. Tu's girl.
Naturally kept secluded.
Not anyone can request to see her
and expect her presence.
Tang,
it's crowded tonight.
Security is messy.
I'll go check.
Good.
If you fancy any beauty,
bid boldly.
I wouldn't dare.
Chat with Mr. Tu.
Alright.
Jiasheng.
Take care, Mr. Zhao.
Distinguished guests,
please prepare your bidding paddles.
If you admire this
22-year-old,
double-degree beauty,
show your sincerity.
Let's eagerly anticipate.
Please bid.
Three hundred thousand.
Three hundred thirty thousand.
Three fifty.
Four fifty.
One million.
Seems our esteemed guests
all greatly admire
(Display it on the LED screen?)
this young
and beautiful
college girl.
Any higher bids?
Please.
Turns out she's a tramp.
Stop pretending to be pure.
We trusted
Deep In The Bustle's reputation.
College girl? Really?
But she looks like
nothing but a hussy.
If she stays at Deep In The Bustle,
we won't visit again.
Too dirty.
♪If the heart can't hear the sorrow♪
♪It only makes everything look so fake♪
♪Your eyes resemble hers too much♪
♪Who makes me forget whom♪
♪The warmth in my heart is fading♪
♪Every glance feels like atonement♪
♪Ambiguity hidden in the night breeze♪
♪Blows away the chance to explain♪
♪I feel guilty♪
♪I'll have no regrets
even I leave quietly♪
♪Even in tears♪
♪It doesn't matter♪
♪We embrace in dreams♪
♪I let down all my defenses♪
♪Though the story has its end♪
♪I'll journey with you all my life♪