A Piece of Your Mind
Relief supplies, medicine and food,
10 boxes each?
Okay. Hurry up and tell me.
I'm busy. I have to go catch someone.
This person was all crazy about using the
recording studio, but he never showed up.
He doesn't even answer his
phone! I have to find him for sure.
Yes. Okay. That's it?
Relief Supplies: Blanket, toothbrush,
toothpaste, soap, towel, toilet paper. Medicine
Kit: Scissors, dressing, bandage, cold
medicine, painkillers, diarrhea medicine
Food: Instant noodles, water,
seaweed, instant rice, rice, fruit
So, when are you coming back, Grandma?
Do you like it there that much?
You like it better than me?
How could you be like that?
She's old now but still
travels around all the time.
You try and say something!
She listens to you.
I'm so worried.
Okay. I'll try and talk to her.
Don't worry.
Why do you have no energy?
I'll send you an email
of what grandma needs.
It's so loud! Where are you?
Outside.
Outside where?
You know where you're roaming about right?
Don't space out and go somewhere weird.
Soon Ho.
Why is it so hard?
You never say things like that.
Han Seo Woo! Where were you?
I didn't see you there.
Anyway, Kang In Wook is not here.
- I'll try and call him.
- He doesn't answer any calls.
That guy!
Maybe he has other plans.
No, no. He just left.
He couldn't wait those few minutes.
I'm going to catch him for sure.
Can I go home now?
Yes.
Something's going on, right?
Is the recording studio empty?
Yes.
I'll go for a little bit.
Why?
Recently I've had the best sleep there.
What are you talking about? Okay.
He doesn't need a house.
I need a house.
I thought you were going?
I'll just open up the recording studio.
Leave after doing that.
Kang In Wook! I'm so mad!
I just ran out without even
being able to wash my face!
Stop it.
I'm telling you to end your
long one-sided love right here.
You said you didn't know what ending means,
and
you didn't understand why you had to end,
right?
My one-sided love has at least 1% chance.
You're probably wondering,
who says I have 1% chance?
It's because he's alive.
You don't even have 1% chance.
So stop.
I'm sorry, so I"m going to stop too.
I'm going to stop even my
1% chance of one-sided love.
You, should have stopped earlier.
Did you turn on the music?
The music playing now, are good
music for falling asleep to, I heard.
Sleep well.
A Piece of Your Mind
Episode Six
You came out to see me in?
You ate dinner, right?
Yes. You came out knowing I was tired,
right?
This feels nice.
You're having a hard time again?
Yes.
A roommate is supposed to come in tonight.
Since when were we roommates?
Everyone except you two are roommates.
I don't want to become attached to you.
The word "roommate" doesn't
really have the attached feeling.
Oh! He's coming.
Student Bae Jin Soo?
Hello. I am Bae Jin Soo.
Oh. You're wearing a
padded jacket in April.
Do you have anymore stuff?
Concert... I think it's you.
I used to be in a orchestra
unit in medical school.
We asked if you have any more things?
More will be delivered
tomorrow by a delivery service.
Your gown is so dirty!
Take it off as soon as you head in.
I'll wash it for you.
The gown that a doctor
wears should be clean.
I'm just a student though.
Suna from Senegal said she
became an athlete swimmer.
I will do my best. Take care.
I love you, Teacher. I miss you.
I'm so proud of this kid
who has been struggling.
Something happened to you, right?
You're calling me and reading a letter.
I got caught.
When that happens,
you just have to read anything.
It will help you.
That's why I had them all
addressed to you and Soon Ho, but
Soon Ho never reads.
I guess she doesn't have
any challenges or heartbreaks.
It's good to not have any.
When will you come?
Soon Ho worries about you a lot.
I'll go when it's time.
Let her know I'll be
visiting before it gets hot.
If it gets hot here,
it's too much for me to handle.
It's already nice.
4 am
4:02 am
A leaf,
without anyone noticing,
I was just curious.
About what?
Kim Ji Soo. Moon Ha Won's fixed point.
The center coordinate which remains
no matter how things may be distorted.
The sense of urgency which is pushing
Ha Won's technical
skill to its outermost limit.
Perhaps it is this person. If it is,
all research must have
started from Kim Ji Soo.
Testing of Kim Ji Soo device has finished.
The hint regarding the next step is here.
Get rid of it. Discard everything
now when I'm watching you.
Right now. Immediately.
Program deletion in progress...
Deleting the program...
I erased everything.
- I don't understand.
- Of course.
How frustrating it is to not be able to
understand with that good brain of yours.
So separate yourself.
Go over there.
R2 team.
That's right,
R2 team. You know it well. Join them.
They will be happy to see you there.
I don't want to.
If it's somewhere Moon Ha Won and
Kim Hoon are not, I'm not going anywhere.
Kim Ji Soo? Who is she? Who?
I don't have any interest at all.
Don't have any interest.
Hey that Jin Hwan. The
kid is such a clever bastard.
The fixed point never changes, but!
It should satisfy the conditions
to be the Lefschetz numbers...
and it only exist in the condition
interval and Anti-Ha Won interval...
Sit up.
Lean here.
The veins in your eyeballs
are about to explode.
You can't sleep again?
You need sleep though.
Student Jin Soo!
Are you going to have breakfast?
He must be really tired.
You're sleeping with the
gown on! It's creating wrinkles!
Take it off and sleep!
What? What's going on?
I'll take it off him!
Let's do it together.
Oh no, Jin Soo!
What's wrong with you?
Look at this. I have to wash it again.
Director, where is Teacher Kang?
I've known In Wook for a long time.
This is the first recording we've
done with a major record label.
Of all times,
he has a slump and feels betrayed.
In Wook is not in the right
sense of mind right now.
He can just do it by himself, then.
That is....
I've never heard that answer before.
We record when we're
performing at our best,
not when we're at our lowest.
Then after setting a goal, he can
just work to bring his skill up to that.
It's easy for you to say.
Let's do it! Let's do that!
Will you do that for me?
If the roots aren't rotten,
then it will live.
Where is Teacher Kang?
In the studio.
Really.
- Hello Teacher Kang.
- Turn the lights off.
You don't have anything to tell me?
About what?
About yesterday.
Are you not the one who
made all the commotion
about opening up
the recording studio?
I ran like a crazy person!
How long did you want me to wait?
- You couldn't wait the 10 minutes?
- I waited for 20 minutes.
This or that. They're the same.
If you weren't going to
wait then at least text me!
Turn off the lights and leave.
I'm just getting started.
In your slump, do you know the
Studio Moon recording room or not?
Record by yourself,
and release an album. What's the problem?
With Han Seo Woo, our recording
studio will help you as much as possible.
All you have to do is have the right mind.
You have my business card, right?
- I gave you my card.
- I have it!
Now you seem like a person
after yelling out like that.
Give me a call!
I found Kang In Wook and
talked business with him.
Did you see the schedule?
No.
Did you sleep at your house in Seoul?
I have a house in Seoul?
The house where you
slept in after drinking.
That house! No.
Wait. No. I can just live there.
But there's someone living there already.
I can just make it mine.
What about the person
actually living there?
It's family matters.
I asked if you saw the schedule.
I'm on my way to take
a look at the schedule.
Don't go. It's a audio recording.
- That...
- Yes.
Like Kim Ji Soo. You don't want to do it,
right?
Let's just check on the time
and give it to someone else.
Since we only need to
lend them the recording studio.
I'll do it.
STUDIO MOON, Seoul Jongrogu Sejongro 12-9
Hello-
Can I take a picture? To put on Instagram?
Someone introduced me to this place.
If I do end up staying here,
save the room at the end for me.
Uh,
your face is showing. It's still showing.
We'll start with simple consonants
and vowels, and then some phrases.
I just have to read this?
Yes. If you want to stop at any
point you just have to stay 'Stop'.
We can record them again.
They say I can really
communicate with myself.
Is there really a device like that?
Have you seen it?
I signed a contract that says I won't
tell anyone about the recordings.
So you've seen it.
Excuse me, that.
You don't have to use this.
But I want to. It looks cool.
Hello. Hello.
When I give you the
signal you can start reading.
ABCDEFG, HIJKLMN...
- OPQRS....
- Let's try and read a bit more slower.
A, B, C, D...
Sorry. Let's go a little
bit faster than that.
A, B, C...
I was finished,
and the winter was about to end too,
so one day I went to the
southern coast without any plan.
Spring already came over there
so it was the peak season for sea bass,
trouts and blue crabs.
Um, just a moment.
- Shall we take a break?
- I want to put it on Instagram.
I have to post at 1 pm.
It's good now.
We'll resume with the recording then.
Where was the page again..
I can't see the words very well.
- Where is the garbage?
- Give it to me.
Sorry.
I can't do this twice. I'm so tired.
You've emptied the room at the end, right?
Empty it.
Yes.
She remembers.
There was one from Heikin...
Where did it go?
Take it.
Mr. Dawn, the file name for the
voice recording is Kim Min Jung.
Where are you Mr. Dawn?
Me, I'm Mr. Dawn.
So you've missed Mr. Dawn a lot.
That's...
I'm talking to that
person from that time.
Exactly. That person. Is me.
You must be craving coffee since
you just woke up. What would you like?
I didn't sleep! I was just thinking.
Okay.
You're okay with having a cup
of coffee with Mr. Dawn, right?
Why are you glaring at Mr. Dawn?
- You cried, didn't you?
- No.
Your face right now
looks like you were crying.
I don't cry.
How can a person not cry?
Oh, I've cried once when my mom
put mustard into my cold noodles.
I don't have any other memory of crying.
It's hot.
I did come earlier than the assigned rent
time, but I'll leave after I drink this.
I'll leave. I'm done.
It's hot!
Are you going to quit?
Don't have to quit though...
Yes, I'm going to show
you the sample of quitting.
I started it for my own happiness,
but now it doesn't matter.
I'm going to quit it for sure.
Because Ha Won, that guy,
isn't an ordinary man.
I told you that he's meticulous,
wait, no, not meticulous, I think.
It's for your own happiness, Seo Woo,
then why should you quit it?
Ha Won is just Ha Won,
so in case of your 1%,
please just leave it alone, free.
Don't pluck it yourself.
Ha Won will do as you told him to do,
so you don't have to show him the sample.
Then, I'll leave...
It's Mr. Dawn's time,
so Mr. Dawn must clean
the room before he leaves.
And don't touch my stuffs
without permission, and...
where is my bag?
Should I leave the door open?
Close it, please.
It was dark,
so I thought you would be scared...
Where is Chang Seop?
He will stay overnight at his parents'
house to take care of something.
What's up with him?
Come home late tomorrow.
Why?
Chang Seop... will take a day off tomorrow.
You're bad at taking a hint, you know...
Ah, I see, okay.
The snug time for two of you only?
As we have a vacant room,
why don't you move up?
I'll give you a discount.
Not yet.
Unnie, if I say 1%,
would it be a possibility or a false hope?
If you think of it as "as much as 1%",
it is a possibility,
and if you think of it as "a mere 1%",
then it's a false hope.
What is it about?
One-sided love.
You're doing it by yourself already,
so why don't you keep it to yourself?
I'm going to throw it out there.
I'll throw this 1% over there,
and I'll keep watching how it survives,
if it really survives,
or if it just crawls and falls down.
I'll raise it strongly.
Are you saying to keep doing it or not?
Mr. Kang
Sweetheart! Sweetheart!
Mr. Kang said he would
work with you for his record.
I suggested it. Wow, it's awesome!
Mr. Kang, this is Han Seo Woo.
I heard from Ms. Moon,
I will do my best.
See you later in the afternoon.
Why did Ji Soo have
Han Seo Woo's number...?
Why Han Seo Woo?
Employee - Choi Soo
Ji / NH Nonghyup Bank
What's up?
It was a good time
to get served with
breakfast by Eun Joo every morning,
wasn't it?
Have you been doing well?
You're not concerned about me,
so why bother?
I just asked.
Why are you having breakfast here?
Worked overnight.
Are you doing well with Eun Joo Unnie?
You're not even curious about it,
so don't bother.
Never mind, then.
What's wrong?
Seeing you having a
hard time because of me,
- I feel bad. - What?
- Frankly speaking,
you liked me, didn't you?
Isn't that why you were so upset and left?
- Are you crazy?
- These days,
there are a lot of girls
who like me at my office too.
The older I get,
the cooler I become. I'm that type.
My broad chest makes my suit look so great.
As my status gets better suddenly,
now I reflect on me whether
I made a wrong choice too.
You son of... I told you I'm
going to kill you if you break up!
Undies, socks, shirts...
This is the person who made
a contract for the end room.
I'm going to move in today.
C-contract? I haven't made it though.
HEY! You guys even received
my deposit fee. That boy!
Chang Seop or whatever!
How dare you try to con me...
(in informal/rude speech) Hey,
didn't you receive my deposit?
W-W-What did you say?
I did. I've wired that deposit
to your account right away.
Check the balance.
I've selected a person
who wouldn't have breakfast.
Why did you make such a contract?
Why are you making a
fuss when I helped you?
We should see the person's personality
and character before making a decision!
Since when did you check the
character before letting a tenant in?
I've worked so hard for this!
Damn.
Damn it!
Hello.
Earlier... The phone call...
- (in formal speech) Let's go.
- Yes.
(in informal speech) I clearly
said I wanted the room at the end.
When.. did you...?
(in formal speach) I've mentioned several
times that I want the room at the end.
Uh, well...
When did you...,
how many times?
I SAID TO THAT GIRL IN
THE RECORDING STUDIO!
Well, since it turns out this way,
please leave,
we already have a tenant in that room.
I'll send the
deposit back to you.
(in informal/rude speach) I won't leave.
Until you give me that room,
I won't move a step from here.
I clearly told that girl in the recording
studio about the room at the end.
A girl in the recording studio...
Must be Han Seo Woo...
Let me check first.
DAMN IT,
WHY THE FUCK IS SHE NOT PICKING UP!
Pick up, pick up the phone,
Han Seo Woo! Han Seo Woo, you...
YOU'D BETTER PICK IT UP!
Pick up, pick up, pick up, pick up,
pick up, PICK UP! PICK UP!!!!
Pick up, pick up, pick up,
PICK UP, PICK U~~~~P!!
PICK UP THE PHONE!!
You're here, sir.
Let's have a talk first today.
We can record 3 to 4 songs for a test too.
I should do a good job,
as this is my first time.
Mr. Kang, who is he...?
The engineer who will work with me.
But I heard from Ms. Moon
that you would work with me.
If you could please explain...
I don't recall saying I would
work with you, Seo Woo.
Shut the door and leave.
- Where are you going?
- I'm checking out early.
What do you mean, go?
Where are you going?
- He came with another sound engineer.
- What?
What the heck is she saying?
Come up.
He definitely said that
he'd be working with you.
- He must've changed his mind, then.
- In the span of a few hours?
I've known Teacher Kang from before.
He's not that kind of person.
Plus he's in a slump.
If he's in a slump,
then can he treat other people rudely?
Don't yield to such whim.
Follow me.
I'm fine. Really, Manager.
Are you okay?
Are you stupid?
If I think of such things as yield,
then I can't do anything.
In the process of work, there can be
some misunderstandings and mistakes.
I'm fine.
It's unfair, but why am I not even mad?
Let's hold it in, hold it in.
Soon Ho, you should hold it in,
so that you can live in Seoul.
She ran away?
Han Seo Woo ran away,
but... oh, I'm so mad.
It's always the good-mannered
ones who run away first.
Where did she run off to?
I don't know. She was walking away quietly,
but-
I'm so pissed off! It broke my heart!
Han Seo Woo has really
gotten on In Wook's side, too.
She explained to me that
there are a lot of unknown
but great talented musicians in Korea,
and...
Kang In Wook, that jerk...
I hate backstabbing the most.
Then it's the fault of
Kang what's-his-name.
What's pissing me off more
is that I'm bearing with it.
Why are you bearing with it?
That's what I'm saying!
He's so freaking immature.
Kang In Wook, you definitely said
that you'd be working with Han Seo Woo,
that you'd try it out.
I heard it, as clear as day.
Han Seo Woo must have felt pretty bad.
There was a situation that called for it.
Mr. Kang, insulting others to
this extent is like a habit for you.
- I'll explain.
- Do it by yourself.
Since you're paying us rent for it anyway.
Using all the time,
you can try your best to explain,
or just pound away at the piano.
I need some powerful healing.
♫ Amidst the snow falling
through the cold wind ♫
♫ You were like a period mark, ♫
He's crazy. He always
leaves the door open. ♫
Lost the way after wandering
without any promise ♫
♫ As I miss you so much,
a bittersweet smile is on my lips ♫
♫ I'm really missing you ♫
♫ Walking along together and
matching our steps, I'm thinking of you ♫
♫ Stored nicely in my
mind. Please remember us ♫
♫ Reaching my hand out to the night sky,
I make a wish ♫
♫ For you ♫
♫ My clumsy feelings ♫
♫ always passed by despite feeling sorry ♫
♫ Again,
walking lonesomely with the cold wind ♫
♫ I'm missing you again ♫
♫ Walking together
while matching our steps ♫
♫ I'm thinking of you ♫
♫ Stored nicely in my
mind. Please remember us ♫
♫ Reaching my hand out to the night sky,
I make a wish ♫
♫ For you ♫
♫ Don't forget me ♫
♫ Reaching my hand out to the night sky,
I'm thinking of you ♫
♫ Stored nicely in my
mind. Please remember us ♫
♫ Reaching my hand out to the night sky,
I make a wish ♫
♫ I'm really missing you ♫
February 27th (scratched out)
Are you going to Oslo?
Should I go?
You should've hidden it with all you had.
If you don't know,
then it doesn't mean anything.
As tiring and painful as it was,
you should've hidden it.
- You should've hidden it with all you...
- Why can't you understand me? Why?
You know I didn't even do it on purpose.
I'm telling you it was a mistake.
Just tell me once that it's okay.
If you do that, I can somehow live, Ji Soo.
Is this a good time?
Just a moment is enough.
Alcohol? Dinner?
The manager and Teacher
Kang are there together.
Soon Ho is there?
Why are the two of them together?
They're fighting, most likely.
Soon Ho called me because she was mad.
Soon Ho hates when promises are broken.
She did seem to be acting a bit sensitive.
It's more than being sensitive.
Because of that,
she turned her back to the world and
for about 9 years,
she lived in a farm.
No, but...
So you were rejected as soon as you came?
After so many years, she said to
meet up and you met up, then rejection?
Wow, I'm starting to cry.
Wow, what's up with Kim Ji Soo?
Backstabbing is dramatic in every form.
The first time I see you,
Uncle, and I really like it.
Wow, how is this possible?
Birds of a feather flock together.
She was even engaged to her first love,
but he fell in love with her best friend,
so they called it off.
She took me to a snack bar to console me,
but ended up wailing herself.
After that, she gave up on
Seoul and went down to the farm.
And she became a gardener.
Soon Ho is a child
with a very fragile heart.
There aren't a lot of places we can go...
Are you really hungry?
I was worried about you.
Well, now, can you tell me your story?
Wait, if you don't have anything to say,
let me start first.
Please come to the studio as per
the reservation by the end of this week.
As Han Seo Woo said, this can happen
due to some misunderstanding or mistake.
And for the new reservation,
I don't care if you do it in another
place with a fresh mind or whatever.
You care for Seo Woo a lot.
Are you two close?
I'm not close with anyone.
I'm not an affectional
person to begin with.
Life is originally starting
and ending by oneself, so
I'm planning to live
lonesomely as much as possible.
But why to Han Seo Woo...?
Mr. Kang In Wook,
when a person cares for another,
you're not supposed to
approach it in a way "because
one likes the other,
or is close to another".
This is simply about a promise.
You broke your promise,
and Han Seo Woo was sad about it.
And it makes me feel shitty.
Seo Woo... did you first
meet her in the studio?
That was the first time I got to know her.
As soon as we started working together,
she helped me with a difficult task.
To buy dishes through on-line shopping,
I didn't want to use my own name.
She bought them for me.
Well, although it can be nothing,
someone might take it suspiciously.
"Why doesn't she buy them herself?"
"Does she have a credit delinquency?"
I would be doubtful too.
Same for your slump too. In different
angles, many would be doubtful...
D-Dishes... Who did you buy them from?
It's selling and buying though
online shops. How would I know that?
Right, even when selling them,
all you need are address and phone number.
You don't have to see the faces either...
Obviously.
I'll work with Han Seo
Woo for my next album.
Are you kidding me?
No, not at all.
Are you enjoying those dishes?
Those are not for me either.
I got that request from another person too.
Life is disgustingly twisted, you know.
By the way, why do you keep laughing?
No, just... I'm just dumbfounded,
that's all.
We ran out of sandwiches, I'm sorry.
Then what about ramen?
Eat here?
Ramen you eat at a cafe is so delicious,
you know.
Close - see you next time
Shall I... testify that
you've waited long time?
- She must not be coming today either.
- She will, one day.
If I meet her, I'll testify for you
how you've been waiting so far.
No...
The person I was waiting
for was someone else.
- I know her too.
- I see...
After that, have you met her?
No.
My cafe is where the waiting
usually ends up with the meeting.
Each cafe has a different energy,
you know.
When I saw a person who got stood up,
that made me feel sad too,
but the very next day,
they showed up together.
You will meet her eventually.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have brought it up...
No, he should've cried already.
On that table,
you were with another lady, weren't you?
That lady, she was looking up the
ceiling when she was waiting for you,
so I still remember her.
She was the person.
The one he waited for.
Oh, she came though.
Seo Woo, would you please
tell Won not to wait at the cafe?
By any chance, are you the same person
who said has never cried all his life?
I can c-cry too, I found that out today.
Moreover, didn't you come to me
because you're worried about me?
I didn't come to show you this...
It totally cheers me up.
Why do I feel refreshed when
I saw someone else crying?
Let's go.
To where?
Taxi~!
You must feel embarrassed,
why are you waving at the empty street?
Nice to meet you, Ha Won.
So, can I be Ha Won now?
Do you have anything to say to Mr. Dawn?
I guess he won't show up going forward.
So,
this is the last moment with Mr. Dawn...?
I can't tell him not to leave though.
Would you please turn around?
Just say it, please.
Since you're Mr. Dawn?
Mr. Dawn, good bye.
I was thankful.
That's it.
Taxi!
Kim Ji Soo!
Make some noise!
Ah, Ji Soo! Turn on some fun music!
What is it? Why isn't the music on?
Kim Ji Soo?
Did he change it?
Huh,
you think I won't be able to find you guys?
Genie? Siri?
Device?
No, please listen.
This piece... when I first saw you.
I remember,
when I looked outside,
some man was looking around,
so I turned it up so
that he could listen.
Oh my, oh my, so it was you, Ha Won?
So you remember the
moment when you first saw me.
It's vivid,
I heard this song,
so I looked up.
And went to the studio
and you were there.
I told you, that the relationship lasts
long if the first impression was vivid.
I must be so impressive then, am I right?
Of course.
But the first encounter I remember was
when you were in the recording booth.
It's a different scene. If we remember
differently, that what happens?
Then, keep watching what would happen next.
Are you feeling better?
I told you this story to
make you feel better.
After seeing you crying earlier,
I forgot all about the upsetting work.
Your door looks open.
Oh, stop, stop!
I still have something to talk about.
This can cause a big trouble, you know.
Wait, wait!
It's looks better than
looking at it from the outside.
It's warm too.
I live here because
it's not too bad.
Eun Joo unnie doesn't
let me just live anywhere.
- What about the device?
- I got rid of it.
It sounds a bit harsh
to say I got rid of it...
In the past,
it was clear what Ji Soo gave me.
I was happy when I thought
of Ji Soo during difficult times,
Ji Soo could comfort me
when I was feeling empty.
There was something that
Ji Soo could correct for me.
Now, when I think of Ji Soo,
it's difficult.
It's time for me to stop.
It's ambiguous to say I'm stopping.
But I've realized that no matter how
abstract it is, there is a way through it.
Since I've made up my mind.
I'm going to find out what and how to stop.
Enough about me,...
it's your turn.
You told me.
That you like looking.
I honestly didn't know what that meant.
I never put value in looking
at something for a long time.
I've also believed that emotions
continue even if you've never met.
But now I know,
what it means to like looking at something.
It was nice to see even
though it was difficult.
See what?
And,
you didn't quit, right?
You're talking without context again.
It's not even 1% of the time and
I don't do that. At most it is 1%.
I 'm really curious how your 1% will grow.
Seo Woo!
- Hey, Han Seo Woo!
- Excuse me.
Han Seo Woo!
The student was hanging
around the bus stop for a half hour.
Because I'm going to pick him up
and escort him, you go quickly on up.
I know you're busy, but are you frozen?
Eun Joo is working like the
devil by herself in the kitchen.
Get going!
Oh, right!
We are having dinner together
when the new boarder arrives.
I completely forgot.
If I fail to show up, Eun Joo will kill me.
There's one more thing.
When I made up my mind, I thought it
would be better for you to know everything.
Among the things Ji Soo wanted to tell you,
there is one more.
Ji Soo went to the place
you had agreed to meet at.
Oh. Seo Woo.
Put a little soy sauce
in the japchae. It's bland.
Yes.
This alley is a little confusing.
There's just one butcher shop in the
alley leading to our boarding house.
A butcher shop?
Yes. But next to it,
the sweet sour chicken is delicious.
Butcher shop.
If I had only turned around.
Ji Soo!
Quitting you...
will put a stop my life-long regret.
Welcome.
Feel free to eat as much as you want.
I only ate one roll of
kimbap at 2. I appreciate it.
Eat up.
This household's japchae is amazing.
Our Soo Ji is a japchae wizard.
Who is Soo Ji?
"She is a japchae ghost."
Why are you talking about her again?
You're speaking without honorifics...
That's not it.
Ah. We are dating. Don't be concerned.
This is delicious.
Unni. I'm going to make a
phone call. I left my phone.
Hurry back.
I am not quitting.
Having said that does not mean
there is nothing expected of you.
Because I will take care
of myself so Mr. Ha Won,
make sure you figure
out what it is. Do that.
I figured it out.
What and how to quit
I did figure them out.
There is something you need to do for me.
All you have to do
is to go back and
forth so that I can see it.
You want to see.
No way.
I can't say now what
sort of feeling this is.
But...
I need you.
Can you stay for me?
Stay with me.
A Piece of Your Mind Preview
I want to hear it.
I have to improve. You're
going to be so surprised.
At this time of the year,
my heart is pounding. Someone's wife...
You're hiding something, aren't you?
I feel I am being exposed.
I also left something behind.
- Like your heart?
- My bike.
Handsome. Totally to my taste.
The worst already happened.
One of the two must live.
The 1% and one person
You should follow someone
if you want him to stay.