[This series was filmed under
the preventive measures by the emergency decree]
[Characters, behaviors, places, agencies, occupations
and events in this series are fictional and for entertainment purposes only]
[It is not intended to promote any action in the series.
Viewer's discretion is advised]
We agree that you have our protection
in exchange of all evidences pointing to the crimes
of the ones behind the Italians.
Tomorrow, Porsche and I will go get it.
No.
Only you and I, the two of us.
I told you Porsche couldn't be trusted.
Lock him up.
I knew that you'd trus-
Run away with me, Porsche.
Right now,
everything is going according to Tawan's plan.
He's about to break the two families apart
by using me and you as his tools.
And how can I know
that you're telling the truth, Vegas?
No matter how bad I am,
if it's for the person I love,
I will never hurt his feelings.
If I run, I'll become a traitor.
But if you don't run,
you gotta be here,
and you can't do a thing.
Porsche, you choose.
Stop it!
Don't make this hard on me.
Go, Vegas!
Porsche.
You have to trust me.
Why are you pretending to be asleep?
Well,
I'm scared
that if I look at you,
I'll cry.
Why's that?
I...
I've always felt
that I'm an unlucky person.
But today,
I've realized
that all the lucks I have
are for being here with you.
Kim.
I love you.
Do you love me?
I...
I'm hungry.
Let's find something to eat.
Mmm, okay.
Then,
I'll...
I'll make you some fried eggs.
Here.
It's a smiley face.
Where are his eyes?
Oh.
I'll be right back.
[Gotta go, sorry]
Help me!
Help!
Help me, Kim, help me!
Kim!
Chay!
What have we got?
Umm, it seems encrypted, Mr. Kinn.
If anyone's trying to get in,
it'll be locked automatically.
I'm try--
I'm trying to fix it.
I think it's locked if
there's access from other devices
that don't have the correct IP.
Or maybe it's nothing at all.
The encryption is to stall the time.
If you have so much time trying to prove me wrong,
don't you think it'd be better to go after the escapee?
Tawan.
Go back to your room.
Mr. Kinn.
Mr. Kinn, do you still trust Porsche?
You think that there's a mole here for Vegas, right?
I believe there are some clues in Vegas' secret room.
Last time, you went in by the system.
But this time, you're gonna go undercover.
What if you get caught, what are you going to do?
I may get tortured.
They may get me to talk.
And once I have no more use, they'll kill me.
So you want me to send you to die?
I must go because I trust Porsche.
So what should we do?
Right now, the main family is hunting us.
We need to find the evidence to prove our innocence.
Before we do that,
can we go get my brother first?
Yeah.
Tomorrow, we're gonna go get Porchay.
Kinn.
What happened at the house?
I've missed you.
See you around.
Excuse me.
Could you help me with this?
Thank you.
I'm coming in.
Hey.
Let me check that first.
You may go.
What the heck is this?
It's alright. It's Mr. Vegas'.
Okay.
We'll take it from here.
Er, sir.
May I use the toilet, please?
I can't hold it anymore.
Go, hurry.
Thank you so much.
Shoot, what the frick?
Arm, you're so awesome.
Porchay.
Chay.
He's not home.
[At the warehouse near Nuea Napa Pier, 4 p.m. Come alone]
Darn.
This must be freaking Tawan's doing.
If you wanna help Porchay,
we must go find the evidence.
I got an information about Tawan,
that he worked with the Yakuzas.
If we go there,
we will find the evidence that they're in contact.
But--
We won't fricking find anything.
I'll find my brother.
And if they've done anything to Porchay,
I'll freking kill each and every one of them.
We're in, Mr. Kinn.
But there's nothing left.
The thumbdrive itself is the virus.
It destroys every of our CCTV.
Urgent, Tawan has run away.
Mr. Kinn, Tawan's escaped.
Capture him.
Chay.
Porchay.
What the heck did you do to my brother?
This world is cruel,
don't you think?
Hey.
Hey, what the heck are you doing?
Tawan, you jerk!
Hey.
What the heck are you doing?
Darn you.
You're a dead man if I can untie this.
Are you angry?
You're angry, right?
You really love you brother, don't you?
- You love him. huh?
- Hey!
Do you love him so much?
- There. There.
- Hey!
- Jerk!
- You love him so much, don't you?
Porsche.
Make sure you're free first
before having that smartmouth.
You think I'm here alone?
Mr. Kinn, I've got it.
It's the emails with all information sent to them.
There's work schedule
and important documents.
Is it Tawan?
I'm having Arm dig into it now.
But I think there's more than one person.
It maybe Mr. Tawan and one of our bodyguards.
Right now, Tawan is missing.
I think he must be going to see Vegas.
Find his whereabouts.
Roger that, sir. I'll have Arm
locate Vegas from his cell phone.
And once I get it,
I'll send it to you as soon as I can.
Okay.
I'll be the one putting an end to this show.
So it's you.
What the heck are you doing?
What did I do wrong?
I'm helping you, Vegas.
I was with the main family for a long time
and didn't get anything.
So this is what I gotta do.
A guy like Kinn, he keeps his information safe
with his important one.
Or do you care about him, Vegas?
No.
No, no, no.
But this wasn't the fricking plan.
What the heck is going on, Vegas?
He's your cousin.
How could you do this to your families?
Whose family?
What family?
The main family?
That filthy family.
I don't take them as my family.
You're such a jerk.
You've just realized that?
I've been exchanging the information with
the Yakuzas and the Italians for a long time.
But when Don died,
the Yakuzas threatened to blackmail me.
And send this information to the main family.
But I don't get a fricking thing back.
All because of your dumbass.
I'm sorry.
Kinn will never let you guys go.
What if the story goes this way,
"Actually,
the bodyguard that he trusts most,
has been sending the information to the Yakuzas.
And when he gets caught,
he kidnaps Kinn's ex,
in order to blame him
and then runs away to hide with his brother.",
Kinn will suddenly look like a fool.
And no one is going to respect him.
But luckily,
I know of the plan,
so I help my cousin catch the traitor.
Kinn is not that stupid to believe you.
You dumb.
And...
what if there's a fake evidence?
Porsche's been in contact with them,
and that evidence is dropped in the crime scene.
Even he doesn't want to believe it,
he can't do anything about it.
What do you fricking get from killing me?
What do I get?
Kinn's got his heartbroken again.
Because he gets fooled again
by the ones he trusts most.
The main family will get weaker and weaker.
Because they got a stupid leader.
Unskilled.
And that's all it takes for us
to be together, right, Vegas?
Mr. Vegas,
the main family is heading here.
God darn it!
Vegas.
Let's run.
Thanks for putting up with me.
Now, go rest.
I got here first.
Mr. Kinn is on his way.
Thanks so much, man.
You, come with me.
Darn you!
Get Porchay outta here.
Go!
The main family didn't get you a bulletproof vest?
Porsche.
Big.
Mr. Kinn loves you so much.
Please take care of him.
Darn you, Tawan!
Big!
You--
Hey!
Drop the gun.
And I'll let you live.
Kinn.
Porsche is the one who betrayed you.
I've known about your plan long ago.
Big.
Porsche, are you alright?
I survived once.
Are you really going to kill me again, Kinn?
Please give me one last chance, Kinn.
I love you, Kinn.
Stop pretending.
You never loved me.
Stop bullcrapping.
You said you loved Vegas earlier.
Now that you're useless, he abandoned you.
Stop being so stupid.
No!
He didn't leave me.
He's waiting for me.
He just used you.
A selfish guy like you,
who would want to be with?
Vegas!
It's Vegas!
Vegas said he loved me.
Vegas said he'd marry me.
Vegas!
Where is Vegas? Help me, Vegas.
You said we'd be together forever.
Vegas!
Vegas.
Stay with me like this forever.
Of course.
But you gotta help me.
Do you really want me to do that?
Trust me.
After all this, I'll become the leader.
More importantly, Papa will accept us.
Vegas.
I love you, Tawan.
Marry me.
I love you, Vegas.
Kinn.
I'm sorry.
But if I can't be happy,
no one will ever be happy too.
Run!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Are you?
Everything is under control, Mr. Kinn.
But Big...
Just take care of what needs to be done.
It wouldn't have been like this,
if you guys had had a better boss.
Where is Kim?
Mr. Kim is safe. He left.
Chay, can you hear me?
I'm sorry.
Do you know what you're doing?
You lied to me.
I'm sorry.
I don't like myself being this.
I put you in danger.
What if something were to happen to you,
I wouldn't forgive myself.
Sorry.
But that something didn't happen,
and look at how you feel now.
And how about me? How would I feel?
Chay.
Porchay.
Give him time.
What about Vegas?
He must have crossed the border by now.
This country, any jerk with money
could run off easily.
But someone must be responsible for this.
Can I ask you something?
Was it true about what you said?
Said what?
That you knew everything from the start.
I knew from the start that
Tawan was working for Vegas.
And Pete, found the evidence
that they both had been in contact.
I was there to tell you.
But you fricking ran first.
Hey.
Two brothers, same personality.
My plan is all ruined because of you.
So, you think
how a guy like you should be punished?
You're laughing?
Oh, you're still smiling?
One more time?
I'm sorry.
Mr. Kan.
What the heck are you and Vegas doing?
I'm being honest, sir.
Mr. Kan, I apologize.
Didn't I tell you
not to do what's not my order?
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, n--
You two, go clean up the mess Vegas did.
Where is Vegas?
He ran away, so I had to come here instead.
I brought you something.
Open it.
What?
Your guy who betrayed us.
Us?
Which us?
How could you say that?
This was him betraying the main family.
And worked for Vegas, ain't it?
You've misunderstood.
I saw him taking both of our families' information
to sell to other gangs.
I think Vegas was just trying to lure him.
So he could expose him.
Expose?
If he's that good of a person, why would he run away?
He had to run to settle first.
Ran from the ones who don't listen to reasoning.
And only want to punish.
Here's some evidence.
But someone must be responsible for this.
If you think that the minor family is the traitors,
you can take my life.
Are you going to shoot him yourself?
Or are you going to let me?
Our Papa used to say that
true victory comes from not taking advantage
from the ones who are weaker.
Thank you, brother.
But you must bring Vegas here to talk to me.
Yes, I will.
You know,
I never take advantages.
Why did you call me?
I noticed that we were kinda busy.
But now everything seems to be settled now.
I think it's about time you apologize.
Huh?
Apologizing to you?
I think you're the one who needs to apologize.
Why do I have to apologize?
Which one should I go first?
You, bringing your ex into the house?
Or you, locking me up?
Locking you up less than a day
and you ran off with a guy?
Do you think I'm that easy?
Well, you don't seem to be so difficult.
Is that what's coming out of your mouth?
If you knew the plan from the start,
why didn't you tell me?
The plan was about to succeed,
if you didn't run off with Vegas.
He fooled me.
And did you let him fool you?
You're doing it again, jerk.
You never trust me.
So are we good now?
If you wanna know,
you gotta try...
Darn you!
That's disgusting, darn!
Now, we're good.
What are you so moody about?
Or do you want another one?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Do you want another one?
You want more? Huh?
Yeah, smile. That makes you so cute.
It's been tough lately.
Porchay wants me to resign.
And if I don't,
he'll cut me off.
Yeah.
I'm stressed too.
It's like I've forgotten something.
But I can't think of what I've forgotten.
If you can think of it, would it be called "forgotten"?
Smile.
Oh, you're growling.
Don't fart again now.
Okay.
Man!
♪It's you♪
♪It's because of you♪
♪Even if we face a world without stars
but we both will overcome that♪
♪No matter for how long♪
♪Embrace me♪
Feels so good.
♪It's time for you to stop♪
♪Drop your skeptical act♪
♪Despite the fact that your heart has changed♪
♪Just say it now♪
♪Don't drag any longer♪
♪I'm invisible whether you're with me or not♪
♪No matter what the outcome, I still love you♪
The main family has put you on the blacklist.
They'll send in some guys to check.
Clean this mess up.
Your grandma must really love you.
What the heck are you doing?
I'm gonna hurt you so you'll remember.
Are you happy now?
No.
I've just started.