[This series was filmed under the preventive
measures by the emergency decree.]
[Characters, behaviors, places, agencies, occupations and events
in this series are fictional and for entertainment purposes only.]
[It is not intended to promote any action in the series.
Viewers’ discretion is advised.]
Mr. Don is waiting inside, sir.
Normally, Mr. Korn doesn't have urgent meetings.
I know.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Where is Mr. Korn?
Due to Mr. Korn's health condition,
from now on, Mr. Kinn will be in charge.
Ciao, Kinn.
You are all grown now.
Oh! Mama!
Please, take a seat.
Still, you're fond of Gelato?
No, thank you.
I won't bother you for long.
Welcome to Hum Bar!
Good evening! Hello there!
Please, take the seats, ladies.
Porsche!
Kong.
Yes?
For this beautiful Jang, Pink Lady.
Pink Lady.
And the charming Kaproy...
Vodka Martini, shaken, not stirred.
And for Lada...
a little special, I'll handle it.
My dad hasn't been very well lately.
Things are a bit out of hand.
Just today, that I've had a chance
to look through the company statements.
How excited are you for the big profit?
Right.
The casino is making bigger and bigger profit each year.
So big that...
it arouses someone's greed
to start cheating.
Do you agree?
Calm. Calm down.
If you wanna be on top of the game, you gotta have it all, like him.
Yes, ma'am.
See that? All the ladies are hooked.
Porsche is so cool.
Calm down.
I've done business with your Dad,
for years.
And he's never been disrespectful
with me.
With me!
People says,
I'm more like my Mom.
We were corrupted.
He wouldn't have succeeded
without contribution from my people.
Hopefully, the last case.
Betrayers must die.
We are going to do big business together, Mr. Kinn.
I'm doing quite alright tonight.
Porsche, teach us!
Gimme a thousand.
Hey, Ball, you got some money?
You got it?
I got two hundreds.
Another two, c'mon.
We got five hundred baht.
Please, tell us a little.
You don't have to do anything.
Just give them what they want.
You see those wealthy chicks?
They have no lovers.
But money.
You just need praise them.
And when they give you money...
Thank you, Porsche.
Hey, Porsche. The ladies here are calling for you.
Hurry up!
Take back your money.
I don't take money from my homies.
Thank you.
C'mon, make some drinks for the ladies.
They want you. They miss you.
Right away.
We got company.
Go that way.
I'll take Mr. Kinn through the tunnel. We need backup.
Porsche.
The woman at that table is checking you out.
I know.
This way, Mr. Kinn.
Mr. Kinn, go!
Shit, for god's sake.
Hey!
Help me.
Stay out of this, you piece of shit.
Hey!
Fifty-thousand.
You got it.
One moment.
I told you I needed a moment.
Go ahead.
Wait, man.
You're really have do this?
Hey there.
Hey, fifty-thousand!
You!
Get of me!
Calm down, bro.
Check if more are coming.
Thanks.
Hey.
Give me your bank account number.
I'll transfer the money.
Are you nuts?
Transfer it now.
I don't have a phone with me.
Give me your phone.
I'll have my people handle it.
Here you go, of course.
C'mon, you shithead.
Do I look like a fool?
You'll have your people beat me up.
So what do you want?
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, hey.
Be still, be still.
Take it.
Now, that's better.
I'll have it.
What's your name?
And what's that for?
I'll send you a gift hamper.
My name is Jom.
Mr. Kinn, how are you doing, sir?
I'm okay.
What happened?
Porsche, come sit.
Chai came here to collect the rent.
I happened to be here.
If not, Chay would've been hurt.
Shit.
Thanks a lot, Uncle.
It's alright.
Are you okay?
I'm good.
But why did we stop paying them?
Chay's just started a new semester.
So I haven't been paying them.
They asked for 200,000 baht by this week.
Or they'll take the house.
200,000? Hell with them.
Bro, I'm sorry.
Nah, I was just rambling.
It's alright. I can still take care of it.
Uncle, have you eaten?
I bought some noodles.
Go ahead. Eat with Chay.
I've already had something.
I'll put them in the plate then.
I shouldn't have listened to my friend
and invested in Crypto.
Aside from loss...
we're losing this house.
Forget about it, Uncle.
At least, you're the only person
who's been trying to help us.
If it weren't for you, Chay would...
I haven't helped you guys with anything.
I'm also making things worse.
I'm so sorry.
How much do you think this costs?
Where did you get it?
A customer gave it to me.
Well, I don't really know much about this.
I guess a hundred thousand, maybe.
But that's still not enough.
Whoa, Uncle, if it costs that much...
we'll be fine. I'll find the rest.
How would that be possible?
We only got a few days.
Trust me, Uncle.
We'll be just fine.
You didn't steal this, did you?
C'mon, guys, come on!
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen.
It's time for some violence and the smell of blood.
Are you ready?
Yes!
Ready?
And over here?
We're ready!
Ready?
Go!
Porsche, don't end it too fast.
Stall the time.
When we hit the target, I'll let you know.
Bring it on, buddy.
And finally, our final knockout!
Let's not waste more time.
Are we ready to have some fun?
Are you?
If you are...
Ready.
Fight!
You're doing good, Porsche.
Very well, Porsche.
What? He's about to go down, bro.
Thanks a lot, bro.
Hey, did you miscount this?
Well, only if you'd waited a little longer to knock him down.
Where would I find the money to pay you?
Why don't you go fight yourself?
Hey, c'mon.
Next month, I'll ask for a raise.
Bro!
Hey, hell with him.
Take mine.
I bet on you.
Don't worry.
Let's go grab a bite.
Pineapple. Sausages.
Porsche is here!
Bro, come sit here.
Who won the lottery?
You did.
The watch was worth 700,000 Baht.
C'mon, don't joke around, Uncle.
Really. We got 700,000 Baht.
So we get to keep the house?
And the rest could cover Chay's tuition fee.
Ouch!
Why are we having pizzas then?
Well...
Grab the beers! We need to celebrate!
Beer!
So many many beers!
Bro...
Can I have one?
Oh.
Yours is this one.
And this, is for you, Uncle.
C'mon, cheers. Yeah!
Sir.
Big's wound is more serious than we thought.
He might need to rest for months.
So...
Are you happy now?
It's fortunate they didn't kill you.
Or else you wouldn't be standing here.
You're too hot-tempered.
In this business, you need to know your place.
When I started, I had to greet them
with respect along with gifts.
It's my fault.
I did send some gifts to them
to apologize this morning.
They should be satisfied, I suppose.
What the hell!
What happened here?
Who did it?
I have no idea, sir.
Bring those bastards who did this here,
I'm going to kill them!
Right.
Look at you guys.
And what you've done.
Have we found Jom yet?
We're still looking for him, sir.
No matter who he is, find him quickly.
Yes, sir.
Whoa! Such a surprise.
Well, when I don't have to work, I come to study.
Don't I look like I love studying?
And where are your notes?
Let me copy them.
I already took the notes for you.
Wow. Very kind of you.
What, man?
You're not sharing.
This is so soft. Tastes good.
You wanna eat it, huh?
Is it tasty?
The snack that you stole from me.
It's crunchy too. Is it Ovaltine?
It's done, my dorayaki.
Hey!
Porsche!
Shit. There's no more.
You're unbelievable.
Where is Jom?
Oh, someone's looking for him earlier.
He said to meet him at the basketball field.
Holy shit!
Jom!
Porsche!
Your friend is going to be a star!
Earlier, a guy from a modeling agency
asked me to go to a series casting.
He wanted me to play a waiter
who's actually the greatest boxer undercover.
This role is obviously written for me.
It's my time
to be known to the world.
Yes?
What are you doing?
They're coming a lot.
Who's coming?
I can't fight this any longer, bro.
Fight who?
Who's there, Chay? Talk to me.
Shit! I'm taking a shit.
What do you want? Can't you just wait?
Oh, it's nothing.
Lock up the house.
I thought something happened.
Just lock the house nicely. Beware of the thieves.
Porsche, someone's here for Yok.
Take that for me, would you?
This is pretty nice.
But I'm nicer.
Thank you so much
for wanting to be my bar's partner.
The pleasure is mine.
Wow, you're so cute.
And so are you.
Thank you.
Hey, Porsche.
This is Mr. Kinn.
He's interested in becoming our bar's partner.
But I'm thinking about convincing him
to be another kind of partner.
The name is Porsche?
Yes, Porsche.
Oh, I thought it's something else.
He's the top of our list.
The customers want him.
If it weren't for the customers,
I would have him all by myself.
But that's not right.
May I have a word with the bar's favorite guy?
Of course. Take a good care of Mr. Kinn.
Excuse me.
What?
You're scared I might hurt the people around you?
You think I'm a low-class mafia?
You want your watch back, right?
Nope.
I think you've been fooled.
This watch, at least it should be 2 million Baht.
So what exactly do you want?
Calm down.
I'm here to relax.
Yok told me you're a great bartender.
Make me a drink.
Sugar. Bitter. Liquor.
Fragrant oil of an orange peel.
Wow. Bitter with sweet after taste.
This is nice.
What the hell do you want?
You got your watch back.
I think it's loud here.
Let's find a private spot to talk.
I'm not going.
Well, that's a shame.
This pretty bar might get messy...
Don't you think?
Take it off!
Why did you take me here?
Hey, do you hear me?
Hey! Can you hear me? Shitheads.
Porsche, Pachara, 23 years old.
Former national Taekwando's champion.
Also, an orphan
who has to be fully responsible for his own brother.
His main job is a top list bartender, shaking fast, treating nicely.
Another job,
an underground boxer,
also known as, The Phoenix.
Are you done?
Are you a psycho?
You kidnapped me to tell my story to me.
Are you crazy? You, asshole.
Let go of me! Untie me!
Be my bodyguard.
Be your bodyguard?
And hold my balls like a wallpaper
like these maniacs?
Watch it!
Cut it out.
I know you don't like it.
But this job will make a fortune for your brother and your family.
Yuck.
You think your pennies could buy me and my family.
I would do terrible things for you,
kidnap good people and tie them up,
and dig into their background.
Your friends here would act all cool walking in.
I know your kind very well.
For real?
You, be my bodyguard,
or be the fish's food?
I'm gonna count to three.
One.
Sorry. I'm a bit hasty.
Two.
What the hell!
Me, being your bodyguard?
I'd rather die.
Let him go.
How come you're back empty-handed?
I told you, a guy like him wouldn't work for us.
If you want someone good,
there are lots of guys who are better than him.
Yes, there are.
And just buying them off
with lots of money, they'd follow you.
But to someone, even with lots of money offered,
and he still doesn't want to come.
Don't you think this person is interesting?
He might be just a fool.
How many of our people
were bought by other gangs, or even the smaller families?
He might be whom you've been looking for after all.
Checkmate!
Chay, pack your bags.
Who did this?
Hell with Kinn's people?
Which Kinn?
The mafias.
If it weren't them, who would do such thing?
And are you alright?
I'm okay.
Bro...
Hey!
I've already cleared off all debts.
There must be some kind of misunderstanding.
Well, well...
That money wasn't delivered to us.
Your investor Uncle
invested in my club.
But he must have forgotten
that all the investments have risks.
He still owes me 2 million Baht.
Pull him up!
It's not true, is it, Uncle?
You tell them that it's not true.
Porsche, where have you been?
Everyone knows he's a regular at my club.
And that he told you about the money
he got cheated by his friend,
it's here.
2 million, right?
Give me one month.
Right. I'll give you one day.
If you don't have it by tomorrow,
both of you will be dead bodies on the street.
Let's go.
Porsche, I'm sorry. Porsche.
Porsche, I didn't mean to.
The thing is, Chai really cheated.
Porsche, believe me.
Uncle, stop bullshitting.
Porsche, you gotta believe me.
Are you done, Uncle?
Are you done bullshitting?
I'm your Uncle, Porsche.
Calm down and talk to me nicely, would you?
This is exactly why
I haven't crushed you.
What does a gambler like you care about except yourself.
Leave.
Porsche, forgive me.
Porsche, I know I'm wrong now.
Please.
Please forgive me, Porsche.
Leave!
I've raised you since you were a kid.
Cutting me off like this,
you've really thought it through?
Go ahead. It's still hot.
Alright.
Are we good?
Yeah.
Bro, about the money, just leave it.
We could move to somewhere else.
But I love this house.
Who doesn't love this house, bro?
But...Just forget it.
We could use the rest of the money
and rent a small house.
That's the last savings for your university expense.
Bro, studying won't do us any good now.
Let me help you work.
You know what,
what I want for you the most is,
I want you to have a degree,
have a quality social life and good friends.
I don't want to disappoint our parents.
They know, bro.
They know that you've done your best.
Don't forget, you're not alone in this.
And you're not the only one fighting.
Are you hurt?
Well, I'm not the smart one.
Leave the hard work to me.
Bro, please, we could rent a small house together.
And when we have enough money,
we could open a small bar business
by the beach just like you always wanted to.
You, make the drinks.
And I'll play live music.
Ooh.
So cool.
Haha.
In real life, it's not that easy, you know.
The reason I support you to go study is,
if you play live music,
you'll scare off all the customers.
What the hell?
Ah.
Just wait and see.
I'm seeing it right now.
I love you, bro, very much.
Bro.
Bro...
Chay, I've got good news.
Yok has a nice friend
who's gonna clear all debts for us.
And he is going to help you with the school fees
until you get the degree.
But in exchange, I gotta take care
of his bar in a private island.
I'm so lucky.
I suddenly get to do my dream job.
I guess the atmosphere must be really nice.
Beautiful sand and clear water.
Every where I look, I see happiness.
But unfortunately, there's no phone signal.
No internet.
Or else I'd take photos for you to see every day.
I love you, Chay.
Porsche.
Don't forget our deal.
Well, you too don't forget that your life is mine now.
My life is mine.
You have no right to speak like that with Mr. Kinn.
Why can't I?
Are you a god?
Hey, watch your mouth.
You have no idea that Mr. Kinn...
You'll find out.
Porsche, the boss is calling for you.
I heard that you didn't want to work here?
But I'd love you to be here and be happy.
The hell with happiness.
And about your brother, don't worry.
I'll take care of him as promised.
If you really want me to be the bodyguard here,
I must be in charge of these two.
Good.
You got the guts.
Alright.
Because now Big isn't in the condition.
But Sir...
Well, consider it done.
You all may leave. I'll rest.
Papa.
At last, all the pieces are complete.
Alright, let's start.
This is the product opening party.
I'll take care of Mr. Kinn.
Let me have one.
You think you still working in a bar?
Do you know that you make a fool out of me?
Keep an eye on the new bodyguard named Porsche.
And report to me.