=Unspeakable Longing=
=Episode 8=
(Is he still suspicious of me?)
(What should I do?)
Miss Qiao, how are you feeling?
Thank you for your concern, Your Highness.
My injury is not serious.
Miss, you're still pretending
to be strong at this time!
The physician said
if the wound had gone a bit deeper,
you would have been beyond saving!
Tao, stop talking.
Miss Qiao, I will never forget
your life-saving grace.
Your Highness,
I saved you willingly,
not to demand gratitude
in return.
Your Highness,
can't you see
my feelings for you?
From the first moment I saw you,
I...
Shuangshuang!
Your Highness is here too.
(Surprised to see me, aren't you?)
(Good thing I was smart enough)
(to have someone keep an eye on here.)
You're here to see Miss Qiao too?
Of course.
Miss Qiao was injured because of us,
so as soon as I heard she was awake,
I rushed over.
Miss Qiao, are you feeling better?
Thank you for your concern, Miss Bai.
Miss Qiao,
I had the kitchen
make some chicken soup for you.
Drink it while it's hot.
Your Highness,
our young lady has weak hands
and might pull at her wound.
Why don't you feed her yourself?
After all,
our young lady was injured
for you.
Yes,
I didn't consider that.
Your Highness, let me do it.
Your Highness,
you're used to being served by others.
How would you know
how to serve someone else?
Besides,
if you accidentally hurt Miss Qiao,
that would turn a good deed into a bad one.
Miss Qiao is also my savior.
It's only right for me to take care of her.
That won't do!
Why not?
Since when
do servants decide matters
concerning your Miss Qiao?
Do you want to be the young lady yourself?
- You...
- Lyuluo!
Your Highness, I...
Sister Qiao,
I have experience, don't worry.
Thank you, Miss Bai.
No need to be formal with me.
Here.
Your Highness, Miss Bai,
the chicken soup is delicious.
There's
no need for Miss Bai to continue feeding me.
My injury hasn't healed,
and my head still aches a bit.
Then perhaps…
Miss Qiao should rest well.
I will visit you again later.
Miss Youke, why are you leaving
in such a hurry today?
I think
it's because you're reluctant
to leave Miss Qiao,
so you're walking so slowly.
Lyuluo, let's go.
Miss!
I have no romantic feelings
for Miss Qiao.
She was injured because of me,
so it's only natural for me to visit her.
Alright.
There's something I don't understand.
I hope you
can help clarify.
Go ahead.
How did you know
that I faint when I touch a woman?
Tell me,
how did you know?
Alright, alright.
Isn't it obvious?
I've long heard
that you don't get close to women.
You don't even have a maid in your mansion.
Besides, Lyuluo and Qiao Shuangshuang
once touched you,
and the moment they did,
you fainted.
Who would react like that normally?
(She discovered my strange illness
so early on.)
So you knew from the start
that nothing would happen when we interacted?
Yes.
Aren't I special?
So
this means
we are destined
for each other.
Xu Zeyu, just accept me.
You'll keep this secret.
Alright,
I'll keep your secret
about your gynophobia.
Thank you, Miss Youke.
Since
I've helped you so much,
shouldn't you agree
to a small request of mine?
Go ahead.
You always call me
Miss Youke, Miss Youke.
I'm tired of hearing it.
Why don't you just call me
Youke?
Is that alright?
Youke.
Say it again!
Say it again! Come on!
Are you shy?
Your Highness, say it again!
Greetings, Your Grace.
You sent a signal urgently to see me today.
What's the matter?
Your Grace,
this time I blocked a knife for Xu Zeyu,
and it seems to have temporarily dispelled
his suspicions about me.
You've done well.
However,
the Prime Minister's daughter, Bai Youke,
seems to have fallen in love with Xu Zeyu
and is secretly protecting him.
This is very detrimental to our plan.
Your Grace has meticulously planned
for so many years,
investing a lot of manpower,
material resources,
and financial resources.
I don't want anyone
to hinder our plan.
Anyone who stands in the way
of Xirong's great plan
to annex Jingyao must die.
If Buddha blocks, kill Buddha;
if ghosts block, kill ghosts.
Yes.
(Elegant and Graceful)
Your Highness.
Your injury hasn't healed,
yet you still have the interest
to play the zither.
Your Highness,
the moon is bright tonight,
and I was moved by the scenery.
Therefore,
I transformed my feelings into music
and offer it to you,
hoping you can understand my feelings.
I do understand,
and that's why I hope you
take care of your health.
What are you looking at, Your Highness?
Nothing.
Miss Qiao, the night is deep
and the dew is heavy.
Let's go inside to talk.
That sounds great.
I was just thinking
of discussing poetry and songs with you.
Please.
♪Just pretend you never came♪
♪The past is sealed away♪
♪Too many promises are dusted by stories♪
♪Too much love is destined to part♪
♪You use one look to ask for a kiss♪
♪Thinking you have the talent to love♪
♪My reckless devotion♪
♪In the end, we were still fated
but not destined♪
♪Just a little more, even an inch more♪
♪So foolishly dedicating a lifetime♪
♪Deeply in love♪
♪Mistaking the wrong person for real♪
♪Just pretend you never came♪
♪The past is sealed away♪
♪Too many promises are dusted by stories♪
♪Too much love is destined to part♪
♪You use one look to ask for a kiss♪
♪Thinking you have the talent to love♪
♪My reckless devotion♪
♪In the end, we were still fated
but not destined♪
♪Just a little more, even an inch more♪
♪So foolishly dedicating a lifetime♪
♪Deeply in love♪
♪Mistaking the wrong person for real♪
♪You use one look to ask for a kiss♪
♪Thinking you have the talent to love♪
♪My reckless devotion♪
♪In the end, we were still fated
but not destined♪
♪Just a little more, even an inch more♪
♪So foolishly dedicating a lifetime♪
♪Deeply in love♪
♪Mistaking the wrong person for real♪
(All rights reserved)
(by Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Company Limited)