=Unspeakable Longing=
=Episode 12=
(Prince Rui's Mansion)
(In the middle of the night,)
(where did Qiao Shuangshuang go?)
Miss Qiao.
Sister Youke, you're here.
Come, please enter.
Miss Qiao, why aren't you surprised at all
that I, who should be in prison,
am suddenly out?
Naturally, it's because
His Highness is wise and brilliant.
He has already uncovered the truth
and cleared your name.
But didn't Miss Qiao insist
that you saw me
stealing the drawing with her own eyes?
It was too dark at the time.
I couldn't see clearly.
Miss Qiao, you're really something.
You can turn black into white
without even blushing or hesitating.
Thank you for the compliment, sister.
Qiao Shuangshuang,
you've done so many things
without success.
Aren't you worried
that your behind-the-scenes boss
might abandon you
and find someone else to help?
What do you mean?
The meaning is obvious.
Your boss behind the scenes
thinks I'm more capable than you, so...
Then if I kill you now,
wouldn't I not have to worry
about being discarded?
Don't be rash.
We can talk this through.
Actually, you have another choice.
That is to turn sides, become a witness,
reveal the mastermind behind all this,
and atone for your crimes.
How dare you! You dare to trick me?
You...
(No, the Five Poisons Powder
is taking effect early.)
Qiao Shuangshuang, what's wrong with you?
Let go of me!
Stop pretending to be kind!
People like us,
our lives are as insignificant as ants.
Everyone's life is equal.
There's no distinction
between high and low, noble and humble.
You look down on yourself so much,
how can you face the parents
and relatives who love you?
Parents?
I lost my parents long ago.
They're all dead.
Come here.
Be careful.
Why are you helping me?
I can't just stand by and watch someone die.
You rest first. I'll go find a physician.
No need.
There's no cure for the Five Poisons Powder.
Without the unique antidote,
one can only rely on willpower to endure it.
He treats you like this,
yet you still risk your life to work for him.
Aren't you being foolish?
(In the dense forest of the eastern suburbs)
My Lord.
This is the antidote.
Thank you, My Lord.
My Lord.
I...
My identity has been exposed.
Please punish me.
I am willing to atone
for my crimes with meritorious service.
He discovered your identity
long ago.
Not exposing you
must mean he wants to follow the trail
to find me.
To be safe,
I can only sacrifice a pawn
to protect the king.
(Fragrant Orchid Elegant Chamber)
Miss.
Miss, you're awake.
You're finally awake.
Why am I in bed?
You fell asleep
in Miss Qiao's room last night.
I carried you back.
Then where's Qiao Shuangshuang?
I don't know. I didn't see her.
(Oh no, could it be that Qiao Shuangshuang)
(discovered something and ran away?)
(If she's gone,)
(the clue to finding the mastermind)
(will be lost.)
(All of Xu Zeyu's efforts would be in vain.)
I need to go out for a while.
Where on earth did this Qiao Shuangshuang go?
The best place to hide in the city should be
the dense forest in the suburbs.
Qiao Shuangshuang!
Where are you?
Did I come to the wrong place?
Qiao Shuangshuang.
How are you?
You'll surely die if you continue like this.
We need to find a place
to bandage you quickly.
Where's your lady?
Your Highness.
She went out.
Where did she go?
I don't know.
Did anything happen in the mansion
while I was at the palace?
Miss Qiao has disappeared.
Oh right, the lady went out
after hearing about her disappearance.
Si, bring some men and follow me.
Yes.
It hurts.
Bear with it.
Endure it.
Your Highness, someone said
they saw a young woman
- enter the dense forest.
- Miss Bai!
But this forest is dark and damp,
- full of snakes and wild beasts.
- Miss Bai!
Could Miss Bai have already...
Miss Bai.
Your Highness.
♪Just pretend you never came♪
♪The past is sealed away♪
♪Too many promises are dusted by stories♪
♪Too much love is destined to part♪
♪You use one look to ask for a kiss♪
♪Thinking you have the talent to love♪
♪My reckless devotion♪
♪In the end, we were still fated
but not destined♪
♪Just a little more, even an inch more♪
♪So foolishly dedicating a lifetime♪
♪Deeply in love♪
♪Mistaking the wrong person for real♪
♪Just pretend you never came♪
♪The past is sealed away♪
♪Too many promises are dusted by stories♪
♪Too much love is destined to part♪
♪You use one look to ask for a kiss♪
♪Thinking you have the talent to love♪
♪My reckless devotion♪
♪In the end, we were still fated
but not destined♪
♪Just a little more, even an inch more♪
♪So foolishly dedicating a lifetime♪
♪Deeply in love♪
♪Mistaking the wrong person for real♪
♪You use one look to ask for a kiss♪
♪Thinking you have the talent to love♪
♪My reckless devotion♪
♪In the end, we were still fated
but not destined♪
♪Just a little more, even an inch more♪
♪So foolishly dedicating a lifetime♪
♪Deeply in love♪
♪Mistaking the wrong person for real♪
(All rights reserved)
(by Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Company Limited)