What are you good for?
Didn't I tell you
to drug Mei Yanhong's tea?
Why did Brother Bao drink it?
I'm sorry, Sister Yuejiao.
I really did exactly as you asked
and drugged Boss Mei's tea.
But I didn't expect
Brother Bao to grab it and drink it all.
There was nothing I could do!
Idiot!
So Brother Bao drank it.
Couldn't you drug Mei Yanhong's tea
and make her drink it?
You made me lose
the chance to poison her voice!
If she gets suspicious,
how can I take back the opera house?
I'm sorry, Sister Yuejiao.
I promise I won't make
this kind of mistake again.
Next time?
You think there's a next time?
She got lucky this time.
Let's see who can shield her next.
Go make me a pot of chicken soup.
Go now!
Lord Guan above,
your faithful believer, Mei Yanhong,
sincerely bows to you.
May you bless Hongfu Opera House
with everything going smoothly,
and keep everyone safe.
Senior Sister.
I specially made a bowl of chicken soup
to apologize to you.
Please don't be mad at me.
You are Master's biological daughter,
and my junior sister.
We are family.
How could I be mad at you?
It's just that...
this opera house
is Master's life's work, after all.
Business is already bad enough.
What you said today...
If it ruins the opera house's reputation,
how can I face Master?
Senior Sister,
I was wrong.
I know
you've always been angry.
Back then, Master
gave the opera house and the star performer title
all to me.
That's what made you leave home in anger
to start your own troupe.
About this...
If I were in your shoes,
I would feel it was unfair too.
No, Senior Sister.
I was young and ignorant.
I didn't understand my father's good intentions.
But when I finally understood,
my father had already passed away.
I didn't even get to see him one last time.
Master always had you in his heart.
All these years,
he kept asking around for news of you.
Before he passed,
he even urged me
to make sure I find you and bring you back.
It's just that...
the opera house's business
has been bad all along.
So I...
I know.
I came back this time
just to help you, Senior Sister,
revive the opera house.
But...
I don't know if you, Senior Sister,
are willing to let me stay.
I already said,
we are family.
Of course I want you to stay.
We will
work together as sisters.
From now on,
you just focus on your opera skills,
and hone your craft.
Given time,
this opera house
and the star performer title
will all be yours, won't they?
I knew
Senior Sister loves me the most.
Oh, right.
The chicken soup.
Drink it quickly while it's hot.
It won't taste good when it's cold.
Okay.
Yuejiao,
I'm sorry.
What kind of luck does Mei Yanhong have?
Is Lord Guan really
protecting her this much?
I refuse to believe it.
Chuncheng
What's the situation?
I found that
the victim has two wounds.
One
was caused by a kitchen knife.
The other,
on the artery of her neck,
was caused by a broadsword.
That's the fatal wound.
To kill someone,
why use two murder weapons?
What if
there are two killers?
Xiaochun,
before you heard Xiao Yuejiao scream,
did you hear any fighting inside?
When I came over,
I only heard
Sister Yuejiao's tragic scream.
On your way here,
did you see anyone suspicious?
When I heard Sister Yuejiao's voice,
I rushed over immediately.
But outside the room,
I saw Lord Guan
swing his broadsword.
And then,
I fainted from fear.
Lord Guan?
Could it be
the Lord Guan we worship
in the shrine manifesting himself?
Stop talking nonsense.
How could Lord Guan kill someone?
Boss Mei,
since you usually
worship the statue of Lord Guan,
why don't you
take us all to have a look?
On the broadsword,
there really are bloodstains.
What's going on?
Inspector Huang, it's like this.
It's normal for the broadsword
in our opera house to have blood.
Before every performance,
we use the broadsword to kill a chicken for sacrifice.
But
this doesn't look like chicken blood.
Instead,
it's human blood.
Inspector,
that blood
is very likely mine.
Because
when I put the broadsword away yesterday,
I accidentally
cut my own hand.
So the blood on this blade
is probably mine.
Didn't you say
the other murder weapon
was a kitchen knife?
But earlier in Xiao Yuejiao's room
and in this shrine,
I didn't see a trace of a kitchen knife.
Since it's a kitchen knife,
we have to look in the kitchen.
Nobody move.
Let me do it.
Spirits of heaven and earth,
compass needle, show your power.
Knowing its location,
seeking its direction.
Guide me swiftly,
do not be lost.
According to the compass,
that knife
should be where there is water.
It's here!
Really?
It's really here.
There's blood.
Who's there?
Stop!
You think you can run from me?
Auntie Wang?
Didn't you take the day off today?
It's so late,
why are you here?
Auntie Wang
How did you injure your hand?
Where did you injure it?
When did you injure it?
I got this yesterday...
at home...
while doing chores.
Injured while doing chores at home?
Then why is it
that the knife used to kill Xiao Yuejiao
has a crack on its handle
that matches it perfectly?
Besides, you clearly asked for leave last night.
Why would you be out in the middle of the night,
going to the backyard of the opera house?
Did you stay in the opera house the whole time,
wait until nightfall,
and kill Xiao Yuejiao?