The Loyal Pin
That’s enough! Stop lying!
I will beat this unwanted child to death in front of his own father!
That’s our child.
This marriage…
shall be considered as a void.
Don’t bother paying attention to them, Pattamika.
Please remember…
that I will always be here…
and will never let go of your hands
I am deeply in love with the person I am not able to marry.
Who is that person you love?
Lady Pinlanthita, Father.
Lady Pin?
But isn’t she also a lady like you?
I do not understand what you are asking for.
And no matter how I look at it,
I could not see how it would be possible.
That is why…
I am here to beg for your permission…
to let me continue living my life as it is…
where I will stay single for the rest of my life.
Are you certain that the love you have for Lady Pin…
is one between lovers?
Yes, Father.
Then, why did Lady Pin accept the engagement proposal from Kueakiat?
She does not want me to give up my royal title.
I already told Mother…
that if she does not let me stay with Lady Pin,
I will give up my royal title.
And we will run away together.
Your mother already knew?
So, I’m the last one to know then.
Prince Arnon still doesn’t know about it, Father.
What will you do if I refuse?
My life as a princess is somehow like a pretty bird in a fine cage.
I shall never let anyone force me…
to cage up my heart within that imprisonment ever again.
There is a saying…
that it is impossible for one to always get what they want.
What makes you think that you will be an exemption?
It is because I am your daughter.
My life is, in fact, my own. I alone can live it.
What do you mean?
should I prefer to live my life as I wish and disappear
from your life and our family,
I could have certainly done it.
However, I am still your daughter.
Should I plan to take any course of action,
I still wish to have your permission or approval first.
Are you perhaps threatening me?
Not at all, Father.
I am only explaining to you about my process of thinking.
Is staying with the person you love the most important thing in your life?
Not entirely true, Father.
Should that be the case,
I would have chosen to run away to England with Lady Pin.
Yet in fact, I do love my family as much.
Whether it is you, whom I admire and worship above all.
Or Mother, whom I never wish to be away from her.
And both of my brothers also.
I do not wish to arrange a proper marriage
to put you and our family to shame.
All I wish is to stay quietly by her side…
and grow old together at the Pine Palace.
People would only see us as best companions who prefer a solitary life.
That is all I want.
Can you please allow me to do that, Father?
Does this mean if I am to refuse,
you will choose to leave this palace?
Yes.
What did His Highness say?
I have told him everything.
Now, it is up to him to decide.
Father.
I’d like to talk to you… / If it is about Anin,
just leave.
I do not want to talk about it right now.
What did your father say?
Where is Father?
He only stays in his room and still has not come out.
Let’s sit down and eat.
He is right.
The table is full of your favourite dishes today.
Let’s eat together, Anin.
Pia, serve the rice.
Yes, Your Highness.
Sit down, dear.
Yes, Mother.
Since that day the princess went to talk to His Highness,
he has been quiet and never left his room to eat anything, Your Highness.
What did Princess Alisa do then?
What else could she do, Your Highness?
She could only let it be.
His Highness did not even allow Prince Anan to see him, Your Highness.
He must be very furious.
This is such a serious issue for our palace.
It also has never happened before.
He must be pondering hard over it.
If your father does not approve of your relationship with Lady Pin,
what will you do?
I plan to leave this palace…
and move to England with Lady Pin.
Are you aware of the consequences you will face with such decision?
Living in England will not be as easy and comfortable
as a life here in our palace, dear.
How will you survive then?
Yes, Mother. I am well aware of it.
Lady Pin and I will try to find a job and build our family there.
Please don’t worry, Mother.
Of course, I must be worried. I am your mother after all.
But if it is your happiness,
and you have deeply reflected upon it,
I will not stop you.
I only want you to know…
that I will always be here,
and I will always worry about you and care for you.
Have you told your aunt about your plan
to take Lady Pin to live in England with you?
Not yet, Mother.
Your aunt loves Lady Pin very dearly.
Will she let you take her niece away from her?
I am worried about that too.
Why would you like to see me, Your Highness?
You were quite unwell recently. Are you fully recovered?
Yes, Your Highness.
I’d like to apologize to you.
Apologize about what, Your Highness?
For forcing you upon marriage…
and putting you in distress.
Can you forgive me?
I understand that you love me more than anyone.
And everything that you do…
is all because you wish me to have the best in life.
I have never felt mad or angry with you, Your Highness.
But my well-wish almost destroyed the rest of your life.
Without you,
there would never be me today.
Your Highness.
Princess Alisa would like to request for your presence.
Please come in.
Have a seat, dear.
These are for you and Lady Pin.
Why would you give us these precious gifts, Your Highness?
Lady Pin and I have not done any merits or virtue to deserve such gifts.
I only wish to do it merely for my own satisfaction.
But…
There is no but.
Inside these boxes are beautifully crafted ancient diamond jewellery.
I’d like to give them to Lady Pin.
And this box…
is for you.
By giving me and Lady Pin such invaluable gifts,
are you perhaps expecting anything in return, Your Highness?
Please only keep in mind that…
what I am doing is the most justifiable and appropriate thing to do.
What did you just say?
You are going to move to England with Lady Pin?
Yes.
That is why I’d like to ask for your permission first.
What did His Highness say about this?
I told Father that I will not be married for the rest of my life.
For I only wish to spend my life with Lady Pin,
the woman I have always been in love with.
But Father still has not said anything yet.
So, I believe this is perhaps the only way…
that would allow me to be with Lady Pin.
Now, I understand…
why Princess Alisa has given me those precious gifts earlier.
She must have predicted it.
Did Mother do that?
I haven’t a clue before.
Your mother must have known…
that you would come to talk to me about Lady Pin.
Mother is so kind to me.
As for your request,
please allow me some time to ponder over it.
I believe His Highness must not be very pleased
with your decision to move away to England.
I’d like to suggest you to try talking to your father again.
You want to talk to His Highness about the princess?
Yes, Your Highness.
I don’t want to see Princess Anin having a dispute with her father.
The Loyal Pin
Princess Alisa has asked me to give these sets of jewellery to you.
To me, Your Highness?
These gifts somehow imply that Her Highness has granted you her approval…
and would like to propose you for Princess Anin.
As for your plan to move to England,
if I were to speak honestly,
I do not wish you to live that far away.
But since you are happy to do it,
I will not stop you.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I only wish you would reconsider it again…
whether this is the best option there is.
By moving away so suddenly despite His Highness’s disagreement,
deep down,
are you certain that you and the princess would find happiness there?
What should I do, Brother?
I don’t want to leave this palace.
But with this situation,
I’m afraid I do not have any choice.
Someday
I’m sure Father will understand you.
I will try to talk to him for you.
Please don’t be sad.
You want to talk to His Highness about the princess?
Yes, Your Highness.
I don’t want to see Princess Anin having a dispute with her father.
I want to do something and stand up for the princess.
What if His Highness gets even more furious?
Whatever will be will be, Your Highness.
But I will not run away.
Nor will I stay silent.
From now on, no matter what you decide to do…
I will always stand by you and support you.
Wait.
Where is His Highness at the moment?
In the study room, my lady.
Are you bringing this to him?
Yes, my lady.
Let me do it.
Your Highness.
I am here to see Lady Pin.
She went to see your father.
You are here to talk about Anin, aren’t you?
Yes, Your Highness.
Just say it then.
I’d like to apologize…
for causing you such a displeasure and irritation, Your Highness.
I am fully aware that I am just a commoner.
And that I have been presumptuous.
But you still do it.
But the princess and I truly love each other, Your Highness.
So what? Hasn’t your wish already been fulfilled?
Why are you telling me this?
The princess is a straightforward person.
She is very honest with her feeling.
That is why she has decided to go away.
On the outside, she might look strong and determined.
But in fact, she is devastated inside.
For she loves you…
and her family more than anything.
Must she take this choice, the princess will surely be in so much pain.
I do not want your decision
to create more scars in her heart, Your Highness.
Are you saying it is my fault?
I am here to beg for your mercy.
Please don’t forbid us from loving each other, Your Highness.
The princess and I
only wish to stay by each other’s side to take care of each other…
and grow old together as companions.
I promise…
that we will not do anything to tarnish your name and reputation.
Can you please give us your approval, Your Highness?
How dare you!
Not only you blame it on me.
You even have the audacity to ask for my approval.
Why didn’t you tell me first?
I’m sorry.
I wanted to do something for you too.
I sincerely love her.
I do not wish to see the person I love living the rest of her life in distress.
If you wish to punish me,
I am willing to accept it, Your Highness.
Fine, you said so yourself.
I will never lose Anin to anyone.
She must stay here with me.
Are you really going to let Anin go, Your Highness?
Do you not love her anymore?
Why must you put her in such a difficult situation?
I will never let her live outside this palace.
She must stay here with me.
What about Lady Pin, Your Highness?
If Lady Pin is a problem,
then I will put an end to it.
Isn’t that a car from the front palace, my lady?
Why is it here at the Lotus Palace?
Please don’t! Don’t do it, please!
Please don’t take them away! Please!
Your Highness!
Please don’t take them away!
What is happening, Your Highness?
Are those my bags?
His Highness has ordered you
to move out of the Lotus Palace immediately.
Move out of this palace immediately?
Please come with me, my lady.
Please, my lady.
Your Highness!
Lady Pin!
Can you not take her now?
Let me talk to His Highness first.
I’m afraid not. It is time.
Please get in the car, my lady.
Your Highness!
Can I at least say goodbye to her first?
No, my lady.
His Highness has forbidden it.
Where are you taking her?
We are not allowed to tell you, Your Highness.
Your Highness!
Where are you taking her?
Lady Pin!
Your Highness!
Don’t you worry, dear!
I will go talk to His Highness for you!
Your Highness!
Lady Pin!
My lady!
Where are you taking me?
Can you tell me where you are taking me?
Are you aware that this relationship is against our moral and tradition?
Are you aware of the consequences of this choice of yours?
Where am I? Please tell me.
The Loyal Pin
Ouch!
Where am I? Please tell me.
Where am I?
Please tell me.
What is happening, Anin?
Why am I here?
Because this is our home.
What do you mean?
I come to beg you for one last time.
Please have sympathy for me.
May I ask you then.
Are you certain you will not change your mind later on…
if one day you happen to meet the man you are interested in?
I have fallen in love with Lady Pin since when I was 14.
And I will always love her for the rest of my life.
Anin.
Are you aware that this relationship is against our moral and tradition?
No one has ever accepted or done it before.
Are you aware of the consequences of this choice of yours?
I am, Father.
It might not be acceptable in our society today.
But in the future, I truly believe that this kind of love…
will be accepted widely.
Our world will be more open and of equality.
Whether men or women,
all of us shall have freedom to portray ourselves and our love.
And become whatever it is that we want to be.
Most importantly, marriage shall be acceptable…
both socially and legally regardless of our gender.
I truly believe that love is far beyond definition.
It shall not be restricted only between a man and a woman.
Just like the love I have for Lady Pin.
I have never considered anything else but her heart.
And even until now, the love I have for her…
has never changed.
No matter what hardship I might face in the future,
I will not be afraid.
For I am surrounded by the people who love me dearly…
like you,
Mother,
both of my brothers,
and Lady Pin.
That is all I ever need in my life.
Father.
I’d like to talk to you about…
About Anin?
Do you know how bold and daring your sister is?
I do, Father.
And you still wish to talk to me for her?
But Father, am I right to understand that deep down…
you have never intended to find a man for her?
Were you to do that,
you would not have waited for this long.
Don’t you try to outsmart me.
I only have yet found a man who deserves to be with Anin.
If such a man does not exist now,
wouldn’t it be impossible to find one in the future?
If Anin wishes to marry without giving up her royal title,
she must marry a Serene Highness Prince or one with a higher rank.
Among those of suitable ranks,
I still do not see anyone who deserves to be with Anin.
I have always been of this opinion…
that no such a man deserves to be with Anin.
It could be because I am very fond of her.
What if it is a lady, Father?
Does a lady deserve to be with Anin?
You are right.
How odd.
When I picture my Anin with any man,
I often find those men inferior to her.
Yet,
when I picture her with Lady Pin,
I do not find anything wrong with it.
As if it is the right place for both of them.
Then, can you please not force her to act against her own will?
My marriage was also arranged out of conventionality.
And I am not able to be with the woman I truly love.
So, I do not want my only sister…
to have the same fate as I do.
But what Anin wants
is beyond what anyone could haver ever done for her.
You do know how much I love her.
No matter what she wishes for, be it a star or the moon,
I am willing to get it for her.
But this time, what she wants…
is the simplest thing ever.
She only wishes to be with the person she loves.
And grow old together with her.
How come you cannot not give it to her now, Father?
She must stay here with me.
What about Lady Pin, Your Highness?
If Lady Pin is a problem,
then I will put an end to it.
What are you going to do, Your Highness?
I will go talk to Pattamika and make a proper proposal…
so that Lady Pin and Anin can finally live together.
What do you mean, Your Highness?
What made you change your mind?
Well, since Anin, Lady Pin, Anan, and even you…
all came marching in and try to persuade me,
if I still remain silent…
I’m afraid everyone in this palace might also come and try to persuade me too.
Why are you giving me all these valuable gifts again, Your Highness?
We’d like to make a proposal…
And ask you to allow Lady Pin to move to the Pine Palace and stay with Anin permanently.
What made you give in to this idea so easily, Your Highness?
As long as Anin will stay,
whatever she wishes for, I am more than willing to give it to her.
As a matter of fact, Father is worrying…
that he still could not find anyone suitable for Anin.
In his view, none of the men deserves to be with her.
Anin’s request was perfectly in accordance with his intention.
So, he agreed to grant her his approval…
for not going to live her life in marriage.
As long as you are not against the idea,
every other thing should be fine.
What about you, Your Highness? Will you agree with the proposal?
Your father has already said so.
What else could I say?
But I’m afraid I cannot allow Lady Pin to move to the Pine Place permanently.
But then…
I can only allow Lady Pin to mainly stay there.
However, she must come to visit the Lotus Palace at times.
My heart will never be at peace if I must see all of Lady Pin’s belongings…
being moved out of the room where she has been staying
since when she was a little girl.
This has already been very kind of you.
There is one more thing…
that I’d like to ask from you, Princess.
What is it?
Please take care of Lady Pin better than how I have taken care of her.
That is the only thing I would like to ask from you.
Yes.
I promise that I will always take good care of her…
for as long as I am still breathing.
Father has already agreed with Princess Patt about us.
So, this is like our first night after the wedding.
What about your father’s order to have me moved out of the Lotus Palace?
So that you can live with me instead.
Were you fooling me?
I just did not have a chance to tell you first.
Does this mean Princess Patt, Prik, and Pia also knew?
Your Highness!
Lady Pin!
Don’t you worry, dear!
I will go talk to His Highness for you!
Lady Pin!
Your Highness!
Ha Ha Ha...
Lady Pin!
How was it?
Did I completely fool her?
I never thought you would be this good, Your Highness.
I have never done anything like this before.
If it weren’t for His Highness, I wouldn’t have done it.
Those tears were pretty.
Weren’t they?
So, everyone is in this charade together?
They just wanted to surprise you.
Do you know how scared and fretful I was?
You don’t have to worry about it anymore.
Let’s go take a look at our room.
Lady Pin must be quite petrified.
Father has set up such a big stage play this time.
It was because Anin said she wanted to surprise Lady Pin.
I thought it would be fun, so I decided to join her.
Now I know whom Anin is taking after.
Everyone had to play their role according to your script, Your Highness.
I still could not believe that you would change your mind so easily
and granted them your approval, Your Highness.
It is because Lady Pin is your niece.
I trust you wholeheartedly that you have brought her up well.
That is why I also trust Lady Pin…
to take care of Anin until they grow old together.
Father is in fact not against what Anin is.
He only worries about her social status.
Yes.
Because in the end,
no matter what she is, she will always be my daughter.
And I love her so much
that I could never force her to do anything against her will.
Am I correct to say that
you are completely enamoured with your daughter, Father?
I love you all the same.
Let’s celebrate. Cheers!
Let’s unwrap Lady Pin’s gift next.
It seems Prince Anan’s gift
might even look inferior when compared to Lady Pin’s.
The Loyal Pin
What are you doing?
Why are you smiling so gleefully?
I’m trying to find a place to put this picture of yours.
Should it be that corner…
Or this corner?
You can put it anywhere you like.
I do not like to look my own picture though.
But I do.
You’re smiling sheepishly. It’s adorable.
Who would be grinning from ear to ear like you?
I never know that you have also kept this picture of mine.
Why should I not keep it?
Why do you keep it?
I already told you.
That I was able to go through those time
while waiting for you by looking at your picture.
I was able to put myself to sleep…
because of seeing your face in the picture.
From now on,
you can go to sleep with me in your arms every night.
Isn’t it good?
It’s a dream that I never dared to dream.
A person like me, sleeping by your side every night.
And growing old with you.
However unreal it might seem to you,
it is happening right in front of you now.
Do you know…
that tonight is our first night after we are officially together?
How so?
Because tonight is the first night that we will start a family together…
under approval and acceptance from Father, Mother, and our aunt.
Then, shall we start our first night now?
Do you like the gift that I gave you?
Very much, Brother.
It is exactly what I am looking for.
Anin, if you keep unwrapping the gifts in front of everyone like this,
wouldn’t my gift look so cheap comparing to our brother’s gift?
That’s good. So that next year you’ll buy me a better gift.
Let’s unwrap Lady Pin’s gift next.
It seems Prince Anan’s gift
might even look inferior when compared to Lady Pin’s.
Can you put this ring on my finger in front of everyone?
Let’s do that.
So that I can be your witness.
Do it! Do it! Do it!
As I have given you my promise,
should one day I find a ring that deserves to be on your finger…
I will put in on your finger to make you completely mine.
Can you please accept this ring…
and become mine for the rest of our lives?
I have in fact…
given my heart and soul to you since the very first day we met.
And this…
is a gift from me.
I baked it myself especially for you, Princess.
Prik and I also helped too, Your Highness.
Yes, Your Highness.
It is my sincere gratitude, Your Highness.
1 2 3.
Please let me help, Your Highness.
Let’s cut the cake together.
I’d like to share my happiness,
all the good things,
and my everything in life with you.
Yes.
I am also willing to share my happiness…
and my everything with you for the rest of my life.
I am 3 months pregnant now, Your Highness.
Is it true?
The Loyal Pin
[5 years later]
After His Highness and Princess Pattamika
had granted approval for me to stay with Anin at the Pine Palace,
Lady Parawatee had brought another good news
to our Savettawarit Palace with her pregnancy.
I am 3 months pregnant now, Your Highness.
Is it true?
Am I going to be an aunt now?
Congratulations, Brother.
Everyone’s hearts were full of joy especially for Prince Anantawut…
for he had always wished to have a daughter
like Princess Anilaphat, his sister.
Can you hear me?
[5 years later]
Eventually, Prince Anan’s dream has finally come true.
Lady Parawatee gave birth to a daughter
who looked exactly like her Aunt Anilaphat.
It was as if they were created by the same hands of God.
Aunt Anin, please wait for me!
Quit playing now, both of you.
Please don’t!
Prince Anan has named his daughter ‘Alinrada’ to match with Anilaphat.
This little princess is so fond of her aunt than she is of her own mother.
Try to be more gentle.
You are ruining the fruits.
Let me show you who to do it.
Princess Patt is still busy with all the chores as usual.
The only difference is…she seems to be less strict.
Perhaps, it is because the princess and I
have broken so many rules and traditions
that she can finally let everything be.
Remove this part first.
Hold it near the end.
Please wait for me, Princess! / Princess Alin!
As for Prik and Pia,
they are now Alin's minions
who must keep running after their new master all day.
Princess Alin! I’m tired already!
Please wait, Your Highness!
Serve you right!
You had to run around after Princess Anin when she was young.
And now you must do the same with Lady Alin.
Just you wait, Pia.
Please wait, Your Highness! / Wait for me, Your Highness!
Your Highness!
As for Lady Uang, she sent us a letter
telling us how our story has given her courage
to refuse a marriage with Lord Muang-Rahm.
And we have heard that Kueakiat is now a father of two children.
Anin is now teaching full-time at the university upon her father’s advice.
Anin.
Yes?
Here is your lunch.
Thank you.
I’m leaving then.
Did you forget something?
Yes.
Apart from the translation work, my main job is to take care of Anin,
sending her off to work in the morning and wait for her to return home.
My princess, please eat something first.
I must also babysit my little princess niece
who is always waiting eagerly for her aunt to return from work.
I’m full now. /  Already?
Knock, knock, knock.
Aunty is back.
Hello, my dear.
I miss you so much.
I have been waiting for so long today.
What would you like to play?
A family of three. I want Aunty to be the father.
And Aunt Pin, the mother.
Do you still have to role play it, my princess?
You already look like a family of three.
What else do you want to play?
Riding horse send to city.
I see.
Yes.
Shall we?
Okay. Can I please have your bag?
Let’s go.
1 2 3
Go! Go chase Prik.
Me again, Your Highness?
I’m so scared, Your Highness.
It’s my turn to chase you now.
I’m going to bite you, Princess!
Is it fun?
Hold me tight.
What are you doing ?
I’m not going to tell you.
I believe it is time to change the name of this Pine Palace
to Pin Palace instead.
Why would you say that?
Because you have been taken care of the palace so well.
You seem to love it much more than I do.
So, maybe we should change the name of this palace…
to Pin Palace instead. Do you agree?
I like the old name better.
You drew a picture of this Pine Palace since when you were little.
I can still remember it vividly.
What did I draw?
You drew a small house…
surrounded by many pine trees.
Then you told me it was the house of your dream.
Look.
This is the house of my dream.
But it is much smaller than the front palace.
I prefer it small and cozy.
Wherever I look, we will always see each other.
It’s very dreamy.
I will build it next to the Lotus Palace.
So that you can always see me.
Who would want to see you all the time?
But if one day I do have a house of my own,
I will ask you to live there with me.
I promise.
At first,
I did not understand the meaning of it.
Until I finally had a chance to live with you at the Pine Palace.
It was only then that I came to realize its true meaning.
A house that no matter where I look,
I will always see you right next to me.
Such house is indeed warm and cozy.
I love you, Anin.
I love you too.
And I want you to know that…
for as long as I live, you will always be loved.
🎵I compare you to a beautiful diamond🎵
🎵You’re as sweet as five-month honey🎵
Come.
Let me read your diary.
🎵You’re as sweet as five-month honey🎵
🎵Drops of diamonds twinkle in the sky🎵
No.
Let me see.
🎵Drops of diamonds twinkle in the sky🎵
No, you can’t.
Let me see.
🎵Drops of diamonds twinkle in the sky🎵
No.
🎵Did they come from the sky or what?🎵
a little.
No.
🎵Did they come from the sky or what?🎵
🎵The drops are here, don’t be unhappy🎵
No.
🎵Let people all over the world cry🎵
🎵Drops of diamonds glitter cheerfully🎵
🎵Too far away to touch🎵
🎵Though when the diamonds drop from the sky🎵
🎵They fall, and the sky is shaken🎵
🎵The stars are sad gems🎵
🎵They won’t hold back the sad tears🎵
🎵I reach out for the drops of diamonds🎵
🎵Carelessly loving and dreaming🎵
🎵Drops of diamonds drop from bright dust🎵
🎵Like they’re in darkness🎵
🎵I reach out for the drops of diamonds🎵
🎵Carelessly loving and dreaming🎵
🎵Drops of diamonds drop from bright dust🎵
🎵Like they’re in darkness🎵
The Loyal Pin