We will expel these 75 students
by the end of this school year.
If you stay here, you can chase your goal.
So don't easily say you'll quit!
Please!
Let Miyazawa stay in school!
Enough is enough!
No matter what's said,
Miyazawa is expelled.
MEISHIN PRIVATE ACADEMY
I act all high and mighty, preaching…
I'm going to quit school.
I'm sorry.
Yet I cry when things go wrong.
What a lame adult I am.
Hey!
-Come on!
-I know how the students will see me.
Oh, no! She's here!
-She came!
-Oh, no!
-You guys go!
-Still, isn't that a bit much?
Hey, hey! Shizuka-sensei!
-Morning.
-Come here!
Wait, I haven't changed my shoes yet.
-It's fine. This is serious.
-What?
-Oh, no!
-Let's go!
Run!
Hey, go to class!
-Hey! Move it, quickly!
-Reality…
often surpasses the imagination.
Go back to class! Don't take pictures!
SHIZUKA URUMI A MURDERER
Whoa, what is this?
Step back.
Get to your seats.
Hey, put your phones away.
Why are you silent, Urumi-sensei?
If you know something about this poster,
please explain.
The other teachers are confused too.
Stop being silent. Say something.
What's the point?
No way Shizuka-sensei
would ever kill anyone.
She would never do that.
Even if she did,
it's not like she'd confess.
You think the real culprit
would confess just like that?
There's no point in asking.
Right, Shizuka-sensei?
You're not helping her.
That poster was just some prank
to harass her.
We should focus on finding out who did it.
We're investigating it now.
But the culprit
avoided the cameras,
they pasted the posters in
the camera blind spots.
There's no footage of them at all.
That means…
It might've been someone among us
who knew the camera layout.
Could it be?
You're saying the culprit
is among us teachers?
I said maybe.
We'll find out later.
What we should be focusing on now
is how to handle the parents.
If this blows up and causes panic…
Urumi-sensei,
I expect you to handle this appropriately.
How do I do this "appropriately"?
All this happening at once, and today,
Ms. Kyoko is away on a business trip.
What should I do?
This "murderer" thing is crazy.
She always acts so haughty, too.
It's just a prank, obviously.
-By who?
-I don't know.
-But she isn't like that…
-What do you know?
They want to ask if that poster's true,
but they can't…
I can really feel it…
Of course it's hard to ask.
Sensei, are you a murderer?
Such a direct question.
I mean, everyone's curious, right?
-Actually, me too.
-Me too.
-Right?
-Once the tension breaks,
curiosity takes over.
I'm sorry…
for upsetting everyone.
-I…
-Sensei.
This thing is going viral.
Will you be okay?
SHIZUKA URUMI IS A MURDERER
Tazawa uploaded it online.
-Nanami?
-Delete it.
You uploaded it right?
-Why are you…
Why are you defending her?
You like her, don't you?
Nanami... likes me?
What are you, a kid?
Pathetic.
Right?
But for a second, I was flustered, too.
How embarrassing.
What do you mean, a kid?
This isn't the time
to be thinking about that.
Why do I have to do what you say?
Shut up and delete it.
You shut up. It's too late now anyway.
-I said delete it!
-What?
Quit it!
Back to your seats.
Urumi-sensei.
A parent from Class 2-10
just contacted us.
They said they want to speak
to you directly.
Oh, no!
Sorry I'm late!
I'm sorry.
-Let's go.
-We're going now.
-Let's go in.
-Leave it to me.
-Geez!
‪I can't get over it.‬
What am I even supposed to say?
I can't lie either.
SHIZUKA URUMI IS A MURDERER
Urumi-sensei.
What is it?
What are you going to tell the parents?
Well…
It seems like you don't know what to say.
That's correct.
Then just follow my instructions
and say exactly what I tell you to.
Take a video.
We are deeply sorry for this incident.
Before explaining anything,
apologize sincerely first.
If you start with an apology,
it'll catch them off guard.
They can't respond with anger.
Right now…
everyone's understandably upset,
and I truly regret causing such concern.
The content of the apology matters.
But,
don't admit the school
is entirely at fault.
Make it clear the school is also a victim,
and show solidarity
by taking sides with the parents.
I'll take whatever criticism comes my way.
But still…
I'm just as outraged that
our students were shaken by this.
No…
I'm more outraged than that.
In fact, expressing more anger
than the parents can be effective.
Then…
could you
explain why this says,
"Urumi Shizuka-sensei is a murderer"?
Is there any truth to that?
-There is…
-Of course,
No way would we accept the poster as true.
Of course not. It's nonsense.
If the culprit turns out to be a student,
the school will have to suggest
punishing them.
As a school,
we will take appropriate action.
Those parents don't want
to cause a fuss and get a student
punished. It's just bad taste.
So that might make them
back off a bit.
So for the students' sake,
it's best we don't be too eager
to find the culprit.
I think we should
proceed cautiously for now.
How does that sound?
Well…
-Yes, that makes sense.
-Thank you.
It's frustrating.
Huh? What is?
When I followed Moriguchi-sensei's advice,
everything went smoothly.
-Isn't that a good thing?
-No, it's not.
We just covered it up
with vague, empty words.
"Proceed with caution"
is the same as doing nothing.
Even if you're right,
no need to get so frustrated.
It just bothers me that
everything went his way.
If they say it like…
Come here, hurry!
Right…
What's wrong, Mrs. Tazawa?
I just saw my son…
Taichi!
What? What happened?
What are you doing?
Blo-…Blood! You're bleeding!
-What was it?
-Sorry!
It's bad. Kaito…
INCOMING CALL - MEISHIN PRIVATE ACADEMY
Yes, this is Nanami.
Tazawa…
Did Nanami really hit you?
What?
Are you saying you don't believe him?
It's not that I don't believe him.
When did I ever hit you?
You did hit me!
-Don't make stuff up!
-Nanami…
Mind what you say, okay?
-Their versions of the story don't match.
-Yes.
-Tazawa "criticized" Nanami's attitude.
-You.
You're looking down on me, right?
What are you talking about?
You always look at me
like I'm beneath you!
Shut up!
Tazawa says
he was attacked, unprovoked.
-Nanami said…
-Stop lying!
KAITO NANAMI
You always look at me
like I'm beneath you!
Say something!
Hey!
Pathetic.
He says he just left
without doing anything.
This is a problem…
By the way, Urumi-sensei,
Have you contacted Nanami's mother?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Kaito has caused trouble.
We haven't determined
Kaito is at fault yet.
But…
I believe
he did resort to violence.
Um…
She said she couldn't come today
due to work.
Isn't that a bit irresponsible?
Right, Vice-Principal?
Work…
So, what happened?
The conversation went nowhere,
so we agreed to talk again tomorrow.
Are you okay?
If I look okay to you, you need glasses.
First the posters, now this.
Today's just been nonstop problems.
So many problems,
I feel like I'm going to puke.
If you're stressed,
you should go to the ocean.
The ocean?
Looking at the sea helps
you forget bad things, right?
This time of year,
the Kamakura coast is great.
That place helps you forget everything.
Just looking at the ocean
makes it all go away.
I wish I were such a simple creature.
So, Tazawa and Nanami…
who do you believe is telling the truth?
Nanami hit Tazawa.
Isn't that fine?
You can't just decide that so easily.
Nanami had used violence
back in middle school.
Still, you shouldn't…
Japan's recidivism rate
is around 50%.
People who do bad things
end up doing it again.
Also, don't forget.
He's on this list.
He's a student this school
has no need for.
That makes this situation
our chance to expel him.
-Yes.
-However…
But Nanami didn't admit to hitting Tazawa.
Even so,
it's still possible to expel him.
Vice-Principal, are you really fine with
just obeying Moriguchi-sensei?
He's the next board chairman anyway.
Of course we obey him.
You're a cold person.
But when we're alone, you're so sweet.
Lately,
we haven't gone for a meal at all.
We…
shouldn't meet too often.
But you still do it anyway.
Bad people just repeat
the same mistakes in the end.
You're terrible.
This place,
is in sight of a security camera.
What?
Wow, your shirt is dirty!
NUMBER 8 STAIRS
Did you know?
Kaito beat up
a classmate in middle school.
-Really messed that guy up.
-Really?
-Kaito…
-Is that true?
-He was bleeding…
-Isn't that scary?
-Scary.
-His face…
-Poor kid…
Scary stuff, huh.
Let's start today's homeroom session.
-Where's Nanami?
-Looks like he already left.
He went home?
Maybe he felt awkward
after hitting Tazawa?
What are you talking about?
He's the one lying.
But he has a record.
Nanami had a violent incident
in middle school.
It seems so.
Do you think Kaito-kun
really hit Tazawa-kun?
What do you think?
Kaito-kun is quiet and reserved.
You can't tell what he's thinking.
But before…
When Hina-chan tried to spread your video…
That wasn't funny.
I don't know much about his past,
But I don't think Kaito-kun would do
something like that.
-I didn't hit him.
-Don't lie.
Why don't you believe your own son?
You already did it before.
I just can't trust you.
I knew it.
You really are
just like your father.
Do whatever you want.
Just stop making me suffer.
I'm tired…
All right, for now,
let's just not think about anything.
Ms. Kyoko is on a business trip.
I'll sleep for now.
URUMI
Why are you here?
I came back.
Because I was worried about you.
You don't seem worried…
Want something to eat?
I'm good. I don't have an appetite anyway.
That prank was terrible, huh.
Posters all over the school…
But the part about me
being a murderer is true.
HIGH SCHOOL GIRL FELL FROM FOOTBRIDGE.
BULLYING TO BLAME?
FUNERAL
That wasn't all your fault.
Not "all," yes…
Maybe someone who knows
about that incident
-put up the posters?
-Shi-chan.
I get why you're panicking,
but don't overthink it now.
Sorry to say this
without considering how you must feel,
but I also heard about Nanami and Tazawa.
Moriguchi-sensei will probably try
to expel Nanami, regardless of the facts.
Like with Miyazawa.
If we want to protect the students
from Moriguchi-sensei's tyranny,
we need your help, Shi-chan.
You don't want
to see them in tears, right?
I…
really…
That's all I want to say.
I must get back to my business trip.
You came all the way here
just to say that?
Wait, you're leaving already?
I brought more food.
I'll eat it.
-I brought beer too.
-I'll have some.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
Damn it…
Good morning.
MEISHIN PRIVATE ACADEMY
-What's wrong, Nanami?
-Got a minute?
-What?
-Sensei…
could you come with me for a bit?
-What? We both have classes.
-There's somewhere I want to go.
No, no.
-You can't.
-I was the one
who put up the posters.
If you want to know why,
come with me.
Hey, is Kaito absent today?
Seems like it.
Maybe he really did hit Tazawa.
Everyone, take a seat.
Why are you here today?
Shizuka-sensei took the day off.
She's feeling under the weather.
I'll be doing homeroom in her place.
Do you know why Kaito's absent?
I haven't been informed.
They say looking at the sea
helps you forget bad things.
Are you one of those people?
But…
no matter how long I stare at it,
I can't forget a thing.
That's good.
What?
It means you aren't so simple that you
forget bad stuff just by looking at sea.
Was that a compliment?
I'm not sure.
Anyway, your promise.
The posters. Why did you do that?
Nanami is even dumber than I thought.
He skips school without clearing his name.
Honestly,
it makes it easier to expel him.
To be honest,
I think Tazawa is the one lying.
What do you mean?
Earlier, in homeroom, he was restless.
Bouncing his leg, touching his face.
They are classic signs of a guilty person.
I thought you were just
a dumb, hot-blooded teacher,
but you observe your students closely.
Even if I'm dumb,
I'm doing more for the students than you.
So…
ｗhy would Tazawa lie?
I don't know.
I see.
Then you can't protect Nanami.
Do you really want to see him
expelled that badly?
Yes.
His violent past in middle school,
coming from a poor family,
For Meishin's future, students like him…
are a burden!
Getting angry and violent already?
At this rate,
you'll be fired before he is.
You really are stupid.
Now,
lower your fist, please.
Lower your fist.
-You really gonna hit me?
-Even if I do, I'll just say I didn't.
-That's not good.
-It doesn't matter.
Violence solves nothing.
Stop it!
There are cameras. You can't hide it.
‪NUMBER 8 STAIRS‬
Answer me.
It was a lie.
Lie?
I didn't do any of that.
I lied just to get you to come here.
What?
When I was little,
I saw a TV show where a student
and a teacher
went on a date at the beach.
That's why I wanted to come here with you.
I remember something.
A forbidden romance
between teacher and student…
Does that mean Nanami likes me?
Is that why he lied?
There's something I want you to hear.
What?
What? What is this?
Why does it feel like
you're about to confess?
Sensei.
How do you get people to believe you?
What are you saying?
I didn't hit Tazawa.
But…
no one will believe me.
Why do you think that?
In 2nd year of middle school,
I hit a classmate.
I got mad over something dumb and hit him.
He fell down from the punch,
and ended up seriously hurt.
Apparently, the other students
found out about it.
No one trusts someone
who has made a mistake before.
-That's not true.
-It is.
Even my mom didn't believe me!
I think…
he did resort to violence.
What happened with you and your mother?
I hit a classmate
-in middle school.
-Hey.
Why did you do that?
-Kaito?
-I just lost my temper.
Are you
that kind of person?
-Answer me!
-My mother pleading to me…
-I…
-You wouldn't do…
Shut up already!
‪Sorry.‬
You're…
just like him.
Just like that man.
My dad was abusive for such a long time.
They finally got divorced
when I started middle school.
But I am his son.
What if I turn into someone like him?
I'm scared of it.
It made me angry.
But you already know this, don't you?
Sensei, you are SEE, right?
Are you?
I told you before…
I don't know what you mean.
Then,
what about that sticker on your phone?
That is SEE's sticker.
SEE
I WRITE ABOUT THINGS THAT INTEREST ME.
Back then,
I read something SEE wrote
and instantly got hooked.
LATEST ARTICLES
I'M ANGRY. WHY AM I SO HAPPY?
I really related
to SEE's joy and rage.
I thought maybe… SEE could help me
overcome my fears.
I thought so and messaged them.
MESSAGE FROM SEE.
I was suprised.
SEE replied with a really long text.
NICE TO MEET YOU. I'M SEE.
"People can only become
the kind of person they want to be.
If you end up like your father,
it's not his fault. It's your choice.
If you want to take a step forward,
-you can do it.
If you want to stop, you can stop.
If you want to take a leap, take it.
Your future is built
from all the choices you make.
So make the decisions
that bring you closer to the person
you want to be.
-Then someday,
-you'll..."
-you'll become that person.
That message…
really saved me.
But…
SEE vanished from the internet…
I never got to say thank you.
So,
when you showed up as my teacher,
I was shocked.
Yes.
We will be waiting.
Goodbye.
Looks like it will go well.
I'll see you later.
Yes.
Are you sure it's okay like this?
Urami-sensei.
What happened?
Moriguchi-sensei
will have a meeting with Nanami's mother
today at four p.m.
Nanami's mother doesn't
trust his son at all,
and she has left the matter to the school.
Moriguchi-sensei is
taking advantage of that
to push for expulsion.
Without even hearing Nanami's side?
The school can expel a student
with parental consent,
even without theirs.
No...
Today, Nanami's
been absent without notice, right?
Yes.
We have to get him here fast
and convince his mother.
Understood.
But why would you tell me this?
I'm still a teacher, you know.
Since that incident in middle school,
things have been tense
between me and Mom.
But like SEE said,
I tried my best in high school
to become the version of me I want to be.
If I did that,
maybe she'd start believing in me too.
But…
So you didn't hit Tazawa?
I did think about it.
But…
I don't want to be like him.
I chose not to.
I see.
No matter what I do,
Mom won't believe me.
Even if I change,
if no one else believes it,
it doesn't matter.
I…
don't know what to do anymore.
INCOMING CALL URAMI
Hello?
Shizuka-sensei, are you all right?
I still feel kind of sick.
Sorry to bring this up now,
but it's urgent.
What happened?
Moriguchi called Nanami's mother
to school at four today.
He's going to talk about expulsion.
-What?
-Today,
Nanami was absent without notice.
-Yes…
-Moriguchi
plans to expel him by getting his mother's
agreement while he's not there.
If she consents,
they can go through with it.
What?
Shizuka-sensei,
can you go to the school
and talk to his mother
before Moriguchi gets to her?
It's three p.m. now.
It takes an hour to get there.
I think I can make it there.
Thanks.
I'll do everything I can from here.
Understood.
Nanami, let's go back to school.
-Hurry!
-Yes.
-Sensei's here.
-Why?
What's going on?
Tazawa, I need to talk to you.
TAXI FARE 8900 YEN
Climbing fast…!
Expulsion, huh?
I won't let them expel you.
I'm paying this much…
TAXI FARE 9100 YEN
Woah!
WHAT KIND OF VIOLENCE
THAT IMPULSE HAPPENS TO ANYONE
MRS. NANAMI, YOU'RE JUST LIKE
JAPANESE SOCIETY
IF YOU WON'T ACCEPT HIM…
MEISHIN PRIVATE ACADEMY
Thank you for coming today.
His homeroom teacher, Urumi-sensei,
is absent due to illness.
Moriguchi-sensei
-will join us in her stead.
-Nice to meet you.
-Get out!
-Okay.
-Let's go!
-Yes.
Regarding what they were doing
behind the gym…
Nanami himself isn't here.
The school has no choice but to take that
as a refusal to speak up.
Is that acceptable?
I apologize for the trouble.
So that means,
What Nanami said was a lie,
and Nanami hit Tazawa.
He would be admitting that, correct?
Yes.
Urumi-sensei. Weren't you feeling unwell?
I'm fine now. Sorry.
Hello, I'm Shizuka Urumi,
Nanami's homeroom teacher.
May I speak with you for a moment?
Unfortunately,
we've already spoken with her.
Nanami, you're being expelled.
She gave her consent.
Has she signed the withdrawal form?
-Not yet.
-Then it's not final.
We'll get a form immediately.
-The form!
-Yes.
SCRIPT
Do you really believe
Nanami would hit someone?
Yes, I do.
He has caused
this sort of trouble in the past.
You're saying once someone does it,
they'll do it again?
His father was that kind of person.
Kaito is his son.
That's just who he is.
That's enough.
His father is one thing.
Kaito is his own person.
Violent behavior isn't hereditary.
It's shaped by one's environment.
If Kaito turns out this way,
you share the blame.
How dare you say that to his mother!
Let me ask you.
What violent actions
has he done, up until now?
The middle school incident,
and shoving you after you scolded him.
That's all, right?
That level of impulse happens to anyone.
And Kaito's tried to change since then.
People can change
if they try.
But if no one acknowledges that effort,
a person will stop changing.
Mrs. Nanami,
you're just like Japanese society today.
You refuse to accept those
with past flaws.
Without that recognition,
no matter how hard they try,
people lose motivation.
If you won't accept him,
you'll break him!
Wait a minute.
Kaito…
really has been trying to change?
Nanami,
you too.
You may be the type
who is reserved and doesn't say anything.
But if you don't say how you feel,
no one will ever understand you.
Have you ever told your mother
how you feel?
You made a mistake, once.
If you've learned from it
and want to earn trust again…
You have to
make an effort to convey your feeling
and sincerity, more than anyone else.
Nanami,
look your mother in the eyes!
‪Mom...‬
MEISHIN PRIVATE ACADEMY
I…
Since that day in middle school, I swore
to never do that kind of thing again.
I didn't hit Tazawa.
I…
would never get violent against anyone.
I'd never do anything that would hurt you.
I…
I believed all this time that
I could become the person I want to be!
So please…
believe in me!
I know the abuse from your ex-husband
must still hurt, mentally.
But…
those scars weren't caused by Kaito.
Kaito is not his father.
Please remember this.
Kaito
is your child,
whom you've lovingly raised for 16 years.
And now he's asking you to believe in him!
As for whether he's lying or now,
I believe no one knows it
better than you, his mother.
-We finished!
-Yes!
Yes!
So it really was Kaito who hit Tazawa?
There's no way Kaito would do that.
But he skipped school,
so that proves he had something to hide.
I agree with Hina-chan.
Kaito-kun didn't do anything wrong.
He isn't that kind of person.
Even if you have
a wonderful relationship with your child,
if Nanami used violence,
he can't avoid expulsion. Withdrawal form…
Kaito didn't use violence.
I believe in Kaito.
Then why was Tazawa bleeding?
-What is it?
-Hey. Tazawa.
It was…
all a lie.
Tell us the truth
about what happened here yesterday.
I told you,
he hit me, here.
-That's the truth.
-Tazawa.
For security purposes,
this school has cameras everywhere.
Of course, this area is recorded too.
We've requested footage from the time
you two were here together.
If you're lying…
tell us the truth
before we see the footage.
You always look at me
like I'm beneath you!
Say something!
What? Come on!
-Pathetic.
-Hey!
Why won't you hit me?
I'm not like my old man.
Wait, hang on!
Damn it!
Why did you lie?
Because I hate him.
He always looks down on me
and it pisses me off.
Nanami is not looking down on you.
You're the one who looks down on Nanami.
I just couldn't bring myself
to admit it was a lie.
Kaito didn't do anything.
I'm sorry.
Now there's no reason to expel Nanami.
It seems that way.
I'm glad.
I'm happy that
Nanami's name is cleared.
Sensei…
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Looks like SEE saved me again.
By the way,
why did SEE…
disappear from the internet?
Shizuka-sensei!
Still, I'm glad everything worked out.
How did you know about the gym camera?
Oh, that was a lie.
There are no cameras behind the gym.
I bluffed.
I'm surprised you could
pull off a trick like that on a student.
Or have you just been
pretending to be dumb?
You seem to know
the camera placements well.
Could it be…
you were the one who
put up the posters?
Saying it's okay to run away
isn't just an excuse
-to escape reality!
-I'm sure there's a purpose behind it!