=The Secret of the Lost Pearl=
=Episode 14=
(Fiction. Do not imitate.)
We used the phoenix pearl pattern
to name the eight chambers.
But the Dui chamber shows Kun.
The Li chamber shows Gen.
(Zhen, Xun)
The Zhen chamber shows Xun.
Only the Kan chamber points to Kan.
Among the eight chambers
we passed through,
the compass needle was chaotic
in four chambers.
Only four chambers pointed
to the correct directions.
Just like you said,
Kun, Gen, Xun, and Kan.
There are only four directions.
Where are the other four?
We fell from above.
That means the other four directions
should be below.
In other words,
there is another space underneath.
If this plane only has four directions,
it is not arranged according
to Fu Xi's Primordial Bagua
or King Wen's Manifested Bagua.
It must follow the Qian Kun diagram,
the 3D Bagua arrangement.
Using the compass needle
as the reference,
the directions corresponding below are
Dui, Zhen, Qian, and Li.
The planar Bagua derived
from the phoenix pearl pattern
and the 3D Bagua indicated
by the compass
overlap in only one chamber.
In other words,
the Kan chamber is this chamber.
Kan belongs to water
and represents the north.
The mechanism
should be on the north side.
Buddy, buddy.
Buddy.
Calm down.
I was tricked too.
I got separated.
How about this?
I will work for you.
I will serve you.
- No.
- Where is my box?
I didn't take that box.
Buddy, Chubby took it.
Where did they run off to?
Chubby
ran that way.
The woman ran that way.
Where could they possibly go?
How would I know?
My guess is
they took that big box to find a buyer.
How did Lu get captured?
He tried to save me.
Look at Huang Long.
Lu exposing himself like that
was basically suicide.
Buddy, calm down.
I understand this. I run a shop.
That box is not worth much.
The real valuables are with you.
Well.
Like this jar.
Let me make an appraisal,
so you can sell it at a high price.
It looks like
this is the real Qian chamber.
The exit should be
behind one of these doors.
This tomb has an exquisite structure
and massive scale.
It could be developed
into a tourist attraction.
Who'd come to a tomb for tourism?
Jade, jade artifacts,
gold and silver treasures.
Farming tools and grain.
Musical instruments and pottery jars.
A scale.
An hourglass.
This is not the exit.
This is a mechanism.
If all those arrows fire at once,
even ten of us wouldn't survive.
The hourglass is the timer.
If we can't solve the mechanism
within a certain time,
I am afraid we will be doomed.
Where did they go?
Why are you so angry?
Look.
Everything here is fine.
Even the oranges fell.
Shut up.
If you don't tell me where they went,
I will blow your head off.
But you told me to shut up.
How am I supposed to tell you
where they are then?
I will kill you.
Wait, wait.
Lu, run.
Go.
Lu, hurry.
Don't move.
This is a linked mechanism.
Something must be placed here
to make the mass on both sides
of the scale equal
to disable the mechanism.
The items on the table
should be the weights.
But in such a short time,
how can we possibly
calculate the exact mass of the weights?
Even the slightest error
will cause the arrows to fire.
If mass will not work,
what about density?
The statue is carved from rock.
The rock layer here is limestone.
Limestone.
These are musical instruments,
ceramics, pottery jars,
jade plaques, and jade belts.
There is a horse.
In every chamber we passed through,
the carvings were phoenix
and pearl patterns.
Why is it that an inconspicuous statue
was placed
at the most important mechanism?
A statue.
Having fun?
Keep playing.
Let us see how you get Ms. He killed.
Huang Long,
release Ms. He now.
Otherwise, I'll blow up the stone box.
Go ahead and try.
Lu, show him the stone box.
See it?
Do you think I wouldn't dare?
All your explosives are in my hands.
In our hands.
Show him the explosives, Lu.
See that?
Don't.
Chubby sure is fierce.
So fierce that he ignores everyone.
What about Ms. He's life?
Cut the nonsense.
Release Ms. He now.
Sure, I can release her.
Give me the box.
Chubby,
why bother?
It is just a box. Just give it to him.
Why fight over it?
Stop talking nonsense.
If we give him the box,
how will Ms. He escape?
What do you suggest then?
Huang Long,
release Ms. He.
We will leave immediately.
We mind our own business.
Otherwise, we will fight to the death.
Fine.
Deal?
Deal.
A statue.
The statue represents the tomb builder.
If we think from another angle,
jade, jade artifacts,
pearls, and treasures represent wealth.
Bamboo slips, brush, ink,
paper, and inkstone
represent wisdom.
Jade plaques and jade belts
represent power.
By placing himself
on one side of the scale,
the tomb builder is asking the visitor
what his life's achievements were worth
and how much value
his life held.
Chubby, light it.
Watch out!
Run!
Chen, hurry!
I'm cutting off your path.
- Go, Lu.
- Lu, hurry.
- My box.
- Go.
Forget the box.
My box.
Bomb!
This jerk is everywhere.
How is it? Are you hurt?
How is it? Are you okay?
I am fine too.
I am fine.
Go. Retreat.
Retreat. Hurry.
♪A tiny ark sails;
the sky opens its eyes♪
♪Stillness in motion,
the earth plays its chord♪
♪A leaf falls;
we cross through time and space♪
♪In a blink, all things rest
upon our hands♪
♪La la♪
♪No line divides the border♪
♪Nothing limits your performance♪
♪Everything shows perfect harmony♪
♪Love circles the sky,
the earth, and our faith♪
♪Hey hey hey♪
♪Hey hey♪
♪Step into the galaxy of colors♪
♪Stars connect our hearts as one♪
♪No difference between you and me♪
♪No lead or side role on this stage♪
♪A perfect life is something we share♪
♪Love declares across the sky and earth♪
♪Huo la yi ya, huo la yi ya♪
♪Time and space go beyond all bounds♪
♪This is our world♪
♪Shining lives bring the change♪
♪In a blink, to forever♪