=Dr. Spring=
No one comes to report after a night.
This wild country girl is energetic.
Mother, where are you going?
Let me take you to watch a good show.
It's called "What's Done Is Done". Come.
=Episode 10=
Open the door.
W-Why is it you two?
Who else could it be?
It's just a cold.
You don't have to make such a fuss.
Here. I cooled it off. It's not hot.
Good girl, drink it.
Bitter.
Not bitter if I feed you.
Mother, it's "What's Done Is Wrong".
Yan, Yan!
My lady!
You two slept together before marriage.
How disgraceful it is! You're shameless!
Whose behavior is really disgraceful?
You...
- Madam, it's done.
- You're disgraceful.
It's good. I'll keep it.
You should paint her more often.
After all, Father isn't here,
and she's so charming.
You must be taking lots of Lust Pills.
Y-You!
Madam, 10 wen.
- No!
- Get lost!
Madam, calm down! Don't be mad!
She passed out!
Madam!
Is she pretending?
She passed out! Get a physician!
Madam! Get a physician!
- (Chest pain? Angina?)
- Madam, wake up.
Madam!
- What do we do?
- Are you okay?
Stop it! Don't touch her!
Shut up! if you want her to be good,
just be quiet!
Go get a physician!
(Lips turn purple.)
My lady, what are you doing?
(Fingers turn cyanotic.)
What are you doing?
(Legs are swollen.)
Does she usually feel sick?
After she gave birth,
her health got worse.
Her legs hurt sometimes.
She always feels tired.
Could it be...?
No! Why did I tell you this?
Madam, wake up, please!
Physician Ling is here.
Move! Let me hold her.
No!
The physician will see her. Get out.
Why are you still there? Come help me.
- What are you doing?
- Rest assured!
What are you doing, my lady?
Are you trying to save her?
Have you forgotten what she did?
You're a girl. She gave you those pills.
If I hadn't arrived in time,
do you know what would have happened?
I'm not gonna help her.
Help me get her to the bed.
Quickly!
You are...
An eye for an eye. A pill for a pill.
Open your mouth.
Not afraid of becoming an accomplice?
Even a murderer can't compete with you.
Tsk. These symptoms
might indicate CTEPH
caused by thrombus detachment.
They not only dilate pulmonary vessels
but also have anticoagulant effects.
She should be grateful.
I don't get what you said,
but a person like her
won't regret it even if you save her.
Li Chunri shouldn't save her, but...
(Zhang Ziqi must save her.)
The physician is here! Make way!
Sir, is she okay?
The pulse is irregular.
But it has begun to stabilize.
She just needs to rest well in her room.
- Thank you.
The house steward asked
Lady Chunri and Mr. Ling to come over.
Mr. Ling's family brought gifts here.
Family?
Yao?
(Prime Minister's Residence)
He has caused you trouble these days.
Mr. Ji, you're too kind.
You brought such generous gifts.
Why didn't you send someone to tell me?
We would be well prepared now.
I didn't want to bother you.
Not at all!
Once the soul-chasing order is issued,
no one can take it back.
If you can't finish it quickly,
I don't mind doing it myself.
This must be my future sister-in-law.
You really look gorgeous.
Thank you. You're really thoughtful.
This way, please.
You're welcome.
Why are you here?
I told you once the order was issued,
no one could take it back.
You've helped me a lot.
It's your marriage.
Of course I want to help you.
Have I not warned you?
Stay out of our business.
I'm just here to pay a visit.
I wonder why Mr. Ling is trapped here.
I've searched Lady Liuyan's room
and the dungeon these days.
Only the Madam's room
had a suspicious medicinal fragrance.
Hey, are you guys finished talking?
I've waited a long time.
Stay away from him. He's dangerous.
He's my cousin!
He's not your cousin!
Of course I'm his cousin.
I...
Guys, let's just forget it.
Forget it?
What?
Getting married?
Or killing...
Killing me with kindness!
Wow, the Ling Family must be wealthy.
Such generous gifts for a bride price.
No, not at all.
All thanks to my cousin.
You're quite welcome.
Mother said she is seriously ill,
and it's not proper to throw a party.
She asked you to leave.
The Madam is ill? I have another gift.
Ling Xinghe, I'm seriously ill now.
What else do you want?
We're here to pay a visit.
How dare you treat my people...
For all I know, there are no people
as you said among officials in Jingzhao
like judicial officials and censors.
How would you like to explain it?
I...
Am I right?
Does the Madam keep them to herself?
I don't understand what you said.
Why don't we go straight in
and ask the Prime Minister?
- How dare you!
- What are you doing?
Stop it!
(Was there a concept of heart disease
in ancient times?)
(Zhou Yuhang as Yu Youde)
Chest impediment is heart disease.
It can be treated with remedies
like massage, acupuncture, diet,
rest, and so on.
For example, congenital heart disease.
Ancient physicians applied
syndrome differentiation and treatment.
Patients can take medicines
that boost qi, warm yang,
move blood, resolve stasis,
unblock collaterals, and relieve pain.
Herbs like Renshen, Huangqi, and Guizhi
can improve heart function.
Acupuncture is helpful as well.
Stimulating acupuncture points promotes
the circulation of qi and blood,
enhances immunity, and regulates
the functions of internal organs,
thereby treating the disease.