=Dr. Spring=
=Episode 18=
Is that you, Ling Xinghe?
Kid, why is it you? Where's Yao?
Grandpa asked me to give you this.
Then he left for a long journey.
How did Yao make it bloom?
This is the snow lotus?
Yeah.
Why is it red?
Yao had the kid tell me
that it can come in two colors.
The white ones
can form a symbiotic relationship,
while the red ones can terminate it.
It's also called 'blood lotus'.
Dissolving the pistil in water can
create a red liquid, the 'blood water'.
Drinking the 'Blood Water'
can terminate the relationship.
This is what was written
on the torn page?
We've learned
of the traitor's hiding place.
We'll take action tonight.
So we...
So we need to terminate it right now.
Once we drink this,
our symbiotic relationship is done.
What are you hesitating for?
Aren't you afraid of dying for him?
If you're not afraid, I am.
Don't forget
you're the sacrifice for Li.
Come on,
let's dissolve this pistil in water.
Leave it to me.
Don't you have more important matters?
I'll get it ready.
This is the Li's hiding place
the shadow guard disclosed. Take a look.
The deserted courtyard
actually conceals another residence.
All guards
are stationed on the perimeter.
We can avoid the guards
from the east side and sneak in.
Catch Li off guard and kill him.
Li is suspicious. Could this be
another one of his schemes?
He might wanna conserve his strength
and distract us.
There is a possibility.
Then we'll just play along.
Make noise on the east side to attract
soldiers and let Li think he has us.
Then we'll enter through the main gate
and go straight for his head.
Understood.
Once this operation is initiated,
it cannot be reversed.
I've specially prepared
'blood water blind box'.
Let's each choose a cup.
If fate wants us
to terminate our relationship right now,
then so be it.
(You don't want to end it either,
do you?)
(As long as you're safe,
I'm okay with anything.)
Stop choosing, just drink.
I don't feel well.
I'll go rest for a while.
Chunri.
Ah.
Chunri, Chunri, are you alright?
Your hand is hurt.
It's nothing.
It seems the blood water worked. We...
This means our relationship
has been terminated.
Aren't you supposed to take action?
Go get ready.
I'll go take care of my wound.
Prime Minister,
we've found their people.
They are hiding in the Yichun House
in Chang'an City.
They sure know how to hide.
House steward.
Yes, sir.
Send someone over there now.
Don't let even a sparrow escape.
I understand.
You really went to
great lengths for her.
Take a look at yourself.
Let's go.
(This day has finally come.)
Report!
Prime Minister, the guards we sent
after Lady Liuyan haven't returned.
Now that the bait has been taken,
let's catch them all at once.
Lady Chunri, my apologies.
Let me go!
Aren't you my father's men?
Why are you arresting me?
Chunri, what in the world is going on?
Don't worry.
At least allow me to tidy up.
(Which blood vessel is severed
in self-decapitation?)
(Xu Ziyin as Li Chunri)
The carotid or the external carotid are important arteries of the neck.
The carotid arteries are located
on both sides of the neck.
They are high-pressure arteries
with a very rich blood flow.
They supply most
of the blood to the brain.
The external carotid arteries are another
critical group of arteries in the neck.
They provide part
of the blood supply to the brain.
Especially to
the posterior cerebral fossa.
Cutting the external carotid artery
can cause severe bleeding and danger.
So we must cherish life.
And protect our neck arteries.
Don't commit suicide.
If he kisses there, well, no matter
how close the relationship is,
don't apply too much force
in this area while kissing.
Ensuring the safety of life
is most important.