=Dr. Spring=
What are you going to do?
I was just joking.
Don't take it seriously.
Listen, I didn't pay for
any additional services.
You're really taking off clothes? Stop.
I was wrong. I won't escape anymore.
=Episode 3=
Don't be like this.
Go ahead.
Why have your injuries
been transferred to me?
How should I know?
I also don't know what's going on.
Do I have to kill you
before I kill myself?
Why did you get injured?
(An evil official's daughter is
in that litter.)
(But Li suddenly brought her back.)
(He must really have something to hide.)
No wonder Prime Minister Li got you back
at this moment.
He wanted to use this secret technique
to make you die for him.
I didn't expect that the two of us were
in a symbiotic relationship.
Are you cursing my father?
It's okay. Prime Minister Li
even killed me, his own daughter.
He's definitely a bad man.
What else do you know?
I know that you didn't kill that person.
I saw it from the rooftop.
That person had a large wound
on the back of the neck.
(It was kind of caused
by a blunt instrument,)
(causing a vertebral artery injury.)
So he was already dead
before you killed him.
I guessed. I'm not good at neurosurgery.
Nonsense.
You're really not a player?
What are you doing?
Let me do it.
(She's so well-versed in medicine.)
The wound on your neck is shallow
and will heal soon.
The stitches are done
and will be removed after seven days.
Remember not to get it wet. Well, okay.
"Well, okay"?
"Okay" means it's finished.
"Well" is a word exclusively used
to ingratiate someone.
If you don't want to be offensive,
you can use this word.
Before we find a way
to lift this bond between us,
your life is my life.
Just stay here.
That is impossible. Bye.
If you escape again,
I will ruin your pretty face.
As long as you're alive,
I can lure Prime Minister Li out.
That's really not necessary.
Hero, I've prepared anti-inflammatory
and pain-relieving medicine for you.
Remember to take it.
A physician won't harm
another physician.
I know what tricks you're playing.
You put knockout drops in it?
Have a good sleep.
Could the effects be transferable too?
Fortunately, this is just a game.
Once I kill him, I can go back.
I am really sorry.
When I return,
I will do my best to treat patients,
being a good physician
who abides by medical ethics.
The black market
in the guide is right here.
The fourth warehouse
on the fourth street, and four...
This is the place.
A warrior's hat was tied with a rope,
and Wugou Sword was as bright as snow.
Thank you.
Are you the top assassin
on the black market?
Are you motivated by love or revenge?
By death with dignity.
Draw the portrait and write the name.
Within two days, this person will
be dead with no corpse left.
(Ling's Clinic)
It's him.
We only deal with killing,
not with catching ghosts.
Can't you see he's a human?
(Ling's Clinic)
Once the soul-chasing order is issued,
no one can take it back.
Have you decided?
If I can't do it,
I have to leave it to the professionals.
I don't have many days left to live.
Where can I go?
(The Prime Minister's Residence)
Even if you look all over Chang'an City,
you must bring Lady Chunri back alive.
Yes.
- My lady, you're back.
My lady, how did you come back?
I return to my home. Any problem?
After all,
I'm the Prime Minister's daughter.
At least before next
Sun and Star Conjunction, right?
If you don't give me a hard time,
I won't do anything foolish again.
As a daughter,
I am willing to do things for my father.
I'm concerned about your safety.
After all,
something awful happened yesterday.
Did you see
what the bad guy looked like?
He's buck-toothed,
like an ugly duckling.
Who are you talking about?
(What were knockout drops
in ancient times?)
(Wu Jifeng as Ling Xinghe)
In historical documents,
the knockout drops
are not explicitly mentioned,
but judging from its effects
and users' symptoms,
it is basically consistent
with ancient anesthetics.
Most people believe that flos daturae
is mixed into the knockout drops.
Flos daturae, also called golden flower,
generally grows by riversides,
fields, or sunny hillsides.
It looks bright and beautiful.
But like some wild mushrooms,
the brighter, the more toxic.
And the knockout drops are made
from mandrake flowers.
Flos daturae varies in color.
The white ones are often made
into a powder used as anesthetics
with effects, such as nerve paralysis
and muscle relaxation.
If you come across flos daturae,
I advise you to stay away from it,
lest you accidentally touch them
and get into trouble with this.