Bride of the Century
That diary ... this is the very last page.
After that day, in my heart...
I've been living with this heavy burden.
I did something a person shouldn't have.
I committed a sin that cannot be forgiven.
Even if I die, I'll accept my punishment.
The reason I'm telling you
all of this is because
Even if you don't say anything, I know.
I'll stay by Kang Ju's side.
I won't leave him.
Kang Ju...
To his mother...
Make sure she doesn't know.
If she finds out,
confusion and pain that she won't be able to stop, will follow her.
Can you promise me?
The only mistake you and I made,
is completely believing in the household's curse.
Fortunately, I was given a chance to overcome my mistake.
Thanks to your mother.
If the world find out the truth, not only will your household be ruined,
but the future of Taeyang Group will also be uncertain.
Ah. I thought you'd be curious...
why Doo Rim came back safely.
I also don't want things to get noisy.
It's over if we break off this marriage.
You know well that you have more to lose than we do.
You also know well that this isn't something you should drag on for long.
I'll give you time until tomorrow.
I feel like we just went through a bad storm.
We overcame a huge wave today, didn't we?
I told you, didn't I? My mom will get over her anger quickly.
To be honest, I'm more worried about your older brother.
You know he's surprisingly scary, don't you?
My brother is?
Are all older brothers like that?
Do they see all men who want to take their younger sister away as thieves?
Sometimes when I see him, he seems like a beast who wants to capture me and eat me.
To your older brother... that's not right.
I should call him brother-in-law now.
Tell him let's have a drink sometime.
Okay.
Your ugly hands became silky hands.
It's because I received a manicure at the nail salon.
Your parents are probably waiting. You should get going.
You didn't sleep a wink at the villa yesterday, did you?
Don't worry about anything now and sleep well.
You too.
I'll go now.
Don't come out. It's very cold outside.
Go in.
Doo Rim!
What happened?
What about the Director?
Jin Ju...
Doctor! How is he?
We tried our best but... we must monitor the results for know.
Jin Ju...
what's going to happen to him?
Because of me... because of me!
What do we do?
That a curse fell on the household wasn't true.
All of this was just a test to find true love.
Now, just to be by that person's side...
I've become the world's happiest bride.
If the world finds out this truth,
Not only will your household be ruined, but the future of Taeyang Group will also be uncertain.
Young Master, are you just getting home?
Aigoo, Young Master. Congratulations.
You must have been suffering a lot.
I'm more excited than when our Mi Soon got married.
Courage, determination, perseverence.
You're very cool. You're the best!
Why are you like this?
An ill-fated love that death can't even tear apart.
Aigoo, so romantic!
Go on in. The president is waiting.
Listen to me.
I've come back, Father.
Thank you for trusting me.
You've done well.
There are so many stars.
There are many stars.
Oppa did? Where and how much is he hurt?
- Where's the hospital?
- I told you Doo Rim is there.
There's no good for you two to run into each other.
Mom!
Yi Hyeon did this. Don't start to waver.
In order to do great things, small sacrifices must be made.
All that's left is for Kang Ju's mother to wave her white flag and surrender.
Then everything will be over.
Oppa.
How can you just sleep like this?
Please open your eyes.
I want to say...
so much to you.
There's so much ...
that I want to say,
I didn't know where to start.
Oppa.
Yi Hyeon.
I thought you would make the right decision.
Please publicly acknowledge Yi Gyeong as the daughter-in-law of Taeyang Group.
Whether you announce the marriage or hold a press conference,
However you would like to, I would just like it if you made a formal announcement as soon as possible.
Of course I should do that. However, as you know,
Kang Ju's grandmother is very ill so we have a lot on our minds right now.
If you wait a bit more, I will announce it publicly.
It's not that I don't trust you, but the truth that I hold...
is a lot more dangerous than the truth you hold.
You know that well, don't you?
Normally in a deal, the side that has a lot to lose,
is the side that also has a lot to endure.
Tell me what you want.
I'll need you to hand over all the Ohsung Construction stocks you own.
And please sign over your Taeyang Group holdings to Yi Gyeong.
You need to show at least that much so that I believe you are accepting my child as your daughter-in-law.
That's the only way I could trust you, don't you think?
Lastly, the funds you offered to invest in Ohsung Construction,
you'll need to deposit that also.
Also, regarding Doo Rim...
Making sure she no longer lingers in Kang Ju's life,
I trust that you will take care of that.
Just eat one spoonful.
You haven't slept or eaten.
What are you going to do if you collapse too?
- What about Grandmother?
- Don't worry.
I told her the Director was hurt at a construction site,
and that you came up from Namhae to help take care of him.
Quickly eat.
You have to eat so you can have strength. And you have to have strength so you can take care of  him.
Oppa. Oppa! Yi Hyeon!
Oppa! Jin Ju, call the doctor! Quickly!
Oppa! Oppa! What am I supposed to do? Oppa!
Oppa, come to your senses!
Doctor! Quickly!
Doctor, is he going to be alright?
He's getting the treatment he needs so don't worry.
Oppa. Yi Hyeon Oppa.
I was so interested in what was on the outside, I failed to look beyond that.
I'm at an age when I should be looking at the horizon, but I've been going around blind.
I've lived a foolish life too.
Who should I blame now?
I loathe and detest myself for believing in such foolish rumors.
Today will be the last time you and I are facing each other like this.
I won't speak for long.
Don't appear in front of Kang Ju. As if you're dead, live quietly without making a sound.
In return, I'll guarantee the safety of your life.
Yi Gyeong's side will not be able to hurt you anymore.
It doesn't matter what happens to me.
But the people who made  Oppa Yi Hyeon like that... I can't forgive them.
Forgiveness is something that someone with power gives to someone weak.
Do you think you have that kind of power?
I don't understand. Why are you watching silently?
It's not because I'm being greedy.
In the beginning, I wanted to be by his side so I tried to reveal the truth.
But not anymore. For him, you shouldn't be like this!
I don't possess the power to forgive them.
That's the reason.
I don't know what happened but that's not possible.
If you committed a sin, it's right that you receive punishment. I'll receive that punishment too.
- If not now, there won't be any other opportunity.
- In your position,
do you think you're worthy of being part of Taeyang Group's family?
Aren't you trying to fulfill your own desires by telling me you'll take all of the punishment?
I told you. It's not because I want Kang Ju!
You and Kang Ju. I don't want you both getting involved in any way.
You two live in completely different worlds.
You cannot mix together and you shouldn't.
I... didn't like him because he's the heir.
Even if he was just an ordinary person...
If he was... I thought he could be mine.
Until now, I've never regretted that I was born by my parents.
But since Kang Ju has entered my heart...
If I was born as a woman who matched him well...
that would've been great. I've thought like that.
But now... I'm so sorry to my parents.
That I thought that for even a moment.
I'm asking you a favor.
If you appear in front of Kang Ju, he will fall into pain.
Disappear. Like someone who never existed in the first place.
That's the way for Kang Ju.
Why did you do that, Mom?
For my sake... you shouldn't have done that.
Because of me, you've become a sinner. How can I live?
I didn't want to embarrass you. I wanted to be a good daughter.
But what is this...
I'm a sinner who has dirtied your life.
I'm sorry, Myeong Hui.
It's all my fault.
I've made you like this.
For having you believe in that family's curse...
It's all my fault.
This foolish and thoughtless mother of yours...
Please forgive me.
Mother! I can't accept this.
How could you do this?
I'm sorry, Ru Mi.
What's the reason? Why are you acknowledging Yi Gyeong?
I don't understand at all.
Did someone find out your weakness?
If not, then you have no reason to do this.
Tell me. I have to know too. I have the right to!
I already met with Yi Gyeong's mother. It's a done deal. You should stop interfering now.
If you don't tell me, I'll just have to personally find Yi Gyeong's mother and hear it.
You won't be able to hear anything even if you go find her.
Mother!
For our household...
Think you're doing this for Kang Ju.
If you can't, I can tell Kang Ju everything.
I was always watching over you as my daughter-in-law.
I thought of you as my only daughter-in-law.
The minute you open your mouth, you and I become enemies.
Do you want to leave me as your enemy?
Don't skip meals and make sure sure you take care of yourself.
- You're the caretaker so you need to stay strong.
- Don't worry Grandma.
Director Jang is not someone who'll go down so easily.
He'll gather his strength and wake up before you know it.
Of course. He's such a strong person.
- I'll be back. Don't come out, Grandma.
- Okay. Go on.
I don't think she's a ghost. She's definitely a living person.
What happened?
Take care of Yi Hyeon.
I think who he needs right now isn't us but you.
If you want to, you can leave far away with him.
I can also look into what can help with his treatment.
Don't pretend that you're doing this for him.
You just want to clean me up so I won't appear before you.
Are you thinking it's because of me that he became that way?
If you didn't get greedy, he wouldn't turn out like this.
That's right.
I was being selfish and wanted Kang Ju and then this happened.
I may be paying the price for my greed right now.
Realizing how agonizing this reality I have to live in is...
What's scarier than the household's curse...
People who attack at any opportunity they get, like starving beasts.
People who wear the mask of a human but are not even human.
Keep one thing in mind.
If you decide something else, I can't guarantee your Grandmother and your friend Jin Ju's safety.
This makes me think that you're really pitiful.
Even throwing away your son...
Even hurting someone's life... what do you gain?
You won't be able to understand.
Since you lived in a different world than us.
If this is your world that you guys talk about,
then even if you offered me loads of money, I don't want to be a part of it.
You may not like me getting mixed up in your world, but I don't like it either.
I hate getting involved with you people. But I still won't forgive you.
I can't even forgive myself for only thinking about what I wanted,
so how could I forgive you?
Until I can forgive myself, I'll live while repaying my debt to Yi Hyeon.
Even if I can't repay it all for my whole life.
Ah, about your brother. He isn't picking up my calls. Is he really busy?
Ah. Did I not tell you?
He got a complaint from a construction site in Dubai.
He left for Dubai the day before yesterday.
It would have been nice to see him. It must be taking long since it's a trip abroad.
Yes. He did mention that he wants to get drinks when he gets back.
That's right.
My gaze...
Voice...
The sound of my breath...
Don't remember anything.
As long as you can smile happily next to someone who isn't me, that's enough.
Live well. Goodbye.
Its been a while, Ru Mi.
Sure. It must have been a while since you've seen me but I can't say the same for myself.
I sent my congratulations to him, so pass.
Your face has brightened up. You look happy.
Thank you.
But why do I not see the ring? Wasn't it a couple ring?
Only you're wearing it.
Did you put it on another girl's hand, perhaps?
I'm just kidding. What kind of man doesn't recognize his own woman?
Sir, I'll leave the files for your approval on your desk.
The ring... what happened?
About that...
You didn't go around pretending to be single, did you?
I'm sorry. I forgot it and left without it.
You're suspicious nowadays. Even at the villa, you seemed like someone who had something to say but didn't.
What was it you were going to say?
- It's nothing.
- Yeah right. You were really serious back then.
You're not really hiding another man somewhere, are you?
Let's stop, Choi Kang Ju.
Let's go now. Mother and Father must be waiting.
- Grandmother. I'm here.
- Ah, you're back.
Why don't you have any energy? Are you sick anywhere?
What? No. I'm just tired.
♫  Is it wrong if I want to see you?  ♫
♫  Is it wrong if I long for you?  ♫
♫  Because I'm sorry for loving you  ♫
♫  I can't let you go  ♫
♫  Even I try to see you I can't see you  ♫
♫  As if  I could reach you in the corner of my eye   ♫
♫   I keep thinking of you so I stop in place  ♫
♫  After a long time passes   ♫
♫  I call out to you in tears  ♫
♫  Is it wrong if I want to see you?   ♫
♫  Is it wrong if I long for you?  ♫
♫   What if I can't hold back any longer?  ♫
♫  There are words I didn't get a chance to say.  ♫
♫  Words I couldn't say because I'm thankful,  ♫
♫  Words I couldn't say because I'm still sorry.  ♫
♫   The words I love you  ♫
This is so tasty. It's nice and tender.
Where is this from? I'll have to order from here again.
What brings you here again?
You're blessed with so much food.
No one's even offered up any food for me in over 100 years.
Then, at least this...
Are you mocking me right now? How can I accepted tainted human food?
I must have been mistaken for a moment. I've committed a sin worthy of death.
I don't think anyone will be offering me any food this year either.
In the end, that child was still unable to overcome her obstacles.
That... since you've mentioned it, I'm going to ask you one thing.
That child... didn't you say something bad would happen to her?
But... she's perfectly fine and alive!
And how could you give me false information?
- Are you going to take responsibility if I go bankrupt?
- You fool!
Are you trying to start a fight with me? If you don't like it, I can always go somewhere else.
No. If you just go like this, then what do I do?
I was wrong. I'm very sorry.
You haven't abandoned, have you?
You need to come back, okay?
- Father, do you like it?
- Of course I do.
I can just wear it like this and go for walks.
- Please invite me along when you go on your next walk Father.
- I'd like that.
If there's someone to talk to, then I won't be bored.
Mother, you should open yours too. Yi Gyeong walked three laps around the department store looking for your gift.
- And I got dragged around for 2 hours too.
- Yes, let's see it.
Kang Ju helped me pick it out.
He said you like scarves.
Try it on Mother.
Later.
- You should try it on.
- I said later.
Mother, don't hate me too much.
I don't expect us to get along. But don't turn your back on me.
Then things will get difficult for both of us.
So?
Grandmother didn't want things to be harder for you either.
She did what she could for you.
And you did as well.
In order to find a bettter match for Kang Ju,
you played with my life.
And you are paying the price for that now.
When did you start fencing?
I learned it for fun in elementary school.
Who are you?
Why are you laughing?
Do you remember that time? You were a one woman show, having fun all by yourself.
It's a shame I was the only one to see it.
Let's stop talking about the past.
Makes sense. You probably don't want to remember those times.
Yes, I don't remember anything.
Is that so? Then should I help you remember?
- What are you doing?
- You still don't remember?
What are you doing?
Shall I close the door again?
- What is it?
- Ah yes, dinner is ready.
Then ...
Let's go now.
Don't you want a little snack?
Let's get a bowl of udon.
Please enjoy.
You know how to eat these things?
Have some.
I can't eat blood sausage. The smell makes my head hurt.
You used to go crazy for blood sausage.
If you don't want any, then fine. I'll eat it all.
Do you remember this place?
Of all the surprising things you've done, this was the best.
this was the best.
You wore that fur coat that looked like
it could keep you warm in Antarctica.
My friends and I were doing cosplay.
You know cosplay, right? How do I look? Don't I look sexy?
You know I get cold easily.
I remember it was really cold that night.
And ... you had something weird on your head.
Oh, that hat? My mom bought it for me as a gift when I graduated.
It's something I cherish.
And you were too afraid you'd get your clothes dirty so you didn't even eat the cake I bought you.
I bought an organic cake especially for you.
It's delicious. It's melting in my mouth.
Have a taste.
How could I eat something like that here?
Since you bought it for me, I took it home and ate it.
Don't worry.
Let's go now.
Last thing. There's one more important thing left.
What?
Who ...
are you ?
Why are you being like this all of a sudden? Stop playing around.
You're not the Jang Yi Gyeong I know.
You got everything wrong.
Everything you said doesn't match what I remember.
If I'm not Jang Yi Gyeong, then who am I?
Speaking of which, you're like a different person to me.
You're not the Kang Ju I know.
We barely got through all those obstacles to get to where we are.
Now that things have settled down, have you changed your mind?
You're not having second thoughts, are you?
I'm really disappointed.
Let's just go.
Even if Kang Ju has caught on, he'll never be able to find Doo Rim.
And what if he does find her?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Do you think love lasts forever?
There's nothing more weak and fickle as the human heart.
If he sees Doo Rim for who she really is,
then do you think Kang Ju will be any different?
Doo Rim. We're in trouble.
What happened?
She already knew everything and found us.
Instead of my friend Jang Yi Gyeong,
should I call you Na Doo Rim.
How did you know about this place?
I'm the first person who found out about you.
And I was the first person to tell Kang Ju's mother.
In the end, you've been caught by me.
You can also say I was the one who saved you from getting killed.
If they were even a minute late, you wouldn't be sitting here right now.
Are you here because you want me to thank you?
How does it feel not having to cosplay as a rich girl and return to your rightful place?
It's not bad. It's familiar and comfortable.
Why did you give up ... on Kang Ju?
You even risked your life, so why?
Were you not serious?
Even if I can't, shouldn't you tell him?
If it were me, I wouldn't have done that.
I even tried to take something I couldn't reach.
But you, you had it all in the palm of your hands but you gave it up.
I wanted him too.
I didn't want anyone else to take him.
Because he was someone I risked my life to protect.
But as my greed grew, my fear grew with it.
As my fear grew, my greed became bigger and bigger so I couldn't see.
And because of my greed, I didn't even know
that the person closest to me was getting hurt and in pain.
I want to think love isn't just holding onto the person.
I have no choice but to let go.
Letting go for the sake of that person has to be love as well.
You're not going to regret it?
I may regret it all of my life.
It's probably how I'm going to pay for my greed.
If Kang Ju somehow finds out about you—
Pretend like you don't know. Please.
Don't let him know that I was even by his side for a brief moment.
If he finds out, he'll be in pain.
I don't care if I get hurt.
But because of me ...
I don't want anyone else to get hurt anymore.
Why is the President's fiancée here?
When did you arrive?
- Were you drinking?
- Yes. We had a company dinner tonight.
Oh, that was Team Leader Lee  just now wasn't it?
Yes. She was sorry she couldn't come by during the grand opening so she just stopped by for a moment.
- You seem really drunk. Why did you come here instead of going home?
- I must be drunk.
Inside the restaurant, there's someone who look's just like the President's fiancée.
You must really be drunk. Why would the President's fiancée be here?
This won't do. Let's get some medicine to sober you up a bit before you go home.
There's a pharmacy right over there. Let's go.
Okay.
What did you want to talk about?
You know, right? The woman I gave the ring to.
Tell me. Please.
You found out sooner than I thought.
I knew you would find out eventually.
Why do I have the ring that should be on Yi Gyeong's hand?
It's exactly what you're thinking.
If you didn't put it on a different woman's finger, then there's no way it would be in my hand.
The person you gave this ring to,
would you believe me if I said it wasn't Yi Gyeong but a knock off?
I probably don't have to tell you the reason for all of this is because of the curse on your family.
And the fact I know all this means
the people around you already know.
Then ...
my mother too?
It takes two cymbals to make a sound. No one wants you to know.
Because the moment you find out, Pandora's box will be opened.
Where is she right now? The woman I gave this ring to.
She went back to her rightful place after she finished the role given to her.
Everyone got what they needed and went back to their lives like nothing happened.
If you keep digging, then a lot of people will suffer.
You'll probably suffer the most.
Do you still want to find her?
I asked you where she is.
This is everything I can tell you. I don't know what will happen beyond this.
The rest is for you to figure out.
You'll have to act quietly.
Because if anyone finds out your searching, they'll make sure you never find her.
The person you are trying to reach ...
President, I brought you something to eat.
- This is ...
- I brought it from Oh Jin Ju's restaurant.
It tastes pretty good.
- Miss Jin Ju.
- Yes. I will bring water.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Oh Jin Ju.
Then, what will happen to Jin Ju?
Even after all that, you're still worried about Jin Ju?
Jin Ju must have been in a tight spot to do that.
Who is Jin Ju to you? Why do you keep protecting her?
Why are you getting mad?
Where is Oh Jin Ju's restaurant?
Did you want to try it out too? Team Leader Lee was also there not too long ago.
Taste Doo Rim
♫  Without you I can't live. I really can't live. ♫
♫ You are my battery. ♫
Bride of the Century