Bride of the Century
Are you playing hide-and-seek? Why are you hiding all of a sudden.
I rushed out of the house so I didn't put on any makeup.
Do you think it's easy for a woman to show a man her face without makeup?
This ... is the kitten from before, right?
What are you doing here with the cat?
Something came up with my friend who was watching Coco.
I was dropping her off with another friend.
- Don't be late because of the cat.
- What?
You didn't forget, did you? My father invited you over.
I didn't forget. Don't worry.
I won't be late. I'll be there after I drop off Coco.
I'm leaving work early too. I'll see you at the house later.
Kang Ju.
Here. This is your jacket from the other night.
You could have given this to me later.
Just in case. I brought it with me as I left the house.
I'm good now that I've seen his face one last time.
Take care Choi Kang Ju.
Let's go.
Yes.
- Sir, the documents you need to sign.
- Ah.
- Please leave them on my desk.
- Yes, sir.
Sir, that's ...
Sweet potato. You know ...
Better?
You can leave now.
Please filet these.
Are you asking me to filet these right now?
During the memorial service last time, you did such a good job,
I'll leave these with you.
What happened?
That's so weird. Last time,
you were like a sushi chef the way you were slicing up that fish.
I overworked my fingers yesterday during the performance.
So that's what happened. I didn't realize.
I shouldn't have bothered you. I'm sorry.
Why don't you go take care of what you need to, I'll take care of this.
If you become his first wife, you will die.
Because I will take your life.
What are you looking at?
Father. I was looking at some old pictures.
This was Kang Ju's grandfather's wedding picture.
Father. Do you ...
know who this woman is?
I'm not sure.
We have so many family members. It's hard to tell who's who.
Why are you curious about this all of a sudden?
Even though it's from a long time ago, she's very pretty.
People cannot believe just because they cannot see.
But just because you cannot see it does not mean it does not exist.
Then ... Taeyang Groups Madam also ...
Of course. Since long ago, she's known everything..
How can you prove that is true? What is the way to verify it?
She existed for hundreds of years.
Then ...
If you look back in time, you can verify it.
We can verify it if we look back in time?
What in the world does that mean?
What are you staring at so intently?
Are you just getting home?
Were you looking at my picture?
You saw me this morning. You get to see me tonight.
That's not enough so you're looking at my pictures too?
Why? You can't get enough of my face that you keep wanting to look at it?
And also, don't think about calling it even with a bag of sweet potatoes.
Do you think adding a bag of sweet potatoes in here is a enough?
Plus, I might get a scar from that cut I got because of you.
See.
So?
Considering that you went out of your way to stop by my office,
I won't ask you to pay me back for it.
Aren't you happy I'm saving you money? I'm in a generous mood.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Shouldn't you be thanking me or something?
Father is in the study. You should go say hello.
The food must not suit your taste.
No, it does, Father.
It's because the wedding is coming up.
When your wedding is coming up, you become sensitive and lose your appetite.
Kang Ju, you will need to look after her.
Yes.
Are you worried about something lately?
There's nothing, Mother.  Please don't worry about it.
When we're done eating, come to the study.
Yes, Father.
Mother, I will take Father's tea to him.
Alright.
I heard your music performance yesterday went very well.  You did a good job.
Take this and use it when you need it.
Father.
I'm trying to earn points with my Daughter-In-Law ahead of time.
Did you call me here today to give me this?
The real reason is to have a rematch.
Excuse me?
Alkkagi.
You won't be able to beat me today.
I've been practicing a lot.
Alkkagi?
Of course.  We should do it.
I'll set up the game, you make the ink.
The ink?
Yes, Father.
Coco, let's go with Unni to see Grandma at Namhae.
Shall we eat?  Wait a minute.
That's right. I forgot to mention Alkkagi in my notes.
That's so important.
Dummy.
What the heck has she been doing while I was gone?
That's why you shouldn't have taught him Alkkagi.
You lost to Father pretty badly, didn't you?
What are you doing?
You're a little strange today.
Someone who used to eat everything is not eating well and not smiling much.
You're not talking much.  Are you upset about something?
What would I have to be upset about?  I even got some spending money from Father.
If that's so, then it's all good.
For that matter, what's going on with you?
Since when have you been so interested in how I'm feeling?
It's not that I'm watching how you're feeling.
It's because you might get stressed again and cause trouble.
Don't worry.  That won't happen.
Stay still.  It didn't get cleaned completely.
You two look very good together.
I was just passing by.
Please continue what you were doing.
What was I doing?  Let's go.
Grandma!
Doo Rim!  Aigoo!
Aigoo, my little puppy, aigoo!
Let me look at you, my little one.
Let's go in, let's go in. What is this?
Don't even get me started.
Because of Doo Rim, I'm going to have to learn how to clean fish.
On top of that, Alkkagi ...
Nothing else happened?
Kang Ju is a little strange.
Are you saying that he figured something out, or what?
It's not that.
I can't put my finger on it.
But anyway, he's different from the Kang Ju of the past.
I'm meeting Kang Ju's Mom tomorrow.
Once we set a date, the marriage will proceed as planned.
Ah, I'm really happy to be home.  And the smell of my Grandma is nice also.
I'm happy too.  I even get to pat my puppy's tush like this also.
My heart ached so much after sending you to Seoul by yourself.
Don't worry, Grandma.  I'm not leaving again.  I'm going to live with you forever.
No, you can't do that.  You should get married.
Didn't you meet any men in Seoul?
- Men?
- Yes.
Moreso that even the smartest men in Gyeongsang-do,
I heard that Seoul men are amiable and are good to women.
There's this Seoul man that I met while working.
His personality is very abrasive, and
you know how a woman's heart is supposed to be more beautiful that her outside appearance, right?
But that man is not like that.  He only likes pretty women.
And he only likes women who like really big breasts.
Aigoo, what? Is he brainless?
A man who is only interested in a women's looks is 100 percent
the kind to cause his wife grief and cheat.
Is that right?  Even you think he's a no.
You must be tired.  Go to sleep.
What is it?  Are you not able to sleep because of the cat?
That's not it.
How is it that I never get used to this place even though I come every day?
Why does the Madam ask me to do these things in the middle of the night?
Aigoo, you scared me!
It's me, Ahjumma.
Aigoo, you scared me.  That took 10 years off my life.
Why?  Did you think I was a ghost?
I just... for some reason this place frightens me.
When the wind blows even slightly, it gives me chills.
But it's so strange, young Master.
You played well here when you were young.
And you always hid here when you played hide-and-seek.
If you happened to get in trouble with the Madam.
You would hide here and not even eat.
There's good sunlight here so it's good for taking naps,
And it's quiet, so it's good for collecting my thoughts.
It really doesn't bother you at all?
This place ...
you do know that this is no ordinary place, right?
While I was so happy about you getting married,
on the other hand, I was worried.
Aigoo, I'm speaking nonsense again.
I'm sorry.  Please don't pay attention to what I just said.
I know why you're saying those things, and what you're thinking, Ahjumma.
I know it all.
The things that you're thinking about,
They won't happen... ever.
Of course.  Those things must not happen again.
Aigoo, of course it can't.
What are you doing here?
Aigoo, Madam.  What are you doing here so late, Madam?
Then I'll let the two of you speak.
I'll have to get new water.
What you were just talking about ...
Mother, that's—
Those stories made up by people who like to talk,
Why would you talk about it?
You shouldn't listen to those things.
You also shouldn't take them to heart.  You know what I'm saying, right?
Yes.
You,
Do you want to be fired?
P- pardon?
- Did I do something wrong?
- I've told you multiple times,
why are you spewing nonsense to Kang Ju?
He's preparing to get married. What if he has a change of heart?
I was wrong.
I'll be more careful from now on.
You must not speak of the annex to Yi Gyeong.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Yes, Madam.
Then, with that date in mind, we'll start to get ready for the wedding.
Also, I'd like to keep the dowry minimal and have a simple wedding.
As you know, the Chairman does not like very loud and extravagant things.
Of course. Lavish weddings can become issues lately.
A social leader like Taeyang Group should set an example.
Thank you for understanding.
Of course. My daughter still has a lot to learn so please take care of her.
A charm that brings me love?
I'm dumb for believing such a thing.
Who said you can just throw that away?
You are ...
I told you not to treat this lightly. Why are you throwing it away willy-nilly?
No thanks. It's yours so you can take it back.
What is it? So you didn't like my gift?
Why do you keep doing this to me?
I wonder, why am I doing this to you?
Are you curious? If you're curious, come here.
If you're curious,
give me 500 won  (approx. 42 cents US Currency)
What are you doing? Are you teasing me?
If you put the bracelet back on, I'll tell you.
Don't bother.
Don't appear in front of me again.
You're such a strange woman.
The bracelet will make the things you really want happen.
Do you still not want it?
As soon as you put this on, good things will happen.
What do you want to do?
Are you going to throw it away or put it back on?
You choose.
It's not because I believe you.
There's nothing to lose.
Oppa Yi Hyeon!
See. What did I tell you?
You wanted it so you made the decision.
Whatever happens from this point forward,
you're going to have to learn to handle it.
Oppa!
We don't have much but please enjoy.
Thank you for the meal.
Grandma, he can't eat all of this.
No, I can eat it all.
You don't have to. How can you eat all of this?
I don't get full no matter how much I eat.
You're so handsome and you eat so well.
Doo Rim must take after your cooking skills.
The food tastes great.
Try some of the fish too.
What is it?
Doo Rim is the same way.
Her ability to bone the fish without it breaking apart was like a work of art.
Doo Rim, did you bone the fish for him too?
Ah, that's ...
When people have a meal together, they start to grow closer.
Good job.
Here, eat.
This you take three pills, three times a day.
And this is for when you go out.
This is a mink scarf that I've always heard about.
This is so expensive.
Grandma, try it on.
I'll help you.
How do I look?
Do I look like a pig with a pearl necklace?
What do mean? It looks perfect on you.
It's very warm and so nice.
The scarf is one thing,
but I'm so taken aback with gratitude for all the thought you put into this.
So whenever I come to visit, you'll give me a heaping bowl of rice
- and bone the fish for me?
- Of course.
And please speak comfortably around me.
Will that be okay?
Of course. That will make me feel better too.
Grandma, you look so cool.
Have you spoken with your grandma?
About the store I mean.
I'm not sure how my grandmother will feel about it.
The sea is her hometown.
And ... this is where my mom and dad went to rest.
When did your parents ...
When I was thirteen,
the two went out fishing.
You know they say,
when a couple truly love each other, they leave this world together.
My dad and mom must have been that way.
Your hands,
are big and warm.
Just like my dad's.
Noona, what are you doing?
I was thinking about whether I'm a spoon or a fork.
But what are you doing here?
I came as a VIP customer today.
Fine.
Then have fun shopping. I have a meeting.
Hey Kang In.
Yes, Noona. What?
Nevermind. You wouldn't know.
What was that?
Spoon.
Fork.
What is she talking about?
Ahjumma, please have these.
What is all this?
These are the new cosmetics we're launching at the department store.
I brought some for you to try.
Oh my.
Goodness. They look expensive.
Are you really giving these to me?
Of course. I've tried these myself.
They make your skin moist and firm. I really liked them.
Oh my goodness.
This is the first time I've seen such nice cosmetics.
I'm so grateful I don't know what to say.
Ahjumma, how long have you been working in this house?
Me? Let me see, it was even before the Madam married into the family,
so more than 30 years.
That's a long time.
It must be hard taking care of such a large home.
Of course. Since we're talking about it,
the only reason this house is still standing is because of me.
No one else could handle it.
Let me see.
Ahjumma, I am curious about something.
What? What is it?
Whatever you're curious about, ask me.
I've been here so long, there's nothing I don't know.
You know some years ago, there were some strange rumors about Kang Ju's family.
That there was a curse passed down through the generations.
That's all nonsense, right?
Well, it's not completely nonsense.
Otherwise, why would Kang Ju's grandmother leave something about it in her will when she died?
Her will?
You cannot tell anybody else about this.
The annex is really ...
She asked we protect the annex no matter what happens.
There must be some truth to it for her to leave it in her will.
Madam follows her will
and makes sure to clean and protect that annex.
Do you think a fork goes well with a coffee cup?
Everyone has a place that suits them.
Goodness, why did she send so much?
That was nice of her.
So is Doo Rim doing well?
Yes. And her grandmother is also doing well.
Have you spoken to her about the store?
She hasn't spoken to her grandmother about it yet.
Since she's lived there her whole life.
Leaving your hometown overnight isn't an easy thing to do.
Maybe it's because we've grown closer while living together,
but strangely something keeps tugging at my heart whenever I think of Doo Rim.
It must have been hard for her to take care of her grandmother at such a young age.
If she lived close, we could check in on her more,
and take care of her. It would be nice.
Yi Hyeon, try to convince her.
Yes, I will.
Aigoo, Doo Rim,
it would be nice for you to meet a man like the Director.
Perhaps he came all the way here,
because he has feelings for you.
It's not like that Grandma. What would he see in me?
Aigoo, what are you saying? What's bad about you?
Any guy who whisks you away should consider himself lucky.
Grandma, should we move to Seoul?
Seoul? Do you want to live in Seoul?
Do you not like it?
Aigoo, why does that matter? We don't have any money to move there anyway.
Truthfully, Grandma. The Director offered to open a restaurant for us in Seoul.
A restaurant? What did you tell him?
I told him I would think about it. If you don't want to, I'm not going.
I also don't feel right leaving with Mom and Dad resting here.
Are the sweet potatoes done?
Let's see if they're done.
Oppa, breakfast is ready. Come down.
Okay.
Oppa, that necktie doesn't look good. It doesn't go well with your outfit.
I think this would look better.
No, I like this one better.
Oppa, is there a girl you're seeing lately?
Don't just spend time working. You should be dating as well.
When I get married, you'll have no one to hang out with. You'll probably be bored.
Don't worry. I have someone to hang out with.
What? Do you have a girlfriend?
This necktie ... I'm right, aren't I? You're acting very strange.
Who gave you this tie?
Who is it from?
Later. Let's eat.
There really must be someone. Who could it be?
Here. This is from Kang Ju's grandmother.
It's an heirloom passed down to the daughters-in-law over the years.
If we adjust it to fit your hand, you won't ever lose it. Here.
Thank you, Mother.
I'll cherish and care for it.
Try it on.
It's a little big.
What is this?
A wedding present. Congratulations.
I saw you getting your engagement ring earlier.
At this point, what else can I do?
I'll wave the white flag. I'm giving up.
I admit it. I was suspicious of you at one point.
Your face was the same but it didn't seem like you.
What are you talking about? Who else could it have been?
But once I saw you playing the piano,
I realized how wrong I was.
Once reality set in, I came back to my senses.
Once that happened,
the road I couldn't see before started to appear.
So now I plan on going down my own road.
That's good. I'm glad.
I'm sorry for giving you a hard time.
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
Thanks for the gift.
I have work to do so I'll leave first.
The wedding bouquet, is it okay if I receive it?
Of course. I'd like that.
Thank you.
Do you think you'll be able to wear that nightgown safely on the first night?
What's with the nightgown?
Ru Mi gave it to me as a wedding present.
Ru Mi did?
But do you think this will look good on you?
What are you doing?
You ... don't wear this and put on that goblin makeup.
Why haven't you been wearing that bracelet lately?
What?
You know ... the one you called a lucky charm or whatever. You wore it everyday.
Oh that. I got tired of wearing it everyday.
Kang Ju, I forgot to mention something earlier.
I made a reservation to look at wedding dresses tomorrow.
Are you free tomorrow?
Jang Yi Gyeong. Jang Yi Gyeong!
What happened?
Kang Ju.
- Are you okay? Are you hurt anywhere?
- What?
How can you just hang up like that?
I thought you were in some kind of accident. You scared me.
A car came out of nowhere ...
You ran out here like this because you thought I was in some kind of accident?
How could I not after you screamed on the phone like that?
Do you think you can drive? Should I call a driver?
No. I'm fine.
Could it ... no. There's no way.
Choi Kang Ju would never ...
Aigoo, my goodness.
These expensive gifts.
On top of that, a restaurant?
There's no way he would do that unless he had feelings for Doo Rim.
Perhaps, the reason Doo Rim can't sleep at night
is because of the Director.
Aigoo, that's it. That's why. Now that they're separated,
she must miss him and I didn't even know.
Doo Rim. Have a seat here.
Grandma, what?
Doo Rim, let's ... go to Seoul.
Grandma.
Why do we have to live in this small town forever?
Let's move to Seoul and make lots of money.
We can live a great life like everyone else.
We tracked the phone number you gave us.
This is the owner of that phone.
This person is ...
You're right. It's Hong Man Su, Kang Ju's maternal grandmother's chauffeur.
She's been abroad recently,
so I think he's taking care of the empty house.
What should we do Chairman? Should we dig deeper?
I have chosen to marry that man.
Even if I lose my life.
I do not regret my decision.
Because I love him more that my own life.
What are you doing here?
What are you hiding right now?
Hiding? What am I hiding?
Is it something I can't see?
What are you doing?
What is this that you keep taking such good care of it?
Did you forget your mother's will?
I'm just following that will.
Her will?
Like my mother,
do you have some ulterior motives for the kids' marriage?
What do you mean?
Thirty years ago, my mother had different thoughts than me.
But my mother accepted the woman I brought home without a fight.
Even though she was a poor girl with a single father who owned a dry cleaning business.
I only found out why she didn't oppose the marriage after that woman died.
If you are planning the same things with Yi Gyeong like my mother did—
If I said no, would you believe me?
You're not going to believe anything I say.
You believe what you want.
I'll believe what I want.
Does that mean you believe that senseless rumor about this family?
Why do you think I'm doing this? It's all for Kang Ju's sake.
Are you in your right mind right now?
Listen to me carefully. If you have different plans for Yi Gyeong,
then I will never forgive you.
It's not true, is it?
It's not like that, right?
Those are made up stories.
You said it yourself. They're all made up.
So why do you believe it? Why?
Kang Ju.
Is that why ... you chose Yi Gyeong instead of Ru Mi?
That's not it. It's not.
I didn't think ... I had a heart.
I wasn't going to ... give my heart away.
But for the first time in my life, I found someone to give my heart to.
You came.
Bride of the Century