♪Dressed in finery, sword in hand,
traversing the world on horseback♪
♪And wiping out all the injustices
in the world♪
♪Purely out of the spirit of youth♪
♪I'll take on a soaring adventure
with you in the wind♪
♪Treading on waves, justice in heart,
laughing with bravery♪
♪We'll reunite at this peak♪
♪Through mountains and rivers,
I'm fortunate to have you by my side♪
♪With wine as a companion,
I never regret the days with you♪
♪Knowing the world is not dichotomous,
we never retreat♪
♪Of all those in this world,
none can be compared to your company♪
♪With pure innocence of heart♪
♪We fear nothing,
only striving to be conscience-clear♪
=The Killing Romance=
♪We fear nothing, only striving to be conscience-clear♪
=Episode 3=
(How Can A Dead Person Come Back to Life?)
(I wonder how long
you can keep this up.)
Young Master Wuji,
why can't you like me a little more?
(How can a dead person
come back to life?)
(Because of You)
I wanted you to sit there.
- What do you need from me?
I'll speak first.
Okay.
Since you are living here now,
you have to follow my rules.
What rules?
First,
keep a distance of at least three feet
from me.
Second,
do not enter my room without permission.
It's not up to you.
What is the third one?
Don't lie to me.
(Is he afraid that I will cheat him
of his wealth, body, and affection?)
If you agree,
sign here.
(Three-point Covenant)
Is it enough?
Now it's my turn.
According to the rules
of the Tang family,
tomorrow is the day I return there
to see my parents.
You don't need to tell me
what you do and where you go.
Wait, you need to go back with me.
I won't go.
Why?
I told you that our marriage...
A nominal marriage without reality.
I see. Then I'll go back by myself.
If there is nothing else,
I'll leave now.
Xiao Fang, prepare the water.
I'm going to take a bath.
Why are you here?
To take a bath. What else?
The sunlight is perfect,
and the water temperature is just right.
I should enjoy it.
Get out.
Why should I?
You take your bath, and I'll take mine.
We won't interfere with each other.
It's not against your rules.
It's definitely
more than three feet now.
(I wonder what you can do about me.)
If you're taking a bath,
why are you still dressed?
I like it this way. Isn't that okay?
Aren't you dressed too?
If you won't take them off,
I'll give you a hand.
Wuji, don't come closer.
Don't you think I won't dare...
Don't come any closer. You...
Young master?
Young master.
Just stand there.
Young master, I've investigated
as you said.
The Tang family in the east of the city
does have a daughter.
Her name is Tang Xiaolu.
She is the one who married you.
The Tang family runs a cloth business.
They are well-known.
Everyone knows about them.
Okay, I got it. You may leave now.
Alright, I'm leaving.
Wuji, I will kill you.
I'm done. Suit yourself.
Are you so afraid that others
might see us together?
I don't allow my woman
to be seen by others
in this kind of situation.
(Did he mean)
(I am his woman?)
Which bride would go back home
by herself?
My parents would scold me.
Now I've really become a joke.
So annoying.
It's all Wuji's fault.
He's heartless, ruthless, and selfish.
Didn't you say you wouldn't come?
You're worried about me?
Stop the nonsense, and let's go.
Since you're here,
do me another favor.
Father, Mother, we're home.
(Tang's Residence)
They should be at home.
Ying'er.
This is Ying'er,
my former personal maid.
Ying'er, where are my parents?
(Tang's Residence)
Ying'er?
This is strange.
Usually, my mother
likes it bright in the house.
Why is it so dark everywhere today?
Father, Mother, I'm back.
Father?
Mother?
No.
♪Speaking of reincarnation,
of life and death♪
♪I've never had fear♪
♪But when it comes to you♪
♪I dare not say a word♪
♪It turns out that regret
is not about parting♪
♪We are so close at distance
yet far away by heart♪
♪It turns out deep love
doesn't always have an ending♪
♪It will either last until death
or be yearned for a lifetime♪
♪Carefully and inappropriately♪
♪I end up with nothing but empty joy♪
♪Even if it takes all my strength♪
♪I'm willing to give up freedom
to get close to you♪
♪I let go of everything
I've ever wanted in life♪
♪I hide my emotions
to play along with you♪
♪Just for that moment of joy♪
♪I walk towards you
against the wind and rain♪
♪I leave all the noise and chaos behind♪
♪There's no way to recall memories
or trace back the obsession♪
♪Because of you♪