♪Dressed in finery, sword in hand,
traversing the world on horseback♪
♪And wiping out all the injustices
in the world♪
♪Purely out of the spirit of youth♪
♪I'll take on a soaring adventure
with you in the wind♪
♪Treading on waves, justice in heart,
laughing with bravery♪
♪We'll reunite at this peak♪
♪Through mountains and rivers,
I'm fortunate to have you by my side♪
♪With wine as a companion,
I never regret the days with you♪
♪Knowing the world is not dichotomous,
we never retreat♪
♪Of all those in this world,
none can be compared to your company♪
♪With pure innocence of heart♪
♪We fear nothing,
only striving to be conscience-clear♪
=The Killing Romance=
♪We fear nothing, only striving to be conscience-clear♪
=Episode 2=
(So What if Love Is Not Mutual?)
(Because of You)
Young master,
we've already closed for the day.
If you're here to seek marriage,
please come back tomorrow.
Since you're seeking marriage,
there's no better day than today.
Please come inside, young master.
Young master!
What kind of marriage are you seeking today?
I'm seeking you.
Fa Wuwei of the Dragon Guardians.
Your Highness.
Long time no see.
It's been three years,
Fa Wuwei.
(Xiao Shi, the Crown Prince)
No, I should call you Young Master Wuji.
Three years ago,
I was secretly sent out of the palace,
which saved me from death.
For three years,
I've been living under a false name,
all in hopes of one day
avenging the Dragon Guardians
and restoring our reputation.
Though I am the Crown Prince,
in the eyes of the empress,
I am nothing
but a pawn to be manipulated.
Since the incident that day,
she has used the excuse
that my father needs rest
to forbid anyone in the court
from seeing him.
Now the empress alone has the say.
There is no one
I can trust in the court.
I feel like I'm walking on thin ice.
You came here today,
which means you trust me and believe
the Dragon Guardians had nothing to do
with the assassination back then.
In that case,
just tell me what you want.
In recent years, strange things
have been happening constantly.
The loyal officials
who used to serve my father
either died of unknown reasons
or are acting crazily.
The rest keep their mouths shut
and no longer care about court affairs.
I came here today,
hoping you can find evidence,
uncover the truth,
and expose the person behind all this
to the world.
As for the person behind all this,
I believe you already have an answer
in your mind.
Heed my order, Fa Wuwei.
(Dragon Guardians)
From now on,
you will resume your role
as a secret agent
and help me reclaim the throne.
Young master, this is the calming tea.
You should drink it first.
Xiao Fang.
Do you think there are really
people who are exactly alike
in this world?
Of course, there are.
Like twins.
Though they might not be
exactly the same from head to toe,
outsiders usually can't tell them apart.
(Twins?)
Young master,
based on the rules, you have to marry me
since you removed my mask.
By the way, I will send
the wedding suit to your house.
You don't need to prepare anything.
Just wait to marry me.
Are you really going to marry her?
So, young master,
will you wear this wedding suit or not?
I'll throw it away now.
Hold on.
This is such fine fabric.
If I don't wear it,
it would be a waste.
Such a fanfare.
What if he refuses to let me in?
Then the Tang family will be disgraced.
No.
The day we're going to get married was in plain sight.
He had his arm around me.
He took my mask off with one hand.
Isn't that what it means to be in love?
I'm from a family with a lot of money.
With my looks.
My personality.
There's no reason for him to refuse.
God, Tang Xiao Lu.
Be confident.
But what if when he sees me
there wasn't a trace of joy on his face.
It's going feel as cold as an ice.
It's like seeing something ominous.
Oops.
It's a pain in the ass.
I don't care.
Let's see what we can do.
Miss, we're here.
Light the firecrackers.
Why hasn't Young Master Wuji
come out to meet her?
Right.
Why is it so lively?
Don't you know etiquette?
Our lady is here.
Where is your young master?
(Because of You)
You are the one who knows no etiquette.
It's so early now.
There he is.
Step out.
So handsome.
She's getting out.
(So he does have me in his heart.)
Young Master Wuji
really kept his promise
and married the one
whose mask was removed by him.
Congratulations!
Miss, we will leave now.
Young master,
isn't it time for us
to worship heaven and earth?
It's okay if we don't.
After all, I don't like formalities.
We can keep things simple.
Then, young master, should we...
Miss, the hand you are holding is mine.
What?
How could he leave me here
just after leading me into the door?
What is going on?
Where is your young master?
Wuji!
(He's still in his wedding suit.)
(I knew he had feelings for me.)
Why are you doing this?
Based on the rules
of the Marital Festival,
I accept that I removed your mask
and we got engaged.
Although you set the wedding date
without discussing it with me,
I married you formally anyway.
But...
But,
I have no feelings for you.
In other words,
out of consideration
for both of our reputations,
this marriage will be one
about husband-and-wife etiquette
without reality.
(A marriage without reality?)
I told Xiao Fang
to prepare the side room.
You will live there from now on.
I don't want to.
It's no different than a fake marriage.
I don't want a marriage like this.
The best man in the whole city?
He is just a stone in the latrine,
stinky and hard.
I was blind.
I actually thought he would treat me
as he does in my dreams.
I must be out of my mind.
Stop.
You came here with a lot of fanfare.
Have you ever thought about
who will be embarrassed
if you go back like this?
Who says I'm going back?
I just want to see if all my dowries
were all moved in
without leaving a single one.
You were so eager to marry me.
What's your purpose? Tell me.
(If I directly tell him)
(that the person in my dream and he
are exactly the same,)
(will I be considered)
(like those women who adore him?)
(No, that's so embarrassing.)
Do I need a reason to like someone?
Wuji, tell me.
Do you really have no feelings
for me at all?
I...
Didn't you just mention
husband-and-wife etiquette?
In my family,
this is the husband-and-wife etiquette.
Fine. I'll live in the side room.
I'm going to collect my dowries.
This is my first kiss.
(Darn it. It's mine too.)
I want you dead!
♪Speaking of reincarnation,
of life and death♪
♪I've never had fear♪
♪But when it comes to you♪
♪I dare not say a word♪
♪It turns out that regret
is not about parting♪
♪We are so close at distance
yet far away by heart♪
♪It turns out deep love
doesn't always have an ending♪
♪It will either last until death
or be yearned for a lifetime♪
♪Carefully and inappropriately♪
♪I end up with nothing but empty joy♪
♪Even if it takes all my strength♪
♪I'm willing to give up freedom
to get close to you♪
♪I let go of everything
I've ever wanted in life♪
♪I hide my emotions
to play along with you♪
♪Just for that moment of joy♪
♪I walk towards you
against the wind and rain♪
♪I leave all the noise and chaos behind♪
♪There's no way to recall memories
or trace back the obsession♪
♪Because of you♪