♪Your secret, dangerous flaws♪
♪I can stay close
without seeing through♪
♪As long as it's about love♪
♪No matter how absurd♪
♪I choose to get used to it♪
♪Truth or lies, you decide what's true♪
♪I won't overturn it anymore♪
♪I cover my eyes and look♪
♪Is love an abyss or a trap♪
♪I only see the sparkle♪
=Turbulent Love=
=Episode 13=
=Pray Heaven Spares This Couple=
Officer Zhou.
You're full of surprises!
Why are you so good to me?
Do you hate Ji Zhijie too?
I don't do favors for free.
Then what do you want?
You just want to mess with Ji Zhijie.
But you're afraid of him.
You can't beat him.
I'm handing you his weakness now.
Once you kill Ji Zhijie,
give her back to me.
So I can play the hero
and then give me the goods.
Officer Zhou.
You're negotiating with me?
Aren't you afraid
I'll report you to the police station?
I have enough dirt on you
to put you in jail for a lifetime!
Besides,
if you keep these goods,
aren't you afraid Suphan
will come after you?
Why not let me sell them for you?
We both profit.
What if I say no?
Coming to see you today means
I'm ready to risk it all.
Alright, Officer Zhou.
But the price has to be right.
Officer Zhou.
I really don't get it.
I get wanting money and power.
But now you want her.
And you hand her over to me.
What are you really after?
What Ji Zhijie can or cannot have,
I want it all.
(Ji Zhijie.)
(Even if you're Liang Zhaokun's wolf,)
(I'm never his lapdog.)
(Everything you want.)
(I'll snatch it all.)
(Pabrik Street No. 27)
Hello?
Hello, Ji Zhijie.
Do you like the photos?
You just want to mess with me.
I can give you whatever you want.
Let her go.
Listen.
I only give you one hour.
Come alone.
Don't bring anything.
If you dare bring anyone else
or a single gun,
or are even a second late,
then I can't guarantee
what you'll get.
If anything happens to Hao Yu,
you'll get nothing.
And I'll take your life.
But you're running out of time.
You only have 58 minutes left.
57 minutes and 59 seconds.
58 seconds!
Go back, I'll go alone.
- Zhijie.
Ji Zhijie!
A life for a life.
They say Ji Zhijie loves you so much.
But why isn't he here yet?
Is he too scared to show up?
You must be so disappointed.
That's okay.
We can finish what we started
all those years ago.
Look.
I prepared this red bed
especially for you.
You're our one and only leading lady.
Has he kissed you here?
What about here?
How about
I make a cut right here first?
How does that sound?
Yingquan.
You just want revenge for the past.
Come at me instead.
I can give you anything you want.
You love playing the hero, don't you?
So I had to give you a chance.
She's in the container
right under my feet.
But,
where is the key?
Ke...
Right here?
Here?
I...
Here.
Here!
I also heard
she's even more afraid of the dark now.
I wonder how
she's doing right now.
Listen.
If you want to save her,
get on your knees like a dog!
In these broken glass shards,
find the key.
Take your time.
You don't have much time left.
Kneel down!
What a touching scene.
It almost makes me cry.
Do you remember
how arrogant you were
when you slashed my face?
I'll never forget it.
Did you ever think
you'd be kneeling before me
like a dog?
♪Don't take amber from my eyes♪
♪I'm scared you'll be swallowed by dark♪
♪Watching you get tied down♪
♪Trapped in the corner♪
♪My heart feels torn apart♪
♪Even if it's an abyss, I'll fall♪
Time is running out!
♪Gray fireworks♪
♪Pushing back the bright corners♪
♪Waiting for you to wakeup♪
♪Hurts me too much♪
♪I'm not afraid of the pain♪
♪Even if I turn to dust for you♪
♪Let the neon lights shatter and fall♪
♪Filling every desolate corner♪
I'm telling you.
You don't have much time left.
♪I pray and confess through pain♪
♪Reflecting on the unbearable past♪
♪Like a fire burning my eyes
from within♪
♪I keep touching♪
♪The lines on your palms♪
♪Now I know what pain is♪
♪You awakened the me deep in my soul♪
♪Gray fireworks♪
♪Pushing back the bright corners♪
Ten.
♪Waiting for you to wakeup♪
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
♪Let the neon lights shatter and fall♪
Five.
Four.
♪Still scared, I erase my wrongs♪
Three.
♪I pray and confess through pain♪
♪I learned to let go of myself♪
♪I burn away every bitter result♪
♪Just to light♪
♪Eternal fireworks for you♪
♪I'm not afraid of the pain♪
♪Even if I turn to dust for you♪
♪Let the neon lights shatter and fall♪
♪Filling every desolate corner♪
♪Don't leave me to survive alone♪
♪Still scared, I erase my wrongs♪
♪I pray and confess through pain♪
♪Only your love can♪
♪Take away the pain♪
Hao Yu, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Stay still if you don't want to die.
I know you won't let me go.
But as agreed, let Hao Yu go.
Do you think
I'm that trustworthy?
Then I deserve to die knowing the truth.
I need to confirm something
before I die.
Alright.
Go ahead, I'll grant your last wish.
Speak.
You saved Weihao
and lured Zhong Jiali
to ally with you, right?
Of course.
If Liang Zhaokun wasn't such a tyrant
and you weren't so blinded by love,
causing so much resentment,
I wouldn't have had a chance.
You killed Suchart.
After learning Zhong Jiali
failed to get the goods,
you incited Weihao to kill me
and take those goods.
Right?
Who does Suchart think he is?
Using his brother's status,
he dared to boss me around.
He's just like you.
You both deserve to die!
What did you do to him?
I destroyed his body
and framed you for it.
So you could seize power
and get revenge on me.
After taking the goods,
so you think you can
boss Suphan around, right?
Bingo!
I'll not only boss him around.
I'll boss you around too!
I'll take everything
you have.
And wipe out your Cangfeng!
You knew today was a death trap.
Yet you still came.
Then I'll have to
fulfill your tragic love story.
I'll kill you all.
Then return to Seronport
and rule Southeast Asia.
Rule Southeast Asia!
Go to hell!
You heartless Yingquan!
Dreaming of ruling Southeast Asia?
Pay for my brother's life!
Ji Zhijie.
A life for a life.
You scum killed my brother
and stole the goods meant for me.
Yet you still dare to look for me?
Bring it on!
I'll send you to hell right now!
I looked for you
because I thought you're reasonable.
I don't have time to explain.
If you want to know who killed Suchart,
come with me to Yingquan's place.
Once you know the truth,
you must cooperate with me.
Why should I trust you?
Yingquan's territory is also yours.
I'm all alone now.
What trouble could I possibly cause?
Pay for my brother's life!
I swore not to kill.
You take him. I'll find the goods.
I'll go look for the goods.
You wait here.
I... I'll go with you.
It's not a total loss.
Zhijie.
- Feilong, take him alive.
- Yes.
Feihu, move the goods now.
Before something goes wrong.
Got it.
It's okay now.
- It's okay. You're safe.
- It's okay.
You're safe now.
It's over.
(Police Station)
Have him fill out this form.
- Right.
- Keep a close eye.
Let's go.
Get this straight.
We are the victims here.
You failed to protect us.
You let my wife get kidnapped.
And I got injured.
Instead of catching the culprit,
why did you bring me here?
Please watch your language.
Legally, you are not married.
Whether we are married or not
is none of your business.
Is Officer Zhou
holding a personal grudge?
We received a tip.
Suspecting you of illegal trading.
Leading to a public disturbance.
Please cooperate with our investigation.
Zhou Ziheng, I'm warning you.
If you do anything
out of line to Hao Yu,
I don't know what I'll do.
Mr. Ji, please calm down.
We're all law enforcers.
And Officer Zhou
is the best officer we have.
This is a legal interrogation.
If nothing is found,
we'll release you right away.
You'd better.
My lawyer is on the way.
Okay.
Watch him.
I've turned off the audio and cameras.
You can speak freely now.
Hao Yu.
Did you hear what I said?
What do you want me to say?
Where are the goods?
How did you find me?
I told you
we have more than one mole
and informant.
Didn't your informant and mole know
that I was drugged, kidnapped
and almost died there?
I'm sorry.
You went through so much.
Do you still remember
what your kidnapper looked like?
Any memory of him?
You can tell my colleagues.
We can help you find him.
I'm not afraid of dying.
For my parents,
my brother,
and Mr. Guan
to rest in peace,
I chose this path of revenge myself.
I promised godfather
to do things legally and justly.
Of course I know that.
That's exactly why
we must finish this mission quickly.
I'm really worried about you.
Have you ever truly worried about me?
If it weren't for Ji Zhijie
and Suphan today,
I would have died there!
Ji Zhijie, Ji Zhijie.
Ji Zhijie!
You keep saying he did so much for you.
What about me?
To keep you from being exposed,
I played along with you
to frame Weihao.
Then I destroyed the data
and framed Zhong Jiali.
I risked my life
to apply for a special mission
from the police station
to catch Ji Zhijie.
All to take down Cangfeng.
I even got injured
and demoted.
Everything I did
was to hide your identity
as an informant.
So Cangfeng wouldn't find out.
Can't you see that?
Or
have you fallen in love with Ji Zhijie?
You want to betray Mr. Guan?
I'm not the one betraying Mr. Guan.
I was drugged and kidnapped today.
Ji Zhijie and Suphan saved me.
I saw someone stealing the goods.
That guy
even shot at me.
And then,
by coincidence,
we ran into you.
And you brought us here.
That's everything that happened today.
Alright.
Yingquan is dead.
I heard Suphan is in Seronport too.
Ji Zhijie will probably
finish this deal soon.
Your mission now
is to find the goods
as soon as possible.
And tell me right away.
Why do you care so much about the goods?
Shouldn't we
investigate their deal
and take them all down?
Right.
Of course that's what I think.
Hao Yu,
how are you?
Are you okay?
Did he hurt you?
I'm fine.
But look at you,
you're a mess
and still worrying about me.
My husband is badly injured.
If Officer Zhou has nothing else,
we'll be leaving now.
Feilong, let's go.
We're going to the hospital.
Better have the doctor
come to the house.
Hurry.
Let's go.
I'm fine. They're just scratches.
Don't talk.
Okay, okay.
Alright.
It's not the first time.
Hao Yu, I'm really fine.
These are just scratches.
I'm perfectly fine.
What if
Suphan's men hadn't shown up today?
Shanmao just wanted to
show me who's boss.
As long as I'm alive,
he can torture me all he wants.
Your safety's all that counts.
Alright, alright.
Don't cry.
We're both safe now.
It's all my fault.
I should've had someone protect you.
Don't cry.
It's okay.
Do you still remember
how they kidnapped you?
I...
I was just
going to buy something,
and then I took a shortcut.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's fine.
Ji Zhijie,
why?
You're clearly a bad guy,
but you're always so good to me.
Always showing up when I need you most.
Time for your medicine.
It's too bitter.
Now I need a little
sweet reward.
It works better than medicine.
♪Don't take amber from my eyes♪
♪I'm scared you'll be swallowed by dark♪
♪Watching you get tied down♪
♪Trapped in the corner♪
♪My heart feels torn apart♪
♪Even if it's an abyss, I'll fall♪
♪Gray fireworks♪
♪Pushing back the bright corners♪
♪Waiting for you to wakeup♪
♪Hurts me too much♪
♪I'm not afraid of the pain♪
♪Even if I turn to dust for you♪
♪Let the neon lights shatter and fall♪
♪Filling every desolate corner♪
♪Don't leave me to survive alone♪
♪Still scared, I erase my wrongs♪
♪I pray and confess through pain♪
♪I learned to let go of myself♪
♪I burn away every bitter result♪
♪Just to light♪
♪Eternal fireworks for you♪
♪I'm not afraid of the pain♪
♪Even if I turn to dust for you♪
♪Let the neon lights shatter and fall♪
♪Filling every desolate corner♪
♪Don't leave me to survive alone♪
♪Still scared, I erase my wrongs♪
♪I pray and confess through pain♪