♪Your secret, dangerous flaws♪
♪I can stay close
without seeing through♪
♪As long as it's about love♪
♪No matter how absurd♪
♪I choose to get used to it♪
♪Truth or lies, you decide what's true♪
♪I won't overturn it anymore♪
♪I cover my eyes and look♪
♪Is love an abyss or a trap♪
♪I only see the sparkle♪
=Turbulent Love=
=Episode 19=
=Too Beautiful to Touch=
Hao Yu.
- Ji Zhijie...
- Hao Yu?
Ji Zhijie.
Hao Yu.
Feihu?
Xiaocui?
You guys...
Why are you here?
Weren't you...
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Mr. Ji saved me.
You're safe now.
Don't you worry.
Zhijie had it all planned.
We are all fine.
Zhijie did all this to earn
the trust of Councilman Zhu
and Zhu Shuyi, so he could dismantle
the forces in Seronport.
He even had me fooled at first.
We grew up following Zhijie.
He's always been good to us.
And for you, Yu...
He'd never let a hair on your head be harmed.
That's why I found it so weird.
On the day he drove me away,
I went back to see him.
Zhijie.
I told you to leave.
Why are you back?
Go away!
I said go away!
Zhijie,
I've been with you all these years.
Even if you're wrong,
I'll do as you say.
But driving me away?
I can't do it.
Hit me.
Beat me to death.
Just take my life.
There's no one else here.
Please tell me the truth.
I've said all I need to say.
Don't you get it?
I'm not like Feihu or Feiying.
Even if I have to go,
or if I die,
I want to die knowing the truth.
Feiying, Feihu,
and Xiaocui
are all alive.
I'll have someone pull you out of the water.
Don't be afraid.
From now on,
just follow my lead.
I'd save you for Hao Yu's sake anyway.
Why are you crying?
So that's why you did it, Zhijie.
Now I understand.
Zhijie,
you're quite the actor.
We were forced to join Cangfeng.
We've done the dirty work,
shed blood and taken lives.
But now, I want to do something right.
We've nearly died several times.
You saved us every time.
My life
is yours to take.
But please don't drive us away.
Same here.
Why did Ji Zhijie do this?
Why didn't he say anything?
Where is he now?
Yu.
Since you started hurting yourself,
Zhijie has been
drowning in guilt.
Hao Yu.
Hao Yu!
The doctor said it was luckily found early.
The cut isn't deep.
(Does loving me)
(make you feel like dying?)
♪Suddenly the sky turns dark♪
♪The rain of love is pouring down heavily♪
♪Before fate is washed away♪
♪My soul's been flooded♪
One of you is human,
the other is a monster.
We are from two different worlds.
Even if you're willing to crawl
out of hell in human skin for her sake-
Too many lies stood in our way-
Suspicion, and hatred.
Your lives
aren't yours to decide.
Even if you tore out
your heart to give to her,
she wouldn't accept it.
From the very beginning,
you were wrong.
Dead wrong!
When I adopted you,
I meant to raise you
as my successor.
But everything went wrong.
Love isn't forcing,
controlling, or possessing.
Love is about respect
and fulfillment.
What do you want me to fulfill?
Hao Yu?
What do you want?
Turn myself in right now,
let you kill me right here,
or wipe out all of the forces
in Cangfeng and Seronport?
Will that make you happy?
Will it?
But you won't do that.
(I will.)
(I will do that,)
(but not just yet.)
(I'm going to clear)
(this treacherous path for you.)
(Since I love you,)
(I won't tie you down.)
(I want you to be happy.)
♪Love took...♪
(So whatever you want to do,)
(whatever justice you're after,)
(I'll get it back for you with my own hands.)
(Hao Yu,)
(wake up.)
(You have to live on to hate me.)
♪Entangled with you♪
♪Let me stay in your rainy days♪
♪Unaware of the changing seasons♪
♪With eyes closed♪
♪Your hate or lies♪
♪I take it all as love♪
Eat.
Ji Zhijie, what do you want?
If you leave even a grain of rice,
I'll dump it.
If you hurt yourself again,
I'll make all of Seronport
taste what it feels like.
Ji Zhijie, you're crazy!
I gave you a chance.
Eat.
Since you'd rather choose death over me,
I'm done treating you like a fragile prize.
You're not going to the UK.
I won't indulge or spoil you anymore.
Hao Yu, I want you to live and pay
for what you've done.
But I promise,
if you behave yourself and eat properly,
I'll let you go.
(I'm sorry.)
(If hate is what keeps you alive,)
(then hate me.)
(Keep hating me,)
(pull yourself together,)
(do whatever it takes
to take me down, and kill me.)
(Besides,)
(even if you look me with such loathing,)
(I want that gaze to
linger on me a little longer.)
Tell Councilman Zhu
I accept his gifts.
Round up the guys. Ancestral hall. Now.
Zhijie.
Have you made up your mind?
Feilong.
I need to see someone first.
Okay.
You wanted to see me?
That's a surprise.
I've gone through all your police files.
You're the cleanest cop and the most
upright one.
I want to work with you.
I will help you dismantle
every syndicate in Seronport.
Including you?
Including me,
and Cangfeng.
But I have a few conditions.
My guys
were forced into Cangfeng.
Some don't deserve to die.
If the law allows,
I want their sentences reduced.
Give them a chance to start over
and go straight.
You have my word.
Anything else?
She has been your source.
Whatever happens,
you must make sure
she's safe and free.
Don't worry.
My duty is to protect every citizen
in Seronport.
One more thing.
To make her eat,
I've done something highly disrespectful.
I hope you can go see her.
Help her pull it together.
Make her believe there is
still hope and good cops
left in this world.
Ji Zhijie,
you're just like the rumors-
brave, resourceful,
and a hopeless romantic.
I'm not a big hero.
I don't have your grand ambitions.
(Guan Renjie)
I won't give up.
You shouldn't either!
Officer Guan wouldn't want you to give up!
Walk me through
your plan.
I'm going all in
to become the kingpin.
(If falling into a darker world)
(can buy your path to the light,)
(then I'll stay)
(in the abyss forever.)
- (Playing along with hypocrites)
- A pleasure.
(isn't hard at all.)
- (What's hard is)
- Cheers.
Cheers.
(facing the people who care about you)
(and lying to their faces.)
Who told you to do that?
Got guts now, huh?
- Who told you to do that?
- Zhijie.
Zhijie...
Come on, Feiying. Are you a model citizen?
Never done a dirty deed in your life?
And now you're lecturing me on morality?
Who taught you that?
- You!
- Zhijie.
Drag him to the kennel.
Then send him to Councilman Zhu
to kneel for forgiveness.
Don't come back until he's satisfied.
Zhijie!
I'm still your boss anyway.
Don't think I don't know
Lianxing offered you
a truckload of gold,
and now you dare talk to me like this.
If you want out,
get out right now!
They did offer it to me,
but I didn't take a single piece.
Don't believe rumors and turn against us.
I do have my suspicions.
Let me tell you, Feilong.
All good things come to an end.
Go.
You.
And you.
All of you, go.
Go abroad.
Go to Xingzhou Port.
Get out of Seronport.
From today on,
I won't tolerate a single whiff of betrayal.
This isn't like you at all.
If you have a plan or a problem,
please just tell us.
Didn't I make myself clear?
This is exactly what I want!
All of you, get out!
Fine.
Zhijie,
you want us to leave,
but I, Feilong,
won't leave Ji Zhijie and Cangfeng!
(And the hardest part of all this-)
Hao Yu, stop flattering yourself.
(is facing you.)
Get this straight.
The only reason I'm keeping you alive
is to torture you
and make you pay.
You'd better stay home
and keep out of trouble.
The more you try to bring me down,
the more you'll see
I'm untouchable.
Miss Hao!
Please save me!
- What are you doing?
- Save me!
- Save me
- Get up.
What happened to you?
Feihu,
Ji Zhijie took over Li Island
to build a factory
and turned a lounge into a marketplace.
He made me transfer it to Zhu Shuyi
just to run this shady business?
No, no, no.
There must be some misunderstanding.
(You're so smart.)
(You must know what I'm doing.)
(Your sense of justice will)
(definitely make you step in.)
(But to earn the trust)
(of the Councilman and Zhu Shuyi,)
- (I must keep playing the tyrant)
- You...
(and be cruel to you.)
(Only this way)
(can I clear you of this completely.)
- M-My face...
- I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
- My hair!
I'm so sorry, Miss Zhu.
I'm sorry.
Miss Zhu and I have some unfinished business.
I'll apologize to Miss Zhu.
I'll beg for her forgiveness, okay?
Keep kneeling if you want.
In the past,
- (It's going to rain.)
- Zhong Jiali told me
you were a hopeless romantic.
- (I must get Zhu Shuyi in soon.)
- But you don't
come across that way.
People change.
Earlier,
the sea breeze felt nice.
But now it's all dark clouds
and lightning out there.
Miss Zhu,
what I want now
is money, power, and status-
more than
Liang Zhaokun ever had.
You've been good to me.
I'd say you are the perfect
candidate for a marriage alliance.
Right now,
you're the one I approve of the most.
Tomorrow,
I'll take you to meet the insiders.
And we'll tell them
about our marriage.
It looks like
I'll have to stay
at your place tonight.
Those reporters haven't left yet.
Stay as long as you like.
So,
which room is mine?
Whichever you want.
It's going to rain.
Miss Zhu, you're so eager to marry me.
Do you expect me to
clean up the Councilman's mess?
Mr. Ji,
you'll have twice the leverage.
Buy one, get one free.
From now on,
these will be your key assets in the game.
The more blame you take for Godfather,
the more rewards he will give you.
Your position
will only keep rising.
I understand.
I hope this is a good idea.
So, tonight...
Miss Zhu, you should get some rest.
I'll leave you be.
I'll sleep in the study.
Give her an umbrella and bring her in.
Tell her she's wasting her time.
Say it the way I taught you.
Go.
Miss Hao, it's raining.
Get up and come inside.
I told you to check on Feihu.
How are they doing?
I just came from the kennel.
Feihu...
He's barely recognizable.
But luckily, Feilong arrived in time
and sent him to the hospital.
He said he doesn't blame you
and you shouldn't blame yourself.
He also said
although he doesn't know as much as Feilong
about what happened between you and Zhijie,
he wants you to take care of yourself.
He'll never see you any differently.
And if you
really can't hold on anymore,
just leave.
Because Zhijie
is not the same as before.
I'll talk to him.
- Ji Zhijie!
- It won't work, Miss Hao.
- It won't work!
It won't work.
I heard him on the phone.
That waitress's eyes
have been gouged out.
It's true, Miss Hao.
They took videos and photos
for Mr. Ji and Miss Zhu to confirm.
Get up.
You're all thumbs.
You can't do anything right.
After tonight...
Right,
tonight is the night.
As long as you behave
and stay in line,
I can let you go.
You will be free.
(I can't stand treating you)
(like this even for a single day.)
(I want to hold your hand.)
(I want you to hug me.)
(I want to hug you too.)
(But I can't drop)
(this charade now.)
You have a fever.
Don't you hate me?
Just go away.
Go!
(I don't want to let you go.)
(But...)
(I have no choice.)
Go!
All of you, go!
Go away.
(I have to wait)
(until the day I gain their full trust.)
(Only then can I safely send you away.)
Cheers.
If you want in,
you need to prove yourself.
If you can't deal with her,
we'll do it for you.
She's no threat.
Don't waste your breath on her.
I raise this glass
to the big picture.
Smart boy.
Cheers.
To the big picture.
Come on, dig in.
Come on.
(They are threating you.)
(You're putting yourself at risk.)
(The safest way)
(is to make you disappear)
(and remove you from the plan completely.)
You set this up.
After Guan Renjie died,
Zhou Ziheng showed up.
After a reporter died,
random cops showed up.
You're the one who deserves to die!
I'm done protecting her.
Do whatever you want.
(Alright.)
(It's all over.)
(Everything is over.)
Hello?
The new product launch today.
Are you all set?
Yes.
All the key figures will be there today.
This time,
we must make sure nothing goes wrong.
Sure.
(Hao Yu,)
(it's finally coming to an end.)
♪Don't take amber from my eyes♪
♪I'm scared you'll be swallowed by dark♪
♪Watching you get tied down♪
♪Trapped in the corner♪
♪My heart feels torn apart♪
♪Even if it's an abyss, I'll fall♪
♪Gray fireworks♪
♪Pushing back the bright corners♪
♪Waiting for you to wake up♪
♪Hurts me too much♪
♪I'm not afraid of the pain♪
♪Even if I turn to dust for you♪
♪Let the neon lights shatter and fall♪
♪Filling every desolate corner♪
♪Don't leave me to survive alone♪
♪Still scared, I erase my wrongs♪
♪I pray and confess through pain♪
♪I learned to let go of myself♪
♪I burn away every bitter result♪
♪Just to light♪
♪Eternal fireworks for you♪
♪I'm not afraid of the pain♪
♪Even if I turn to dust for you♪
♪Let the neon lights shatter and fall♪
♪Filling every desolate corner♪
♪Don't leave me to survive alone♪
♪Still scared, I erase my wrongs♪
♪I pray and confess through pain♪