♪The spring breeze whispers
through the evening glow♪
♪Wandering clouds ride a white steed♪
♪Plucking the stars from the sky♪
♪Weaving them into a crown of blossoms♪
♪Red hues tint both cheeks♪
♪A light boat glides through
the Milky Way♪
♪Whose beautiful lass is laughing
on the Magpie Bridge?♪
♪It's her♪
♪Eager to see the world's splendor♪
♪Running down into the changing world♪
♪A playful, innocent little lass♪
♪This bustling world♪
♪As bright as a painting♪
♪Look at how the fireworks
dye the spring breeze♪
♪The light breeze stirs
countless flowers♪
♪Who smiles warmly among the leaves?♪
♪Let the years pass
with laughter and tears♪
♪In this world, let me♪
♪Love♪
♪Freely♪
[When Fate Plays Matchmaker]
[Episode 15]
Miss Zhao, do you remember saying
you'd be there for me
if I ever needed help?
I do.
What can I do for you, Mr. Cao?
I'd like to ask you
to help me find a good match.
May I ask
what kind of girl
you are interested in?
She has delicate willow-leaf brows
and charming almond eyes,
unpretentious and buoyant.
She is unaffected by power and wealth,
with a heart that is both just and kind.
Aspirations and courage
shine through her eyes,
and her heart is filled
with care for the people.
In the face of danger, she remains true
to loyalty and righteousness.
She often wears
a golden bracelet on her left wrist.
Mr. Cao, are you referring to...
Shuangshuang, I've had feelings for you.
I truly appreciate
how you helped me
through the toughest times
in my life.
Mother,
have some water.
Since Master is not home,
we have to do whatever First Madam says.
Even if they died,
it would just be
the death of two pests in her eyes.
Let's not get involved and leave.
Mr. Cao, it's me,
Zhao Shuangshuang.
Mr. Cao, I've already checked.
Master Cao will be back in ten days.
You two must hang in there.
I'll figure out a way
to bring you more food.
It was because of you
that I made it until my father returned,
though my mother didn't.
To be honest,
at that time,
I didn't know
when Master Cao would return.
I just picked a day that seemed
neither too distant nor too soon,
hoping it would give you both some hope.
Thank you, Shuangshuang.
You've become my hope.
From then on, even in my darkest hours,
you were the beacon within me.
I know we're not connected
by a romance line,
but I believe that wise man
guided me here
because I'm destined
to meet you.
I have never been so devoted
to any other woman.
Shuangshuang,
will you give me a chance?
So it turns out my fated match
is none other than Mr. Cao.
Mr. Cheng,
I guess you've never met someone
to make your heart race.
That kind of feeling
is just a momentary impulse.
Though the feeling may be momentary,
the heart
isn't like the liquor in this pot.
It's not something
you can pour out at will.
It'll be alright.
From now on,
I've got you covered.
Could it be
that I've really fallen
for Zhao Shuangshuang?
I have faith that the matchmaking vision
is always right.
My fated match
is Mr. Cao.
So, you are saying
that he came back
from the Yue Lao Temple,
slept for two whole days,
and ended up like this?
Yes.
You can't be serious.
Did you mention
that Miss Zhao came back with Mr. Cao?
Yes.
I see now.
Watch this.
Zhao Shuangshuang is here.
Who are you looking for,
Cheng?
She's not here.
Cheng,
once you start to long for someone,
you'll taste the bitterness of love.
Let me tell you,
young women today value directness.
You're a man,
so tell her if you like her.
I...
Who said I like her?
But what exactly do you mean
by "directness?"
The gaze is everything.
Give her a gaze
that's both intense and casual.
Let your eyes show
a mix of deep affection
and a bit of wildness.
Then, when she's distracted,
pull her into your arms
and whisper in your sexiest voice,
''I want you
to be mine."
If I knew how to pull that off,
do you think
I'd still be sharing a room with him?
Is it really true
that the young women these days
prefer directness?
Don't underestimate my simple tricks.
I'm sure
it will help you win her heart.
Once Zhao Shuangshuang sees it,
she'll be all smitten...
Who's talking about me?
♪Petals fall like rain
outside the window♪
♪Murmurings whisper around my ears♪
♪My mind is clear at this moment♪
♪With a smile, the spring breeze
charms the years of youth♪
♪Affection's threads entwine♪
♪The journey stretches on and on♪
♪My heart blooms with joy before you♪
♪Revealing what's hidden♪
♪Just in time for an old friend♪
♪Whose youth lingers,
awaiting my return?♪
♪With adoration, I trace your face♪
♪The red candle sways,
my heart in disarray♪
♪Who paints their longing
across their brow?♪
♪A hint of yearning gently swings♪
♪With love's brush, I trace your face♪
♪The red candle sways,
my heart in disarray♪
♪In shades of gray,
fate takes many turns♪
♪Unfolding my hand,
where fate's tale is etched♪