♪The spring breeze whispers
through the evening glow♪
♪Wandering clouds ride a white steed♪
♪Plucking the stars from the sky♪
♪Weaving them into a crown of blossoms♪
♪Red hues tint both cheeks♪
♪A light boat glides through
the Milky Way♪
♪Whose beautiful lass is laughing
on the Magpie Bridge?♪
♪It's her♪
♪Eager to see the world's splendor♪
♪Running down into the changing world♪
♪A playful, innocent little lass♪
♪This bustling world♪
♪As bright as a painting♪
♪Look at how the fireworks
dye the spring breeze♪
♪The light breeze stirs
countless flowers♪
♪Who smiles warmly among the leaves?♪
♪Let the years pass
with laughter and tears♪
♪In this world, let me♪
♪Love♪
♪Freely♪
[When Fate Plays Matchmaker]
[Episode 21]
Bad news.
What's wrong?
Did something happen to Shuangshuang?
Say something.
It's not Mrs. Zhao.
It's Miss Li.
I just heard
that she's already married to Mr. Guo.
Didn't Lian say before
that Miss Li was supposed
to marry Mr. Zhou?
Yes, I don't know why
she ended up marrying Guo Chuan.
Does Shuangshuang know about this?
I've already sent someone to inform her.
Bad news.
Bad news. Mr. Liang, Cheng Yin,
help Miss Zhao.
What happened to Shuangshuang? Tell me.
Make it clear.
Miss Zhao just rescued Miss Li
from Guo's Mansion,
and is now confronting Cao Sui.
Why do I have to worry
so much about you all recently?
Wait for me.
I'll rely on you for this matter.
Be careful with the steps.
Also, Mr. Guo,
we'd better not meet here next time.
Zhao Shuangshuang
has already found out about Lin Susu.
So what?
What can a mere matchmaker do to me?
By the way,
find that Li woman for me.
How dare she escape!
I'll make sure she regrets it.
My father
once had a serious illness relapse,
but thanks to Mr. Guo,
he narrowly escaped death.
I truly appreciated it.
But after marrying into the Guo family,
I discovered that it was all a trap.
I wanted to divorce him,
[Li Jingshu]
but Guo Chuan refused.
He even abused me.
When I tried to escape,
no matter where I went,
they always managed to catch me.
Miss Li,
I'm at fault
for what has happened to you.
Miss Zhao,
you've been deceived by Cao Sui, too.
I overheard
that Cao Sui married you
just to control your agency
and help high-ranking officials
find concubines.
Farewell, sir.
Go and catch them.
How come you're here?
What? Am I not allowed to be here?
Is it that I'm not supposed
to see you and Guo Chuan
doing wicked deeds?
Or that I'm not meant to know
you were responsible for the deaths
of Cheng Zhi and Lin Susu?
Cao Sui,
I always thought
you were my destined partner,
but it turns out
you were just using me all along.
Shuangshuang,
it's not what you think.
I do love you.
Tell me,
did you and Guo Chuan scheme
to have Miss Li
marry into the Guo family?
Calm down.
The reason I'm doing this is...
Was it you behind what happened
to Lin Susu as well?
Tell me!
Can you guess
what that person went out to do?
He went to catch those folks
from the matchmaking agency.
Find that Li woman for me.
This person
looks kind of familiar.
So Cao Sui has been setting me up
from the very beginning.
Kill me.
Come on!
I'll give you the chance.
For every wound you inflict on me,
I'll make sure one of them pays.
And if I die,
these four will go down with me.
You're shameless!
Shuangshuang,
you're better suited
to accompany me in the guesthouse.
Shuangshuang,
I truly love you.
If you agree to share your life with me,
we'll have wealth and prestige
beyond measure.
Isn't that enough?
I can't bear this kind of life.
I only help those
who are meant to be together.
I don't care for wealth, prestige,
or empty titles.
Get real!
Being kind-hearted
won't guarantee success.
It won't pave my way to the top.
Nor will it bring
my mother back to life!
Is that why you killed Cheng Zhi
and Lin Susu?
It wasn't me who killed him,
but Lin Susu!
If she had agreed to marry Mr. Guo
as his concubine,
I wouldn't have had to make up stories
in front of the Lin family,
saying he was the son
of their sworn enemy.
Cao Sui,
I didn't expect you to be so cruel.
I truly regret it.
I should never have brought you food
in the first place.
From today on,
our engagement
is dissolved.
From now on,
we'll have nothing to do
with each other.
Let go of me!
What can you do once you leave here?
Do you really think
you're the top matchmaker in Lin'an?
You only succeeded
because of your matchmaking vision.
Now that it's been taken away,
what's left for you?
How do you know that?
I heard you and Lian talking that day.
I've plotted so much,
but I never considered using it
to threaten you.
Why?
Because I truly love you.
Yet now, you want to leave me.
Let go of me!
Don't forget.
They're still in my hands.
If you step out of this door today,
tomorrow will be their doomsday.
Cao Sui, you're despicable!
That's right.
From now on, if there's anything I want,
no one can stop me.
Our wedding will be in two days.
What you choose to do
is entirely up to you.
Miss Zhao,
have you decided to marry Cao Sui?
Why not escape now
while no one's around?
If I leave now,
Cheng Yin and the others
will be in danger.
I can't just walk away like this.
But Miss Zhao,
you mustn't place yourself
in such danger.
Cheng Yin has his trick of deception,
they might have already escaped.
But if you
did marry into the Cao family,
do you think they would release you
without consequences?
You always put others first,
but what about yourself?
I can't let Cheng Yin
face any more danger.
Besides, I'm partly to blame
for his senior's death.
I owe him this.
Miss Zhao, are you ready?
Almost.
Lian,
I need you to prepare something for me.
♪Petals fall like rain
outside the window♪
♪Murmurings whisper around my ears♪
♪My mind is clear at this moment♪
♪With a smile, the spring breeze
charms the years of youth♪
♪Affection's threads entwine♪
♪The journey stretches on and on♪
♪My heart blooms with joy before you♪
♪Revealing what's hidden♪
♪Just in time for an old friend♪
♪Whose youth lingers,
awaiting my return?♪
♪With adoration, I trace your face♪
♪The red candle sways,
my heart in disarray♪
♪Who paints their longing
across their brow?♪
♪A hint of yearning gently swings♪
♪With love's brush, I trace your face♪
♪The red candle sways,
my heart in disarray♪
♪In shades of gray,
fate takes many turns♪
♪Unfolding my hand,
where fate's tale is etched♪