f♪The spring breeze whispers
through the evening glow♪
♪Wandering clouds ride a white steed♪
♪Plucking the stars from the sky♪
♪Weaving them into a crown of blossoms♪
♪Red hues tint both cheeks♪
♪A light boat glides through
the Milky Way♪
♪Whose beautiful lass is laughing
on the Magpie Bridge?♪
♪It's her♪
♪Eager to see the world's splendor♪
♪Running down into the changing world♪
♪A playful, innocent little lass♪
♪This bustling world♪
♪As bright as a painting♪
♪Look at how the fireworks
dye the spring breeze♪
♪The light breeze stirs
countless flowers♪
♪Who smiles warmly among the leaves?♪
♪Let the years pass
with laughter and tears♪
♪In this world, let me♪
♪Love♪
♪Freely♪
[When Fate Plays Matchmaker]
[Episode 10]
When will I finally get to dress up
just for myself?
Miss Zhao,
all you need is one last deal.
Why do you insist on breaking off
Miss Song's engagement to the Yuans?
I made a mistake in matchmaking once,
and I can't let it happen again.
[Memorial tablet
of Lin Susu, my beloved daughter]
Susu, my dear daughter,
how could you
depart this life before me?
Miss Zhao.
It's all because Miss Song
offered me such a generous sum.
Who could say no to money, right?
Go and see if Cheng Yin
has arrived yet.
Mr. Liang is taking forever. Go.
He's coming.
Miss Zhao,
why have you taken
this wedding attire out again?
I was just thinking
that maybe I should marry
in Miss Song's place.
Miss Zhao, you can't do that.
The Yuan family isn't one to mess with.
You'll be heading straight for trouble.
Shuangshuang
was an orphaned girl,
so she wished
to get married early.
Then I'll start a family
with my destined one for a lifetime.
From now on,
this place will be your home!
As long as there's food on my table,
there'll be enough for you too!
Here, take a chicken drumstick!
Who I marry doesn't really matter.
My life isn't all that precious.
But Miss Song is different.
If we help her fulfill her wish,
more people will benefit,
right?
But,
what about you, Miss Zhao?
Don't you have someone you fancy?
Even Lian
knows about her feelings for me now.
Why bring that up? Say something else.
Say something else.
Miss Zhao, you've done so much
just to find
and marry your true love.
If you end up
marrying into the Yuan family,
wouldn't that ruin your life?
This won't do.
Even if I can't marry her,
she shouldn't ruin her life
by marrying just anyone.
This isn't right.
She shouldn't be ruined by marriage.
Who's to blame for my miserable fate?
I'm all by myself,
what can I do?
Cheng Yin must have heard
what we said by now.
Why hasn't he come in?
Miss Zhao, Mr. Cao is here.
Forget it, looks like
I can't rely on Cheng Yin after all.
Lian, I'll go and see Mr. Cao.
Please have some tea, Mr. Cao.
I just can't bring myself
to watch Miss Song
marry into the Yuan family.
I've failed the task
due to my incompetence.
Please forgive me, Mr. Cao.
You're being too hard on yourself.
I understand.
Love can't be forced,
so it's not your fault.
Mr. Cao,
you are such a kind person.
Would it be all right
if I ask for one more tiny favor?
Don't worry,
I'll take care of things
on the Song family's side.
This woman isn't persistent at all.
One moment she's asking for my help,
and the next she's off
seeking assistance elsewhere.
She didn't even try to ask me again.
What are you doing?
Mr. Liang asked me
to bring you some snacks.
Oh, by the way,
I've agreed to help
with what you asked.
The servant here
is a little thoughtless.
My apologies, Mr. Cao.
I'll talk to you about it later.
You go back first.
I already said I'd help you.
Go back.
Sorry about that, Mr. Cao.
No worries.
If the servant is difficult to manage,
we can always sack him
and find someone else.
I came today
to bring you some treats.
I'm not sure
if you still like these apricot cakes.
I do.
They're my favorites.
How about I bring you apricot cakes
from time to time?
This man is quite something.
Why is he trying to get close to her
when requesting the matchmaking service?
That's great.
Should you need
any assistance in the future,
I'll definitely be there to help.
I've been told
that you have a matchmaking vision.
Would you be willing
to take a look at my fate?
Perhaps the time hasn't come yet.
Your matchmaking thread hasn't appeared.
Then, I wonder,
where does yours lead to?
To be honest,
mine hasn't appeared either.
Looks like we're both in the same boat.
Asking her to read your fate?
I think you're just trying
to flirt with the girl.
What are you doing, Cheng Yin?
Give me your hand.
Your hand.
How could you use the cloth
for cleaning windows to wipe my hand?
You are so annoying.
Weren't we supposed
to help Miss Song together?
Why is there suddenly
an unknown person showing up?
Won't this just make things
more complicated?
Didn't you tell me this afternoon
that you weren't willing to help me?
But I just changed my mind.
Well, it's a bit late
for you to change your mind.
Mr. Cao has already agreed to help me
and even gave me
these delicious apricot cakes.
Have you never had apricot cakes before?
Look at you,
all excited over something so trivial.
My senior always warned me
not to eat anything
from unknown sources.
♪Petals fall like rain
outside the window♪
♪Murmurings whisper around my ears♪
♪My mind is clear at this moment♪
♪With a smile, the spring breeze
charms the years of youth♪
♪Affection's threads entwine♪
♪The journey stretches on and on♪
♪My heart blooms with joy before you♪
♪Revealing what's hidden♪
♪Just in time for an old friend♪
♪Whose youth lingers,
awaiting my return?♪
♪With adoration, I trace your face♪
♪The red candle sways,
my heart in disarray♪
♪Who paints their longing
across their brow?♪
♪A hint of yearning gently swings♪
♪With love's brush, I trace your face♪
♪The red candle sways,
my heart in disarray♪
♪In shades of gray,
fate takes many turns♪
♪Unfolding my hand,
where fate's tale is etched♪