[Killing intent!]
[No!]
Your demon power is weak.
Why bother resisting?
Today, you'll die!
[A'Li.]
[What's wrong?]
[I found a story]
[I must tell you.]
A'Li.
A'Li, something's wrong!
A butterfly flew back from Little White.
He might be caught by a demon hunter!
Stay calm.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Why hasn't A'Li come back yet?
What are you doing here?
Little Bell Spirit,
have you never left the Demon Village?
So what?
[The guardian of the barrier]
[must not leave the Demon Village.]
[Hidden places]
there will be lion-like Suanni patterns.
It seems my investigation is correct.
You
are the evil spirit guarding the barrier.
Shen Que,
the demons of the Demon Village have never done evil.
If you hurt me,
they will be threatened.
I will definitely take your life.
You will surely regret it.
To slay demons and evil,
what is there to regret?
Focus your mind,
calm the waters...
A'Li!
Zhongjing,
protect His Highness!
A'Li!
You're finally back!
You know, I've been so worried
that I couldn't eat or sleep!
I had to transform
and force myself to stay calm!
Don't worry.
Little White,
we have to trust A'Li.
She'll handle this.
Love is against selfishness,
cowardice,
betrayal, and greed in one's bones.
Love is a moment outside of order,
knowing the other's shortcomings,
yet always feeling indebted.
A'Li,
recently, you've been entering dreams and getting hurt,
Your spiritual power is greatly depleted.
If you don't consume the nightmares of the Utmost Evil One
and continue cultivation,
I'm afraid
you won't have the strength to keep searching for the Spiritual Root.
I won't forgive you.
Shen Que.
Welcome back, Your Highness.
What are these two baskets?
Your Highness,
this is what Meng Li...
Your Highness, you've had a long day.
Master is still recovering.
He can't meet you for now.
He asked me to tell you,
your bravery in the Demon Village
is commendable.
Your courage is unmatched,
a blessing to the people.
Thank you, State Preceptor.
I'll visit you another day.
Your Highness,
take a good rest.
His Highness was injured by the witch
and lost his memory.
He barely escaped from the Demon Village.
Remember,
don't mention
his past with that witch.
It will confuse him.
That Meng Li
really hurt His Highness?
Don't ask too much.
Just take care of him.
Yes.
Why are you so lazy?
You could have taken shape if you tried harder.
Stop lying there.
Get up and move.
Move.
So what if we take shape?
We just bask in the sun,
absorbing the essence of nature.
Taking shape has many benefits.
You can move freely,
explore every corner of the world,
instead of being stuck in one place
like you are now.
But you've taken human form,
and you're still stuck here.
What's the difference between us?
You...
Alright, Little Bell.
I'm sorry.
I'll cultivate harder.
Don't be upset.
We all know
you stay here to protect
our clan's barrier.
You're a hero to us.
It's good enough.
Our clan is full of
beautiful scenery.
I'm already grateful to
protect such a beautiful place.
But what's the world outside like?
If there were no demon hunters,
I'd like to be the wind,
going wherever I want,
seeing everything in the world.
You never got to see the world
for the sake of our clan.
In your next life,
you can be a tree,
or a gust of wind,
whatever you wish.