Why am I imprisoned here?
Daozhi,
you don't remember me?
Of course I do.
You've done so many evil deeds,
how could I forget?
Li,
I've been studying ancient texts.
I think
if I remove the spiritual root,
Shen Que might not necessarily die.
Is that true?
Back then,
he used the threads of affection
to seal your spiritual root in your divine consciousness.
If the spiritual root is extracted,
he may not necessarily die.
It might also
cause the threads of affection binding you two
to quietly dissipate.
Are you saying
he will completely forget me?
All your memories of him over a century will be erased,
and they can never be restored.
Shen Que,
you've forgotten a lot.
I'll help you remember.
You evil spirit,
unable to win in a fair fight,
you resort to sweet talk.
You dare to deceive me?
Do you really want to kill me?
I'm the Virtuous Prince, Shen Que.
It's my duty to slay evil.
Even if I have to die,
I'll kill you here today.
How about
I help you?
Your Highness,
you want my life,
and I've given it to you.
Even if you fight with your life,
you can't kill me.
Why doesn't the Soul-Devouring Bone Sword work on you?
What kind of evil spirit are you?
Have you ever seen me do evil
or kill the innocent?
I ask myself,
I've done nothing wrong.
I never meant to hurt you.
As for you,
the demon hunters from Qingdu Temple want to kill you.
You'd better stay in the Demon Village.
If you don't hurt those lesser demons,
they won't bother you.
Master,
we suffered heavy casualties
in the attack on the Demon Village.
Useless fools.
They're dead.
They don't matter.
Master.
Your incompetence
made me feel happy for nothing.
I'm stupid.
I don't understand what you mean.
Meng Li has become a demon.
The Demon Clan is getting rampant.
The mortal world will become a hell.
Master.
But the Demon Clan didn't kill innocent people.
If we destroy their village
to destroy the Demon Village
because of Meng Li.
Please think twice
and don't make a wrong decision.
The most urgent task now
is not to destroy the Demon Village.
My Soul Entity is getting weaker.
I must find a new body as soon as possible.
I shouldn't have been soft that day
and let you spare his life.
It's not his fault.
He wanted to kill you.
yet you still defend him.
Now he only remembers
he's the Virtuous Prince with the Demon
Capture Order, determined to slay demons.
What's wrong with that?
Do you realize
without his memory,
he's no longer the Shen Daozhi who loves you?
I understand the situation.
Any discomfort after becoming a demon?
Feelings of losing control?
I'm always worried the demonic power will backfire on you.
The demonic nature is under control.
My mind is clearer
than before.
I used to need the dreamer to be asleep.
Now I can enter dreams
whenever and wherever.
But
some abilities remain dormant.
What abilities?
I haven't fully grasped them yet.
No rush.
Rest assured.
Fine.
Shen Que can stay in the Demon Village.
I'll keep an eye on him.
He won't get hurt,
and he won't hurt you or your kind.
The kids are off to eat.
Okay.
Your Highness.
It's me.
Where are you?
I'm trapped in the Demon Village
by Meng Li.
Demon girl?
That dream-eating enchantress
is the last demon in the rumors?
Does Qingdu Temple know about this?
Do you remember
the past?
What past?
Nothing.
I'll tell Master
about Meng Li becoming a demon.
But he's weak from injuries
and can't fight her.
I just heard
her demonic nature is not mature yet.
Now is the best time to kill her.
But
there is a barrier in the Demon Village.
I'm afraid we need to find a way to open it.
Where there is a barrier,
there must be a guardian artifact.
Your Highness should pay attention to the holy object in the Demon Village.
This object cannot leave the Demon Village.
In a hidden place, there will be a lion-like Suanni pattern.
Find the guardian artifact,
you'll find the way to break it.
Got it.
I see you left food for me.
But I'm not used to eating alone.
Can we
share?
I apologize for
my earlier rudeness.
It's because
I can't remember the past,
so I'm a bit scared.
I hope
please forgive me.
You know I'm a demon hunter,
yet you didn't guard against me,
even healed my wounds.
Do we
have a shared past?
We indeed
have a deep history,
but there's no rush.
We have all the time in the world.
Very well.
Then I'll join you
to retrieve our memories.
Are you looking for something?
Don't get me wrong.
I'm just curious about the items
of the Demon Clan.
Shen Que,
do you know that outside the village,
the demon hunters from Qingdu Temple are after you?
You must stay in the village,
or I won't be able to protect you.
[After me?]
[Is it because of her?]
Fine,
I'll do as you say.
[You're so good to me.]
[Could we have been...]
[a couple?]
[These eyes...]
[I feel like I've seen them before...]
[That's impossible.]
Are you done staring?
You don't use a sword,
so why do you have this?
Your Highness,
aren't you overstepping?
A'Li!
A'Li, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Then why the big noise?
Your Highness,
if you have no other tricks,
please leave.
[This cannot leave the Demon Village.]
[Look for a lion-like Suanni pattern.]
[Find the guardian artifact,]
[you'll find the way to break it.]
Your Highness,
we've got news from the Demon Village.
We've found the guardian.
Today,
we'll avenge our fallen brothers
and destroy the village.
The demons are cunning.
Don't act rashly.
When the barrier is down,
we'll charge in
and avenge our fallen brothers.
All disciples, on my mark!
March!
Yes, sir!
I sense killing intent!
This is bad!
Your demon power is weak.
Why bother resisting?
You won't be coming back from this!