I think we can use it together.
Okay.
Please, leave.
You shouldn't be here.
Mister and Sungyeol are waiting for you.
Can't you also wait for me?
You worry about Sungyeol, don't you?
Woohyun and Sungyeol too... I wish we could all live together.
But it's like strangers becoming a family.
Woohyun and Sungyeol always being on each other's sides,
I wish we could live like that.
Could we?
Eventually.
My goodness. It's just us two again.
Whatever it is you want to do... don't try to get it if it breaks you.
I've come too far to stop.
So, just give up.
Just forget that I am your child.
Do you think a person can forget his own child?
Since the teacher helped us, shouldn't we do the same?
The person who has more should be the one looking over the one with less though.
But it's all because of us... She probably doesn't have a house or money.
If you give her a place to sleep...
Our house isn't somewhere anyone can sleep in.
But the ethics teacher isn't "anyone," she's your mom.
She's not my mom.
Do you know that you two are bad? If you both say that she's not your mom,
have you thought about how she might feel?
And if I acknowledge that she's my mom, what about Sungyeol?
If it's because of Sungyeol...
Sungyeol needs her. Someone he can call mom.
You need her, too! Can't you both call her mom?
At the restaurant you call people mom all the time, but why can't you now?
Humans are really weird!
Then, are all South Korean women my mom?
Everything can disappear in front of your eyes, is it satisfying?
It's not Seulbi.
Seulbi... What's her secret?
It's none of your business.
If I say something about Seulbi, will something even happen?
What are you guys talking about, making it seem so serious?
Don't do something you're going to regret.
It'd be best if you didn't provoke me.
Quiet!
Let's see here.
My good kids... You've grown a lot.
Where'd you go after you left us?
Do you know how much the substitute bothered us?
Okay...
I'm sorry. You guys are going to forgive me, right?
For free??!
You should buy us pizza, Teacher.
Ooooh! Chicken, chicken, too!!
Chicken! Chicken! Chicken!!!!
Chicken!
Okay, okay, okay!
I'll do this to make you guys happy,
but... you have to do well on this test. Okay?
Yes!
Here.
The money from the part-time job that you didn't get. 31,500 won. (about $30).
This... How did you...?
The owner seemed pretty sorry.
Thank you.
I thought of you sometimes.
Well, I thought of you every day.
- Let's treat each other well.
- Why are they like that??
The Ethics teacher must be frustrated, too.
Everyone sit down.
I can't see the questions.
What is this?
Wait! I can see it again!
The tests...
They've disappeared?
This time it's the whole test?
That's actually better.
Lee Seulbi, isn't it because of you?
Why is it Seulbi's fault that they disappeared?
You have supernatural powers though. Why don't you go find them?
What nonsense you're speaking.
Teacher, I found them.
What is this?
What?
Isn't it strange?
I think I saw Seulbi's wrist sparkle.
Hey! I was using a mirror to joke around~
Hey, no wonder.
I was just joking.
Hey, but you know Taeho got hurt and he can't open his eye.
I'll head over to eat lunch with Yena first.
Hey, Kisoo. Are you hungry?
Hey! I'm sensitive there.
Stop it!
Here, here, here.
It's fun, right? You must feel so smug.
If I'm not here, you would be eating alone. Let's eat together.
Stop acting nice. And you!
Something weird was sparkling.
Your nails are nice. Did you do them?
No, my mom. After doing these, she was so proud.
You're close with your mom.
You can't get close with a nagging queen.
But wait, why are you changing the topic? You're making me confused.
What's that on your wrist again?
Hey, girls, I want to join you for lunch.
Welcome.
Cutie, hi!
What's with you?
I need to find something out.
Hey, a hole's going to form from your staring. Stop it.
Seulbi, let's go get something to drink.
Geez, really now.
Mom, these guys are making me cry!
- Now, it's just us two.
- Hey, won't you let go?
I just need to check them out.
Let go of me!
I definitely saw it earlier.
It sparkled!
Hey, I have something to tell you.
Huh? In a bit, I'm almost done.
I like you, too!
Say that again.
Then, from today, it's day one as a couple!
What's going on?
A friend was saying that while her mom was painting her nails, she would listen to her nag
and chat with each other and get closer.
You want to get closer to me?
Why?
Because you are Woohyun's and Sungyeol's mom.
I'm not a person who has the right to be called mom.
Mom. Dad. They say you don't need a right to become those two.
You only need love.
You love both Woohyun and Sungyeol.
What is this?
I'll go find Woohyun.
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't erase it!
Hey, Lee Seulbi!
Hey, come here right now!
That little!
Seulbi has the ability to make people happy.
That is why Sungyeol must like Seulbi.
Don't be sorry.
At some point, Sungyeol will understand your feelings.
By telling all the students, does this mean that something more dangerous can happen in the future?
I'll clean it for you.
Hey, hurry up!
Try saying "Please clean it for me."
Will that be okay?
I will clean it for you~
I don't think you can act cute anywhere.
Why? Why won't it work?
Why? Why? Why? Why?
♫  It was the beginning of fall  ♫
♫  when it was cold but not really cold  ♫
♫  You seemed like you’d be cold  ♫
It would be great if this would get cleaned off.
What's wrong?
You're going to be okay. Don't worry too much.
♫  and today the sunshine is warm  ♫
♫   Spring has come and you’re in front of me  ♫
The answer key is gone?
Does that even make sense?
When you left school, did you not lock the cabinet?
That's right.
Oh, Jesus. One minute, I'll take out all of the CCTVs...
No. Did you notice any suspicious activity while the students were taking the test?
There is, isn't there? Who is it?
One moment, I need to find something.
Hey, I mean who is it?
What did she see?
Hey, was it you?
There was definitely something strange going on with you during the test.
You took the answer key, didn't you?
Is that true?
- Wow.
-  You really have no morals, do you?
Hey!
Are you guys writing a fantasy novel?
Do you have evidence that Seulbi did it?
- Hey, hand it over! Where is it?
- Give it to us!
- Where did you hide it?
- Hand it over!
Yesterday, I definitely saw the Ethics teacher take the answer key with her.
If you're going to complain, go and complain to the Ethics teacher.
The Ethics teacher is your mom, go ask her.
Or would she answer more kindly when her biological son asks her,
where the answer key is?
For you, it would be okay... since you're in last place anyway.
Wouldn't it be better for you to tell your parents that the answer key was stolen rather than that you got last place?
Don't go anywhere and stay here.
Thank you.
No need to say thank you, I was not helping you anyhow.
Even though, thank you.
From now on, don't say the words "Thank you" and "Sorry" to me.
Where would I find the answer key?
Now all the kids are siding with me. Don't you think someone's helping me?
That someone must have the same heart as you.
Is that so?
Then that person will take Seulbi away, too.
Give up Seulbi. It's the only way for all three of us to be under the same sky.
That punk!
What a relief.
How did you think of this?
Writing board.
You can't always say what's in your heart, so you can write it here.
"Let me become first place."
"Let me not go to after-school tutoring."
"Please let Yoomin like Seunghun ♥"
Hey, this is your handwriting!
They aren't marks, they're all wishes.
Yep, it's a wish marking board. Why don't you write one down, too?
Let all the wishes come true, bippity- boppity- boo!
Bippity- boppity- boo!
Lower lower. A little lower.
Hey! What are you doing?
We hadn't had a photozone in a long time.
Yoohwan's idea is the best!
But why, out of the blue, this?
We'll start with Seulbi.
Who came up with the idea that angels have wings?
They always do in children's books and comics.
And they need wings to fly around.
But they'd probably be able to fly around without wings.
The angel's life is the wings. And so that's what makes an angel an angel.
Angel? What angel— Let's just put wings on your mouth, huh?
It's your mouth that's a problem.
It's Kisoo and Yoohwan's masterpiece. A photozone. It's pretty, right?
Thanks for earlier and the other day.
My other half! I'll help you with your part-time job!
Sorry, now it'll be uncomfortable.
What should we do first?
Seulbi?
What's that?
Why don't you just go and study?
Baby! Honey!
Why is she giving me the cold shoulder? Did I do something wrong?
I think there are also humans who don't express their thankful or loving heart.
The moment I tell about Seulbi, you and Seulbi will be forever—
I can't rest and take an eye off Sungyeol for fear of what he might do.
The only person I can ask the favor of is you, although I'm sorry.
What's the weird stuff that's been happening yesterday and today?
You know something, don't you?
Have you found the tests?
Not yet.
The students' lives are on the line with this issue.
It's sad to hear that their lives depend on one answer key book.
Would that be the only solution?
Is there a solution to life?
If there's something going on, tell me.
That way we can find a solution.
I have a favor to ask.
Just what are you going to do?
I can't just leave Woohyun like that,
and I can't leave him to live with Seulbi alone either.
What about Sungyeol? You don't worry about him?
Woohyun and Sungyeol are both my kids.
Until they accept me, I'll just have to wait.
I have a favor to ask you.
Seulbi...
Seulbi... I'm trusting you to watch her well.
You don't need to tell me what to do.
If she disappears, you can't see her again.
It'll be fair to both of us.
This is better than her disappearing forever.
Do you trust me?
Yeah.
Why?
Because you like Seulbi, too.
Because you still want to see her.
No matter what happens, don't send her to me.
I'm begging you.
♫  It was the beginning of fall  ♫
♫  when it was cold but not really cold  ♫
♫  You seemed like you’d be cold but
you were wearing short clothes  ♫
♫  The season passed  ♫
♫  and today the sunshine is warm  ♫
Let's go.
♫  Spring has come and you’re in front of me  ♫
♫  You’re looking at me, and you’re smiling  ♫
♫  I can’t breathe  ♫
Whatever I say, even though it might sound like lies, I'm telling the truth.
Believe me.
I'll always believe you. We promised, remember?
I don't think I can go on like this. Because of you, everything is so difficult.
Leave.
I said everything's annoying.
You know I hate annoying things the most, right?
You said you only feel safe when I'm next to you.
I feel like there'll only be more days like today.
And everyone started to suspect you.
Getting into danger because of you is becoming annoying.
So leave.
I'll believe your lies.
Where do I need to go?
♫  You’re looking at me, and you’re smiling  ♫
♫  I can’t breathe  ♫
♫  Just one look from you is so overwhelming for me  ♫
♫  So I’m looking at you like this  ♫
♫  I’m waiting for you  ♫
Why are you crying?
If you're going to be like that.
It's weird. I don't want to cry but I keep sweating from my eyes.
Never cry in front of me again.
♫  Each body movement from you is so overwhelming for me  ♫
♫  So I’m looking at you like this  ♫
Don't forgive me.
How am I going to live when only a day barely passed?
Okay! I leveled up!
Hey, Kisoo! Want to go get food with me?
Eat breakfast, or else your head will go bad.
You eat breakfast every day, but why is your head so bad?
Hey, you! My head's good, all right?
I'm just saving it to use for the future.
Right, Seulbi?
What? Oh, yeah.
Okay! Now, next!
Woohyun came in!
That's right! Yes, okay!
Oh yesss! Another win!
Hey, why am I so good at this?
Hey, do it again! Reset!
Okay, bet on it.
Okay, call!
Hey, look!
All right! Another win!
Are you okay?
What?
Even if you're smiling on the outside, you seem to be crying on the inside.
I never knew I had so many faces.
Is there a problem with Seulbi?
There's nothing for you to know.
I'm good at catching things. If you need help, you can use me.
I don't need your help.
If you fix your problem, tell me!
I feel sorry for you, so I can do anything for you.
Nothing was caught on CCTV and
if we can't find the answer key, what will we do with the students' lessons?
This is horrible for their college resumes.
This really is a big deal.
Ugh! Just where did it go?
We'll have to look for it! For our students!
Senior!
Because of you and me, the students' lives are getting destroyed.
That won't happen.
Because I'll do anything. Because we're friends.
Senior, you don't have friends. Right?
I have a lot. So try all you want.
If I can just put you back in your place, I'm going to do anything.
Why are you letting Seulbi stay at Sungyeol's place?
Because I'm a scaredy-cat.
Because I'm cowardly.
It's because of Sungyeol, right?
Aren't you going to deliver?
Hey! What exactly are you thinking?
A bad thing is happening, a bad thing.
I know, right...
What am I thinking?
Seulbi, I'm now going home. Don't stay outside mad and come inside.
Is that Seulbi?
Why are you making their lives worse?
Me?
They aren't going to break up just because you stand between them.
Weren't you Woohyun's friend?
You just stay as Woohyun's friend.
Hey! That kid!
Why? What?
I'm not talking to you, all right.
I recently just changed my position, you know.
Let's go.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey.
What's up with you guys?
What do you mean? We're here to catch the cowardly mouse.
They say when the mouse is pushed to a corner, it'll bite the cat.
I wonder about this handsome looking mouse right here.
Don't come closer.
Go away.
Hey, why cry out? We're not going to hit you.
Because of you, I think I lived my life so badly,
that I'm turning a new leaf.
Here, get up.
Thanks.
I'm saying this while thinking of the past,
but in the future, don't appear in front of me.
Didn't I tell you that I'll kill you if you appeared in this neighborhood?
Hey, what's wrong with your face?
Was it Jaeseok?
These days he's like a toothless tiger.
But you who're still getting hit is...
I was just protecting a friendship.
Why don't you just protect your body?
You look terrible.
Thanks!
Perhaps... is the content in the book all true?
It's right, right?
You'll keep the secret, right?
It won't do anything just because I keep the secret.
I'm scared.
That she'll disappear like that.
That I'll have to live without seeing her.
Let's look for a solution.
If this book is really right, there should be other books that tell of a solution.
I'll look for it, too.
Thanks.
I'll go now.
If you're going to be this hurt,
can you tell me about Seulbi?
About there being something weird about her on test day.
About Seulbi saying she wanted to be a human.
That the answer key disappeared... all of it. It's because I think they might all have something to do with Seulbi.
I wish you wouldn't ask.
I have to protect her, you know.
Seulbi will be looking for the answer key alone.
I don't know if she'll be able to find it though...
♫  That’s not how I feel but I made you sad again  ♫
That’s not how I feel, I’ve never hated you  ♫
Seulbi's at school right now. Don't leave her alone.
♫  Thank you  ♫
♫  So many things happened so far  ♫
♫  There were times when things were hard and tiring  ♫
♫  Love is still so hard for us  ♫
Do you think you'll be able to block us just because you do this?
You can't ever take Seulbi away.
When I count to 3, run to the school; I'll run in the opposite direction.
One, two, three!
I'm leaving her in your care.
Just why are you doing this to this extent?
It's going to go into their resumes, so it's important for our country's students.
Don't you feel injustice after the kids hurt you that way?
I don't like that they're getting in trouble because of me.
If it weren't for me, this situation wouldn't have occurred in the first place.
I'll finish up and leave, so you head out...
Thank you.
What about Seulbi?
No need to concern yourself.
Oh, you scared me!
What are you doing there?
What about Seulbi? Is she sleeping?
I'm scared.
What's wrong?
I feel like I'm turning into a monster.
Please hold onto me.
That's right, Dad will hold on to you.
How do you have this...?
It's not possible that you did it?
I found it. I tried to tape it together.
What is the secret that you all are hiding? And what are you exactly?
Why did Woohyun send you to Sungyeol?
Don't try to know anything.
Everyone! The answer key was found!
What? Really?
♫  It was the beginning of fall  ♫
♫   When it was cold but not really cold  ♫
♫  You seemed like you’d be cold  ♫
♫  But you were wearing short clothes  ♫
♫  The season passed  ♫
♫  And today the sunshine is warm  ♫
♫  Spring has come  ♫
♫  And you’re in front of me  ♫
I'm eating well, and sleeping well.
It would be good if you can do the same.
♫  Just one look from you is so overwhelming for me  ♫
♫  So I’m looking at you like this  ♫
Is it okay to leave Woohyun like that?
Outside he laughs like a maniac, and when he comes into the shop he gets depressed...
He doesn't eat or sleep. He's killing me.
Taeho? Taeho? Did someone call me?
But Seulbi...
Yes, Sir.
Hey! If you're going to talk about another girl, just go to your after-school tutoring.
No, no, no.
It's over, right?
There are five minutes left.
Hey! Just go. You're making it chaotic.
Let's go.
I'm leaving first.
Yes.
All right, let's try it one more time.
Teacher will probably find out very soon also, right? Continuing to lie is hard.
Sometimes there are times when you need to lie to protect the other person.
For that person...
They are the words I always say to you... the words I'll have to continue to say to you...
I'll come back.
Seulbi!
Woohyun is really sick, come quickly.
I'll just see him for a minute, Woohyun is sick.
If you see him for a bit, you'll want to see him more; and then tomorrow you will want to see him more, and more after that.
And during those times you won't think of me once.
It's really just for a bit, he's sick!
I'll go.
Seulbi, are you okay?
Seulbi.
Come back to your senses.
Seulbi, you okay?
They say feeling the other's pain is love, but these two get sick at the same time.
Hurry and get better, Seulbi.
When someone is sick and tired, there's someone who gains strength.
- Hey, let's go quickly.
- There's nothing I can do.
Don't turn around. I'm not there.
They say she's an alien.
Is Seulbi really a ghost?
No matter what circumstance, we're always together!
- Seulbi!
- Seulbi disappeared.
I'm going to reveal everything.
Sungyeol!