[Love of the Divine Tree]
[Episode 33]
This is for you, Master.
Look at this little angry doll.
Doesn't it look
exactly like you?
Next time you feel like getting mad,
just squeeze it hard.
Childish.
Who would want something like this?
Xue Ranran,
you'd better make me fall for you soon,
or your Golden Core will be in danger.
Just like the fierce beast recorded
in "The Collection of Entertainment."
Master, wait for me!
Hurry up.
Guardian.
Ranran, you're back too.
From now on, the daily meals at Mount Wester
will be handled by Xue Ranran.
That's wonderful!
Guardian, I knew
you care for Ranran the most.
Guardian,
those new disciples
you asked us to recruit
have completed their aptitude tests.
New disciples?
Master,
since you're willing to take on disciples now,
why not call back Xi'er
and the others?
They've been waiting at the foot of the mountain
for your instructions.
They're so foolish.
What use do I have for them?
I only want disciples
with exceptional talents and Spiritual Roots.
Well,
with more disciples at Mount Wester,
there will surely be
more trivial matters to handle.
Mount Wester is so vast.
Mr. Yu Chen and Ms. Yu Tong
can't handle everything on their own.
Xi'er and the others know Mount Wester well.
They can be of great help.
If you don't say anything,
I'll take it as a yes.
Thank you, Master!
Who are you?
How dare you trespass into Celestial Sect!
So you're the immortal masters
from Eternal Sect and Hollow Sect.
What brings you to Mount Scarlet
at this late hour?
Where's Wei Jiu?
Get him out!
His Lordship is in seclusion.
If you have anything to say,
you can say it to me.
Many demonic beasts
have been devilized lately.
Is that the doing of you demons?
Devilized demonic beasts?
We don't have time to waste
on something so pointless.
Now that Celestial Sect has been rebuilt,
demons have an endless source of power,
and many lost demonic techniques have resurfaced.
Why would we devilize
demonic beasts?
I don't care how the so-called righteous sects
view us,
but demonic cultivators
and the Heavenly Ones
have just chosen
different cultivation methods.
We exist in the same world.
What reason do demons have
to cause chaos or destroy it?
Fine.
I'll believe you for now.
However, this wave of devilization
is no small matter.
You demons
have always known more
about devilized things.
If you truly have nothing to do with
the devilization,
do you have any way
to help us investigate?
Alright.
I'll send word
for all our demons
to stay vigilant against the devilization.
If we uncover anything,
you'll be informed immediately.
Then consider this a temporary alliance
between us.
Greetings, My Lord.
My Lord.
Elder Tu,
how dare you make an agreement
with the Heavenly Ones
while I was in seclusion?
Since when do I
need to answer to those Heavenly Ones?
This is outrageous!
My apologies.
I overstepped
and acted on my own.
I'm willing to accept punishment.
Expel me from Celestial Sect.
You only need
to announce to the Heavenly Sects
that Celestial Sect has no one named Tu Jiuyuan,
and the agreement I made
will naturally be void.
You...
Everyone, leave us.
Yes!
Tu Jiuyuan,
what's wrong with you?
I merely scolded you a bit,
and you want to leave?
Actually…
Actually, it's not that serious.
I am
a magnanimous person.
Considering
your years of loyalty,
I'll let this slide.
You should be thanking me now.
I once promised the former sovereign
to assist you.
Now that you've rebuilt Celestial Sect
and got what you wanted,
my promise has been fulfilled.
I just want freedom now.
I want to leave this place that has caged me for half my life
and live freely as I please.
Stop!
Why hasn't
your wound healed?
It's just a minor injury.
Don't worry about it.
Your wound hasn't even healed.
Why are you in such a hurry to leave?
You...
Don't tell me
you're leaving because you loved me
but couldn't have me
and your love has turned into hate.
Actually,
that day in the netherworld…
If I told her
that I went back to find her,
I'd be so embarrassed.
Never mind.
You...
Look at you, so badly injured.
After all these years,
you're still so weak.
I…
I'll allow you
to cultivate with me
and share my spiritual power.
Happy now?
My Lord, you misunderstand.
I've long let go of love,
and there's no hate to hold onto either.
I just want to live
a different life.
My Lord,
take care of yourself.
Stop!
Who said
your promise to that old man
has been fulfilled?
My true goal
is to bring back the golden age of demonic cultivation.
Rebuilding Celestial Sect
was only the beginning.
If you want to leave,
you have to help me
break the Five Deadly Formations
at the peak of Mount Scarlet
so I can
reach its dark side
and obtain the legendary Gold Refining Fire.
Gold Refining Fire?
Yes.
Demonic creatures all fear it.
If I can get it,
I'll be able to control
and command those devilized beasts,
bending them
to my will.
By then,
all Heavenly Sects
will have to kneel before me,
and Celestial Sect
will rise above them all.
Only then
will your promise
be truly fulfilled.
Then I'll let you go.
But
if you fail to break the Five Deadly Formations
and get the Gold Refining Fire,
you'll have to stay here.
Ranran.
Ms. Yu Tong.
How are Xi'er and the others
settling in?
Earlier, they went
to pay their respects to Master.
But Master found it troublesome
and just responded from inside the room
without letting them in.
They're now
tidying up their rooms.
Good.
[Su Yishui's disciple, Shen Kuo]
[Su Yishui's disciple, Yue Sheng]
That's Xue Ranran.
She came first in the Marrow-Cleansing Pool
and gained its spiritual power.
Today, I'll cook
a good meal for everyone
to celebrate.
I'll be going now.
Usually, by this time,
she has already brought me tea and snacks.
What's going on today?
Xue Ranran.
Xue Ranran!
Still nowhere to be seen.
How could any girl
be as irresistible as she is?
One step forward, two steps back,
never truly making progress!
Hello, Ms. Xue.
I'm a new disciple, Yue Sheng.
I look forward to learning from you.
Yue Sheng, nice to meet you.
I can wash the vegetables
for you, Ms. Xue.
No need for that.
It's fine. I enjoy washing vegetables.
Ms. Xue,
just leave this kind of work to him.
Alright.
Thank you.
Okay.
Ms. Xue,
let me help with something else.
No need.
Ms. Xue,
my name is Shen Kuo.
From now on, I'll handle
all the cutting.
Thank you then.
It's nothing.
Ms. Xue, let me help you.
You're quite skilled, aren't you?
I learned this
somewhere else
before coming here.
Honestly, I joined Wester Sect
because I admire you, Ms. Xue.
Ignore him, Ms. Xue.
The vegetables are washed.
I heard your alchemy skills are incredible.
Could I learn from you sometime?
Sure.
I'll teach you another day.
It's a deal!
I want to learn too.
Ms. Xue.
You can't learn!
Master.
-Master.
So lively here, huh?
Since you have so much free time
to chat and joke around,
then go to Westerly Valley
and hold a handstand for 20 hours!
Yes.
Yes, Master.
Wait.
From now on, none of you are allowed
to go near the kitchen again.
-Yes.
Master.
I brought you lunch.
Master?
Master.
After teaching your junior brothers alchemy
and having fun with them,
you finally remembered your master?
Master,
you're not jealous, are you?
Jealous?
I'm only cooperating with you
to break the Soul-Cleansing Charm.
Why would I be jealous?
Then what is this about?
I just didn't expect
Mu Qingge's foolish younger sister
to be just like her,
flirting with everyone
and being so fickle.
I'm foolish?
And I, Mu Qingge, am fickle?
You insulted me twice
in just one sentence.
Yeah,
you're right.
I do like
handsome, debonair men.
However,
I already
have someone I love.
And I love him wholeheartedly
because no one is more handsome
or more worthy of love than him.
Xue Ranran,
don't just talk the talk.
With your little tricks,
how long will you need to pursue me?
When will you finally break the spell?
Since you put it that way,
I guess I'll have to
take it a step further.
Do you think I'll be afraid?
♫After parting, the black silk-like hair turned snow-white♫
♫In secret, I have so much to say to you♫
♫Only after I met you♫
You just asked
if I was jealous.
♫Did I realize there are heaven-like places all because of you♫
I thought I needed to test that.
So what's your conclusion?
♫Maybe a lifetime is too short, too fleeting♫
♫So we were granted a second chance♫
♫With endless time to write our story♫
♫We fulfill the vow forged through many lifetimes♫
♫From now onwards♫
Wait.
Why are you not shy at all
after kissing me?
Have you kissed someone
like this before?
Yeah,
I once kissed a pig.
A pig indeed.
This is outrageous!
I haven't gotten mad yet,
and she's acting all hurt!
Good thing I brought her back.
If I had left her out there,
she'd end up breaking the hearts
of many naive young men!
Kissed a pig...
Hold on.
A pig?
Could it be...
Elder Tu,
you've tried a lot of times.
You need to stop.
Elder Tu.
Greetings, My Lord.
You underestimate the Five Deadly Formations.
With your weak cultivation,
you can't even break through
the outermost barrier,
let alone get in to break them.
Stop wasting your energy.
Go back.
I can't break them now,
but since I made a promise to you,
I'll find a way to break them.
When I do,
I hope you can keep your word.
Fortunately, Tu Jiuyuan
can't get past the barrier.
If she actually managed to enter the formations,
it would be extremely dangerous.
I've tried so many times
but still can't break the formations inside.
I really need to think of
another way.
He kissed me first,
yet he's making me copy the disciples' rules.
He's just being stubborn.
Again?
The cultivation method Uncle Ye Xin taught me
is already showing results.
Let me see
if I can use this formation
to activate the Soul-Devouring Lock again
and take back Xue Ranran's
spiritual power.
Drawing power from me when I have none left?
This could kill me!
I need stronger people!
Yes.
Fortunately, I took the Spirit-Nourishing Pill in advance.
Ranran.
What's wrong?
Why do you look so pale?
Did Guardian…
That's from Master?
He ordered these dishes?
He said
you have to make and bring them to him yourself
to show you really regret your mistake.
Being stubborn again.
If he wants to see me,
why can't he come himself?
Ms. Yu Tong,
please tell him
my hands are sore
from copying the rules and I can't cook.
He'll have to make do with what's available.
As for me,
I regret nothing,
so I won't go and annoy him.
Exactly. Don't always indulge him.
Oh, Ms. Yu Tong,
there's something
I'd like Mr. Yu Chen
to investigate in the capital for me.
Guardian has already sent
Yu Chen to the capital.
I don't know
if it's for the same thing
you want to look into.
Master is also looking for Ye Xin.
Since that's the case,
if Mr. Yu Chen finds anything,
please let me know as well.
She said that?
Ranran looked very pale.
She didn't even eat dinner.
She rushed back with you
without proper rest.
Before that,
she had been physically and mentally drained.
No matter how good others are,
they can't compare to you.
You're elegant and otherworldly,
like fine jade.
Just like these Ice Lotuses.
They may seem cold at first glance,
but upon closer inspection,
they're refreshing to the heart and mind.
They actually make one feel warm and close.
Master,
it's you.
Who else did you think it would be?
This spirit pool
is on my way
from the study to my residence.
Are you perhaps
deliberately staying here
to awake my memories?
Your flirting tricks
seem a bit dull.
What are you expecting?
I just missed you.
Besides, have you forgotten?
Back then,
you taught me cultivation techniques here
in this spirit pool.
I was just using
the technique you taught me to replenish my energy.
Why is your pulse so unstable?
Did your energy go off track during cultivation?
You've been suffering
from the Soul-Devouring Lock all this time.
Why didn't you tell me?
Are you worried about me?
I'm just
worried about my Golden Core
and want to regain my memories as soon as possible.
Since your usual flirting tricks
aren't working,
perhaps you could try
going a bit deeper.
How
do I do that?
I mean,
you could try being a little more affectionate
or lean on me more.
What were you thinking?
You used to do the same,
telling me to ask you for help more.
Immortal Master Xue,
you're here.
I've prepared breakfast for you.
Here.
Why is there
a special serving for me?
Guardian ordered it.
He said he'll be in seclusion
for the next few days,
so you don't need to prepare meals for him.
Seclusion?
But he...
It's not true.
That's just an excuse.
Guardian may not say it outright,
but I can tell
he's just worried you'll overwork yourself.
He even placed a barrier
around the spirit pool.
Except for you,
no one can approach it.
He wants you to go there
every day at noon to replenish your energy.
Junior Brother,
mind moving over a bit
so we can sit and eat?
There's no space left.
Why squeeze in?
Go eat somewhere else.
Junior Brother,
this table
was ours to begin with.
Is your name
carved on the table?
Did any of you see a name here?
Nope.
Me neither.
However, Senior Sister,
if you want to squeeze in,
we wouldn't mind.
Forget it. Ignore him!
How dare you hit me?
Show some respect.
-Let go of me!
-Let go!
Let go!
Let go of me.
Break the spell, you little brat.
Who are you calling a brat?
In Mount Wester,
you're not qualified to call anyone a brat.
You...
Wester Sect's rules have never allowed
junior disciples
to bully their seniors
just because they're more powerful.
A bit of pushing and shoving is one thing,
but using spiritual power to attack someone is another.
Did you intend to kill Senior Bai?
If you continue like this,
when you grow stronger,
won't you end up disrespecting your master?
If I've done wrong,
Master will discipline me.
Who are you to lecture me?
Break the spell!
I'm just someone stronger than you.
You got that line from her, didn't you?
What?
Not convinced?
But it's true that I'm stronger than you.
Master.
What line?
What do you mean?
You made a racket in the dining room.
No one is allowed to eat.
Carry 100 loads of water up the mountain before you can rest.
Yes, Master.
Wait.
Did you guys
not hear what I just said?
Master, you're punishing everyone
without even asking what happened.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Neither did my seniors.
Why should we be punished?
You did nothing wrong?
Then whose fault is it?
Discord among disciples,
disrespect toward seniors,
and fighting within the sect.
Clearly, it's your fault as our master.
Say that again!
Master, fate led you to take them
as your disciples back then.
You once taught them with dedication,
tailoring your guidance to their talents.
Even if you've forgotten the past,
they are still your disciples.
Did I not let them
stay in Mount Wester?
Xue Ranran,
don't think
just because I allow you
to help me recover my memories,
you can be disrespectful to me.
You see it as a mere task,
but I'm speaking from the heart.
You treat them as strangers,
but they're the very disciples
you once personally chose.
Your disregard for them
allowed the new disciples
to treat them
with such disrespect.
You forgot how they once
respected you
and remained loyal to the sect.
You forgot
how they risked their lives with you,
fighting demons without ever backing down.
Even when
the Heavenly Ones turned against you,
they never walked out on you.
Those things you've forgotten
truly happened.
This bond we shared
cannot be erased!
It was me
who made a fuss
and talked back to you today.
I'll take the punishment alone.
I'll carry
all 400 loads of water myself.
Oh, no.
I didn't bring the Spirit-Nourishing Pill.
-Ranran!
The Soul-Devouring Lock.
Master.
Last time, you used a spirit talisman
to draw power from me.
But what happened this time?
Even if you have my Golden Core,
without me activating my power,
there's no way you can continuously
draw power from me.
It worked.
I can draw power from you now.
In that case,
from now on, wherever we go,
you need to stay close to me.
You can use my power whenever you need it.
In the past,
you often transferred spiritual power to me
when I was exhausted from cultivation
and when I was injured.
Later, you
directly connected your spiritual power with mine,
allowing me to draw your power at any time.
I wasn't drawing from you by force.
It's just a habit.
I must have lost my mind
to willingly offer you the spiritual power I got
through painstaking cultivation.
No wonder after 18 years of seclusion,
I barely made any progress.
What kind of spell
did you put on me?
Master, you taught me everything I know.
If I had put a spell on you,
you'd have noticed it.
You truly
loved and cared for me.
You were genuinely nice to me.
Sorry, Master.
I shouldn't have talked back to you in front of everyone.
I should have spoken to you properly.
In fact, you haven't changed at all.
You're still soft-hearted.
You'd still help me out
when I was in danger.
How surprising.
You actually apologized.
You do know
how to be seductive.
The Soul-Devouring Lock is a real pain.
Before I figure out a way
to get rid of it completely,
come here every day at dusk.
I'll help you replenish your energy.
As for your punishment today...
I'll go carry the water right away.
Forget it.
If you exhaust yourself,
it'll be my power that's wasted.
That's no different from punishing myself.
Instead of wasting time on that,
you might as well spend some time reading ancient books
and find out
what Dun Tian intended to do
with that heaven-defying spell.
You're not punishing me anymore?
You're right.
Thank you for your concern and kindness.
You're the best, Master.
[Auspicious and peaceful]
Master is not good with words,
but he's kind-hearted.
He often gives pills to the people at the foot of the mountain.
Me?
Kind-hearted?
Master excels at everything,
except cooking.
But the mooncakes he baked for me
were the best.
I baked mooncakes for her? Shouldn't it have been
the other way around?
When Master gets shy,
he turns his face away and ignores me.
If I tease him with jokes,
he won't look amused,
but his eyes turn warmer than usual.
Nonsense.
Salted dried longans
still aren't to Master's liking,
but he doesn't dislike them either.
He once said,
"The past is the past.
It's nothing
more than memories."
He also said,
"Demonic magic is neither good nor evil.
A technique is just a technique.
Whether one is a demon or an immortal
is determined by the heart."
is determined by the heart.
Whether one is a demon or an immortal
Those things you've forgotten
truly happened.
In fact, you haven't changed at all.
The lost memories
might return soon.
Master.
I punished you all yesterday,
and you all think it was unfair.
Then today, you'll each pick someone
for a test.
I'll test your entry-level skill—
the Lightness Skill.
You need to stand on the grass
without using spiritual power.
Whoever loses
will have to copy the sect rules 100 times.
That's easy.
Master is clearly on our side.
Yue Sheng, you go.
Make them lose completely.
This is the Flame Lava
from Westerly Valley.
With your current abilities,
if you fall in, your body will instantly melt.
But don't worry.
Before your skin is all burned,
I'll fish you out.
You won't die.
Do you still have the guts to try?
I'm willing to try, Master.
I admit defeat.
I'm willing to accept punishment.
-Senior Gao!
-Gao Cang!
He's fine.
Why…
Why isn't the lava hot?
It's not touching me either.
I felt a familiar chill
just now.
Obviously, Master mixed
the extreme yin water from the spirit pool
with the lava in the cauldron.
The two neutralized each other, so it's not hot.
And you won't get any of it on you.
I knew Master wouldn't
be so cruel.
But Gao Cang didn't know.
He just followed Master's order
loyally.
Master,
you're testing
if what I said yesterday is true.
Some of you
have always doubted
whether Gao Cang
is worthy of being your senior brother.
He's so loyal to me.
That alone
surpasses any level of cultivation.
And there's your eldest senior brother,
Bai Baishan.
Tell us, why do you never
use your left hand,
even though it clearly works?
It's by Master's order.
You gave me a chance
to repent
and return to Mount Wester.
I must strictly follow your command
and never disobey you.
Compared to them,
you all still have a long way to go.
Master has even
looked into these matters.
He's willing
to try believing what I said after all.
Master,
I found a few ancient books
about heaven-defying techniques.
I also made
your favorite osmanthus cakes.
Master was reading "The Collection of Entertainment."
I wonder if he was mad
when he saw he was described
as a fierce beast.
[Roster of new recruited Westers]
The new disciples Master has taken in
are all the children of influential court officials
and regional commanders.
This can't be a coincidence.
[I'm Yue Zhiqiu. I hope this letter finds you well.]
[I once served under you and still owe you a debt of gratitude. Since you're planning something big, I'm ready to follow your orders at any time.]
[To Mr. Su]
Put it down.
These days,
you've been reassembling your old allies
and using discipleship to draw in
court officials and regional forces.
You're trying to finish what you couldn't
and wage war for the throne again?
So what if I am?
Have you considered the consequences?
Of course, I seek what I desire.
Xue Ranran,
don't think
you can meddle in this.
We've been to the border towns
and seen how people live there
after a war.
You said yourself
that peace is precious.
Right now, the Great Qi
faces threats from Gaokan at the borders,
while within, feudal lords and kings of foreign lineage
are assembling their own troops.
The imperial court is barely keeping the balance
to let the people live in peace.
Once the balance is broken,
different forces will get involved
in the fight for the throne.
Are you sure such a rushed uprising
can guarantee victory?
It'll only lead to endless wars
and a country torn apart.
Do you think I care about any of that?
You don't get to tell me what to do!
But Master, you once
risked your life for the peace of the world.
How could you not care?
Enough.
You think I'd believe I did those absurd things
just because you said so?
I, Su Yishui,
have only ever pursued absolute power over this universe.
But the truth is,
all these years,
you haven't tried to seize the throne.
You just sealed the Spirit Spring
in the netherworld.
I don't want you to let your youthful impulse
cloud your judgment and make a decision
you'll regret
because you forgot the path you once walked.
Guardian.
Guardian, bad news.
Ranran…
She's surrounded at the foot of the mountain.
What a troublemaker.
I want one too! I want one too!
There's enough for everyone.
I want Sovereign Su!
Alright.
Thank you, miss.
You're welcome.
Let's go and play!
Master.
You bribed Yu Tong
to trick me down the mountain
just to watch this nonsense?
Master, don't be angry.
It's all my fault.
It's just that today
is the Festival of Reverence
in the towns near Mount Wester.
So I wanted you
to see it.
What does that have to do with me?
Because this festival
is held in your honor, Master.
Me?
19 years ago,
war reached Mount Wester,
bringing plague and demons.
Before entering seclusion,
you treated the sick
and saved the people here.
Out of gratitude and respect,
they started
the annual Festival of Reverence.
Master, look.
To them,
the immortals up above are distant and untouchable.
The person in the mountain
who sees them through hardships
and keeps them safe
is the one they truly revere.
Immortal Master Su,
Miss Ranran.
Since you're here,
come in
for some wontons.
Alright, Mr. Xu.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Come.
Here, same as always.
The condiments are here.
Here, Mr. Xu.
You're always so polite.
Immortal Master Su saved my life.
How could I charge him?
Back then, Mr. Xu suffered greatly from the plague.
You saved him,
giving him a second chance at life.
That's why he's so grateful.
When Westers eat here,
he never charges them anything.
Is it delicious?
Master, you once promised
to travel and try everything delicious with me.
But if war breaks out,
none of this will exist anymore.
Immortal Master Su,
Grandmother asked me to thank you.
Thank you.