[Love of the Divine Tree]
[Episode 34]
So,
like this, right now,
Master, don't you like it?
Don't you want moments like this
to last forever?
Master.
Fine.
You're always so talkative.
I actually have grown attached
to this ephemeral joy
and useless happiness.
Over the years,
my state of mind
has actually changed so much.
Guardian,
Yu Chen sent a message.
Ye Xin has returned to the capital.
Stiffly Su,
didn't you say
once I finished crafting the magical weapon
to break the imperial palace's defense formation,
I could come and go freely
here at Mount Wester?
Listen,
if you hadn't secretly
brought Ranran back to Mount Wester again,
I wouldn't even bother with you.
Where's the thing you made?
Where's Ranran?
Did you bully her?
Actually, since coming back this time,
Guardian has been very caring
towards Ranran.
That's more like it.
He should be.
With this thing,
you can come and go freely in the imperial palace.
You brat,
you won't even say thank you now,
huh?
-I can't believe you.
-Mr. Zeng Yi.
Ranran.
Why are you here?
Yu Chen sent a message,
saying Ye Xin has entered the capital.
Guardian borrowed Mr. Zeng's magical weapon
and went to the capital.
If Master confronts him,
who knows what will happen?
Guards!
I want to see my father!
Prince Kang, Su Yan,
conspired with eunuchs and intended to rebel.
You're disloyal and unfilial!
Father is
extremely disappointed in you.
He doesn't want to see you.
Why would I harm my father?
It was you,
Su Yu.
It was you.
You framed me!
You've already
gained complete control over the court.
You deceived His Majesty.
You're the disloyal and unfilial one!
Stop!
Do you really think that without me,
you can gain complete control?
Do you think Father knows nothing
about the strange occurrences in the capital?
Su Yu!
You can never have peace!
[Convergence of Auspiciousness]
Who's there?
Your... Your Highness.
It's me.
It's late and cold.
I just wanted to ask you to go back to your room.
So what if it's you?
Those around you are all kinds
of men of sacrifice
and spies.
Who can you trust?
Wu Mi,
how long have you been by my side?
Your Highness,
I became your shadow guard
right after I finished my apprenticeship
in the ninth year of Zhengyong.
It has been ten years.
Ten years?
Nineteen years ago,
Feng came to serve by my side.
I thought he was loyal,
but I never truly knew his background.
Suddenly, he became
someone I didn't know!
So who are you?
What's your purpose of staying by my side?
I swear to God
I'm absolutely loyal to you!
From now on,
without my summoning,
you don't need to appear.
Yes, Your Highness.
Wait.
From now on,
you don't need to be around me
as my shadow guard
at all times.
Go out now
and take an official position as a palace guard.
Your Highness!
I'm concerned about your safety.
Do as I said!
Yes.
Who's there?
So, the capital
traps lonely souls like you.
You taste no flavor in food or drinks
and see enemies everywhere.
Su Yishui,
you actually have the guts to come here.
I go where I please.
I'm looking for Dun Tian.
Where is he?
You came to beg him to undo
the Soul-Cleansing Charm?
Or
you still can't accept
that you've long been
my defeated foe,
you failed to get what you want,
and you're left with nothing,
so you came to make a futile attempt?
You live
in constant fear and paranoia,
and your life is so dull.
There's nothing enviable about that.
The winner takes all, and the loser gets nothing.
I am the winner.
You've never even seen
the scenery here before.
I can come here whenever I want.
Who can stop me?
Su Yishui,
it seems
you've never beaten me so far.
Stop daydreaming.
I'm not interested
in competing with a sickly person.
Look at you now.
I guess you don't have many days left.
With someone like Dun Tian,
a powerful immortal, helping me,
I will naturally still be the one
who takes all in the end.
Is that so?
I heard you wanted
to use my body to extend your life
and marry Xue Ranran.
Unfortunately, all your schemes
amounted to nothing.
So what if you have Dun Tian's help?
He couldn't even save
his own wife or daughters.
You can't attain ascension or understand
the true meaning of immortality,
of course you don't know
how to make everything start anew.
Make everything start anew?
How?
Why bother asking?
You'll enter this game sooner or later.
If you were to die right now,
could you still make everything start anew?
Who's there?
Dun Tian,
you gave up being an immortal.
Fine, that's your choice.
But what grudge do you have against me?
Why did you attack me again and again?
Su Yishui,
I am not your enemy.
Everything I've done is to help you.
Help me?
You are lurking
in Prince Ping's residence and won't show up.
You deliberately made a plan
to get the Spirit Spring into my heart.
And you launched a sneak attack on me,
erased my memories, and disturbed my mind.
Is that how you help me?
I just want you to know
how one wrong step
led to another,
until you lost everything.
Mu Qingge,
I will spend my whole life seeking revenge!
Su Yu, Prince Ping,
and everyone who plotted against me must die!
You're all the same!
You all betrayed me!
Mu Qingge,
I will definitely kill you!
Even if you torture me to death,
when Prince Ping reigns over the universe
and wipes out Prince Zong's men,
you'll get what you deserve.
Xiaoxiao?
Yes.
It's her.
Back then, the Prince Zong's residence
spread news of Su Xiaoxiao's death.
The truth is she wandered from place to place
and suffered all kinds of humiliation.
She was originally unyielding even in the face of death.
Guess why
she later became disheartened
and lived like a walking corpse.
Ever since she knew
you gave up on claiming the throne,
she had been like that.
Poor girl. It was wrong for her to trust you back then.
She and you
shouldn't have ended up like this.
The dragon scale foretells the future.
This was the destiny you were
meant to fulfill 19 years ago —
ruling the universe
with unparalleled power.
If Mu Qingge hadn't intervened
and forcibly changed everything,
you would have already fulfilled your wish.
I've brought you back to the beginning.
This will once again become
your future destiny.
It's fated.
You will be there no matter what.
Then what about you?
What role do you play in all of this?
I'm merely a guide.
If my reigning over the universe
is the final outcome,
why is Su Yu so certain
that he will get the last laugh?
Isn't that contradictory?
It can only prove
both I
and Su Yu
are merely pawns for you to fulfill
your wish.
And everything you've done
is just to bring your wife and daughters
back to your side.
Clever.
It seems
you've guessed
part of the answer.
However,
while fulfilling my wish,
we can also fulfill
the wishes of many others.
We can achieve
a win-win situation.
I'm all ears.
Don't be impatient.
It's not the time yet.
You're being cagey.
So much for the win-win situation.
Do you expect me to be like Su Yu,
relying on you to live
with a weak body
and obeying all your orders?
I won't let anyone else
control my fate.
I'm actually interested
in fighting against you to the end.
I will never let you have your way!
Interesting.
Su Yu,
after seeing you today,
I really pity you.
I'll let you have the universe!
When the devil came,
it's not like I couldn't dodge.
But you
just used your hand to stop it.
Ms. Wen.
Elder Yan.
Ranran,
let's sit and talk.
I saw Hollow Sect's signal talisman
nearby,
so I rushed here.
On my way here,
I killed a devilized demon.
Just now, we eliminated
a group of devilized demons nearby.
You must have encountered one
that escaped.
Currently,
the devilization of demons is getting worse.
We must solve the problem.
Based on the current information
gathered from various sources,
only the Gold Refining Fire
can thoroughly purify the energy in the universe
and handle the devilization.
The Gold Refining Fire?
It's said that the Spirit Spring,
transformed from Mortal-Demon Lord's spiritual power,
was sealed in the netherworld,
but his remains remained indestructible.
The immortals then
created the Gold Refining Fire
to burn Mortal-Demon Lord's remains to ashes.
Is that it?
Mortal-Demon Lord's remains were sealed
at the former site of Celestial Sect:
Mount Scarlet Flame.
Mount Scarlet Flame
is currently occupied by Wei Jiu.
Tu Jiuyuan, his subordinate,
is willing to cooperate with us
to obtain the Gold Refining Fire together.
Therefore,
I have sent a message
to all the Heavenly Sects,
inviting them to go to Mount Scarlet Flame together
to break the formation and obtain the fire.
But what Tu Jiuyuan wants
might not be what Wei Jiu wants.
Of course we should be wary in case it's a trap.
If we can obtain it peacefully, that's fine.
If not,
we'll take it by force.
Ranran,
Yishui has always been unwilling
to associate with the other Heavenly Sects.
I wonder if Wester Sect
is willing to go with us this time.
No matter what Master's decision is,
I, Xue Ranran,
will definitely do what I can
to help solve the devilization problem.
Who are you sending a message to?
Who is it for?
What's the message about?
I told Master
you plan to secretly go to Mount Scarlet Flame
to get the Gold Refining Fire.
You...
All you care about now
is your master.
Your heart is with her too, right?
Where does that leave me?
Wu,
I'm doing this for you.
Right now, all the Heavenly Sects
are heading to Mount Scarlet Flame.
Master will definitely go too
to obtain the Gold Refining Fire.
You're no match for them.
I revealed your plan
because I want you to give up.
Why do you have to risk your life
for Dun Tian?
You don't understand at all.
I understand.
When you were drunk that day, you said
Dun Tian would take you
to another world —
a world without Qingge.
I just want to know
if you can give me what I want
after all that I've done.
Wu,
I remember you once said
if Mu Qingge didn't exist
in this world,
you might live more at ease.
What if there really is
a world like that?
From beginning to end,
you would be the only daughter in your family.
You wouldn't need to compete with others.
Would you be happy?
You still don't understand.
Uncle Ye Xin just told me
that there is such a world.
He never said
he would take me there.
Because in his eyes,
I'm not important at all.
So I have to get
more useful bargaining chips.
He wants the Gold Refining Fire,
then I have to get
the Gold Refining Fire.
That way,
I can bargain with Uncle Ye Xin
about the next step.
No one can stop me
from getting what I want.
This way, this way.
It was really good tonight.
Goodbye.
I'll come again.
Okay.
When Prince Ping reigns over the universe,
you'll get what you deserve.
Get her out
and take good care of her.
Yes.
Master.
Since everything was fine,
why were you sleeping here?
I heard you went to the capital.
I was worried.
Worried about Su Yu?
Were you worried I would
kill him and his whole family
and just take his place?
Is he...
alright?
You really are worried about him.
I heard you used to live in the imperial palace
and you were around him every day.
And he even wanted to marry you.
How did you manage to flirt with him
while also seducing me?
Who is he to be compared to me?
I'm going to kill him right now!
From beginning to end,
you've always been the one I like.
I was worried about you.
Worried about what?
Do you think I would let
Dun Tian, that old man, manipulate me?
I don't know what Dun Tian's plan is,
but since he desperately wants me
to send an army and create chaos,
I'll do just the opposite of what he wants.
Master,
you're not going to send an army?
I've just decided to postpone the plan
based on the current situation.
Don't think
you've influenced me in any way.
Master, you're wise and strong,
resourceful and reasonable,
and resolute.
By the way,
to solve the devilization problem,
the other Heavenly Sects plan to go to Celestial Sect's Mount Scarlet Flame
to obtain the Gold Refining Fire.
Master, would you like to go together?
Since the devilization problem is somehow
related to Dun Tian,
and he prompted the Heavenly Sects
to get the Gold Refining Fire,
he must be up to something.
Mu...
Mu Qingge
is also determined to obtain the Gold Refining Fire.
Maybe Dun Tian
wants to use the Heavenly Sects
to break the formation and obtain the fire,
and then take it from them.
Something doesn't feel right.
But with devils running rampant,
the world is in chaos.
No matter what Dun Tian is up to,
we can only be cautious
and obtain the Gold Refining Fire
to eliminate devils and restore order.
Indeed, we can't let Dun Tian have his way.
I'll get the Gold Refining Fire
and see what he'll do.
Master,
you're willing to go together?
I heard that a demonic cultivator named Wei Jiu
has been boasting a name on par with mine
to deceive people across the universe
over the past ten-odd years.
I'd like to meet him.
Right,
Wang Suizhi, who sent me the message,
also mentioned something else.
He said
Dun Tian
mentioned another world.
The Spirit Spring.
The Gold Refining Fire.
Make everything start anew.
Another world.
What on earth is their connection?
Sovereign,
you only asked us to keep an eye on Elder Tu
to prevent her from recklessly entering the formation
or suddenly leaving the sect.
But I...
saw something else.
I'm not sure if I should report it to you.
What is it exactly?
What happened to her?
Just tell me!
Elder Tu sent a secret message
to the Heavenly Sects,
inviting them to come
to Celestial Sect's Mount Scarlet Flame
to obtain the Gold Refining Fire.
How dare she...
Does she really want to leave that badly?
Anyway, with the power of Celestial Sect alone,
it would be difficult
to break the Five Deadly Formations in a short time.
Since those Heavenly Sects' men
have been lured here,
why don't I set up a formation
in the back mountain
to welcome them?
After they break the formations,
I'll take advantage of that
to get the Gold Refining Fire.
Sovereign, that's a brilliant strategy.
Then Elder Tu...
Don't let her know.
I
intend to catch her
off guard.
As long as the Gold Refining Fire
isn't given to me by her personally,
it can't be considered that she has fulfilled her promise.
[Mount Wester]
This time,
I can finally ride
the luxurious carriage
I didn't get to ride last time.
The other disciples
are on their way there by riding a sword.
You guys go there by riding a sword too.
You,
get in the carriage.
-Yes, Master.
The carriage...
is for me?
Your spiritual power is so weak,
and you can't ride a sword.
Do you expect me to carry you there?
I'll just ride the carriage then.
Mu Qingge?
What are you doing here?
Back then, you slandered Su Yishui by saying
he was going to turn into a devil.
It almost delayed the sealing of the Spirit Spring.
This time,
what are you up to?
Immortal Master Wen, your words are too harsh.
I was misinformed before,
and I'm truly sorry for that.
So I came here
to help obtain
the Gold Refining Fire
to make amends for that.
Since you're willing
to join us in obtaining the Gold Refining Fire
to suppress devils and benefit the people,
we naturally welcome you.
You came for the Gold Refining Fire.
Is it really for solving the devilization problem?
Mu Qingge!
You disloyal disciple!
Do you want to betray
your master again
in front of everyone?
How could this happen?
No matter how great the protective formation is,
it was given to you.
Yet you won't spend time
fully mastering it.
It's truly a waste on you.
The Soul-Devouring Lock still exists.
If you kill me,
Xue Ranran will die too.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to kill you now.
Don't you enjoy torturing others?
Once the Soul-Devouring Lock is removed,
I'll make you
endure far greater pain.
Today, I have to get the Gold Refining Fire.
Just you wait.
Celestial Sect invited us here,
yet they're not opening the gate.
Could it be that they've changed their minds?
Everyone, you've arrived as promised.
Celestial Sect
will also open the back mountain as promised
for you to obtain the Gold Refining Fire.
Please come with me.
Wait.
You allow us to get
the Gold Refining Fire so easily.
Who knows if this is a trap?
Rest assured, everyone.
I harbor no ill intentions.
It's just that in the back mountain,
there are the Five Deadly Formations
guarding the Gold Refining Fire.
Even I
have no way to break them.
We can only work together.
I
am willing to cooperate with you.
I'm afraid that once we
break the formations,
Celestial Sect
will go back on your word.
If you're worried,
I, Tu Jiuyuan, can make a soul oath.
If Celestial Sect,
in the matter of obtaining the Gold Refining Fire,
does anything to harm the Heavenly Sects
or uses the Heavenly Sects for personal gain,
I, Tu Jiuyuan,
will suffer divine punishment.
Please lead the way, Elder Tu.
Please, everyone.
Report!
My Lord,
in order to gain the trust of the Heavenly Sects,
Elder Tu made a soul oath in front of them.
What?
I had everything prepared,
yet she acted on her own
and made a soul oath!
Everyone,
the Five Deadly Formations are behind the barrier.
Celestial Sect's power is limited.
We still can't break the barrier.
Elder Tu,
His Lordship wants to see you.
He wants you to go immediately.
Got it.
Tu Jiuyuan,
why did you make that soul oath
in front of the Heavenly Sects?
If I hadn't done that,
the Heavenly Sects wouldn't have let
their guard down to cooperate with us.
My Lord, don't worry.
The soul oath was made by me alone.
It won't affect you.
If you want to take it from them,
feel free to do it.
I won't have any complaints.
You...
Fine.
Since you acted on your own,
don't blame me
for disregarding your life!
You brought this upon yourself.
My Lord, may you
get what you want
and dominate the universe early.
My Lord,
should we still proceed with our plan?
Proceed with what?
Withdraw all our people!
Withdraw everyone?
The Heavenly Sects brought many people here.
It might be difficult to deal with them.
Do you want me
to watch her die?
My Lord, you're concerned about Elder Tu.
Why didn't you just tell her?
Shut up!
Why should I
humbly explain my thoughts
to a woman?
Anyway,
try our best to obtain
the Gold Refining Fire
without triggering the soul oath.
The malicious energy is so strong.
I thought the formations were set up by the Immortal Realm.
I heard the Five Deadly Formations
were formed later.
It was originally called the Five Immortal Formations.
The Five Immortal Formations?
That's right.
It's said that
after Mortal-Demon Lord died,
his remains still emitted strong demonic energy.
The Immortal Realm created the Gold Refining Fire
here on Mount Scarlet Flame
to incinerate the remains.
However, even so,
it would still take a few hundred years
to completely burn Mortal-Demon Lord's remains
to ashes.
To prevent people
from coveting the Gold Refining Fire,
the Immortal Realm ordered five guardians of the Heavenly Sects
to set up the Five Immortal Formations here
to protect the Gold Refining Fire.
It's been quite a few hundred years.
The remains of Mortal-Demon Lord
must have been burnt to ashes long ago.
Then how did the Five Immortal Formations
turn into the Five Deadly Formations?
Perhaps it's because many devils died here,
and they had strong resentment.
Over time,
even the Five Immortal Formations had been contaminated
by the malicious energy
and turned into the Five Deadly Formations.
If
Wei Jiu hadn't reopened this mountain gate,
we would never have seen the formations.
That's right!
If our sovereign
hadn't reopened Celestial Sect,
you probably wouldn't even have been able
to climb up this mountain.
Masters of the Heavenly Sects,
you came to the territory of Celestial Sect
and have been observing for quite a while.
I wonder what insights you've gained.
Sovereign Wei, you've been running around for 20 years.
Now that the mountain gate is finally open,
I'm sure you must have studied
the formations thoroughly.
Why don't you
enlighten us?
You...
If Ranran
is willing to stay with me at Mount Scarlet Flame for a few days,
I'll tell you
the secrets of the formations.
This devil is just bluffing.
If he knows the secrets of the formations,
he wouldn't have invited us here to break the formations.
Am I right,
Wei Jiu?
You're right.
The Five Deadly Formations may seem ordinary,
but they're extremely dangerous.
So far, no one has been able
to unravel its mysteries.
But it's said
these five formations
are all interconnected.
If you break one of them,
the other four will automatically become ineffective.
How difficult are these five formations?
It's said they are equally challenging.
Everyone, you will have to
rely on your own capabilities.
Everyone,
I'm willing to lead Luoshan Sect's disciples
to be the scouts for you.
The sovereign of Luoshan Sect
is quite bold.
He has a top-grade formation-breaking weapon.
Of course he's not afraid.
Blood?
There's no sign of life.
They're dead?
The Five Deadly Formations are very mysterious.
Everyone,
don't let your guard down.
Only by breaking the Five Deadly Formations
can we obtain the Gold Refining Fire
to subdue devils.
We, Hollow Sect,
can't back down.
All disciples,
follow me into the formations!
Eternal Sect's disciples, follow me into the formations!
-Yes!
All disciples, follow me to break the formations.
Scud Sect's disciples,
come with me!
Today, no matter what,
I must obtain the Gold Refining Fire.
But that damn Su Yishui has broken
my protective formation.
I need
to figure out a safer way.
Master.
We joined Wester Sect not long ago,
and our power is limited.
Yes, Master.
I... I'm worried we can't be
very helpful and might even
become your burden.
Fine.
Leave the spiritual power
you gained in Wester Sect
and get lost.
Hold on to me tightly!
All of you, hold on tight!
Hold tight!
Xi'er!
[Inside the Five Deadly Formations]
Master, I disobeyed your order.
Please punish me.
You broke the rule to save your fellow disciples.
It's understandable.
Let it go from now on.
My disciples
all died in the vortex.
I want to act together with you.
If you don't want to die in a miserable way,
stop showing up in front of me!
If I die in the formation,
she will die too!
Think about it carefully.
The formation is dangerous.
Everyone, we must be cautious.
The priority is to find the formation's eye.
Once the formations are broken,
I must be the first to obtain the Gold Refining Fire.
Master,
the runes on the ground are very mysterious.
Do you recognize them?
I once saw a world-destroying formation
in an ancient book.
It's called the Three Thousand Realms Tower.
I think it also used
this kind of rune.
It's said that Mortal-Demon Lord
built a devilish tower that can destroy everything
in Celestial Sect.
Could it be...
building the Three Thousand Realms Tower was
why he got killed by the Heavenly Sects?
That ancient book has been lost,
so it's impossible to verify it now.
♫In March, we make rice milk♫
♫And bring it to our daughter for a taste♫
What's that?
♫In April, we make wine♫
♫A day without it♫
♫Leaves us restless♫
Girls, don't cry.
I'll kill all of them for you!
Who is this demoness?
Her malicious energy is so strong.
I don't think she's one of the five guardians
protecting the formations.
They don't have children.
The song?
Little girls?
She's Rong Yao!
Back in the Memory Cave at the Heavenly Meridian Mountain,
I saw Dun Tian's memories.
The tune his wife, Rong Yao, was humming
is exactly what we just heard!
Rong Yao has taken control of the formations.
What?
Dun Tian's wife
can actually contaminate the formations with malicious energy?
Back then, in order to attain enlightenment, Dun Tian
chose to sacrifice his wife and daughters,
while he himself attained ascension.
Rong Yao and their daughters
were abandoned and sacrificed.
Of course she had
strong resentment.
No wonder.
Although Rong Yao is dead,
her resentment hasn't disappeared over the past few hundred years.
And her malicious energy has gradually contaminated the formations.
It seems Dun Tian is not the only one
who can't let it go.
Rong Yao can't let it go either.
Why did you break in?
All of you deserve to die!
Kill!
Fighting the malicious energy is useless!
Rong Yao is the eye of the formation!
We need to break her true form
to escape!
Master,
let me help you.
Divine Tree!
-Master!
You actually managed to hurt me by working together.
I underestimated you.
Your behavior of risking
your lives to protect each other
has really irritated me!
You should know that love
is the most hypocritical
and unreliable in this world!
Today, let me see
how long your hypocritical love
can last!
What did you do to us?
What I cast on you
is Celestial Sect's most powerful torture spell:
the Lone Star Blood Spell!
Those under the spell will endure
searing pain as if consumed by flames.
The stronger one's spiritual power is,
the greater pain that person will suffer.
The blood spell won't end
until either of you dies.
The spell
has connected your spiritual power.
If you transfer
your spiritual power to the other person,
you'll suffer less pain.
How are you feeling?
It's painful, right?
Then transfer
your spiritual power to the other person!
As long as you betray the other,
you can survive!
I'd like to see how much longer you can hold on!
Invoke!
Ranran!
Master!
The Soul-Devouring Lock.
Mu Ranwu and Ranran
are connected by the Soul-Devouring Lock.
They share each other's spiritual power,
so Mu Ranwu is also under the spell
and has been dragged into it!
Master and the others are in danger!
You can't break free from this.
The Lone Star Blood Spell
won't kill all of you.
You have plenty of ways
to ensure your own survival.
What do you think?
Isn't this interesting?
You two
are this monster's target!
Why should I suffer
all this with you
even at this point?
Xue Ranran's spiritual power is weak now.
All the pain and pressure are on my side.
If this continues,
I definitely won't be able to withstand it.
Xue Ranran!
I don't want any of this anymore!
I'm giving it all back to you!
I'm giving all the spiritual power
back to you!
Xue Ranran, I'm giving it all back to you!
Ranran!
The Soul-Devouring Lock is broken!
Oh no.
Since the Soul-Devouring Lock is broken,
all the spiritual power has returned to Ranran's body.
These blood chains...
The stronger Ranran's spiritual power is,
the greater pain she will suffer!
Give it to me!
This is mine!
Don't hit my sister!
This is my Mount Wester.
Shui,
it's you.
Shui?
I've regained all my spiritual power
at the Transcendence Stage.
If you want to live,
just transfer your spiritual power
to the other person!
Today, let me see which of you
can win and which of you
will die first!
Sword of Non-Attachment!
Focus and gather the power.
Harness the energy to command the spirits!
Converge!
What are you doing?
Temporarily boosting
your spiritual power through the living creatures
will make the blood chains rush towards you!
You won't be able to withstand it!
Cut the crap!
I'm not doing this to save you.
I came here to break the formations
to obtain the Gold Refining Fire.
We can't all die here!
But you...
Ranran,
listen to me.
Rong Yao's malicious energy is truly formidable,
but she's used it all
on the blood chain formation.
Rong Yao herself
is now the most vulnerable.
Now,
I'm drawing the blood chains to myself
to reduce your pain.
You take this chance to gather your power
and attack Rong Yao directly!
We only have one chance.
You have to succeed!
-Master!