[Love of the Divine Tree]
[Episode 39]
A secret passage has to be hidden, of course.
Am I
supposed to install
a big red-painted door here?
Alright.
Getting in smoothly is what matters most.
This doghole really does
lead directly to the main hall entrance,
avoiding those shadow people outside.
That imposter must be
in the main hall right now.
You guys handle
the scum outside for me,
and I go and kill that imposter. Be careful.
Everyone, be careful.
Don't get the blood on you.
Yes.
Be careful.
Let's go.
You actually want to kill me?
If that's the case,
don't blame me for showing no mercy.
You impostor,
I'm here today
to settle the score with you!
This Sun-Radiant Pearls
Zeng Yi gave me
are really useful.
They contain
the sunlight of midday.
You impostors
don't have shadows under the sunlight.
That's because
this extreme yang light
weakens your spiritual power, right?
Go to hell!
If you dare make another move,
I'll kill Tu Jiuyuan.
If I die, she dies too.
How do I know if she's real or fake?
If she's fake,
I'd be at a big loss.
It's more worthwhile to kill you.
Sure enough,
once the source has been eliminated,
the shadow people dissipated.
You didn't die.
You're still alive
and weren't replaced.
Elder Tu,
are you alright?
The fetus is stable.
There's no major issue.
It seems that
when the Two-headed Deceptive Python tried to replicate you,
it had no effect on the fetus in your womb.
So, from beginning to end,
it was unable to replicate you.
Tu Jiuyuan,
who allowed you to act on your own
and stay by that impostor's side?
You were all lovey-dovey with that impostor,
and...
And...
about the child in your belly...
This is my private matter.
It's none of your business.
None of my business?
Then whose business is it?
You've got some nerve, Tu Jiuyuan.
Tell me,
who has the guts?
Wei Jiu,
what nonsense are you talking about?
The number one shadow person has been eliminated.
The others who were controlling
the various sects of the Heavenly Sects
should have dissipated by now.
The disciples of each sect
have received the news
and should have returned to their sects.
But why haven't
the spiritual channels of these major sects
been closed yet?
It's Wen Hongshan.
What's wrong?
The entrances of the Four Heavenly Sects
have not opened.
People from all sects are being blocked
outside the barrier set by Dun Tian
and cannot enter to close the spiritual channels.
Do you think
this is the end?
No one can stop me.
Three Thousand Realms Tower, rise!
How could this be?
The core of the formation
that Dun Tian wanted to use to build the tower
has already been destroyed.
The Three Children are no longer in his hands.
Even the shadow people
he manipulated and used are gone.
What else can he do?
Why hasn't he stopped yet?
Could it be that Dun Tian still has a backup plan
we don't know about?
Now,
after all this effort,
we still haven't reclaimed the spiritual channels.
Does this mean
that this fate is truly unstoppable?
I don't believe in fate.
Everything Shui and I have experienced in two lifetimes
has long made me understand one thing:
Every single prophecy
recorded in the Heavenly Book
can actually change.
In other words,
everything
that everyone does
leads to a corresponding result.
I produced the effect because I created the cause.
The path
is something we forge ourselves.
We still have plenty of time
to change everything.
It's too early to admit defeat.
The priority now is to find out
where Dun Tian is currently building the tower
and stop him.
This reminds me of something.
Hundreds of years ago,
the Mortal-Demon Lord tried
to build the tower at Mount Scarlet Flame.
There are still marks left
from the spiritual power burning at that time.
Perhaps we can
find some other clues there.
[Mount Scarlet Flame]
When the Mortal-Demon Lord
built the tower's core here,
he must have also needed
to find several spiritual channels
to supply energy to it.
I've looked around
and there are indeed
traces of mountain veins
passing through the ground.
Not every place
can withstand the power
gathered from the spiritual channels.
This is an ancient scroll
we found in the secret cave where the Mortal-Demon Lord
cultivated in the past.
Look.
In this picture, there is a figure beneath the tower.
What does this mean?
And this one?
These are the places the Mortal-Demon Lord found
that could withstand
the convergence of the spiritual channels.
So that means
if Dun Tian wants to build the Three Thousand Realms Tower,
the the tower's core can only be in these few locations.
If we split up and investigate now,
do we still have time?
The Mortal-Demon Lord
chose Mount Scarlet Flame back then.
And Dun Tian originally
chose Puxin Village.
Aside from
their abundant spiritual energy,
what do these two places have in common?
The south of Scarlet River
and the east of Mount Ying.
Ancient texts record
that the First God created nine voids,
and among the nine voids,
there are Scarlet River and Mount Ying.
Mount Scarlet Flame and Puxin Village
happen to be located precisely
on the southeast positions of Scarlet River and Mount Ying.
There's only one place
that can withstand the convergence
of the spiritual channels
and is located in the southeast position
of one of the voids—
Mount Wester.
Dun Tian plans to build the Three Thousand Realms Tower
on our Mount Wester?
So it's not for the spiritual channel.
It's to use it as the foundation for the tower's core.
Ranran,
Qing Luo has disappeared.
Last time, you warned me
that Dun Tian might try to seize the Dragon's child,
and I immediately went to summon him.
But he had slipped out of Dragon Island.
I searched for a long time
and found that his Dragon Breath
had vanished at the edge
of the Sea of Immortality.
I've searched everywhere,
but there's no trace of him.
Zeng Yi,
take the disciples back
to the vicinity of Mount Wester to check the situation.
Find more people to help.
Don't act rashly for now.
Ranran and I will go to
the edge of the Sea of Immortality to investigate.
Once we find Qing Luo,
we will meet you at Mount Wester.
Okay.
I'll go to Mount Wester with you.
You're pregnant.
Why are you going there?
There are no dry decks when the ship is sinking.
If the whole world
were to be overturned,
what would be the use of me staying here
on Mount Scarlet Flame, doing nothing?
Alright.
Let's split up.
[Sea of Immortality]
By the Sea of Immortality,
this is the only strange place.
Could that blood mist be…
The blood mist formed from the flood dragon pearls
is the most coveted delicacy of the Dragon Clan.
Qing Luo is here.
It's you.
Since you've found your way here,
why are you sneaking around?
You want to ruin my big plan?
Wu,
look at yourself.
The demonic energy that Dun Tian lent you before
has already invaded your flesh and blood.
You'll definitely fall into demonic ways.
Stop now.
Wang Suizhi!
Today is the deadline.
If I don't send the little Green Dragon away,
I'll die!
Yet you're still here talking nonsense!
No.
You'll be fine.
I told you
I could help you break the Life-Death Spell.
How did the Life-Death Spell that was cast on me
transfer to you?
You...
How did you manage to do that?
As an unqualified cultivator,
the only skill I'm good at
is manipulating fate.
Wu,
I know these years
have been difficult for you.
Let me bear the pain
of the Life-Death Spell for you.
You shortened your lifespan
to swap your fate with mine.
When the Life-Death Spell strikes,
you will...
You don't need to borrow demonic energy anymore,
and you don't need to be controlled by Dun Tian from now on.
Wu,
release the Green Dragon.
The world is vast.
There are so many interesting places
worth seeing.
Wu!
Who gave you the permission to make the decision on your own?
Release the Green Dragon
and let you die in my place?
And then what?
Wang Suizhi,
and then,
are you going to leave me alone?
I won't accept it!
If you continue like this,
you'll be corrupted by demonic energy
and lose yourself forever.
So what?
All these years,
you're the only one who has always stayed
by my side.
All the way
till now,
I only have you left.
I will never
let the Life-Death Spell strike.
I will send the Green Dragon to Dun Tian,
and then let you
live on with me!
Wu!
Wu.
She's about to fall into demonic ways.
Master,
Wu has absorbed too much demonic energy.
Please save her!
Qingge,
you came after all.
What now?
are you going to put on airs again
and lecture me from your high horse?
Wu,
I heard about Suizhi
and the Life-Death Spell.
Stop the formation for now,
and let's think of a way together.
There must be a solution.
I don't need your solutions!
From the past until now,
whenever you look at me,
it always feels like you're giving me charity.
I don't want your charity!
This time,
I will save Suizhi myself.
The Three Thousand Realms.
I'm going to
the Three Thousand Realms with him,
becoming the master of the Heavenly Sects
and trampling you underfoot.
Oh no.
The little Green Dragon has been sent away.
Wu!
She has completely fallen into demonic ways.
There's only killing intent left in her heart.
With this blood-colored totem,
she will self-destruct,
killing all living beings here,
including herself.
Wu,
I can't let you hurt yourself,
nor can I let you hurt Master.
This is the last thing
I can do for you.
Suizhi,
are you going to scatter your heart?
Master,
Wu...
will definitely turn back!
Suizhi?
Suizhi!
Wu,
you're alright.
That's great.
Why are you so foolish?
Why did you
sacrifice your life for me?
I observe fate.
All my life, I've sought profit and avoided harm.
But when I met you,
I realized that
when we meet the ones we love,
even a brief moment of closeness
is enough to cherish for a lifetime.
No.
I will save you.
I will save you!
Why?
Dun Tian,
lend me your demonic energy!
Dun Tian!
No.
Suizhi,
I'll go and beg Dun Tian again.
I will think of a way!
I will find a way!
Wu,
don't waste energy for me,
and don't go to Dun Tian.
All I wish
is that you can stay away from all of this
and live a peaceful life.
Master,
I'm an unfilial disciple
and have disappointed you.
But I beg you,
please forgive Wu.
She has lost all her spiritual power
and can't do anything anymore.
Just let her
live the rest of her life
as an ordinary person.
If there is a next life,
I will serve you
to repay your kindness.
Even if you hadn't said it,
she was, after all, my sister in a past life.
You...
don't need to worry.
Wu,
let me
read your fortune one last time.
The rest of your life
will be peaceful
and happy.
Very good.
♫Who knows the loneliness of mountains and seas?♫
Suizhi!
♫The sharp wind cuts at my heart♫
Wang Suizhi! Wang Suizhi!
♫Hold a drop of blood♫
Suizhi!
♫Tattered flowers and tears♫
♫Reincarnating but to no avail♫
Wang Suizhi! Wang Suizhi!
Wang Suizhi!
♫Devoting one's life despite knowing it can't be♫
Do you remember that
25 years ago,
you saved me at the foot of Mount Wester?
♫Coming to the abyss despite knowing retreat is possible♫
I was not a talented cultivator
and was bullied by my senior brothers.
You stood up for me.
♫Who says the world is full of wrongs?♫
♫I seize the Way and choose heaven♫
So what if you're not talented?
If your hands are so idle,
I'll chop them all off for you.
♫It won't be a waste of my life to burn until I wither♫
I thought you were a disciple of the Wester Sect,
so I joined the Wester Sect.
♫There's no need to discuss right or wrong♫
I'm really grateful to you.
♫I can sacrifice my life♫
♫All rules can be dismantled♫
♫Die in this world♫
♫The masses spread rumors that are hard to swallow♫
Every time you came to Mount Wester,
♫I haven't said anything yet, my heart is clear♫
I was so happy
to see you.
♫I still don't regret it; I'll pay for it all my life♫
I've always hoped
♫You know my heart, won't go against my wishes♫
that you could live a happier life.
♫Don't speak of redressing injustices♫
Master,
do you have any clues about Wu's whereabouts?
♫Don't let others pity me♫
Why are you looking for her?
♫Try your best to forget me♫
Why?
♫I'll go through hardships and never break down♫
Why? Why?
♫I vow to fight against darkness♫
In my heart,
♫Love punishes me a thousand times, yet a merciful heart pardons me♫
compared to anyone,
you have always been the best.
♫No pain, no resentment♫
Suizhi.
Immortals?
So many immortals.
Immortals.
I'll find immortals to save Suizhi.
So many immortals.
Immortals.
Wu...
has lost her sanity.
With the demonic energy entering her body,
she was supposed to become
a bloodthirsty and murderous Mortal-Demon.
But now that she has lost her sanity,
she's immune to being controlled.
It's a blessing in disguise.
The demonic clouds are gathering in the sky.
The anomaly is...
The Three Thousand Realms Tower is about to form.
How could this be?
Ranran.
Su Yishui.
I followed the compass
you left behind
and finally found you.
Su Yu
was taken away by Dun Tian.
The surroundings of Qiongqi Village
are covered by a hidden barrier.
How did Dun Tian find him?
It was His Highness
who walked out of the barrier on his own.
Come, look.
These vegetables have grown so well.
Thank you, Auntie.
What a bountiful harvest!
It's too much.
We can't finish them in the next few days.
Are you going to the market?
Yes, we're going to the market
to take a look around.
We're off then.
Alright.
It's absolutely true.
I saw the notice with my own eyes.
Minister Zhou was arrested
and charged with
the serious crime of kidnapping the Crown Prince.
And he'll be executed soon.
This minister has always been a loyal official.
How could he kidnap the Crown Prince?
I think
it's a setup.
Speaking of which,
it's all because the Crown Prince is missing
that the capital
is in such chaos.
Your Highness,
so you're here.
I was planning to return with you anyway.
There's no need to make things difficult for Minister Zhou.
Let him go.
Your Highness, I've been searching for you for days.
I know
we're on the same page.
Now,
Su Yi and Qing Luo
have both fallen into his hands.
But what about the Demon's child?
The Demon's child no longer exists.
The Child of the Human Emperor,
the Child of the Divine Dragon,
and the Child of the True Devil.
The Three Children are all here.
The strange phenomenon of the Three Thousand Realms Tower
is the proof.
Feihua,
may I ask you for a favor?
Wu has lost all her cultivation
and her sanity.
Please take her to Qiongqi Village.
Alright.
So,
where are you going?
Back to Mount Wester.
We need to save Mount Wester
before the Three Thousand Realms Tower
is fully formed,
and save this world as well.
Master, Ranran.
This strange phenomenon of the Three Thousand Realms Tower in the sky…
It seems
your trip to rescue the little Green Dragon
was in vain.
What happened?
Ranran, Master,
the entrance to the Wester Sect
is sealed by Dun Tian with a barrier.
It's the same kind of barrier as the ones that
seal the spiritual channels of the Four Heavenly Sects.
We can't break through it.
If we delay any longer,
the Three Thousand Realms Tower
will be fully formed.
This barrier
was set by the power from the Immortal Realm.
Once you step in, heavenly thunder will strike.
We can't even take a step in.
To break through an Immortal Realm barrier,
we need the power from the Immortal Realm.
The power of the Immortal Realm?
But we are all mortals.
Where can we get the power from the Immortal Realm?
We have it.
Where did you get the power from the Immortal Realm?
This Heavenly Book
is originally a treasure from the Immortal Realm.
This fragment of the Heavenly Book
still retains some residual immortal power.
We can use this
to pass through Dun Tian's barrier.
You actually have the Heavenly Book?
Even just a small piece of this thing
is a priceless treasure.
If you destroy it,
won't that be a terrible waste?
It's a critical moment.
Should we keep the Heavenly Book
and die with it?
Wait for my news.
You want to face death
alone again?
What about me?
But the remaining power of the Heavenly Book isn't enough.
It's safer
if one person does it.
Then why don't you let me go alone?
You won't have a second chance
to leave me behind
and face danger on your own.
If we're going, we go together.
But two people
will consume more power.
Once the Heavenly Book's power is exhausted…
Do you remember the Death Realm at Wangxiang Pass?
Back then, the two of us—
one expelled the impurities, the other brought in the new.
Our spiritual power circulated as if we were one.
This time, we'll use the same method.
♫For you, I dare to face a thousand arrows♫
♫My spiritual sense returning to nothingness, and my Spirit Root scattering♫
♫Even if I must die, I will use the last piece♫
♫Of my broken body to protect you♫
Oh no.
That's the Three Thousand Realms Tower!
The Three Thousand Realms Tower has formed?
-Master!
Shui,
we're about to pass through the barrier.
Tu Jiuyuan, what are you doing?
You're pregnant.
Why are you getting involved in this mess?
If no one can stop Dun Tian,
how much longer can we survive?
I didn't expect the overflowing Space-Time Power
of the Three Thousand Realms Tower
to be so powerful.
If this continues,
before Dun Tian sacrifices the world,
the entire earth will collapse.
Master and Ranran are fighting desperately inside.
As a disciple of the Wester Sect,
I must also
contribute my strength!
Before Master and Ranran
stop Dun Tian,
let's protect the mortal world!
Uncle Master?
All the Heavenly Ones
who could come are here.
This evil, monstrous thing
is delaying my drinking!
Let's handle the important thing first.
You need to survive
to drink your wine.
Use your magical weapons
to resist the overflowing power
of the Three Thousand Realms Tower!
Fellow cultivators,
the demons are wreaking havoc, and the world is in chaos.
As cultivators,
what should we do?
Hold our swords and protect the world! Even if we die, we'll have no regrets!
The space-time turbulence
caused me to take so long to land.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
How did Mount Wester
become like this?
This is a new space created by the Three Thousand Realms Tower,
attached to Mount Wester.
I'm afraid Mount Wester
has already been destroyed beyond recognition
by the space-time turbulence.
Withered trees can sprout again,
and broken houses can be rebuilt.
As long as we're all here,
everything can be started anew.
We somehow
ended up in this hellish place.
How do we get back?
We're here to stop Dun Tian.
Why should we go back?
Stop joking.
The Three Thousand Realms Tower
is an evil being that even immortals can't deal with.
When the tower hadn't formed, there might have been a way.
Now that the tower has formed,
what can we do?
That's right.
Now that things have come to this point,
how can we give up?
It's just one last fight.
Sovereign Wei,
thank you for your help earlier.
Please stay here
and wait for our news.
It created four identical worlds.
It's the infancy of the Three Thousand Realms.
If it's left to grow,
more and more such worlds will appear,
eventually breaking through this space
and extending to the outside world.
The road to the Three Thousand Realms Tower
must be within these four worlds.
We'll find it faster if we split up.
Anyway,
I can't escape from here.
Count me in.
Each of us will carry a golden talisman
and enter one of these four worlds.
Once you find Dun Tian
and the Three Thousand Realms Tower,
light the talisman to signal.
Since this is just the infancy
of the new world,
we should be able
to break through the space and reunite.
If anyone
encounters danger,
we must not act on our own.
Always report first, then plan afterward.
You must be careful,
Ranran!
Why are you...
here?
Dun Tian is in my world.
The others have all fallen into his hands.
Come with me now.
Ranran, why are you doing this?
Shui and I agreed
to report first when anything happens.
But you suddenly barged in here.
Clearly, you're an imposter.
Looks like Dun Tian and the Three Thousand Realms Tower
are within my world.
As expected of Mu Qingge.
Clever indeed.
But unfortunately,
you're still going to die here.
Demon's child?
How could he endure the Spirit Spring
while impersonating Shui?
You are...
a shadow person?
That's right.
How could this be?
The shadow people have disappeared.
Why are you...
Since the Two-headed Deceptive Python has two heads,
the first shadow people it created
were two.
One was Wei Jiu,
and the other was me.
As long as we both exist,
the shadow people after us
can be infinitely replicated.
You thought you won
by killing the fake Wei Jiu.
How laughable.
I see.
So those shadow people dissipated
to conceal your existence.
I've replicated everything from Su Yishui,
including the body of the Demon's child.
So naturally, I can absorb the Spirit Spring
and use it for my master.
Mu Qingge,
now you should understand.
It's not impossible
for the Demon Child to kill you!
Shadow people?
When I fell into demonic ways,
Dun Tian led me to summon the Two-headed Deceptive Python.
So that was his plan for me all along.
He was prepared from the start,
intending to trap us.
The Tainted Demonic Serpent Formation has formed.
It can't be broken in a short time.
Stay here obediently
and wait for the opening of the Three Thousand Realms.
Tu Jiuyuan,
are you alright?
You bullied my people?
You're seeking death!
Wei Jiu!
You're nothing.
I won't die.
I will...
get you out of here soon.
Back then,
I used the Blood-bound Net
to trap you two.
I can sacrifice my own blood
and try it again!
It will only last for a moment.
Don't...
miss it.
Wei Jiu!
The Demon's child is so precious.
How could I bear to release him
and let you kill him?
He is just a shadow
projected by a space
I created.
Since you're here,
then come out and meet me.
This damn Dun Tian.
He made me, a dignified demon lord,
sacrifice myself for others.
How...
How embarrassing.
Wei Jiu is severely injured.
I need to sustain his energy
to heal him.
You must stop Dun Tian.
Alright.
Long time no see.
You don't need to look at me like that.
Su Yishui,
I've been planning this for years.
Among all my pawns,
you are the most disobedient one.
I painstakingly built
countless steps,
and yet you refuse to step on them.
You're so annoying.
Very well.
My whole life
has been burdened by your schemes.
But at least I didn't give you what you want.
If I can cause you some trouble,
that's good enough.
This is your nature.
I've figured it out.
It's impossible
to make you change.
The only way
is to create a new version of you.
Finally,
I have your shadow person.
When you destroyed your Golden Core
and separated from the Spirit Spring for Ranran,
I knew
I had succeeded.
I know that Uncle Ye Xin
is just your false form.
But even so,
I've always remembered
the favor of your upbringing.
You were born in this world,
grew up in this world,
and the memories you're longing for
also originated from this world.
I'll advise you one last time.
Please stop.
Advise me?
Mu Qingge,
if it weren't for you,
I would have reunited with my wife
and children over a decade ago.
If it weren't for you,
Su Yishui wouldn't have
become such a problem.
Yet
you've always wanted to repay the favor
of my upbringing.
But I regret it
every moment.
I regret that at that time
I had a whim
and decided to raise you.
But it's all over now.
It will be over soon.
The Three Thousand Realms Tower is about to form.
By then,
I will go and seek my fulfillment.
And you
will face your demise!
Be careful!
Here it comes again!
I will protect you!
One wisp of qi to break the galaxy!
How did this happen?
With our combined attack,
even an immortal
couldn't
heal immediately after being injured.
Unless...
this isn't his true form!
In this painting,
there's a figure under the tower.
The painting we saw in the Celestial Sect.
Forming the tower with a mortal body?
Dun Tian is using his own mortal body
to form the Three Thousand Realms Tower.
No wonder, even though we destroyed the tower's core,
he was easily able
to move it to Mount Wester.
That's right.
All of this
is thanks to you.
I am the tower,
and the tower is me.
What do you have to defeat me?