Is it okay to fall in love with you, Haruta?
- Pardon?
- I can kiss just anyone.
Haruta already has his match.
You're also in love with him. Why aren't you telling him directly?
I don't wish for anything more than our current relationship.
- Why?
- This is my father!
Say what?
[Kurosawa]
Haruta,
what is your relationship with Hina?
We were in the same club in high school,
[Soichi Haruta | Cabin Attendant]
and we're still friends now.
[Musashi Kurosawa | Captain]
I see. Are you two friends?
Y-Yes!
[Hina Tachibana | PR Staff]
That's right. We meet up occasionally.
I'll get straight to the point.
Are you two...
dating? Is that it?
N-No, that's not...
It's not like that!
Of course...
He gave me the okay sign back then.
Sorry for not telling you about my dad.
I didn't mean to keep it from you, Haru.
- Haru?
- What?
It's nothing... I just realized you call him Haru.
But your surname is "Tachibana".
And your surname is "Kurosawa", right?
My parents divorced when I was little.
I've lived with Mom until...
she passed away due to an illness.
I'm sorry to hear that.
- It's fine!
- Too bad.
- You two work together, right?
- Yes.
Haruta and I...
have a good relationship.
Thank you.
Really? I'm so glad.
- Right?
- Pardon?
Right?
Why is he staring at me?
With that said... Let's go, Haru.
Where are you going?
- To the Sky World Park!
- Sky World Park?
Yes.
- Together?
- Of course!
W-W-Wait!
What's going on here?
Is this... a date?
Haruta, who do you like more...
Me or Hina?
Tell me. Say it.
Which one is it?
- Excuse me?
- Oh...
It slipped out...
So creepy. Let's go, Haru! Come on!
- Did you call your father creepy?
- Excuse us.
- Haruta?
- E-Excuse me!
Haruta?
Haruta!
Haruta...
I should have a proper conversation with Captain,
and ask him what this was all about?
Is it okay to fall in love with you, Haruta?
Excuse me.
I'd like to ask you a question.
Hypothetically speaking,
if someone asks you, "Is it okay to fall in love with you?"
What does that mean?
[Haruka Neko | Cabin Attendant]
[Tamiyo Arisugawa | Cabin Attendant]
Are you bragging?
- He's totally bragging.
- Right?
I'm not. It's hypothetical. I'm not talking about myself.
You're an awful liar.
I know. It's Hina, right?
- That's so sweet.
- Totally.
- That's not it.
- That's a love confession, all right.
- What?
- That's a line manga characters use when they're 100% sure it's going to work!
- Only if they are 100% sure.
- 100%?
- Maybe 200 or 300%?
- Right.
Come on! Hurry up and decide, Haruta!
You're wrong! It's really not like that!
- Good morning!
- Huh? Good morning!
The Tokyo-Ishigaki flight will finally start in three days.
- Right.
- As for the on-board announcements...
Haruta, would you like to try it?
[Misae Jumonji | Cabin Attendant]
- Me?
- Haruta?
Do you think Haruta can handle such an important duty?
- Watch it!
- Well, it's a much-anticipated new route,
so I think Haruta's fresh image will work well.
Fresh? Me?
What? He bumped into your dad?
[Kaname Shinomiya | Mechanic]
The both of them seemed so awkward.
It was my fault for not telling Haru about my dad.
You didn't tell him?
I thought they both already knew about that.
My dad's been acting weird ever since.
Oh my god!
- Welcome home.
- I'm back.
- You're late.
- Am I?
- How about tomorrow?
- Sorry?
What time are you coming back tomorrow?
I might be a little late.
- Come straight home.
- What?
- Come straight home. Straight home!
- Why? Why?
Straight home.
He may not be fond of Haru.
- Could it be... that you love Haru?
- I love him.
Well, who knows...?
Maybe he's simply jealous that his beloved daughter
might be stolen away.
Do you think so?
Shino, what's wrong?
You're sweating. Are you okay?
Well, it's hot! Yeah! It's really hot in here!
Really? I feel kind of cold.
The Captain must feel lonely.
Good point.
- That reminds me, Shino!
- Yes?
The PR department received a request.
- For me?
- Yes.
When will the Captain be back today?
Never mind.
Okay, practice time!
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome aboard Tenku Peach Airlines.
This is Flight Number...
- Ninety-nine...
- Come home!
- Come back!
- Don't come to my workplace.
You're going to regret it!
I have no interest in that at all.
He's at it again?
Are you sure about that?
[Ryu Naruse | Copilot]
Naruse, are you causing trouble again?
Naruse, don't ignore me.
What are you...?
You're really annoying.
Excuse me?
Hey, Naruse!
What the heck is wrong with him?
He's really something. Seriously...
That's long! What is this?
Dear Mr. Haruta,
you came all the way to my home the other day,
but I failed to offer you proper hospitality. I'm very sorry.
That day, I felt like my daughter was taken away from me.
I also felt like you were cheating on me.
I felt so confused, which even surprised myself.
But I believe you weren't lying about accepting my love
when I confessed.
H-Hold on a second.
My feelings
have already departed for the destination Love.
Have a happy flight today.
Sincerely yours.
What? Does he think I accepted his love?
How? How? Where? When?
- I can't accept your love.
- Is that an okay sign? Hooray!
Captain totally misunderstood me.
Attention passengers, I have one question.
Since when did I become the Captain's boyfriend?
Ouch!
Jesus...
[Soichi Haruta]
[Ryu Naruse]
[Kaname Shinomiya]
[Musashi Kurosawa]
[Ossan's Love: in the sky]
[3rd Flight | Endless Rain]
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to Tenku...
What am I going to do?
Hot!
Wait. Don't go, Naruse.
Don't run away. Just eat it here. It's hot!
- Jeez!
- I'm sorry. That was hot.
My bad. Here, take a seat.
It was hot!
What do you want?
You can't keep doing those things.
- What things?
- The thing with the woman this afternoon.
After causing trouble to the company,
you're making the same mistake again.
That was my younger sister.
That woman is my younger sister.
What?
What? That was your younger sister?
Well?
Sorry, I misunderstood...
She's your little sister?
I was wrong.
I'm also sorry about dropping your food.
It was too hot.
I don't care.
It was too hot to hold it.
What are you reading? Ancient burial mounds?
[Keyhole-Shaped Ancient Burial Mounds]
Come on, show me.
Why not? Is it interesting to read?
- What is this?
- What do you care about my hobby so much?
You don't need to get that upset!
We're on the same team. It's a casual talk.
Listen.
It was just a kiss,
don't take it so seriously.
I don't.
I just want to have a normal conversation with you...
as colleagues.
- So annoying.
- Why?
This is a rare occasion.
- Shino, welcome home.
- Hi.
Where are you going?
- Naruse!
- Not so fast.
I said, wait!
Hold on a minute. That's hot.
Are you eating gratin again?
- What did you eat for lunch?
- Gratin.
- Breakfast? Gratin, right?
- Grati—
If you keep this up, you'll to ruin your health.
Wait here.
Annoying!
[Have a happy flight today. Sincerely yours.]
[Read]
No response, huh?
You're waitin' for something', aren't ya?
What?
You over there!
[Fortune Telling]
[Genuine! Granny of Aomono Yokocho | Fortune Telling]
So?
What's troubling you?
Well... due to my job
my hours are irregular.
No, no. That's not it, is it?
You're right.
Actually, right now...
in my old age, I'm in love with—
That's it!
Yes.
Well...
I got the okay from this person,
but with someone else... how do I put it?
I saw them flirting with another person.
So...
I've been wondering what's going on?
Is that two-timing?
I'd like to know
what this person thinks of me.
They want to make you jealous.
- What?
- Flirting with someone else in front of you...
They're fanning the flames of your jealousy.
Is Haruta trying...
to make me jealous?
So that's what it was?
This person likes you, too.
- Likes me?
- That's right.
Thank you!
Good, good.
You naughty Haruta.
I heard from Hina. That must have been rough.
It really felt like time froze.
Did you know about that?
He didn't know that Captain Kurosawa is Hina's dad.
Am I the only one who didn't know?
Show some interest.
I think you guys make a good couple.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Fine. I'll go get seconds.
That's irrelevant. What's so fine about that?
If you insist...
Hey, eat the carrots too.
Why are you giving him advice?
What?
You like him, don't you?
Stop.
I'll tell him for you.
No, you won't.
I think you two suit each other.
Thanks for the food.
Naruse, you're done?
[Keyhole-Shaped Ancient Burial Mounds]
Keyhole-shaped ancient burial mounds?
Oh, right!
I want to ask you a favor.
What is it?
You have one new message.
Big Brother, as I mentioned this afternoon,
Dad has something to tell you, too.
If you want to meet up, give me a call.
It hasn't changed at all.
How many years has it been?
I'll be forty-one tomorrow,
so it's been twenty-three years?
- Shino, is your birthday tomorrow?
- Yeah.
Let's celebrate!
Won't you be in Ishigaki?
My flight is in the morning, so I'll be back in Tokyo that evening.
By the way, did you think of what you're going to say to the class?
That's right...
I still haven't grasped the situation. Why me?
It's because we were invited.
- Here.
- Okay.
[Come Back, Seniors!]
"Come back, Seniors"?
It's a request from your alma mater.
Every year they invite seniors in different fields to teach a class.
But... I've never taught before.
And I'll be alone?
You can bring someone to assist you.
Then why me?
Why not? You're just going to sleep away your day anyway.
- I've got lots of things to do.
- Like what?
Watching TV, reading manga, watching more TV...
So there's nothing to do!
You joined the company after our great captain inspired you.
Maybe students will be inspired by you, and become a CA.
I'm not great at all. I don't have any self-confidence.
Okay, okay...
There are no issues with the weather.
The visibility is all clear.
Yes, Sir. Oh!
Will this be enough fuel?
[Magozaburo Karasuma | Dispatcher]
Considering the weight and the winds, that should be just right.
You're the best, Karasuma!
Well, have a great flight today.
Karasuma, did something good happen to you?
Not really. Let me ask you the same, Captain?
Nothing really happened.
I'm so curious.
Well, well...
Everything will work out in the end!
(T/N: It's a dialect of Ishigaki Island, Okinawa.)
Haru is clumsy and sometimes runs around in circles,
but he's a kind and honest person.
What am I doing?
- That's crazy!
- Tell me about it.
Good afternoon!
Hina, we heard.
About what?
"Is it okay to fall in love with you?" I don't hate the confession.
- Excuse me?
- Come on.
There is nothing to be embarrassed about.
But he's thickheaded to understand, so we gave him the right encouragement.
We told him it was a love confession.
But I never said anything like that.
- Sure. Whatever.
- Don't try to fool us.
What? Wait a minute.
Did Haru tell you that?
Yeah! He looked all happy and everything.
It was annoying how confused he looked.
I was really annoyed by his confused act.
Who does he think he is?
He said, "This is not me."
It was unbelievable.
After checking your assigned aircraft and repair details on the schedule,
please proceed unerringly and avoid delaying the next flight.
The most important key to this is team work
and completing the tasks without error within the allotted time.
Well, I just became a cabin attendant.
I overslept, and messed up a lot on the first day.
So I wasn't allowed to board the airplane.
- Sir?
- Yes?
Why did you decide to become a CA, Mr. Haruta?
Well... you see...
[Soichi Haruta]
At my old job, everyone was really close like a family.
I really loved that aspect.
As for the job as CAs,
the bond of the team is incredibly important.
So naturally, I thought I'd like that.
I thought it'd be a good fit for me.
That's why.
Mr. Shinomiya and Mr. Haruta, thank you for coming!
- Thank you!
- See you around.
- See you.
- Thanks.
Thank you!
Bye-bye!
Shino, can I go to the restroom?
I'll go greet the teacher.
Okay.
[Ossan's Love: In The Sky]
You look exhausted.
Well...
I don't think so.
I just wanted to check the condition of my fellow crewmate.
Captain Kurosawa,
I'm sorry for causing trouble before.
Well...
there are times when you can't express your thought well,
and that might cause misunderstandings.
I know how hard you work.
I'm always on your side.
Because you always look after us, Captain,
we can concentrate on our work with reassurance.
Thank you.
Well...
even I... have things
I feel lost over.
Thank you for the drink.
Where did Shino go?
Amazing. I had no idea you could play the piano.
Well, but I don't even know the name of this song.
- You don't?
- No.
My music teacher taught it to me
after school.
It's kind of a sad song, huh?
Shall we head home?
Wait! I want to play, too.
Can you play?
- Not at all.
- What?
Let's see...
- Huh?
- What's that?
- Twinkle, twinkle. ♪ Twinkle, twinkle... ♪
- Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star?
"Do". Yeah, that's it.
- Twice?
- ♪ Do, do. ♪ Yeah. ♪ So, so. ♪
♪ La, la, so. ♪ Yeah.
♪ Fa, fa, mi, mi, re, re, do. ♪
- Do that again.
- Again? It's boring. I want to play a different song.
A different song?
Next, the pilot of the new route,
Captain Musashi Kurosawa will say a few words.
Good morning, everyone. I'm Kurosawa, the captain of the flight to Ishigaki.
As the captain of the flight to Ishigaki,
[Kanta Michibata | Mechanic]
I'm very honored to take on
this important responsibility. Also...
All 180 seats have been booked.
We'll also sell commemorative items in-flight today.
Let's sell lots of them!
Haruta, are you prepared for the announcements?
Yes. I thought of a fun way to greet everyone.
It doesn't have to be funny. Please do the ordinary one.
I know that! But since it's the first flight to Ishigaki,
I thought I'd try speaking in a dialect.
Don't do that.
I smell disaster.
Why don't you try it now?
- Right now?
- Yes, right now.
Good of the morning, thanks be to you for making of the choice
to fly with Tenku Peach Airline—
Stop, stop, stop!
That's terrible! It's a disaster, all right.
If you're going to do it, please be serious.
I was being really serious.
It'd be a problem if the passengers can't understand the important notices. Right, Captain?
Precious...
Captain?
It would be nice to add a few words.
Since this is a special flight,
it'd be best to stick to the basics.
Okay, I understand.
- Well, let's have a good flight.
- Likewise, Sir.
Captain, could you spare me some time?
- About that?
- Yes, about that.
[Ossan's Love: In The Sky]
It's about the text message you sent me.
I'm sorry. It was a bit... long, wasn't it?
- There's been a misunderstanding.
- What?
You asked me, "Is it okay to fall in love with you?"
And my answer to that...
You said "okay", right?
Well... actually, at that time, I...
was just holding my head like this.
And said, "What do I do?" My hand gesture probably looked like a circle.
- That was a circle, wasn't it?
- No, it wasn't.
I was just holding my head!
Like this! B-Besides,
I wouldn't answer "yes" or "no" without confirming your intention.
It was a love confession.
It means I love you.
Captain, do you mean you like me as...?
It's love.
Lo...
W-Well, my respect for you hasn't changed.
However, I'm not sure about accepting your love and being your lover...
Wait, listen!
I also really like you, Captain.
What I meant was... Captain, what I feel for you is...
I love you!
Captain, please don't dance.
I know this is a selfish request,
but I'd like to focus on my job as a cabin attendant right now.
Captain, please don't dance. Captain, Captain!
Captain, please don't dance. Please!
Right now, I'd like to focus on my job as a CA.
I'm begging you, please!
I got it.
Thanks for telling me that.
- I'm sorry.
- Not at all.
Thank you.
What?
He understood me, right?
He... gave up?
Thank goodness!
I got through to him.
They're trying to make you jealous.
Naughty Haruta, you're intentionally pushing me away
and trying to make me jealous?
Wait... is that really the case?
Wait... did I just get...
rejected?
Neko, what's wrong?
I'll be right there.
What? It wasn't you?
Right.
I never asked him, "Is it okay to fall in love?"
What? Then, who did?
I mean, I'm sorry.
It's totally fine.
Probably... he was told that by someone he doesn't even like.
There's nothing to worry.
There's nothing going on between Haru and me.
I see. I'll be off, then.
Sorry, have a good flight!
Attention all passengers of
Tenku Peach Airlines 348 for Osaka.
[Kurumi Naruse]
[Reject]
[Kurumi Naruse: Call Rejected]
[Tenku Peach Airlines]
Shino, you're the birthday boy. You should be resting.
I can't just sit around.
Haruta won't be any help to us. He just eats all the food.
Hina, let's make the cake together.
I'm already on it.
[Happy Birthday]
Oh, no... the oranges!
- Crap!
- Hey, watch it!
Just relax.
Shino, apparently the "Come back, Seniors" was a great success.
They contacted me to pass along their thanks.
Kids these days are so earnest.
They even listened to someone like me.
What about Haru? Did he do well?
Next is "so". ♪ So, so... ♪
♪ La, la... ♪
Well, the dough...
didn't rise so well.
What about Haruta?
Did Haru mess up or something?
No! Haru did great, of course.
- Really? Thank goodness.
- Yeah.
Is it going to rain?
Oh, my.
The wind is too strong.
They might not be able to land in this condition.
Wait...
Are they going to hold out in the air for a little longer?
- The wind is too strong.
- Roger that.
We'll stand by in the air.
He might be late.
I hope they could land in Tokyo safely.
- Wait, Hina...
- Yes?
You see...
I bought a present, but I forgot it at my place.
What? What are you going to do?
- What should I do?
- Are you asking me?
- What do I do? What do I do?
- Calm down. Are you okay?
What do I do? What do I do?
- Relax, just relax!
- I'm going to go get it.
Are you leaving?
- Excellent work.
- We're back.
Excellent work.
- Excellent work.
- We're back.
Excellent work! Excellent work!
- My shoulders are so stiff.
- Excellent work!
- Dispatch!
Everyone, great work today.
Thank you, Sir.
Thanks to all of you, our first flight to Ishigaki Island went smoothly.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you.
I'll be off.
Naruse, Shino's birthday party is today. Hey!
- I'll pass.
- Why? Come.
What's his deal?
He was in such a hurry. Did something happen?
- Did you see that?
- We sure did.
I bet he caused more trouble.
- Again?
- He's a troublemaker.
We finished the tea earlier.
- I'll go buy some more quickly.
- I'll go.
You can't. This is your birthday, Shino.
It's fine! It's going to rain soon. Just wait here.
Wait!
All right. See you tomorrow.
Hello, this is Tenku Peach Airlines.
Yes?
Naruse?
What?
What's with him? Why didn't he say anything?
His father?
I've tried calling him several times, but...
Dad is in critical condition. He might not make it in time.
Was he carrying all the burden by himself?
I mean, I... Damn it!
Where in the world is Naruse?
I knew it.
♫ It's amazing how you can warm up the cold winter ♫
[Hina, there's something I have to tell you]
♫ I've noticed small changes ♫
♫  in you before everyone else has.
When you follow her with your eyes, you look sorrowful ♫
[Haru is clumsy and sometimes runs around in circles, but he's a kind and honest man.]
♫ Even if I wish for one or two, I'm not her ♫
♫ I can't be her substitute ♫
Shino!
Naruse!
I've been looking all over for you.
Naruse, go see your dad.
Are you listening to me?
What?
He just...
passed away.
♫ Please stay with me ♫
Stop.
Let go! What do you think you're doing?
I can't just leave you alone!
I'm sorry. I had no idea.
Shino!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry...
I... like Haruta.
I...
like Haruta.
[Ossan's Love: In The Sky]