Is it okay to fall in love with you, Haruta?
- Pardon?
- I can kiss just anyone.
I'll stop loving you. Please give me more time.
You don't like me, do you?
Do you like someone else?
It seems like... I love you.
l love you, Haruta.
I'd like you to go out with me. First, let's date for a week as a trial!
Huh?
[Day 1]
[Soichi Haruta | Cabin Attendant]
Good morning.
Just for a week to start!
It's my only wish in life.
Okay, okay, then let's do this.
We don't even have to date, but for one week...
you'll spend time with me and follow my plans.
[Kaname Shinomiya | Mechanic]
After that, I'll ask you again how you feel.
Okay? That would be fine, right?
W-Well... that would be...
Shino, good morning.
Maybe you should change your way to address me.
- Huh?
- "Shinomy" might work.
Shi-chan? Miya-chan? Kanamecho?
- I prefer Shino...
- Okay.
Now!
Pull a card for day one.
Huh? A c-card?
I've written down events I've thought up.
But if you don't like them, don't hesitate to tell me.
I'll take the one on the edge.
"Let's make omelet rice"?
You picked a basic one at the beginning.
Basic?
Good morning.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- Am I not good enough?
- No.
Why did I do that?
- N-Naruse...
- Shinomiya.
Did you check the issue with the aircraft temperature control?
[Ryu Naruse | Copilot]
Sorry, I'll check it later.
Thanks.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- Good morning!
[Musashi Kurosawa | Captain]
Morning.
- Haru rejected me.
- Did you say rejected?
Excuse me.
Captain, um...
About Hina...
I don't want to hear it right now.
We can't talk about that in a place like this!
I'm sorry.
What? What happened?
Huh? How did this happen?
Attention all passengers!
I'm very ashamed to be asking you all this, but...
where in the world is the love's emergency exit?
[Soichi Haruta]
[Ryu Naruse]
[Kaname Shinomiya]
[Musashi Kurosawa]
[Ossan's Love: In The Sky]
Have a good day.
You, too.
[6th Flight | Our Seven Days]
I have so many questions I want to ask.
Kurosawa!
What? You're trying it out for a week?
[Haruka Neko | Cabin Attendant]
Yeah. I guess it ended up that way.
With whom?
Shino, right?
What?
It's too obvious.
But why the weird method?
You don't want to date him, do you?
- No.
- Then why did you agree?
I guess...
I do like Shino.
It's really fun to be around him.
Although I don't have romantic feelings for him,
it's unbearable to lose his friendship.
You're too naive.
The world works this way.
- Good morning.
I would like to introduce a new CA who will be joining our team today.
Good morning. I worked at Dubai Airlines until two months ago.
I'm Reiji Shishimaru, 35 years old.
[Reiji Shishimaru | Cabin Attendant]
I look forward to working with you.
Welcome.
Shishimaru?
Nice to meet you.
- I'm Shishimaru.
- I'm Soichi Haruta.
I'm 35 as well. Nice to meet you.
We are the same age?
Haruppi, nice to meet you.
Haruppi?!
And you...
can call me Reiji.
Reiji?
- My name is Neko.
- Like "cat"?
- Meow!
- Meow, huh?
Nice to meet you.
These are the tablets we use for every briefing.
- To use it, you...
- Oh, I figured it out on my own earlier.
Amazing!
But the weather map is a little tricky.
- Here, right?
- Yes.
Flights to Sapporo will get a bit of crosswind, I see.
Hey Tenpichi, tell me the speed of crosswind.
25 knots.
H-Hold on, there's a function like that?
Amazing!
Haruta, you're in charge of teaching Reiji about our duties, okay?
Is there anything he doesn't know?
We'll have to throw him a welcome party.
I'll look for a place.
Are there any foods you can't eat?
I'm fine with everything.
Me, too.
I'm not picky.
Got it.
I'll let you guys know once I decided.
I'll go introduce myself to everyone else.
Competent men are something else.
[Misae Jumonji | Cabin Attendant]
Most guys would just ask what you wanted to eat, right?
[Tamiyo Arisugawa | Cabin Attendant]
He asked if there is any food we can't eat.
Wh-What's the difference?
He has a good place in mind.
Don't you find him too mysterious?
- What do you mean?
- He's 35, handsome,
is capable at work, friendly, and has a good personality.
Such a man does really exist?
Huh? You're the opposite in every way.
- You're inverse Reiji!
- Inverse Reiji?
Oh, Naruse!
- Are you here for Shino?
- Not really.
Shino!
[Kanta Michibata | Mechanic]
Shino?
The cause was a malfunction with the pack system, after all.
We're repairing it now to return it to normal.
Understood. I'll tell the captain.
Huh? Was that it?
- What?
- You came all the way out here. There's nothing else?
Well...
Are you free this Saturday?
- Huh?
- Well...
Sunday would work too, I guess.
I have plans this weekend. I'm sorry. What's up?
It's nothing.
It's fine.
See you around.
Naruse!
I've started...
dating Haruta.
- What?
- Well, I mean...
we're not really dating yet. We're trying out for a week.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Just do whatever you like.
What?
Why are you angry?
- Hey!
- It's your daddy!
- Thank you very much.
- You're welcome.
- Nina, Nina, Nina!
- Say bye-bye!
- Bye-bye!
- Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
That pretty much covers everything.
There's nothing else I can teach you.
- Do you think I'll be okay?
- You're perfect.
Thanks.
Geez.
You like kids, don't you, Haruppi?
Are you married?
No, no.
How about you, Reiji?
I'm single.
The only people who like me are guys.
What?
I totally get that.
Is it the same for you?
- Don't even ask.
- But, you know,
- I'm fine with either guys or girls.
- Huh?
Whether you like someone depends on the person, you know?
Well... that's.... I suppose.
It's shocking that Haruta turned down Hina.
[Magozaburo Karasuma | Dispatcher]
Did I back out for the sake of my daughter's happiness for nothing?
What's going to happen to me?
What's going to happen? What's going to happen?
Nothing's going to happen!
- What was that?
- Huh?
Sorry, I was so absorbed in thoughts.
Sorry about that.
- Nothing will happen? Are you okay?
- Oh, I was just...
- Cheers!
This is a welcome party for Reiji, and a party to comfort Hina!
- Hey, don't say that!
- Jumonji!
- What's going on?
- Her heart was broken.
- Don't spill the beans, Neko.
- Why not?
[Hina Tachibana | PR Staff]
- By a coworker?
- It's Haruta.
- Haruppi?
- Huh? Haruppi?
- Haruppi? Haruppi?
- He's way too unreliable.
- He's middle-aged on the outside, but a toddler on the inside!
- It's terrible.
Haru has his charms, too!
Haruppi was showing me around today.
He is unreliable, but he's kind to everyone.
He's an incredibly nice guy.
Well, I suppose he is.
You're a lovely person to fall for a man like that.
But he did turn me down.
In that case... Waiter, another bottle, please.
Drink your sorrow away tonight.
- Drink up, drink up!
- That's just juice!
- What are you doing?
- Putting it on the rice...
[Day 1 | Let's Make Omelet Rice]
Why are you doing that?
When cutting it with a knife...
- There you go!
- That's amazing!
I was worried at first and wondering how this week would be,
but I realized this was the same Shino I've always known.
[Day 2]
Shino, Shino...
- What is this?
- Right, it's my recommendation.
- Your recommendation?
- Take whatever you like.
This is so difficult.
[Day 2 | Let's Make a Toy]
Shino, you're good at this.
- I need to assemble the three wings...
- Here, I'm done.
That's amazing!
The propeller! The propeller!
It's fragile!
- The tapioca pearls went into my mouth.
- It's delicious.
[Day 3 | Let's Drink Bubble Tea]
- I've always wanted to try it. My first bubble tea.
- Your first bubble tea.
Nothing feels different between us.
What does it mean to date?
[Day 4 | Let's Go To a Bathhouse]
It's been so long since I've come to a bathhouse.
- It's so boring coming alone.
- Totally!
Crap, I can't see! Help!
Oh!
I drew a line between friendship and love.
- Was I the one who's too self-conscious?
- I want to drink coffee with milk.
Maybe I should face Shino without any prejudices?
[Day 5]
Captain.
What an intense atmosphere.
Let's work hard today.
Let's work hard.
I brought this situation upon myself.
I have to redeem myself by working hard,
or I'll be a failure as a human being!
Can I help you, Sir?
You have your ticket, so next is the security check.
- Thank you so much!
- It's my pleasure.
These are the flyers for the airport!
Huh? I-I'm sorry! I'll fix it right away!
- Give me a break!
- Haruta!
- Y-Yes?
You're on standby this afternoon, right?
I need you to be on the flight to Matsuyama. Can you do it?
- Of course I can!
- Really?
- I'll go put out the flyers.
- No, I'll correct my own mistake.
- Let me do it.
- I'll be right back.
What?
What did you think about the Fukuoka flight the other day that diverted to Kansai?
Even if I were on board,
I might have turned back.
Is that right?
What do you think, Naruse?
I think he made his decision too early.
You would have stalled a little longer?
Yes. I might have found another approach.
So he shouldn't have turned around?
That's what I think.
Why did I step aside?
- What are you talking about?
- It's nothing.
Hina has been going through a lot.
Are you referring to Haruta?
I heard he's dating Shinomiya now.
Are you okay?
Is that... the truth?
It's the truth, indeed.
What? L-Listen... You know, I... I...
Well...
Hina said she liked Haruta, so I stepped aside.
I did a "go-around" knowing it'll break my heart.
Haruta is easily swayed by others.
I personally heard this from Shinomiya.
I don't wish for anything more than our current relationship.
I won't get in the way of your love.
He did wish for it, and now he's getting in my way.
No, Haruta just has to refuse him point-blank.
- He doesn't love him, anyway.
- Obviously, he doesn't.
It's Shinomiya's fault for seducing him.
- It's Haruta's fault.
- It's Shinomiya's!
- It's Haruta! Haruta!
- It's Shinomiya! Shinomiya!
- It's Haruta!
- I told you, it's Shinomiya!
I told you, it's Haruta!
- It's Shinomiya!
- Haruta!
- Shinomiya! Shinomi...
- Do you want to fight? Huh?
Descent.
Roger.
I'm sorry.
Nevertheless, Naruse...
why are you sticking up for Shinomiya?
I'm not really sticking up for him.
Is it love?
What?
Naruse... are you in love?
Huh? I... What?
What? What?
What's wrong?
- What's the matter?
- Huh?
- What's wrong? Sit down.
- What? Huh?
- Sit down. Calm down.
- No, no, no way!
Don't put that in the pot!
Naruse, Naruse... Listen to me.
When it comes to those two, our interests are aligned, you see?
You have...
I have...
Captain,
why don't we go get some relief?
[Ossan's Love: In The Sky]
I'm ready.
- Let's do this!
- Yeah!
I'll send it flying! Ding!
Okay.
Wait!
What's wrong?
- What is it?
- Over there.
- Huh?
- Look over there.
What?
How's the new guy doing?
[Let's Go To a Batting Cage]
He's amazing.
He was working overseas, right?
Yeah.
He's a quick learner.
He does everything fast and perfectly.
He's totally different from me.
Are you feeling anxious now, Haruta?
Well...
To be honest, I am.
Everything I do is half-assed.
That's why I wanted to do my job properly at least.
And I'm trying, but...
You're up next, Haruta.
Okay.
Can you hear them?
Not a thing.
And this feels kind of futile...
Right?
Why are we hiding like burglars?
You're right.
We shouldn't be sneaking around.
- Let's go hit.
- What?
Batting.
- Good luck!
- Don't underestimate me.
[Home Run]
You did it!
- You're incredible!
- What just happened? It's too loud.
You hit a home run!
That's awesome!
- Captain?
- Naruse?
You're going to bunt? What? Why?
I didn't know what you like, so I bought drinks randomly...
W-Well...
C-Cap...
Thanks.
I'll leave them here.
How unexpected that we all meet here.
I know.
So you two are dating?
- No...
- No, we're not.
But, you know,
I heard rumors that you were.
Well, that's...
I gave him a week to consider.
Like a trial period.
What?
What? A trial period?
A trial period?
Is there such a mail-order-like romance?
I wonder if you can return the goods.
Instant love?
- Haruta.
- Yes?
Is this the reason you rejected Hina?
Captain, that's not the case.
Ding-dong, ding-dong.
Whooo! Whoo-hoo!
Fourth batter and first baseman Kurosawa. Woo-hoo!
Does anyone want beer? Beer, anyone?
Fall back, Kurosawa! Retire already!
Fall back, you idiot!
Fourth batter and first baseman Kurosawa. Woo-hoo!
- What a duffer, Haruta!
- Why did you come here?
Who knows?
Bring it on!
- Three strikes.
- I'm telling you
- to pay attention to me.
- Ouch, ouch, ouch!
- Troublemaker, Haruta!
- Me? Me?
Come to my bat.
- Haruta!
- Me again?
[Day 6]
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
This is terrible.
Young man!
- I have a favor to ask of you.
- Yes, what can I do for you?
I want to change this flight to an earlier one. Can you do that?
Yes, I understood. It'll take a moment.
What?
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry I'm late. Sorry.
- Is everything okay?
- It's fine. I'm sorry.
I told you our study meeting starts at 2 p.m., didn't I?
You did. I'm sorry, let's get started.
Where's your tablet?
Haruta, Haruta!
You've been holding onto a passenger's ticket, haven't you?
- Ticket?
- Yes.
I want to change this flight to an earlier one. Can you do that?
Come on.
It's going to take off soon!
- Sorry, I'll take care of it now!
- Wait, wait!
The ground staff has already resolved it.
Is that true?
- Thank goodness.
- Seriously.
Holding on to a passenger's ticket is unheard of.
- I'm sorry.
- This affects the company's reputation.
Get yourself together!
I will... I'm so sorry.
Haruta.
One second.
Yes?
I'm really sorry.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry. I was trying to do everything right, but...
Don't do everything at once. Be responsible for one task at a time.
- Yes, Sir.
- These are the basics.
Yes, Sir. I'm sorry.
You'll be fine.
I know you can do it.
Thank you.
Right.
- You're home?
- Welcome home.
Are you tired?
I was a little sleepy.
Let's draw the sixth card, Shino.
You don't have to push yourself.
I'm not pushing myself at all.
There!
This one.
"A relaxing DVD viewing."
- Relaxing.
Oh, thanks.
- You'll get cold, Shino.
- I'm fine.
Let's share, then. Take half.
This is warm.
Why did she fall down at the crucial moment?
Oh, no.
They're in danger.
I knew she was going to die.
- She's not going to make it.
- I hate this.
It's going to get her leg.
What was that?
[Day 7]
You've been working hard.
You, too.
You've caught a cold, haven't you?
But it's Reiji's first flight today.
He'll need me, his partner.
Well, I'll be off!
Take care.
Hey!
- Haruta?
- Haruta!
- What's the matter?
[Ossan's Love: In The Sky]
Seriously? Crap!
I'm done for it. I have a flight.
I'm sorry, Captain.
I've sent another CA. Go home and rest.
- I can still go.
- I said, go home!
Captain...
You probably think it's just a cold.
But what happens if you pass out on the flight?
Not only you can't provide service,
but what about your duty to protect passengers' lives?
If you can't see your surroundings, you're going to lose something important one day.
A self-centered person like you has no right to be in the air!
You...
need to seriously re-examine yourself.
Haruppi.
People love you.
No one else would scold you so seriously.
Gosh, I really hate myself.
I always mess up and cause trouble for everyone.
But it's good that you've realized that now.
It's never too late to change.
Come on.
Haru-haru-haru-ppi! You can change!
What was that?
I've got to go to my first flight.
Sorry.
Do you want a souvenir?
Cookies from Okinawa? Fried donuts?
- A lion-dog statue?
- A lion-dog statue.
- A lion-dog statue...
Shishimaru, the lion-dog?
(T/N: Shishi means a lion.)
- Okay, okay! Get going.
- I'm off.
Stop messing around already.
What a weird guy.
Thanks for the food.
You should go to bed.
Shino... the last card.
Don't worry about it today.
But I want to.
All right.
Here.
Okay.
"Let's hold hands."
Thank you.
This week really flew by, didn't it?
I...
want to tell you something, Shino.
Me, too.
I...
won't date you, Haruta.
I'm sorry about this week.
What did you want to tell me?
I...
realized after spending this week with you,
that I really do love you, Shino.
But it's not...
a romantic feeling.
As a person, as my senior,
and as my friend, I love you.
That's why...
I can't... date you, Shino.
By telling you this, our relationship might change,
or things may get awkward,
but I needed to be honest with you about this.
I'm sorry.
I get it. I get it.
Thank you for being honest with me.
Thank you.
[Ossan's Love: In The Sky]
I...
told Shino that I can't date him.
So?
I just wanted to tell you.
I see.
I'm really sorry about the other day.
I was just forcing my feelings onto you.
I'm sorry about that.
That's why...
What?
It's nothing.
Naruse!
Good night.
♫ I saw my happiness reflecting in your eyes ♫
♫ I've been searching for a future full of laughter ♫
♫ Your simple words of good morning delight my world ♫
♫ It's amazing  ♫
♫ How you can warm up the cold winter ♫
Do you want some hotpot udon?
♫ Because I've always been watching you, I've noticed ♫
♫ Small changes in you ♫
♫ Before everyone else has ♫
♫ When you follow her with your eyes, you look sorrowful ♫
Why?
Why this trial?
♫ Even if I wish for one or two, I'm not her ♫
I guess...
my pride gets the worst of me, although my chances were slim.
Besides, it was you who stirred me up.
You said, Haruta and I would be a good match.
♫ Till the day you wake up ♫
I thought I have at least 2% chance with him.
♫ It's a fleeting dream I saw in a pipe dream ♫
♫ While letting the short white breath, and say,
"I'm lonely" and "I'm sad" ♫
♫ I wanted to say those words by your side ♫
I...
wouldn't need a trial.
Haruppi.
♫ Who should I tell about the sudden snow? ♫
Where is your umbrella?
Ta-da, it's a lion-dog.
♫ How about you? ♫
My first flight was great.
♫ It seems like it was a stupid question ♫
♫ Your gaze just answered all my questions ♫
What's wrong?
♫ I want you to follow me with your eyes ♫
I just...
♫ Even if the third and fourth come true, I feel lifeless ♫
♫ I can never be your first ♫
I see.
You've done your best, right?
Haruppi.
♫ It's a fleeting dream I saw in broad daylight ♫
Wh-What are you doing?
Stop!
I...
I'll make you forget him.
H-Hold on!
Naruse! Naru... Wait!
Stop it!
You...
need to stop toying with people's feelings.
I'm serious.
What?
But...
I don't know what to do.
I thought...
I could kiss anyone.
But now...
I don't want to do it with anyone but you.
Good morning!
Good morning! Morning!
- What?
- Are you kidding me?
- Is this for real?
- I can't believe it!
What is it? What is it? Morning.
"Executive Officer, Reiji Shishimaru."
Executive Officer?
What?
Excuse me.
We've been waiting for you,
Captain Kurosawa.
I know this is sudden, but...
[Reiji Shishimaru | Executive Officer]
[Ossan's Love: In The Sky]