I'm afraid they'll disturb my dreams
The wind blows, the night falls, and the night returns
There's a ray of light
Time is like a needle that stitches every morning and night
The memories engraved deep in my heart
The eyes are turned back, counting the seconds
It's you
I'm afraid they'll disturb my dreams
The wind blows, the night falls, and the night returns
It's you
I'm afraid they'll disturb my dreams
The wind blows, the night falls, and the night returns
It's you
Even if the clouds are vast, the mountains are hard to reach
The road is hard to cross, the clouds are hard to cross
I meet you, even if there are two thousand seasons
I'm afraid they'll disturb my dreams
The Wind and The Sword
Episode 16
Fang Xian, the thing I gave you yesterday, give it back to me.
What is it?
That letter.
Letter?
This one?
Yes.
What's inside?
Don't! Give it to me!
What?
Are you giving it to me or not?
I'm not.
I said I'm not giving it to you.
Give it to me!
A letter?
Why are you giving me a letter?
If I give you a letter, are you going to give me a letter?
Are you?
I'm not giving it to you.
You're so annoying!
Fang Xian!
Grandpa!
I know you love each other.
But this morning, you were just like this.
Look at you.
Here, take it.
This is a divorce letter?
What does this mean?
It's so obvious!
Do you know that your marriage
is a promise between me and his grandfather?
How can you just say that
you can divorce me?
Grandpa, I'm sorry. I was wrong.
Don't worry.
I promise I'll give you an explanation.
Mei Yuan!
I want you to swear in front of me
that you'll never divorce me!
What?
I saw you make a vow here today.
You'll never divorce me.
If you break it, you'll be punished.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Don't worry.
Mei Yuan has sworn in front of me.
You can just stand there
and swear in front of me.
If that's the case,
don't blame me for being rude.
Aren't they having a good time?
Young Master, I've been waiting for you for a long time.
Feng Qingyang.
Young Master, I did it for your own good!
Unlock the antidote! Unlock the antidote!
Unlock the antidote!
Young Master, I'm just a pharmacist.
If you keep shaking it,
I'll break my neck.
It's broken.
You're even calling yourself a pharmacist.
You even used up my martial arts.
What kind of a ring is this?
Don't worry, Young Master.
The time has not yet come.
When the time comes,
I'll definitely give you the antidote.
You're just playing around.
Young Master, tell me.
What other side effects do you have
besides the use of martial arts?
I do have some.
Tell me.
I want to try it out.
Can I exchange bodies with you?
Exchange bodies?
Tell me in detail.
Young Master.
No, no, no, no.
Qingyang, don't go!
My dear,
we've acquired so many storefronts.
What are they for?
You understand, right?
Tianxiang Pond has been in a hot business.
It's a must to expand.
We're expanding?
To the opposite of Tianxiang Pond?
How can we lose money like this?
You don't understand.
I'm building a workshop.
I want to wake up the people's spirit of martial arts.
Just like that man.
That man?
Tianyu, wait a minute.
Do you have a crush on him?
How do you know, Young Master?
Have you seen him?
Actually, I've heard from Miss.
It's said that that man,
the good master of Zhang Yi,
is a famous and honest man.
I'm leaving.
Then it's not me.
After all, the inner corner of the outer ship of the hero is a horror.
I have to perform well.
Tianxiang Pond
Tianyu,
tell me.
The broken shop I spent a lot of money to buy,
how did it become like this?
Miss, I think this kind of shop
is necessary to buy with a lot of money.
But I want to lose the money.
This...
Miss, you're here.
Fang Xian,
what did you do?
I...
I just lost a little bit of my strength.
But the time is limited.
I can only do this.
Miss,
if we open the shop on time,
there will be no problem.
Don't worry.
Okay, okay.
Open the shop, right?
Tianyu,
send an official notice.
The shop is open today.
50 taels per person.
What?
You paid so much for me.
You don't deserve 50 taels?
Miss,
I know you love me.
But it's not worth it.
You're worth it.
Miss,
you don't really have to
set the price of our workshop so high for me.
I just made a little contribution.
Don't think I won't dare to
hire you because you
used my body to swear.
When will you
be in charge of the business?
Can you really
do business like this?
You're smart.
You're smart enough to go out
and borrow people with just an umbrella.
Or do you think
you can make me moved
by taking me home?
Childish.
If you catch a cold,
you'll be doomed.
Miss,
are you worried about me?
Oh,
you brought two umbrellas.
You took one out on purpose.
Fang Xian,
you're so thoughtful.
Miss,
I didn't mean to be unkind.
I just
want to get closer to you.
Be careful.
Wait a minute.
Did something happen again?
Is it about the training room again?
Did you make a lot of money again?
Did Fang Xian
make a mess again?
No.
What's wrong with me?
You didn't go to the training room today?
No.
Okay.
I'll see who's
doing me a favor today.
Miss.
Wait for me.
It's okay.
Don't wait for me.
Don't...
Don't mind me.
Keep practicing.
I'm here to ask
if you're satisfied
with the service
of our training room today.
Miss,
your hobby is really simple.
Here's the thing.
I'm the owner of this shop.
I just want to ask you
if there's anything
that you're not satisfied with.
Just ask me.
Don't...
Don't hide it from me.
I'll try to meet your requirements.
Okay?
I understand.
Look, Miss.
It's so dirty here.
You're so unkind
to clean here.
You're the first one to open the shop.
Because I'm happy,
I invite you to have a drink.
How about it?
Okay.
So that's your hobby.
I told you.
You're not drunk tonight.
Should I practice?
It's okay, sir.
Miss is always so rich.
I'll drink it.
You guys drink as you like.
Be careful.
Eat well and drink well.
My legs hurt.
Honey,
how about I massage you?
You can massage?
I can't.
Do you want to try?
You're a man.
I didn't expect you to massage women.
And you're still angry.
So you care more about that man?
What?
You care so much about that man?
I just want to know
who is so lucky
to get your love.
Maybe I'm not as lucky as that man.
But I'm sure you don't like
a man who is a man.
Since I'm your husband,
I have more advantages than him.
I don't have the courage to fight for it.
If you like that man who is righteous,
kind and kind,
I'll do it better than him.
A thousand times better.
You...
What are you doing?
Why do you do this?
And you're not a commodity.
You don't have the right to say that.
If you want to leave me,
you can say I'm not hard-working enough.
Why don't you
have a better husband?
You know I'm not lucky.
I'm not lucky.
Where did you get your love from?
From the first time I saw you.
Ying Zhu.
My lady.
Get out.
I don't know why.
But I'll take responsibility.
My lady.
Oh, no.
How could I
take Fang Xian as my mistress?
How can I be worthy of her?
I'm sorry.