I'm afraid they'll disturb my dream.
I've always thought of you, and I'm always in your arms.
There's a book of light and rain.
Time is passing, and every moment is in the memory of the past.
The words are engraved in the book, and the diary is yours.
I'm afraid they'll disturb my dream.
I've always thought of you, and I'm always in your arms.
The diary is yours.
I'm afraid they'll disturb my dream.
The wind is blowing, and it's you.
The clouds are always shining, and the mountains are hard to control.
The road is a pity.
I've met you, even if I'm two thousand years old, what's the point?
The words are engraved in the book, and the diary is yours.
I'm afraid they'll disturb my dream.
The End
Episode 1
Mei Yuan, isn't Fang Xian smoking meat?
Damn it.
I'm a great fan of food and food, and I'm also a great fan of the world.
So I've studied a lot.
I didn't guess the wrong words.
I've seen the family's work, and I've seen the family's work, and I've seen the family's work, and I'm also a great fan of the world.
Wait.
Take a good look.
The family is so great.
Fang Xian's memory is not only the effect of the massage,
but also the clean function.
It's so wonderful.
No.
Shunan, I can't forget it.
It's not worth the time.
Great.
It's great to see the family's work, and the family is so great to see Fang Xian.
She was so clever and prepared.
That's why she's my opponent.
I'm going to the meeting place.
Great.
You won.
My dear, I've done it.
I didn't expect you to be so close to Fang Xian.
Why do you have to work so hard?
There's no chance in the future.
In the future?
In a few days,
I'll be able to see Tian Xiang Chi getting more and more popular.
My chances will be less and less.
So you shouldn't have done that.
You just want to chase after me.
If you can deal with my sister and Fang Xian,
I'll agree to let you chase after me.
Miss Mei Ming, you're drunk.
I won't take the risk.
Then you can take me as a support.
You can agree to help me deal with my sister and Fang Xian.
Miss Mei Ming, in order to become your royal doctor,
I can only use the soul-saving magic.
I'm going to the meeting place.
My dear.
Don't move.
What are you looking at?
When I left the family,
I met a few unfaithful children.
I don't know why they lived in the same place.
The water was sealed by the guards.
Where did they get the water?
The place where the water was kept is just a piece of cake.
The water is used only by those few people.
I'm afraid they can only get the water from the river.
They're all children. It's dangerous to go to the mountains.
It's not like they're just keeping the water from the guards.
Don't worry too much.
I'll ask the imperial doctor to find out.
You helped me once before.
I helped you this time, too.
I'm sorry.
Fang Xian.
Thank you.
Lady.
I want...
No.
Lucky.
Miss Wu,
and Huang anterior.
Come on, tamamer you can go.
When there's nothing else to do,
I'll abandon you for an answer please.
Choose where to go first.
So beautiful!
Thank you, I'm switchingeur.
Look,
an ordinary smile
will pull usOLI to take everything,
Many people have forced them to go out of the city to get water.
They are so selfish.
They didn't even let me go.
Ting Yu, do you still know what it is?
It's...
The new minister asked us to prepare the tombstone to make the water.
Who is the new minister?
Tell me.
It's...
Song Kang and Song Da.
Is Song Kang and the watchman saved?
Can we go up and find out about this?
That makes sense.
We can find a chance to talk to Song Kang and Song Da.
You are here.
Father.
The invitation from Song's Mansion.
Congratulations to Song Kang Rongsheng.
Congratulations to the watchman and the beauty.
I am personally honored to be here.
This is my husband, Fang Xian.
I know that Fang Xian is a famous person in Taizhou.
But today's banquet, you have to keep your promise.
This is what a dog can do inside.
You are still laughing.
Lady, why don't I go back first?
All guests are here.
How can I let you leave like this?
Please come in.
Wait.
You have a plan.
Enough.
What occasion is it today?
What are you making?
I'm sorry.
I was so busy today.
I didn't expect to make such a mess.
I was in a bad mood.
Mei Yuan, are you all right?
You are fine, right?
I'm fine.
My wife is here to take care of me.
Song Kang, I won't talk to you anymore.
I don't need you to make me a meal.
I'm asking you.
Are you the one who made the water in the city go crazy?
Why do you ask me?
I'm doing this for your good.
After all, you are going to hand over the court to the people.
I'm just preparing it in advance.
For years,
not only did Marquis Yan Qing give the people a title,
but also gave the people a title of the water in the city.
How about the power?
For years, who has the power to write the title of Marquis Yan Qing?
Is it because you have a good idea?
Song Si Li is serious.
In the case of Mu Yu's death,
Tian Xiang Chi and Si Li are one of the new ones.
That's good.
Since we are in love,
we used to be close friends.
I'm still thinking about you.
I'll send you guys to the banquet.
No need.
We are not in the same boat.
I can't eat this meal.
Let's go.
If you mess with me again,
be careful!
Be careful of what?
Sorry, ma'am.
I'm confused. I didn't know it was you.
You really think you are the master? You still dare to know me?
I was originally...
house arresting you all day long.
Go lose your temper.
Xie climbing is too hard to stand.
You can have it like this!
juk증
Why do you pretend to be
wondering if I'm lying?
Don't別 Tre heir to se9
Santing love,
and Don's daughter to Scushizhu
I won't worry about giving birth at all.
Really?
However,
even if you always收 heart and mind to me,
on your out side, you're very polite.
However, you're sour as you were being sent to me only today.
You seduced me.
And you got bored because of my charm?
People often ask,
how can someone like to beéged
on his wife and children?
You need to be more careful
of being a man.
You shouldOL
You're jealous. You're really...
I didn't expect that.
I'm sorry, girl.
I like you very much.
What?
Look at your moon.