Chancellor Gao,
I am deeply grateful for your help
these past days.
No need to thank me.
If anything,
I am the one who owes you.
I was too wary of you back then.
You are His Majesty's strategist.
You shoulder the fate of the realm.
It was right for you
to be cautious of me.
Hearing you say so
and thinking
of the steamed buns
I've been sending you this past month,
I can finally feel at ease.
It's been over a month.
Is your hand healed?
Yes.
And your legs?
Probably
about the same as yours.
It is already the Zi hour.
Time is running short.
But at least
it is a gentle night.
What is this?
It reads like a farewell letter.
And he tells us not to worry?
Stop worrying.
Huai'an will be fine.
Sir.
CANGYUE TOWER
Mr. Wuyin.
Please rest here.
At dawn, General Fengshan will await you
at Taiqing Hall.
Sir,
don't be uneasy about tonight.
I will stand guard.
I'm not uneasy.
I'm simply wondering
why a prosperous city like Chang'an
produces such folk.
A slave girl who could play the guqin
turned out
to be an assassin.
A peddler who appeared
to be from Tiemo turned out
to be the mastermind.
And then there's Yan Fengshan.
He wants to borrow my troops
to attack his own city.
Dealing with these people
is exhausting.
That's enough for today.
You should rest early as well.
Yes, sir.
As long as you keep quiet,
you will be fine.
We go way back.
I have something to discuss with you.
Don't breathe into my palm.
Two men alone in the dark
at this hour
is strange enough as it is.
Stop laughing.
I'm going to move my hand away.
As long as you don't shout,
my axe
will stay where it is.
Come on.
At least let me light a candle
so I can see
which old acquaintance you are.
We're two grown men alone in the dark.
It's strange enough.
Don't mimic me.
Fine.
- I don't recognize you.
- Hold on.
I'm not some maiden. Why the rush?
Your tone sounds familiar.
Why can't I place it?
Be patient.
You'll know soon enough.
This grows stranger by the moment.
I still don't recognize you.
Wuyin Chong,
you came to Chang'an as a secret envoy
and the Tiemo prince,
so I shall meet you
as the Emperor of Chang'an.
I just want you to know
that I am still alive.
The Xiao imperial line
still has a survivor.
Whatever you discussed
with that traitor Yan Fengshan
won't count.
We do go way back.
The whole world believes you died
in the palace fire.
Who would have thought?
The look in your eyes,
the way you speak,
and even the way you do things
have all changed.
But you are the Emperor of Chang'an.
Why hide your own face?
Why do you think?
To protect myself, of course,
while I deal with Yan Fengshan.
Just as you said,
you are now nothing more
than a fugitive trying to stay alive.
What right have you to supplant
Yan Fengshan and make a pact with me?
You call yourself an emperor,
but do you have any force to command?
Xie Huai'an truly is
the smartest man in the world.
He even guessed every sentence
and every word
you were going to say.
It's the Chou hour.
Come with me.
I'll show you
the force I command.
Please enjoy, sirs.
Why are you staring at me?
Your force isn't here yet anyway.
Who says?
Listen.
That is just one of my guards.
He is there
to keep you from trying anything.
Listen more closely.
Rumor holds that Chang'an
fell into chaos last month.
Xiao Wuyang and Gu Yu vanished,
their fate unknown.
The great strategist Gao Yan
had his legs broken.
He now moves on a cart
and is kept in the palace
as a lantern keeper,
only allowed out at the Chou hour
to deliver memorials to Yan Fengshan.
That Xie Huai'an you mentioned
managed to get Gao Yan out.
A remarkable feat.
I am that force.
The Xiao imperial line
still has a survivor,
and Gu Yu of the Baiwenhu Army
still lives.
Chang'an
is not yet ruled by Yan Fengshan.
Whatever pact you plan to make
with him tomorrow
will not stand.
Chang'an
will change hands again,
and the fight will be
against Yan Fengshan.
If you make a pact with him,
the north will also change hands,
and the fight will be against you.
General Gu,
my people and yours have fought for years.
We have never feared you.
His Majesty,
I,
and the entire city of Chang'an
have been pressed to this state
by Yan Fengshan,
but we have not been defeated.
You are not without fear.
You fear the one
who has been planning all of this for us.
Xie Huai'an is the son of Liu Ziwen.
He's the one who gave you a new face
and the one who helped you survive.
Am I right?
Yes.
The last two generations of the Liu family
produced extraordinary men in succession.
They have used up
decades of Chang'an's fortune.
I understand now.
This night shall be
the most unforgettable of my life.
Tonight makes me
fall in love with Chang'an anew.
Your Majesty, it has been a long time.
We actually met before.
You simply didn't know it was me.
Keeping you hidden at his side
was indeed the best strategy.
But according to the plan,
he should already be
in Yan Fengshan's hands now.
On the road toward killing Yan Fengshan,
all of us must pay a price.
May I have that flask of wine?
Is it for Chancellor Gao?
This painting of you
bears my wish for you.
I hope you can tend flowers,
keep a cat,
nap on the porch,
and live in peace,
even for just one day.
You're awake.
The General has gone to the palace
to meet Wuyin Chong.
He instructed me to treat you as a guest.
I brought you a basin of water
to wipe the blood off.
You knew she lay buried here?
Yes.
And you still chose
to stay in this residence?
Yes.
Were you involved
in her death as well?
- Take care.
- Goodbye.
Yes.
Then you too, must die.
FOR LIU ZIWEN ONLY
This is my plan.
It…
it is far too risky.
Back then,
you did not help my father
get rid of Yan Fengshan.
I will not question
your reasons.
It is
only natural for people
to put themselves first.
I am using your guilt
toward the Liu family
to force your hand.
I am the one going too far.
Mr. Yang.
We act at the Chou hour.
By the Yin hour,
Yan Fengshan will have received the news
and realized you were involved.
You must depart at once.
Zhu Zhilong will be waiting for you
at the Yuelao Temple
50 li west of the city.
After this,
your business in Chang'an and elsewhere
will certainly be affected.
If I prevail in the following days,
I shall repay
every loss you suffer.
Boss.
Boss, what's going on?
Is the court cleaning house?
The books we cannot let anyone see
are over there.
I'll get them.
Boss,
what is wrong with you?
General Fengshan,
my master says
the agreement you and he
were about to reach
does not align with Tiemo's interests,
so it will be set aside for now.
But the army we sent
to hold back the Baiwenhu Army
will not retreat.
Everything will remain as it is.
General, you may rest assured.
I see.
The struggle for Chang'an is not yet over.
My master hopes you will soon become
the one who rules Chang'an.
Old friend,
do not worry about the outcome anymore.
Rest in peace.
General Fengshan.
This life-and-death plan of Gao Yan's
was executed flawlessly
with the people outside.
You were the one handling
all the message delivery, weren't you?
So Gu Yu had been hiding here
for over a month?
No wonder even after
searching all of Chang'an,
we never found a trace.
Gao Yan and Gu Yu actually joined hands.
I accept my loss
in this round.
Cease this pretense.
A man who has served three emperors
has eyes sharper than a blade.
You know perfectly well
if I intend to kill you.
Your eyes are sharp too, General.
All I did was sigh once
while wiping the floor,
and you noticed immediately.
When you were setting this up,
White Hair had already fallen
into my hands.
Otherwise,
I truly would have killed you.
I helped you get into the palace
so you could live out your years in peace.
This is a good place to grow old quietly.
Stay here and behave yourself.
- Sir.
- Come in.
I have conveyed your message
to Yan Fengshan.
But Yan Fengshan has always
been scheming and calculating.
Given the situation,
we should return to Tiemo
as soon as possible.
I understand what you mean,
but Yan Fengshan would not
dare move against us.
Even so, it is time to head back.
FUZE INN
This is a rare treat in Chang'an.
Want one?
Sure.
This end
is most bitter.
You shouldn't
chew too much of it,
or all you'll taste
is bitterness.
Of course I know that.
Twenty-five years ago,
I infiltrated Tiemo as a scout.
I barely had any money.
It was freezing there,
and chewing this was how I kept warm
and stayed awake.
It used to be cheaper than horse fodder.
But now the price has gone up.
A small bundle
costs two liang.
At your request,
the Tiemo forces have held
the Baiwenhu Army in a standoff.
They stand so close
their horses are near nose to nose.
With things so tense,
few merchants dare travel back and forth.
The supply is unstable,
and naturally,
the price rises.
Last night, you staged quite a show.
You did far more
than persuade Wuyin Chong.
The sharp merchants will soon realize
the Tiemo forces will not march south.
When that happens,
the price will naturally fall again.
The whole game has been thrown into chaos,
yet you seem remarkably calm.
Victory and defeat
are commonplace in warfare.
One who cares too much
about gains and losses
cannot be a true commander.
Speaking of which,
you cling to gains and losses quite a bit.
You buried Wei Qianting,
sent Pu Nichuan to his death,
and killed Liu Ziyan with your own hands.
Qingyi has vanished,
and even Wang Pu
was outwitted and killed by you.
All I have left beside me is Zhiying.
Do you intend to kill her too?
Of course.
I care deeply
about settling scores.
On the road of revenge,
I cannot allow even one enemy
to meet a good end.
And forget not,
you're one of them too.
Then
why didn't you kill Yang Chuhao?
He stood by and did nothing.
That is not a capital crime.
I still
have my principles.
Back then, he stood by and did nothing.
Last night, he chose to help you.
I have my principles too.
He will know no peaceful end.
Too bad you won't find him.
Speaking of which,
there is a young man surnamed Su
working under Yang Chuhao.
Do you remember him?
We crossed paths once.
I looked into him.
He is not a Huben member.
Of all involved in Yang's affairs,
Yang himself is the only Huben member.
That boy truly is not.
Anyone who can catch your eye
must have some wits.
To work for Yang Chuhao
and even handle something
as important as the accounts,
wits alone aren't enough.
He must also have a story behind him.
‪He's like you.