This is ...
You bastard.
What is this? What kind of bastard are you?
What kind of bastard makes threats over taking out small private loans?
Yes, Section Chief?
Section Chief?
Hello, this is Cha Soo Yeong.
Detective, I'm the man at the junk yard
whom you asked for help to look for the unregistered vehicle.
Yes, sir?
I don't know if this will help.
I heard there's someone in the area who used to
lend money to the people who ran the unregistered vehicles business.
That person could know the whereabouts of that unregistered vehicle, don't you think?
Someone who lent them money?
He lent money for them to buy the vehicles.
Who is it?
His name is Chim Sa Bong.
Chim Sa Bong?
That's all I know.
Thank you, sir. Thank you so much.
Chim Sa Bong?
What is it?
Could I perhaps see the files from my mom's case 20 years ago again?
Hey, are you at this again?
Asking about that is a yearly event for you, isn't it?
I thought there could be clues I missed by chance.
There's none. Nothing.
Also, the statute of limitations has long expired!
Then... by chance, have you heard of Chim Sa Bong?
Chim Sa Bong?
It seems like he might be a person who knows about the unregistered vehicle, Mucheon 11-A5897.
Hey, I'm busy so I'm hanging up.
Why Chim Sa Bong of all people?
Let it go!
♫ May God protect and preserve our country!
It's mine!
I found 4789.
It's a special suite at Yooseong Mental Hospital.
4789, 4789.
Eom Soo Tak?
Yes, Doctor.
Is it time to take my medicine?
Who are you? Who are you?
You're not that bastard.
Who sent you?
Ha Tae Sik.
Ha Tae Sik? Ha Tae Sik?
Where is it? Ha Tae Sik. Ha Tae Sik.
Joonggeon three-way intersection. Joonggeon three-way intersection.
That's right. The three-way-intersection...
He said he needed a corpse.
When I was eating, he called me and said he needed a corpse.
One that was burnt to a crisp.
The boat was on fire.
I just needed money.
All I did was just put it there!
Someone saw me.
Eom Soo Tak.
That bastard saw you?
I see.
You also saw that bastard.
You also saw him? That bastard?
Continue. And then?
Save me! Please save me!
4789! 4789! 4789!
There's no one else here besides the two of us.
It's okay. Tell me.
So what happened?
Eun Joo...
Eun Joo?
Was that your girlfriend?
Eun Joo.
He killed... Eun Joo in front of my eyes.
That bastard killed your girlfriend?
I'm fine!
I'm... 4789.
4789! 4789! 4789!
It's safe here. It's safe here.
It's safe here. He said it's safe here.
4789, 4789, 4789, 4789.
4789.
You know how I feel.
No! No! You don't know!
You haven't been to hell!
Hell?
Hell!
Dark and suffocating,
repeated excruciating pain every day,
that damned hell!
I have been there too.
That hell.
You too? You came back alive from it, too?
Like me?
I'm still there.
You are?
I resurrected.
I resurrected!
Tell me, Eom Soo Tak.
How did you resurrect from that hell?
Ha Tae Sik told me about this place.
He said I would be safe here.
He hid you here after you ran away?
Did Ha Tae Sik really send you?
Then it's not safe here anymore!
4789! 4789! 4789!
Devil! Devil! Devil bastard! Crazy bastard!
Yellow color... Dol Ak. Dol Ak!
Dol Ak! I saw Dol Ak.
Dol Ak. I can't talk about that.
4789 will protect me.
Eom Soo Tak, be quiet!
Someone is coming.
Hello, I'm from Mucheon Metropolitan Police Agency.
Oh okay.
I have a few questions to ask regarding a case we are investigating.
Do the numbers 4789 ring a bell?
It's a special suite at our hospital.
A hospital room.
What is the name of the admitted patient?
It's that bastard. That bastard is coming.
Be quiet.
Eom Soo Tak!
- Eom Soo Tak, what's wrong? Who are you?
- Doctor, Doctor!
Please help me. That bastard came.
- I understand, so please calm down.
- Doctor! Doctor, save me!
Calm down, okay? Wait just one moment.
Eom Soo Tak, please give me your arm.
Eom Soo Tak!
Calm down, please. Eom Soo Tak!
You're working with that bastard, aren't you?
Don't come any closer! I'll kill him.
This is the safest place for you.
That bastard has come. That bastard is here!
- Don't do something you'll regret. Come on.
- Stay back!
Calm down, please. Eom Soo Tak!
Eom Soo Tak. Eom Soo Tak!
Open the door, quickly!
Hurry! Hurry!
Let's create a suspect.
Someone in his thirties whom we won't be able to identify.
Male. We need a body.
I know a guy who takes care of that stuff.
In return, this is the last deal we make.
Code zero. Code zero.
A patient from Yooseong Mental Hospital has escaped.
I repeat, a patient from Yooseong Mental Hospital has escaped.
You'll need to take measures.
Eom Soo Tak, who escaped from the hospital, is connected to that bastard.
We need the local police, not Mucheon Metropolitan Police Agency,
to catch him quietly.
Okay. I'll let the station in the hospital's vicinity know.
Okay, I got it.
4789 is a patient named Eom Soo Tak.
Five years ago, Ha Tae Sik asked him to
put a fake corpse at the Joonggeon three-way intersection in place of that bastard.
He was kidnapped by that bastard and ran away,
and Ha Tae Sik hid him here.
That bastard let Eom Soo Tak go on purpose.
That sounds like you are saying that you can catch that bastard.
Eom Soo Tak fled. Hurry.
That bastard will definitely look for Eom Soo Tak.
We'll find him. I'll call you later.
4789 was Ha Tae Sik's minion.
Even though he ran away, he couldn't have gone far. We have to find him.
I'll keep an eye on Oh Hyeon Jae.
He's not the kind of person who would lose him from his grasp.
I'm sure he has a plan.
But one thing is certain.
That the information you gave me was right.
What is it that you really want?
When we catch that bastard, under the guise of emergency,
I'll use my discretion.
What do you mean? That you'll shoot?
Perhaps, is it because you want to kill that bastard with your own hands...
Let's say that that's how much I want to catch him.
Now, please give me the information that you have.
Not yet. Let's wait and see.
- Where is it?
- Over there.
Over there.
In this little village, this is the second suicide already.
Hey, it's different this time.
It's Section Chief Bang.
What in the world is going on here?
I know.
This is another suicide.
I hear he had a lot of gambling debt.
There are rumors about him getting private loans.
What? Someone else died in a matter of days?
It's that man!
- You don't know anything?
- Not much yet.
Right? I told you.
Give me the last caller's number.
What is this atmosphere that's like the quiet in the middle of a typhoon?
What do you mean a typhoon?
It's too quiet.
Hello, it's Cha Soo Yeong.
I'm Detective Kim Woo Sik at Hwayeong Police Station.
By chance, do you know Detective Bang Sang Sik?
Yes, I do.
Have some coffee.
Thank you.
You're a Metropolitan Investigation Unit detective?
Yes.
What is the cause of death?
He committed suicide. A hiker found him a short while ago.
He hung himself on a tree.
You called him many times yesterday.
Oh... yes. We only got to speak once.
I had something personal to ask him.
But he called me back at night.
You said you're Detective Cha Soo Yeong, right?
Your name was in his notebook as well.
This looks like a case I was investigating.
I had asked him about Chim Sa Bong.
Did he look into Chim Sa Bong by any chance?
I'm not sure about that.
Only he would know the contents of his notebook.
Could I maybe see his case file?
Hello, Team Leader?
Yes. Okay.
Goodbye.
Hello?
Sunbae, it's me.
You know that Section Chief Bang died, right?
Of course, I do. I saw him in person.
The news already spread that far?
I'm at Hwayeong Police Station.
He called me before that happened.
He did? To you? Why?
I had made a request before.
I was the last one he spoke to, so I'm here to give a witness statement.
What did you request?
There's something.
Sunbae, was there anything odd about him lately?
There are rumors that he was gambling and that he got private loans.
These rumors were going around.
You're at Hwayeong Police Station? You want me to come get you?
No. I'll call you later.
Gambling and private loans?
Private loans...
Gambling, unregistered car...
Ah, whom can I ask?
Gosh, you scared me!
Long time no see.
Have you been well?
Your son is so cute.
My son takes after me.
Your wife is beautiful too.
I used to be the face of our faction. At one point.
Whenever I appeared, Haewol-dong used to be at a standstill.
The women used to come out in droves,
and it used to cause tons of traffic.
Water is...
Speaking of my son, he aced his math test two days ago.
He's so great at addition and subtraction.
- But...
- Yes?
I'm curious about something.
If the CEO of a detective agency cheats, who investigates that?
That's my specialty.
This is...
What can I do for you, Detective?
Unregistered cars and...
Chim Sa Bong. Please find everything related to them.
Okay, I will.
Wow, you're good at making deals.
Let's become partners later when you quit being a police...
She learned from Oh Hyeon Jae...
- It's him, right?
- Yes, I think it is.
Team 3, we found the hospital escapee.
Located the escapee of Yooseong Mental Hospital.
He has gone into Yongmo Cathedral.
Everyone be calm. Don't provoke him.
Just watch him for the time being.
We're only to standby for now.
Don't provoke him and wait outside until reinforcements come.
4789! 4789!
No! Don't come near!
You two go that way, and the two of you search over here. Let's go.
Yes.
Stop right there! Hey, you!
Stop! Stop! You, stop there!
Stop!
Where did he go? Find him!
Where is he?
Hurry up!
Where has he gone? Where is he?
- Search thoroughly for him.
- Yes, sir. Let's go!
They've lost him.
I am not sure
why you are so obsessed with that bastard.
I have a debt to settle with that bastard too.
Crazy bastard! Yellow color... Dol Ak. Dol Ak!
Dol Ak. I saw Dol Ak.
- Yes?
- Detective, I found Chim Sa Bong.
Her name is Bong Yeon Ja.
In Tsim Sha Tsui ( an area of Hong Kong ), she multiplied a vast amount of money and came back.
But this grandma does tons of business with
private loans, unregistered cars, and such.
On the surface, she runs a landscaping company.
Landscaping company? Okay.
Please send me her address.
Hey, Cha Soo Yeong!
Yes?
Why are you so busy?
Ah, that...
Hey, why does it seem like everyone on the team is busy but me?
You guys aren't meeting separately behind my back, are you?
No, I'm not. I have some personal business to take care of.
Personal business?
Still, you shouldn't run around by yourself.
Excuse me.
I don't have anything to sell yet.
I'm from the Mucheon Metropolitan Police Agency's Metropolitan Investigation Unit.
Excuse me, but are you Bong Yeon Ja?
Why are you looking for me?
I heard that you're the bankroller for Mucheon's unregistered car business.
And so?
By chance, among the unregistered car businesses,
have you heard of Choigang Engine?
Oh, I don't know.
What would an old woman who is almost dying know?
Then, do you know Section Chief Bang at Hwayeong Police Station?
Who?
Section Chief Bang Sang Sik from the Hwayeong Police Station.
What would someone like that have anything to do with a shabby vinyl greenhouse?
Yes. Okay.
Ma'am, did you personally tie that burlap bag of manure?
These days, I have no strength in my hands,
so it's hard for me even to tie anything.
You should leave now. I'm a busy person.
When did you break your nails?
My nails?
Why are you curious about my nails?
Did you say you're a detective?
There have been hundreds of detectives who have come here.
I don't know why you came looking for me,
but bring me a warrant.
Bring me a warrant!
A warrant!
Leave!
- Ma'am.
- Yeah?
- Please calm down and use words.
- Words? Huh?
I told you not to go around alone!
How many crimes have you committed that you're threatening a detective who just came to ask some questions?
Now, what should I look for?
There should be a ledger.
She's a loan shark, so she should have a ledger hidden somewhere.
Okay. Then I'll look inside. You search out here.
Okay.
A black stain?
Kim Sang Gil.
Did you find something?
Detective Yang, there's something strange about Section Chief Bang's death.
His name is in here,
and I think he's connected to Chim Sa Bong.
What do you mean?
Please finish up here and take this.
I need to go somewhere.
Hey! Hey, Cha Soo Yeong! Hey! Hey!
What the?
Located the patient who escaped from Yooseong Mental Hospital.
Cheongdang area, Mount 1.
Patrol units, assemble quickly.
Detective Cha, as you requested, I found the address of Kim Sang Gil.
I'm sure it's somewhere nearby.
Call forensics and search the area thoroughly!
Yes, sir.
Let's go. Hurry!
He's still warm.
It looks like he died not too long ago.
How did you know where Eom Soo Tak would be?
We were too late.
Did you lose him?
Yes.
Why did you go at it alone instead of with the team?
It's a GPS. I planted it on Eom Soo Tak.
He couldn't have gone that far.
We lost the bastard.
Are you certain that bastard killed him?
Has that bastard really showed up?
Deputy Commissioner, don't keep bringing that bastard up.
Let's just...
leave it as an unsolved case.
Okay, I understand.
Eon Soo Tak's body will be left as a cold case.
But why did Oh Hyeon Jae give this to you?
It was a golden opportunity to catch that bastard.
I'm sure he has another plan.
Another plan?
Excuse me. Do you know where #27-3 is?
Try going up that way.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Who is it?
May I come in for a moment?
Did you come from the community center?
Are you Kim Sang Gil, born in 1964?
Who are you?
Mucheon 11 A5897.
Have you driven this unregistered car?
I don't know.
Please leave now.
Twenty years ago on October 10, 2000 at 2 PM, at an intersection in Hongwoon-myeon,
a black car was involved in a hit-and-run accident.
At the time, the driver was wearing a black hat.
The accident at that time... killed 37-year-old Jeong Eun Mi.
Besides you, there was also a child in the car.
Even the rag doll that the child was holding...
There's someone who remembers it all.
Who are you?
A witness and the victim's daughter.
That was something from a long time ago.
What are you trying to do about it now?
The statute of limitations has expired.
It hasn't expired for me!
I...
I became a cop because of this.
Get up.
Get up!
Kim Sang Gil, you are being arrested for the crime of a fatal hit-and-run
which killed 37-year-old Jeong Eun Mi on October 10, 2000,
on an intersection in Hongwoon-myeon,
which falls under Additional Punishment Law on Specific Crimes.
I should have just died then.
You have the rights to defend yourself, to appoint an attorney,
and to refuse to give testimony.
In addition, you have the right to request a judicial review of the legality of this arrest.
I, Mucheon Metropolitan Police Agency's Investigation Unit Detective Cha Soo Yeong, have notified you of all this.
Don't arrest me;  just kill me.
I should have died then.
I should have just died then.
It's been hell.
Kill you?
You want me to kill you?
I dreamt of arresting you more than a hundred times over the last twenty years.
The statute of limitations has expired.
I can't arrest you.
Continue to live in this hell that you can't die from
like I am.
You must keep living. Don't die.
♫  My deep shadow  ♫
♫  Your petals brush by  ♫
♫  La la la la la la la la la  ♫
♫  Left alone in the rough wind  ♫
♫  The petals withered  ♫
Soo Yeong, thank you for not giving up.
♫  I fell asleep with you in my arms  ♫
Dol Ak. It's here.
Eom Soo Tak hit this sign as he was running away.
And he saw the words 'Dol Ak' here.
Yellow color... Dol Ak. Dol Ak!
This is  the place where Eom Soo Tak and his girlfriend were buried.
That bastard must've been very excited.
A secret and familiar place
that could excite him to the extreme.
I am certain that his hideout is near.
The reason why he is aware of the situation
is because he is wiretapping into the police radio.
I am sure that strong radio signals will be transmitted from his hideout.
Remember...
who told you to kill Isu.
You will have to tell me.
What's wrong?
Dad, I caught the culprit.
I caught the culprit who hit Mom and ran.
Really?
You caught him?
You've been through a lot, my daughter.
Dad, I'm sorry.
I found him too late.
I'm so sorry that I couldn't do anything.
It's me.
I guess something must have happened?
I found the guy who hit my mom and ran.
That's a relief.
May I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
When you helped me on the first case with Jo Seong Ae,
you said this to me.
You said you weren’t interested.
Why did you help me?
I never helped you.
Then why?
I pitied you.
I pity myself, too.
What did you mean by that?
Scars...
A sense of loss for those whose tomorrow will never come.
Look here, Cha Soo Yeong.
Try to fight it.
If you don't want to be weakened.
I need you right now.
♫  Confess your sins with blinks  ♫
♫  Eyes you flicker  ♫
♫  As though putting together fragmented traces  ♫
♫  The memories which you have lost  ♫
♫  You left me behind  ♫
Detective Oh.
♫  Who wandered alone searching for you  ♫
This is that bastard's hideout.
You finally found it.
That's right.
Have you contacted Team Leader yet?
Not yet.
Memorize using your photographic memory first.
That doll isn't a victim's.
It's definitely that bastard's.
It must have some special meaning.
This doll...
I know it.
Twenty years ago, in the car that hit my mom and ran,
the child who was sitting in the back was holding this doll.
Tell me one person whom you want to kill.
You did well.
Do you remember that doll?
What do you know that you came to see me?
For five years now, why must we continue to do something that makes us tremble?
I can't stand to see the organization I belong to falter.
Being predictable isn't his style.
We have to find his goal.
What's the evidence that Director Choi wants to hide?
What the hell is going on?
You weren't going to be able to catch him from the first place.
That bastard just cut off his tail, that's all.