Tell me one person whom you want to kill.
You did well.
I switched the order, but it's not working out well.
I usually kill first and then put it in.
Hwang Ha Yeong, tell me one person whom you want to kill.
You never know. I might let you live.
Spare...
What?
Spare me.
I can't hear you.
Spare me! Spare me! Spare me!
Wrong answer.
Spare me!
Hey there.
Please save me.
Who is it?
Save me.
Are you okay?
I'm so scared.
He's going to kill me.
I'm a police officer.
You will survive this. You will.
He's going to kill me now. He will end up killing me.
We will survive.
Th- there. There's a light over there.
Go there and ask for help.
We have to get to the road. We have to go further away.
I'm scared. My legs are shaking.
Save me...
Are you okay? Just gather up your strength a little more.
Mom...
- Just a little more.
- Mom...
Unni. Unni, hurry up.
No, no!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry. He said he would spare me. I'm sorry.
- What?
- Sorry.
So why would you put your hope in someone?
Look carefully at what the woman you tried to save did to you.
You said you would let me live if I brought her here.
Please spare me.
Spare me!
Hwang Ha Yeong, tell me one person whom you want to kill.
No one!
No one? Wrong answer.
Save me...
No! No!
No!
No! You bastard!
Tell me whom you want to kill.
Hwang Ha Yeong. Hwang Ha Yeong.
Wrong answer.
Try again.
I don't know.
Think of that jerk next to you.
That jerk who makes a big deal as though he knows everything about me.
Oh Hyeon Jae.
Oh Hyeon Jae? You want to kill him?
He's my objective but not the answer.
He's too good to kill so easily.
Now, try again.
Tell me one person whom you want to kill.
I don't know. I don't know!
- You know the answer.
- I don't know!
Think carefully.
Spare me.
If you want to live, tell me the name in your head.
Spare me. Spare me!
- Tell me.
- I'll do everything you ask, so spare me.
You'll do everything I ask?
Tell me the name.
Unni, my most precious unni gave me the best gift in the world.
Thank you.
Isu.
What did you say?
Han Isu.
Bingo.
I'm letting you live since you got the answer right.
You did well. Good job.
We have Detective Oh Hyeon Jae here, the criminal profiler at the Metropolitan Investigation Unit.
Detective Oh Hyeon Jae, if your hypothesis is correct,
how would the culprit ask the victims?
Look, tell me one person whom you want to kill.
That is the last thing you must do in this world before you die.
This is that bastard's hideout.
You finally found it.
That's right.
Have you contacted Team Leader yet?
Not yet.
Memorize using your photographic memory first.
That doll isn't a victim's.
It's definitely that bastard's.
It must have some special meaning.
This doll...
I know it.
Twenty years ago, in the car that hit my mom and ran,
the child who was sitting in the back was holding this doll.
There was a child?
If this doll is his,
then that bastard was in the car...
That child...
There's a high probability of that.
Cha Soo Yeong, the scene of the accident at that time,
can you recall it?
A man wearing a black cap was driving
and a child was in the back.
The child was holding that doll.
A boy who looks to be about
11 to 13 years old.
That child...
He was smiling.
During the moment that the accident happened,
he was smiling.
Cha Soo Yeong, there's something you need to do.
Shin Gyeong Soo.
The one who's in a coma?
Is he a copycat of the bastard?
Shin Gyeong Soo isn't a copycat.
They're a lot closer.
This Matryoshka doll...
The one that was found at Shin Gyeong Soo's house,
it could be the last one of that Matryoshka doll.
I'm sure there's a link between Shin Gyeong Soo and that bastard.
First, find out what contact that bastard had with Shin Gyeong Soo when he was young.
Shin Gyeong Soo or Kim Sang Gil, whichever one it is,
we're getting closer to the bastard.
What about this place? What should we do about it?
We have no use for it anymore.
That bastard won't come here anymore.
When you first came, you gave me only the intel I wanted.
Very actively, even though it wasn't your job.
At the time, it was the only way for me to become a part of the Metropolitan Investigative Unit.
People always have a goal.
The Ha Tae Sik case...
there were a lot of variables.
Right, there were.
This time, there will be many variables, too.
Being predictable isn't his style.
We have to find his goal.
That's how the winner will be decided.
Tell me.
The GPS you put in Eom Soo Tak's shoe.
It was brilliant.
Because of that, I thought you were looking for Eom Soo Tak...
But you got me.
It's my turn next.
I'll anticipate it.
You find me.
Then...
I'll tell you who told me to kill Isu.
His voice has started trembling.
He has lost his composure.
What happened to Cha Soo Yeong?
Handing Chim Sa Bong over to you.
She'll be back.
I'm sorry.
Oh, you came. The youngest is the master.
Hey, we had to prepare the briefing for Chim Sa Bong.
Thank you.
Let's start.
It's a case Cha Soo Yeong brought.
It's a bigger case than expected.
Park Choon Gil, who was first discovered in the hills of Hongwoon-myeon,
looks to have been killed by Lee Jong Soo after being paid off by Bong Yeon Ja,
and was made to look like a suicide.
Section Chief Bang looks to have been killed the same way.
Interrogate Bong Yeon Ja and Lee Jong Soo separately.
You know the prisoner's dilemma?
Get them to confess to the crime without confrontation.
We need a testimony from the first police officer at the scene
in order to hold a corroborative investigation,
so we've requested for him to be dispatched here until the case is solved.
His name is Kang Dong Sik, who's Cha Soo Yeong's sunbae from Hongwoon Police Station.
I got it.
Senior Policeman Kang Dong Sik, whom you asked to be dispatched, says he is here downstairs right now.
Okay, bring him up.
Sunbae.
Soo Yeong.
I heard you were dispatched because of Section Chief Bang's case.
They need a statement from the first person on scene and the related files,
so I brought everything.
Okay. Let's go.
Hey.
Is something the matter?
No, why?
You're not your usual self.
Why do you seem so dark?
What is it? Tell me.
Later. I'll tell you in time.
Let's go.
Hurry.
I'm so curious.
Mr. Kim Sang Gil. Mr. Kim Sang Gil.
Who is it?
Are you Kim Sang Gil?
Who are you?
A female detective came by before, right?
Stop coming to see me.
It's hard for me, too.
I want to turn back time, too.
Please leave already!
Your health must not be good.
Living is hell.
But... you still pray.
Your rosary is very worn. An important prayer, perhaps?
Are you a detective, too?
It's all in the past.
Kim Sang Gil, it doesn't seem to be only about the hit-and-run accident.
What do you know that you came to see me?
Do you remember that doll?
Was the child sitting in the back of the car during the accident that day your son?
He was.
It was a prayer for your son.
That child... I abandoned him.
Yo Han.
What are you doing here?
I was looking for you for a long time.
What is that doll?
And what is that blood?!
Mom, from now on... this doll is mine.
Honey, I'm home.
Honey.
Oh, Yo Han, what are you doing?
Honey. Honey!
Honey, Honey!
After my wife's funeral was over,
I was driving like mad saying to myself I should kill the boy and myself.
But on the way, I hit that female detective's mother.
Close your eyes while eating candy.
Then it'll all be over.
Yo Han... I don't think I can live with you. Sorry.
Back then, I really...
I couldn't see straight.
The child... What is that child's name?
Kim Yo Han.
Kim... Yo Han.
Detective Lee, let's talk.
What does it mean that you gave this to me?
I know that you're Director Choi's person.
I want to be a detective, that's why.
A real detective.
That alone doesn't explain it.
Team Leader, when I was young,
I liked it better outside than inside of a school.
While hanging out outside like that,
I nearly ended up going to juvenile hall.
That's when Director Choi helped me.
He even helped me go to college.
To me, he's my savior.
And?
That was it.
I did everything he asked while feeling grateful.
It was loyalty.
Though, in the end, he just used me.
So now... I am not really sure where I am supposed to go.
Take the path you want.
From now on, as a detective,
carry out the investigation in the way you believe is right.
What is the evidence that was taken out?
That's... handcuffs.
Handcuffs? The evidence Director Choi wanted to hide was handcuffs?
Yes.
This evidence will only be used to catch that bastard.
And I'll be the only one who'll have knowledge of this for the time being.
Also, a real detective isn't made by someone else.
The case for Eom Soo Tak's corpse on the hill has been closed as an unsolved case.
For five years now, why must we continue to do something that makes us tremble?
Of course, we have to do it.
What?
In order to protect the organization,
there has to be some self-sacrifice.
What is left by us doing this?
Once everything comes to light, we'll be discarded.
I guess we don't share the same values.
Do you want to see the police in a fragile state like it was five years ago?
Getting beat up from the inside and verbally abused from the outside.
Being despised for being incompetent!
I can't stand to see the organization I belong to falter.
So? What are you planning to do?
Whatever I can, I'll do.
I'll catch that bastard first no matter what.
You have a good plan in mind?
Information on him that not even Oh Hyeon Jae has.
With that card, I'll catch him before Oh Hyeon Jae and cover it up again.
Chim Sa Bong. Bong Yeon Ja, who dealt with a vast amount of money in Tsim Sha Tsui, Hong Kong.
Wow, I didn't know I would meet you in person.
You started a private loan business in Korea, provided money to civil servants, and threatened them.
Wow. You sure are a big player.
Why did you kill Section Chief Bang?
I didn't kill him.
Then why did you kill Park Choon Gil on the hills of Hongwoon-myeon and make it look like a suicide?
After Park Choon Gil's death, his adopted son, Jong Soo, received inheritance.
But why is Jong Soo working at your greenhouse?
Here.
Look at the knots.
The ones on Bang Sang Sik and Park Choon Gil
are just like the knots you make on your manure burlap bags.
You're laughing?
Think about it.
An old lady like me without any strength,
how could I kill those men?
Also, I never knew how scary that kid, Jong Soo, was.
Excuse me.
The villagers told me that if someone borrows money from you and doesn't pay back,
that the person disappears without a trace after handing over notarized agreements
that he'll hand over the deeds to his houses and land.
That's all gossip.
I didn't want to say this,
but Lee Jong Soo admitted everything.
If you don't want to die in jail, tell us the truth.
W-What did Lee Jong Soo admit?
Everything.
Chim Sa Bong told you everything?
So why don't you come clean, too,
and receive a reduced sentence?
Chim Sa Bong admitted to Section Chief Bang, too?
Not him. Honestly.
Park Choon Gil or Section Chief Bang, I don't know anything.
There's no reason for me to kill them.
Oh, especially Section Chief Bang,
I could have used him to my advantage for a long, long time.
Why would I kill him?
She's keeps denying it until the end.
Team Leader.
Yes?
Right.
What should we do about him?
Tell him to be on standby until Bong Yeon Ja case's is resolved.
I'll make a formal request to Hongwoon Police Station.
Hwang Ha Yeong.
Yeah, Hyung.
(some women use this term when they're close friends with an older male, especially in a male dominated environment)
Let's speak casually without rank for the first time in five years.
What's up with you these days? Is something going on?
No.
That's not true. Why are you pretending?
- What do you mean?
- As if you're all right.
When you don't look okay.
Also, don't disappear like how you did five years ago.
You know, right?
My phone is always on.
Onju orphanage?
Onju orphanage.
If they grew up in the same orphanage...
Is he currently able to communicate?
Yes. He can handle simple conversations.
Okay. Please continue to maintain security.
He's a suspect in an important case.
Other than me, who's in charge of the case, you can't let anyone else know.
Don't let anyone in, nor let any other detectives know.
Okay.
If Shin Gyeong Soo is being controlled by someone...
That would be the real culprit.
Kim Sang Gil's son is the bastard.
His name is Kim Yo Han. He disappeared 20 years ago.
Kim Sang Gil doesn't know anything about him.
If he grew up in an orphanage because of that,
he could have grown up with Shin Gyeong Soo.
Shin Gyeong Soo grew up at a place called Onju Orphanage.
Onju Orphanage...
Let's talk for a moment.
Shin Gyeong Soo is being controlled by the bastard.
I'm sure they knew each other.
When he finds out that Shin Gyeong Soo is awake,
he might come to kill him.
You want to set a trap using Shin Gyeong Soo as bait?
I want the trap to be set densely.
Also give me the information on that bastard related to the handcuffs.
Team Leader Hwang, how did you...
We're running out of time.
Until he was 14 years old, Shin Gyeong Soo
grew up at Onju Orphanage which was run by a Catholic foundation.
The bastard probably had nowhere to go but to an orphanage too.
If he grew up with Shin Gyeong Soo,
it's not a simple case of gas-lighting.
They're much more intimately connected.
Like communicated insanity.
Communicated insanity?
A shared consciousness... It's a symptom where they have the same delusions.
What brings you here?
We're from the Mucheon Metropolitan Police Agency's Investigation Unit.
We heard the director has been here the longest.
Would it be possible to see him right now?
Oh, he won't be able to answer very well due to Alzheimer's.
I ask for your understanding.
Of course.
- Director, it's me.
- Who?
- Dominique.
- Oh, Dominique.
We have guests.
They're detectives.
They have some questions for you.
Hello, Director.
I'm Detective Cha Soo Yeong from the Metropolitan Investigation Unit.
We came to ask a few things about a case we're investigating.
It was a long time ago so you may not remember,
but about 20 years ago, did a child named Kim Yo Han
come to this orphanage?
Yo Han.
I knew this day would come some day.
Pardon?
I have looked after many kids in my life,
but there was no one odd like him.
That's interesting, Father.
Father, what kind of a child was he?
He was very different.
Over here! Kick it!
- Hey, we're going first.
- We're going.
- That kid...
- Yo Han!
He had a knack for drawing people to him.
The three of them always went around together.
Even siblings couldn't be that close.
By chance, do you have any photos left of them?
The kid holding the doll. It is him.
Really, the three of them were so eccentric.
Who pushed him? Who pushed Daniel?
Daniel could die!
- I did it.
- What?
Yo Han, you tell me.
Who did it, Yo Han?
- Father, stop bothering Gyeong Soo and Yo Han.
- What?
- It's all my doing.
Yo Han was Luciel, Gyeong Soo was Gabriel,
and Jeong Hwan was Michael.
Luciel is a fallen angel, Gabriel delivers news,
and Michael symbolizes an army.
If Jeong Hwan is Michael,
he must have protected the other two.
How did you know?
Jeong Hwan... cared about Yo Han and Gyeong Soo extremely.
But more so, Yo Han.
Father, the kid holding the doll.
Is he Yo Han?
Yes. The one on the right is Gyeong Soo.
Shin Gyeong Soo?
Where's Kim Yo Han right now?
He was adopted by a couple.
They lived in Dol Ak Valley, as I recall.
Dol Ak Valley?
I saw Dol Ak.
And the last kid here is Jeong Hwan then?
- Where is he right now?
- Huh?
You met Jeong Hwan a moment ago.
Dominique is Jeong Hwan.
Father, where's Father Dominique?
- He went to his room earlier.
- Where's his room?
Go around this way. It's the last one on the second floor.
Search here.
Cha Soo Yeong. It's a Matryoshka doll.
Shin Gyeong Soo and Dominique followed that bastard.
Even after they went out into the society, they didn't let go of each other.
Especially Dominique, he would have done everything the bastard asked of him.
Can you recall this building? Try.
It's the hospital where Shin Gyeong Soo was admitted.
A hospital?
As expected, Dominique continuously kept his eye on Shin Gyeong Soo
because the bastard asked him to.
Shin Gyeong Soo is in a coma right now.
Shin Gyeong Soo...
He's awake.
Mr. Shin Gyeon Soo, it's time for your—
It's an emergency! Shin Gyeong Soo has disappeared right now!
- What?
Yes? What did you say?
Shin Gyeong Soo ran away? We'll be right there.
- What are you talking about?
- Shin Gyeong Soo ran away from the hospital.
A guy who was in a coma?
Call Team Leader and Cha Soo Yeong.
Yes, sir.
The customer's phone is turned off—
Team Leader's phone is off.
Let's go to the hospital first.
Shin Gyeong Soo disappeared from the hospital.
He couldn't have gone far. Find him quickly!
Yes, Detective Jang?
Hey Cha Soo Yeong, Shin Gyeong Soo ran away.
Quickly come to the hospital and provide backup.
Yes, I understand.
They said Shin Gyeong Soo ran away.
What happened?  He was in a coma. Why would he suddenly run away?
He didn't suddenly run away. He woke up earlier.
Then that means, we weren't told that he had gained consciousness?
Someone planned it.
It means someone came up with a game plan.
A suspect of a murder case has escaped.
He escaped from the hospital. Asking for backup.
That bastard knew I would wake up.
There was a place he told me to come to when I woke up.
Get me out of here.
Then... I'll take you to where you can meet the bastard.
Fine.
But... how will you get me out of here?
I'll take care of it.
- Any news from headquarters?
- Not yet.
- Find out.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Officer Kim, come with me.
- Yes.
Don't get any ideas. Take me to that bastard.
You'll meet him soon.
But keep your promise. That you'll give me freedom.
Go in first.
You must be looking for me. I'm Dominique.
Detective Yang!
Hey, Cha Soo Yeong! Where have you been?
I was out with Detective Oh.
- Where is he?
- He's tending to another matter.
What the hell is going on?
- Where's Team Leader?
- Her phone is still turned off.
Oh, this is so frustrating.
Anyway, in Shin Gyeong Soo's physical state, he can't have gone outside of the hospital.
I'll search the exits thoroughly with Detective Jang,
so you two go to the security office and find out what's happening.
Okay.
What are you? Are you his lackey?
That's the wrong question, Detective Oh Hyeon Jae.
The three of us are of one body.
You can't catch Gyeong Soo.
You have a more important task.
Continue.
Aren't you curious about who wanted Han Isu dead?
Turn around.
Tell me one person whom you want to kill.
If you catch me, I'll let you hear the rest.
We just have to go a little further.
Don't play any tricks.
What are you guys planning?
You're impatient.
Tell me.
Yes. Everything that happened today was Yo Han's plan.
You, me, and everyone
are in the palm of his hands.
But you know something?
At the critical moment when you have to tell someone about me,
you'll protect me, right?
Even if it means putting your lives on the line!
What do you mean?
What are you doing?
The drug that will save me.
We are one.
My will is Yo Han's will.
Everything is...
Yo Han's will.
But, you punk,
where is that bastard right now?
Yo Han was right.
If I talk about Han Isu,
that you wouldn't go to
Shin Gyeong Soo.
Detective Yang, it's me.
Shin Gyeong Soo is dead.
I'm at the Joonggeon three-way intersection.
Team Leader, are you okay?
- Detective Jang and Lee, take care of the scene.
- Okay.
Are you okay?
Something's happened.
What's going on?
Please restrict the area well.
What happened?
I caught Shin Gyeong Soo when he was running away,
and we got into an accident while I was taking him with me.
Hwang Ha Yeong.
Fine.
I know you came up with this game plan.
I could have caught him,
but I lost him.
No. You weren't going to be able to catch him from the first place.
That bastard just cut off his tail, that's all.
They're the handcuffs that Oh Hyeon Jae put on that bastard five years ago.
But that bastard...
He took off the handcuffs that Oh Hyeon Jae put on him.
It means he had the key for the cuffs that were distributed that year.
That bastard...
is a policeman.
Hurry!
Over here!
Please stay out. Please stay out.
It's dangerous here.
Please stay out.
How is the bastard who died five years ago still walking around right now?
It's interesting, isn't it?
The cause of death for both of them is the same.
They were both poisoned with potassium cyanide.
They both committed suicide.
This reminds me of the saying "keep your friends close and your enemies closer."
If Detective Oh was his usual self,
he wouldn't have shared information.
Why did he do that?
I can see an outline of you. Just wait.
We'll meet soon.