♪There's no sign of anything special♪
♪Didn't save the world much♪
♪You just appeared out of nowhere
when I wasn't looking♪
♪The future's in the future♪
♪Now is the time
for you and me to meet♪
♪Let it all come true♪
♪No matter how dangerous
and far the road will be♪
♪We'll always be in love♪
♪That's how lucky we are♪
♪Every day is so bright and shiny♪
♪There's no such thing
as a smooth ride♪
♪There's a cloudy day
every now and then♪
♪There's nothing in our love
that can be repeated by anyone else♪
♪The future's in the future♪
♪Now is the time
for you and me to meet♪
♪Let it all come true♪
♪We'll always be in love♪
♪That's how lucky we are♪
♪Every day is so bright and shiny♪
[You'll Never Walk Alone]
[Pure fiction.
Resemblance to reality is coincidental.]
[Episode 9]
Come in.
Nanny.
I'm hurt.
You are hurt?
Go back and take a nap then.
It's true. Look.
You...
Look.
What happened?
How did you get so seriously hurt?
Is it that serious?
Yes.
Take a photo for me.
Now is not the time to do that.
Show it to me.
You are unbelievable.
The wound is quite deep.
See?
Let me apply some medicine for you.
It's really serious.
This is the worst injury
that I've ever had in my life.
You said that the last time too.
It's even more serious this time.
Stop talking.
Where did you go?
I'll explain it to you later.
Now, I feel that it hurts even more.
Let me cut it open for you.
Why are you holding the scissors?
To cut your shirt open.
Otherwise, how can I apply
the medicine on you?
Don't move.
Do you need to go to the hospital?
Let me sanitize the area for you first.
Hang in there. It'll be painful.
Do it gently.
Xia Yuan, thank you.
So, you said that you were going out.
But you went to the warehouse
and got hurt so badly.
I didn't mean to keep it
a secret from you.
I think what you did was too risky.
You'll expose yourself.
How about we leave?
There's no need.
They didn't see my face.
They wouldn't know it was me.
Moreover,
if we leave out of the blue right now,
we'll paint a big fat target
on our back.
It's too dangerous for you
to be there now.
It's okay.
You don't have to worry about it.
I'll take good care of myself.
Besides,
I wasn't injured by others.
I injured myself.
Loris.
Xia Yuan.
Help me organize these files
as soon as possible.
No problem.
Come on. Last five.
Come.
Four more. Breathe out.
Three more.
Come on.
Breathe out. Yes.
Two. Last one.
Okay.
I can't get up anymore. Give me a hand.
Here.
If only
I can hold your hands like this forever.
I really hope that time
can stand still right now.
Can you not go?
I'm sorry, Sophia.
I have things to do tonight.
Bye.
I'll get going now. Bye.
(It's okay.)
(I'll wait for you.)
(Mr. Xu.)
(Why is Loris investigating Mr. Xu?)
(Can it be that...)
Did you inspect the goods today?
Ya. They are all set.
Who was at the warehouse?
I don't know yet.
But I have an idea.
Who?
A Chinese guy.
He can't hurt us.
He's got no evidence.
What we need to do now
is to get the goods
into Mr. Xu's warehouse.
From there,
we get the goods onto the ship.
The ship sets sail,
we call the cops.
There's enough stuff in there
to put them away for a long, long time.
But we can't mess this up.
Ya. Great.
What's that?
July has been here.
How do you know that?
I can smell her perfume.
Hao Weilai.
What's wrong?
When I was by the office door,
I heard Loris and Tom planning
to frame Mr. Xu.
Loris is going to frame him?
I already said that he was
not a good man.
We have to call the police.
We can't. We can't prove it.
The police won't believe in us.
What should we do?
How about this?
Tomorrow morning,
pack your bags
and leave at once.
I'll look for the evidence.
Will it be safe for you?
I don't know.
How is your packing going on?
I'm almost done.
I'll go there now.
How's your wound?
I'm fine.
After you quit,
go to the beach to meet up
with Ye Siqi and the others.
Be careful.
You too.
Hey, Future.
Hi.
Xia Yuan.
Why aren't you at work today?
There has been an emergency in my house.
I have to go back.
I'm just about to hand in
my resignation letter to you.
Do you have to leave in such a rush?
How about
I treat you to dinner tonight?
To thank you
for what you've done for my company.
I'll pass.
My parents are waiting for me at home.
I'm in a rush to go back to them.
But you are leaving soon.
And I don't know
when I can see you again.
Let me give you a proper farewell.
If your family needs anything
or if you need my help,
you can always come to me.
Loris.
Where are we going?
You'll know when we get there.
Is it far away?
No.
We'll be there soon.
And you'll love that place.
What are you doing?
- Stop!
Don't move!
Stop!
What happened?
Someone broke into the warehouse.
Have you seen his face?
No. But I think he's an Asian.
Is he still here?
Yes. I'm sure.
You all, block the gates.
Loris.
Yes. Are you sure it's him?
Okay.
Don't worry.
I won't do anything to you.
I just want to take you to someone.
I don't want anyone to know
that I came here today.
Yes, Sir.
All the monitors have been handled by me
and all the gates have been locked.
He's still here.
He's still here?
Yes.
Weilai.
Xia Yuan is right beside me.
We are going to have dinner.
Do you want to join us?
Weilai.
If you come out,
I can ensure your safety.
But if you don't come out,
I can't promise you anything.
I'll count to three.
One,
two.
Loris.
I'll come with you.
Let Xia Yuan go.
Now, it's not about you coming with me.
Both of you are coming with me.
Please come down.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
Has Hao Weilai contacted you?
No.
I think something is wrong.
I can't get in contact
with my sister too.
Let me give him a call, then.
(Sorry.)
(The subscriber you have dialed
has powered off.)
His phone is powered off.
Did something
happen to them?
I don't think so.
Maybe
they are having fun out there
and their phones
have run out of power.
I hope so.
Don't think too much.
Loris.
Let her go.
Don't make me sound so mean.
As if I've kidnapped her.
Xia Yuan.
Have I treated you unkindly?
See?
I'm a gentleman.
I'm not violent.
I just wanted to have a meal
with Xia Yuan.
I never thought that things
would turn out like this.
Loris.
I beg you. Let her go.
She has nothing to do with this.
Come at me if you have
a grudge toward me.
Stop trying to act
like a hero in front of her.
Tom, you got some gum?
Xia Yuan.
Actually, I've always admired you.
But you've disappointed me this time.
I treated you so well.
Why did you lie to me?
Loris, what are you trying to do?
But even if you lie to me,
I still won't hurt you.
Have a good rest here.
Look at you.
Such a nice couple.
You know.
I don't like my boss's behaviour.
He's too kind.
He's a nice guy.
He's a gentleman.
But if you are in my country,
if you do something wrong,
you'll have to be punished.
Tom, let her go.
We must have...
You don't know how to shut up,
don't you?
Open your mouth.
Now! Open it.
You never know how to shut up.
Take it.
Don't blame others for your mistakes,
okay?
You want to play this game?
Perfect. Let's play.
No. What are you doing?
You like this?
Ready?
Stop!
Let's go, guys.
Hao Weilai.
Are you okay?
Hao Weilai!
Boss.
So, what should I do next?
I mean, those two people.
Should I take care of them?
We are not mafias. We are businessmen.
Just don't hurt them.
Okay. So what should I do?
Keep a good eye on them.
They are not a threat to us.
As long as we stick to the plan,
we'll be fine.
I see.
The ship sets sail tomorrow.
After that, we'll release them.
Until then, I don't want any problems.
Got it, Boss.
Qiao Bin.
I still think that something
is not right.
My sister and Hao Weilai's phones
won't be turned off at the same time.
Do you still remember
what Hao Weilai said about
Loris having ill intentions
toward my sister?
Did he...
It must be him.
Let's go and find them
at the wharf right now.
That'll be too late.
Let's just call the police.
Hao Weilai.
You can't pass out now.
How do you feel?
Do you feel dizzy?
Can you see clearly?
I have to think.
I'm sure we can escape.
Come.
Get up.
Are you okay?
How do you feel?
Get up.
Why is your head bleeding?
How do you feel?
Can you see me clearly?
Is it painful?
How do you feel?
What?
What are you trying to say?
Okay.
The towel.
Bend your head down.
How do you feel?
Do you feel better now?
We have to think.
Let me check if there's an exit here.
We need to find a way to escape.
Where is the exit.
Xia Yuan.
If we can't escape,
will you blame me?
Let's not talk about that.
We have to find a way.
I'm sure we can escape.
Come.
Let's stand with our backs
facing each other
so that we can untie the ropes.
Not that one.
The one inside it.
Not like that.
It's getting tighter now.
I can't untie it.
Try doing it from this side.
Can you untie it?
Can you see the knot?
Yes.
Tug on it again.
You've untied it.
Come.
Come. Let me untie you.
Hang in there.
Okay.
How do you feel?
I'm fine.
Rest here for a while.
I'll look for an exit.
It's locked from the outside.
I'll check the back of the room.
Xia Yuan.
There's a vent here.
Let's go.
Be careful.
No.
Shit.
Boss, they've escaped.
Give me your hand.
Let's go. Over there.
- Let's go down.
- Stop!
Stop!
Over there.
Let's go. Over there.
- There they are!
- Catch them!
This way.
- Stop!
Don't move!
- There you are!
- Stop!
Don't move!
And here we are.
Catch them.
Okay. Enough.
Enough.
How are you feeling?
Little boy.
I told you not to mess with me.
You don't listen.
You like to show off.
You like to be the hero.
How does the hero feel now?
You know.
The sad thing is,
this poor girl
is going to suffer a lot.
That's a pity.
Because my boss has a big crush on you.
Tom.
You are committing a crime right now.
So scared.
Guys, they are yours.
- Don't move!
- Freeze!
Stay on the ground!
You, get down!
You, get on the ground.
Freeze.
Boss.
There's a cop at the gate.
Okay.
[Caution]
[Police]
When we got into the car,
they blindfolded us.
They didn't want us to know
where they were going.
I felt that something was not right.
So, I used my own method
to memorize the route.
Do you want to know
what method I used?
No. Get straight to the point.
The point is,
look.
This is the photo that I took.
It's a proof that they are trying
to frame Mischief Man.
Okay. I got it.
(I wonder how Hao Weilai is right now.)
(Why isn't he out yet?)
(I hope he's fine.)
Yuan, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Sorry for being late.
You are not too late.
Luckily, you called the police in time.
Where's Hao Weilai?
Hao Weilai
is a crucial witness.
They are still taking his statement.
I heard that Loris is still on the run.
What are the police going to do?
They've already issued
an arrest warrant on him.
Thank you. You can go now.
You are welcome.
Officer.
Do you really don't want to know
about my mind map?
You can note it down.
I can tell you more.
No.
It has nothing to do with the case.
Officer.
I have another question for you.
I transported these goods without
knowing better.
So, I didn't commit a crime, right?
You are right. Don't worry.
What are you going
to do with those goods?
Where are they now?
We have recorded everything.
All the goods have been confiscated.
Let me tell you.
It was so dangerous just now.
Mr. Xu.
The police station just gave me a call.
They told me that Loris
sneaked in a batch of illegal goods
into our warehouse.
But
fortunately, Mischief Boy
and his friend found out
about it in time.
The police have already
confiscated those goods.
Were they in danger?
They are fine.
They are giving their statements
at the police station now.
But
Loris got away.
Let's go.
Let's go and bring them back.
You don't have to go.
I've asked Scar to go
and bring them back.
And I'll go to the police station
to find out more about it.
Okay.
Make sure to prioritize their safety.
Don't worry.
Okay.
[One-Way, Police Station]
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank you, Sir.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Let's go.
Where are we going?
I don't know.
Loris is still on the run.
It won't be safe for us
no matter where we go.
Hello, Mischief Man.
(Mischief Boy.)
(I've sent someone to pick you up.)
(His name is Scar.)
(The car is right outside the station.)
(Get into the car now.)
Where are we going? Hello?
Hello?
Mischief Man.
Mr. Xu.
He said that he sent someone
to pick us up.
And that person is just right outside.
Let's go.
Okay.
You don't know
how dangerous it was for us.
Xia Yuan and I couldn't escape.
And we were chased by a group of men.
What happened in the end?
Who am I?
I took Xia Yuan's hand
and ran upstairs.
We kept running.
And we were blocked by a door.
What could we do?
I used my body to ram on the door.
I kept doing that
until the door opened up.
But think about it.
We were at the rooftop.
Where could we escape to, right?
When our lives were
on the precipice of death...
What happened in the end?
Tell us what happened.
- In the end, the police came.
- In the end, we...
Why did you do that?
Why didn't you let me finish the story?
It ended with the arrival
of the police, right?
Fine. The police came.
Don't I get any merits?
Let me tell you.
Thanks to Hao Weilai
who's smart and resourceful,
we managed to escape
so that the police could save us.
Are you satisfied now?
That's more like it.
I'm grateful
that both of you are safe and sound.
Hao Weilai, that's an improvement.
You've gotten better and better.
He's not the only hero here.
After all, we called the police, right?
Enough.
Thank you for saving us.
I'll forever be in your debt.
You can repay us with money.
I don't have it.
Treat us to a meal, then.
Why did you say that?
Scar.
Where are we going now?
You'll know when we get there.
This house is too big.
We are here.
Mr. Xu.
Mischief Man.
You are so rude.
Why didn't you come out to welcome me?
You brat.
Mischief Boy.
I'm here
to welcome you, right?
Hao Weilai is so shameless.
They knew each other in the past.
They almost became sworn brothers.
I've never seen these two before.
I am Ye Siqi.
You can call me Ye.
I am Qiao Bin.
You can call me Qiao.
Okay.
You can call me Mr. Xu.
- Hello, Mr. Xu.
Mr. Xu.
Thank you for saving us.
You are welcome.
Xia.
You've gone through a lot today.
We already know
what happened.
It was so dangerous.
Fortunately,
all of you are back in one piece.
I really
have to thank you this time.
Otherwise, we wouldn't know where to go.
Enough.
I should be the one to thank you.
Loris
did those things to frame me.
If it wasn't for you,
I would be sitting
in prison right now.
But I still have to remind you
that if something like that
happen again in the future,
call the police first.
Don't take things into your own hands.
We didn't want to alert them.
We wanted to call the police
right after we got the evidence.
But they found out.
Luckily, everything ended well.
Yes.
Looks like you are both injured.
I'm fine.
You are bleeding.
I'm bleeding.
Doctor.
Come. Look at you.
You are hurt. Hurry up.
Let's give you a wash
and dress the wound.
Look at you.
You need to take good care of yourself.
Okay.
Mr. Xu's house is so big.
What do you do for a living?
He is the president of our local
Chinese Chamber of Commerce.
Mischief Boy.
Go and get your wound treated first.
This way, please.
Yes. Eat.
Eat more, children.
If it's not enough, I'll ask
the kitchen to prepare more food.
Mischief Man.
This is the best meal
that I've had in a long time.
Really? Eat more, then.
You should stay here.
Then you'll get to eat
authentic Chinese food
every day.
Xia, Mischief Boy.
Think about it.
Stay, okay?
Mischief Man.
We don't want to trouble you.
Not at all.
Think about it.
Loris is still on the run.
You are still in danger.
So, this is the safest place
for you to stay in.
Yuan, stay here.
It's too dangerous outside.
Staying with Mr. Xu
is the safest option for you.
Yes.
Okay then. Sorry for the trouble.
It's no trouble at all.
To be honest,
I've already got the guest rooms
ready for you.
Mischief Man.
Your house is so beautiful
and it has a garden.
Why do you have to go to the park?
Because I'm lonely.
After living abroad for so many years,
I've made a fortune for myself.
But I'm living in such a big house
all by myself.
Everyone goes out to work every day.
I don't even have someone to talk to.
I...
I just want to go out,
make new friends
and talk to everyone.
So, I'm really happy to have you here.
You can find a partner for yourself.
You brat.
If that's the case, we'll stay here
and accompany you, the lonely man.
That's great.
Come. Cheers.
Firstly,
thank you.
You've been of great help to me.
Secondly,
welcome to my mansion.
Cheers.
♪You are like a fire♪
♪You burn me with your flame♪
Come. Take a seat.
Mr. Xu.
Sit anywhere you like.
Come. Biao.
Mischief Man,
this place is not bad at all.
It even has a KTV.
Mr. Xu.
What?
Mischief Man?
What's wrong?
We are in a group
called the Mischief Duo, right?
He is Hao Weilai.
She is Xia Yuan.
He is Biao.
They are very close to Mr. Xu.
Hello, Mr. Biao.
Hello.
Don't squeeze his hand so hard.
Mr. Xu.
Are these the kids who you saved?
Yes.
We are all Chinese.
It's not easy for us
to live in a foreign land.
It's my fortune
to be able to help them.
How heroic.
Okay.
You can go and have fun.
Quan, come out for a while.
Okay.
Have fun.
Thank you, Mr. Xu.
You are welcome.
Take a seat.
Go.
Come here.
Don't be shy. Sit here.
Eat a banana.
Eat it.
Sing.
He's being shy.
Come.
I'll go first.
♪Your big eyes♪
♪Are bright and they sparkle♪
♪Like the stars in the sky♪
♪The brightest star♪
♪You are like a fire♪
♪You burn me with your flame♪
I already said that we should leave.
♪Although I like you♪
♪I've never told you about it♪
♪I also know♪
♪That you love me♪
Mr. Xu.
I haven't seen you being so happy
in a long time.
Right?
By the way,
what have you found out?
How's Hui lately?
The Young Master is going quite well.
That's good.
That's nice.
Tell me.
How nice it would be
if Hui was here today.
You can leave now.
I want to have some alone time.
(Xia Yuan.)
(I'm so disappointed in you.)
(Haven't I treated you well enough?)
(But you and Hao Weilai
have ruined my life.)
(I won't forgive you.)
♪I know it's not good♪
♪A weird silence♪
♪There are things I don't talk about
because I don't want to♪
♪You know that you are losing
when you try to ask someone to stay♪
♪Should I just laugh at myself♪
♪The best thing in life
is that you have had it♪
♪I know it's not good♪
♪Just happen to have a breakdown♪
♪But I can't take it anymore,
not even a second♪
♪Who'd have thought
that damages would come at this time♪
♪I can't even hide from it♪
♪I'll just have to forget about you
and run away tomorrow♪
♪I met you
on the street corner that year♪
♪I let go of the hand
that I held so tightly♪
♪The memories are silent,
the promises are clamouring♪
♪I don't know
if it's a good ending or not♪
♪Dry the tears and hide the pain♪
♪It's too early to say
such a cruel thing♪
♪Walk away from each other quietly♪