♪The painting is filled with old dreams
and the moonlight is scattered♪
♪I draw a flower when
the light is half dim♪
♪The wind blows through the eyebrows
and the insanity remains♪
♪One more step
and everything will be fine♪
♪Who says that things are
unpredictable? You're still around♪
♪The lonely shadows
of the past have gone♪
♪I'll take the hardships
and turn them into liquor♪
♪Old friends will never be forgotten♪
♪Who says the world
has changed? You never left♪
♪Yesterday's sorrows
and joys are long gone♪
♪I hold the light in my hands
only to see this love last♪
♪A million dreams for me
to look back on♪
=Order of the Sommelier=
=Episode 5=
(Underage viewers are advised to
watch under parental consent.)
(I'm starting to transform.)
(My power is not sufficient
to maintain this form.)
(I need to leave.)
(This place is not for me either.)
(Why did I end up here?)
I'm really leaving this time.
Take care.
I can't believe
that Zhu Ping
is hanging out with a demon.
Luckily, Elder Qu is an expert
and has kept him under control.
I guess
he's probably turning into a demon too
after
hanging out with a demon all day.
Exactly.
Let's go.
Where is Zhu Ping now?
He's at the east end of the village.
He's an idiot.
He doesn't even know
we're on to him.
Keeping me at home to recover
and cooking for me every day.
Do they think I'm stupid?
You guys must be up to no good.
The Thirty-Six Stratagems.
I'll be on my way.
(It's finally dark.)
(I hope Zhu Ping)
(is not frightened)
(to see me like this.)
Whatever.
Save him first.
Oh, gosh.
Move!
Get out of the way!
Give me the key.
Help!
Zhu Ping.
Zhu Ping, it's okay.
- I'm here to save you.
- Demon.
Demon.
Where is it?
Elder Qu is right.
Open the door.
The demon really came.
You foul demon.
How dare you come?
Scram!
Say it again.
Scram.
Say it again!
Scram!
Get lost.
Well then.
You forced me.
Scram!
Demon, get lost!
How dare you come?
- Are you okay?
- Don't come over.
They said...
Go!
Zhu Ping.
What's wrong?
It's me, Hu Shen.
We are friends.
Is a demon
worthy of a friend?
Should I call you stupid
or naive?
Don't you realise it yet?
This is
a set-up to get you.
I didn't expect you
to show up yourself.
Sure enough.
You are indeed a demon.
Too dumb!
When we had a drink,
you said you'd never
hate me.
You
also blocked an arrow for me.
If I knew you were a demon,
would I drink with you?
It makes me sick to even think about it.
Scram!
Get out of here!
I don't want to see you again.
Look at you now.
How do you deserve to be my friend?
Go!
Leave!
♪Which door to open
so that I can see you again?♪
♪When the world is snowing heavily♪
♪I look back and
you still look the same♪
♪I lost my friends
and started to wander♪
♪Which liquor shall I drink with you?♪
♪We'll drink and travel
to a certain place♪
♪The world and the spiritual realm
are all connected♪
♪Remembering the old days♪
♪The past is quietly
waiting to be unsealed♪
♪It reminds me of my intent♪
♪Why is reality sometimes more
like a dream than memories♪
♪We promised to walk
together through the glory♪
♪I once had you to see
the whole world together♪
(Do not sell alcohol to minors.
Underage drinking is not permitted.)