♪You're nobody to me♪
♪How come I'm intoxicated
by your imperfect disguise♪
♪I'm nobody to you♪
♪How can I defend against
the flirtations in your eyes♪
♪You're nobody to me♪
♪Don't bother with the jealousy
in my moods♪
♪Become somebody to me♪
♪Stop circling. Your pulse is fading♪
♪If it's love, make it simple♪
♪Dark blooms ignite
as night's dazzling fireworks♪
♪Your belated vows gently warm my heart♪
♪The apple reflects the lamp's glow,
mirroring your eyes' sparkle♪
♪My thoughts slip into your vortex♪
♪You're nobody to me♪
♪How come I'm intoxicated
by your imperfect disguise♪
♪I'm nobody to you♪
♪How can I defend against
the flirtations in your eyes♪
♪You're nobody to me♪
♪Don't bother with the jealousy
in my moods♪
♪Become somebody to me♪
♪Stop circling. Your pulse is fading♪
♪If it's love, make it simple♪
=Stealth=
=Episode 23=
Shaofei.
How about
I come with you to the company?
Let's get the agreement done.
You've just recovered.
Stay at home and rest.
Alright then.
Be safe.
(Xue Shaofei)
(Meng Shaofei)
(Two passports?)
What are you doing?
Xue Fanyu's phone
keeps ringing.
Someone is calling again.
What should we do?
It's still ringing.
Answer it.
Why aren't you answering?
Hello, who is this?
Oh, Mr. Zhao.
Xue isn't feeling well recently.
Don't worry. I'll take good care of him.
Hmm.
Bye.
It's okay.
Song.
You're doing great.
Shaofei.
Let's
cheers.
To our victory.
Shaofei.
I feel a bit stifled.
Wanna go out for a walk.
Song.
I want you to remain
the CEO's wife of the Yulin Group.
Shaofei.
You agreed to give me more time.
Song.
I kept letting you use me,
hoping you'd finally leave that jerk.
I really like you.
You let me down greatly.
Song.
You shouldn't have betrayed me.
Mr. Xue, what happened?
Injured?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Where is Yiyi?
That day Miss Song went to the warehouse
and saw Meng Shaofei snatched her bag.
She then suspected
Meng Shaofei killed her mom,
asking for my help.
Song.
Shaofei.
You even let her
do such risky things?
Calm down.
Mr. Xue.
Miss Song found something.
Six years ago,
Meng Shaofei never skipped class.
He found an Asian doppelgänger
to attend classes in his place.
She also found out
Meng Shaofei has two passports.
He returned to China
earlier than we expected.
It was before Dr. Song's death.
We were all misled.
It's Miss Song.
Yiyi.
Brother, it's me.
Where is Yiyi?
If you want to see her,
come to the company's rooftop alone.
You're awake?
Calm.
Xue Fanyu
is about to be finished soon.
Why are you laughing?
You used Yang Nana as a front,
Wu Di as a shield,
and then me to control Xue Fanyu.
You've always hidden behind women.
Now,
the rat's finally come out
into the open.
You actually think that of me?
When did you start suspecting me?
Your mom's diary.
At first,
I just felt your particular attention
to my mom's stuff.
Song.
Shaofei.
Why are you here?
I finished the work.
Came to keep you company.
I'm here to pick something up.
I'll accompany you.
Later on,
I found you're not what I thought.
So I started to investigate you.
You've already got the company.
I just have one question.
Did you
kill my mom?
You'll know the answer soon.
Don't be scared.
I'll take you away.
Brother.
I've been waiting for you for ages.
Get up.
Turn around.
Back off.
Hurry up.
I said hurry up!
I've given you the Yulin Group.
What else do you want?
I
want your life.
Leave here.
Quiet.
What should I do?
Your suicide note is ready.
Will it be that Song died by accident?
Or you
committed suicide out of guilt
for killing Dr. Song?
Fanyu, leave here!
Be quiet!
Ok, fine.
I'll do it.
Then hurry up.
If you dare to hurt her,
I'll never forgive you, even in death.
Xue Fanyu.
Go to hell.
Six years ago, that night,
it was you, right?
So what if it was?
After tonight, no one will know.
- Let go.
- Back off.
Xue.
Miss Song.
You're awake.
Bai Chun.
Where's Xue?
Where is he now?
Is he alright?
Mr. Xue left you
all the company shares
(Property Ownership; Divorce Agreement)
and the villa.
What's that supposed to mean?
Also this.
Mr. Xue is very sorry
for making you suffer all this.
No matter what you say,
he cannot forgive himself.
So, Mr. Xue says
he won't bother you again.
I'm sorry, Miss Song.
(The flowers have been watered.)
(Mr. Xue has been here?)
Xue...
Miss Song.
What's the matter?
Meng Shaofei admitted guilt
at the station.
One more thing.
We were all wrong about the truth
six years ago.
♪Love cannot be told or showed♪
♪Determined to speak up, with no waver♪
♪Tears cannot fall or stray♪
♪Refusing to sink with aimless drifting♪
♪Vows merge like converging streams♪
♪Yet they keep us apart♪
♪Maybe destiny isn't out of reach♪
♪Time is the mistake♪
♪As I slowly approach the vortex♪
♪I hear only the bursting silence♪
♪A chain binds quietly, sealing my ears♪
♪Embracing the vortex with all my might♪
♪I feel my body falling♪
♪A past promise♪
♪Seals my body tight♪