♪You're nobody to me♪
♪How come I'm intoxicated
by your imperfect disguise♪
♪I'm nobody to you♪
♪How can I defend against
the flirtations in your eyes♪
♪You're nobody to me♪
♪Don't bother with the jealousy
in my moods♪
♪Become somebody to me♪
♪Stop circling. Your pulse is fading♪
♪If it's love, make it simple♪
♪Dark blooms ignite
as night's dazzling fireworks♪
♪Your belated vows gently warm my heart♪
♪The apple reflects the lamp's glow,
mirroring your eyes' sparkle♪
♪My thoughts slip into your vortex♪
♪You're nobody to me♪
♪How come I'm intoxicated
by your imperfect disguise♪
♪I'm nobody to you♪
♪How can I defend against
the flirtations in your eyes♪
♪You're nobody to me♪
♪Don't bother with the jealousy
in my moods♪
♪Become somebody to me♪
♪Stop circling. Your pulse is fading♪
♪If it's love, make it simple♪
=Stealth=
=Episode 2=
Song.
Master.
What are you doing?
Shaofei.
We...
What else can it be?
A man and a woman.
Ms. Yang.
You must've misunderstood.
They didn't mean it.
Everyone's got this bag these days.
Time to throw it away.
Ms. Yang.
I have
a self-made perfume here.
Fanyu.
When will you
acknowledge me as Mrs. Xue?
(He's getting married?)
It's getting late.
Time to go.
Ms. Yang.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry, Ms. Yang.
Mrs. Xue.
Such bad luck.
Shaofei.
Let's go.
Mr. Yu is waiting for us.
- Let's go.
- Ms. Yang.
You don't really think
you can get into the Yulin Group
through Yang Nana, do you?
What's it to you?
Do you really think
your little tricks with Shaofei
will work as you wish?
Sorry.
I'm really sorry, Ms. Yang.
Your flight is tonight.
Why?
Because I am your
dead uncle.
What are you doing?
This outfit doesn't suit you.
Don't wear it again.
Okay.
If you ask me to take it off,
I'll take it off.
I'll go over.
Long time no see.
Ms. Li. Ms. Shen.
Ms. Yang.
It's very flattering.
A new product launches today, I heard.
Of course, perfect for you.
Gangzi.
This scent is unique.
About this scent,
its top notes are leaves and wild roses.
Am I right, Ms. Yang?
Gangzi.
The middle notes...
It's not right.
It's not my perfume.
How could that be?
This isn't my bag.
You can't even tell?
There's no time.
Hello, everyone.
Great welcome to
the new product launch
of our Yulin Group.
We present this perfume with sincerity.
Ms. Yang,
your new perfume is quite unique.
But what are the middle notes?
The middle notes...
I knew it.
A nanny previously.
How...
Ms. Yang.
Who is this?
The middle notes of this perfume are
plum trees,
mimosa and clary sage.
Right, Ms. Yang?
Right.
We were just waiting for her.
Meet our new team member.
Her name is...
My name is Song Yiyi.
Song, right.
So next,
Song will
tell us briefly about
the creative concept
behind this new perfume.
Good. Good.
(Our perfume)
- (features a rare aquatic note.)
- Mr. Xue.
- (Its inspiration is drawn from)
- Miss Song aims to
- (a sunset-drenched beach.)
- join the R&D team.
- Shall we...
- It's fine.
(Its fragrance)
(takes you to a summer dusk
with sea breezes.)
Let her enjoy happiness a bit more.
Let us indulge in a dream
of unrestrained joy
in this serene and slightly tipsy night.
So what is the name of this perfume?
(Yulin Group)
Song.
Our perfume is named "Stealth",
embodying a fleeting existence
veiled by falsehoods.
Light and shadow intertwine,
with no interference.
Good.
- Good.
- Good, good.
Song, you can do it.
Hmm.
(Mom.)
(This is where you used to work.)
(Here I am.)
(Why I'm in the parking lot?)
What exactly do you want?
Go to the airport.
Three years ago,
you took away my mom's shares.
Isn't that enough
to exchange for my freedom?
Drive.
Master.
- Master. Master.
- Shaofei?
Master, open the door.
Master.
Shaofei, what do you want?
Master, you can't take Song away.
She's not your Ms. Right.
No matter what,
I just hope Song can do what she wants.
Naive.
Drive.
Master.
What you want?
- Out of your mind?
- Master.
- Why meddle in my life?
As long as you are not married,
- I've the right.
- Master.
Fine.
Then I will get married right now.
Stop the car.
Shaofei.
Are you willing to marry me?
Marry me.
(How dare you take my man?)
Miss Song and Mr. Meng
met while studying abroad.
This time, it's also Mr. Meng
who helped her join the Yulin Group.
However,
would you really see Miss Song
marry Mr. Meng?
Do you know how to make roses thrive?
The damaged part
must be cut off promptly.
A softer heart
just makes the roses wilt faster.
♪Love cannot be told or showed♪
♪Determined to speak up, with no waver♪
♪Tears cannot fall or stray♪
♪Refusing to sink with aimless drifting♪
♪Vows merge like converging streams♪
♪Yet they keep us apart♪
♪Maybe destiny isn't out of reach♪
♪Time is the mistake♪
♪As I slowly approach the vortex♪
♪I hear only the bursting silence♪
♪A chain binds quietly, sealing my ears♪
♪Embracing the vortex with all my might♪
♪I feel my body falling♪
♪A past promise♪
♪Seals my body tight♪