[Dark Night and Dawn]
[Episode 30]
Yes.
He did play well.
But he forgot who we are—
the ones who can flip the board at any time.
That's a good point.
Eat before you go.
Okay.
Sir,
as requested by Taiwan,
we've already sent the coordinates
for important facilities like power plants,
water plants, and mechanical equipment.
Not just coordinates,
and the weather,
wind direction,
factory safety, production, and prevention.
Li Xu needs to get a handle on
their rhythm and pattern.
The more precise, the better.
Okay.
The New Year is coming, right?
Let's set off some firecrackers
to ward off the evil spirits and bring luck.
Go grab a bottle of liquor.
Alright, let's have a drink.
This time, a total of 67 bombs were
dropped over Shanghai.
The aim was to
cause large-scale blackouts and water cuts in Shanghai.
They took off from Zhoushan Airport,
attacking Shanghai in four waves.
Hurry!
Bring a stretcher, quick!
There's someone down there.
Coming.
Quick, lift him onto the stretcher.
Be careful.
Careful, careful!
Hurry!
Dr. Wang.
Get the patient out first.
Over there!
Hurry!
Stretcher.
Two people over here.
Wrap up.
Yaohong, here, here, here!
How are you?
Huzi.
Nurse!
Shaobai!
Don't move him! Shaobai!
Doctor! Doc-
Hurry up.
His neck.
Nurse!
Be careful. The bombs are coming any minute.
Dr. Jin, there are more severe cases over here!
Hang in there, dude!
-Help him!
-Hang in there.
Take care of him.
Over here.
Get a stretcher.
Stretcher.
Hang in there.
Hurry. Here.
Dude.
Coming.
The stretcher is here.
There, hurry up!
Stretcher, over here!
Do something! Hurry!
And...
Hold on!
You must hold on!
Shaobai.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let's get out of here!
Hang in there.
Dude.
Wang, Zhao, hurry to save people.
Hurry!
Hurry up!
One, two.
Shaobai!
What?
What are you doing?
Let me go!
I'm going to shoot that bastard!
Put the gun down, now.
Put the gun down!
Put the gun down.
I want to kill him too,
but not now.
We still have to wait.
Lu,
this is Shanghai.
This is my home.
I'm useless, Lu.
Listen,
listen,
I promise you,
I will let him
and the people behind him
pay for what they did today.
Every single one of them.
I'm a man of my word.
Trust me.
Ten miles,
all plunged into darkness.
The last time Shanghai was
this quiet at night must've been
when it was still a small fishing village.
Boss,
the Yangshupu Power Plant was hit by over a dozen bombs.
There's a massive blackout across Shanghai.
Almost all factories in the city have shut down production.
Even the water plant's affected.
If this keeps up,
it won't be long before they cause trouble at the Communist
Military Control.
Mr. Mao is pleased.
He sent a telegram to commend us.
With this operation,
he's likely to join the Political Action Committee
under Mr. Chingkuo's direct leadership.
We'll get even more support in the future.
The reason
our party has fallen so far
is because
we haven't dealt with the people who need to be killed.
Send a reply to Mr. Mao.
Tell him
the next set of bombing coordinates
will be
provided soon.
Chief,
if this bombing continues,
Shanghai will be ruined.
Even if we reclaim it,
we'll only get a pile of rubble.
What's destroyed are just insignificant ants.
Shanghai will always be Shanghai.
No one can change that fact.
What we're doing now
is purifying Shanghai completely.
The city's water and power supply are still under repair.
Chiang's forces chose this time to bomb us.
What's their aim?
They want to turn Shanghai into
a city without water and electricity,
to paralyze the lives of ordinary people,
to ruin our New China's
first New Year.
Their intentions are truly despicable.
They're taking advantage of us because we lack
air force and air control.
Mr. Yang,
I'll go get some water.
Put it there.
Come, sit down.
Okay.
They think they can bully us because we don't have
air force and air control.
But that's just their wishful thinking.
Can we just sit and wait?
Let me tell you,
after coordination by the central government,
the Soviets are sending an Air Force Corps.
They'll soon arrive secretly in Shanghai.
By then,
we'll set up
a joint Air Defense Command Post.
I was thinking of
assigning you to assist in
ensuring the security of the command center.
Rest assured,
I'll complete the task.
I actually think
this is
a great chance to eliminate Shrike.
You mean
it's time to take advantage of the mole?
Look,
you can't block the light.
How long has it been?
Not even 42 hours,
and Shanghai has already restored water and electricity.
Kuomintang's
bombings and schemes—
against us Communists and the people—
are nothing but an ant shaking a tree.
They won't succeed.
Mrs. Zhang,
the food's almost ready.
Go get the comrade from
the well-drilling team to eat.
Alright.
Madam,
add a dish,
luncheon meat.
I usually don't even eat this myself.
Mr. Wang,
how come you have so much luncheon meat?
Did you stock up during the Liberation?
What are you talking about?
This is fresh!
Look, look.
Doesn't seem like Mr. Wang's style at all.
He's usually so stingy.
Not anymore.
Who are you calling stingy?
Who's stingy?
Look,
the Kuomintang's planes bombed us,
leaving us without water or electricity.
The well-drilling team has been working
day and night to dig wells for us,
without asking for money.
What's the big deal of these?
Mr. Wang,
you're quite enlightened now.
United
we stand,
right?
You've improved.
Of course.
All the men in Taiping Lane went to
help with the rescue.
The women
either sew sandbags
or cook meals.
I can't fall behind.
Indeed.
Grandma Lin,
where's Uncle Lin?
He's with the well-drilling team.
Why?
Aunt Jin Yan called for him,
said it's urgent.
I'll go get him.
-Slow down.
Don't fall.
Asked me to provide Shanghai's
recovery and production plans?
As soon as possible.
These factories
will be our main targets in the next
round of bombing.
You're bombing again?
Falcon,
I'm already under watch by the police.
Everything I do will be in vain.
If something goes wrong,
we're all doomed.
You need to complete the task I've given you.
Don't make me repeat myself.
A few days ago, with Li Yuquan's issue,
I did save your life after all.
I also want to ask you—
were you trying to save me
or kill me?
I asked my people.
They said it was a warning shot.
A warning shot?
Shooting into the air is a warning,
but shooting at me is not.
You have my weakness.
No matter what I say or do,
it's wrong.
You should
be less calculative
and cooperate with us.
We won't harm Jin Yan.
You know,
this is the deal you made with Shrike.
At your age,
I assume you have a wife and kids, right?
Why do you ask?
I can tell that.
You couldn't kill me,
so now you're going after my family?
It seems that this knot will never be untied.
Falcon,
you and Shaobai
were once partners,
and technically, you're my junior.
Shrike holds something over me,
making me work for him.
But I think you're different.
Forget it if you mind.
I really am different.
I chose this willingly.
Shrike treats me well.
Good, then.
That's good.
I read in the papers—
the last Falcon,
Wang Liqun,
was his student.
To get promoted,
he betrayed Wang Liqun's
own brother
to the Japanese.
What are you trying to say?
I'm saying that
everything we do
is for our families.
I think you're the same.
You talk too much.
I'll get you Shanghai's recovery plan
as soon as I can.
Are you looking for me, Yan?
Look at these two reports.
One is the anthrax test report,
and the other is Li Yuquan's autopsy.
[Shanghai Health Laboratory]
Comparing the two reports,
[Inspection time: January 25, 1950]
Li Yuquan died before
the anthrax bacteria started to die off.
This means
the bacteria research base at the sugar factory
was moved after Li Yuquan's death.
[Testing Precautions]
Uncle Jin
may have connections with the agents.
We all know Uncle Jin.
If he's helping agents,
he must be under some threat,
having no choice.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
Shaobai,
do you have solid evidence?
I have a way to verify it.
Mr. Jin,
why is the lady's car door open?
It's...
Ms. Zhang.
Has Yan come back?
Not yet.
Is this the Forensics Department?
Is Dr. Jin Yan there?
I'm her father.
Dr. Jin left after her shift.
Okay.
Madam,
has
Shaobai come back?
Not yet,
still working overtime.
What's wrong, Jin?
No, it's nothing.
I'll wait until he's back.
Goodbye.
Zhou, drive.
Let's go.
Zhou, drive faster.
Go to Lanting Studio.
Okay.
Shaobai,
follow them.
Mr. Jin,
do you suspect
Shrike sent someone to kidnap the lady?
We're almost at Lanting Studio.
Don't stop.
Continue driving.
Where are we going?
The Social Affairs Office.
Mr. Jin,
calm down. Have some water first.
How long will Director Lu be back?
He went to the bureau for a meeting.
He should be back soon.
I'll ask him to come here when he comes back.
Okay.
I have something to do.
Come on.
Hide here.
This is Lu's office.
They won't come in without reason.
Uncle Jin just reported it.
If Lu knows about this,
we will be in trouble.
Director Lu.
Dr. Jin.
What are you doing here?
Come here.
What's wrong?
I'll make it short.
Uncle Jin might think
Yan was kidnapped by agents.
He's here to report it.
You're testing him?
Why didn't you inform me first?
You may not agree even if I ask in advance.
There's no time to explain.
Uncle Jin is downstairs now.
I'll deal with you later.
You can scold me all you want,
but Uncle Jin's already here.
Let's deal with him first.
Wait for me here.
It's okay.
Shaobai.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Mr. Jin.
I just got back from a mission.
Uncle Jin.
Director Lu.
Yan is missing.
I suspect she was kidnapped.
Mr. Jin, calm down.
Take your time.
When I got home, I saw Yan's car,
but the window and door were left open.
Yan isn't a careless person.
I've searched the whole house
and the Forensics Department.
She's nowhere to be found.
Doesn't this look like a kidnapping?
So, you think
Dr. Jin was taken from right
outside your house?
It's possible.
Uncle Jin,
don't be too upset.
Of course I am!
Yan is my only daughter!
She might be kidnapped now!
If something really happens to her,
do you understand
my feelings of a father?
Mr. Jin,
try to stay calm.
We'll do everything we can to find Dr. Jin
and inform you immediately.
I'm sorry, Uncle Jin.
New Year is coming soon.
If anything happens to Yan,
how can I spend the New Year?
Mr. Jin.
Director Lu.
Your dad's really worried about you.
Shaobai,
did my dad say anything?
Not much,
just that he's worried.
No news is good news.
Don't stress too much, Yan.
Kidnapped?
I'll see how you wrap this up.
I'll find a way to explain to my dad.
Sorry to trouble you, Director Lu.
Shaobai,
I'm leaving.
Mr. Jin,
how did you figure out
the Social Affairs Office was testing you?
I think it's probably
just Yan acting on her own.
Shrike has no reason
to kidnap Yan
over the recovery plan,
especially since I already agreed to help.
So where are we going now?
Home.
Let's wait for Yan at home.
Okay.
What do you think about
Jin Maochang's behavior today?
Are you suggesting he came
to the Social Affairs Office on purpose?
There are two possibilities.
One, he truly believed
Jin Yan was kidnapped by agents.
The other is that
he's aware we're testing him
because of the Li Yuquan case.
He came to report because he found something.
So it could be his strategy
coming here to report.
[Be modest, cautious, humble, and patient]
Lu,
I also felt something was off.
Since I went to his house to investigate white phosphorus,
Uncle Jin has been acting strange.
Plus what happened later,
I think he is hiding something from me.
We've been following Uncle Jin today.
Is it possible that we were discovered?
[Be modest, cautious, humble, and patient]
That's possible.
If so, his visit to the Social Affairs Office
was a test for us.
Tracking and counter tracking.
It's not as simple as you think.
Alright.
What do you think
we should do about Uncle Jin?
[Be modest, cautious, humble, and patient]
Do nothing.
You and Jin Yan
stop making any moves.
Let Jin Maochang believe
we no longer
suspect him.
I understand.
Dad.
You're still up?
You're finally back.
I was so worried.
I went to the hospital.
What happened?
It's nothing.
On the way home,
I saw an accident at the intersection,
so I helped take the injured to the hospital.
I've been busy until now.
Oh, that's what happened.
What's wrong, Dad?
Nothing.
I was just worried because it was so late
and you weren't home,
so I went to the Public Security Bureau to report it.
Tell Director Lu about it.
Since you are back,
ask him to cancel the report.
Okay, Dad.
I'm already an adult.
You don't have to worry so much.
No matter how grown-up you are,
you're still my daughter.
You must be tired.
Go upstairs and rest.
Mr. Jin,
how did you figure out
the Social Affairs Office was testing you?
I think it's probably
just Yan acting on her own.
I don't blame you.
As long as you're fine.
The higher-ups are very pleased
with the bombing operation.
They sent congratulations
and praised
everyone of us.
It's my duty.
The New Year is coming.
I think we should do something.
Use some funds to buy
New Year's goods for every household
to
express thanks to their families.
Li Xu, you handle it.
Okay.
Purchasing
and distributing.
Be careful.
Falcon,
as the action team's leader,
I think you should stay,
in case any operations come up.
Okay.
No objections.
But, Chief,
I think I'm the better
for this mission.
I'm wanted in Shanghai,
so I can't move around.
I could lay low for a few days in Zhejiang.
Besides,
I have a lot of experience in action.
I can handle any
unexpected situations.
I think there's another reason
that's more valid
than what you just said.
Is Zhao Lan going to give birth?
Yes.
You should go check on her.
Okay.
Then
you two swap duties.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to express my greetings
with these spring couplets.
Thank you, Chief.
Pack these up.
[Lanting Studio]
How is it going in Lanting Studio?
Everything is fine.
Xu Wei has bought a lot of goods recently,
like he's preparing to visit relatives.
Keep a close watch on him.
Now that we've removed Li Yuquan,
we can act more freely.
Do we have
enough manpower?
If we follow them separately,
it's a bit tight.
If you need anything,
just ask Zhou for help.
Whether it's money or a place,
he'll provide it.
Got it.
Recruit people as soon as possible.
What kind of people do you need?
Just three things:
good fighters,
tight-lipped,
and only care about money.
I wish they were all like your brother.
You're not bad either.
I'll do my best.
Mr. Jin, what's this for?
New Year's money for the two kids.
Take it.
It's for the kids.
Their father is gone.
Poor things.
Buy them some nice clothes and food
so they can have a good New Year.
Thank you,
Mr. Jin.
I'll head back now.
Elder Grandma,
why is the "Fu" character upside down?
Because it's the New Year,
so the good fortune has arrived.
Younger Grandma,
why are you sweeping so high?
That's called
"dusting the eaves."
It sweeps away bad luck—
the more we sweep, the more prosperous we'll be.
Got it?
Feihang,
go check if Uncle Lin
and the others have come back.
Okay.
Uncle, Uncle Lin.
Feihang.
They're back.
Let's go.
You're wearing new clothes, Feihang.
So beautiful.
Hello, Mr. Lu.
Happy New Year.
There was some work at the office,
so I'm a bit late.
It's okay.
Happy New Year.
You brought gifts?
I told him not to, but he insisted.
Said you all like it.
He insisted to buy.
Now that everyone's here,
I'll start preparing the New Year's dinner.
Okay.
I'll go bring out the dishes.
Need help?
No, no.
Shaobai, come help me.
Let's go help.
Grandma, let me help you.
Come on. Good girl.
Feihang wants to help too.
Take a seat.
Dad.
I'm back.
Stand still.
Wash your hands. Time to eat.
Has Ms. Zhang gone home?
Yes,
I gave her the holiday off.
It's New Year.
Everyone should reunite with their families.
Go get changed.
No.
The hospital's short on staff.
I'll have dinner with you
and then go back to help.
Just the two of us here.
It's always so quiet
around the New Year.
You're just used to the hustle and bustle.
Whether it's at the factory or in business,
you're always surrounded by people.
So, it feels off when
it comes to the New Year.
Being with them is all for work.
Being with my daughter, that's real peace.
Having you with me,
I'm very content.
Here's a gift for you.
Thank you, Dad.
Dad.
I wish you
health and longevity.
Yan, I wish you
beauty and safety.
Thank you, Dad.
Come on, Feihang.
Serve your Auntie first.
Have an egg dumpling.
It brings wealth and prosperity, okay?
Come on.
Here, Feihang,
have a meatball.
Here.
May we all be united.
Now, thank Grandma.
Thank you, Grandma.
Come on,
have some chili,
for a life full of energy.
Good for you.
Well,
Director Lu,
can I call you Zhengyang from now on?
Have some shrimp.
It means "welcome"
in Shanghainese.
-Yes.
-Welcome.
Thank you.
Mr. Zhengyang,
are you used to Shanghai cuisine now?
I'm getting used to it.
The more I eat, the better it tastes.
Really?
Feihang and I
haven't celebrated the New Year like this for years.
We should thank you
and Shaobai.
Don't be so polite.
Since Feihang came,
my moms have been so much happier.
Right?
Yeah.
Since she came,
our house has been livelier.
Yes.
We should thank you.
Yeah.
Thank you, Feihang.
Would you like some soup?
The power's out again.
Power's out?
I'll go get candles.
I'll do it.
Fireworks!
Look, everyone!
Look at that.
With the lights out, the fireworks shine even brighter.
Yes.
Feihang,
look at the fireworks.
Does it look like a blooming flower?
Isn't it beautiful?
Yes.
Fireworks and firecrackers, just like always.
When have the people of Shanghai
ever been scared?
We'll make it through.
We will, for sure!
Dad.
I've washed the dishes.
Now I'll
go back to the hospital.
It's dark outside,
and the hospital's cold.
Take this blanket with you.
Thanks, Dad.
There's a little girl who keeps kicking off her covers.
She can use it.
Take care of yourself too.
I have you,
always taking the best care of me.
Hearing that
makes it all worth it.
I'm leaving.
Dad,
happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
Here you go.
Here, take it.
Thank you.
This eight-treasure rice is delicious.
We made it ourselves.
Here.
Thank you.
You're so kind.
We're bombed every day.
We don't even have a place to cook,
let alone a New Year's meal.
You're welcome.
Let's all happily welcome
the New Year together.
Okay.
Okay?
Good people are blessed.
Take it.
Thank you.
We made the pastries too.
There's enough for every household.
Xiaohua,
you're like a little cat.
Go home and give her a bath.
Let's start
the New Year clean.
Okay?
Here.
Here you go.
Come on.
Help yourselves.
Don't forget the pastries.
Take it.
Pastries.
Help yourself.
It's New Year.
Let's have a drink.
Pour it up.
Thanks.
How about
I drink with you?
Sure.
Pour it up.
Sir,
happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
Take it easy.
Here.
Have a bite
to go with it.
Sir.
What's wrong?
Let's have a baby.
You're drunk after one drink?
I'm not drunk.
It's time to let bygones be bygones.
Hello?
I've sent out the recovery plan.
Thank you.
The Year of the Ox is finally over.
Yeah.
The Year of the Tiger is coming.
Wish you
the strength of a roaring tiger.
And wish you
safety in the Year of the Tiger.
We should all stay safe.
Come here, come here.
Is it beautiful?
Yes.
Make a wish.
I wish
our child
can be born healthy
and grow up
happily.
I also wish for
your peace,
health,
and happiness.
And I hope
our family can
always stay together,
never apart.
Tracking is a key skill for
us investigators.
It's not as simple as you think.
Years of police experience
might work with ordinary suspects,
but dealing with agents
requires specialized training.
[Xinxing Pharmacy]
[Taiping Lane No.11]
Thank you.
Give it to me.
I want one.
Shanghai People's Radio,
March 14th.
Tonight,
two B25 bombers of the Kuomintang
flew over the Jiangnan Shipyard,
getting hit head-on by our anti-aircraft fire.
A B25 bomber was shot down
while the other fled in panic.
This is the fourth enemy aircraft
shot down this month.
Mayor Chen Yi
stated after the 2.6 bombing
that we must protect
Shanghai's skies at all costs.
According to intelligence from Taiwan,
it wasn't anti-aircraft fire that
took down our planes—
but a new Soviet Warrior Migg15.
The Soviet Air Force Corps has stationed in Shanghai.
The Communists are trying to
take control of the skies.
We need to take out their
command center.
No matter how many planes they send,
we'll turn them into scrap metal.
The Communists will guard it fiercely.
It'll be hard to pinpoint
their command post.
Start with Lu Zhengyang.
He used to work
in political security,
so he's likely responsible for their safety.
Falcon,
you
inform Nyctibius
to prepare for a new mission.
Yes, sir.