[Dark Night and Dawn]
[Episode 20]
I know nothing I say now will help.
You think just because you weren't driving, you're in the clear?
Public or private,
right or wrong, friend or foe—
when will you learn to
distinguish these?
You knew Xu Wei's whereabouts.
Why didn't you report it
and acted without telling us?
Do you realize that
catching Xu Wei
could lead us straight to identifying the identity of Shrike
and completely eliminating these agents?
But he's still my brother.
We've been together for so many years.
He wasn't a bad person back then.
I always thought I could save him.
Now, to completely disregard our brotherhood—
honestly,
I can't do it.
I just can't get over this.
My heart is flesh.
Your heart is flesh.
Isn't mine flesh?
So many people have sacrificed.
They were under my leadership.
Their parents ask me for their sons,
and their wives for their husbands.
What should I tell them?
Tell me,
what should I tell them?
I'm sorry.
This is indeed my fault.
Yes,
you're unworthy of the title
"People's Police."
Do you think
an old cop like me
can never be a good police?
Whether you can be a good police,
you have to
ask yourself.
You're right.
Whether it's punishment or sentence, I accept it.
Take him away
to await punishment.
The first time I came here,
I was in handcuffs.
Now, it's the same.
I know the way.
Let's go.
He's waiting for you.
You didn't follow Shrike's order and almost got caught.
You're on your own now.
Chief,
I have nothing to say.
I'm at your disposal.
If your subordinate made such a mistake,
how would you handle it?
Minor ones get punished,
and major ones
get shot.
Think about it.
You could shoot me, too.
Just like
you killed Wang Liqun.
Maybe killing me
will make you the Chief.
Take care of Zhao Lan for me.
You know the rules.
Very good.
The flowers Feihang drew are interesting.
Is this a car?
You made it yourself, huh?
Don't make fun of the new student.
Focus on your drawing.
Feihang,
do you prefer
cars more?
I like flowers too.
I just want to draw something more useful.
I'll build them in the future.
You think cars are more useful
and want to build them?
Great. I support your idea.
But
I think
you are learning how to draw,
right?
So you need to first grasp
the basics of drawing.
For example, the perspective and proportion.
When we look at things,
the closer things are bigger,
right?
Distant ones are smaller
and their
colors will be lighter.
The closer one's color will be heavier.
If you understand these concepts of
perspective, proportion, and shading,
whatever you draw will be right.
I don't understand.
It's okay. Let me show you, okay?
Come on.
Let me draw a leaf for you, okay?
This leaf is big.
Let's draw two flowers.
This one is bigger, okay?
Okay.
What do you think this is?
Does it look like a car?
Yes.
So, I used flowers
to assemble a car for you.
My point is,
don't just draw something because it's useful.
Once you choose a subject to draw,
treat it seriously.
It should reflect your fundamental
understanding of drawing.
Now, you try.
The towel's gone.
Did you take the wrong one?
Forget it,
I'll find it for you.
Next time.
No, you're not cleaned up yet.
Don't move.
Thank you.
I remember when we first came to Shanghai,
so many soldiers
had never seen electric lights
or showerheads.
They fiddled with the switches
and made a lot of jokes.
Exactly.
I remember back then
everyone was watching us,
wondering how these country folks
would manage Shanghai.
Luckily, our local comrades
helped us a lot
and we got used it.
Look at our Office 2.
Looks like
you're beating around the bush
to speak well of Lin Shaobai, aren't you?
Nothing gets past you.
Lin Shaobai's been in solitary confinement
for days now.
I was planning to have him publicly
reflect at the department
to warn the others.
It's gentle.
Gentle? I'll hit you harder.
I mean the punishment is too gentle.
He's lack of discipline.
Someone as reckless as him will
definitely cause big trouble in the future.
Yes.
One bad apple
spoils the bunch.
Lin Shaobai
knows Shanghai well
and has solved many cases,
but that doesn't offset his faults.
Someone like him
should be expelled from the Public Security Bureau.
Too heavy.
Mr. Yang,
I also think the punishment is too heavy.
Your hands are heavy.
I'll be gentler then.
Lin Shaobai has made so many mistakes
and must be expelled.
Hu, what are you looking at?
The Director is discussing Lin Shaobai
with Deputy Commissioner Yang.
Keep it down.
Anyway, our Office 2
won't keep him any longer.
I hope that's what you really think.
Haven't you heard?
Hu from the Police Pigeon Squad told me,
Lin Shaobai always goes to him.
Look, someone from our office
neglects his duties.
Mr. Yang,
he can't do anything great.
Just right for keeping pigeons.
After all this talk,
this is what you're trying to say.
Alright.
Only expel Lin Shaobai
from your office then.
Aren't I the head of the Office 2?
Now you're meddling in the Police Pigeon Squad too.
You've already figured out a way out for Lin Shaobai.
I'm
mainly helping Hu.
The Police Pigeon Squad isn't under your control.
If anything goes wrong,
who will be responsible?
Me.
I'll take responsibility.
If there's any problem,
I'll face punishment with him,
even expulsion.
Nonsense!
You've already vouched for him once.
Well, Mr. Yang,
this is the last time.
I promise!
One more mistake and he's out.
Thank you so much!
Where's my towel?
Here.
Director,
you always have a way.
What way?
It's Deputy Commissioner Yang who values talent.
Lu,
I haven't heard Hu asking for him.
Let's get the leaders' approval first,
then I'll talk to Hu.
Once Hu agrees, let him go
clean pigeon droppings.
Where are we heading
after all this time?
The boss said,
you're in for the strictest punishment.
Just wait.
Lan.
Wei.
Wei, what took you so long?
Almost done.
Thank you.
Let's enjoy ourselves today.
While you were away,
Ms. Zhang and Mr. Wang took good care of me.
They know I'm pregnant,
and won't let me do anything.
Look, I've become fat.
They handle big things, and we support at home.
We're all family here.
Mom, is everything okay here?
Yes, don't worry.
Work hard with your boss.
Okay.
Don't worry. We're here.
Now, people here
think we are a family.
You two can work hard outside,
and leave the home to me.
Rest assured.
Mr. Wang, a toast to you.
Cheers.
Oh,
there's soup.
I'll go get it.
Sit down, I'll get it.
I'll go with you.
The boss said,
this is to teach you a lesson
you'll never forget.
No more mistakes from now on.
This is the last chance.
Reward for punishment.
I will never forget it.
Cheers.
Wang.
Lan.
today is like a dream.
Once your job is done,
that dream will come true.
When the time comes,
we'll find a place like this
to settle down.
Okay?
I still want to go back to Shanghai.
Can you talk to your superior
to transfer you
to a different post?
I'd like to be back before the baby is born.
Just wait a bit longer.
Trust me,
I'll make sure you and the baby
live a happy life.
Trust me.
I trust you.
Come get me soon.
Okay.
Why are you here?
The punishment is out?
Whatever it is, I'll take it.
You're just
being stubborn.
Trying to play tricks
and say things at wtll.
You think this is some martial arts novel?
Is this all
you're capable of?
Xu.
Just say it.
Spit it out.
How many years?
If Lu hadn't pleaded for you,
you would've been sentenced to three to five years.
He actually pleaded for me?
I thought he'd be happy to see me dead.
How much do you know about Lu?
He put his own career
on the line to keep you here.
At least he's loyal.
Stop talking about loyalty.
If you continue to act recklessly, he'll be implicated.
Don't worry, Xu.
He's never bet wrong on me.
I won't let him lose.
You can't stay in the Social Affairs Office anymore.
There's a spot in the Police Pigeon Squad.
Do you want to go?
Me, raising pigeons?
No, the pigeon poop stinks.
I'm a police officer.
I don't run a farm.
Why would I go there?
Lu asked me to tell you,
if you go,
you can still be a police officer.
If you don't, you can never come back.
Are you okay?
Feihang, are you okay?
Feihang.
Feihang, get up.
Feihang!
Feihang.
Are you okay?
What happened?
Feihang.
Mr. Zheng, I really appreciate it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It's our duty as teachers.
Feihang has congenital heart disease.
You should know it.
I know.
The doctor just said
if she had arrived a little later,
it could've been life-threatening.
So, you need to inform
the school about such situations.
For example, you know me,
so you could've told me,
or if you don't trust me,
that's fine,
inform the principal
or another teacher.
If something like this happens again,
we can be prepared.
I was careless.
Director Lu, I have a suggestion for you.
Go ahead.
I understand
your work is busy,
but no matter how busy,
you can't neglect your child's health.
You're right.
I have classes at school.
I'll leave it to you.
Okay, Mr. Zheng, thank you.
Goodbye.
Sorry for taking up your time.
It's okay.
[Doctors Work Code II]
This congenital heart disease
is quite serious.
Our hospital isn't
equipped for surgery yet.
You need to make plans as soon as possible.
[Doctors Work Code II]
Thank you, doctor.
Okay.
Director, this is a big deal.
Why didn't you tell us earlier?
We could have all helped out,
finding a way together.
It's okay.
[Doctors Work Code II]
Uncle, I fell asleep again.
It's okay.
I'm here.
You will be fine.
So don't worry, Uncle.
By the way,
why did Mr. Zheng send you here?
He must be passing by.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I misunderstood Mr. Zheng before.
Now we owe him such a big favor.
I don't know how to repay it.
Mr. Zheng is very nice to me.
He taught me how to draw patiently.
Now everyone praises me that
my drawing is getting better.
Really?
Then, when you're better,
you'll draw one for me.
Let's see if it looks like me.
Sure, I'll draw it for you when I'm better.
Replace these rats,
and bring in a new batch.
Remember, burn them
and bury them deep.
Yes.
Here.
Stop digging.
Let's go.
Dr. Jin,
do you have
Song Ci's "Collected Cases of Injustice Rectified"?
May I borrow it?
Here.
Thank you.
Why did you borrow so many books?
You never know you need them until you do.
I have to work hard.
I've looked into it.
These are all Western
books on physiology and anatomy.
In 1905,
the Governor of the Eastern Three Provinces and the Viceroy
set up an institute for inspection studies in Jilin,
taking in young people.
If I remember right,
it was in 1908.
Yes, the third year after that.
In 1908,
those young people
specifically studied these
Western books on physiology and anatomy.
After graduation, they replaced the earlier coroners
which are what we now call medical examiners.
Looks like you're determined this time.
I've burned my boats.
I have to learn to grow up.
I can't always be a burden to others.
After these books, you also need to read
Professor Lin Ji's
"Criminal Investigation Studies"
and "General Forensics."
[Criminal Investigation Studies]
Lin who?
Lin Ji.
He laid the foundation for our country's forensic science system.
Which Ji is that?
Look it up yourself.
Hello?
Mr. Yang.
What?
There are several more cases of anthrax?
Okay, Mr. Yang.
I used to work with Dr. Zhao.
I'll follow up on it.
Okay, I'm on my way now.
Liu Rui, let's head to Guangci Hospital.
Okay.
[Criminal Investigation Studies]
These five people came to the hospital one after another,
no more than three days apart.
Using infectious disease investigation methods,
[Initial diagnosis: Cutaneus anthrax]
I've recorded all their family members'
health statuses.
Fortunately, none were infected.
So the source of the infection shouldn't be near their homes.
The records also include all the places
they visited in the five days before getting sick.
Everything they could remember
has been written down.
They've all been to the Sitang River in Wusong District.
One of the patients works at the Sitang River.
[The source of the infection is the Sitang River in Wusong District.]
What does he do?
He's a sugar factory worker.
I remember him.
He was the first recent case to get sick.
Is it the Jin's Sugar Factory?
Excuse me.
Police.
Please open the door.
This is my ID.
[Seal of Shanghai People's Government Public Security Bureau]
Have you made an appointment with Mr. Li?
No.
Sorry, then.
You can't come in.
Sir, I'm a police officer.
We have an important investigation to conduct.
I don't care what you're investigating.
There's been too much news about PLA
imposters around here.
If I let in some agents, I'd lose my job.
[Seal of Shanghai People's Government Public Security Bureau]
How could I be an agent?
We suspect there's
a source of anthrax contamination at the sugar factory.
We need to conduct a sample investigation.
If the situation gets worse because of your interference,
it won't be just a loss of job.
How could there be anthrax at the sugar factory?
Open the door now.
Well, I...
I have to ask Mr. Li.
I'll say it one last time.
Anthrax is a highly infectious virus.
One more minute,
you might get infected too.
My name is Jin Yan.
I'll take responsibility if anything happens.
Open the door now.
Wait a minute.
I'll go get the key.
She said her name is Jin Yan.
I couldn't stop her.
Are you blind? She's the boss's daughter!
Get out!
Dr. Ogura.
The police are here.
They might visit your institute.
Stick to the plan.
Yes.
Be quick. I can't hold her off for long.
We've got samples from several workshops.
We still need to wait for the test results.
Let's go.
There's still one spot left.
Don't miss it. Let's take a look.
[Sugar Research Institute]
My Lady.
My Lady, what brings you here?
Mr. Li.
You came at the right time.
It's for work.
Please take us in.
No, no, no.
[Sugar Research Institute]
Please wait.
My Lady,
this area contains trade secrets.
Even I'm not allowed in.
The sugar factory is owned by the Jins.
I'm the daughter of the Jins. Would I leak secrets?
Mr. Li, right?
We're just here to take samples
to identify the source of the anthrax.
Turns out we're all family here.
Please cooperate.
What?
Anthrax?
My Lady,
you can't investigate it.
Our factory prioritizes hygiene above all.
You won't even find a fly here.
How could there be a source of contamination?
Once you enter,
whether there are bacteria or not,
if word gets out,
who would buy our sugar?
We couldn't do business anymore.
What's more important, business or human lives?
Two workers from the factory have been infected.
See for yourself.
Well...
To be safe,
I should ask Mr. Jin for his permission.
My Lady, you may not know.
Mr. Jin might be nice to you,
but he's very strict
with us subordinates.
Please.
I'll go in whether my dad agrees or not.
[Sugar Research Institute]
What are you waiting for?
Open the door.
My Lady,
as Mr. Jin ordered,
I won't go in.
[Isolation Area Keep Clean]
Excuse me.
We are the police.
This is a routine procedure.
We're here to collect samples.
Please leave.
Let's begin.
[Sugar Research Institute]
My Lady,
is there a problem?
After collecting the samples,
we need to go back for testing to get the results.
When will the results be out?
Are you in a hurry?
Not really.
After all, I'm the manager of this sugar factory.
I'm responsible for the whole plant.
But I'm confident there won't be any issues
with our factory,
especially the Sugar Research Institute.
It's managed directly by Mr. Jin,
cleaner than any other workshop here.
If there were any contamination source,
the researchers inside
would be the first to get infected.
They're all fine now.
I hope so.
We still need to collect samples nearby.
See you.
Take care.
Hello, this is Jin Maochang.
Keep an eye on your daughter.
Today she went to the sugar research institute
to investigate anthrax.
How did she suspect there?
It should be the hospital.
They received a few patients nearby.
That's your issue,
not mine.
Take care of your lab and
ensure no contamination leaks.
We'll handle it,
but if your daughter
sees something she shouldn't,
you know the consequences.
[Public phone]
I heard you went to the sugar factory today.
I was about to tell you.
Some factory workers
and people passing by have contracted anthrax.
There might be a source of infection nearby.
This is a big deal.
You must investigate it carefully.
But you were being too forceful
at the factory today.
The workers saw it.
They might talk about
you acting high and mighty.
It's not good for you.
If something like this happens again,
let me know first.
It was an emergency,
and I wanted to clarify the situation quickly
to prevent further infections.
Next time you investigate around the factory,
Mr. Li will assist you.
He's familiar with the surroundings.
Dad,
if you really want to help me,
just tell the factory
to let me in anytime.
No problem.
[Voting box]
One vote for Ye Fanshu.
[Taiping Lane Residents Meeting]
One vote for Li Zhaodi.
One vote for Zhou Kui.
[Voting box]
One vote for Liu Dongsheng.
One vote for Ye Gengshu.
I'm shy.
The voting is over.
[Taiping Lane Residents Meeting]
The top
three vote-getters are
Ye Gengshu,
[Voting box]
Li Guangtian,
[Taiping Lane Residents Meeting]
and
Zhang Xuemei.
Next, I'd like to invite them
to say a few words for us.
Let's welcome.
As the committee member,
our role is to strive for
[Taiping Lane Residents Meeting]
unity and welfare for everyone.
I promise
to do my utmost.
But let me be clear,
if you voted for me hoping for favors
[Taiping Lane Residents Meeting]
because of Shaobai's influence,
then I don't want this position.
Just appointed and already setting rules for us.
I didn't.
[Voting box]
Don't worry.
Shaobai isn't just your family's treasure
but also Taiping Lane's pride.
Yes.
Shaobai's handling big cases—
raiding gold vaults, catching counterfeiters,
[Taiping Lane Residents Meeting]
arresting agents.
We won't bother him with
our trivial matters.
People in our community are conscientious.
In that case, I'll take the position.
[Taiping Lane Residents Meeting]
Hello, Lanting Studio.
Mr. Zheng.
I'd like to meet you.
We at Xiya Watches
want to refresh our sign.
I'll visit you tomorrow.
How about now?
Let's go to Zhoushan.
Alright.
[On an Island in Zhoushan]
Follow me.
Director.
You're here.
Shrike.
Take a seat.
Director.
Come here.
Why are you here in person?
Staying in Xiamen is too stifling.
I need some fresh air.
Just send a telegram if you need anything.
It's too dangerous
to come out now.
There are over 1,000 islands in Zhoushan.
I'm not worried about them.
I'm worried about our internal affairs.
Lanting,
there are some
things I need to tell you.
You might not know.
While the front is fighting,
some at the rear
are playing dirty tricks,
even reaching into our NBIS.
They told me
the work at Shanghai Station is not good,
suggesting I remove you
as the Chief of the Shanghai Station.
I have a clear attitude.
If they want to remove you,
they have to remove me too.
To be honest,
if it wasn't for the Kuomintang,
I could have gone to America.
I understand.
Director,
I shouldn't
tell you these.
I didn't come here
just to complain.
There's something important.
Go ahead.
I heard from Guiheng that
some merchants in Shanghai
are storing up supplies.
Yes, that's true.
It's typical behavior of the people.
They're mainly stockpiling rice, cotton,
coal, and other
daily necessities.
So, I was thinking,
could we do something right now?
Look.
people in the Communist-controlled areas
need supplies
to live,
and so do the people
on the island.
If you could use your influence
to get a few dozen boats'
worth of grain and cotton
to the island,
that would be a great achievement.
And it could also shut up
those who criticize you from behind.
Normally, I shouldn't
refuse to do this.
But there have been
some changes at the Shanghai Station recently,
and the Communists have suspected me.
So, my plan is
to lie low for a while
and see how things go.
If we act rashly now,
I'm afraid...
I'm afraid it's too late.
Lanting, look,
with the war situation being so tense,
we must stand united.
We must achieve a great victory
to prove our Shanghai Station's loyalty.
Yes, at times like this,
we need to prioritize things.
If we run out of food, some people might starve,
but if we lose the Shanghai Station,
it will be nearly impossible for the NBIS
to establish a counteroffensive stronghold
in Shanghai in the future.
Shrike,
the Director came here himself.
Is this your attitude?
What do you mean, Secretary Liu?
That's what I mean.
Let me tell you,
acting impulsively now
might land you, Liu Guiheng,
in the Communist jail.
I'm not afraid of death.
Guiheng.
Stop arguing.
Lanting,
let me show you something.
A written instruction from the President?
Yes.
It could be seen as a commendation
for our Shanghai Station,
but also as encouragement
and expectation from the President.
Lanting,
I think the President wants a victory more than
anyone else right now.
Understood.
Dozens of ships' worth of grain is no small feat,
but I'll do my best to ensure it's done.
Okay.
The President
saw your effort, sir.
But
isn't it too risky
to take action now?
No venture, no gain.
We have to take the risk.
We can't let the President down.
Warm up some wine. Let's celebrate.
Okay.
Falcon will be back soon.
Ask Jin Maochang to get a new identity for him.
Okay.
I'm leaving. Enjoy.
Shaobai, have some too.
I have.
Come here.
Why are you working in police uniform today?
You have discipline. Don't you remember?
The counterfeit case has been solved.
I made a merit and got transferred to the bureau.
Really?
So, does that mean
you're getting promoted?
You could say that.
Now that I'm in the new post,
I basically have the final say.
Good for you, Shaobai.
Will it be busier
than the Social Affairs Office?
No way.
It'll be much more relaxed there,
and safer too.
I can even come home early to spend time with you.
Really?
Then come home early tonight.
I'll cook something nice for you.
Okay,
I'm leaving now.
Come home early.
Got it.
You're in good health,
climbing these stairs every day.
I've gotten used to it over the years.
You look weaker than me.
It's alright, not too breathless.
So many pigeons.
Of course there are pigeons.
This smell...
Fine.
Stop studying the smell.
Come here.
Attention!