[Dark Night and Dawn]
[Episode 36]
It's over.
It's all over.
There were only so few people left,
and they are all dead now.
I deserve it! I deserve it!
Why did I have to come back?
I almost died
for that little money!
How stupid!
[Xiya Timepiece Store]
Lu?
I knew you'd still be here.
If I left like that,
it'd be hard to explain to Deputy Commissioner Yang, right?
Deputy Commissioner Yang is very concerned about your safety.
He asked me to take you back as soon as possible.
Lu.
I can't go back with you now.
Why?
That letter of accusation was written by Liu Guiheng.
We all know
what he wants.
More importantly, Xu Wei is also in Shanghai now.
That means Shrike hasn't left yet.
Only by following Liu Guiheng's clue
can we find Shrike faster.
Even if you follow Liu Guiheng's clue,
it will still be very hard to find Shrike.
One false move,
and you could be in danger at any time.
If I can't find him, we can make him come to me.
We found ten gold bars,
eight gold watch,
and 10,000 US dollars
when we raided this place before.
I just noticed that the money hiding place
has been touched recently.
So it's very likely
that Liu Guiheng will
come back for that money.
We can find a way to lure him here.
Lu.
Shrike may release anthrax to society at any time.
Only by following Liu Guiheng's clue
can we catch him as fast as possible.
We can't lose this opportunity.
But I have to ensure your safety.
I understand.
But more importantly, we have to ensure
the safety of the people in our city.
Zhengyang.
What Shaobai said makes sense.
This is our only option now.
Don't worry.
I'm a lucky man.
I won't die so easily.
Have a candy to keep you safe.
Zhengyang.
What should we tell them when we go back?
What are you waiting for?
Go after him.
[Xiya Timepiece Store]
Chief.
Today's newspaper.
[Nanjing Arsenic Poisoning Case, Coffin Opened for Autopsy and Evidence Collection]
Are you new here?
Let me tell you
what your future work will be.
You need to read a lot of newspapers
or ask around somewhere.
I don't care.
But if you find any bridge collapsed,
any railway line got dug up,
or any government employee
or leader's obituary,
which means they died,
I don't care why,
but you have to
write it in the report to the higher-ups
and say
it was us who did that.
We...
So how did we do it specifically?
What an idiot.
Can't you just write
the collapsed bridge
was blown up
by us?
The destroyed railway line
was dug up by us?
Can't you write the government leader died
because we assassinated him?
Anyway, there is only one purpose.
Do whatever it takes
to get the funds approved by the higher-ups.
Do you understand what I said?
Yes.
Chief.
I saw this a couple of days ago.
On March 15,
Wang Xiangyi, the captain of
the Fourth Detachment of the Maritime Self-Defense Corps of Zhenan Administration,
a Kuomintang bandit who's been entrenched in Dachen,
led 1,500 people to
land in Songmen,
Linchuan, and Guanzhuang in three groups,
and harassed our people.
This is quality news.
Chief.
This incident happened
before you came.
And it failed very soon after that.
It failed, so what?
The Fourth Detachment failed,
but we can make up a Fifth Detachment
or a Sixth Detachment.
The purpose of us being here
is to keep fighting.
Although we've lost many battles,
we only became stronger and stronger.
1,500 people of the Fourth Detachment
died.
Then let's make
the head count of the Fifth Detachment 2,000.
This is how the report will be written.
I think
we're going too far
if we make it up like this, don't... Don't you think?
Who between us is the chief?
Just write
whatever I tell you to write.
Don't think too much.
Be bolder.
No one will check.
Commissioner Mao won't quibble over the details with me either.
The point is we must
make some achievements.
[Shop for Rent: No. 32 North Hutang Road, former Xiya Timepiece Store for rent]
Go to Xiya Timepiece Store
at No. 32 North Hutang Road now,
find out about its leasing situation,
and then come back and report to me.
Go.
Chief.
I know how to find out about it,
but how should I make this up
in the report?
Make what up?
What's there to make up about this?
Are you stupid?
There are just two things to do!
Go figure out its leasing situation,
and then come back and report to me!
Do you understand?
Yes!
Idiot.
Timepiece store for rent?
I searched there last time, but there was no gold bar.
No, I have to go search again.
[Xiya Timepiece Store]
[Shop for Rent: Low rent. Pre-lease now. Phone number: 4655]
Let's go.
Be careful.
[Shenghe]
Do you think you are Sherlock Holmes?
Lin Shaobai.
How have you been?
You've been good,
but I've been screwed by you.
Cut the crap.
Let's talk inside.
[Shenghe]
Notify Huzi
to bring a team here to support.
Yes.
[Shenghe]
Who do you think I'm photographing?
Turn around a bit.
Done.
Develop the photo later,
and write in the report to the higher-ups
that the backbone of the Social Affairs Office
of Shanghai Public Security Bureau...
No.
Put it down as Director.
Write that Director Lin Shaobai was captured by us.
Nothing is better
than some solid merits.
Secretary Liu.
So it was you who wrote
that letter of accusation?
It was indeed me.
How did you like it?
Listen to my advice.
If you come with me to the police station now and explain the situation,
you may be able to get a chance to redeem yourself.
Are you out of your mind?
You know where I am,
and you saw me.
You think you can leave?
Kill him.
Don't splatter blood everywhere.
Get a basin to hold his blood.
Ten gold bars, 10,000 US dollars, and 8 gold watch.
So you took them!
Do you know how long I've been looking for them?
Where is my money?
Give my money back!
Hey.
Why are you yelling so loudly?
After you left last time,
I was the one who searched your watch shop.
You know what I mean, right?
I'll strangle you to death!
Where is my money? Give it back to me!
I still remembered it just now,
but you suddenly scared me by strangling me.
The blood couldn't circulate in my brain,
so I forgot.
Where was it?
You think I don't know medicine,
right?
Trying to play tricks with me?
Give me the knife.
If you don't tell me
where my money is,
you'll be useless.
I'll stab you to death today, do you believe me?
If you kill me,
you'll never know where the money is.
You...
Why did you have to
tie me up so tightly?
You really wanted to strangle me to death?
Sorry.
Go get me some tea.
I'm a bit thirsty.
Serve tea.
Liu.
You go first.
Here's what I thought, Liu.
If I help you now,
I'll become an agent too.
I won't be able to stay in Shanghai anymore.
But I'm a native Shanghainese.
What should I do with the rest of my life?
Buddy.
You don't have to worry about that.
I can take you to Taiwan
or Hong Kong by then.
You can choose where you want to stay.
And I'll get you a job there.
You'll have nothing to worry about.
There's too little meat for too many wolves in Taiwan, if you know what I mean.
You don't have to lie to me.
I know it very well.
My friend.
You, get out.
I have
been promoted to the chief of Shanghai Special Station.
Now my words weigh a lot
in NBIS.
Even Commissioner Mao Renfeng
has to show me some respect...
Or should I say, honor me.
Hey.
Liu.
You're the chief now?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I'm a little hungry.
How about we talk while eating?
Sure.
Get us some dishes.
Chief Liu.
Who is it?
At such a late hour.
[Shenghe]
Don't speak.
How's the taste?
The beef from Huang's
is still better.
I'll buy Huang's beef tomorrow.
Yes.
It's not that good.
Don't move!
You came so fast.
Why did you fall to the ground?
Come on.
Why are you having a feast here, Lin Shaobai?
No.
Sit.
You are meeting for the first time.
Let me introduce.
This is Director Lu of the Social Affairs Office.
This is
Chief Liu Guiheng of Shanghai Special Station,
Chief Liu.
Hello, Chief Liu.
Hello, Director Lu.
Look at me.
Chief Liu, I suddenly remembered.
That money of yours
has long been turned over to the national treasury.
You tricked me once, and I cheated you once in return.
We're even now.
Okay.
If I were you, I would have done the same.
Huzi.
Take the rest of them back.
Shaobai, Xiaoman.
Interrogate him on the spot.
Yes.
Hello, Director Lu.
Liu Guiheng.
I advise you to tell the truth.
I don't need your advice.
Is everything ready?
Don't just...
Don't beat around the bush.
Get to the point.
First,
I want to say
a Kuomintang agent of my level,
whether being reactive or proactive,
must have
the blood of the Communist Party on my hands.
I hereby
plead guilty.
Second,
what I want to confess is that
I'm already extremely disappointed
in Kuomintang.
They sent me back this time
to stir up trouble
just to get me killed.
Those bastards have abandoned me.
Over the years,
they forced me
to do a few things against the people.
But I have conscience.
I avoided and refused
as much as I could.
You know the rules of NBIS.
Anyone who disobeys orders will be shot.
This is the rule set by Dai Li.
I had no choice. I was forced.
I've been living in pain every day.
Third,
I want to admit that
I'm guilty!
Sit down.
I've been dealing with you guys
for so many years.
I can feel more and more deeply that
only the Communist Party truly works
for the sake of the people
and hopes they can live a good life.
You are wholeheartedly willing
to sacrifice your lives for the people
at any cost.
But what about Kuomintang?
They eat, drink, gamble, and engage in corruption.
They oppress the people
and go against the people.
And they failed in the end as expected.
That's why they say, "Those who win the people's hearts win the country."
I, Liu Guiheng, hereby declare that
I won't go against the trend of times
and be a bad guy who's hostile to the people.
There's a saying in "Comprehensive Mirror in Aid of Governance" that
whoever goes against the historical trend
will be crushed
into pieces by the wheels of history.
Well said.
But I remember you just said
you wanted to kill me,
and you wanted to get a basin to hold my blood.
Shaobai, that was a mis...
Don't touch me.
That was a misunderstanding.
I sincerely hope
you can give me a chance
to redeem myself.
I can prove right now that
Lin Shaobai was framed by us at that time.
He's innocent.
Liu Guiheng.
We all know
your sincerity of confession.
But what we want to know most now
is whether Zheng Lanting is still in Shanghai,
and where exactly he is.
Director.
Zheng Lanting
has never left Shanghai.
But as for his exact whereabouts,
I don't know about that.
You talked so much nonsense,
but when it comes to key issues, you shut your mouth?
You are the chief of Shanghai Special Station.
How could you not know where he is?
Director.
I really don't know where Zheng Lanting is.
The conflict between Zheng Lanting and I is very deep.
This lunatic even took my man away
for bacterial in vivo experiments
and made him rotten all over.
We are both chiefs.
We have something in common.
You are a chief,
while I'm a police officer.
You are a leader.
Zheng Lanting never obeys
my management.
Even those thugs who work for him
dare to arrange work for me.
All the bad things were done by Zheng Lanting.
There are a lot of things that I don't know.
I feel so aggrieved as the chief.
How do you usually contact each other?
Via telegram.
Telegram?
No wonder Director Lu is a leader.
He's so good at grasping the key to the problem.
I can send a telegram to him
and ask him out.
After all, I'm still the chief.
I still have this power.
By then,
you guys
can set up a dragnet
and catch him once and for all.
Let him be judged by the people!
We don't need you to teach us what to do.
Right. Right.
Listen carefully.
The telegram you send
must be accurate and credible.
Do not arouse any suspicion of Shrike.
Also, he's wanted now.
He won't show up easily.
Think about what you need to send
to get him to come in person.
Yes. Right.
Think about it carefully.
If you fail to redeem yourself this time,
you won't have such an opportunity again in the future.
We can only take you back and shoot you.
Okay.
There are always more solutions than difficulties.
Director.
In NBIS,
there's an ace killer
named Liu Quande.
You know him, right?
It's claimed that he's a perfect shot,
and he's succeeded in every assassination
except for that time
when he tried to assassinate
Mr. Chen, Chenyi.
He was personally assigned by Mao Renfeng
to execute the special assassination order.
This assassination order
is still valid now.
[Please come to Shenghe Pawnshop tomorrow at 3 p.m. to discuss the specific plan.]
[Your station is ordered to use anthrax to execute the special assassination order to assassinate Chen Yi.]
Mr. Zheng, there's a telegram from Liu Guiheng
saying that Commissioner Mao Renfeng issued a new order
to assassinate Chen Yi with anthrax.
As the saying goes, meat-eaters are fools, and they cannot plan ahead.
They are all losers
who are not good enough to accomplish anything, but more than capable to spoil things.
One false move,
and everything we did could come to naught.
So what should I reply?
We have to let the higher-ups know that
our target is not any person,
but the entire Shanghai.
Everything we do now
must make way for the Sea Subversion Plan.
Last time when we tried to assassinate Meng Heng,
we used Liu Guiheng's men as bait
for distraction.
Many of his men died.
He must have a lot of resentment built up in his heart.
If we do that,
I'm afraid it'll be bad for you.
After all, he's still the nominal chief.
I can't fall out with him openly.
Otherwise, I won't be able to explain to Taiwan.
Reply to him that
I'll be there on time.
Okay.
Xiao Yun.
You've been working hard this year.
When everything is over,
I'll take you to a place
and live
a carefree and leisurely life there.
Thank you.
Go.
Okay.
Liu Guiheng
[Shenghe Pawnshop]
is seeing
Zheng Lanting
[The front door] [The back door]
at Shenghe Pawnshop.
[Shenghe]
We need to make arming preparations in advance.
[Dexing Trading Company]
The front door.
The back door.
The tobacco and liquor shop, and the grocery store.
Set up ambushes at the above places in advance according to the plan just now.
[Map of Shanghai]
Besides, considering that Zheng Lanting
may carry anthrax weapons,
Dr. Jin will take a few medical staff
on this action with us.
This way, they can provide timely treatment if an accident occurs.
Yes.
The new type of anthrax developed by Zheng Lanting
is not only highly toxic,
but also has greatly enhanced drug resistance.
So everyone must be extra careful
during the action.
Thank you.
Lin Shaobai and I
[Shenghe Pawnshop]
will ambush in the pawnshop in advance.
We'll arrest Zheng Lanting
as soon as he arrives.
-Yes.
Yes.
Hello.
You've reached Shenghe Pawnshop.
Mr. Liu.
How's business?
Why do you have time
to make telephone calls?
Didn't we agree to talk face to face?
It's not safe to talk on the phone.
You...
I'm not going.
What?
You're not coming?
You have to come.
We had a deal.
This is about an important task assigned by the higher-ups.
How can you not come?
I'll see you at Leyouyuan Restaurant at 5:30.
Leyouyuan Restaurant? Where is it?
You have half an hour. It's up to you whether you come or not.
Hello?
When did he say you'll meet?
He changed the place.
He asked me to meet him at Leyouyuan Restaurant at 5:30.
There's half an hour left.
Could it be he noticed something wrong?
Although he's always paranoid and cautious,
it shouldn't be.
Let's hurry over.
Please.
You want me to go alone?
This won't bode well.
Liu Guiheng.
There's no turning back now.
Are you trying to back out?
How could you say that?
He's the one who changed...
Dear Liu. Listen.
Just pretend nothing happened
and meet him the way you should.
We'll arrange our comrades nearby to protect you.
What's there to be afraid of?
Don't you know who Zheng Lanting is?
If he finds anything wrong,
I will die there.
So many comrades
will be there protecting you.
Besides,
it'll be a merit of yours
if you manage to Zheng Lanting this time.
A great merit.
Do you think you'll have this kind of opportunity
to redeem yourself and reduce sentence again in the future?
You want to persuade me with this?
Forget it.
I'd rather
go to jail.
Even if I have to stay in jail for the rest of my life,
it's still better than going there to die.
Why are you such a coward?
Can't you think about the bright side?
Fine.
Let me think about it.
Okay.
Take your time.
It's okay
if you don't want this chance.
But you have to think it through.
If you don't make contributions this time,
even shooting you would be merciful when we take you back.
Liu Guiheng.
We are giving you a chance,
but you don't want it.
Remember.
You've done so many bad things.
Actually, you didn't even turn yourself in.
Be ready to stand trial.
Let's go, Shaobai.
Director.
Director, I'll go.
I'll go meet Zheng Lanting.
Even if I die,
I must catch Zheng Lanting!
With you heroes behind me,
I'm not afraid.
I'll go meet him. I'm not afraid.
But Director, I...
I have a question.
If I catch Zheng Lanting myself,
will it count as a great merit?
Does my surrender still count?
It depends on your performance.
Okay.
Give me a gun, please.
Okay?
Remember.
When you see him,
you're still the rightful chief of Shanghai Special Station.
I'll try my best.
Director, I'll try my best.
Please.
[Leyouyuan Restaurant]
A pot of water please.
Coming right up.
Why are you here alone?
Where is Shrike?
Nobody is following you, is there?
Why do you have so much to ask?
When I started working in the Telecom Department of NBIS,
you were still a nobody.
We agreed to meet here.
Are you changing it again?
Do you
still take me as chief or not?
Where's Shrike?
I'm leaving.
Are you in a hurry to leave?
So you are here.
This place Xiao Yun picked
is full of traffic.
There are exits everywhere,
and it's a restaurant.
Once we shoot,
we may get innocent people hurt.
Zheng Lanting really knows how to choose a place to meet.
That's right.
Once the shootout begins,
the civilians down there will be in danger.
I've arranged someone
to evacuate the crowd outside.
Now it depends on
how long Liu Guiheng can stall him in there.
The dishes are ready. I had to at least show up.
Bro.
You and I should be sincere with each other.
Do you have to
make things so complicated for me?
It's not easy to meet in this situation.
I think we should get down to business.
Okay.
Can we wait until they come out before arresting him?
If he has anthrax bacteria on him,
the situation will be more difficult to control
once he gets outside.
The fist thing we need to do now
is to evacuate the crowd
in the restaurant.
Xiao Yun has been keeping watch on the second floor.
They are familiar with all our people.
We need to find a new face.
Someone smart.
[Leyouyuan Restaurant]
[Leyouyuan]
Sir, can I help you?
[Police]
[Name: Yi Jiang]
The assassin who tried to kill Chen Yi, Liu Quande,
failed.
I received an urgent telegram from the bureau,
asking you to use your anthrax bacteria
to continue the assassination.
And the bureau criticized me,
saying I'm a loser.
Because I still don't know
where your secret anthrax experiment base
is.
You've become more and more talkative since you became the chief.
Please tell the higher-ups that
the anthrax weapon I developed
is not targeted at any person,
but to bring down the entire Shanghai.
As for the research base,
I suggest you not to inquire.
The more you know,
the worse it is for you.
Do you understand what I mean?
You said
you want to bring down the entire Shanghai with anthrax bacteria?
You heard it right.
Are you kidding me?
The main task of the bureau now
is to assassinate Chen Yi.
If you do this...
Chief Liu.
Calm down. Sit down.
How do you want me to report to the bureau?
What do you want to do?
Hurry up and leave.
There's a gas leak here. Leave.
There's a gas leak.
Let's go.
We were just having a meal. How come this happened?
It's time to take action.
Hurry up and leave.
Hurry up and leave. There's a gas leak.
There's a gas leak here.
Hurry up and leave.
There's a gas leak.
Bosses.
There's a gas leak in our restaurant. Please leave.
You have to think about me.
Mr. Zheng, something happened.
They say there's a gas leak here.
The guests outside have been evacuated.
Why are you pointing the gun at me?
Stop talking and run!
You lured the police here, didn't you?
What are you talking about?
You chose this place!
How dare you set me up?
Zheng Lanting.
Cut the crap!
Grenade!
Save him!
Go upstairs!
Xiao Yun!
Don't do anything stupid.
Don't do anything stupid!
Tell them
not to come up.
Or I'll shoot you!
Don't come up! Don't come up!
Put the gun down!
Chief.
All clear. We can leave now.
Xiao Yun!
Retreat!
Save him!
Take Mr. Zheng and leave!
Let's go, Chief!
Xiao Yun!
Go!
Let's go, Chief.
Let's go!
Xiao Yun!
Go!
Let's go!
Attack!
Go!
Yan!
Go after them!
Go!
[Zhongtian Chemical Plant]
Boss.
Make this car disappear.
Yes.
Let's go.
Wipe down the car and dispose of it.
Yes.
Where is Boss's wife?
Miss.
Tell me.
How should I deal with you?
You killed my father.
Unfortunately, I failed to kill you myself.
I understand you saying this
as his daughter.
But he was not just a father.
He was disloyal.
Didn't he deserve to die?
Killing people to establish prestige
is nothing but a sign of extreme weakness.
You will definitely lose.
Really?
But unfortunately,
before that,
you'll be the ones destroyed by the anthrax weapon,
not me.
If this is what you want,
then you're no different from the devil.
For faith,
if I don't go to hell,
who will?
Take her out.
Put her in there with the test subjects.
Let her experience what hell is like.
Take her away.
Yes.
Go.
Please let me go.
I beg you.
Please let me go!
Chief.
[Shenghe Pawnshop]
I found it, Director.
This Leyouyuan Restaurant
was a former NBIS stronghold.
So it has a secret door.
Even the boss who later rented it didn't know about it.
The stolen car
has been found.
It was abandoned in the wilderness.
But no blood was found in the car.
Dr. Jin should still be alive.
Deputy Commissioner Yang asked us
to arrest Zheng Lanting
and save Dr. Jin
at any cost.
Our top priority now
is to confirm the location of this anthrax base.
Lu.
Zheng Lanting's anthrax research
has reached the experimental stage.
Meng Heng can't be the only one there.
He must have captured more people there
to experiment on.