[Dark Night and Dawn]
[Episode 14]
[Post Office]
I'm leaving then.
Goodbye.
Feel free to come to me if you need anything in the future.
The prices will absolutely be fair.
You're my regular customer.
Thank you, Boss.
Okay. Goodbye.
[Deshengxiang Refined Pigment Store]
Hello, what would you like?
Hello, police.
Boss.
What was that lady doing here just now?
She's from a studio.
She ordered some pigments here a few days ago.
She came here today to tell me something happened at home.
She doesn't need them, so she returned them.
Okay, thank you.
Okay, goodbye.
[Xiya Timepiece Store]
Where is your boss?
Sir, what can I do for you?
I'm here to pick up the watch.
Show me the receipt.
I don't have it.
The owner of the watch is Shrike.
I was wondering who it was.
It's you.
You ran away from Zhoushan back then.
I thought you were dead.
Now you work for Shrike.
Why didn't he tell me?
The operation to rescue Shrike must be cancelled tomorrow.
Xu Wei,
have you forgotten who you are?
How dare you talk to me like that!
Shrike
has a quirk.
He always likes to use bird names
as code names for his subordinates.
What's your code name?
Falcon.
Falcon is dead.
I'll resurrect it.
Zombie Sparrow sent you here, right?
She underestimated my determination
and overestimated you.
Don't move!
Shrike said
you are self-conceited.
You always do things beyond your capability.
If you move again, I'll shoot you!
If you shoot me, you'll alarm the neighbors
and lure the police here.
And your identity will be exposed.
It's useless to stop me.
Yang Hui will still take action tomorrow.
[Xiya Timepiece Store]
[Specializing in precision repair] [Selling high-end timepieces]
Mr. Zheng, you're still up.
I can't sleep.
Sit. Sit.
I'm here to tell you
you can leave tomorrow morning.
So you've found out the truth. I'm innocent, right?
I can go home?
You misunderstood, Mr. Zheng.
I'm going to tell you first
so that you can be prepared.
The higher-ups
have decided to transfer you to Beijing.
Where?
Beijing.
Bei...
Well,
you want to investigate me in Beijing because you can't find out the truth in Shanghai?
I know you've suffered, Mr. Zheng.
If I were them,
I would have let you go long ago.
But I really can't make the decision
for the higher-ups.
I can't believe it.
Mr. Zheng.
You should rest early.
Don't think too much.
They will
find out the truth soon
to clear your name.
I should get going.
They are waiting for me.
Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
Have a good rest.
Okay.
[Map of areas near Shanghai and Suzhou]
This is the transfer route.
We'll use a cargo train tomorrow.
If the agents take action,
innocent people won't be implicated.
I've told him about the transfer.
Lu,
if we really have wronged him,
how should we explain to him tomorrow?
Tell him the truth. Ask for his understanding.
Annoying.
Mr. Zheng.
We should hit the road.
Okay.
Coming.
What's wrong, Mr. Zheng?
Nothing.
You were fine yesterday.
How did you become like this suddenly?
Huzi.
What happened last night?
After you told him about the transfer yesterday,
he couldn't sleep all night.
He tossed and turned,
and his breathing was fast and heavy.
Those should be symptoms
caused by acute anxiety.
It can lead to heart palpitations, sweating, and even convulsions.
Looks like he really is scared.
Mr. Zheng.
Don't be too anxious.
It's nothing serious.
We'll let you go after we find out the truth.
As long as you can clear my name,
I'll cooperate with you in anything.
Considering his current condition,
it's not suitable to transfer him now.
Why don't we wait a few days?
Mr. Zheng.
Thank you for your cooperation.
We'll do our best to ensure your safety.
I'll go with you and take more sedatives.
Skip the formalities.
H-Help me up.
[Shanghai North]
Here, Mr. Zheng, have a seat.
What's the situation over there?
Everything is normal.
If I were an agent,
I wouldn't take action at the train station either.
There are so many soldiers of the People's Liberation Army
and policemen.
[Shanghai North]
Deputy Chief Yang,
why hasn't Liu Guiheng come here yet?
Ignore him.
We can succeed by ourselves.
After the explosion later,
kill everyone on the train.
Kill them all.
Okay.
Take whatever you want on the train.
-Great!
Great!
Guys, we can have meat.
What's there to be happy about now?
Are the explosives set?
If the explosives are set, hide!
Mr. Zheng. Have some water.
Okay, thank you.
Are you feeling better?
I think I can still hold on.
That's good.
Have you ever been to Beijing?
No.
I've been living in Shanghai.
I've only been to some small cities nearby.
It's said
the weather in the south and north is different.
The scenery
is also quite different.
I stayed in Yan'an for two years.
Mr. Zheng, if you
see the loess plateau there,
you would also be stunned.
I really want to take a look.
Have you noticed this?
Differences in geographical environments
can shape the course of history
in different ways.
Really?
Look.
Historically, nations in the northwest usually had
advantages when campaigning against the southeast,
while those in the southeast faced greater challenges when advancing toward the northwest.
This...
Is that so?
I've never heard of it.
What I heard is
the south was known for talents and the north was known for generals.
The people in the north were a bit tough,
so they were aggressive and good at fighting.
The people in the south indulged in pleasure and comfort.
They paid attention to the four arts of the Chinese scholar,
so they lost their territories.
Not exactly.
Look at the current Kuomintang.
It occupies the southeast region.
It also claimed it would attack the mainland.
But the people represent the general trend.
Yes.
It's useless to resist desperately.
War is indeed too horrible.
We ordinary people just want
to live a peaceful life.
Yes.
Mr. Zheng, what you want
is also what all the Chinese people want.
Have some water.
What are you doing here?
Abort the mission.
Shrike has his own plan.
This is Director's order.
Do you listen to Director or Shrike?
Liu Guiheng is using you!
Who do you think you are?
How dare you talk to Deputy Chief Yang like that!
I'm the new leader of the action team.
I'm the new Falcon.
I'll verify it after the operation.
Take him away and get ready to take action.
Let go of me!
Move!
If you are exposed,
I will
die with you.
Don't move!
I'll kill him if you move again!
[Kunshan]
Did we really wrong him?
Let's go back.
[Kunshan]
Young man, what's going on?
Aren't we going to Beijing?
Why... Why are we going back?
Mr. Zheng,
we policemen have our own procedures in case handling.
You just need to cooperate.
No, no.
I don't understand this.
You told me we were going to Beijing.
How... How can we go back?
Isn't this torment?
Are you kidding me?
Where is your leader?
Your... Your Director Lu.
Director Lu,
please come here!
Mr. Zheng, don't shout.
What's going on?
I trusted you very much.
You're fooling me, aren't you?
Look how sick I am.
I've been cooperating with your investigation, right?
Mr. Zheng.
Calm down first.
I can't calm down.
You have to give me an explanation.
Now I doubt
if you are still the police for the people.
Which law allows you
to imprison a teacher like me
for so many days?
What exactly do you want?
Mr. Zheng, this trip
is also part of the political examination.
Please understand.
What kind of logic is that?
It's a waste of manpower and money.
All of you, sit down.
Don't...
The bathroom.
Okay, I'll go with you.
It's done.
Don't worry.
Continue to keep an eye on Yang Hui.
He's the key to Mr. Zheng's plan.
First, Mr. Zheng misled the police
and made them think Yang Hui is Shrike.
Then Mr. Zheng let the police find the code book in Yang Hui's house
and told Yang Hui
he can only help him out of trouble if he makes a big scene.
Lastly, he'll use you to deal with Liu Guiheng.
Now, I guess Yang Hui
must have contacted the Anti-Communist Salvation Army.
I guess the NBIS
will send a telegram soon
to approve Yang Hui's application
for the Anti-Communist Salvation Army's operation.
The Communist Party will
decipher this telegram
based on the code book
found in Yang Hui's house
to intercept them in advance.
So the Anti-Communist Salvation Army will definitely fail.
And they have clues on Yang Hui.
Your mission is
to ensure Yang Hui's death
is perfectly timed.
Got it.
When we transferred Zheng Lanting,
the agents didn't take action at all.
Lu,
can this prove
Zheng Lanting has nothing to do with the agents?
During his imprisonment,
I always kept an eye on him.
I didn't notice anything unusual.
Director,
did we really catch the wrong person?
These days,
I've been pretending to be close to him.
I found that
he is nothing like a timid person
everyone says he is.
Instead, he always looks relaxed,
as if everything
is under his control.
We'll draw a conclusion
after we catch Yang Hui.
[Office 2 of Social Affairs Office]
Director,
the Investigation and Monitoring Division sent a message.
They used the code book
to decipher a telegram sent by the NBIS.
The agents will take action tonight.
They'll assassinate industrialists.
Deputy Commissioner Yang.
[Telegram Deciphering Paper of Shanghai People's Government Public Security Bureau]
According to the telegram,
the agents assigned to this operation
are directly under the command of the NBIS.
Their rank is not low.
Tonight's meeting between the municipal government
and industrialists are very important.
So after the discussion of the city leaders,
the meeting will proceed as usual.
But as for the meeting's location,
we'll make other arrangements.
You can do whatever you want.
Hurry! Keep up!
[Shanghai People's Government Public Security Bureau]
Commander Liu.
These are American weapons.
Just do what you want boldly.
After it's done...
You'll get a lot of silver dollars.
Great!
Deal!
Shoot!
They are inside!
Guys, kill them!
Shoot!
Move! Are you scared?
My monthly salary is not very much.
No need to risk my life.
What are you doing?
Come back!
Coward!
Shoot!
Put your hands on your head!
Squat!
Don't move!
I'm sorry, Director.
I won't do it again.
It's good that you're okay.
You guys are so patient.
You only took action when they
were so close to you.
When I heard their gunfire,
I realized it was just a test.
Later, the gunfire grew more intense.
It indicated their leader was about to appear.
This telegram code book
is like the borax in Ghost Hand Luo San's belly.
They want to lure us into another trap.
[Telegram Code Book]
Then let's play along.
Ask Captain Zhang to cooperate with you.
You only brought a few useless men.
How dare you call yourself a commander!
You... are a fast runner!
Good.
So you went to catch him.
You're very smart.
Take us to Yang Hui
to make contributions.
Deputy Commissioner Yang,
what's the situation on Lu's side?
They are lying in wait.
He is lying in wait on the river
with our water policemen.
Yang Hui and his men can't escape this time.
He's here!
Turn around! Shut up!
Just repeat after me.
Do you understand?
Deputy Chief Yang!
It's me!
Liu!
We won,
but we lost many men!
You should reward us generously!
He's trying to win my sympathy.
Dock the boat.
Dock the boat!
Guo Chao,
deliver it to him.
Okay.
Thank you, Commander Liu.
Deputy Chief Yang said
you guys should rest well to recover.
There will be
many big deals in the future.
Why didn't Deputy Chief Yang come ashore?
I have something to tell him.
Deputy Chief Yang will see you
when he wants to see you.
Let's go.
Go!
Don't move.
Xiaoman!
Back off!
Don't shoot!
Take it!
Deputy Commissioner Yang,
why don't I go talk to him?
It's not your turn to do it.
Don't come any closer!
Back off!
Don't be nervous.
Look.
I'm not taking
any weapon with me.
I just want to come here to talk to you.
Tell them to drop their guns.
Drop your guns.
I know you.
You're Deputy Commissioner Yang,
their leader.
Since you know me,
you should know
there's no harm in talking to me, right?
Yang Hui,
you must be waiting
for your boat on the river to save you.
I'm afraid you'll be disappointed.
Our water policemen
have cut off your retreat.
My death would be worth it.
A life for a life.
Even if I die,
I'll make her die with me.
I came here to talk to you
because I want to give you a chance to live.
How about this?
Let her go.
I'll be your hostage.
You'll be my hostage?
Aren't you afraid of death?
You won't be that stupid.
If you kill me,
you can never escape alive.
Did you hear that?
Our water policemen have succeeded.
If you want to live,
do as I say.
Okay.
Raise your hands.
Walk towards me slowly.
Don't move!
If you dare to play tricks with me,
I'll put a bullet in your head!
Yang Hui,
let's think from your point of view.
First, your identity has been exposed.
Second,
the Anti-Communist Salvation Army was destroyed because of you.
Even if you can escape,
will your superior
let you go easily?
I made contributions to Kuomintang.
They won't treat me like that.
Don't be stubborn.
When things go wrong, you look for a scapegoat.
That is your tradition.
Do you still need me to remind you?
Drop your weapon
and cooperate with us.
That is your final way out.
Why should I trust you?
You know our policies.
You don't have time to think about it.
Give me the gun!
Your mission is to ensure
Yang Hui's death is perfectly timed.
Don't come any closer!
I knew you're not a good guy.
Go to hell!
[Telegram Deciphering Paper of the NBIS of the National Defense Department]
[Translated News]
[Content]
[Jinsheng Bank]
[Zhang Guoqiang, He Gui, Hao Yu, Shen Haiyan]
[Li Wensheng, Yang Baojun, Zhang Huixin, Shen Xing]
Look at this.
Wang Liqun?
This has established a linkage to the previous cases.
This should be Shrike's base.
[Wang Liqun] [Hospital's picture poster]
What we can confirm now is
what we destroyed this time
is a mobile base
of the Shanghai Special Operation Station.
That's why
it had been hard for us
to find clues about agents all this time.
Our colleagues from the Evidence Division
have taken photos of all the evidence
and pasted them here.
In the base,
we found two transmitter-receivers,
gold bars taken from Jinsheng Bank,
the list of the Anti-Communist Salvation Army's members,
[Wang Liqun] [Hospital's picture poster]
a large number of telegrams among agents,
a photo,
and five portraits.
What's worth our attention is
there is a date on the back
of every portrait.
April 29.
That is the date
of the Fuzhou Road Explosion four years ago.
I've seen her before.
She was also at the scene of the Fuzhou Road Explosion
four years ago.
She got in the car with Wang Liqun.
She was badly injured and covered in blood.
I don't think she survived.
Every year on her death anniversary,
he would draw a portrait of her to mourn her.
Her relationship with Shrike
is very special.
And this photo.
When it was found,
[Wang Liqun]
[Yang Hui] [Shrike]
it was torn into pieces.
But we pieced them together.
[Wang Liqun]
There are two people in the photo.
The one in the front is Yang Hui.
The one behind him is Wang Liqun.
On the back of this photo,
there is also a very blurry date.
[Wang Liqun] [Hospital's picture poster]
It's probably December 1938.
That was the graduation time
of the first Linli Special Training Class of the NBIS.
Looks like Yang Hui
was the mentor Wang Liqun mentioned.
He was the perpetrator of the explosion four years ago.
He also had anthrax bacteria.
Those are the evidence.
The driver in the car accident back then
was also him.
Then everything is very clear.
All the evidence shows
Yang Hui was Shrike,
the chief of the Shanghai Special Station.
We are lucky.
We just joined them and already solved such a big case.
Who could the person firing the blank shot at the scene be?
Do you really think Yang Hui was Shrike?
All the evidence we have now
shows he was.
[Be modest, cautious, humble, and patient]
That's the problem.
Everything we found out about him
and even his death
happened at the perfect timing.
It's like
someone arranged everything in advance.
It's indeed possible.
[Be modest, cautious, humble, and patient]
After we thoroughly investigate the Shanghai Special Station
and find the most direct witness,
the truth will come out.
If Yang Hui was not Shrike,
the real Shrike
will be a very tricky opponent.
Mr. Zheng, you still are not feeling well?
It doesn't matter how I'm feeling.
Just tell me what I should do to cooperate with you.
You can leave now.
I can leave now?
Yes.
Director Lu,
do you know how I managed to get through
the past few days?
Each day felt like a year.
When I was lying here just now, I was thinking
back then,
even when the Japanese gave us a hard time,
I don't think it was that hard.
You're right.
Mr. Zheng, I'm sorry for having made you suffer.
Fine. Working people are not afraid of hardships.
We're just afraid of being wronged.
You're too serious, Mr. Zheng.
Your wife
is waiting for you at the gate to go home.
Let me walk you out.
No, no, no.
I can't just leave
like this.
If I leave here with nothing,
what will the teachers and students in the school think of me?
How should I explain to my neighbors
and my friends?
You have to clear my name.
At least you should give me a certificate.
The content
of the certificate has to be as follows:
the police's investigation over the past few days shows
Zheng Lanting is a good citizen.
He is not an agent.
Okay.
The students have been waiting for you, right?
How have you been? Is everything alright?
It's okay.
Let's...
go home.
Goodbye.
Lanting.
Get me some hot water.
Okay.
It's almost done.
Right.
Take a photo
of the certificate and develop it.
I'll hang it in the studio tomorrow.
Lanting,
time to eat.
Where are the paintings
in the drawer in the room upstairs?
I put those paintings
in Yang Hui's house.
The police can be more convinced
that he was Shrike after finding them.
I just wanted to clear your name.
I'm going to say it again.
Please don't touch
anything in that room
without my permission.
Got it?
Yes.
Let's eat.
Today's dinner
is a hearty one.
Thank you.
Xu Wei,
you will die a horrible death.
Shrike.
You're back.
Great.
It must be because
Yang Hui followed my order
and saved you, right?
It was just a trivial matter. No need to bother Yang Hui.
The Public Security Bureau has found out the truth.
I'm innocent now.
That's good.
Xu Wei told me
you made great efforts
to save me.
So I specially came here to thank you.
No! No!
Shrike,
what are you going to do?
We have the same rank
in the NBIS.
Without Boss's order,
don't you dare touch me.
Xu Wei!
Xu Wei, what are you going to do?
Don't say that.
We are comrades.
Why would I touch you?
It's just that young people
are ignorant.
Secretary Liu, please don't take it to heart.
Your whole body must be numb.
It's fine.
Not very numb.
Relax yourself.
The point is...
Shrike,
there shouldn't be
any misunderstanding between us.
Like you said just now,
we are comrades.
And we both are working in Shanghai.
We should...
take care of each other...
and help each other, right?
I
really wanted to save you.
It took me a lot of effort.
You really wanted to save him?
You mean it took you a lot of effort to stab him in the back.
Who do you think you are?
Who are you to speak here?
You're trying to drive a wedge between the higher-ups.
This crime alone
is enough for me to kill you according to our law!
You bastard!
Shrike,
don't listen to him.
You know clearly
what kind of person I am.
I'm not that kind of person.
What kind of person do you mean?