[Dark Night and Dawn]
[Episode 8]
All the materials are here.
Let's start with him.
Sir, Lin Shaobai from Office 2, reporting for duty.
Late on your first day?
Absolutely not.
I actually arrived quite early.
[Case of Liu Mingjian]
It just occurred to me that we came to work so early this morning
that surely no one's had breakfast yet.
So, I ran through several streets
to get some snacks for everyone.
Here, try some.
These crab shell pies are amazing.
They're delicious.
And these, sesame rice balls.
Pork chop with rice cakes.
These are all top-notch snacks.
They're definitely as good as those from the Shanghai Family Restaurant.
You'll know once you try them.
You're so particular.
Shaobai, the pork chop with rice cakes is from Xian De Lai.
Xu, you're indeed from Shanghai. You know the good stuff.
Director Lu.
We're in the middle of a meeting. Is food really that important?
You, write me a self-criticism later.
Come on, I was just a little late, Director Lu.
Isn't that a bit too severe?
[Case of Liu Mingjian]
Oh, right,
this is for you.
[Case of Liu Mingjian]
I've already had breakfast.
This isn't breakfast, and it's not for you to eat either.
[Case of Liu Mingjian]
It's for the jasmine plant in your room.
You've just been watering that jasmine.
Its leaves are turning yellow and wilting.
[Case of Liu Mingjian]
This is a special fertilizer made of
plant ash, soybean cake, and river mud, mixed together.
My Auntie made it,
and we've always used it at home. It works wonders.
It's just that we have too much at home. We can't use it all.
Director Lu, please help me use some of it.
Just leave it there.
Okay.
But you still have to write that self-criticism.
No one in Office 2
should be late on their first day.
Sir, Cen Xiaoman, reporting for duty!
Late on your first day at work?
Sorry, miss,
what's your name again?
Cen Xiaoman. "Xiaoman" means the "Grain Full" season.
I was born on that day, easy to remember.
Why are you late?
I'm sorry.
Last night, I was so excited about becoming a police officer
and catching agents that I couldn't sleep.
[Case of Liu Mingjian]
Actually, I got up at 5 a.m.
However, I was too excited
and ended up reporting to the Fuzhou Road Public Security Bureau instead.
Only when I got there did I realize that the Social Affairs Office
wasn't at that bureau.
That was when I rushed over here.
This definitely calls for written self-criticism, right?
And it needs to be deep, with at least a thousand words long,
right?
Mr. Lin Shaobai is absolutely right.
The self-criticism must be thorough.
So, we'll go by
Mr. Lin Shaobai's rule,
over a thousand words.
However,
Miss Cen Xiaoman, you don't need to write one.
It's you who has to write.
What?
Lu, that's a double standard.
She's new. It's normal for her
to get the location wrong.
You're a senior officer.
Tardiness is unacceptable for you.
Yes!
You come with me.
Stop what you're doing for a moment.
Let me introduce her to you.
This is Miss Cen Xiaoman,
a university graduate.
She's been assigned here after graduation.
By the way,
Mr. Huzi still lacks
some skills in keeping the interrogation record.
From now on, Xiaoman can assist you with that.
Really, Director?
Miss Xiaoman, you couldn't have come at a better time.
You don't know me.
When it comes to writing materials or reports,
I'm completely clueless, like a monk...
In the dark.
I have no brain for it.
You just want me to organize reports and write materials?
Director, I request to be assigned to the frontlines of anti-espionage!
[Case of Liu Mingjian]
Full of enthusiasm. We should all learn from her.
Once you've familiarized yourself with the work here,
there will be opportunities.
Okay.
Director, you have to keep your word!
Hurry up.
[The Joint Trust Warehouse]
This way.
Hurry up.
Move it over. Move it over.
That's all the strength you've got?
How is it going?
The workers are all tight-lipped.
Weren't you a cop before?
Is this the best you can do?
Anyway, I'll give you two more days.
If you still can't find out anything
about the Hook Sword Gang and Dai Yueqing,
I'll chop your hands off.
Cen Xiaoman. Lin Shaobai.
Yes!
This is the confidentiality regulation.
When you go back, not only do you need to memorize it,
but you also have to engrave it in your mind.
No matter who it is
or under any circumstances,
you must never make a mistake regarding this matter.
Understand?
Yes.
Here's your police uniform.
No uniform for me?
You are...
I'm auxiliary personnel. I know.
You'll get a uniform
when you officially join us.
Director, what does "auxiliary personnel" mean?
It means a special talent recruited by an exception.
Then you must have some extraordinary skills.
As expected from Miss Xiaoman, a university graduate.
From now on, you'll follow me.
Don't get arrogant.
There's still a lot for you to learn.
Alright, now on behalf of Office 2,
I hereby officially welcome you.
Hello?
I'm looking for Jin Yan from the Forensics Department.
That's me.
Miss, it's me, Zhou.
Something happened to Mr. Jin at the dock.
Please come quickly and check on him.
What happened to my dad?
He suddenly had chest pain,
so we had to call you.
I'll be right there. Don't let him move.
Liu Rui, I have to leave now.
Mr. Jin,
we've called the young lady.
When she gets here,
you take her onto the boat.
[Ticket Office]
Everything is all set.
As long as she's on the boat, I'll be at ease.
What if she realizes that something's wrong?
Even if you have to tie her up, make sure she gets on that ship.
Got it.
Miss, you're finally here.
How is my dad?
It's hard to say right now.
He's resting in the medical room of the boat.
Please go and check on him.
Let's go.
What exactly do you want?
Please leave my daughter out of this.
Are you getting more and more muddled with age?
Sending your daughter abroad...
is that safe?
We have a lot of men overseas.
It'd be very easy to take care of her.
What were you thinking?
That's not how a person should react.
Think it through.
Yan!
Dad!
They said you were on the boat.
How are you feeling?
I just saw a guest off.
I felt a bit unwell.
I'm fine now after resting for a bit.
Zhou and the others were just making a fuss,
insisting on calling you.
Your hands are still cold.
You should go to the hospital for a check-up.
Even if I do, they'll just tell me to rest more and exercise.
Go. I'll go tomorrow.
No, we're going now.
Let's go.
You've been working so hard lately. You're too tired.
How about we take a break from work
and rest for a bit?
If only I could, that would be great.
But I can't.
Yan,
quit your job at the hospital.
I was actually going to talk to you about that.
I'm now working as a medical examiner at the Public Security Bureau.
You already knew that, didn't you?
He even called me at the office.
I also heard it from someone else.
I knew you weren't planning on telling me,
right?
A girl working as a medical examiner,
dealing with corpses every day...
Dad, it's the new society now.
Your mindset has to change too.
Besides, forensic work is about skill,
not gender.
I don't care. Whether you agree or not,
I'll continue to be a medical examiner.
You're my only daughter.
Yan, you must learn how to protect yourself.
As long as you agree,
I will protect myself.
Does it look good?
Yes.
This is something I've always wanted to give you.
Give it to me?
Shanghai has been liberated.
You do work at the Public Security Bureau,
but there are still regulations on firearms.
This gun is for you to protect yourself.
Alright, I can't argue with you.
Thank you, Dad.
Yan, I'm tired.
I'm going to rest for a bit.
Okay.
Zhou, drive slowly.
[42839]
Hello?
I'm Bulbul. I'm willing to cooperate,
but I have one condition.
I want the position of Chairman
of the Labor, Military, and Commerce Association.
I have a very strong competitor,
Liu Xisheng.
[Case of Liu Mingjian]
There are too many case files.
Going through them one by one like this
is a slow method.
We've been looking through them for so long,
yet we haven't found a single clue.
It's useless.
Slow methods are often the most effective.
Rushing will only slow you down.
We're working overtime tonight. All of these files need to be reviewed.
Yes.
Okay, Director.
No sleep tonight then.
Xiaoman,
you must be tired, right?
You don't look too good.
I'm not tired.
The energy of youth.
How much have you gone through?
You're flipping so fast.
Can you be more thorough?
As a senior,
I have to teach you something.
This isn't how you go through files.
Don't just pretend to be busy
by rummaging through papers...
Hold on.
Director, I think I've found something.
[Case of Liu Mingjian]
There are two cases that share overlapping characteristics
with the suspect.
The first case is from 1940, during the Japanese occupation.
The Provisional Government of Shanghai issued a warrant.
This saboteur is named Takanashi Ken,
who was likely a Chinese pretending to be Japanese.
He used a butterfly knife and escaped capture by the Japanese.
The second case, here.
In 1946,
a gang fight occurred at the Laoximen Casino on Zhonghua Road.
This criminal named Chen Yingwu
injured someone with a butterfly knife.
The surname "Takanashi"
is rare in Japan.
The Chinese translation of its pronunciation
is "Yingwu."
And considering the use of the butterfly knife,
we can deduce
that this suspect operated
under a Japanese alias during the Japanese occupation.
After the victory in the Counter-Japanese War,
he used his old ID to apply for a fake household registration
but kept the name "Yingwu."
Frequent identity changes
also match the behavior of an agent.
Good for you.
Wait, you've gone through all those files?
Yes.
And you've even memorized all of them?
I know speed reading and shorthand.
I can finish reading a book
ten times faster than the average person.
What are speed reading and shorthand?
Your analysis just now was excellent.
Anything else?
The key is in this second case.
After Chen Yingwu was arrested,
he was bailed out by a businessman named Li Qian.
His registered address was
Xincheng Mechanical and Electrical Trading Company
at 63 Route Pere Robert at that time.
Li Qian is the general manager of this company.
[Li Qian]
Find Li Qian immediately
and arrest him if you resist.
Yes.
This is Jin Maochang.
Liu Xisheng's reputation is already ruined.
He's no longer in a position to compete with you.
Your efficiency
is truly impressive.
From now on,
we can officially begin our cooperation, right?
The police have already gotten to the bottom
of Liu Mingjian's case.
It's very likely connected to some agents.
If it were in the past, every one of us
might have been rounded up and tortured.
But this is the new government now.
They don't do collective punishment.
However, we should regard this as a warning.
You must conduct thorough
internal checks at your factories and docks.
If anyone is found to have something to do with agents,
there will be no leniency.
Mr. Jin is right.
We can't let any "bad apples"
into our factories.
Yuquan,
there's an old workshop in your sugar factory
that has been left unused.
I'm planning to fix it up
to set up a sugar research institute there.
Mr. Jin, why go through the trouble
of setting up a research institute?
You need to look further ahead.
Although Shanghai has been liberated,
the South is still at war.
Sugar is a crucial strategic resource.
Building a sugar research institute
is about increasing both the quantity and quality of sugar production.
You're busy with your work,
so I'll personally oversee this.
Just focus on getting your current workshops in order.
No need to divide your attention on this matter.
Okay.
[Sugar Research Institute]
Mr. Jin.
We're all on the same side now.
If you wanna say something, just say it.
Putting up a sign and setting off fireworks.
Isn't that a bit too much?
Not at all.
If we acted too discreetly and concealed everything,
it would actually draw more attention.
Now, by being open about it,
no one pays any mind about it.
Shrike said that this is called "hiding in plain sight."
Got it.
Also,
make sure to tell your sugar factory workers
to stop wandering around this place for no reason.
This area involves trade secrets,
so for the researchers...
Give them some peace.
Already taken care of it.
I've still got matters to attend to at my factory,
so I'll take my leave now.
[Flammable]
Be gentle, gentle.
Ogura?
Mr. Wang.
You've worked hard.
We've got the venue
and the equipment for you.
Yes.
I hope you can speed up your research as much as possible.
Mr. Zheng
is usually very kind,
but if he gets impatient...
it may be hard for you to handle.
Please tell Mr. Zheng
that I won't make him wait too long.
If you encounter any difficulties during the research, just let us know.
Mr. Wang.
You can't smoke
here.
Look...
Look at me. My mind is slipping.
Hurry up the progress.
Mr. Jin.
Agent Chen is here.
I've heard so much about you.
Mr. Jin.
Agent Chen.
Who is this?
Jiang Yang.
He is the best
among the assassins I represent.
He also has the nickname
"The Lone Wolf of the Rong Club."
It's been tough for everyone
since Golden Rong of the former Zhongxin Club
stepped down.
Yeah.
Out of loyalty to the underworld, I've been keeping him fed.
There are seven or eight others like him.
Rest assured, with me here,
everything will be kept strictly confidential.
What other qualities does he have?
He cares about money.
How far does that go?
Only cares about money.
One thousand dollars.
Could you take care of him?
Mr. Jin.
Mr. Jiang,
it seems you're exactly the person I've been looking for.
Boss,
what else would you like me to do?
Your gang has many people.
Activate them all
and find this person.
Xu.
It's already time.
Why isn't he here yet?
Don't worry.
He definitely comes to this Western restaurant every day.
Just keep a close watch.
Director.
He isn't here yet.
Keep a close watch.
Everyone, gather around.
Let me repeat it again.
The goal of this mission
is not to kill the suspect.
We need to capture him alive.
[Charlie's Restaurant]
Director, Li Qian is here.
Xiang,
take someone to guard the back door of the restaurant.
Okay.
Follow me.
Yes. Let's go.
Xu, you
keep an eye on the front door.
Okay.
Huzi, you go to the restaurant with me.
Wait.
Huzi can't go. Let me go with you instead.
Why?
Clothing. You'll be suspected for sure
if you go in dressed like that.
We're both in casual short jackets.
How are you better than me?
It's not just a little better.
I'm wearing an American M41 jacket,
worth ten silver dollars.
Besides, have you ever used a knife and fork?
Have you ever tried Western food before?
We Shanghai people have keen eyes.
We'd spot you in a heartbeat.
It's so dangerous; do you think I want to go?
Director.
Listen to him.
You come with me.
It's for your own good.
Young man, would you like a piece of pork chop?
Give me a piece.
Make it a little more tender.
Okay, got it.
Western food won't fill you up. We should eat something beforehand.
Want to try some?
It's so delicious.
Sir, here's your steak.
Please enjoy.
May I have a napkin, please?
Gentlemen, hello.
Please place your order.
Let me order.
Two Wellington steaks.
How well done would you like your steak?
One stake is enough.
You must try the steak here.
Get him a medium-well done one.
For mine, medium is fine.
Also a shrimp and salmon salad.
Two servings of chocolate cake.
Hennessy... Two glasses of it with ice.
And...
That's all.
We don't need wine.
No. No.
W-W-We have to have the wine.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
That will be three silver dollars in total.
Sorry, sir.
We don't accept RMB here.
The new government has implemented regulations.
All commercial establishments
must use RMB.
Sir, please bear with us.
The exchange rate between RMB and silver dollars
fluctuates frequently.
Right now, 1,000 RMB can be exchanged for one silver dollar,
but by tomorrow morning,
it might need 1,200 RMB.
Three silver dollars, right?
Here.
Thank you.
Please wait a moment. The food is coming right up.
Remove this.
You must try the steak here.
You'll remember the taste of this restaurant
once you try it.
With the prices they charge,
I don't need to eat to remember this place.
But, let me say this in front.
You can't take me to this restaurant
while I have to pay.
You have to reimburse me.
There are standards for reimbursement.
This little money
doesn't even meet the reimbursement threshold.
Well.
I'm auxiliary personnel,
and my salary is even halved.
Can you bear to let me spend the money?
Why did you have to order that much?
And the wine?
The wine is a must.
You'll know later.
Sir, your wine.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Enjoy.
Li Qian and his bodyguard have guns.
The chauffeur doesn't.
Be careful.
Come on, Mr. Lu.
Let's celebrate.
Sure.
Hurry up!
Hurry!
Boss.
How's the dock recently?
Nothing much going on.
We are all on high alert.
We won't let the River Gang take advantage of us.
Keep a close watch here.
Please.
I'm going to the restroom.
Okay.
He's heading to the restroom.
Mr. Lu.
A toast to you.
I... I have to down this drink.
Too fast. Drink slowly.
You've had too much. Look at you.
Let me help you there.
Go. Let's go.
Steady.
You drank so much.
Please move aside. My friend is drunk.
I'm so sorry.
The restroom is temporarily unavailable.
What do you want?
Watch out.
Retreat!
Hurry up!
Get down! Get down!
[Charlie's Restaurant]
Get down!
Back off!
All of you, back off!
[Charlie's Restaurant]
Don't move!
Back off! Back off!
Let her go!
Don't move!
You're pretty fast.
Sir,
I splashed the oil just in time, right?
I'm with the Public Security Bureau.
[August First]
I'm here on a mission.
I'd like to ask for your help.
Are you here to catch bad guys?
How can I help you?
Awesome, boss.
Thank you.
If you need anything, come to me.
Take him away.
[Charlie's Restaurant]
Go!
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Hurry up!
You're so different, are you?
Give it to me!
Give me the money!
What are you doing?
Come on!
Don't move!
Let go of him!
Go away!
Let's see who dares to move!
Let go of him!
You can fight, huh?
But you look unfamiliar.
What's your story?
I used to be a soldier.
I fought against the Communists in Xuzhou.
Now that the Communists have taken over the place,
I have nowhere else to go.
I can only scrape by working at the docks.
Boss,
I'm really at the end of my rope.
I want to join the Hook Sword Gang.
With someone backing me, I can have a meal.
What's your name?
Wei Shan.
How about this?
We've got a score to settle with the River Gang in a couple of days.
You follow me.
If you kill one,
you're one of us.
If you kill ten, we are brothers.
Thank you, boss.
Mr. Wei.
What? You still want to fight me?
No. No.
Since the Boss values you so much,
we are brothers from now on.
Earlier, I offended you.
Me and the brothers want to buy you drinks.
I'll treat.
Conflict breeds friendship, right?
We can let you pay.
I just joined the gang.
You guys tell me the rules of the gang.
Wouldn't that be great?
Actually, there aren't many rules.
You just need to hand over 20% of your earnings.
If something goes wrong, the Boss has your back.
To put it bluntly,
that 20 percent is protection money.
That guy with the beard is our Boss, right?
The Boss has a Boss above him too.
Our Chief is very mysterious.
I've been working at the docks for years,
but I've never seen him even once.
But I've heard
that our Chief really loves dancing.
He likes dancing?
He has a private box at the Xianlemen Ballroom year-round.
Wei,
you're so good at fighting.
If you make it up the ranks,
please look out for us.
We're all brothers. You don't need to say that.
Come on. Let's go for a drink.
Let's go!
Let's go for a drink!
Li Qian,
you're quite agile for a fat guy.
You flatter me.
We hope you'll cooperate fully
to receive lenient treatment.
Absolutely, absolutely.
In 1946,
you bailed out Chen Yingwu, didn't you?
So, that's what it is about.
You even found out about such a trivial matter.
I'm impressed.
You caught me here to find him, right?
Take a look at these sketches.
Would this count as a contribution?
Yes.
No, not this one.
Yeah, this one, this one.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Tell us about him.
His real name is Wang Liqun.
He was the captain of the Sixth Action Squad of NBIS in Shanghai.
During the Japanese occupation, both of us were undercover in Shanghai.
We collaborated on some operations,
but we didn't know each other well.
In 1946, I left NBIS
and started my own business.
Shortly after opening my business,
I got a request to bail him out.
He was not the type of person I could afford to offend,
so I bailed him out.
But after he was released, he saw me,
he didn't say a word and, just left.
Did you see him again later?
No.
No, I've almost forgotten about him.
I met him once,
around the end of the Battle of Hsupeng...
No.
Your Party calls it the "Huaihai Campaign."
One day, he invited me out for a drink.
Actually, he was just testing the waters,
seeing if I'd be willing to go undercover
for NBIS in Shanghai.
I politely declined.
Since then, I really haven't been in contact with him.
Do you know where he was staying at that time?
No.
He was always very meticulous.
He always picked the restaurant.
After dinner that day,
he even said he'd take me to a Turkish bath.
I turned him down politely.
I've told you everything I know.
That should count as cooperation, right?
He was likely living around the Putuo area.
Putuo?
Why there?
After a Turkish bath, you may be exhausted.
It wouldn't make sense for him to go to a bathhouse
far away from his home.
So, he was probably living near the bathhouse.
There weren't many Turkish bathhouses open back then.
Only a few were on Fuxing Road in Putuo.
It's called Xinma Road now.
Within a five-kilometer radius of that area,
it's quite likely that he lived there.
This is the room.
Do you know what time it is?
Why are you here?
About that Hook Sword Gang...
Come inside and talk.
What did you find out?
I've found some information about the Hook Sword Gang.
The real boss's surname is Dai,
and he's got a private box at the Xianlemen dance hall.
Xianlemen is a nice place.
Don't you know you're dirty?
It's okay.
She is a foreign chick. She doesn't understand Chinese.
Go ahead.
The Hook Sword Gang and the River Gang have a longstanding conflict.
They're going to fight in a few days.
We can use this opportunity to pull the Hook Sword Gang in
to reach cooperation.
Who said that we want to collaborate with them?
They've got a lot of men and control the docks.
If we work together...
You're meddling in so many things.
How dare you give your opinions about higher-up's business?
Just stick to your job and carry the bag.
Why are you still standing here?
How about I go and you stay here?
Wang Liqun sure was quite the lecher.
Why?
This is adult talk; children shouldn't interrupt.
He should have had a very strict superior.
Getting arrested for gambling and fighting
is a minor offense.
There's no need for him to go through so much trouble to find Li Qian.
With his rank,
he could have easily had any agent
bail him out.
He did it this way,
probably because he wanted to keep it from his superior.
I think so too.
Director, I have another question.
Go ahead.
Why would someone be exhausted
after a Turkish bath?
Mr. Shaobai,
tell me about it, please?
I...
Well...
Lu!
Where are you going?
Here is the thing.
Our Director Lu
has a lot of life experience.
Lu,
explain it to our Xiaoman.
Yes, Director, please tell me about it.
It's because...
M-M-Maybe.
I suppose...
I-I-I suppose...
Well...
It's cold water and then hot water...
Well, there are many temperature changes
like this.
So, it makes people... tired easily.
Lin Shaobai, why are you laughing?
No,
I just thought of something really funny.
Anyway, it's getting late.
We should go home now.
We still have inspections tomorrow.
Don't be late tomorrow, understood?
Got it.
Yes.
By the way,
you take the office car and send Xiaoman home.
It's not safe for a young girl this late at night.
Well...
Don't be late for work tomorrow!
W-W-Why don't you send her?
Wait, where are you going?
Are you heading to a bathhouse...
Didn't you hear the Director?
I still have questions to ask you.
Let's go.
Are you suggesting letting Shaobai pull the strings?
That won't work; it'll only reflect poorly on him.
But even if we go early in the morning,
it's hard to get tickets for "The White-Haired Girl."
They say it's really good.
It's a new society now.
We are the family of a police officer.
We need to maintain the public image for them.
You're right.
Forget it. Let's not go.
We don't want people gossiping,
and we definitely don't want to make Shaobai look bad.
I'm back.
Shaobai, you're back.
Everyone, pause what you're doing for a moment.
The group assignment sheet
for the investigation areas is out.
Take a look, everyone.
This is yours.
Okay.
Cen Xiaoman.
Lin Shaobai.
You two are a team.
This sheet lists the areas
you're responsible for.
Xu,
hand them out.
Okay.
Here.
We have to check every household one by one?
Well...
I've got no problem with that.
But Xiaoman is a girl...
I'm okay with that.
Don't use me as an excuse.
This is your salary for last month.
If you don't want to do it,
I'll take it back.
It's payday.
Lu, wait.
It's just a few bills,
and they're all in RMB.
Lu,
this is half of
what you told me.
I know;
times are tough right now.
But I stayed up late and worked overtime, too.
The supplemental pay guidelines
are still being finalized.
Make sure you've got your assigned areas.
Yes, Director.
Mr. Zheng?
Did we get paid today?
Yes. Yes.
And in full.
It's a good thing that the new government won't deduct our salaries.
Yes. Yes.
Do they pay us in silver dollars?
No. No.
The People's Government pays in RMB, of course.
[Director's Office]
I firmly believe
that the RMB will never end up
like the gold yuan notes.
If you've got something to say, just say it.
Here's the thing, Director Lu.
About the halved salary,
I totally understand.
I have no complaints at all.
But I'm just wondering...
Well...
Can you compensate me?
Okay.
No. No.
I don't want money.
The word "compensate" is a bit too much.
I was wondering
if you could do me a favor.
Well,
could you help me get two tickets for "The White-Haired Girl"?
Just two tickets.
I know.
With your connections,
a quick call could do the trick.
It's just that my mom and Auntie
really want to see the show,
but they haven't been able to get tickets.