♪I sink my soul to the lakebed,
where it vanishes into dust♪
♪Drowning in the hollow,
boundless pale between us♪
♪In the silent dark,
I can't see what lies ahead of us♪
♪Wandering alone in solitude♪
♪Drifting with the waves
a thousand miles away♪
♪Where upon the river
does the moon not shine?♪
♪Frost glides unseen through the air
and into the past♪
♪We gaze at each other in silence♪
♪Who are the river and moon
waiting for?♪
♪I only see the Yangtze
carrying its endless stream♪
=Bloom Once More=
=Episode 17=
Later on,
I started having doubts too.
Well...
She started
acting stranger and stranger.
It was like...
She had completely
forgotten everything about the city.
And...
Her temper and personality
changed drastically too.
She is not Her Highness at all.
She's just an impostor
disguised as Her Highness
to infiltrate Changping Capital.
In fact,
I'd been suspecting it for a long time.
But...
But since I was young,
Ping's mother and I
had been childhood sweethearts.
We truly loved each other.
Without absolute certainty,
I...
I didn't dare pierce
that final veil of doubt.
That day, His Majesty brought me
to the City Lord's Manor.
I thought I was going to die there.
But I never imagined he and I
were the same kind of people.
Hah, so it was Hongyue!
Speak!
Did you and Hongyue collude
and do something to my wife?
Hongyue is such a kind girl.
There's no way she would've
harmed Her Highness with me.
Besides,
I've been searching
for Hongyue's whereabouts all these years.
It's me who should be asking you.
Where did you people hide Hongyue?
Why have I never seen her
again?
You're as short-tempered as me.
What's your name?
Weichen.
Weichen of the Tianji Pavilion?
The Tianji Pavilion has protected
Changping Capital's
national divine artifact,
the Donghuang Bell,
for a thousand years.
Besides,
those of Tianji Pavilion
are bound by sacred oath.
They would never do anything
to harm Changping Capital.
Weichen and Hongyue's bond
was just like mine with her.
We understood each other
deeply from the start.
His Majesty respected that I was
a descendant of the shaman clan,
so he told me
about the Earth Seal Scroll.
When I saw the Earth Seal Scroll,
I could feel it
held extraordinary power.
Unfortunately,
my cultivation was too shallow
to decipher its mysteries.
So I stayed hidden in the secret chamber
to investigate alongside His Majesty
the truth behind Her Highness
and the Earth Seal Scroll.
I believed
that once we uncovered the truth,
I'd definitely see you again.
Later on,
I don't even know what happened,
but my health just kept declining.
Eventually,
I couldn't even get out of bed.
But...
Changping Capital cannot go a day
without a ruler.
After much thought...
I asked Weichen
to disguise himself as me
to be my eyes, my mouth,
to maintain peace
in Changping Capital for me.
At the same time,
he was to continue the investigation.
Over the years,
I've searched
for documents that could unlock
the secret of the Earth Seal Scroll.
But to no avail.
Once, I went to the storage pavilion
to study the structure
of the Earth Seal Scroll.
But I didn't expect
Lu Li was guarding the pavilion.
I feared my presence would be exposed,
so from that day on,
every time I went
to the storage pavilion,
I disguised myself as Her Highness.
So no one would grow suspicious of me.
I see.
The City Lord was poisoned gradually.
It was likely Hailing Incense.
Hailing Incense?
It comes from Western Niuhe Plain.
Its subtle scent excites the senses,
but over time,
it drains your life.
You waste away like a dying flame.
No wonder I too
have been sluggish these past years.
I always lose my temper,
and I'm even hallucinating at times.
Her Highness always lit incense herself
in our room every day.
That must've been Hailing Incense.
Qianqian.
Feeling good?
Breathe it in deeply.
You'll feel even better.
Lass.
I saved your life back then.
This pitiful life of yours
has always belonged to me.
Now...
it's time to give it back.
Who's there?
I'm Yao Wei. A physician from Western Plain
seeks audience outside.
That's a divine healer
I hired from Western Plain
to prepare a calming prescription
for His Majesty.
Bring him in now.
Yes.
Why did that fool
come through the main gate?
I, Hua Qingming, am willing
to arrest the fake Her Highness.
I shall investigate all the cases thoroughly,
including Her Highness's attack,
the injustice against Hongyue,
the Princess's replacement,
Lu Li's treason,
the impersonation of Her Majesty,
(Earth Seal Scroll)
and the plot to destroy the kingdom.
I ask for Majesty's permission
to look into these cases.
You brought me here
to swap your face with that girl's?
What happened 18 years ago
is already exposed.
I can no longer stay here
in Changping Capital.
It was you
who changed my face back then.
Now...
you have to help me again.
Help you?
Master gave you a death order.
If you fail the mission,
you won't need to return to Ximu at all.
Now that the plot has been revealed,
do you think Master will spare you?
Why not help me instead?
I've saved up a fortune
in Changping Capital over the years.
I'll give you half of that.
Let's disappear
from this world completely.
That would be the best option
for us both.
How much?
Enough to buy half the city.
I want it in silver.
Go.
I want her alive.
There are things I need to ask her.
Yes.
It hurts, Mother!
Mother, I'm Qianqian!
You're Qianqian?
You fool!
You're just a fake I picked up
eighteen years ago at a mass grave!
Get in!
What did you say?
Listen here.
Your life
is no different from a stray dog's.
I gave you eighteen years of life
and luxury you never deserved!
You can return it to me now.
Right? That's not too much to ask, no?
Mother!
My child...
Don't blame me.
Every man for himself,
and devil take the hindmost.
The plan
has failed.
If it had succeeded,
perhaps I
could've made you
a noble lady ruling a region.
In
another
life,
then.
♪In the misty mortal world,
my teary eyes brim with unspoken words♪
♪Longing weaves
through the night wind like thread♪
♪Who can unravel old dreams
and tangled grudges of the past?♪
♪A lone lamp burns through the night,
stained by endless zephyr♪
♪Half a life adrift and swaying,
where does a fleeting soul belong?♪
♪Love and hate vanish in a blink,
leaving only emptiness♪
♪With flowers fallen and the moon gone,
a season together turns to sorrow♪
♪Fate begins and ends,
but who was I meant to live for?♪
♪Time rushes by,
leaving parting songs with eternity♪
♪Love stays foolish,
and farewells never end♪
♪With a parting song, I take your hand♪
♪Together, even worlds apart,
we live as one♪
♪The wind carries the scent of flowers
into ailing dreams♪