♪I sink my soul to the lake bed,
where it vanishes into dust♪
♪Drowning in the hollow,
boundless pale between us♪
♪In the silent dark,
I can't see what lies ahead of us♪
♪Wandering alone in solitude♪
♪Drifting with the waves
a thousand miles away♪
♪Where upon the river
does the moon not shine?♪
♪Frost glides unseen through the air
and into the past♪
♪We gaze at each other in silence♪
♪Who are the river and moon waiting for?♪
♪I only see the Yangtze
carrying its endless stream♪
=Bloom Once More=
=Episode 13=
He talked so sweetly.
And then vanished without a trace
in the blink of an eye.
That wretched man!
Liar!
They are all liars!
Maybe Weichen did not lie to you.
Maybe he has been looking for you
all this time,
Hongyue.
What did you just call me?
The traitorous general
from 18 years ago.
Hongyue.
Let me go!
Don't move. Resistance is futile.
You might as well be good
and let me enjoy you.
You fat pig!
Bald donkey!
Do you even know who I am?
When I get out of here, I'll have my father
cut you into pieces and feed you to the dogs!
You hit me?
Behave yourself!
Let go of me!
You're a feisty one.
I like that.
Once the aphrodisiac kicks in,
I'm going to enjoy
every last inch of you.
Sir!
What's wrong?
You're so rough.
You're hurting me.
You're terrible.
Changed your mind?
Mm.
Good.
If you've changed your mind,
then this is mutual.
That way,
you won't be the only one suffering.
Come here.
Sir.
What now?
My legs are still tied.
How are we supposed
to have fun like this?
I see.
Hang on. I'll fix it right now.
I'm getting impatient.
I can't wait a moment longer.
Hurry up!
Untie it faster!
Come…
Bald donkey!
Fat pig!
Lord Zhennan,
why would you say such a thing?
For over a decade,
my Fallen Blossom Lane has seen
thousands of warriors and heroes
come and go.
Who doesn't know the name Yue Yong?
Hongyue?
Afraid I've never heard of her.
18 years ago,
Her Majesty had a personal bodyguard
named Hongyue.
That year,
coincidentally the year
the princess was born,
Her Majesty went to Mount Wanfu
to offer prayers.
Suddenly,
Hongyue ambushed Her Majesty
and the infant princess.
Thanks to the heavens,
Her Majesty managed to escape
with the princess.
Hongyue failed
in her assassination attempt
and fled Changping Capital,
vanishing under a false name.
Everyone in Changping Capital
knows about this.
So it was you, you shameless traitor,
who attacked my mother back then!
I…
Zhuge Renfeng once said
that shortly after your disappearance,
Weichen also vanished.
But before he disappeared,
he said he still had
worldly attachments,
and wandered off chasing after you.
I believe anyone
with true feelings for this world
would never betray the people they love.
So, Hongyue,
what exactly do you know?
Can you tell us?
It was the 45th year of Mingdu.
I was escorting Her Majesty
up the mountain to pray
when we were ambushed by assailants.
Her Majesty took an arrow to the leg.
In desperation,
she entrusted me with the princess
and with the hairpin
now on your head.
I fled for a full day and night
before collapsing in a remote village.
Hongyue!
Where are you, Hongyue?
Your Highness.
Hongyue, you worried me!
Give Qianqian to me.
Weren't you…
I was lucky just now
to escape the pursuers.
So I came straight to find you both.
Hand Qianqian over to me.
Hongyue.
Good work, Hongyue.
No.
You're not Her Highness.
Seize her!
Curses! She gave me a piece of wood!
Where's the real Lu Qianqian?
Master instructed you to bring the Earth
Seal Scroll into Changping Capital.
Everything else will come later.
After I fainted,
I remember nothing.
Fortunately,
I wasn't fatally wounded.
Once I recovered,
I discovered
I had become the most wanted criminal
in all of Changping Capital.
I had hidden the princess in a haystack,
but I was never able to find her again.
With no other option,
I changed my name to Yue Yong
and stayed hidden
in Fallen Blossom Lane.
Barely surviving,
while secretly gathering information.
One day, I swore,
I would uncover the truth behind it all.
Miss.
The first time you came,
I recognized the hairpin on your head.
That is the keepsake Her Majesty left
for the princess.
May I ask where you got it from?
Was the place where you were found
that day Qianchuan Ridge?
How do you know that?
I am Hua Qingming,
Lord Zhenbei of Changping Capital.
The true owner of this hairpin
is Yue.
This is the keepsake my mother
gave her life to leave for me.
Ms. Yue.
Do you have
a six-pointed star-shaped birthmark
on your back?
Is this the mark?
Left Guard Commander Hongyue
pays respects to Your Highness.
Aah!
Stay away!
Stay away from me!
You think you can run?
I was just planning
to have a little fun with you.
But you had to make it this difficult.
Don't blame me for what comes next.
Go ahead, run!
So it was you who kidnapped Lu Qianqian?
That's right.
All these years,
I have been trying to uncover the truth,
who the current Her Majesty really is,
and why that person
disguised themselves as Her Majesty.
I was buying supplies
in Changping Capital
and happened to see Lu Qianqian alone
at a snake charmer's stall.
I seized the opportunity to abduct her.
After capturing her,
I confirmed
that the current Lu Qianqian
has no six-pointed star birthmark.
Which means the real princess
never fell into the hands of that fake.
And wouldn't you know it,
that very day, you all showed up
at Fallen Blossom Lane.
But since
you had already seen the hairpin
and suspected I was the princess
you once lost,
why would you send me
to steal the Earth Seal Scroll?
The Earth Seal Scroll appeared
in Changping Capital together
with that fake.
That mysterious person and the imposter
place so much importance on both
the scroll and the missing princess,
so I figured the two must be connected.
So I took a gamble and sent you
to steal the Earth Seal Scroll.
As for its true purpose,
I have no idea.
What should we do now?
I've already tattooed
a matching six-pointed star
on Lu Qianqian's back.
You rescue Lu Qianqian from Zhao Laosan,
and return to the capital to report in.
Once that fake
sees the tattoo on Lu Qianqian's back,
they will surely panic
and expose their secret.
Let's not tell Lu Buping
the full truth for now.
I've had my fun.
It's time for you to die.
No, please! Don't kill me!
Please…
Don't kill me…
Qianqian!
Are you all right, Qianqian?
Careful, Yue.
Are you all right?
He…
He assaulted…
He assaulted me…
You did what to my sister?
I'll make you pay!
You're going to pay for this!
Stop!
I'll kick you to death,
you disgusting lecher!
Stop!
How dare you lay a hand on her!
I'll beat you to a pulp!
How dare you!
You lecherous scum!
Let's return to the City Lord's Manor
and report in.
(City Lord's Manor)
Qian!
Qianqian!
Are you hurt?
What did they do to you?
Tell me.
I'm here.
- Don't touch me…
- Qianqian…
Don't touch me!
♪In the misty mortal world,
my teary eyes brim with unspoken words♪
♪Longing weaves
through the night wind like thread♪
♪Who can unravel old dreams
and tangled grudges of the past?♪
♪A lone lamp burns through the night,
stained by endless zephyr♪
♪Half a life adrift and swaying,
where does a fleeting soul belong?♪
♪Love and hate vanish in a blink,
leaving only emptiness♪
♪With flowers fallen and the moon gone,
a season together turns to sorrow♪
♪Fate begins and ends,
but who was I meant to live for?♪
♪Time rushes by,
leaving parting songs with eternity♪
♪Love stays foolish,
and farewells never end♪
♪With a parting song, I take your hand♪
♪Together, even worlds apart,
we live as one♪
♪The wind carries the scent of flowers
into ailing dreams♪