♪Come and show your edge♪
♪Don't be afraid to get hurt♪
♪Fly between heaven and earth♪
♪Stand proudly above the clouds♪
♪Little by little♪
♪Blood trickled down the fingertips♪
♪Wipe your tears away♪
♪Before the storm comes ♪
♪Endless nights♪
♪Endless dreams♪
♪The smile that swore to protect♪
♪Desired entanglement from birth♪
♪Will last forever♪
♪Love is a cage, hate is a shackle,
wandering in the mortal world♪
♪Met countless evil spirits♪
♪Permeated the heart
in the name of kindness♪
♪Come on, break through the fate♪
♪In the direction of the wind♪
♪Bury the moonlight♪
♪Come and take the chance♪
♪Exhaust all your faith♪
♪Come and show your edge♪
♪Don't be afraid to get hurt♪
♪Fly between heaven and earth♪
♪Stand proudly above the clouds♪
=The Journey of Chongzi=
(Adapted from "The Journey of Chongzi" by Shu Ke)
=Episode 8=
(Is Zhuo Hao)
(serious about it?)
Getting married with him?
What would happen if Master found out?
Is he really going to marry me to Qinghua?
No.
I can't tell him.
I just want to be with Master forever.
Chong Zi will love this gift.
No, I have to hurry up.
That elm-headed Qin Ke
and the impenetrable Luo Yinfan
are by her side all day long.
If they took advantage of it,
I'd be heartbroken.
I have to go.
Where are you going?
Grab your daughter-in-law.
Stop.
Which immortal lady
do you want to tease again?
There are already many immortal ladies
who have come to Qinghua.
How long are you going to mess around?
Father, I'm serious this time.
I swear I really want to marry
Sage Chonghua's disciple.
If it were her,
it would be absolutely impossible.
Why?
Didn't you quite like her before?
She is clever, quick-witted and charming.
But I heard that Luo Yinfan
kept her by his side,
although he doted on her
in every possible way,
he never taught her any spells,
which is very suspicious.
Moreover, it was rumored that
Chong Zi could retreat unscathed
after encountering Wan Jie twice.
There must be
something wrong.
Father, you have taught me
since I was a child that
seeing is believing.
Why have you been swayed
by rumors yourself?
Seeing is believing.
But there is no smoke without fire.
I've heard everything you said,
and I know it all.
But I still like her.
I only like her.
Enough.
I...
This is your spur of the moment
and doesn't count.
You need to be cautious
about this matter,
and never act willfully.
- Father!
- You...
I fell in love with her
from the first time I met her.
I know that before, I was naughty.
But
after meeting her,
there is no one else in my heart
except her.
Father, I understand your concern.
I also know that marriage
should not be trifled with.
I know better than anyone
what Chong Zi is like.
Get up.
If you don't agree, I won't get up.
You!
Father, I have never begged you
for anything since I was a child.
Father, please promise me.
Father, please.
Forget it.
I will
seek a marriage alliance for you.
Really? Great!
- I'm going to marry her!
- You...
Master didn't come to see me again.
Is it because I caused
too much trouble for him
and he thinks I'm disobedient?
What exactly does Master think of me?
(Chonghua Palace)
No matter how much
she usually talks back to me,
now it seems that
she is just the little girl
when she went up the mountain.
Master.
Get married.
Get married to Master.
Chong.
What are you talking about?
I don't want to get married.
I'd like to be with Master forever.
Your master has been making you kneel.
Why do you still want to be with him?
I am willing to.
No one can replace Master.
Look at you.
I promised you that
I will always be with you.
What else do you want?
(Luo Yinfan.)
(When did you become so fussy?)
Greetings to Mr. Luo.
What's up?
The Councilor said that
a distinguished guest is visiting,
and asked you to go and meet him.
Did he say who's coming?
It's Zhuo Yao, the lord of Qinghua Palace.
It is said that
he's here to ask you for something.
I thought it was just a joke.
I didn't expect my son
to be so infatuated with
Sage Chonghua's disciple.
In desperation, as a father,
I had no choice but to boldly
propose marriage
and make an appointment with Chong Zi.
(Chong Zi is born with evil breath.)
(It would be a good thing for
Nanhua and Yinfan)
(if she took this opportunity to leave.)
Nanhua and Qinghua have always
been on friendly terms.
I wanted to bring my niece Suqiu
and Young Master Zhuo together.
Unexpectedly, Young Master Zhuo
likes Chong Zi.
That would be great.
The two kids
are about the same age and temperament.
They are a perfect match.
That's good.
Let's wait until Mr. Luo arrives
to discuss this matter.
Could it be that Chong Zi
already has an agreed marriage?
Not yet.
That being the case,
and they like each other,
wouldn't it be the best?
Could it be that Nanhua
looks down on Qinghua
and thinks we are not worthy?
I don't agree.
Mr. Luo.
Why?
Chong Zi is still young,
not yet suitable for marriage.
In the Mortal World, women at this age
can get married and have children.
She still needs to devote herself to practice
and cultivate the immortal bones.
She can still practice
after getting married.
She is my disciple
and has to be by my side.
Mr. Luo, you protect your disciple
so closely.
Is it really like rumors that
there is some ulterior secret
hidden in Chong Zi?
Of course not.
What Mr. Luo means is that
Chong Zi is still young
and doesn't know many etiquettes.
He's afraid that
she will cause trouble to Qinghua
after getting married.
Lord Zhuo made unfounded speculation
about Nanhua's disciples for no reason.
Your behavior
is as low as a countryman.
You!
Good.
It seems that Qinghua
is self-sentimental
about the marriage.
Goodbye.
Lord Zhuo. Lord Zhuo.
Lord Zhuo.
You...
You went so far.
Now that you know he will propose,
you should be prepared.
But after all,
this is Chong Zi's main affair.
As her master, you turned them down
without even asking her.
Chong Zi is still young and has no relatives.
Of course I should call the shots for her.
I mean
you should at least let her know about it.
What if she wants to go?
Young Master Zhuo is a promising
young man of the immortal sect,
and is fine-looking.
If he took the initiative
to propose marriage,
no one would say no.
I heard from Zhenzhu that
he and Chong Zi get along well.
If she really wants to,
we can't stop this.
Yinfan.
She cherishes the gift
I prepared for her so much.
The Shadow Mirror of Qinghua Palace.
Quite rare.
It should be sent by Zhuo Hao.
(Zhuo Hao is really romantic)
(and good at pleasing girls.)
Master.
It makes sense.
It may be a little lonely
to stay with me on Zizhu Peak all day.
No, Master.
I am not familiar with Zhuo Hao.
I just received this mirror.
You've grown up.
It's good to have your own ideas.
I won't interfere with
who you make friends with.
Just if you have any ideas,
you can tell me yourself.
Look.
Haven't you always wanted to hang out?
If you two do find each other congenial,
I will promise you.
You can leave Zizhu Peak
to see the outside world.
Think about it carefully
and tell me your decision.
Master, I am not getting married.
I am not willing to.
He and I are just friends.
No, not even friends.
How could I fall in love with him?
Even if I fall in love with Lion,
I won't fall in love with him.
You bad mirror.
I'm going to smash you.
It's all your fault.
Master.
Don't leave me, okay?
If you leave,
you will never find
such an obedient disciple as me.
I can make you happy,
walk Lion for you
and prepare herbal cuisine.
Master, even if you
don't think about me,
you should think about yourself.
Master.
Okay, don't cry.
What are you talking about?
In fact, Qinghua came to
propose marriage today.
But I have declined for you.
As for that mirror,
just throw it away.
Master.
How can you tease me with such a thing?
You don't even know how sad I am.
You still cry like a child
for no reason.
If you are like this,
how will you get married in the future?
Right?
I don't want to get married.
I will always be with Master.
You are a troublemaker,
and you can only cause trouble
wherever you go.
If I leave you,
I don't know who can
cope with the aftermath for you.
Only I can discipline you.
You are a blockhead.
Only I can stand you.
What to do?
It seems that we two weirdos
can only depend on each other
on Zizhu Peak.
Depend on each other?
Really?
What a shame.
Qinghua is
thoroughly discredited.
What a shame.
Sage Chonghua really refused
without leaving any room?
From now on, forget about the marriage
between you and Chong Zi,
and you are not allowed
to mention it again.
No way.
I'm going to ask Luo Yinfan.
Why did he make the decision
for Chong Zi?
Stop.
- You don't feel ashamed enough?
- I...
Listen.
You are not allowed to
go to Nanhua anymore,
let alone see Chong Zi.
- Why?
- You!
I'm going.
I have to ask Chong Zi face to face.
How dare you!
I have to go!
- Dad, it hurts.
- Go.
Shut yourself up
and reflect on yourself.
Dad, it hurts.
Master, hurry up.
What are you up to?
Come on and take a seat.
Master, sit down.
Are you in trouble again?
No!
I don't just get into trouble every day.
Master, if you don't like it,
you can't scold me,
and you can't show it.
After the fish
was cooked by me before,
you have been depressed every day,
and always in a daze by the water.
So I secretly went to the Mortal World
to catch...
To buy a fish.
It's not an immortal fish though,
but a normal fish,
just like me.
Even so,
it will stay with you
for the rest of the time,
until you don't need it,
until it dies.
Master, don't leave it behind.
You should cherish it
like how you cherished the fish I killed.
By the way, Master,
I swear that
I will protect it well
and prevent it from being hurt.
Who else would hurt it but you?
Then give it a name.
It would be called Zi.
You can't eat yourself.
But fish is different from me.
I don't want it to be called Zi.
I like Zi to keep me company.
Which Zi are you talking about?
Master, look.
The relationship between Chong Zi
and Luo Yinfan
progressed very quickly,
even smoother
than we planned.
The two of them are destined.
Of course it's smooth.
How does she treat Wan Jie?
It seems that she has realized
that Wan Jie is Chu Bufu.
The person who led her
into the immortal sect
has now become a demon.
It must be hard
for her to let go.
It's best not to let go.
Now is the time.
It's time to take actions.
Tianmo Token.
Isn't it sealed?
How can it move by itself?
Something's up!
Tianmo Token...
Something happened to Tianmo Token!
(Patriarch's Hall)
Senior.
What happened?
Someone broke into
the Patriarch's Hall last night.
(Liuhe Hall)
Someone broke into
the Patriarch's Hall last night,
trying to cast the blood curse
to awaken the Tianmo Token.
Tianmo Token?
This is not true.
Just a nightmare.
The matter of Tianmo Token
is of great importance.
I'm afraid we have a spy
from the Demon World.
We have to investigate thoroughly.
- Yes.
Does any of you know the origin
of the Tianmo Token?
I heard of some.
Say it.
Decades ago, Demon King
Ni Lun was ambitious.
He not only led the demons
to tyrannize the Mortal World,
but also boldly invaded
the Immortal World.
Dozens of sects including Tianshan Sect
and Shushan Sect
were hit hard.
Ni Lun even attacked Nanhua,
attempting to enter the Tongtian Portal
and destroy the Six-world Monument.
Fortunately, Celestial King of Nanhua
beheaded him
with the method of extinction
in Jitian Techniques.
Celestial King of Nanhua was also
injured and passed away.
Ni Lun
used this Tianmo Token
to summon the demons.
The reason why the Demon World
is different today
is precisely because
it has been sealed by Ni Lun.
Since then, no Demon King
can use this to summon the demons.
I think the most important reason
is not because
the Tianmo Token was sealed,
but because
the disciples in the immortal sects
never forget their important responsibilities,
keep in mind the teachings
of the Celestial King,
and work together
to protect the common people.
Therefore, the demons
are no longer rampant,
and the world is at peace.
- Right.
- Exactly.
Tianmo Token is cast forbidden technique
by Ni Lun,
and only the blood curse cast by
close relatives can unravel it.
Now there is blood on it.
Obviously,
someone sneaked into
the Patriarch's Hall last night
in an attempt to use the blood curse
to awaken Tianmo Token.
But this person didn't succeed.
That being the case,
it is useless to delve into it.
Ni Lun had no blood relatives.
It's natural for him to fail.
It's just that this person
tried to awaken Tianmo Token
with evil intentions.
If this person is left in Nanhua,
something will happen in the future.
As a disciple of Nanhua,
this person has evil thoughts.
Nanhua will never keep this kind of scum.
If he volunteers to be executed,
Sage Tianji and I
will make an exception.
Otherwise,
we will punish him severely
according to our rules.
What?
No one dares to admit?
That being the case,
Sage Tianji, please predict
and find out the truth.
No.
It's just a dream. It's not real.
Why are you still quibbling?
It's obviously you.
Could it be possible to fake it?
I...
It's not your turn to speak.
Mu Yu, as the chief disciple,
is this how you teach
your disciples to behave?
If you can't teach them well,
I'll take care of it for you.
Miaoyuan contradicted
for the sake of Nanhua.
The Book of Secrets has reproduced
yesterday's scene.
It was Chong Zi who cast the blood curse
in an attempt to awaken Tianmo Token.
How long are you going to protect her?
It wasn't me.
I was groggy last night,
as if I had dreamed about this scene.
But that was just a dream.
I didn't go anywhere last night,
just stayed in my room.
And I have nightmares
whenever I see Tianmo Token.
I'm even hiding from it,
how could I go look for it?
According to what you said,
Sage Tianji got you wrong?
It was really not me.
It flew towards me by itself.
And I never learned
the blood curse.
Someone, catch the traitor Chong Zi.
Who dares to move?
I know my disciple's temperament best.
Although she's brave,
she doesn't dare to do this,
and she has no reason to do so.
How can we be convinced
based on her statement alone?
It's really strange.
If Chong Zi deliberately concealed it,
why would she say
such a credible statement
like a nightmare?
I remember that
Demon King Ni Lun had subordinates
who are good at the nightmare technique,
and they can manipulate people's minds.
Chong Zi may have been hit
by the nightmare technique.
Nonsense.
Nanhua is heavily guarded,
and there are mythical creatures
guarding the mountain.
How can the spies
of the Demon World get in?
Since Sage Tianji can reproduce
what happened yesterday,
he will also be able to determine
whether Chong Zi was haunted
by the nightmare technique.
I am willing to let Sage Tianji check.
Councilor.
That being the case,
we can first put Chong Zi
in the Immortal Prison
to separate her from the Tianmo Token.
We will talk about other things
in detail later.
What do you think?
My master would agree.
As long as I can prove my innocence,
I am willing to cooperate with anything.
It's just that if the truth comes out,
Councilor Sage, please be impartial,
and don't use evil breath
to blame me casually.
You!
Are you really willing to
go to Immortal Prison?
Suffering is nothing
compared to innocence.
Besides, I believe that Master
will uphold justice for me.
You are worthy of being my disciple.
As the disciple of Sage Chonghua,
you never practice martial arts with us.
It just so happens that
our masters are not here today.
Show me
what supreme spells
Sage Chonghua taught you.
I don't want to fight with you.
But I do.
Aren't you with evil breath?
Don't hold yourself.
Just show us.
Or if you call me senior
and say that you are not worthy
to be Sage Chonghua's disciple,
I will let you go.
It's a pity that
I am the only disciple of my master.
Luo Yinfan's disciple
will never be competitive,
let alone hurt others.
How do you deserve to be Nanhua's senior?
Really?
How dare you bully her,
and abuse the lynching of your disciple?
Young Master Zhuo, you got us wrong.
We are just punishing her for Nanhua.
Punish?
What qualifications do you have
to punish Chong Zi?
You may not know.
Chong Zi attempted
to steal the Tianmo Token.
Councilor Sage ordered us
to send her to the Immortal Prison
without delay.
Ignore them.
Chong Zi, I will take you away.
I can't go with you.
Otherwise, it would be difficult for me
to prove my innocence.
I promised to wait for Master.
He will pick me up in a few days.
I believe in him.
If I go with you,
where can he find me?
Why are you talking about
your master all the time?
You care so much about him,
but what about him?
He leaves you at the mercy of others.
In the end, it's you who suffers.
Young Master Zhuo, you'd better
not meddle in our affairs.
Please make way
and facilitate my work.
If you insist on stopping us,
don't blame us for offending you.
Let's go. Ignore them.
She's mine.
Chong Zi!
It's all your fault.
If you hadn't been
meddling in our business,
Chong Zi wouldn't have been taken away
by Wan Jie at all.
I have to report to Sage Chonghua now.
Are you still suspecting that
it is a nightmare technique?
But Senior said that
Nanhua was heavily guarded.
How could the disciples
of the immortal sect
know the spells of the demons?
What if there is an escaped criminal?
What happened
before Chong Zi
entered the Patriarch's Hall?
Did you find any clues
in the Book of Secrets?
If it granted whatever is requested,
it wouldn't be called Book of Secrets.
It will take some time
to know the leads you want.
But I always feel that this matter
is aimed at your disciple.
Mr. Luo.
Just now came the urgent report that
Sima Miaoyuan and the others
were attacked on the way
to send Chong Zi away.
Chong Zi
was robbed by Wan Jie.
(What is this place?)
(Because before being a demon,)
(Wan Jie was Chu Bufu,)
(the famous chief disciple
of Changsheng Palace)
(as well as your Mr. Immortal.)
Who are you?
I met you once in Panhai Town.
You were an immortal back then.
Piss off.
Do you still remember
the beggar you rescued
in Panhai Town?
They all bullied me,
stoned me,
and even tried to pluck my eyes.
I have been looking for you
all these years,
and I just want to say thank you
to you personally.
Although your appearance has changed,
I know that
you are Chu Bufu,
the chief disciple of Changsheng Palace.
There is no Chu Bufu here,
only the Demon King Wan Jie.
It doesn't matter if you don't admit it.
I'm not afraid of you.
My magical skills are very powerful now,
and I am no longer
that beggar
who allowed others to bully me.
Born with evil breath.
No wonder Luo Yinfan wants you.
Since you don't admit that
you are Mr. Immortal,
there is no need for me
to get close to you.
You are the Demon King.
I am just a humble disciple
of Nanhua.
What good would it do you to kidnap me?
So noisy.
If you could be quiet,
I might save your life.
Tell me
why.
According to what you said,
you want Chong Zi to fend for herself?
She intentionally
approached Tianmo Token,
which was obviously
out of sheer scheming.
If you hadn't blindly protected her,
she would have been kicked out
of Nanhua long ago.
Now it is her fate
to be robbed by Wan Jie,
and she cannot blame anyone else.
Others will be of no use.
I will be looking for her myself.
Yinfan.
She is like this now,
and you still insist on finding her
and saving her with all your strength.
Not to mention how ruthless
Wan Jie is
and how hard to find the hiding place,
just because you risk your life
in order to find Chong Zi
is already breaking the rules.
Rules?
Councilor,
if I can't even protect my own disciple,
how can I protect the Immortal World
and the common people?
Someone.
Yes, sir.
Send an order
to let all the disciples
find Chong Zi's whereabouts.
Once there is news about her,
report to me as soon as possible.
Yes.
Wait.
Remember.
Report to me
as soon as you find
Chong Zi's whereabouts.
Don't let anyone else know, understand?
Chong Zi
is just the nemesis in Yinfan's life.
Hand over Chong Zi.
Otherwise don't blame me for being rude.
Why are you here?
I didn't expect you
to look for your disciple.
I should ask you this.
Ask me?
If you hadn't sent Chong Zi
to the Immortal Prison,
she wouldn't have encountered this.
There is no need for outsiders
to intervene in my disciple's affairs.
You lost your disciple.
Yet you come to Demon King Hall.
Isn't it ridiculous?
Hand over Wan Jie.
Otherwise,
I will slaughter
your Demon Palace today.
Wan Jie is not here.
It's useless for you to make trouble here.
It is impossible for you not to know.
Wan Jie is arrogant
as the Demon King,
and disdains to be with us.
The Land of Tribulations
is a place that is
neither in the Immortal World
nor in the Demon World.
Is my tip too obvious?
Mr. Zhuo, is there something else?
If you're late,
Luo Yinfan will take the lead.
Today I will spare your lives.
I will teach you a lesson next time.
♪When affection turns into stars♪
♪Missing would go afar♪
♪Passed by in this lifetime♪
♪Gazed with eager expectation♪
♪Fate is destined to be immortal♪
♪Don't be afraid to hold hands♪
♪If the heart traps itself♪
♪Who can escape♪
♪Looking back, nowhere to stay♪
♪May time flow back into your eyes again♪
♪The desire of a lifetime,
being together till the end of the world♪
♪Love and hate exist persistently♪
♪The trick of fate burns out the lights♪
♪The moonlight shines on me♪
♪The past is drifting with deep love♪
♪Years hurry on,
when will the lovers meet again♪
♪Looking back,
unpredictable cause and effect♪
♪Joys and sorrows,
separations and reunions♪
♪Feel reluctant
to cut the lingering affection♪
♪Wish to be together from dawn to dusk♪
♪Spring comes and autumn goes
with all ending in smoke♪
♪You are always in my mind♪
(The right of communication through network
exclusively belongs to Tencent.)