♪Come and show your edge♪
♪Don't be afraid to get hurt♪
♪Fly between heaven and earth♪
♪Stand proudly above the clouds♪
♪Little by little♪
♪Blood trickled down the fingertips♪
♪Wipe your tears away♪
♪Before the storm comes ♪
♪Endless nights♪
♪Endless dreams♪
♪The smile that swore to protect♪
♪Desired entanglement from birth♪
♪Will last forever♪
♪Love is a cage, hate is a shackle,
wandering in the mortal world♪
♪Met countless evil spirits♪
♪Permeated the heart
in the name of kindness♪
♪Come on, break through the fate♪
♪In the direction of the wind♪
♪Bury the moonlight♪
♪Come and take the chance♪
♪Exhaust all your faith♪
♪Come and show your edge♪
♪Don't be afraid to get hurt♪
♪Fly between heaven and earth♪
♪Stand proudly above the clouds♪
=The Journey of Chongzi=
(Adapted from "The Journey of Chongzi" by Shu Ke)
=Episode 33=
(Xichun Restaurant)
Miss Zi, here you are.
Come in, please.
Miss Zi.
Are you changing wine or dine-in today?
This way, please.
Miss Zi, take a seat.
Serve me
all the fine wine and food here.
Today is about celebrating.
Get me more wine.
My master loves it.
Sure, hold on.
Sir, this way, please.
Mas...
This way.
Why are you still here?
Shouldn't we
be here?
Didn't you say you were going
to Qinghua Palace today?
Right.
Yu Du is about to leave.
Now that the Qinghua Palace
is badly hurt,
the demons must be ready to rebel.
We have to get the drop on,
not just sit still.
The rampant demons
need to be rectified.
I will go with you.
No need.
I can go by myself.
A lot has happened recently.
You'd better guard Nanhua
with Councilor.
Right.
Yinfan.
Come over.
Master.
Yinfan.
Here.
Ke.
Councilor and Supervisor are now
discussing important matters.
Don't go in yet.
Also,
don't bother Supervisor Sage recently.
He needs to have a rest-cure.
If anything happens,
be sure to let me know first.
What happened to Sage Chonghua?
No more asking.
Just do as I say.
Master, you are back.
Why are you here?
I'm your disciple.
Of course I am here.
Did you forget?
Disciple?
When did I accept a disciple?
Master, look.
I didn't lie to you.
(Modified Recipe of Jade Wheel Cake)
I made Jade Wheel Cake for you
according to the pastries
in Xichun Restaurant.
So
I did take in a female disciple.
Master.
Don't you remember anything?
My biological parents died early,
and my stepmother wanted
to sell me to a brothel.
It was you who saved me
and brought me back to Nanhua.
I wasn't worthy to be your disciple.
Both Councilor and Sage Tianji
objected.
But because of my pitiful background,
you resisted all the odds
and insisted on accepting me as a disciple.
Master.
You said that
you will protect me,
let me not be afraid,
and stay by your side with peace of mind.
It's a big deal.
Why don't I remember that?
Why am I losing this memory?
You must have been too tired
from practicing recently.
Master.
Don't you believe me?
Give me some time to think about it.
I see.
It must be that I did something wrong
to make you angry,
so you deliberately pretend
to lose your memories
and want to drive me away.
Never mind.
I won't make it hard for you.
As a mere mortal,
I am very satisfied
to be by your side for so long.
Yinfan.
What are you...
Councilor,
she's loose-lipped.
She really shouldn't have
offended you.
But please forgive her disrespect
for the sake of her being
my future disciple.
Now that you don't need me,
I should be leaving.
Wait.
Master.
Do you have anything else to tell me?
I didn't mean I'd drive you away.
The things I promised you
will never change.
You are still my disciple.
♪If I hadn't brushed away
the cloud and mist♪
♪Barely to catch a glimpse♪
♪How could there be distracting thoughts♪
♪Entangled with each other
and owe each other♪
♪Dreams of two worlds come and go♪
Miss Zi.
It's already three o'clock in the afternoon.
♪Everything has changed, tears falling♪
♪The moment of hugging♪
♪I hope♪
(Xichun Restaurant)
♪I fall and hang around in the waves♪
♪Dyed with love and missing♪
Miss Zi.
It's nine o'clock.
Look.
There's no one else now.
♪I hope you can look down on the world♪
Miss Zi.
If you don't want to go back,
my boss said that
you can stay here
for one night today,
and keep waiting tomorrow.
No way.
What if he doesn't see me
when he comes
and then he just leaves?
You must have never imagined that
Luo Yinfan is mine now.
I finally replaced you
and got everything you got.
(Xichun Restaurant)
Miss Zi.
Take your time.
Close the door.
Okay.
Why don't you come home so late?
Who are you waiting for?
Me?
How dare you beat me?
(Master won't like me this way.)
I don't want to kill.
Piss off.
(Xichun Restaurant)
(Panhai Town)
♪It rains the whole night,
and a tear falls♪
(Xichun Restaurant)
♪I miss you so much♪
♪I wander in the world day by day♪
♪But I keep a light that shone on you♪
♪So I can keep your shadow in mind♪
♪I love you since I was young♪
♪I won't regret loving you even if I die♪
♪I only hope we can spend time together♪
♪After meeting you♪
(I can't believe you lied to me.)
(But why don't you come?)
♪There is no right or wrong in love and hate,
but there are demons in our minds♪
♪After meeting you♪
♪I'm most afraid that everything is an illusion,
alone in joys and sorrows♪
♪I'm willing to die for you♪
♪If we meet again in the afterlife,
don't try to feel the vicissitudes of life♪
Young Master.
You woke up.
Here.
Did he come
at last?
He said he would start over with me.
He said
he would give up anything for me.
Why am I so stupid?
He obviously wouldn't do that for me,
but I still believed him.
Young Master.
Are you here to laugh at me?
You are right.
I am a complete fool
and deserve to be let down!
Everything I said before
was meant to scare you.
Maybe
something happened to Luo Yinfan.
Others may not believe him.
But you, Young Master,
how could you not believe him?
Is it you?
You kept him from coming to see me,
didn't you?
If I really did this,
why did I send you away
from Shuiyue City back then?
Why didn't he come to see me?
What is more important
than the agreement between us?
He abandoned me again.
Again and again.
He abandoned me again!
Believe it or not,
you did nothing wrong.
Even if he breaks his promise,
you will not be left alone.
Young Master.
I will always be with you.
It is best
if you want to return to Shuiyue City.
If you want to ask him,
I will accompany you to Nanhua.
Wherever you want to go,
I will be by your side.
She woke up.
I really underestimated Demon Zi.
She waited for him without sleep
for two days and two nights.
But Luo Yinfan
still didn't surprise me.
I'm a little bored
watching the show.
Your happiness
is built on the pain of others?
The Demon King's vision
is far above yours.
Of course, he would find this
upside-down and artificial drama
boring and ridiculous.
If you want to achieve something great,
you have to suffer torture.
Do you think I don't care
about Queen Zi's life?
You are completely wrong.
I just
want to do her a favor
and wake her up.
Save your high-sounding words.
If I know
you did something to hurt her,
I won't let you go.
Are you worthy of threatening me?
Take care of your young master.
Queen Zi.
If it's about Luo Yinfan,
no need to say it.
Or
are you here to laugh at me too?
You just love the wrong person.
Why should I laugh at you?
I just blame myself.
If I had known this,
I shouldn't have said those things
to you that night
to make you so sad now.
Why did he use the excuse
of protecting me
to hurt me?
To Luo Yinfan,
am I just a plaything at beck and call?
What does he think of me?
It's really not his style
to be so impulsive.
Instead of pitying yourself here,
you might as well ask him face to face.
Ask him?
He didn't even want to come to see me,
so why should I ask for a snub?
That being the case,
you should think about
the way ahead.
You rejected the Demon King
because of Luo Yinfan.
And he has failed you now.
It's okay if you can let go of everything
and travel around the world.
If you want to take revenge,
or keep staying in the Demon World,
you have no choice
but to make peace with the Demon King.
Did Wang Yue
tell you anything about me?
The Demon King is not angry at all
about your affairs,
and even asked me to tell you that
although you can't be a couple,
your status in the Demon World
has never changed.
He wants something from me.
It's really weird.
He didn't even come to see you
after something so big happened.
It may be that he has been busy
with the affairs of Jinchi and his wife recently
and has no time for you.
Jinchi?
What happened to them?
Jinchi voluntarily gave up the centurial spell
in exchange for the 30-year lifespan
of the two of them as mortals.
What?
They have a lifespan of
hundreds of years
after surrendering to the Demon World.
Isn't it good?
Jinchi said that
Lady Bai was implanted with a blood thorn
in her heart
by the people of the immortal sect
back then,
and the pain could go through
her whole body with just a slight movement.
He didn't want to see Lady Bai
suffer so much
and live in pain,
so he made a deal with Wang Yue.
Since then,
Lady Bai has recovered
from all illnesses,
but the two of them
will always be mortals.
Is it really worth it
just to live for 30 years?
Use Blood Torture in exchange for
staying peacefully with your beloved one
for 30 years.
I think it's worth it.
They probably thought so too.
Tomorrow, the Hundred-Eyed Demon Cave
will open,
and the demon scent of heaven and earth
will enter the world,
which will be extremely beneficial
to the cultivation of the demons.
This is the top priority
of the Demon World for hundreds of years.
I have long arranged for the valley owners
to prepare for several months.
Today
I summoned you all
to choose a leader
who can lead the demons.
This time,
Demon Zi will be the leader
of the demon army
to subdue
the Hundred-Eyed Celestial Demon.
Demon Zi.
Are you willing to take on
this important task?
(You have no choice)
(but to make peace with the Demon King.)
Now that you've made up your mind,
I'd accept the order.
Okay.
While all the protectors are here today,
choose one to be
your lieutenant general.
I heard that there seems
to be a Longevity Herb
in the Hundred-Eyed Demon Cave.
First come, first served.
Yin Shuixian is willing to help Queen Zi
to take down the Hundred-Eyed
Demon Cave together.
Demon Zi.
Head straight to the East Sea
with all the demon soldiers,
and after you subdue
the Hundred-Eyed Celestial Demon,
you can return to the Demon World.
With the help of
Tian Zhixie and Protector Yin,
it must be a piece of cake.
In this battle with
the Hundred-eyed Celestial Demon,
everyone has to listen to
the arrangement of Demon Zi.
Her orders are as my own.
Understand?
- Yes.
How is it?
Do you think the Demon World is good
after you went out for a while?
At least
no one lies to you here.
What does my business
have to do with you?
Take it.
Although someone
ruined our wedding this time,
it's not your fault.
According to the agreement,
the Tianmo Token and the demon sword
are still yours.
I won't take them away.
Should I thank you?
You owe me
more than a thank you.
Now that I have got the Tianmo Token
without us being married,
I will give you something in return.
I will help you subdue
the Hundred-Eyed Demon.
(After I take down
the Hundred-Eyed Demon tomorrow)
(and get the Longevity Herb,)
(my husband can prolong his life
by another 16 years.)
My bad.
I woke you up.
Shuixian.
I just dreamed about the past.
In the heavy snow,
I stood in a lush plum forest.
You ran to me
in white
and called me Master.
At that time,
I wasn't that sick and weak.
I led you to practice swordsmanship,
cultivate,
and travel around.
Master.
Do you remember all this?
I remember bits and pieces,
but not everything.
Why are you crying?
Master.
I...
Don't call me Master.
That's all in the past.
We have been a couple for so many years.
Just call me honey.
Honey.
Don't you blame me?
What are you to blame?
I expelled you from the Tianshan Mountain
at that time,
but it was just an expedient measure,
so that I could be with you
in an open and aboveboard manner
after the war.
Fortunately,
after going around and around,
we finally became a couple.
Qinghua sent a message saying that
the Hundred-Eyed Demon Cave
has been opened,
and the demon scent will enter the world.
By then,
a monster conceived by heaven and earth
will show up.
If the demons succeed,
they will definitely bring disaster
to the world.
Yinfan.
Got it.
I will lead people to surrender it.
Sage Chonghua.
I am also going.
Yinfan should go to
the Hundred-Eyed Demon Cave alone.
Qin Ke.
Go to other sects
to report the news.
Yes.
Master, I will go with you.
I also want to share worries
for the immortal sect.
Yinfan.
Have you heard that
a new general named Demon Zi
joined the Demon World?
That demon is extremely cunning.
You must be careful.
Demon Zi?
How come I have no impression?
Master, you have never
fought with her before.
Of course you don't know her.
It is said that Demon Zi is scheming,
ruthless,
and good at psychological attacks.
Don't believe what she says,
nor be fooled by her.
Just follow me.
I will make her executed.
Yes.
Sage Chonghua.
You should go before it's too late.
I'll go see what Senior Qin has to say.
And I'll be right there.
All right.
How could Sage Chonghua
not know Chong Zi?
What did you do to him?
Why can't he remember anything?
As you can see,
Supervisor no longer remembers
who Chong Zi is.
That being the case,
no matter how angry you are,
it will not help.
But I would be very happy
if I were you.
Without Luo Yinfan as hindrance,
perhaps Chong Zi would
take another look at you.
Wouldn't everyone be happy?
How about you?
Why do you call him Master?
Although
Supervisor can't remember
Chong Zi anymore,
some memories
are not so easy to forget.
He remembers that
he was supposed to have a disciple.
Since that person cannot be Chong Zi,
it can only be me.
I'm about the same age as her,
with similar experiences.
I am the best candidate
to take her place in Supervisor's heart.
You are simply grabbing.
Aren't you afraid of being exposed?
Who?
No one in Nanhua or
even the immortal sect
wants Luo Yinfan to remember Chong Zi.
As long as Councilor
and your master don't say anything,
I'm his only disciple.
Qin Ke.
You'd better mind your own business.
This is related to Nanhua's foundation,
and it is not something
you can interfere with.
There are many ways to
keep Sage Chonghua in Nanhua,
but it should not be cheating.
My master and Councilor are wrong.
As for you...
You changed your identity
and took over other's place
just to satisfy your own selfishness.
So shameless.
I did all this by Councilor's default.
You dare not disobey your masters
in the main hall,
but blame me here.
You!
You can go and explain all this
to Sage Chonghua.
It's just that can you bear
the consequences afterwards?
You are not worthy to
be Miss Zhuo's disciple.
I will do better than her.
(Liuhe Hall)
Lord Zhuo.
Why did you suddenly
pass on the position
to Young Master Zhuo?
Hao lost all his spiritual power
after being stabbed by Demon Zi.
As a father,
I couldn't just watch my son
turn into a cripple.
Demon Zi was so mad
that she hurt Zhuo Hao.
Everyone can see
how Zhuo Hao treats her.
How did she become like this?
Sage Tianji.
It was my fault that
I was disrespectful to your sect before.
Here
I apologize to you.
Lord Zhuo, no need for this.
In fact, now I've figured it out.
As long as Hao is safe and sound,
nothing else matters.
Sage Tianji.
If you can predict all that's to happen,
you should be able to see Hao's future.
I have a request.
If something happens to me,
I hope you will take good care of Hao,
and don't let him go astray.
Lord Zhuo, don't worry.
Yinfan...
He won't be as confused as before.
Nanhua
will never leave Young Master Zhuo alone.
Great.
♪Juvenile with a spring shirt,
toast to the past♪
You...
Isn't my drawing good?
♪Call the names of the old friend,
but no one comes back♪
She is always
my perfect match.
♪The world is silent,
and I will never regret the encounter in this life♪
♪The galaxy is full of stars,
willing to fall into the endless abyss♪
♪The mountains and the sea separate us,
but we are heart to heart♪
♪Lovesickness is wondering in my heart♪
♪Life is like a dream, stick to
that person's return date♪
(No.)
(She did that to drive me away.)
(I was tricked.)
(Chong Zi would never treat me like that.)
♪We have been separated for years,
even the moon knows how affectionate I am♪
♪After turning around, who can bear to forget♪
♪Sigh for this life and the rest of my life
to meet you in my dream♪
The weather is changing.
This is a sign that the Demon Cave
is about to open.
The entry of demon scent into the world
is of great benefit to the Demon World.
A monster conceived by heaven and earth
will show up.
Monster?
Young Master, don't worry.
Just use the Demon King's relic,
the Eye of the Demon God,
to subdue it
for your urging.
Will the immortal sect be involved?
This is a big event of the Demon World.
Of course we are the first to sense it.
But once the Demon Cave is opened,
the immortal sect will definitely notice it.
This place is quite close
to Qinghua Palace.
Young Master, resolve it as soon as possible.
Otherwise, things will be hard to tell
after they arrive.
It's coming.
♪Come on, break through the fate♪
♪In the direction of the wind♪
♪Bury the moonlight♪
♪Come and take the chance♪
♪Exhaust all your faith♪
♪Come and show your edge♪
♪Don't be afraid to get hurt♪
♪Fly between heaven and earth♪
♪Stand proudly above the clouds♪
♪Little by little♪
♪Blood trickled down the fingertips♪
♪Wipe your tears away♪
♪Before the storm comes ♪
♪Endless nights♪
♪Endless dreams♪
♪The smile that swore to protect♪
♪When I open my eyes,
the sword of Ni Lun reappears♪
♪In an instant, there are
dark clouds and lightning♪
♪Don't ask the heaven
how to judge good from evil♪
♪People's hearts are the hardest to tell♪
♪Come on, pick up the affectionate sword
and slash at the ruthless flower♪
♪The wind blows the dust,
and there is a depression in the world♪
♪I've heard that things are changing♪
♪Light the agarwood under the moon♪
♪Memories flow in the galaxy♪
♪Even the gods can't escape♪
♪The heart is softened♪
♪Desired entanglement from birth
will last forever♪
♪Love is a cage, hate is a shackle,
wandering in the mortal world♪
♪Met countless evil spirits♪
♪Permeated the heart
in the name of kindness♪
♪Come and show your edge♪
♪Don't be afraid to get hurt♪
♪Fly between heaven and earth♪
♪Stand proudly above the clouds♪
Is it dead?
The Hundred-Eyed Demon
just had its eyes taken away
by the Eye of the Demon God.
It won't die.
It's him.
Young Master, stay here.
Did you forget what he did to you before?
He finally dared to show up.
I need to ask him clearly.
Young Master.
Are you Demon Zi?
♪When affection turns into stars♪
♪Missing would go afar♪
♪Passed by in this lifetime♪
♪Gazed with eager expectation♪
♪Fate is destined to be immortal♪
♪Don't be afraid to hold hands♪
♪If the heart traps itself♪
♪Who can escape♪
♪Looking back, nowhere to stay♪
♪May time flow back into your eyes again♪
♪The desire of a lifetime,
being together till the end of the world♪
♪Love and hate exist persistently♪
♪The trick of fate burns out the lights♪
♪The moonlight shines on me♪
♪The past is drifting with deep love♪
♪Years hurry on,
when will the lovers meet again♪
♪Looking back,
unpredictable cause and effect♪
♪Joys and sorrows,
separations and reunions♪
♪Feel reluctant
to cut the lingering affection♪
♪Wish to be together from dawn to dusk♪
♪Spring comes and autumn goes
with all ending in smoke♪
♪You are always in my mind♪
(The right of communication through network
exclusively belongs to Tencent.)