(Kim So Hyun)
(Lee Hong Ju and Kang Hoo Young)
(Chae Jong Hyeop)
(Yun Ji On)
(Kim Da Som)
(Serendipity's Embrace)
(Episode 7)
I'll read your feedback later. You should go now.
What's wrong, Jun Ho? Are you sick?
What if I am?
What if I left because I was sick?
Would you take me back?
Get up first.
Do you think you can get up?
Hong Ju.
I've been very sick.
I couldn't breathe.
My hands shook.
I couldn't even write a single word.
I didn't know.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want you to see me like this.
I had to leave you when you were crying.
How do you think I felt then?
We've known each other for a decade.
You had feelings for me for all those years.
You have always been special to me.
Even when we were apart, it was the same.
It was the same for you too.
I'll call Mr. Ju and ask him to come and check on you.
You should rest up.
Lee Hong Ju.
You're still going to leave?
How could you do this to me?
I was sick too!
Please forgive me.
Actually,
I really wanted to know why you left.
For three years,
I beat myself up wondering what I had done...
or what I hadn't done.
With you gone,
I thought that it was my fault that everyone around me was leaving.
I told myself that again and again.
But now that I know why you left,
I'm angry.
You would have left me anyway no matter what I did.
You were...
going to leave without explaining anything to me.
Forgive you?
Yes, I will. I think I can forgive you now.
You gave me the answer to a question...
I had been struggling with my whole life.
That people who leave had a reason to do so.
And that...
isn't my fault.
I know that now thanks to you.
Hong Ju. Hear me out.
Right.
I must make something clear.
I have feelings for someone else.
I will probably...
end up liking him a lot more than now.
My decision won't change either.
I won't go back alone.
If you insist on having your way,
I'll give it my all this time.
- Give your all to what? - Everything I hadn't tried before.
Causing trouble or going astray.
Hoo Young.
Hey.
Do Seon. He's been acting weird lately, right?
He keeps surprising me these days.
Did he suddenly become someone else?
Or has he always been like that? Did he just hold back...
(Accident prone area, slow down)
I'll step down from the project.
Why?
I'm sorry.
I can't separate my private life from work.
Did Mr. Bang do something to you?
No.
Then did you?
Yes. I did.
Okay. You can step down.
I don't want to force you to take on the project...
when you don't want to.
I'm sorry.
(Turn "My Avant-garde Lover" into an animated movie!)
I don't need this anymore. Take it.
(Please hire me as an employee of Peter's Pen.)
(Applicant Lee Hong Ju)
(Turn "My Avant-garde Lover" into an animated movie!)
I stayed up all night writing that for the first time in my life,
and I found a dream.
I want people like me...
to see our animated movies...
and have warm and fun dreams.
(Turn "My Avant-garde Lover" into an animated movie!)
Did you enjoy typing this up?
Yes.
How much?
Enough not to know I'd stayed up...
and that the sun had risen.
(Turn "My Avant-garde Lover" into an animated movie!)
Seriously. What's up with the PE teacher?
Our college entrance exam is over. Do we still have to go to school?
- Exactly. - Forget about him.
He's always been so annoying.
Hey, did you watch the drama?
The male supporting character is totally my type.
You guys are so lucky.
Pardon?
You can hang out with your friends from morning until night.
You can have your meals at proper times.
If you get sleepy, you can take a nap.
Then you can get up and eat some more.
Things were better when I was in school.
Are you describing a puppy kindergarten?
Hey, don't play along.
She's...
She's a weirdo. Don't talk to her.
Do I look like a weirdo?
In what ways?
Is it weird that I yelled at a sick guy?
Or is it weird that I turned down a great opportunity?
How am I weird?
Guys.
What's wrong with her?
- Hey, wait up. - Guys. Let's just talk.
I won.
Hong Ju.
Lee Hong Ju!
Kang Hoo Young.
Don't come here. Stay there for a second.
You're late.
I'm sorry. I hit traffic.
Did something happen to you?
I'll do whatever I want today no matter what.
Look at them.
- Gosh. - Hey.
You can't ride that together.
- Let's run! - Hey!
Hey!
(Spectator mode)
- Go. - Right.
- What's this? - Game over.
What?
That's understandable.
You have to aim their heads.
- There are so many heads. - Keep shooting at them.
I'm doing that.
- Game over. - My gun is a bit weird.
I stand next to her on purpose
But for some reason, I feel as if I'm not good enough
No, I'm good
You don't have to feel such pressure
I'm not seeing anyone right now anyway
But why can't you say
What was that? That was rude.
I'm sorry. I pressed it before I could stop myself.
I see. I've been hogging the microphone.
Here.
I think you'll be pretty surprised this time.
So you're quite the singer?
On a sunny day
Would you go on a trip with me?
To a very far place
So we don't have to come back
On a sunny day
Would you go on a trip with me?
To a very far place
So we don't have to come back
So no one can find us
Gosh, how can his voice sound so sexy?
So we spent over 100 dollars at the arcade?
This is all because the consumer price index in Korea...
went up 5.3 percent this year.
It's because you were awful at those games.
I was?
You spent several dollars when I only spent 50 cents.
No way.
Being awful at games isn't a big deal. I had so much fun.
Same here.
I was in the mood for some arcade games today too.
- We were in the same boat. - Why?
Did you get stressed out at work?
Something like that.
That's unexpected. I didn't think you'd get stressed out at work.
So I quit my job.
Hey. What did you say? You quit your job?
Lee Hong Ju, my arm.
Hey, don't tell me it's because of me.
Because I told you not to go to the US?
It's not like that.
Then what? Why did you suddenly quit your job?
Lee Hong Ju.
You don't have to worry about this.
I'm Kang Hoo Young.
You win.
Just trust me.
Okay.
From now on, I'm only going to trust you.
(To celebrate the publication of "You from the Island")
("How to Date Right")
("The Law of Dating")
This is all because of Kang Hoo Young.
After getting turned down by him, I must have lost my mind.
(Ms. Kim)
I thought he had a big chest.
You said he had a big heart and was reliable.
What's the point of having a big chest?
A handsome face is what matters for men.
Well, I have to agree on that.
Exactly.
I'm sorry.
You should have stopped me.
I was clearly on the wrong path.
- You seemed happy. - What? As if.
Seriously. It was a close one.
I nearly abandoned...
the lifelong ideals and values I sought in men.
Darn it.
I'm done with dating.
I'm going to focus on my job for the time being. Seriously.
What are you talking about?
You should date. Dating is awesome.
Awesome, my foot.
It's emotionally draining,
and I'll have more things to worry about.
What if I fight with my boyfriend?
Then don't fight with him.
Besides, your job is more emotionally draining.
There are so many things you must handle for your students.
With my job, I'll at least get something out of it.
What will dating leave me?
(Trash, "My Avant-garde Lover")
You'll get love.
Gosh, you've changed.
That's not true.
I simply returned to my old self.
Gosh, whatever. I hate you. I'm hanging up.
(Ms. Kim)
Love, my foot.
Hiking boots aren't just for the mountains.
They are nice. They can protect my ankles.
Are they a bit heavy?
Great. They're perfect.
This is much better.
Darn it.
Why can't I stop thinking about him?
("My Avant-garde Lover")
("How to Date Right")
Hong Ju.
Hey, did you go for a run?
Yes. But I could exercise a bit more.
I might walk a bit more...
that way.
You and I are going in the same direction.
I'll walk with you.
Sounds good.
Mom?
"Mom?"
Hello. I'm Lee Hong Ju.
I'm Baek Do Seon.
I didn't know you were meeting a friend at this hour.
Mom, Hong Ju is...
Hoo Young hasn't come back to Korea for a very long time.
Thank you for showing him around.
Sure.
She's my girlfriend.
Ms. Lee.
I need to talk to my son for a moment.
Could you give us some privacy?
- Mom. - Hoo Young.
I'll see you next time.
Uncle Wook. It's an emergency.
So you met her again.
You know her?
I know everything there is to know about you.
So tell me. Are you in the mood to cause trouble now?
My decision has nothing to do with Hong Ju.
It's my business. And I made the decision.
Okay. If you say so, then it must be true.
Gosh.
What?
How did you... Why...
What are you doing here?
The house looks very different.
I only asked you to manage the property.
You hated the house because it reminded you of your husband.
Hey.
What husband?
It's not like you're going to move back to Korea.
Don't book me a hotel room.
I'll live here while I stay in Korea.
Why?
No!
Leave, Baek Do Seon!
Go back to the US!
Leave!
We made an offer to adapt our animation series,
"The Airport Diary," into an animated movie.
The investor and distribution agency gave us positive feedback.
We'll have a meeting with the CEO sometime next week.
Alter. Kang Hoo Young's mother moved into the house.
Try to avoid her as much as possible. Your safety comes first!
How much progress have you made with "Flower That Blooms at Night?"
- What? - A status update on "FTBN."
Okay.
The director said Yeo Hwa's outfit in the beginning looked too plain.
The designers are revising the outfit.
It's a mourning dress. Of course, it must be plain, not flashy.
You can't accept all of his demands.
He said adding some white embroidery patterns...
on the collars or dress strips might be okay.
The director said you gave him the idea.
Next.
Was that everything?
All right then.
I have to pick a new main producer for "My Avant-garde Lover."
I know that you already have existing projects.
But this project will be a meaningful one...
to your career and our company.
Check your schedules.
If you're interested, come to my office.
If you're not sure you can handle the project,
don't even try to knock on my door.
Hey, you can't be here right now.
- Go home. - No, I won't.
I thought your mother was downstairs.
- Yes, she is. - Then...
Seriously?
We ran into my mom this morning. Did that startle you a lot?
You startled me even more just now.
Is your mother going to stay at the hideout?
Yes.
Should I stay somewhere else for a while, then?
I can stay at Hye Ji's.
Where would you go when I'll be here?
I'll feel uncomfortable.
I think your mother doesn't like me.
She's always like that.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
I wondered who you were like. You're like your mother.
I lack facial expressions and...
Hey. When did I say that?
So...
don't worry too much.
I'm partially responsible.
I'm that fatally charming.
What's this silence?
You're right.
You're fatally charming.
If you admit that so fast,
responsibility will become an issue.
I'm your responsibility.
You got shameless since you quit your job.
Right.
I'm jobless.
You're smiling. Are you pleased to be jobless?
I'm pleased that I have time to spend with you.
I don't like you much today.
You should go.
I don't want to.
I'll stay a bit longer.
No. I'll stay a lot longer.
Okay, then.
- What do you think? - Thank you.
Here you go.
Hey.
The lunch rush is crazy.
- I'll clean this table for you. - Okay.
- Why is it so crowded? - I don't know.
Welcome. A table for three?
- Yes. - Then...
You, move.
Sit over here. Study the menu and order.
- Excuse me. - Yes?
We're still waiting for our food.
It'll be right out. Please wait.
Shall we ask what's good?
Yes, let's.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Is the kimchi jjigae any good?
- Yes. - What else is good here?
Everything's good.
Can we have two kimchi jjigae and spicy stir-fried pork?
Sure.
- Sang Pil. - Yes?
Two kimchi jjigae and spicy stir-fried pork.
- Thanks. - Goodbye.
- Gosh. - That was good.
Goodness.
Here goes.
I'm not used to the weight.
Could you please not do anything?
- We're ready to pay. - Okay.
Don't mind me. It's fine.
Don't say that. It's not fine.
I'm not fine.
Do you know how many bowls you smashed?
Don't worry. I'm good with numbers.
I'll help you pay.
We enjoyed the food.
It was real tasty, and you're cute.
Don't.
- Thank you. - You're good-looking.
Stop it.
- Come by again. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Eat on time.
Ask Sang Pil to cook you something nice.
- Okay. - Hey, can you do the dishes?
(Hong Ju)
Hoo Young?
You just stand still over there.
I'd much prefer that.
Sang Pil.
- Do you need help with anything? - No, stay on your phone.
(Quarterly Sales Report)
You lost three clients this year already.
One of them said...
they wanted to work with their main bank instead.
So what?
Did you say, "I understand. Goodbye?"
No. We tried to persuade them to stay with us, of course.
- Can you excuse us? - Yes.
(Rock Asset)
What are you doing?
What does it look like I'm doing?
Venting at us.
You can't control Hoo Young, so you're taking it out on us.
- That's right. - That's right?
You got sued for doing a crappy job,
so I sent someone over and you made him quit.
Wouldn't I want to vent?
The former was me, but not the latter.
That was...
Lee Hong Ju, I bet.
How do you know?
Do you remember Goblin Tteokbokki that was by our school?
I'm there having lunch.
What's crazy is, the lady here remembers you.
(Goblin Tteokbokki)
Hoo Young? Kang Hoo Young?
The handsome math genius.
I know him well.
He's still just the same. He's so cool.
And... This is a secret.
I'm dating him.
I told her we're dating.
Hong Ju. Lying so blatantly makes you look bad.
It's the truth. Why won't you believe me?
He's not crazy enough to date you.
- He might date me, though. - She didn't believe me.
She said you're not crazy enough to date me.
How could you?
- Let's eat. - Gosh.
You need to come here with me to prove you're crazy.
I'll come to Grilling Meat when I get off work at 6pm.
Let's have meat for dinner.
It's crazy having to deal with so many customers.
Are you loving it? You quit work to date.
Are you happy?
Yes.
What? I'm scared of you now.
People die if they change so suddenly.
I'll come by at lunchtime for a while.
What?
I'm free during the day.
No, thanks. Stay free.
Darn it.
Six o'clock is so far off.
Darn Hoo Young.
He doesn't come to work...
or answer my calls.
Where is he doing and what?
My intestines are all twisted.
Is it my stomach?
It must be both. Darn.
Bae Hye Sook.
Are you leaving?
Did you have dinner?
I don't think we're close enough to ask each other such questions.
Why not?
Neighbors are close enough to ask each other such questions.
- Baek Wook. - Yes?
I won't park here anymore.
So stop drunk-dialing me.
Why should we do this when we're both in our 40s?
It's childish.
You.
What are you doing?
Now that you're in your 40s,
are you losing control?
Your dress got caught in the door.
Why are you so clumsy?
Darn you!
Why would you touch my skirt?
I can't stand you. Get lost!
Hey, Bae Hye Sook.
Hey! You!
Your skirt was lodged in the door.
You could get hurt!
Why would you be so angry about that?
I couldn't handle today's outfit, so I came to get changed.
I'll come and get you.
Why bother when I can come over?
Cook some meat...
so I can eat as soon as I get there.
(To Jun Ho)
- The crazy... - What?
Get some meat on the grill. I'll be right there.
(To Jun Ho)
What are you doing, Mr. Bang?
I'm flying paper planes.
Why would you throw paper planes here...
that are made with these?
What should I do, then?
I don't want to keep these anymore.
It's too dangerous to burn them,
and throwing them in the trash...
would be too upsetting.
Throw them away with the other trash.
That's cold, Hong Ju.
I won't cling to you. Let's break up.
We broke up three years ago.
Yes. We broke up three years ago.
(My dear...)
The guy you're seeing.
Is he a nice guy?
Yes.
Okay.
Good.
But Hong Ju.
I don't think...
I believe in love anymore.
Breaking up.
I thought it was so painful that I'd die.
But I didn't die.
I survived, and now I'm in love again.
Like me, you'll feel better soon.
This is no fun.
This is your heart.
You throw it away.
Good for you, Bang Jun Ho.
You did good.
The planes.
He threw so many.
I wrote so many letters.
Hello.
I guess some kids threw paper planes.
I thought you were just cute.
(My dear...)
You must have a complicated love life.
Darn it.
Why are you both letting the meat burn?
I'm not in the mood to cook.
What's up with you?
Are you waiting for Hong Ju?
What a devoted boyfriend.
Hye Ji.
Did Hong Ju tell you anything?
Like what?
(Hong Ju)
(I'll be there soon. Start without me.)
I'll be there soon. Start without me.
Is that company crazy?
Why else...
would they ask Oddball to work with Bang Jun Ho?
And don't you say anything around Hoo Young.
Oddball won't do it. I know her.
You don't know anything.
Hong Ju had the face of someone dying to do it.
Hoo Young quit his job...
and spent the whole day here.
How could Hong Ju even consider that job?
Did she look like she wanted to do it or was she going to...
Why are you changing...
This is on you, Sang Pil.
What did I do?
I'll get Hong Ju.
What...
(Grilling Meat Again Today)
Hoo Young...
is best off not knowing about any of this, right?
I don't know what you saw but...
You don't have to explain.
I don't want my Hoo Young to get...
dragged into something that pathetic.
Ms. Lee.
I get that we're connected in an interesting way,
but don't waste pointless time.
My Hoo Young will take over Rock Asset's head office.
He could become much greater if he wants to.
Do you get what I'm saying?
No.
I came here to get him.
This isn't the place for him.
Isn't that...
for Hoo Young to decide?
My decision is his decision.
- Hoo Young... - Hoo Young...
became a softie since he returned to this place.
He was never like that.
I'd like you...
to let him go.
I'm not keeping him here.
Then...
is my Hoo Young the clingy one?
- He's clinging to you? - Yes.
He was a total flirt.
I was in a car accident recently.
I told him not to, but he insisted on looking after me.
He said he was pleased I broke up...
and kissed me first.
He took me to the seaside.
I kept telling him no,
but he kept saying he wanted to, so...
So...
you gave in?
The cool and handsome Hoo Young was flirting with me.
How could I not give in?
You're right.
You must've had no choice but to fall for him.
But do you think...
you were the only one?
I'm worried that Hoo Young changes partners so frequently.
He made so many young girls cry.
But...
men fall in and out of love easily.
It might sound crass,
but I don't think my son's any different.
Before you get hurt,
I'd like you to end it.
If you're done, I'd like to go.
Did you...
stop to think what Hoo Young could lose because of you?
If the smart guy did the math and made up his mind,
doesn't that mean he thinks I'm worth more than all that?
(I'll love only Jun Ho forever.)
What are you doing here?
Why are you out in the cold?
I was thinking.
Is something wrong?
Sandra and Sarah.
Amanda. Selena.
Were any of your exes called that?
What?
You had lots of girlfriends in the US.
What on earth...
Did you meet my mom?
Yes. And she told me...
she was concerned that you made many girls cry.
Hong Ju, that's...
Why should I hear about that from her?
Don't take what she says seriously.
Shouldn't I?
Then...
shouldn't I take it seriously that she said she came for you?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you about Mom.
But I told you I won't go back.
What if you leave anyway?
Do I have to be left clueless...
and find out after the fact?
Instead of getting upset because of what my mom said,
shouldn't you trust me?
How can I trust you in this situation?
You didn't tell me about Bang Jun Ho because you didn't trust me?
Why would you mention him?
You don't have to worry about that.
How can I not worry about that?
I saw how much you cried because of him.
I know what you did,
so how could I...
How could I not care?
I ended it.
I'm over him.
You don't trust me either.
- Hong Ju. - Leave it.
You're the same.
- You always... - Not another word.
You always just up and leave.
I'd forgotten that.
Hong Ju.
Haven't you left for work yet?
Is this what you call...
"going astray?"
I couldn't sleep well.
I'll be lying down just a little more.
That's good!
- Let's go! - You can do it!
- Hey! - Hey!
Don't rush it.
Oh, no.
No one can do it. Oh, no.
(Obok High School)
I'm hungry.
Hurry up. That was so hard.
Where should we go?
What is it?
Did you come here to visit someone?
No.
I came to confess.
I'm not leaving until I express my feelings for him.
My heart is overflowing.
I feel suffocated because it keeps overflowing.
It might kill me if I don't tell him.
We should meet again when Jun Ho is discharged from the military.
I'll make sure to show you our love then.
I completely forgot about it.
How can you forget that?
Is that day a bad memory for you?
How come it is related to Bang Jun Ho?
It's a memory related to me.
How can I not worry about that?
I saw how much you cried because of him.
I know what you did,
so how could I...
How could I not care?
Oddball.
Hye Ji, what do I do?
Why?
What on earth did I do in front of Hoo Young?
Gosh, I completely forgot about it.
Did you have a big argument yesterday?
What is that? Did you argue or not?
- I don't know. - It's okay.
A relationship consists of half love and half argument. Forget about it.
What should we eat? Let's go.
- I don't have... - Don't say you don't have appetite.
I even requested a permission to go out, which is rare.
Let's eat something delicious.
What do you want to have?
Gosh.
Hong Ju went on and on about the hideout.
And it really is a hideout.
I didn't know Mr. Baek was design-savvy and rich like this.
Gosh, I've been too rude to him.
I didn't contact you after I left yesterday. I'm sorry.
What?
I knew you wouldn't come back.
I knew you would have a drink.
But you drank too much.
I should've bought some fruits at least.
How about your restaurant?
I thought a lot after coming back from the beach trip.
"Why did I want to open a restaurant?"
"Was my goal success or happiness?"
I work without any days off.
I wondered if I was successful or happy.
Selena is Selena Gomez.
Is Sandra Bullock or Oh?
How did you even come up with that?
You're laughing too much.
You did well.
I ate a leg.
For today, you eat mine too.
You look worn out from everything you've been through.
Hoo Young must be even more upset.
Why? What did you say?
I said he would leave too.
Just like Jun Ho.
Are you out of your mind, Oddball?
His mother came to take him to the US. What do I do then?
He said he was not going to leave.
It's going to be fine then. What's the problem?
He did,
but I think...
he knows I was going to work with Jun Ho again.
Oh, right.
Oddball, it upsets me even more.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why do you do it all by yourself?
I've been telling you how upsetting it is since before.
It's because I don't want you to worry.
After I solve the issue...
That's what I'm saying. You can take care of everything by yourself.
You're good at everything. So I don't have to worry, right?
You take care of it by yourself.
This is for you. I'm fine.
Eat.
So your attitude is all wrong.
You should've pretended you didn't know.
Just like Hong Ju is the only one in your life.
In the present, in the past, and in the future.
- She's the only one. - The only one?
No, that's not good.
The more loved ones you have, the better it is.
They say the more, the better. Don't you know it?
Let me show you something funny.
Before I show it to you,
you should never tell...
Hong Ju and Hye Ji that I showed you this.
It will end my life.
Gosh.
This is when I was on my final leave from the military.
Look at them.
Hye Ji was a mess, preparing for the teacher certification exam.
As for Hong Ju...
She had a heavy workload at work.
Because of them, I almost decided to become a professional soldier.
What's this?
Oh, this is the picture of Hong Ju's name.
It was her company's first animated movie.
She said her name was in the credit.
But it was so small and fast that I couldn't find it.
We had to watch the movie three times...
to take a picture of her name.
("The Airport Diary")
It was a day before the winter vacation ceremony.
Hong Ju had indigestion after eating tteokbokki.
Hye Ji and I were so shocked that day.
She was whining so much, saying she didn't want to see a doctor.
My goodness.
Hong Ju said this when she was drunk one day.
She's had the same nightmare since she was little.
She sees different places and people,
but she always chases them.
She thought about what kind of nightmare it was while chasing them.
They said they would come back...
and see her later.
But they left without saying goodbye,
so she didn't know it was the last moment, which scared her.
Hey, Hoo Young.
Wait right there. I'll be there soon.
Wait.
When are you going back to the US?
Come to think of it,
it's not like you've ever told me before leaving.
Must I be kept in the dark again...
and find out only after you leave?
You always just up and leave.
I'd forgotten that.
I asked...
what she wanted to do when she caught them.
She said she wanted to say goodbye.
Then she wouldn't have to keep waiting.
My bus has come. Bye.
Then goodbye, Hoo Young. It was nice seeing you.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Everyone...
has a painful spot.
Do it again.
Hey. Block it.
Hey.
Okay.
Be careful.
Pass the ball.
Go.
- Hey! - Hey!
Defend.
- Go! - Go!
Ms. Kim, dodge it!
Mr. Son?
It's a relief.
Mr. Son.
Mr. Son, are you all right?
Mr. Son. Oh, my gosh.
- Are you okay? - Get him up.
- Should we call the ambulance? - Try getting him up.
Mr. Son, are you okay?
Are you all right?
(Make a bed after waking up!)
It hurts.
Mr. Son.
I know you aren't sleeping.
Look at me. I want to see if your nose is okay.
I'm fine. This is...
nothing.
You don't look fine.
What's this? Your cute face has been all wounded.
Mr. Son.
Are you still going to say you don't like me?
From the beginning,
you were the only one for me.
I love you.
I mean... I love you.
I love you!
You don't have to say it many times.
I love you too.
(Teachers Only)
My gosh.
Oh, my.
Hello, ma'am.
Goodbye.
- Who are you? - Sorry?
Me?
I'm Hoo Young's best friend,
Kwon Sang Pil.
I was in the same class with him for three years in high school.
I'm his best friend.
I see.
By the way, where is Hoo Young?
Sorry?
He was here just now.
But he's not anymore.
I don't know then.
I'll get going.
What are you doing here?
The one who is living here.
I made her cry.
Let's go down. You'll catch a cold.
Mom.
Have you ever regretted leaving Korea?
No.
Have you ever missed the country?
Not even once.
You know what?
When I was tired and weary,
it came to my mind.
I don't have a lot of memories,
so it's always the same few moments.
But after thinking about those moments,
everything...
became better.
I didn't know the reason back then,
but now that I'm back,
I realized it.
I...
was missing this place.
I was missing her.
I miss her.
You go inside first.
See you tomorrow.
(Peter's Pen)
Are you okay?
Why did you run like that? I was going to go to you.
Hoo Young.
(Serendipity's Embrace)
(Goblin Tteokbokki)
So you're not really going to Europe with me?
I found a company I want to work for.
It's a winter vacation soon.
Why do you want to find a job so soon?
I want to work for them so much.
They don't receive resumes.
They review project proposals instead.
I like the name too. "Peter's Pen."
My dad said he would pay for the trip for both of us.
I want to go with you.
Here.
Send me a lot of pictures. Okay?
- Hello. - Hi.
Why is it so cold?
You ordered a lot. This is awesome.
Why do you keep calling him?
I didn't. I thought you called him.
Why is that important?
What's important is that we have similar tastes.
It would've been even better with Hoo Young.
Why are you looking for someone who emigrated?
But it does make me sad.
I wish he had graduated with us.
Do you think you're as upset as me?
I'm more upset.
He didn't even say goodbye before he left.
"See you tomorrow." Then he fled to the US.
- He did? - Yes.
He doesn't even pick up his phone.
What's the matter, Oddball? Why are you crying? What happened?
I'm not crying.
Am I crying?
It happened many times when I was younger.
Did you make her cry?
How can I make her cry?
I came just now. I didn't even eat a lot of food.
I feel a pain here.
I didn't know the name of the emotion I had.
I didn't know the reason either.
Do you feel a pain here?
Is it indigestion?
You shouldn't have eaten so much.
Come on!
Do you want me to get you medicines?
Or do you want to go to a hospital?
I don't like hospitals.
I don't...
want to go.
Who made Hong Ju cry?
Don't cry.
I thought I didn't know because I was young.
But I still have moments like that even when I'm grown up.
(Goblin Tteokbokki)
(Special thanks to Kim Jung Nan for the cameo appearance)
Do you want to eat ramyeon?
I said we would just have ramyeon.
What are you thinking?
- Hey. - Why? Do you have a headache?
Ever since he came back, every day felt like some vacation.
Good morning.
What are we?
We both love Hoo Young.
- Hoo Young? - From now on,
I'm going to file a lawsuit against you.
I know it's not an easy decision to make,
but I don't think I can live without you.
Let's go to the US together.