(Kim So Hyun)
(Lee Hong Ju and Kang Hoo Young)
(Chae Jong Hyeop)
(Yun Ji On)
(Kim Da Som)
(Serendipity's Embrace)
I'm okay.
I wasn't hit by a car. I tripped as I was dodging.
Why did they call you?
Anyway, you must be busy. I'm sorry. I'll take it from here.
Hong Ju.
I'm really fine. You can go.
Stop telling me to go. I'm not going anywhere.
Hey. There's no need to get worked up.
I didn't want to bother you for nothing.
"Nothing?"
Do you still think it's nothing?
Excuse me.
I'm the one who should listen to people's heartbeat here.
Oh, yes.
Doctor.
Please listen after he leaves.
I was very shocked because of the accident.
(Obok Hospital)
Why did he do that all of a sudden?
He was speaking rudely yesterday.
Was it because he was sorry?
No way.
Hong Ju, that's a foolish delusion.
You're Hye Ji's friend. I'm warning you for being like this.
My gosh.
(Caution, MRI Scan Room)
Ma'am, don't move your head.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Mr. Kim.
Yes, Ms. Kim.
Please give a closing message to my class.
Why? What's the matter?
Hong Ju got into a car accident. She's in a hospital.
What? Was she hurt badly?
Where is the hospital? I'll get going.
You said you had plans this evening, Dad.
Hong Ju woke up and is getting a check-up now.
How did she get into an accident?
The aftereffects of a car accident are so terrifying.
- Mr. Son. - Yes.
- Did you bring your car? - Yes, I did.
Then please go to a hospital with Ms. Kim.
One of our graduates got into an accident...
- and was sent to a hospital. - Oh, my.
No, Mr. Son. I can go by myself.
Hey, what's important about a car accident...
is that you should take care of the aftermath properly.
If it's just two girls, they might look down on you and ignore you.
Mr. Kim.
We're not girls. We're grown women.
Please go to my class and wrap up the day for my students.
You don't need to worry, Mr. Son.
What?
It's not like they've handled the aftermath of a car accident before.
Let me drive you there.
Oh, yes.
I called you just a while ago.
The security room?
Yes. Thank you. Okay.
Why did he abandon the suitcase...
and come to a hospital all of a sudden?
Ms. Kim!
Oh, gosh. I'm saved.
You saved my life again, Mr...
Where did he go?
Change into sneakers.
They won't be too big if I tie the shoelaces.
I washed them. They're clean.
They're big,
but thank you.
I'll call you after parking the car.
Okay. Call me.
Mr. Baek.
Ms. Kim.
Please stay in the waiting room until I call her name.
Okay. Thank you.
(Obok Hospital)
Anyway, thank you, Hoo Young.
You must be sorry for what you said yesterday.
I accept your apology.
You can take care of your friend in the hospital now.
Why would you come up with the reason for me?
Will you keep... Oh, gosh.
Look to the front.
Make sure to tell the doctor that your neck hurts.
Is she all right? Where is she?
He said there were no major issues, and they're coming to the lobby.
She should just be hospitalized.
I know.
But you know she hates hospitals.
My goodness.
Mr. Baek.
You knew it, didn't you?
I know she hates it when they call for a guardian in a hospital.
But she has guardians, including me and you.
Not that.
What, then?
Hoo Young likes her.
Honestly, I didn't know he liked her this much.
I think he's never been so reckless...
in his life. My gosh.
He's so reckless.
Mr. Baek.
Would you like to be on the same side as me?
Is Hye Ji here?
- I said we were coming down. - I see.
Did you have fun with Hye Ji yesterday?
There are so many guys who like her.
It's an honour for you.
Hong Ju.
Hye Ji and I...
I should keep pretending to know nothing about this too, right?
This is crazy.
Why?
No. It's nothing.
Hoo Young. Let's talk for a moment.
I have a favour to ask.
Please don't take it too personally.
Do you want me to leave again?
Stop flirting with me.
Stop doing what?
It might be because you lived in the US. It became your habit.
But people might misunderstand your behaviour.
Of course, I'm not saying I misunderstood you.
It's just that I'm quite conservative...
and it makes me very uncomfortable.
Hey.
So please be careful.
Hye Ji.
Oddball.
"Flirting?"
You look like a mess.
It's not a minor accident.
You're even wearing a cast.
Hye Ji, why did you come only now?
I'm sorry.
The car ran into me.
A car as big as this ran into me at full speed.
I avoided it like this, but I had serious leg cramps.
Look at my forehead too.
It hurt so much. Look.
Which jerk scratched my best friend's forehead?
Who drives like that?
It was so scary.
Oh, my. It must've been so painful.
Gosh.
Hoo Young!
It's Uncle Wook.
Uncle.
Why did you abandon your suitcase?
It's okay. Wash it with hydrogen peroxide.
- It will become clean. - I was busy flirting.
This is driving me crazy.
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
It hurts.
Where is that jerk? Did they run?
Gosh.
By the way, why did you call Hoo Young?
I had no choice. I couldn't go right away because of class.
You could've called Sang Pil.
I don't know. Hoo Young just popped into my mind at that moment.
My goodness.
Anyway, I'm done being your Cupid.
You guys meet on your own from now on.
Well...
The thing is...
Kyung Taek.
What's going on?
I wasn't going to tell you like this.
But I'm...
dating him.
What?
I mean...
What about Hoo Young?
Why do you ask?
He's my first love. That's all.
Kyung Taek likes me very much.
Right?
Yes, I do.
I've been liking her very much for a long time.
I went on a blind date to hide it.
I'm so sorry, Hong Ju.
I'm sorry for what he did.
No.
You don't have to apologize to me.
I told Hoo Young yesterday. He knows.
I was also going to tell you yesterday,
but you just left.
- I want you to congratulate me. - Congratulate you on what?
Let's talk on our way.
Isn't it more convenient for you to get in his car?
No.
Hoo Young, you said you were going home, right?
Yes. Why?
Please let my Oddball stay in your place then.
She can't get up and down the rooftop...
with her legs in this state.
Your place has many rooms.
- Hye Ji. - It's a good idea.
I was worried about leaving you alone. It's a good idea.
Go to his place and take a rest.
Why are you guys acting like this? I can take care of myself.
Uncle Wook, let me go home quickly.
I'm tired just standing like this.
Okay. Let's go. Get in the car quickly.
Mr. Baek.
Didn't you say you should go back to your office?
We're going to school. We can drive you to your office.
It would be inconvenient to stop by his place.
Why would it be inconvenient? It's right over...
I have something urgent at work, so I think I should head back first.
Hoo Young, take care of Oddball.
Oddball, you take care of your body.
I'll buy you meat later.
We'll get going. Let's go.
- What? - Let's go.
Uncle Wook.
Oddball, this is an important moment. Good luck.
I mean...
Bye.
- Hey. - Travel safely.
Hey, take good care of your body. All right?
What's up with everyone?
Let's go home.
I'm so uncomfortable with him.
- Gosh. - Let's go.
It seems like an important call. Why don't you pick it up?
The vibration is so loud that I woke up.
Yes, Ms. Bae. How was the meeting?
Do you like her that much?
Congratulations.
Sorry?
Yes, I like her very much.
Mr. Son, you can stop now.
We're not dating at all.
I'm sorry. You were perplexed, right?
No, I wasn't.
I tried my best.
But I don't think she would believe that I'm your boyfriend.
Well, I believed it.
What you believe doesn't matter.
I mean...
What's this?
You said you wanted to help Hoo Young and Oddball date.
Why did you lie that you guys were dating?
Ms. Kim lied so that your nephew doesn't misunderstand...
that something is going on between Hong Ju and me.
I went on a blind date with her.
Hong Ju and who?
Me.
You...
Wait.
So he's the one?
Yes.
You totally got me.
I really thought you liked Ms. Kim.
You're a good actor.
- You're a good actor. My gosh. - I got it, Uncle Wook.
I sent the version revised by the design team...
to the director.
No. Of course, I'll take care of it until the end.
The new project is just starting its planning stages, so it's fine.
Since I can't go today, I'll go next week.
Yes.
I can still check it,
so please send me the edited version.
Okay.
(Watch "My Home, My Mother.")
(Mother)
(Decline)
Pick it up if you need to.
I'm done with my call now.
It's not urgent.
I was supposed to attend a meeting,
but everyone was concerned because they couldn't reach me.
Do you not play hooky anymore?
How can I play hooky when it's my job?
You used to play hooky a lot.
You played hooky and stayed up all night with me.
When did we do that?
You're making things up.
Don't you remember?
The day we went to Cheorwon.
I'm not sleeping with you.
I never said that.
Of course, we'll sleep in separate rooms.
(November 14, 2013, 9:10pm)
(Reed field in Gangpo-ri, Cheorwon)
Let's go to the main street to hail a cab.
We can take a cab to go to the bus terminal.
So you do know how to think with your brain.
I wonder how well your brain works for you to be here right now.
Today, I wanted to show you what true love is.
But the timing was bad.
We should meet again when Jun Ho is discharged from the military.
I'll make sure to show you our love then.
Hoo Young?
Hey.
Where are you?
This is not funny. Come out.
Hong Ju.
Hoo Young.
Hey, why are you in there?
(Caution: Fall Hazard)
It's too muddy.
I don't think I can go up on my own.
Do you see a strap or a stick around you?
Hey, look at you.
Are you dumb?
Will you keep laughing?
I'll try to find something useful.
Darn it.
I will never...
get into anything with you again.
(Caution: Fall Hazard)
Hong Ju?
Hong Ju.
Hong Ju!
What?
Hurry up and find something.
I'm searching.
- Hong Ju. - What now?
Don't leave me behind.
I've been trying not to do it since earlier.
My gosh.
(Caution: Fall Hazard)
(30 minutes later)
Hong Ju.
Are you dumb?
Did you...
Did you think you could pull someone up with this?
They say a drowning man will grasp at straws.
That means they'll do anything including something pointless.
Does it?
"Does it?"
What are you doing down here anyway?
You even left your bag and phone up there.
Only someone stupid would think of jumping in.
Yes, I'm stupid.
I'm so stupid...
I couldn't think of what to do, okay?
I called, and you didn't answer,
and I thought you were drowning or something.
- Pull. - Climb higher.
Keep pulling.
Hey.
(Safety First)
Kang Hoo Young.
Are you okay?
Hey!
Oh, no.
Kang Hoo Young.
Kang Hoo Young!
You should've called for help first.
I know that.
I know I'm stupid, and I don't think.
I didn't say you didn't think.
Hey, is your head okay?
Yes, it's okay.
What about you? Were you hurt?
No.
We don't have to worry.
The ground is firm. It's not a swamp.
What if it were a swamp?
Why worry what if it were when it's not?
Aren't you scared of being in a place like this?
Why would I be when you're here too?
It was worse trying to look for something to save you with.
A frog screamed right into my year.
Ribbit, ribbit.
Why would you be scared of a frog?
What a chicken.
You must remember.
We climbed out after sunrise...
when the soldiers found us.
You trembled in fear all night.
I did not.
I just remembered everything.
You meant to go somewhere else that day.
Where was it?
- Seoul National University. - Yes, there.
Why were you going to go there?
- For an interview. - Right, an interview.
An interview? What interview?
An interview on since when, why, and how...
I got so good at math.
I see.
So that happened.
I'd forgotten completely.
How could you forget that?
I forget bad memories easily.
Was that day a bad memory to you?
Everything related to Bang Jun Ho is bad.
How is that related to Bang Jun Ho?
That memory was about us.
Don't.
I can manage.
Is that flirting too?
I know you mean to help, but I'm fine.
I should be able to manage on my own.
I can't rely on your help.
It's okay to let me help when I'm around.
I guess so?
Thanks, anyway.
I'll make it up to you with a fried chicken voucher.
You're going to climb the stairs like that?
You bet.
- Do you want a piggyback? - Forget it.
Should I carry you instead?
Shut your mouth before I...
Nice catch.
Oh, dear.
Thanks for sparing me.
I'll spend my second life to eat more...
and play more.
Shouldn't you be thanking me?
Three fried chicken vouchers.
Who says fried chicken will cut it?
Give me the prescription. I'll get your medicine.
Leave it. I'll get it myself tomorrow.
The prescription.
What do you want for dinner?
No, I'm fine.
I'll leave after a short break.
Don't you dare say "I'm fine" again.
Rest up while I get some groceries.
What's up with him?
Oh, I don't know. I'm starving.
I'm so hungry I feel nauseous.
Goodness.
What a lovely sight.
You're looking after each other until the end.
How about a toast?
Good job today.
(Grilling Meat Again Today)
What a weird combination this is.
Kim Hye Ji,
Hong Ju's landlord minus Hong Ju...
Who's he?
He's...
Oddball's blind date...
and Ms. Kim's boyfriend for the day.
Well...
Oh, you're into weird chicks, bro.
I'll move my clothes.
He's not your bro. He's a teacher.
A teacher?
I'm Son Kyung Taek. I teach PE at Obok High School.
Oh, I see. Nice to meet you.
May I pour you a shot of soju?
Yes, sure.
He deserves a new introduction.
I know the landlord. Why?
He's Kang Hoo Young's uncle.
What?
No way. They don't look alike at all.
Mr. Kwon.
That hurts.
We do look alike. Look carefully.
Hey.
- You do look alike. - Right?
- With Hoo Young's mom. - Darn you.
I'm his mom's brother,
- so that would be true. - How strange.
- But Hoo Young and I... - No.
- have the same nose and mouth. - We all live in Obok-dong.
Then Kang Hoo Young's staying at...
The house right below Oddball.
What? Are they shooting a melodrama?
They parted suddenly in high school...
only for a fateful reunion...
Sit.
You knew.
Then you should've told me Hoo Young liked Oddball.
Hey.
How could I tell you something...
Hoo Young hadn't told anyone himself?
I did what was right and loyal.
You were too slow to pick up on it.
Even a passing dog would notice now.
Hey, give me your glass.
Forget your first love.
You and Hoo Young were never meant to be.
Hey.
Wait.
Ms. Kim's first love is Hoo Young?
- Yes. - For real?
Yes.
Why don't you act loyal or do right by me?
Mr. Son, is the meat...
to your liking?
Yes. It's delicious.
That's good to hear.
Back in high school.
Hoo Young was my first love,
and he told me my best friend is his first love.
But so what?
This was never a secret,
and I got over it just fine.
I even pretended to be dating Mr. Son.
The rest is up to them.
- Right? - Yes.
It's okay. It's fine.
Darn you.
Why did you go and do that?
What?
Oh, that?
Because Hong Ju graduated from Obok High too.
That school serves their students for so many years.
I wonder if Hoo Young is taking good care of Oddball.
You're back.
What's for dinner?
You.
You're crazy, Hong Ju.
Get out of me, you evil spirit.
Is sexual frustration this scary?
I should go home.
I have chills.
Would it be easier to crawl?
Okay.
You really don't listen.
Are you Kang Hoo Young?
What do you mean?
Evil spirit or Hoo Young, whatever you are,
don't mind me and go on your way.
What's going on?
What are you doing? Put me down.
Move and we'll both fall.
Wait here for a bit.
(Porridge)
I found a porridge place, so I got you some.
You had a bad scare, so get some rest.
And take your medicine.
See you in the morning.
Hoo Young.
Thanks.
Sure.
You're such a good guy.
I guess my memories of you were twisted.
But then,
we never were that close in school.
I'd have forgotten you if it hadn't been for Hye Ji.
You too, right?
To be honest, we're Friend Three to each other, aren't we?
Call me when you're up. See you.
Was he offended?
No. That's his fault.
Why would he get flirty?
What are you doing? Put me down.
- Move and we'll both fall. - See?
He crossed the line first.
Get lost.
Leave, evil spirit!
(Medicine)
We never were that close in school.
I'd have forgotten you if it hadn't been for Hye Ji.
To be honest, we're Friend Three to each other, aren't we?
How many times can she dump me before I even tell her?
Hey. Aren't you supposed to be on the plane right now?
Why are you still in Korea?
When will you be back?
I'll be there.
Get over here now.
I'm not asking for a favour. I'm demanding as a client.
(Peter's Pen)
No.
I won't be there.
(Producer Lee Hong Ju)
(Animation Company Producer)
What do you want?
Well, you know...
I was wondering if that was my seat.
I thought you were going to say you'd fallen for me at first sight,
or if I were free after school,
or something like that. It's a shame you didn't.
What?
Can you stop that?
Be considerate of others.
(4 years ago, Young Writer Award interview, 2019)
- Put the chair over here. - Okay.
I'd like this to be the backdrop for the interview.
Mr. Bang can sit here, and I'll sit here.
Sounds good.
I'm glad I'm not late.
You didn't have to come.
You said you worked all night.
I said I'd be your stylist for the day.
You look pretty good.
I'll be watching from the back.
Relax and speak freely.
Lee Hong Ju.
Are you here to watch in case my tongue slips?
No.
It's Mr. Bang the writer's first interview after winning.
I have to be here.
Plus, if you have someone...
in your corner, it's extra reassuring.
Yes.
Mr. Bang is ready.
Hey.
Mr. Bang. Will you sit down?
Okay.
Do your best. Good luck.
Thanks.
What did you do first after learning...
you'd won the award?
What did I do first?
I called an acquaintance who always reads my works first.
I see.
Who is that acquaintance?
Oh, dear.
My trusted number one fan who loved everything...
I ever wrote.
My rough and ragged stories that just entered the world...
slowly became refined with each expression...
that person made.
That person helped me a lot this time as well.
When I called and said I'd won the Young Writer Award,
they burst into tears.
I was the one who wanted to cry.
I couldn't because I had to console them.
Gosh.
- Thanks so much for today. - Not at all.
- Thank you. - Good job.
Please write favourably about me.
- Okay. - Sure.
She said she'd watch.
Lee Hong...
Ju.
Mr. Bang.
Well...
I know this could come across as rude but...
Are you seeing someone?
Yes.
I think I am now.
(Production producers)
(Kim Young Ji, Lee Hong Ju)
(Lee Hong Ju)
What about Hong Ju? Did you see her?
That's what you ask first when I just negotiated a deal?
She didn't answer her phone all day today.
Does she really not want to work with me?
If you'd told her the truth back then,
she wouldn't have cried,
and you'd be fine and all would be well.
Tell her what?
That I had panic attacks and couldn't write a word?
That countless breaches of contracts had left me penniless?
She thinks I'm the best writer in the world.
How could I tell her the truth?
Don't people who truly love each other...
stay together when one of them hits rock bottom?
I didn't want to drag her down just to stay with me.
Of course, not.
Hong Ju will work on your project as the producer.
See? I told you she would do it.
She joined the animation company for me.
She said she wanted to make my story into an anime.
(Production producer: Lee Chun Ho, Kim Young Ji, Lee Hong Ju)
I'll change everything back to where it was.
(Producer Lee Hong Ju)
So to you, I'm just Friend Three who went to the same school?
(November of 2013, reed field in Gangpo-ri, Cheorwon)
(4:30am)
How about Truth or Dare?
This isn't the time to play games.
I'm so sleepy. That's why.
Let's tell each other a shocking secret,
so it chases away sleep.
If the secret is lame, you get a finger flick.
Who will judge if it's lame or not?
Well,
if it doesn't chase away sleep, it's a lame secret.
Let's do it. You go first.
Me first?
My dear Jun Ho is so handsome.
Gosh. Why did you hit me?
I'm sleepy.
I see. That's how you'll play?
It's your turn now.
Let's see what kind of shocking secret you have.
Come to think of it,
wouldn't it be weirder...
to have some shocking secret at our age?
You're not getting away with it. Spill.
I got one math question wrong on the midterm exam.
You really are a genius.
I got one question wrong.
I was once ranked last in the whole school.
That time, I went with number two...
for all of my answers on the English exam.
But none of the answers was number two. I'm not lying.
I went to the English teacher to complain...
how it could be possible.
There were 40 questions and had 5 multiple choices.
Shouldn't each choice be correct at least for eight questions?
Are you surprised? Are you shocked?
Yes.
I'm also shocked by that ridiculous reasoning of yours.
Right? Yes!
It's your turn now.
Just hit me.
I don't have a secret that's more shocking than that.
Spill.
I don't have one.
Well,
I have...
never told anyone about this.
I wanted to be an animation director.
Really?
Did that chase away sleep?
You just made that up, didn't you?
But you don't look like the anime type.
I'm serious.
Really?
I love anime too!
You watched the shows too, right?
When we were kids,
there were cartoon TV shows throughout the day.
I watched every single one!
I learned about the world through cartoons.
You'll need to learn more through another method.
How come it's in the past tense?
You don't want to be one now?
Dreams don't always come true.
Right.
Well, it's the same as the Santa not existing.
Santa doesn't exist, but people say he does.
Dreams don't come true, but people say they do.
Did the anime teach you that too?
Hoo Young. Let me take your dream job.
- What? - I'll be an animation director.
My homeroom teacher keeps asking me what I want to be...
and bugging me to write a plan for my future career.
But I don't have one.
I just solved my problem.
It's difficult to become an animation director.
Nothing is easy in life. You just go for it.
What? You don't want me to take it?
It's not that.
Okay. I recognize your input.
Then I will give you...
five percent of my salary.
- Really? - Yes.
(Ms. Kim)
(Should I say it's a morning full of love?)
Should I say it's a morning full of love?
Yes, thanks to you.
Did you sleep well?
How could she when there's a guy in the house?
What nonsense is that?
If there was a guy, I would've known about him.
Gosh, be quiet.
Don't ruin it. You stay out of it.
What about work, Oddball?
I'm taking the week off. I'm not feeling well.
I only had porridge yesterday. I'm starving.
(Ms. Kim invited Kang Hoo Young.)
Darn it. Why did she invite Kang Hoo Young?
Come down. Let's have breakfast.
Why would I do that?
Then should I come upstairs?
- I can... - Sit down.
You walking around like that inconveniences me more.
Is that so? Okay. I'm a guest, after all.
How's the food?
It's not too salty. It's good.
Hong Ju doesn't like salty food.
Make sure to serve her meat as one of the side dishes.
You'll have desserts after the meal, right?
Gosh. That would be too much. I'm good.
If you want to have tiramisu, I have to take it out now.
Here's my tip.
Oddball is crazy about tiramisu.
If you have it, you can take it out.
Okay.
Thanks for the food.
You made time to look after your school friend.
You're a good person.
Is that so? I'm glad to hear that.
- I'll get going then. - Wait.
We have unfinished business to settle.
I don't have anything else to say.
Five percent.
Five percent?
Five percent of your salary.
For my input. Don't you remember?
What input did you have for my salary? That's absurd.
Okay. I recognize your input.
Then I will give you...
five percent of my salary.
What are you talking about?
Five percent?
It's the promise you made...
to this Friend Three from the same school.
You said you remembered everything that happened that day.
Hey, but that's...
I wonder how much money I would be entitled to...
if you've been working for ten years.
Gosh. You worked hard, Hong Ju.
Here. Enjoy it.
I'll run the numbers for us. You remember, right?
That I'm good at math.
It won't be easy to win Hong Ju over.
That's not because you're my first love.
You don't have the right to know what kind of relationship...
she had before meeting you.
But some jerk went abroad without telling her.
So Hong Ju had the worst breakup ever.
She was utterly appalled by any kind of romantic relationship.
I barely managed to get her to go on a blind date.
But then she met you.
Is that so?
I don't know what happened between you guys in the past.
I want Hong Ju to be happy.
But as of yesterday, you passed.
That's reassuring.
Did you tell her how you feel?
She told me that I was just...
Friend Three from the same school.
Friend Three?
But she doesn't know anyone from school.
So what will you do?
I should be her close friend first.
Well, I only said that...
because I fell into the pit because of you.
I wasn't thinking straight then.
That's not legally binding.
I don't remember us losing our minds when we talked.
Gosh, we were.
We fell into the pit and had nowhere to go.
Of course, I was losing it.
Well, I wasn't.
But I was.
People just blab about stuff they don't mean before dying.
Besides, let's keep things clear.
I said I would do that if I were to become a director.
But I'm not a director.
I'm just a lowly employee at an animation production company.
So that promise is invalid. Got that?
You're laughing?
Gosh. I had no idea you would be this serious...
about giving me excuses.
Hong Ju. You are...
What?
Hey. Kang Hoo Young. You...
I was serious about this because you asked.
I thought you wanted to take my salary as your asset.
You're such a heartless guy.
You're nothing but a little kid!
You're more than capable of doing that!
If you add up ten years' worth of your salary,
will it be somewhere around ten million dollars?
I don't work with any asset that's lower than that.
Taking 5 percent of that would give me a mere 500,000 dollars.
I see.
You must be so successful then.
How's work? Is it fun?
Oh, stop it.
Besides, how can work be fun?
Watching anime is only fun.
You have no idea how much work there is.
When I started my job, I was the receipt girl.
I don't get paid a lot, but I still worked hard for it.
How could you mock me by talking about taking a cut?
I was just happy about your job.
I had no idea you would be making anime.
I told you that was my plan.
I doubt I could be a director.
But I'll join a project as a main producer this time.
Impressive.
You transcend my expectations every time.
Well, I tend to do that.
If you have time, do you want to watch the movies we worked on?
You can see my name on the end credits.
Let's watch it now.
Let me finish this first.
Eat a lot.
("Cloud Bread 3")
Hello.
Excuse me.
Where's Ms. Lee Hong Ju?
Ms. Lee?
Gosh, this is exhausting.
Hey, I'll go and bring my laptop.
- You want me to carry you again? - No.
It's better to climb up without the crutches.
I'll jump on one leg.
Keep your distance.
Gosh.
Lee Hong Ju.
What brings you here, Mr. Bang?
I heard the meeting got delayed because of an accident.
I guess I heard wrong.
I'm sorry that the project got delayed because of me.
This is all your career means to you?
If you're not going to give it your all,
I'll have to reconsider...
working with you.
You...
Then kick me out.
Hong Ju... Why are you acting like this?
If you don't know the answer to that, I'll be really angry.
You said you would always love me.
You told me you would never change.
That's what you told me.
I did?
I'm sorry to break it to you.
But I've changed.
Do you understand why I'm acting like this?
Then could you leave?
I'm not done talking to you yet.
If you grab my hand again,
I'll really slap you.
What are you doing here?
I'm in pain.
You said you would jump on one leg.
Why did you walk up on your own? Did you want to look that tough?
Does it hurt a lot?
Like crazy.
And it's embarrassing.
I'm embarrassed that you keep witnessing my ruined romance.
Then I'm going to feel bad...
because I'm happy...
that your romance failed.
Sitting down here...
reminds me of the night we fell into the pit.
Stop bringing back the past I want to forget about.
Lee Hong Ju.
Recover quickly...
with your leg injury and your heartache.
(Serendipity's Embrace)
(Obok High School)
Memories are unstable...
because some memories are remembered only by one person.
(Caution: Fall Hazard)
Kang Hoo Young.
What was that just now?
Just now, my heart...
skipped a beat.
(Lee Hong Ju)
I guess only I was startled.
Memories are unstable.
Think about it seriously starting now.
If we're just friends and nothing else.
- I feel awkward around him. - Hoo Young!
I'm having more fun now.
I'm on your mind now. Aren't I?
I'll stop feeling self-conscious around Kang Hoo Young.
I'll just have fun.
You were about to kiss me just now, right?
I'm here to take Hoo Young with me.
Are you going somewhere?
Should I really go?