Episode 22
I'm sorry we couldn't tell you right away.
I was fifteen years old back then.
If I knew then, I wouldn't have been able to endure it.
♬  But it's killing me to see you go after all this time  ♬
Until now, you two worried about me and tried to protect me.
I know all.
Thank you.
Our Seo Yeon... is all grown up now.
I thought you'd hate us and resent us for not telling you.
Elder Oppa... are you crying?
Crying? As if!
Why are you crying?
I'm not, you punk!
I'm not crying.
Leave him alone.  He is in the andropause.
Still... Even if you're all grown up, drinking in front of your older brothers is a little too much.
I drink a lot in front of Second Oppa.
I'm a regular at his bar.
You punk, not only do you not stop her from drinking but your  give  her drinks?
Her tolerance for alcohol is higher than yours.
No way.  You should learn how to drink from the oldest brother.
Here.
Be quiet. Elder Oppa can't drink at all.
He doesn't live up to his body size.
I'm sorry.
Seo Yeon... This oppa is sorry!
Please!
I wondered who made such a noise but it's you, Eldest Brother.
Our youngest!  Our little puppy!
Hyung is sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Seo Joon.
You're heavy!
I'm sorry to Seo Joon!
Why did you drink so much?
Ah seriously.
- It's Noona's boyfriend.
- What?
Go inside first.
I'll introduce myself again. I'm Lee Kang Woo.
Go inside.
- That rascal did—
- Let's get inside!
- He did—
- I told you to get inside!
Please—
You bother me.
Oppa.
What is it, Joo Seo Yeon?
Did your battery go out? Is it broken?
Never mind. There must be a situation.
Are you tired of me?
I'm sorry, Lee Kang Woo.
No, it's okay.
I'm not that angry.
♬  I purposefully take a few steps back  ♬
♬  I look at you walking without me  ♬
♬  I look at you  ♬
♬  There is a void beside you  ♬
But... Why didn't you contact me today?
Because I thought I'd want to see you if I heard your voice.
Don't you like me too much, Joo Seo Yeon? Do it moderately.
No, I cancel what I just said.
Like me like crazy!
Completely!
Got it?
You're heavy.
Even if I'm heavy, endure it.
Joo Seo Yeon is a woman who can bear this much weight.
Kang Woo...
What did you just say?
Not 'Lee Kang Woo', you said 'Kang Woo', right?
If I'm mean to you in the future, hate me a lot.
- What?
- You have to curse at me and resent me, okay?
Don't hold back. You got that?
You got it?
But no matter how mean you are to me,
if you just call me by saying 'Kang Woo',
I think it will be okay.
So, if there's anything that makes you sad or angry,
vent it all on me. Everything.
Now I won't bother you.
When you have time, call me.
Even if I want to hear your voice, I'll hold back.  Even if I miss you, I'll hold back as well.
I'll wait for you quietly.
Go in.
After I see you leave.
Okay, then.
I'm leaving.
Bye-bye.
You're dating him again?
No.
It's a no again?
Is it him?
The one you went to meet with mother and father on the day of the accident.
Your middle school classmate and the one you wronged back then, right?
Are you okay?
If I'm having a hard time, help me, Younger Oppa.
Anytime.
That easily?
She's acting like she's okay, isn't she?
You're awake already?
I get drunk fast and sober up fast too.
Watch her carefully!
She is hanging by a thread right now.
You're still not asleep?
Don't worry. I'll protect you, Unni.
His eyes, nose, and mouth are all the same.
They are the same person.
I told them to go. It was because of me
that Mom and Dad died. Because of me...
Seo Yeon...
It's because of me that Mom and Dad died.
No, it's because of this person.
They said he was Sinhwa Food's grandson, right?
What do you do in your free time, Noona?
- Huh?
- What?
I said, what do you do in your free time?
- What?!
- I heard you got fired from your chief director position.
I heard you were going to come in the headquarters. That is the last quarter's performance reports.  Just look at them.
Why should I look at them?  You know very well what I am doing.
Are you doing it?  If you do, can you have free time?
You're doing it while playing around.
When you said you didn't need two jobs, I thought you were doing it very seriously.
That...
Working hours and this kind of hours are different.
Who's the person from the police station last time?
The person I like.
Which family and who?
She is only daughter from Joo family.
Even though I can, you can't.
- I can choose anyone I want, but you can't.
- What are you talking about?
- Can you introduce her to Mom and Grandma right now?
- Yeah.
You're very selfish.
What do you have right now?  Can you show the accomplishments or results of what you want to do?
Are you independent financially?
Your unplanned action would hurt her.
Don't think Mom is an easy person.  She is very stubborn when it comes to her kids' matters.
Especially when it comes to your matters.
Lee Kang Woo!
It's nothing. I came to my senses thanks to you.
You're right. There's no need to console me.
What is he saying? Pick it up.
What?
Oh.
I'll approve no matter what.
Regardless of what man you choose.
So be on my side as well.
Deal?
Deal.
Assistant Manager, are you waiting for someone's call?
No. Waiting, as if.
I should've taken her to her house that day.
Ah, did she fall while walking back by any chance?
Her knee was bleeding or something?
Yes, this is Lee Kang Hee.
- Are you okay?
- Pardon?
Mr. Joo Won Jae?
That day... Did you get back well?
Of course.
I thought otherwise because you didn't call me.
Did you wait for my call?
No, I didn't exactly wait...
Do you want to eat dinner with me?
Or some other time if you already have an appointment.
I don't have any appointments.
I don't make any appointments since I don't know when you would call me.
I contracted with you, when and where, anytime from 6 p to midnight.
You're a faithful worker.
It was good of me to make that contract.
Of course. You can't find anyone like me anywhere.
I'm very useful.
So... I'll see you later.
Ah, so embarrassing.
How could I prattle on like this?
I'll see you later, Mr. Joo Won Jae.
You're very selfish.
What do you have right now?
Can you show the accomplishments or results of what you want to do?
Okay!
Let's meet in the evening. I have something to say—
Let's meet in the evening. I have something to sa—
Ah, that surprised me.
Who?
Aunt?
Health Teacher's aunt is the mother of Lee Kang Woo.
I didn't even think about it.
Welcome.
Then I definitely saw you that other time as well.
I'm so stupid.  Stupid!  Stupid!
But... Why did you come here?
Are you dating Kang Woo?
- Pardon?
- Why are you so surprised?
Then... Did you think you would continue to go unnoticed?
I don't need to talk long.
Break up with Kang Woo.
Shinhwa Food's family is not a pushover.
Of course, it must be difficult for you to break up.
That's why I came to make it easy for you.
Yes. I'll do that.
I'm sorry for causing you an inconvenience.
No, well...
What was that? So easily?
I prepared ten of these.
She didn't even look at them.
Ah, this place is cozier than I thought.
Are you okay?
I saw my aunt here.
Don't worry.
Hyung won't ever give you up.
As long as you don't let go of him first.
That should be the case, right?
As long as I don't let go of him first.
Yes. Hyung won't let go first.
Please don't tell Mi Kyeong.
She'll be sad.
Yes, don't worry.
Thank you.
I'm always thankful.
What are you going to do if you get caught by Kang Woo, Mother?
- Even if you didn't stop my wife—
- Ah, really.
If it were possible, I would.
You heard it from Lawyer Kim too.
Her parents passed away earlier and she has step-siblings.
If Kang Woo finds out, he'll go crazy.
If he gets upset, he will be more dogged than Kang Hee.
So that's why you just need to keep your mouth shut.
Mother, I need to get ready for a meeting so...
- Sit down!
- Okay.
Give me your phone.
- What?
- Until Kang Woo's issue is resolved,
your phone will be confiscated for the time being.
Mother,  I'm working and receiving a lot of phone calls in the business matters.
- What did you say?
- Mother, still...
There must be some business calls.
Honey.
What happened?
I'm not sure whether she is shrewd or stupid.
What are you talking about? Did she say she won't ever break up with him?
No!  She said very easily she would break up with him.
No... How many of those did you give her?
- I didn't even give one of them.
- What?
Aigoo. Is it because you're the chief director?
It's too soon for you to be off work.
You have nothing different from me.
Your face looks good.
I worried about you just in case.  But I guess you really don't know anything.
What are you talking about?
If someone is hurting or dying next to you, you won't know anything.
What?
Do you know what doctors have to beware of the most in surgery?
Conceit.
Even if a doctor, who repeated  the same surgery several hundred times, is conceited about his skill, he'll easily make a mistake.
Still, if the doctor admits his mistake and retrieves himself neatly, everything will be fine.
But if he gets stubborn, everything will be complicated.
What do you want to say?
Don't loosen up.
Because if you make one mistake, I won't lose that opportunity.
Ha! She already got off from work.
She didn't show herself to me all day long.
Hyung, why didn't you come to practice again today?
I made an excuse to the dance instructor saying you were sick but
call me as soon as you hear this.
Who are you? Who are you to come to a stranger's house—
Lee Joo Hee?!
What is with your appearance?
What is it? Don't you have tutoring today?
What? No. Tutor Ho Dol called me.
Second Hyung, did you see Lee Joo Hee just now?  Why does she go around like that?
- What?
- I mean,
Lee Joo Hee doesn't look like Lee Joo Hee!
What is about Lee Joo Hee looking like Lee Joo Hee?
Are you asking as if you don't know?
Sneakers, pants, and her short hair, but just now she had makeup and a skirt on.
Never mind.
What did he say? The tutor.
What was the reason he said for his not being able to come?
Just that he had a situation. Maybe he's sick?
How stuffy do these friends (cars) feel?
They must be jealous when they see other cars out on the streets through the windows.
Do you feel stuffy at your office too?
I'm hungry.
Come here.
Please have a seat.
These are new, so wear them comfortably.
Thank you.
What did you eat for lunch?
I just ate simply, a glass of milk.
I thought that would be so.
This looks really delicious.
I went to many places while making sales.  This place has the most delicious food like a homemade meal.
Did you buy it on purpose?
Well, I'm assuming other guys have taken you to nice and expensive places.
I just wanted you to eat comfortably.
Here.
Not really.
Are you uncomfortable?
I've been to nice and expensive places
but not with men.
Why? You must've dated many guys.
38.
You met 38 guys...
I mean I haven't properly dated anyone these past 38 years.
I've been to several blind dates,
but I was studying, learning how to work, and going to work.
This really tastes like home food.
♬  Sorry if you got a problem with yourself  ♬
♬  You tryin' to put it on me, I don't need no help  ♬
Hyung! Hyung!
Hyung, Hyung! Did you see this?
♬  Why you tryin' to talk so much? (So much)  ♬
Why are you back? I heard the company told you not to come anymore.
That's ridiculous.  How much money did I earn for them?
I mean, Hyung.  Have you seen this? What an absurd video is up on the internet?
Then do you want to date me?
♬  Why you tryin' to talk so much?   ♬
Look at him.
What's this?
I don't know. A dummy unluckily got caught.
You like it to death?
Smile, smile.
Smile so you look better in the video.
Did you think I was really one of your kind?
Joo Seo Yeon... I'm sure there's something going on.
Your phone is not connected so it goes to the voice mail...
Look at this! She doesn't answer my calls!
Yes.  I came to the place of the last call.
I'll check a little bit more and call you back.
Excuse me.
Have you seen anyone that looks like this?
No, I haven't.
Okay.
But... Who are you?
I'm a police officer. Then, I will leave now.
What was that? A police officer is looking for Baek Jang Mi?
What's going on in this house?
I'm a crazy b*tch.
It'll be okay if I'm the crazy b*tch. Only me.
I did well, right? I didn't bother you, right?
I only thought of you a little and I got a lot of work done.
I did well, right?
You did well.
Why are you being like this? Did something happen?
Exactly how much is this house?
- What?
- Is this house yours?
Well, the house is in my name.
So you're saying that all of this stuff is yours?
Well.
This is the same thing that Elder Oppa has.
He has an eye for choosing clothes.
He bought it with 36 monthly payments and I think he is still paying.
- You bought it with one payment, didn't you?
- Yeah.
You really are rich, Lee Kang Woo.
Why are you being like this?
I just realized.
What?
Your place and my place.
- What?
- Like a fool, I forgot.
That you are a grandson of Sinhwa Food.
Why did I forget that? Don't you think I'm an idiot?
It doesn't make sense–you and me.
Do you know why I don't look like my brothers?
They're not my biological brothers.
As you already know, my parents
passed away.
I'm an orphan.
What are you doing right now?
Do you need more explanation?
I feel like I'm getting pathetic.
Just let's stop when we are in moderation.
In moderation?
It's obvious. Even if we keep meeting, I'll be at a loss.
Did you meet me calculating the benefit or loss?
You don't know
because you've never been in a subordinate position.
So Lee Kang Woo, let's break up now–
Joo Seo Yeon!
Why are you being like this, Seo Yeon?
I'm sorry. I did wrong.
Don't do this, Seo Yeon. Hm?
You have a guest!
Who is it?
Pardon?
By any chance, are you Kang Woo's girlfriend?
That's right, my girlfriend.
Why? That's right.
You're my girl.
♫  I'm always by your side  ♫
♫  There is I who only look at you  ♫
♫  Whenever and wherever I'm next to you  ♫
♫  How do you not know?  How do you not know?  ♫
♫  I didn't say anything, but my eyes say  ♫
Love With Flaws
♫  How don't you notice?  ♫
Doesn't like you because you're handsome. Doesn't like you because you're ugly. But now she says she doesn't like you because you're a chaebol's grandson?
Do it moderately.
You got caught!
What's your identity?
I'll protect Unni Seo Yeon.
If I don't need anything but all I need is just that woman, am I crazy?
I don't know.  I'm going to get upset now.
I'll die.
Don't cry! I told you to stop crying!
Just play around with me then throw me away.
Come to your senses, Lee Kang Woo. I think you're crazy.
Lee Kang Woo is dying with bleeding.
Why do you give up on me by getting scared beforehand?
I don't love you.
♫  Would you please notice, my love?  ♫