Noona.
Don't say anything, punk.
Go in.
First, Lee Joo Hee, now her. What's wrong with everyone?
The caller is currently not available—
Jang Woo isn't picking up?
No, he's not answering.
Is there really something going on?
He must've been really shocked because of the fan cam comments.
- Pardon?
- He hasn't been coming out since then.
Hyung, I'm in front of your house but you're not home.
Call me.
Message was recorded.
Lee Joo Hee?
Drinking Karaoke Bar
Is she crazy?
Ow! Ow! What are you doing?
That's what I should be asking.
Oh, that's—
Of all the things you've done, now you're working in a bar?
- What?
- I thought you had your head on straight,
I'm disappointed in you Lee Joo Hee, I'm disappointed.
Who are you to butt in?
- What?
- You told me to not meddle in your life.
Do you think you're something just because we live together?
Whether I work in a bar or not, it's none of your business.
You're going to go back?
Hey! Hey, Lee Joo Hee!
Two of them...
live together?
He said he was sorry!
What?
The video... He apologized for the video!
It probably wasn't easy to apologize in person.
- In-person?
- He's probably not as bad as I thought he was.
So you guys met? Again?
Huh? Well, he called saying he had something to say.
Why are you here?
To brag about that?
I thought you would like it if you knew.
Hang around then go.
Okay.
♬    Hey Laura, sweet     ♬
It's you right? The idiot in the video.
Oh! P-Park Seok Min!
Wow, I thought you would die in a hole somewhere,
but you're braver than I thought.
I'm sorry?
Are you here alone?
I was about to head home.
Why already?
You want to go out and get a drink?
♬    Let's turn off the radio and let's go dancing     ♬
♬     Are you going to sit at home all night?    ♬
Are you looking for the kid?
Yeah, did you see him?
I think he left with Seok Min.
Who?
So annoying.
Who is it?
Oh, Hyung!  What are you doing here?
- Where is he?
- What?
I asked where he is.
What —  Why are you being like this?
What's wrong?
Hyung, I asked what's going on.
Oh, Hyungnim.
Hey!! Why are you here!
Pardon?
Huh?  What? You're something else, Hyung.
Oh, you're here for him?
Why are you wearing clothes like this?
It's my house, can't I wear what I want?
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Ho Dol,
let's see each other often.
Joo Won Seok! You're a human after all. Hyung, you're human with a heart, too.
Why would you follow someone you don't know?
It's Park Seok Min. Everyone in Korea knows him.
So? You follow him to his house because you know his face?
Ah, because Park Seok Min said he would give me these.
You want to go out for a drink?
Not really...
Not really? Do you know who I am? I'm Park Seok Min!
I'm not really a fan.
I'm Park Seok Min, a top star, Park Seok Min!
I'm a fan of High Seven.
- Who?
- High Seven!
- High Seven.
Aren't they cool? Park Seok Min said he was in the same agency as they were and he had a bunch of these.
- Fasten your belt.
- Okay.
What should I do with you?
Lee Min Hyeok. You're not coming today?
I'm not going.
- Why?
-  I'm busy.
Then when are you coming? Should I pick you up?
Cold bastard.
Seo Yeon decided to live a wild life with me from now on.
What was that picture?
It took you thirty minutes to get here. It should've taken only ten minutes.
Are you really going to end things with Seo Yeon like this?
Never mind. You probably wouldn't have come here like this if you were.
What do you want me to do? Seo Yeon said no.
What more do you want from me?
Seriously, "the king has the ears of an ass."
As long as I know you're not giving up, it's fine.
Since you're here, take me home.
- What?
- What, friends can give each other rides.
Seo Yeon just fell asleep. She won't come out even if you wait.
- She's sleeping?
- Yeah, she's sleeping.
That's a relief that she can sleep.
Sleep well, Joo Seo Yeon.
Seon Yeon, let's play.
Unni.
Welcome.
Hello. Is Mr. Joo Won Jae here?
Oh, Deputy Chief? Hold on a minute.
Deputy Chief, you have a guest.
Who?
Director Lee Kang Hee sent me here.
♬  I never feel so loved  ♬
♬  I've been having dreams  ♬
Breach of contract...penalty is ten times the promised contract amount...
Breach of contract?
Lawsuit? Deputy Chief, did you cause trouble?
♬  I wanted it to happen  ♬
I told you to review carefully before signing.
Didn't you read the penalty clause?
I wonder why you trusted me and just signed it.
When one side fails to carry out the terms of the contract,
the penalty is ten times the promised contract amount.
Let's call it even, with a date that's not part of the contract.
I'm curious as to why women like you.
It makes me jealous, too.
Didn't you understand what I said the other night? I—
I know. I know that you're a gold digger.
But at thirty-eight years old,  I have yet to date anyone properly.
It is not something to brag about, is it?
Nine of ten people would say she must have some kind of flaws.
I've never thought that way, not even once.
Right. Instead, you said I was sweet and beautiful.
Of all the compliments I've received, I liked those the best.
I've fallen for your trick, I did.
Ms. Lee Kang Hee, I am...
You see, I am...
I like you, Joo Won Jae. What about you?
Do you want to continue to eat meals with me, talk with me,
and stay with me?
♫   Your face that I see every day  ♫
♫  Your breath that I feel every day  ♫
Because of Lee Kang Woo, don't draw the line with me.
I'm asking you for this favor.
♫  I smile looking at you  ♫
I guess she decided not to grant me that favor.
♫  Why is that you don't see me  ♫
♫  I'm always by your side  ♫
♫  I'm here, who sees you   ♫
♫  No matter where I'm here. Why is it that you don't know?  ♫
♫  How can you not know? Even though I've never expressed it  ♫
What am I doing exactly?
I shouldn't behave this way to the health teacher.
Again you're behaving this way.
Hello!
Why are you doing this exactly? Doesn't your forehead hurt?
Well...it's just my habit.
You sure have strange habits.
I was grateful last time.
If it weren't for you, I would have been a laughingstock.
Wear this on your date with my Kang Woo.
- Pardon?
- I can guess so obviously the situation when you dressed like that in the crowded area.
Shouldn't you think about taking care of saving my Kang Woo's face, too?
Or ask Kang Woo to buy some clothes for you.
I guess you haven't heard from Kang Woo yet...
Heard what?
No way! I requested that of you and you couldn't momentarily endure?
You didn't immediately break up with him, did you?
Well, I...
You didn't, right?
No. I didn't.
Of course, you shouldn't.
I'm making a plan that makes two of you naturally break up.
So understand it.
Go safely.
I'm going crazy.
You, you, look at you.  I thought you wouldn't function properly.
You finally came back to your sens—
What should I do with him? Kill him or let him live?
What is this?
Something similar to the vibe of  High Seven's stan?
I like Joo Won Jae.  How about you?
No. Don't covet.
No, no.
Antoinette?
Hello.
Who?
I'm Lee Min Hyeok, who works at the same school as Teacher Joo does.
But who do you think I am so you're greeting me?
Aren't you a family member of Teacher Joo?
Your eyes look like hers.
Mine and Seo Yeon's look like?
You're here!
How are you here, Health Teacher.
You don't need to get up.  Sit down. Sit.
Why didn't you tell me there was such a great bachelor at your school?
This man has very good eyes.
He has very observant eyes.
- Oppa!
- Yes?
Could you leave us alone?
Oh, where's my brain?  Talk to each other.  Hey, I told you to sit down.
Talk to each other here, at a place where it's wide open, not in the room.
- Oppa!
- I'm going!  I said I'm going.
Why are you rushing me out?
Why does he act like this?
I'm sorry.
No, don't mention it.  He is broad-minded and good.
But what made you come here?
You avoided me at school so I came here to see you for a short while.
It's right you're avoiding me, isn't it?
Yes.
Teacher Joo, you don't like me?
Pardon? What are you talking about?
Why do I not like you, Health Teacher?
It's a relief.
If it's not that you don't like me but the situation makes you uncomfortable, it'll be enough for me.
- Excuse me—
- I'll get going.
Teacher.
Yes?
Would you like to have dinner with me?
- Pardon?
- I want to treat you with dinner.
There is a pretty good restaurant nearby.  Their food is really good.
No, thank you.  I don't want to have dinner with you, Teacher Joo.
Pardon?  Why?  Are you busy?
No, I'm not busy and I'm hungry.
Then why not?
I think you would clearly finish up with me while eating dinner.
Well...
Lee Min Hyeok even came to your house?
I'm not sure what I'm really doing.
Don't blame yourself too much.
Everyone has to settle their own feelings on their own. There's nothing you can do.
There's nothing you can do.
What was bad was that I was looking for something similarities to Lee Kang Woo from Health Teacher.
I was thinking this part resembles.  It's right that they are cousins.
Do you miss Lee Kang Woo a lot?
Should I just tell Lee Kang Woo everything and get killed bravely?
What if I see him once more with the excuse of returning this?
No.  If I see him once, then I'll want to see him twice.
If I see him twice, then I'll want to see him three times.
No.
What are they?
I thought you might miss him.
♫  Even if I shout while looking at the empty sky, you don't answer back  ♫
His facial expression is as same as yours.
♫  Do you know my sad tears that I couldn't even forget?  ♫
♫  Do you hear my voice?  ♫
♫  Thinking you might come back all day long every day  ♫
♫  Wandering around your empty place, I missed you  ♫
♫  My painful heart is already covered with tears  ♫
♫  I don't even know whether even a smarting wound hurts  ♫
♫  Did you know I was waiting for you like this?  ♫
Was it true?
Was it really because of me?
Are you okay?
You can't get up because you hurt or you won't get up because you are embarrassed?
Half and half.
You missed one "0".
I'm talking about your share of living expenses. It was short by one "0".
Did you notice it now?
No wonder why you didn't attack me even if you looked at it.  You must've been out of your mind.
I did it on purpose.
On purpose?
You've been strange these days. You usually couldn't cry but now you cry every night.
Can you even see with the swollen eyelids?
Did you notice that I was crying?
I'm your older brother.
I live such a scum life so I'm not qualified to say this to someone else but—
You're the main base of our family.
Right.  Watching you as the main base,
I think your sunglasses are related to our parents' accident, right?
What if Dad had chosen a different way?
What if he hadn't chosen me, who was ugly and mean?
I heard that when people see an accident in front of their own eyes, they try to avoid it no matter what,
distancing themselves from danger, even if it would be a little bit of distance.
One of the police said this back then.
Three of you couldn't have survived that kind of accident.
The driver must've instinctively protected you, no matter how he thought about it.
What?
He said it seemed the driver rather swerved the car toward her side.
In order to save two of you in the back seats.
Seo Yeon.
Come to your sense.
We're fine, Seo Yeon.
You were not for their choice.
But you were for their instinct to them.
What on earth...
Who was I?
You were the one and only lovely daughter to them.
And no matter what kind of situation it was,
Mom and Dad didn't want to be an obstacle to your life.
Mom and Dad protected your life and love.
I wish your life and love would end up with uncommon happiness.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I dared to want Joo Seo Yeon.
Seo Yeon, don't look back.
Don't look back and just go.
Mom and Dad are fine.
Never look back.
Good daughter.
Joo Seo Yeon
Lee Kang Woo, I'm in front of your house right now.
Do you know this phone's owner?
Who are you?
There was a car accident. This phone was here on the street.
- What?
-  There was an accident.  Accident!
What does it mean?
There is no way.
No, it's not.
Why did Lee Kang Woo...
No, he didn't.
You scared me!
What?  What?
Lee Kang Woo.
How can you...?
What about?
- Where is your phone?
- My phone?
I lost it.
On the way here, there was an accident ahead of me.  So I reported it then I might've dropped it.
But why are you here?
- You're supposed to not be—
- I like you, Lee Kang Woo.
You–  What did you just say?
I love you.
♫  It looks like you're coming to me from somewhere  ♫
♫  Now, I can't bear it anymore   ♫
♫  This night, this night, if I'm able to spend this night with you again  ♫
♫  All of this, all of this, I want to give you all of my love  ♫
♫  Like the small leaves falling on the ground  ♫
Love with Flaws
I should not do it to you.
He also should contemplate and can choose his way.
You don't like me anymore?
I should be abandoned by you.
Hyung, you're pooping right now.  You're pooping because you have too many blessings.
So you're telling that Min Hyeok also likes that lady...
You're really a professional player, Joo Won Jae.
Are you confident you won't have regret?
I'm very jealous of you, who get all preferential treatment even if you didn't do anything.
What should I do?  I think my dad saw the video of me.
I won't send you home today.  Don't arouse me.
I won't go.  I'll stay with you.
♫  Now, I can't bear it anymore  ♫