Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
Our Hearts as One ❤️ Team@Viki.com
You can find them, right, Lieutenant Baek?
They shoot from the highest point.
Even I'm aware of that.
Let's stop now.
Put that gun down, Seung Tae.
Nothing's going to change even if you kill him.
I'm just following orders.
We're not soldiers.
Have you forgotten?
How did our comrades die?
It was my fault.
I couldn't protect them
and I was foolish.
Right.
You can't carry out a great task
when you have a woman you love.
If you get in my way again,
you'll be killed.
Oh Seung Tae!
Seung Tae.
"A gun isn't a toy."
"Fire first if you don't want to die."
You told me that.
We meet again here.
We said, let's not meet again.
Yes.
Because we were always unhappy
whenever we were together.
So, go now.
But
I was happy because of you.
Please take good care of Yeong Ok,
buddy.
You're so annoying from
the beginning to the end.
Do you know that?
As for Seung Tae, I will…
Wake up.
Wake up!
You even survived that hellish 112 Unit.
You can't just die like this.
♫  ♫
Wake up.
Comrade Jae Hoon.
♫  ♫
How have you been?
Nice to see you, Baek Yeong Ok.
♫  ♫
Upon hearing that we were going
to hide the target in a safe house,
the first one to bite the bait will be Shadow.
But an unexpected event took place.
So more time and effort
were needed accordingly.
If it's the safest to hide
the real one among fake ones,
as for the thief who is
trying to steal the real one,
where would he be to have
the highest chance of success?
The guard who is protecting
the real one is the culprit.
Send them all out.
- Pardon?
- What's going on?
They're plotting something.
They're plotting to kill me.
Are you all right?
We must catch Shadow.
For Comrade Jae Hoon.
It's for all of us too.
Okay, all of you, get out.
­
Mayor Won, what do you mean
they're plotting something?
You're aware that someone
tried to assassinate Lloyd, right?
Yes.
It wasn't Violet's doing.
Then, who…
North Korea tried to kill
Lloyd as well as me, the mayor,
to destroy Pyeonghwasi's
security and its existence.
- It was North Korea's special operations.
- What did you say?
Comrade Won Tae Sook.
- Drop your gun.
- You drop it first, Comrade.
Drop the gun now!
You drop it first!
Drop it!
The security team…
It doesn't work? Then, we need to break it.
It's bulletproof glass, so we could get hurt.
Vice Commissioner Lee, open the door.
Open the door, Vice Commissioner Lee!
Vice Commissioner Lee! Open the door now!
It's Baek Yeong Ok.
Baek Yeong Ok is framing me as Shadow
and is trying to turn Pyeonghwasi upside down.
She's a spy sent by North Korea.
Have you lost your mind? What are you saying?
How do you plan to handle all this?
Open the door now, Mayor Won.
Or should I call you Shadow now?
From the start, when my car
without the GPS changed the route,
you were the one who was able
to inform the sniper about this.
You were hiding right next to the target.
You are Shadow, Mayor Won Tae Sook.
Now, everything makes sense.
Making sense, my foot.
This is all North Korea's doing.
It is not.
What can I do to make you trust me?
You have to convince me
that you're trustworthy.
Do you all want to die together?
Now, we're
on the same side.
Fine.
Why did you do that?
Were you trying to start a war in Pyeonghwasi?
Won Tae Sook.
You're under arrest for violating
the unification security law.
Arrest her.
Freeze!
Drop your gun!
You don't know anything.
They say, a hero is always
an embodiment of turbulence.
Peace? Reconciliation?
Those things don't suit me.
The country's chaos and
heightened security concerns
made me who I am today.
That's the power that sustains me.
I don't
want to lose that power.
Put that gun down.
It's over now.
I started it,
so I'll end it too.
To become who I am today,
do you even know how many
sacrifices I had to make?
Sacrifices, my foot.
Do you really think
that you've become a hero
of Pyeonghwasi? Seriously?
Sorry to break it to you,
but hero is someone else, not me.
Lieutenant Baek, go ahead and shoot.
I trust you, Lieutenant Baek.
­
Comrades.
Don't act rashly!
Shoot now.
I said, shoot now!
I can't trust myself.
But I trust you. Just shoot!
But what if…
But what if something goes wrong?
Without you, Comrade No,
I have no faith I can live now.
That's not true.
Don't say that.
Just…
Just shoot already!
What?
This isn't what I intended.
It's a misunderstanding.
­
Lloyd!
No!
Comrade No.
Comrade No, wake up!
Wake up!
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
I should've done it sooner…
­
No matter how thoughtless
and pretentious you could be
and even a bluffer…
Say it now.
I love you.
I really love you.
Comrade No.
If I can hear it one more time,
I'll have no regrets.
I love you too.
Can you say what you just said one more time?
Which one?
I feel a little better
hearing that you love me.
Comrade No.
A bulletproof vest is a must, you know?
I'm used to that facial expression.
So sweet, man.
I feel rewarded
for bridging the lovers together.
I love you.
I love you more.
Prosecutors arrested Won Tae Sook,
the first mayor of Pyeonghwasi, a pilot city,
on charges of violating
the unification security law
and forming an anti-state organization.
Won Tae Sook was accused of supporting and
instigating conflicts between the two Koreas
and interfering with
peaceful unification through
an anti-unification
terrorist group called Violet.
Pyeonghwasi's disastrous crisis
and the risk to its very existence
were overcome by great efforts of
the Unified Korean Armed Force Unit.
The two Koreas agreed
to receive preliminary candidate
registration soon to hold a special election
to elect the mayor of Pyeonghwasi.
[Operating Center]
­
What about you?
Of course, don't worry.
I'll be right here waiting for you.
Okay?
Mi Rae, when you're finished with your surgery,
let's go play at Pyeonghwa Park again.
Let's eat gimbap and ramyeon,
and I'll win you a giant plush toy too.
Please sing for me too.
I'm indeed a better singer than Avon, right?
Yes, of course.
You're serious about singing.
I'll be back.
Meanwhile, please take good care of my sister.
Let's go inside now.
Baek Mi Rae, you've got this.
Don't you worry a thing.
­
Don't worry too much, okay?
She'll be okay.
She has dystocia.
She's carrying two, not one.
Bringing new lives
isn't going to be easy.
Be patient.
­
What do you mean?
I'm sorry
that I didn't tell you sooner.
Did
Comrade Seong Jae Hoon really come by?
Yes.
Thank you for coming.
I have no reason to avoid you.
I lost so much because of you.
So what? Do you want to take revenge?
I don't have a reason to do so anymore.
Because I'm leaving.
Then, why did you want to see me?
I want to catch one of
them at least before I go.
Shadow?
I've never seen them in person,
either, so I don't know who it is.
But I know what their next plan is.
Shadow will attempt to kill you for sure.
Number Ones of the South and
North cannot be the targets now.
So you'd make the most impact.
And the moment you're targeted
will be the golden opportunity
to capture Shadow.
So, it sounds like you're
asking me to be the bait.
But why should I?
Because we must catch Shadow
in order for Yeong Ok to return.
And why should I trust you?
For Yeong Ok's sake, I don't want
you to be hurt.
In any case, they're going to
try to take you to a safe house.
Based on the safe house information alone,
we can't conclude that person to be Shadow.
But what if I change the location abruptly?
If someone knows about
that and contacts Seung Tae,
that person would be…
Shadow.
Yes.
Is that why you did such a thing?
Offered yourself as bait?
Yes.
­
T-Thank you.
Our baby, Pyeong Hwa, is born.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
What about Tong Il?
As for Tong Il… Not yet.
My goodness. This is
so hard. So hard.
­
Mom.
- Please eat.
- Eat up.
Is the guardian of Baek Mi Rae here?
Yes. I'm Baek Mi Rae's guardian.
Her surgery went well. She's
in the recovery room now.
Thank you.
Please charge this credit card.
You may pay at the reception.
At the reception?
- Got it.
- Okay.
Lloyd?
Song I.
What are you doing here?
Hey, you…
Are you all right?
Are you sure you're okay?
I am.
I'll be able to walk again.
I'm sorry to cause you trouble.
No, don't say that.
I'm so relieved and thankful
that you're up like this.
You'll hold a concert once
you get discharged, right?
I'll go for sure.
Of course, you must.
I'm a father now!
Sir!
Congratulations. Congratulations.
Now I'm Pyeong Hwa and Tong Il's father.
Comrade Seung Min is holding up well.
Comrade Sae Yeong, you're doing great.
It's only been five minutes. Hang in there!
Bring on the strength of the corn
that you ate in times of suffering.
- Hey, remember the hell week. Hang on.
- Who's the boss? Come on, let's go!
35, 36…
- Hang on for a little longer.
- 37.
- 38.
- Come on, man.
What was that?
What do you think you're doing?
Come to think of it,
this is meaningless.
I quit.
I quit too.
But it's only been five minutes.
Weak. Bros, you're all weak.
Come here for a second.
Drink this.
Now that Mi Rae's surgery went well,
let's unite now.
That's not up to us.
I mean, the two of us should unite first.
Let's be together for the rest of our lives.
Are you
asking me to marry you?
Answer me now.
I don't want to.
Why not?
W-Why not?
Both of us want to be together
so desperately. So, why not?
I don't want to.
Tell me if I'm lacking something or
if you don't like something about me.
I'll fix it.
Why are you like this all of a sudden?
You order me around to deliver boxes.
Are you sure I'm the owner?
Why do you keep ordering wine
that doesn't even sell well?
Natasha.
She used to like it.
She looks so lovely.
­
When are we going to unite?
Well, when the time comes, I suppose.
So, when is that?
I heard that marriage is off limits if you'll
continue being a singer after your discharge.
So you're saying, you haven't
accepted my proposal for my sake?
Not necessarily.
I love you.
I too
love you.
What do I do?
Can you say it one more time?
I
do
love
you.
Turn around and bow.
I'm so happy.
Three, two, one.
Throw it!
- Comrade Lieutenant Baek.
- Lloyd.
She'll marry me. She'll marry me.
Credit final
It's F-FITA!
­
♪ Every emotion I feel right now ♪
♪ I hope you feel the same ♪
♪ I've fallen for your beautiful gaze ♪
♪ I can't even breathe in this place ♪
♪ Follow me ♪
♪ I only see you ♪
♪ I'll hold your hand ♪
- Lloyd!
♪ Who is wishing ♪
♪ If you call me like this ♪
♪ Reality keeps changing ♪
♪ Mirror ♪
♪ Oh, love actually ♪
♪ A new miracle before me ♪
♪ A little closer ♪
♪ Be with me until the end ♪
♪ Stop everything, baby ♪
♪ In the midst of emotions,
it becomes the same ♪
♪ Mirror, mirror, mirror, baby ♪
♪ Look at me, lady. I want you ♪
♪ You and I now, mirror mirror mirroring ♪
Lloyd!
♫  ♫
♪ Who is wishing ♪
♪ If you call me like this ♪
♪ Reality keeps changing ♪
♪ Mirror ♪
♪ Oh, love actually ♪
♪ A new miracle before me ♪
♪ A little closer ♪
My passionate romance
and my soul's agony are still ongoing.
At this place,
we dreamed of peace achieved
by the unification of the two Koreas
and saw the hope of trying to understand
each other beyond the border.
I look forward
to the future when that hope
turns into a beautiful reality.
♫ I hope ♫
♫ They reach you someday ♫
♫ My steps toward you ♫
♫ I used to keep it a secret ♫
♫ The way I feel ♫
♫ I won't hide it any longer ♫
♫ I can do anything ♫
♫ You are my everything ♫
♫ It's so precious ♫
♫ So I kept holding it back ♫
♫ The one phrase, I love you ♫
♫ I shout it out confidently ♫
♫ To you ♫
♫ I hope ♫
♫ They reach you someday ♫
♫ My steps toward you ♫
♫ I used to keep it a secret ♫
♫ The way I feel ♫
♫ I won't hide it any longer ♫
♫ I can do anything ♫
♫ You are my everything ♫
- Thank you. Take care.
- Thank you.
Take care.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
Our Hearts as One ❤️ Team@Viki.com
[Mountain Hawks of Unified Armed Force Unit,
gather at the point. Dispatched to Afghanistan]
Get moving!
♫ I'm clumsy and awkward ♫
♫ But I try to act like it's nothing ♫
♫ As a day goes by ♫
♫ And another month goes by ♫
♫ Will I be ♫
♫ A little closer to you then ♫
♫ You and me ♫
♫ So special ♫
♫ Love my hurt ♫
♫ Only for you ♫
♫ I wish for you ♫
♫ I was hoping for romance ♫
♫ A heart-pounding day ♫