Older sister
Younger sister
Brother!
Bro!
What should I call?
What do you want?
I come to get money back that you borrowed.
Hey! Bro!
What?
I come to get money back.
Give me please.
No! Go away!
Can she do that?
Pay money back to me, please.
I don't want to hurt women.
Wait wait!
Calm down bro.
I...
I'm joking.
I can't hurt anyone.
That's all.
So....When you can give money to me?
Do you have....
Not have, Not run, Not pay!
Do you understand?
Damn it!
Why it so hard to get money back?
It's so hard everywhere.
What should I do?
Hi! My friend, Sun.
Mek!
You frightened me.
Please don't come quietly.
You're a little jumpy.
What's wrong?
You make your face like a monkey's ass.
Let's smile.
Mek!
Don't be serious
I think you're not success again.
Right?
So, what's your problem?
Can you tell your buddy?
I went to get money everywhere,
but I didn't get from anyone.
Especialy, this man!
He never give to me.
Oh my friend.
I'll do it for you.
Please hold this.
I'll get money from that guy for you.
No way!
I ask him all these months
He never give to me.
Hey~ Who am I?
I'm a teacher Mek.
Prepare to respect me.
Hello uncle~
Okay. Fully payment.
Principal and interest
I already count it.
How can you do that?
I never get it.
He never give to me.
That's fine.
Let's go.
Practice so hard, my friend.
Mek! Sun!
Exercise so hard~
I just practice
Did your dad found your couple to you?
Sun!
Watch your mouth.
Why you poke me, Mek?
Why you look at me like that, Ashing?
I mean your competitor.
You known that his dad didn't made this boxing camp for competition.
My friends~
Do you come to see my dad?
He's inside there.
Just go.
Yes, sir!
Okay
Who's there?
Sun and Mek
This is Tai.
He tooks internship.
Let's be friend.
Okay boss.
He doesn't look like trainee.
He looks like work more than 10 years.
Where is my money?
Here it is.
It's fully payment.
Who get this money?
Sun.
Yes
I am.
I let you answer again.
It's me.
Sun!
When you can work by yourself?
If you don't have Mek, what should you do?
I'm so sorry, boss.
I promise it won't be like this again.
How many times you said that?
I'm so much kind for you, right?
It's not like that boss.
When I go to get money,
Moo Brother will use axe to kill me!
I don't care.
I give you one month.
One month!
If you can't do it,
I will let you...
Do nothing.
And let Tai replace you to work.
He will work with Mek.
How about me?
What do you want me to do?
Anything
If you can't do it, you fire!
Boss! You can't do that!
Why can't I?
I'm your boss!
It's not why.
But it can't be like that.
Just like that! I give you one month.
Go! Not go?
No! Boss!
Sun, we should go now.
Boss is very angry.
Excuse me, boss.
Good bye boss.
Mek!
Just go!
Why? Will you jump to river?
Go ahead.
That's fine.
Please jump.
Go ahead buddy!
Don't you think I really jump?
Do you dare?
It's a pitty for my handsome face.
D*mn!
Boring!!
What's that noise?
What are you doing here?
I just come to take a photo.
And say hi to my new friend.
Because we will work together soon.
Right?
And you,
Tell me when you ready to work with me.
I'm always.
What the heck on you?!
That's nothing buddy.
When I saw him,
I'm so dissatisfied.
You think too much.
Shall we go home?
Or jump to the river?
I'm kidding.
Hey!
Don't you really ask me anything?
Ask what?
Are you my son?
Okay
What's happen daddy?
I'm so disappoint in you.
Dad
Will you be sued?
That's right.
You've to help me now.
How?!
It's a lot of money!
Ten million baht!
You must get money from my deptor to me.
Dad! It's not about me!
Dept pays by himself.
Wait!
You...
Dad
If not,
I'll call the police.
It's not funny.
Funny?
How can you arrest me?
I haven't done anything wrong.
Wrong!
You're wrong.
How?!
This!
You play slot casino online.
Do you want to see me filed for bankruptcy?
That's fine.
If you don't help me, I'm fine.
Sometimes, we should have father when we are ready.
And this is the place you have to go.
Boss!
Why always me?
I don't want to go to work far away!
Please let me go is better than him.
Piss off!
Tai
I really want you to hand this job.
But it's very important job,
and I need someone I can trust.
Boss, did you mean
Am I not trustworthy?
Not really?
And you just started to work here.
Another one,
This job is ....
His father's money.
It's right to let his son do it.
But...I'm...
Can I go instead of him?
Stop it!
Sun
I give you a last chance.
If you don't do it, you really fired!!
Boss!
That's all.
I give you one month.
If you can't do it.
Don't need to comeback!!
Remember that!
Hey!
Who are you?
Hey!!
What the f*ck you doing?
I ask who are you?
And who are you?
Don't piss me off.
If you don't want to tell me,
Just get out of my place!
Is this your place?
Yes
This is my house.
I won't go.
You won't go?
Do you want to have a problem?
Yep
I do it for you!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Is he your friend?
No, he is deptor.
Ah~ Just deptor.
If you want to meet my dad,
he is over there.
Listen to me first.
His father is your dad's deptor.
But he doesn't have money.
So, he send him for clear the interest.
Is that true?
What's it going to be useful for?
Hey! What's happen?
You're here.
Yes.
I'm so boring about deptors.
Really boring.
It's good that you come.
Ashing, if you want anything, you can use him to do it.
Just think he is your servant.
Dad!
I don't want him.
Come on~
What's your nam? Huh?
Your name?
Umm..
Huh?
Fine!
You don't have to answer,
But you have to stay here.
And take care of my son.
Do you understand?
When you stay here,
just do everything that boss want.
Okay?
Ashing!
Congrats to you.
You got your mate now!
Hey!
He will punch your face if you said like that.
I'm kidding.
Let's talk about yours.
And I'm hungry now.
Shall we find some food?
Ashing
Do you join with us?
Yes, I'll change clothes first.
Hey! Let's go together!
What's that noise?
Let's go.
Go go!
Sun...
Can I go with you?
Can you go?
Can you ask your dad for me?
Nah...
I don't want to bother.
You know that?
I'm fine, Mek.
I can do it.
Are you crazy?
It's ten million!
I'm not crazy.
You can't do that.
Agree.
Why you laughing?
Just only ten baht, you can't get it back.
Don't you remember when we were young?
If Ashing and I didn't help you,
You can't get that ten baht.
Give money back to me now!
Ouch!
I don't have! I won't give you.
If not, I will tell your mother!
Okay, fine!
That's when I was a kid, don't take it all together.
Whenever you can't do it.
If you don't have Mek,
You got kicked out a long time ago.
Ashing!
Are you my friend?
Don't you think to cheer me up?
Okay~ When you arrive there
If you want our help,
Just call me, okay?
Thanks buddy.
Eh? How about me?
You're just friend.
You said that? Fine~
I'll tell dad to kick you out.
Come on, save yourself first.
You first.
Just watch yourself.
Be aware about Tai.
I think he'll work better than you.
Someday, you'll out on
Mek and Sun
to be Tai and Mek.
Wow! Such a nice name.
Are you gossip about me?
Let's eat.
One black coffee, please.
D*mn it.
Look at him.
He has money to eat well.
But he doesn't have money to pay.
Is he too much?
Is that normal?
People need to feed himself.
Do you want him to photosynthesize?
No!
Before he having happy,
He has to pay bepts first!
What will you do?
Come, I'll do this case.
You!
Who are you?
Who do you owe?
You get the wrong person.
Hey~
Just pay back the money.
You gonna make the big problems.
Are you threaten me?
I'll call the police!
How dare you?
Just pay back the money.
You can eat something expensive.
You can buy new phone.
Hey! Will you attack me?
Should I use violent?
Or put it on the internet?
Creditors must ask the debtor politely.
Respect and refrain from condemnation.
Not to cause the debtor to be disgraced or shamed
To protect the rights of the debtor.
Otherwise, they will be punished according to Act 13.
Who are you?
I'm a lawyer. I just walked past.
Lawyer, help me, please.
You are the same.
Deptors must pay money back to Creditors.
Did you know?
Creditors can bring all evidence of your borrowing money
to sue you as well.
Give me your money.
Here you are. Please don't mess with me anymore.
Enough.
How can he do that?
We got the money. Just don't care him.
Where's he from?
You haven't pack your stuff yet. Let's go back home.
You'll traveling tomorrow.
Let's take the money to boss.
That's right.
Next day
Hello, dad?
Don't worry.
That ten million,
I'll take it for you.
Bon Voyage, my son.
Thanks dad.
Wish the mission will success.
See you dad.
Your name, sir.
I'm David.
Okay
Yes, thank you.
Mek, sir.
Mr. Mek...Okay.
Is this the pier to take boat?
Yes, that way.
You! Can I ask something?
Is this the boat go to Arthid Island?
And what time will you get off?
The Boat to Arthid Island is already out. It's the boat to Pra Chan Island.
Huh? Pra Chan?
If you hurry, you can ask boss.
Maybe he can bring you together.
What did she say?
Pick it up.
Hey
You
I want to go to Arthid Island.
Do you know there?
Lifting slowly.
I can pay for it. Please bring me with you.
I'll lift it.
Such a rude person.
Don't let me see you again.
You're heartless!
So cruel hearted!
Evil-minded!!
What should I do now?
Let's stay here first.
Excuse me, sir.
I want a room with single bed.
Here, room number 305 at third floor.
You can pay rent fee when you check out.
Thank you.
It's so haunting people and haunting hotels.
Do you scare of ghost?
Ghost?
Hey uncle~
Who scare?
Ghost must scare of me.
That's good.
Good luck.
You're kidding me.
Where should I go?
Thanks.
What?! Double bed?
It's because of you.
I've to be in trouble.
Wait and see
Let I found you.
Who's that?
Yes?
Ghost isn't real.
According to science,
he'll kncok wrong.
When we open the door,
That's a relief.
What the?!
Ghost isn't real.
What the f*ck!
I won't stay here!!
Ghost!
Uncle! I want to change the room!
You said you're not scare of ghost.
Ghost?
The water comes not well.
Please~ I want to take a shower.
None.
This boy got the last one.
Can you....
change the room with me?
Oh! You know that?
Ghost can go anywhere.
It's not about ghost.
It's about water isn't good.
I want to take a shower.
If it true,
how can I change the room with you?
Clearly....
Actually, the water comes well.
But I'm scare of ghost.
Let me change the room, please~
Shall we sleep together?
Really?
It's already morning in a few hours.
I'll went in the morning.
Sure!!
I'm fine now.
I'll also save on accommodation costs.
You can join with me.
I don't want the room now.
That's alright.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Please.
Thanks.
By the way, your face is not familiar at all.
What are you doing here?
I'll get money....
I mean I'm on traveling.
And tomorrow, Mister......
Can I call "You"?
Our age probably wasn't that much different.
I'm Nemo.
I'm Sun.
What's your plan tomorrow?
I'll go to island.
Arthid Island.
Do you know there?
Of course!!
I'll go there too!
Really?
Can I go with you?
Pleaseeeeee
Sure!!
But you've to sleep early.
I want to get the first boat.
Okay, deal!
Please bring me with you.
I find the guide whole day.
If not you, I'll be bad.
Okay.
Why is your face so familiar?
Have we met before?
I think no.
It's so beatiful.
Isn't it?
I really love this place so much.
So fresh!!
What's that noise?
Bro!
Do you come to see P'Arthid?
Do you know him?
Of course!
How can I meet him?
Go back!
No!
If you pay, I'll go then.
Pay for what?
Just go back to Bangkok!
How dare you chasing me?
You'll know who am I.
What do you want from me?
Do you see my dad?
He was interested in collecting debts and releasing that stupid loan.
I said go back to Bangkok!
Don't chase me, I'll go soon.
Or if you want to go back a lot, take 10 million back to my father.