The legendary search
for the next top models and actors
that reshaped the Thai entertainment
and fashion industries is back.
Join me, Kim Goodburn,
on this historic new journey.
This is The Face Men Thailand Season 4.
Last week, Team Mentor Pancake-Ananda
executed a flawless campaign strategy
and snatched the ultimate victory.
Kimhan from Team Mentor Pancake-Ananda.
So this is what victory smells like.
Remember this.
Forcing Mentor Off
to send Mew to the Black Room.
While Mentor Mile sent Gluf
since he can't walk the Final Walk anyway.
I'm no longer eligible, so he sent me in.
Is that so?
Do you want to save him?
You can go get him.
Gluf was ultimately saved
by Mentor Jes and Bible.
And Mew was finally eliminated.
Gluf, you're a survivor.
What kind of amulet do you have?
The Sacred Gluf?
The winner
of The Face Men Thailand Season 4
will collaborate with Clear Thailand.
He will receive a one-year supply
of Clear Ice Cool Menthol,
and get the chance to work
with Vaseline Thailand.
Plus, he'll receive
Vaseline SPF50+ PA++++,
Gluta Hyaluronic Acid,
Photoage Defense UV Serum
free for an entire year.
He will also collaborate with AXE
and receive a year's supply
of personal care products.
Bearbeary, only the wearers feel it.
Premium wear for every style,
featuring top design and innovation.
They'll award a 100,000-baht gift voucher.
Strive for perfection
with a membership to Hotman Fitness.
Including an 18-month
personal training program.
Plus a 200,000-baht package
from V Design Clinic.
Get ready to step onto the national screen
through a collaboration
with Channel 3 HD, Thailand.
And sign an acting contract
with Kantana Group Public Company Limited,
Thailand's leading producer
of dramas and films.
Hello, everyone.
- Hello!
Welcome back to The Face Men Thailand,
Week six!
Wow, time flies, doesn't it?
Let's leave all the negativity behind.
We're living in the present now.
My eyes are on the prize.
By now, I believe
you all have enough experience
to tackle whatever comes your way.
If it's a master class or a campaign,
you're ready for the challenge.
Today, we have two mentors
here to guide you
through the master class.
Give it up
for Mentor Pancake and Mentor Jes.
All right. We have a special twist today.
We're jumping straight
into the master class challenge.
Oh, straight to the brief.
No class today?
Guess we're pros now, no learning needed.
I have no idea.
This is totally unpredictable.
Today, our contestants
must use every skill
they've learned so far
to win this master class.
To reveal today's brief, let's welcome
the man bringing us the challenge.
Welcome Pongpisut Limgul,
Commercial Lead for Personal Care
Thailand, Cambodia, and Laos at Unilever!
PONGPISUT LIMGUL
Oab, what kind of challenge
do you have for the guys today?
Today's brief is "The Gravity Scent."
You'll be shooting
a reverse fashion video,
inspired by
the AXE Fine Fragrance Collection TVC
starring Mark Tuan.
What exactly is The Gravity Scent?
It's the scent of our AXE Fine Fragrance,
Blue Lavender.
Co-created with world-class perfumers,
for a premium fragrance
that lasts 72 hours.
A scent so magnetic, it defies gravity.
Essentially,
this AXE Fine Fragrance Collection
has an "Anti-Gravity" effect.
In the commercial,
Mark Tuan exudes charm and confidence.
Most importantly, he's being himself.
He attracts and defies gravity.
Everything around him
is drawn straight to him.
The concept is simple,
but execution is difficult.
You just have to go for it.
For today's reverse fashion video,
we're honored to have a top fashion
photographer in Thailand and Asia.
He'll also be joining us
as a guest judge today.
Welcome Nat Prakobsantisuk!
NAT PRAKOBSANTISUK
TOP FASHION PHOTOGRAPHER
Nat, for today's reverse fashion video,
how are we shooting this?
The guys will have to walk backward.
Meanwhile,
the prop team will shower them
with flower petals.
We'll then edit the footage in reverse.
The real challenge here
is pulling off that backward walk.
You need to calculate
and control every muscle.
And place your feet exactly
like you're walking forward.
Walking backward,
but making it look forward.
How on earth do you pull that off?
Easier said than done, right?
While you're walking backward,
you still have to serve it to the camera
and exude absolute charisma.
Make the audience feel
that your charm defies gravity,
so much so that objects float towards you.
I can barely walk straight.
I trip all the time,
and now I have to walk backwards?
But today, we have
another very special guest judge.
Please welcome Master Mentor Adam!
- Hello.
M.R. CHALERMCHATRI YUKOL
Having Master Mentor Adam
as a judge today,
I just hope the odds are in my favor.
Adam, any advice for the guys
in today's master class?
I want you to enjoy it. Have fun with it.
In past challenges,
you've all looked so stiff and stressed.
I get it, but you need to loosen up.
If you have fun,
your true potential will shine through.
You all made it this far for a reason.
The question is, how do you show it off?
You can only deliver
if you genuinely enjoy the moment.
All right, before we kick off
today's master class,
let's get some quick advice
from our mentors.
Mentor Jes, any words of wisdom
for the guys?
This is tough.
- It's incredibly hard.
- True.
You have to be hyper-aware
of your space and your purpose.
And what you're feeling.
You need a clear storyline.
Everyone's will be completely different.
That uniqueness
is where your true charm lies.
Figure out exactly what vibe
you want to project.
And own it with confidence.
Stay sharp on every single step.
You have to control every backward stride.
Control your body, your face,
everything simultaneously.
No dead eyes. Stay focused.
Keep the story alive in your mind.
Short and sweet.
"Stay sharp on every single step."
That felt personal.
To sum up today's master class brief,
"The Gravity Scent,"
all contestants will be shooting
a reverse fashion video today.
You have to walk the runway backward.
And you only get two takes.
Each take consists
of two continuous scenes.
Scene one, deliver our tagline,
"AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection."
Right after that is scene two.
You need to strut out,
looking like a quintessential AXE guy.
Finally, the footage will be reversed
to create a final cut that showcases
the magnetic pull of the fragrance.
Making objects around you defy gravity.
The tagline is in Thai again today.
It will be tough.
But I really want to win.
Are you ready?
- Ready!
Then get ready for
The Gravity Scent master class!
I'm ready. I won't let the pressure
get me. Just enjoy and have fun.
I'll try my best. Going all in.
That's the game plan.
Wish me luck.
Welcome back
to The Gravity Scent master class.
In today's brief,
the contestants need to walk the runway
to showcase
a fragrance that defies gravity,
with AXE Blue Lavender.
Let's bring out our first contestant.
Give it up for Bonus.
- Oh, wow!
- Nice.
- Go ahead.
- Oh, wow!
So damn handsome.
Don't forget, you only get two takes.
I went in first,
and that took some pressure off.
I just went in, did a little dance,
and loosened up.
I showed them everything I've got.
First take. Whenever you're ready.
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
Is his pace too slow?
- It looks like he's creeping.
- Okay, all right.
It looks like he's just sliding backwards.
Should he stride instead?
Cut!
It will play in reverse.
Oh, if he throws it,
it will reverse back into his hand.
- Like he grabs it. Yes.
- Like this.
- Like it flew back to his hand!
- Yes!
Clever! I like it.
One last take, Bonus.
Whenever you're ready. Action!
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
His delivery is so confident.
- Nailed it.
- So confident.
- Great delivery.
- Good pacing.
With his whole look,
I think he's a perfect fit for AXE.
He's one of my top picks.
He totally embodies the product.
Let's move on to the next contestant.
Donut. First take.
Three, two, one, action!
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
- Dead.
- The product blocked your face.
I didn't realize it in the first take.
I just went with the pose
that felt the most natural.
I chose that pose,
but ended up blocking my face.
Lesson learned, for sure.
You only have one take left, Donut.
Whenever you're ready. Action!
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
This brief really suits Donut.
He's giving pure edge,
masculinity, and cool vibes.
I really see his potential.
- Yes, great confidence.
- Better than I thought.
Donut killed it today.
I didn't expect him to pull this off.
He was so sharp and focused.
Not a single moment
of panic or hesitation.
Next up, Leo!
Here comes the Oppa.
Hello.
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
Oppa nailed the tagline! I'm thrilled.
Was his pronunciation perfect? No.
But it was cute in Oppa's style.
Damn, he designed the walk.
I thought he would struggle
with the lines, but his walk…
No, no. Take two will be better, trust me.
Wow, our Oppa is full of surprises today.
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
He has a gorgeous smile.
Once he relaxed, he completely delivered.
Leo really hit it out of the park here.
And his natural charm
really shone through.
I think Leo is a strong contender.
Fourth up, please welcome Gluf.
- Hello.
First take, Gluf. Action!
He sprayed so much that it left a stain.
He sprayed it too close.
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
- His eyes look a bit dead.
- Right.
- Now…
- He shouldn't have turned.
He shouldn't have turned his head.
He threw off his balance.
Gluf still looks awkward and out of place.
He needs to remember,
this is The Face. It's a competition.
You can't make mistakes.
But he keeps making them.
Gluf, try being yourself.
You don't have to act
like James Bond to be cool.
Just be yourself.
That might work much better.
Take two. Whenever you're ready, action!
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
He's still not projecting…
- Not enough energy or confidence.
- Right.
Gluf is totally overthinking it.
And he's still holding back
his true personality.
If he would only let loose,
he would do so much better.
Let's bring out
the next contestant, Lincoln.
Okay, and I'll do a spin like this.
He's choreographing his own shot.
That's so extra.
It's very creative. I love it.
But it might be too ambitious
for a limited time.
It left too much room for error.
AXE Fine Fragrance Premium.
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection.
- Wasted take.
- "Premium…"
I was a bit worried at first,
and I was overthinking everything.
How to walk, how to sit,
and how it'd look in reverse.
I focused so much on the perfect shot
that I totally blanked.
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
Oh, he's doing too much.
The concept requires effortless cool.
So his performance felt
way too over-the-top.
I was like…
It might work for another campaign,
but for today's concept,
it completely missed the mark.
I did that on purpose.
I made it harder on purpose
to test my limits.
Next up, Kimhan.
I have to admit, I was so stiff.
My mouth and throat were completely dry.
I just didn't feel like myself today.
The pressure got to me.
Ready? Action!
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
Kimhan did great. Flawless and so natural.
Oh, boy.
- Oh, wow!
- So good!
I'm so sick of Kimhan.
He kills every single campaign.
He's so smooth, I'm kind of jealous.
But damn, he's good.
Take two. Action!
AXE Fine Fragrance,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
Perfect. He nailed it.
I love it. Everything was on point.
He kept the energy up.
- Take two looked much more relaxed.
- Right.
But just now, correct me if I'm wrong,
did he say the full tagline?
He missed a bit of it.
- He missed the word "Collection."
- Okay.
- So, I'll leave that up to the judges.
- Oh, boy!
- The judges will look at the big picture.
Talk about turning an opportunity
into a disaster.
What a shame.
Next up, Peem.
Take one. Action!
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unstoppable 72-hour protection.
I tried not to stress.
Just let go and gave it my all.
I'm just here to have fun and relax.
Take two. Action.
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent…
Protecting…
The tagline strikes again, guys.
It's tough when you have
to focus on so many things.
Next up, Pom.
Action!
I was nervous, but I love showing off.
Like, "Watch me work." I loved it.
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
Pom came in so confident.
He's intimidating.
When he walked in, everyone was like…
"Careful now, don't let him lock in."
Take two. Action!
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
Nice.
Pom was another favorite.
His presentation
was unique and totally natural.
He did exceptionally well in this class.
Let's welcome
our ninth contestant, Manyoo!
Take one, Manyoo. Action!
I knew I was going to crush it today.
I already planned out all my movements.
All right, I'm ready.
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent, unexpected…
My mind went blank.
Everything went quiet, and I…
I just couldn't. "Get it together. Focus."
Take two. Action!
AXE Fine Fragrance,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
Honestly, he did a great job.
It was perfectly balanced.
Overall, great.
Manyoo and AXE are a perfect match.
If he had more time to practice
and really understand the product,
Manyoo would've totally crushed it.
And now, for our final contestant.
Come on out, Rome!
- Good luck.
- Go.
- Go get ready.
- Hello.
Take one. Action!
I just went with the flow.
Totally improvised. I just did
whatever felt right in the moment.
But in my head, I knew I had
to keep it cool and edgy.
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent, unexpected…
Seventy-two-hour protection.
- Yes.
- That turn gave major Keanu Reeves vibes.
Damn! He nailed it!
Here he comes. He nailed it.
His body, his hair… Everything was just…
Perfect. Giving total Yakuza vibes.
Take two, Rome. Action!
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
I loved the second take.
He looked relaxed, confident, and smooth.
That turn was effortless.
Total confidence.
He gave a less-is-more performance
with maximum impact.
He totally got
how hand placement and posture
made the reverse shot look perfect.
Cut!
Crushed it, Rome.
Well done!
Top three?
Hearing the comments
and everyone's reactions…
I definitely have a shot.
Don't sleep on me, I'm serious.
Bring it on.
All right,
all ten of our contestants
just presented
a scent that defies gravity,
courtesy of AXE Blue Lavender.
Before we announce the results,
let's hear what the judges
and mentors have to say.
Let's start with Oab.
I loved it.
You all presented AXE incredibly well.
You brought the confidence,
and most importantly, it was fun.
You all exceeded my expectations today.
Everyone looks sharper and more mature.
For just a few weeks of growth,
this is fantastic. Excellent work.
Watching you all
from day one has been a joy.
I'm thrilled you've made it this far.
And my favorite part today
was how entertaining you were.
I had a blast today.
All our guys did amazingly well.
It was beyond expectations.
I didn't think
you could improve this much.
Really brilliant.
Next, we'll announce the top three
who stood out the most
in today's master class,
The Gravity Scent.
Oab, who are
our top three contestants today?
All right, the first person is…
Kimhan.
AXE Fine Fragrance,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
The second person is…
Manyoo.
AXE Fine Fragrance,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
And our third and final person…
Rome.
AXE Fine Fragrance Collection,
premium scent,
unexpected 72-hour protection.
Let's hear some quick comments
from the judges and mentors
on why these three made the cut.
Got to hand it to them.
They served confidence and cool.
They had their own unique swagger.
They were totally themselves.
That coolness and confidence
really came through to us as we watched.
Excellent work.
All three of them made me feel…
Especially Rome, I have to commend him…
He made me feel like there was magic
happening during that spin.
Putting his walk aside,
Manyoo has incredible charm.
You should be acting in dramas.
Your movements were so captivating.
Kimhan, you know your angles.
With one smile, you ooze charm.
Judging today was tough.
Kimhan, you had fun
and entertained us today.
I saw that energy.
That energy radiates.
Keep that up. Great job.
Manyoo, you fumbled the first take.
But you managed to bounce back.
You have charm, and you weaponized it.
In the second take, you brought the power.
Even with the mistakes…
You made up for them
by doing everything else right.
Rome, you exceeded my expectations.
You made it look effortless,
but it wasn't.
Unbelievable. You really came back
to reclaim your throne.
Today was incredible. Truly amazing.
Great job, everyone. Today was fantastic.
I saw real fire and passion today.
Everyone here has so much potential
when they step out there.
All right, and we have
a special prize today, right, Oab?
Yes. Today's winner
of The Gravity Scent master class…
will receive a one-year supply of AXE.
And a 20,000 baht cash prize from AXE.
Now, it's time to reveal the results.
Oab.
Who performed the best
in today's master class?
The winner of The Gravity Scent
master class is…
Rome.
Hold on a second.
This is the scent of a winner.
Yes.
He's a huge threat.
Because his natural vibe
is his secret weapon.
All right, as for the next campaign,
we'll all have to wait and see.
Today's master class
might not have been our strong suit.
But I believe we can make
a comeback in the campaign.
Keep going, guys. Stay strong.
But if you slip up, sorry not sorry.
Please be nice to this little puppy.
What are you doing?
Just shopping on Shopee.
So much stuff. Need anything?
They've got discount codes
and free shipping right now.
Order some AXE for me.
- Every scent.
- Every scent?
- Yes, all of them.
- Buying on Shopee is the best value.
Look, free shipping codes too.
I told you. Shopee has it all,
cheap, fast, and guaranteed.
I'll download the app ASAP.
Okay.
- Need anything else?
- That was fast.
We've come so far.
I want to give it my absolute all.
I'm thrilled. I never thought
I would make it this far.
I'm so proud of myself.
Coming hot off a win last episode,
and we're definitely going to win again.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
Welcome to today's campaign.
I'm sure you've all noticed
how massive our studio is today.
So I guarantee you,
this campaign is going to be epic.
I want this so bad.
We can't afford to lose. We have to win.
We'll make it happen.
You're going to see me
speed and drift like mad.
Now, let's invite the mentors
from all three teams to hear the brief.
Welcome Mentor Pancake,
Mentor Off, and Mentor Mile.
- Hello.
You look good.
Still looking handsome.
It's been a while, but welcome back, Mile.
All right, today we have someone else here
to make a major announcement
for all of us.
Please welcome Cindy.
Hello.
SIRINYA BISHOP
MODEL, ACTRESS, HOST, ACTIVIST
Oh, no! Cindy again.
Here we go again. What new rule is this?
I've been sent by the Master Mentor
and the producers.
One contestant has lost the right
to a spot in the Final Walk.
The show wants this resolved
once and for all.
- Before we move forward.
- All right.
- Gluf, please step forward.
Confused. Anxious. Speechless.
Should I even continue?
We have divided opinions here.
Mentor Off believes
Gluf doesn't deserve
a spot in the Final Walk.
Because you missed a campaign.
Honestly, all of them deserve a chance.
I don't know why he can't let it go.
Mentor Pancake and Mentor Ananda
think it wasn't on purpose,
because he fell ill.
He did nothing wrong.
I don't think that's fair to him.
- So the heartless one thinks one way.
- Hey, attacking me again?
And the kind ones don't?
Anyone trying to eliminate him
might be heartless too.
- Oh no!
Thank you, Pancake.
Sending Gluf in wasn't great.
But what happened
was just part of my game strategy.
Mentor Mile, what's your take on this?
Nobody catches chickenpox
on purpose, right?
But the fact that he called us immediately
to let the production know,
it showed his level of responsibility.
For a 16-year-old to call
and sort it out himself,
he handled it very maturely.
Why let someone so heartless
try to kick him off the show?
He wasn't wrong. Just unlucky.
I'm not heartless at all.
If I were heartless,
I would've eliminated him.
All right. This isn't ending anytime soon.
Mentor Pancake,
what are your thoughts on this?
I think we should give him
a chance to come back.
Fine by me. But can I get two spots?
Meaning he gets one extra spot
for the Final Walk, right?
Can I get an extra spot too? Make it two.
You're not here to ask for an extra spot.
You're here to decide Gluf's fate.
- Okay.
- Play fair.
You got a chance to save your team.
What about my team?
They fought tooth and nail.
Today's meeting has one agenda.
Everything else is off the table.
All right. Based on this, we clearly
aren't reaching an easy conclusion.
Excuse me for a moment.
This feels like a huge deal.
I didn't think missing the Final Walk
would turn into something this big.
PIYARAT KALJAREUK
- I knew it.
- Oh, wow!
Wow, Tae looks sharp today.
When he walked in,
I was like, "Here we go."
We just had a little debate, Tae.
Mentor Pancake and Mentor Mile
want to give Gluf a chance.
Mentor Off agrees, but on what condition?
- One extra Final Walk spot.
- Honestly, this shouldn't be an issue.
- You shouldn't bring it up.
- He's pulling a fast one.
Off is always pulling things like this.
Always playing tactics. It's typical.
Calling me a schemer isn't right.
Mile probably taught you that.
Such a sneaky move.
We were literally just talking about Gluf.
How did you make this
about your own team, Off?
Fair or not, we've made it this far.
Every time he goes
to the elimination room, he survives.
Dude has nine lives.
What amulet are you wearing?
Why are you invincible?
I was numb. I was speechless.
I didn't know how to act.
The bottom line is…
Gluf has the right to enter the selection
process and do the Final Walk.
If Mentor Mile chooses him.
- Hear that?
- Yes. Good for you.
All right. So that means, Gluf…
You're eligible for the Final Walk.
- Congratulations again.
- Congratulations.
That gave me so much motivation.
To fight for everyone who gave me
this chance and cheered me on.
If he ends up representing my team…
Whoever it is, I'll be happy.
I'm proud of my whole team.
All right, and that concludes
today's special ruling.
Any questions from the mentors?
- Anything else?
- No, nothing.
- Got a problem with that?
- Not at all. I accept it.
Listen, everyone on the show
just helped Gluf out.
But I only want to know one thing.
Will Mile help Gluf
make it to the Final Walk?
All right, let's get into
today's challenge.
Let's meet the person
presenting today's brief.
Charin Siriananchai,
Vice President of Passenger Car
Marketing, Toyota Motor Thailand.
CHARIN SIRIANANCHAI
VICE PRESIDENT, PASSENGER CAR
MARKETING, TOYOTA MOTOR THAILAND
Today, your challenge is
a runway fashion video.
The theme is "Drive the Runway."
I want you all
walking alongside our models.
But today, our models aren't human.
They're cars. The ones right behind you.
We have three models today.
First is the Yaris Cross Nightshade,
right back there.
It's a special edition,
rocking all-black accents.
You can notice the metro black style,
pillars, and side mirrors.
Even the roof is also black.
This creates a sleek, two-tone look.
Paired with the Cement Grey body.
- It really makes the car stand out.
- Right.
And it's super striking
with the Metro Stylish front grille.
Exclusive to the Nightshade edition.
Model two is the Corolla Cross GR Sport.
This one is sportier
and way more striking.
It has a fresh front grille design.
Sporty interior seats.
Emblazoned with the GR logo
and striking red seatbelts.
A newly tuned GR steering wheel.
Sport suspension for a confident
and thrilling drive every time.
Finally, the Toyota bZ4X.
A fully electric SUV,
imported straight from Japan.
This car is top-tier quality.
You'll notice the front design
really highlights the front grille.
It's got a hammerhead design.
The headlights sweep across,
giving it a futuristic edge.
Incredible ride quality,
thanks to the e-TNGA platform.
Purpose-built for EVs from the ground up.
Smooth at low speeds.
And super stable when you floor it.
Inside, the bZ4X is spacious enough
to seat five comfortably.
It features a massive
14-inch center screen,
connected to Apple CarPlay
and Android Auto.
Plus all the smart driver-assist features
of a modern EV.
This is wild to me.
I've never done anything like this.
What are we going to do with nine cars?
There's only four of us.
There are too many cars.
And today, directing our fashion video…
Give it up for Tim Phansiri!
Hello!
PHANSIRI SIRIVEJCHAPHAN
THAILAND'S LEADING FASHION PHOTOGRAPHER
Tim, what's the concept
for today's fashion video?
Today, you're putting on
a runway show alongside the cars.
We're turning this parking lot
into your runway.
You need to clearly sell
the attitude of your assigned car.
And this is the first
in the history of The Face Thailand.
Models sharing the runway with cars.
You must showcase
the car's interior features.
At least one feature per person.
Then, walk the runway
to show off its sleek exterior.
Each team must drive at least one car
within the designated area.
You can drive it yourselves,
or our crew can do it for you.
Each mentor gets 20 minutes to rehearse,
and 15 minutes of shared rehearsal time.
The challenge is "Drive the Runway."
We won the master class,
so we get to pick the order first.
Which order do you want?
I would rather take the second team.
All right, you've earned that right.
So, pick your desired lineup.
That's honestly not very fair.
Getting more time is a huge advantage.
So we only get to pick the running order?
Your slot today also determines
which car you'll be shooting with.
The cars are completely randomized.
Which team do you want to go first?
- I would like to pick Team Panda.
- Okay.
Not surprised at all. Honestly, it's fine.
We won't have to sit around
under pressure.
We'll do our best and win.
That means Mentor Mile's team
is going last.
I'm happy to sit back, relax,
and brainstorm while I wait.
Thanks a lot, Rome.
I need one rep from each team
to step forward.
Grab your boards.
Let's see which car
you'll be working with.
Ready? Three, two, one. Reveal!
Oh, okay!
- Cross.
- Yaris Cross.
- Yes.
This model is perfect for us.
We definitely have a shot.
We can play around with so much here.
Going first is Team Pancake-Ananda.
You'll be shooting with the bZ4X.
Second up is Mentor Off's team.
You get the Yaris Cross Nightshade.
And finally, Mentor Mile's team!
You get the Corolla Cross GR Sport.
Everyone, go get ready.
Let's do this!
Give it 250 percent today. Go all out!
We're on location today
at a massive studio.
It's pretty impressive.
We have to manage the space,
and there are cars involved.
So this is going to be
quite the challenge.
- Hello.
- Hello, Pancake.
Let me ask straight away.
What exactly are you looking for?
I want the contestants' walk
to reflect the car's character.
They need to blend in seamlessly
and highlight the car's best features.
Any specific features
you want us to highlight?
- The front has a hammerhead design.
- There?
- The front grille, the headlights.
- Right.
The body color contrast…
- It's striking, but still very classy.
- Right.
We want an executive look.
- But modern and energetic.
- Understood.
Noted.
About the lights…
- I'll let you know what we need.
- Sure.
- And the music?
- It should be upbeat, with an urban vibe.
Think street hip-hop,
but with an executive vibe.
Could you show us the car?
Just a quick look.
- Sure.
- All right.
For a fashion video,
I think they want versatility.
We're playing businessmen,
but with a Gen Z edge.
It's a perfect mix
that suits my boys completely.
And we got
the Toyota Yaris Cross Nightshade.
It totally fits our team.
It's urban, stylish, and sporty.
I can picture the blocking
and how to pose the guys.
I know exactly what vibe to go for.
- Start the clock.
- Okay, let's go.
Is the core focus
the runway or the fashion video?
Or should we balance both equally?
I think the true format
- is a fashion video.
- Okay.
- A blend of both.
- Okay. Blend.
For the Toyota Yaris Cross,
the features we want to highlight
are mostly on the exterior.
We're open to interior shots too, though.
You could also emphasize
its compact SUV features.
It has great utility.
The seats fold to expand the cabin.
You can showcase all that.
Here's the big question.
What do I need to do to win?
The key is bringing out the best.
- In both the car and the models.
- Right.
You must reflect the car's image
- according to the brief.
- Right.
For the Toyota Yaris Cross Nightshade,
they gave us three cars for this campaign.
So we need to maximize their potential.
We have to present the cars perfectly
without making it look too salesy.
Wow, gorgeous car.
Give me a second to check it out.
Before I asked my questions,
I took a look at the car.
It's not against the rules.
I'm sure other teams did it too.
I really like the car.
I just wanted to get
a real feel for it first.
Let's get straight to it. First question.
What new elements of the GR Sport
do you want highlighted, Charin?
First, the design.
The grille is exclusive to this model.
- Plus the GR logo.
- Okay. Right.
The interior has sport seats
with the GR logo on the headrests.
The GR logo on the steering wheel
reflects its superior handling.
Both the steering and the suspension
have been specially tuned by GR.
How do you define "sporty"?
How do you define that vibe?
What do you want to see in this challenge?
Energetic, responsive,
and totally under control.
About the cars modeling alongside guys…
What's the ratio? Who gets more focus?
Or is it up to my design?
Balance the fashion video
and the runway aspects.
Are you judging
mostly on the live fashion show
or the final video?
It will be a mix of both.
Last question.
If my boys win,
does the mentor get a discount on the car?
I'm confident
that our concept works perfectly.
It won't get completely changed
like it did with that dining table runway.
Hello.
- Hello.
Okay.
Before going on set,
we had already briefed them
on exactly who needed to do what.
I have to give them credit.
They kept their cool.
We're going to walk back deeper…
- To shift the mood.
- Yes.
- Walk back a little deeper.
We were completely on the same page today.
So working together was easy.
The boys had their own creative ideas,
so I let them run with them.
I just want them to try out
what they genuinely want to do.
As long as it fits
within the framework of our show.
Five, four, three, two, action!
Now, Donut starts walking in.
Once he reaches this mark,
can we bring the lights up?
The tricky part was the cars' light cues.
For the opening, we wanted it to go,
boom, and the lights flash on.
But for the lights to flash,
we had to start the cars at the same time.
We had to sync up
so many moving parts, fast.
This round really tested
how we manage time and talent.
I think the judges will see it.
The other teams are done for.
We'll set the bar way too high.
Drivers! Can we do
the first pattern, the Y-formation?
If we can open with that,
it'll be creative, high impact.
The client will love it.
At the start, Tim. For the lighting…
- A-B-C-D, three times, please.
- Got it.
Rehearsals were a bit of a mess.
First pattern was right.
But the second pattern?
That was another story.
Why not park in the middle?
They kept driving in circles.
We had to show
the storyboard to the drivers first,
so they would understand
the patterns we needed.
Can I have extra time?
Oh, you stopped the clock.
Thank you.
Wishing you abundance and prosperity.
I'm super stressed, but that's okay.
Since they stopped the clock,
we should be fine.
One, two, three, hit the lights!
Let's go, let's go. Oh, wow!
You're making me want to buy the car.
I was totally blown away
by Off's blocking.
I know we're going to kill it.
Pop the trunk.
Yo, what's up, man?
I won the master class,
so I'm not flopping now.
I'm owning this episode.
Come on, guys. Follow me.
There's no Team Mile today.
We're Team Corolla Cross GR Sport.
Models and drivers gather here.
Let me brief you real quick.
I called them all over
to look at this storyboard
because we're all one team.
We weren't just here to compete.
At least, I wasn't.
My job was to make this show
look spectacular in the time we had.
If you mess up the real take,
it's unforgivable.
Mile laid out every single step for us.
No mistakes, guys.
Gluf, get out of the car.
Keep it energetic. Pose at the front.
Now, walk over to Manyoo.
Walk with confidence, on the beat.
Manyoo, get ready.
The blocking was so complicated
that the mentor didn't have time
to walk me through the details.
So we had to improvise
and add our own flair.
Leo stumbled a lot during rehearsal
because he kept doubting himself.
But with his experience, I know
he'll deliver when the cameras roll.
Hold on, let's restart.
You guys forgot the choreography.
Cut the music.
At the beginning,
we have to build it up slowly.
Don't build muscle memory
around a mistake. If it's wrong, restart.
Okay, pan to Peem. Buckle up.
That seatbelt pull felt stiff.
It wasn't smooth.
It made me look totally rushed.
Like I rushed the whole sequence.
Even the way I grabbed
the wheel was totally off.
Rehearsal mistakes happen,
but the show must go on.
I'm giving this campaign my all
to prove I deserve this spot.
Welcome back
to the Drive the Runway campaign!
Today, each team will be joined
by very special models,
the new Toyota cars.
But before we kick off today's campaign,
let me introduce our two guest judges.
Both are multi-talented
models, actors, and singers.
Mew Suppasit and Tul Pakorn!
- Hello!
- Welcome!
Our first team is geared up and ready.
Let's bring out
the first team of the campaign,
Team Pancake-Ananda!
Going first with a one-take long shot?
It's insane. Even pros struggle with this.
The most crucial thing
is the boys' energy.
Are the walkies ready in all the cars?
Middle black car is ready.
Oh, they've got walkies.
They even brought their own.
The white car is ready.
I have to pull out every trick.
So many moving parts.
Camera angles, the products,
and the models. It was a lot to focus on.
The white car.
The black car.
The gray car.
The timing was spot on.
It was a perfect opening.
So nerve-wracking!
- Great inner energy.
- Agree.
Donut has so much charisma.
He wasn't overacting, just being himself.
Donut is hot.
- Blond suits him.
- Very much.
That opening was killer. Donut killed it.
His charisma really popped,
especially with that new blond hair.
He has improved so much
since the beginning.
He nailed the look for this brief.
The car window wouldn't roll down.
Donut couldn't get the window down.
So the interior features we needed
to show off were completely missed.
The camera didn't catch him.
Either the camera missed his cue,
or he forgot to look into the camera.
- Did it open during rehearsal?
- Yes! I'm so confused.
It was fine in rehearsal.
When I got inside,
it was supposed to roll down.
I was supposed to touch the screen,
and the camera would shoot
through the window.
It'd catch me using the screen,
and I'd work the camera.
But during the actual take,
the engine was off,
and the camera had already moved
to Lincoln.
I think we did okay.
Usually, when you do this a lot,
you stop getting nervous.
But I still was.
Let's go. Time to show off
the spacious interior.
The camera was at the rear,
and Lincoln turned to face it.
Lincoln just couldn't focus.
His eyes were darting everywhere.
It was a live, one-take shot.
But I think we still stuck to the plan.
You look gorgeous at the front.
Kimhan was incredibly confident.
He delivered it perfectly.
When he added his own flair,
it became a very memorable shot.
His instinct for interacting
with the audience is unteachable.
If it were any other guy
besides Kimhan doing that,
it wouldn't have looked nearly as sexy.
The movement is cool, but a bit too calm.
This blocking is sick.
I love the backward walk with the car.
The timing of reversing
and slowly lifting his leg,
that was gorgeous.
Right?
This is the shot the client can use.
For a fashion show or a fashion video.
Guys in the car, get ready.
Lincoln, Donut.
Donut nailed the ending.
But from afar,
Kimhan completely
and effortlessly stole the spotlight.
Kimhan really stood out
and completely overshadowed the rest.
How they play with the headlights is cool.
Love it. Using the lights
really made everything pop.
I'm done stressing now.
When I stress, I dance.
So I danced.
I tried to think about
what they wanted to do
to bring fresh energy.
The judges were watching so intensely.
None of them were vibing with us.
We were dancing and hyping it up.
Everyone was dead silent.
It was dry. Like, bone dry.
Bring it, bring the energy!
Vibe with each other to hype ourselves up.
So I cranked up the energy.
The car has an executive vibe.
It required a sense of maturity.
These moves kind of clashed
with that mature vibe.
Something fell off.
- He didn't break character.
- He kept going.
I noticed because the wire
was dangling behind me.
I didn't care. I just kept going.
I'm a pro.
I handled that crisis well today.
That was intense.
- It really was, Tae.
- So intense.
With a massive long take like this.
From a production standpoint,
it's incredibly hard.
I was like this.
I wanted to bite my nails.
The suspense was killing me.
Good show.
Very different from the first walk
or the dining table walk,
which felt a bit conservative.
Mentor Pancake is done playing it safe.
Five, four, three, two.
If you can keep your cool
and get the job done,
I consider that being fully prepared.
Honestly, I was quite terrified.
Started and ended beautifully. Perfect.
Let's meet the second team.
Please welcome Mentor Off's team.
Team Pancake is very intimidating.
Now, it's up to our boys
to handle the pressure.
Come on, come on.
Once it started, my heart was pounding.
Give it energy! All right?
I just felt the power and let it out.
Through my hands, through my face.
Mostly here.
Hit me with the lights and the music.
I had fun, I enjoyed it.
Our car is
the Toyota Yaris Cross Nightshade.
Sporty, fun, and urban.
The first five seconds
were literally just his butt.
In a normal fashion theme,
you need to grab attention instantly.
They just keep swiping things.
We wanted the car to stand out.
But we forgot that we were facing
our backsides to the judges.
If the judges don't see it,
I'll voice it for them.
Wow, forming a Y for Yaris.
Hyping up your own team, huh?
Guiding the judges already?
Followed by presenting the wheels.
Absolutely beautiful.
I was owning the camera.
As soon as the camera panned down…
I walked over, cut in front,
and gave the car a touch.
But in the end, we absolutely loved
the Toyota Yaris Cross Nightshade.
Bonus!
- Yes.
A little magic show! A magic show!
I'm so proud! How was that?
We nailed it, right?
Hey, that's wow. That's chic.
A little touch of magic, but cute.
- When did they get in?
- Good angles.
It's all just angles.
I don't think the judges
even noticed that.
That the other two
were already in the car.
Pom and I had to get
into position behind the car.
Ready for the next scene.
It's spacious inside.
It fits two people comfortably.
We kept it fun, upbeat, and party-like.
Go for it, boys. Give your all.
For the Yaris Cross,
we have to showcase modernity.
Energy, paired with youthful
coolness and fun.
I switched the styles,
walked in with a fierce face.
I couldn't find the cam,
so I served face to Royal Mom instead.
Fierce eyes, serve face, strike a pose.
Oh, is this a crosswalk?
Wow, for Yaris Cross!
He's constantly guiding the judges.
Without all that guidance,
I wouldn't have noticed.
Well, speaking of that.
Ananda guided the judges last time.
That turn was way too close to the model.
I'm confident. I've got a special talent.
My runway walk was fierce.
This part is good.
This is good.
Just like before, sell the car.
In my head, I really love that car.
Nice wheels. I paced back and forth,
letting my character shine.
Booty down, booty up.
- Touching it like he's about to steal it.
- Right? My thoughts too.
- Looks dangerous.
- Suspicious.
- Might be the outfit and face.
- Sorry, I can change outfits, not my face.
Why touch the car?
- Appreciate the color, cement grey.
- Right.
The way they touched the car
killed the mood. Too sluggish.
When he touched the gray car
and the wheels too.
I think it wasn't sharp.
Trying too hard to sell something
makes people change the channel.
I loved the moment
they got in and let the car shine.
- These cars are our models too.
- Oh, the models.
We showed these men,
now it's time for the cars.
It felt a bit repetitive and dragged on.
It needed a real climax before the end.
It might feel a bit quiet
and lack the impact of the others.
But we felt it was super smooth.
He stepped out looking like a new man.
Where did his old clothes go?
I was quietly panicking in the car,
then stepped out feeling brand new.
- Oh, wow.
- Yes.
That was a quick change.
The new outfit should've had
a totally different vibe
from the original look.
Honestly, I didn't notice it,
but the narration sold it.
I have to praise Off.
He played the game perfectly on set.
My job was to get my boys
to the finish line. That's all.
Now I get why boxing matches
have commentators.
The music totally changed the mood.
It fell a bit flat right at the end.
It hurt the mood a little.
We're in the final episodes now.
I want us all to make it to the end.
Winning is another story. We'll see.
But overall, I'm happy.
I think everything
came together perfectly.
We just kept it cool
and ended with some handsome poses.
- The formation is stunning.
- Right.
A stunning ending.
I'm glad we gave them that energy.
All of them matched that energy perfectly.
I loved working on this.
That's a wrap.
They knew they had nailed it.
And they were glowing
as they walked off set.
They gave it their all and owned it.
Tough choice for the client and judges.
Because it was so fun to watch.
Give us a nice bow.
Okay.
- Do they look like car thieves?
- Yes.
- Still?
Hey, did you get the keys?
Judges, please have mercy
on these car thieves.
No stealing, just nailing the brief.
Thank you.
And now, the final team
for the Drive the Runway campaign.
Team Mentor Mile, come on out!
Come on!
- Hello.
All right, let's go. Go!
They're energetic.
I'm pretty confident in our plan.
It's stunning and totally unique.
Here we go. The show must go on.
Beat drop, lights on.
Next beat, lights on.
Fourth beat, lights on,
and cue the upbeat.
I mapped it to the music.
It is my favorite track of the three.
If this were a real commercial,
these beats are everything.
Gluf! Gluf!
Gluf hit the beat and passed it to Manyoo.
They looked confident. I'm happy.
We want to represent the brand.
Like, "These are our cars,
and we love them."
- That's good.
- They transition between characters well.
Team Mentor Mile's opening
gave me chills. It was intimidating.
I loved their transitions and pacing.
Everyone worked the camera perfectly.
They're presenting the product.
Selling the car without trying too hard.
Everything fell right into place.
Yes!
- Let's go.
- Is that the real honk?
Yes, it was to signal the next move.
Beep-beep! Off loved it, Pan loved it.
Everyone was thrilled, then we drove off.
It was sporty and active.
The transitions between the car
and the models
felt powerful.
Stunning. It made me want
to jump in that car too.
The lighting hit
at the exact right moment.
This is the winning shot.
They're crossing too. Crossing paths.
- Okay!
- Yes!
- Cross GR Sport.
The first part was a nine out of ten.
With so little time and such a huge crew,
perfection is impossible.
This is the Corolla Cross GR Sport.
It gives off an active vibe,
and the energy totally matches
what this car is all about.
- Oh, boy. That was so close.
- Oh, no!
Is the car going to bump into Leo?
Leo totally lost his composure too.
That little jolt really threw me off.
Peem looked so panicked on camera.
Peem hesitated, unsure how to help Leo.
So the whole thing started to fall apart.
- What just happened?
- Why did he drive over there?
- Did the driver miss his cue?
- Formation seems right.
The driver parked incorrectly.
What do we do now?
Wait, the car formation is completely off.
I was confused too.
No idea what they were trying
to showcase there.
That was wrong.
We rehearsed a crosswalk from both sides.
Looping back to hit the mark.
Reset. This part is crucial.
Manyoo, get out now, hurry!
Make it quick and energetic!
Energy, guys! Give me more energy!
Leo's walk was relaxed.
It wasn't working.
Oh, right.
That dead air lasted way too long.
We froze and stood there quite a while.
Leo and I completely lost our smiles.
Oh, boy.
That was bad.
I mean, I'm not mad, but…
If this were my gig
and we weren't filming live,
I would cuss them out.
I'm not joking.
But it's their first time.
I'll let it slide.
I just tried to keep it smooth
and tried to reconnect.
The second that door opened,
we got to own it.
Compared to how I used to be,
I think I did quite well.
What is Leo saying?
They're giving a flashmob vibe, right?
A bit cringey.
Leo's energy was insane.
He pushed through.
Leo kept the hype alive.
What was that? What's with the megaphone?
I'm so confused.
What were you even yelling?
You could see his confidence drop.
It totally killed his charisma.
Unlike the opening. Everything felt off.
It's like looking in a mirror.
I love this storytelling.
The taste level is completely there.
We needed something fresh for the show.
In the second half, we gave them space
to let their true personalities shine.
This stage should be
their playground to get creative.
Totally matched the car
with our characters.
Honestly, I've never given
a perfect performance.
But this time,
I would say I hit a solid 85.
- Nice.
- Wow, how did he hold that pose?
The ending was solid for me.
Everyone looked incredibly sharp.
It's hard to replicate rehearsal.
I was less nervous doing it live.
We already won.
We're definitely partying after this.
Okay.
Can I send the driver to the Black Room?
He totally messed up the formation.
Oh, no.
I wanted the cars to park perfectly.
To give the vibe that they're exploring
a new place together.
Honestly, I'm really rooting
for Team Mile.
Let me process exactly
what just happened out there.
I need to take a closer look
at that replay.
Got it.
What should I do?
Who should I send to the Black Room?
And now, we have one final show left.
If you're ready,
let's kick off the finale show!
It's week six, guys!
Show absolutely everything on the runway!
It's time to show us
what you're truly capable of.
Wow, the cars are so sick!
Whatever happens out there,
it's live, so own it with confidence.
Stay present in the moment.
- That woke me up!
- Woke me up!
- Right?
- Yes.
The honking and the high beams,
it just spiked the energy.
So hot!
That was good.
Altogether, impactful.
- They look great.
- Yes.
Each team served
a completely different vibe.
And that was good.
- And that concludes our finale runway!
- Okay.
They pulled it off well,
ten models and nine cars.
The crew really put their hearts
into this for our boys.
Now, let's hear
what the judges have to say.
This fashion video is the final product
that should be ready for the client.
We're going to find which team
delivered the smoothest run
with the fewest flaws.
Let's start with Mentor Pancake
and Ananda's team.
For Mentor Pancake and Ananda's team,
presenting the bZ4X…
It had a very calm yet powerful vibe.
Today's performance
was absolutely excellent.
Especially the movement.
The guys and the cars synced up perfectly.
The way you used the lights and the cars…
It elevated the performance,
making it super fun and thrilling.
- That's what I loved about it.
- Thank you.
It was a fantastic opening show
that really grabbed my attention.
Right from the moment
they walked down the stairs.
What really stuck with me was…
when Kimhan stepped back,
and the car followed, it was…
Wow, just amazing.
There were flaws, though.
The shot where we were supposed
to see inside the car…
That feature was totally lost.
Such a missed opportunity.
Donut has that raw, rugged energy.
So when it came to cars and machines,
he was totally in his element.
As for Lincoln, I have to say…
You need to be ready.
Sometimes his eyes go blank,
or he just lacks…
that sharpness the other guys have.
Pan's show really surprised me.
I could see Pan throw playing it safe
right out the window.
You stepped out of the box
and made it super fun to watch.
I'm just glad our whole team
managed to create something totally new.
Let's move on
to our second team, Mentor Off's.
The Yaris Cross
is a city car built for fun.
You presented both the cars
and the models so seamlessly.
It was a really fun show.
All the choreography,
it felt like it had a hidden meaning
to sell the car.
It's tough. It's neck-and-neck
with Pan's team.
Looking at all three teams overall,
Off played it the safest.
But doing that meant the guys
didn't have to carry a massive burden.
They looked cohesive,
with no one outshining the rest.
It was highly entertaining.
But I had an issue with the opening.
I saw their butts.
You should've drawn us
into the story a lot faster.
Overall, it dragged on a bit.
There were some surprising moments.
Touching the car totally killed the vibe.
Then came the outfit change later on,
which finally brought the energy back.
If Off hadn't narrated every single shot,
I'm not sure we would've known
what's going on.
Honestly, without the narration,
it would've been so flat.
Bonus is a very niche kind of handsome.
Rome and Pom are straight-up models.
But today, Bonus blended in perfectly
with Rome and Pom.
I really loved that.
All right, we've heard
the feedback for two teams.
Now for our final team,
Mentor Mile's team.
Yes, Mile's team represented
the Corolla Cross GR Sport.
I really want to praise that opening.
I could really feel the confidence.
The runway walk syncing
with the beat made it super fun.
The energy was felt.
However, the middle section
was completely disconnected.
They definitely stumbled a bit.
I really admire Mile's concept.
The storyline was crystal clear.
And the transitions
were incredibly smooth.
There was one shot that made
all of us go, "Wow."
Even if the middle section
got a little confusing,
it was just an ambitious
technical challenge.
Which killed the momentum slightly.
I agree with Cindy's feedback.
She caught every detail and didn't
hold back, be it praise or critique.
Mile's show looked incredibly strong.
And it was risky to have four models.
There were so many elements.
With all those cars and people,
it was very hard to pull off.
And they didn't handle it smoothly.
Manyoo looked incredibly handsome
and performed naturally today.
Peem was still a bit awkward, though.
But it's endearing. Hit or miss,
Peem always gives it his all.
I didn't expect much from Leo,
coming in with his rapper vibe.
But he was actually charming.
And Gluf really tried to project strength.
By the middle, it just fell apart.
Let's not kid ourselves.
I was really rooting for Mile today.
Even though
he probably didn't want my pity.
- I definitely did!
- I just wanted to cheer him on.
Off was solid and consistent.
But Pancake was the winner in my eyes.
I've watched Pancake's journey
since Season 6.
And seeing her this time,
I just want to say thank you.
I stepped out of my comfort zone.
It's a huge relief, honestly.
Charin, what does
today's winning team receive?
Today's winning team
will be featured on Toyota
Digital Billboards across Bangkok.
Awesome. Okay.
Fantastic!
And now, it's time
to announce the results.
Charin, which team won
Drive the Runway campaign?
The winner of today's campaign is
Mentor Off's team.
Thank you.
We gave the client exactly
what they wanted today.
I think that's what secured our win.
And for today,
a big thank you to our judges
for joining us to judge today's campaign.
Also, a special thanks
to Royal Mom and Tim…
for helping direct
our fashion video today.
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
- Glad to participate, thank you.
And last but not least,
thank you to all three of our mentors.
Thank you.
The product was the main key. I admit it.
It's a graceful defeat.
I'm sick of eliminating.
But if you want someone gone,
whisper it to me.
His decision would be fair.
But I'm not sure
which soap opera he's into right now.
Whatever he just watched,
he'll reuse the script.
You can't trust anyone.
Not a single soul today.
Greetings, greetings, and greetings.
Sorry, I'm a bit late.
The vibe was tense. I was like,
"Oh, man, what's going on?"
I couldn't read the room.
Have a seat. Sit down.
I was trying to read your vibe.
- Take a guess.
- Analyze him.
- Still handsome.
- Handsome.
He must be in a good mood.
No Black Room today.
We lost, you a-hole.
Are you serious?
We did all that and still lost?
Man. We did so well.
Was there really
another team better than us?
The situation was incredibly stressful.
Let's start with the opening.
What did you say? "Let's go, baby"?
Calling the cars "baby,"
it just didn't work.
He pointed out flaws,
and they were spot on.
We might have actually lost.
Moving on to Rome.
You stressed out again. Your face…
- It showed.
- Yes.
I don't know, I was just scared
of messing up the walk.
I thought then, "We probably lost."
But I didn't dare ask Off which team won.
I was afraid it would bring
everyone down even more.
Another thing, that final group pose.
You two did the exact same pose. Boom.
The exact same pose,
and I was like, "Oh, shit."
I told you to figure out an ending pose!
I completely tuned out
and stared at the floor.
Like I wasn't there.
I started thinking,
"What's the Black Room like?
What will I say?"
Who should I pick?
I don't know who to pick either.
It's stressful. Really?
We did so well in the end.
Do we really have to send
someone to the Black Room?
You seem so chill.
- Hello.
Today?
I tried to look like I was having fun,
but deep down I was worried.
Let me get straight to the point. Sorry.
The thing is…
We didn't win.
Just letting you know, we didn't win.
Ananda got straight to it.
Sharp and direct.
From what I heard,
our show was the most complete.
The best, show-wise.
But our mistakes were on
the client's technical side.
The car's functions.
The first flaw was the screen
in Donut's car, right?
And Lincoln's part.
The timing of opening the trunk
didn't sync with the camera.
But we have to accept it.
A mistake is a mistake, okay?
Call it bad luck. Call it whatever.
But we can't make excuses.
We just have to accept it.
Even if we couldn't fully control
everything.
Missing the brief was the biggest issue.
Because we're here
to deliver on the brief.
And if we fail the brief, it's game over.
I don't know who Ananda will pick.
But if he picks me,
I might be speechless right now.
But when the time comes,
like a cornered dog,
I have to speak up and fight.
- Hey, how's it going?
- Hello.
I brought you guys some gifts.
Thank you.
I brought some snacks.
Is it good news or bad news today?
My heart was pounding so fast right then.
How are you feeling?
When things glitched,
I was like, "Oh, man, what do we do?"
But we all agreed that our opening
was incredibly strong.
I was slightly panicked,
but I didn't know how it looked on camera.
A little bit.
We want to win
just like everyone else. It hurts.
Because we have to send someone
to the Black Room again.
It sucks when we don't win, because…
I have to send someone to the Black Room.
I just want to protect everyone
as much as I can. That's how I feel.
Speaking of improvement,
I feel like our team
has improved the most.
And I loved the ending
where you guys celebrated together.
It was such
a beautiful brotherhood moment.
That's why I don't want to lose anyone.
Which right now, I'm just acting.
Seriously?
- Wait, did we win?
- Yes.
We know we're good.
We were bound to win anyway.
I knew it!
I knew it. Because the energy that day…
The energy was amazing.
It had to be winning energy.
The winner's prize is getting featured
on digital billboards all over Bangkok.
- Oh, wow.
- It's enough.
- That's already amazing.
- More than enough.
A childhood dream.
I can't wait to see it while driving past
the billboards. I'll look for my photo.
Let's do what I feel is most fair.
I'm sending both of you, okay?
I think it's very fair.
Fair to both of them.
Because both of your performances
were neck and neck.
You both made mistakes, okay?
And neither of you
did better than the other.
So I'm not saving anyone.
I'm not going to…
Look, both of you made mistakes.
Just tiny ones.
But they were there.
You have to understand that.
Instead of saving one of you,
I'll be fair. You're both going in.
Then tell Off why you deserve to be here.
First, my advice is to admit that…
- I messed up.
- Mistakes were actually made.
A technical error
that we didn't mean to happen.
Things were out of our control. Next time,
we'll make sure it doesn't happen again.
I don't want to hear excuses like…
"Oh, if this didn't happen,
I wouldn't have…"
Then focus on what matters.
Why you deserve to stay.
I'm not afraid to go in.
But once I'm there,
I just hope I make it back.
But the chances
of returning are pretty slim.
Don't cry yet, or you'll make me cry.
I feel like it comes down
to the performance.
Since both of their works were so similar…
They both have to go.
Everyone did their part well.
But having to choose one of you…
It's really hard.
Ultimately…
Leo.
I picked Leo.
It might be a bit hard
to coach him on set.
Because we already have four people.
Especially with the language barrier,
trying to understand things. So it's Leo.
Personally, I'm not a super energetic guy.
I'm not that enthusiastic.
I just like being quiet in my corner.
But I don't know
if it's the nature of this show
that makes it so hard for me to be alone.
But I know this experience
will help me, my teammates,
and Mentor Mile too.
Everyone cared for me and helped me.
I felt it, so I tried harder.
But because I can't speak Thai…
And my English isn't perfect either,
I get even more confused.
And when the results
don't always turn out the way I want,
I feel even more lost in myself.
Even so, Mile always looked out for me.
I could see that he really cared.
I don't know what to say.
But what I want to say most right now is…
Joining this show,
I've felt so much connection, gratitude,
and love for everyone here.
More importantly,
these feelings will last a lifetime.
Oppa is the big brother of the house.
And everyone in the team adores him.
Be proud that everyone believes in you.
I think Mentor Off
might just be kind for once.
I have faith that Leo is going to fight.
And he'll do great.
Even if his Thai isn't perfect.
He'll fight to come back
because he loves us all.
Hello.
Pan and Ananda sent two of you?
They're playing games with me,
sending both of you.
Mile sent in a strong player.
They're definitely pushing me
to keep you all.
It's so obvious.
Look, this is the final Black Room.
Why would Ananda send two people?
What was his reason?
Because during yesterday's campaign,
the mistake was on both of us.
We were supposed to show the cars'
features, but the camera didn't catch it.
Everything else was perfect.
I'm sure you saw that too.
But the camera missed
the features the client wanted.
And it happened to us
because we were the ones using the cars.
So Ananda took the fairest route
and sent us both in.
Lincoln, tell me first.
Why did your team lose?
It was a technical issue.
I felt our teamwork was amazing.
I really thought we could win.
It was just a technicality.
Technicality? Then why didn't my team
have any technical errors?
Because…
We tried to do something a bit harder.
You think mine was easy?
No, I didn't mean yours was easy.
Just for our skill level.
But I just want to say
we really gave it our all.
I know. Everyone did great.
This last campaign
was the closest match yet.
But next week is the Final Walk.
If he sent you two here and kept Kimhan,
hasn't he already made up his mind?
What do you think?
- I don't think so.
- You don't think so?
So, why didn't he send all three?
It was a technical issue.
It wasn't your fault, was it?
Right, a technical issue.
Right, a technical issue for both of you.
- Yes.
Why not send all three?
He judged based on the performance.
Because the technical errors happened
specifically with my car and Lincoln's.
Kimhan couldn't drive
and didn't use the car.
He executed everything
much smoother than us.
That's why he chose
to send the two of us here.
I get the technical errors.
But when mistakes happen,
you have to blame yourself first.
That mindset is wrong.
Why couldn't you
solve the problem on the spot?
Sending two people in.
I wouldn't do it. It's too risky.
I'm not trying to blame anyone.
I just feel like he has low-key
already made up his mind.
Let me talk to Leo.
I want to know why Mile sent you.
I think Mile gave me a major role
in this campaign.
So I fully committed
and poured everything into it.
But ultimately, our team lost.
Therefore, I have to take responsibility
for that failure.
But from what I saw yesterday,
you weren't the worst performer, Leo.
I honestly can't say
whether I did the best or the worst,
now that I'm standing in the Black Room…
It doesn't even matter anymore.
Does the language barrier
affect your work?
Even though it gets frustrating
not being able to speak Thai well myself,
I want to say that
in the master classes and campaigns,
I don't think language
was an obstacle for me at all.
I will try my absolute best with my Thai.
And I…
I am practicing my Thai
as much as I can right now.
You might need to practice a little more.
Yes.
At the end of the day, I just feel like
if mentors can send you into this room,
it means they have their eyes set
on someone for the Final Walk.
If not this week,
you'll get heartbroken next week.
If not today, then tomorrow.
It's not like that.
There's still one more task left.
I don't think my mentors have decided.
They may want to judge the next challenge.
Are you sure?
But what if you get back
and the Final Walk goes to Kimhan?
I don't want your mentors to hurt you.
I can do it myself.
That way, you won't resent them.
Resenting me is better.
Even if Mile already has
a Final Walk pick in mind…
And even if that person isn't me,
there's still time…
Plenty of time to change a person's mind.
Therefore, I deserve the chance to stay.
I understand
this is a competition for all of us.
But I believe
I still have the potential to improve.
Ananda didn't save my boy.
Pan didn't save my boy either.
You remember that?
I really started from zero, you know that.
I've been steadily improving step by step.
I never get tired, never give up.
I'm always ready to learn new things.
The game is almost over.
This is the final stretch.
Please, give me the chance.
I really love you guys,
but this is a game.
Both Lincoln and Donut…
Neither of you is The Face.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, I understand.
- I'm so sorry.
- I understand.
Leo.
You're not The Face either.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
When I first met Mile,
I felt that if I was chosen
or got to pick my mentor,
it was always going to be Mile.
I wanted us
to reach the Final Walk together.
But now, I have to leave the show.
I'm still so grateful he took care of me.
Thank you so much.
I don't feel bad. I'm just grateful
to have made it to week six.
I never thought I would survive this long.
And I'm glad I got to know
Mentor Ananda and Mentor Pancake.
They were so kind to me.
Am I sad? Yes, I am.
Whatever caused the mistakes
that happened,
I can't blame anyone else. It's on me.
I just want to tell Kimhan
that I believe in him.
He can bring home the win for Team Panda.
I believe in his potential.
Keep fighting. You've got this.
He brought a suitcase.
Is that his elimination room outfit?
He looks badass. Has a suitcase with him.
I'm not buying any insurance. Not buying.
And the survivor… is in here.
First off,
if that's a Dior bag, I'm opening it.
What's his game here?
No one. They're all gone.
Nobody. I eliminated them all.
You eliminated all three, Off?
I thought he was joking at first.
Deep down, I kept hoping
Donut would walk back in.
- Did you really mean it?
- Really?
I mean it.
Yesterday, you said you won't eliminate.
That was yesterday.
This is today.
Now, I believe it.
There really is no honor among thieves.
Hold on. Seriously?
You eliminated everyone?
- They're gone.
- Damn.
I'm being serious, Mile.
Is this your final decision?
I was in shock. What a massive plot twist.
All in one go?
That's it. My mind is made up.
No second-guessing.
Sent in three, eliminated all three.
It's all for my own boys.
Honestly, I feel like this is bullsh--
I'm not cursing at Off.
- Who didn't fight for it?
- None of them did.
Are you clenching your fists, Mile?
Mile, it's all just a game.
Outside of this, we're still friends.
I'm not mad. I'm not mad at all.
But since when were we even friends?
Who do you see in the Final Walk?
If it's Leo, you shouldn't have sent him.
I don't know what Mile was thinking.
Sure, Leo messed up.
But he probably wasn't the weakest link.
I love all my guys.
If I could just send the weakest link,
I would've sent the driver in.
Are you saying
Leo didn't fight for his spot?
- He fought. Just not hard enough.
- I see.
This is pure gameplay.
Off's totally playing the game.
I get it.
- If he fought harder, I would've kept him.
- I get it.
Honestly, I'm a fair guy.
But if it were me, I would never send Leo.
I'm playing the game too.
I wouldn't make a stupid move like that.
No way.
I don't believe my boys didn't fight.
I asked him,
"Where do you think you went wrong?"
"Technical issue."
First rule,
if you lose, you blame yourself.
- Donut…
- Donut blamed technical issues too.
Really? Are you serious?
Donut would never say that.
Do you believe this?
We were very clear about this.
Go check the tape.
I think Ananda must be furious right now.
Every time I stand here and speak,
it's the truth.
I don't joke around on this show.
He still doesn't believe that Donut
blamed the technical issues.
When we spoke privately in the room,
he kept blaming himself.
- I see.
- Yes.
Deep down,
I know he wouldn't make excuses.
If someone actually took the blame,
I would keep him right here.
That's just cruel. Don't you have a heart?
Seriously, I love the kid.
No, you don't.
If you did, you would give him a chance.
Let's go home.
What he did today wasn't a strategy.
It's just who he is.
I'd say worse, but they'd bleep it out.
Let's leave it at that.
Mile is the hero. I'm the villain.
Whatever he calls me, I'm the bad guy.
If I clap back, I'm still the bad guy.
I get hate from him and his fans.
- You okay? You'll do this for Donut?
- I want to do it for Donut.
Let me propose this. Let's be fair.
If Kimhan wins the next campaign,
I want this, okay?
The next prize is two Final Walk spots.
But how is that fair if I win?
So there must be
two Final Walk spots for my team.
I'm giving Donut a chance.
At least let him come back.
I want to fight for someone.
And that someone is Donut.
Huge congrats to our first
Final Walk team, Team Panda.
I'm so happy for them.
I must have jumped more than ten times.
Today, I just have
to grit my teeth and fight.
I've never seen Kimhan this stressed.
But you have so many guys.
It's a waste of time.
- Who's next?
- You're up!
This is a once-in-a-lifetime shot.
I have to take it.
Here's some lucky money.
A bribe?
This is an incentive. This is a bribe.
Go! Good job!
Give it everything!
Subtitle translation by: Sarunpon T.