The legendary search
for the next top models and actors
that reshaped the Thai entertainment
and fashion industries is back.
Join me, Kim Goodburn,
on this historic new journey.
This is The Face Men Thailand Season 4.
And now, we have the contestants
for The Face Men Thailand Season 4.
All 15 of them.
Team Mentor Pancake and Mentor Ananda
grabbed PP, an all-rounder
in music and sports.
Donut, an intense young CEO
and business owner.
Kimhan, a cool professional model.
Lincoln, a determined Asian-German guy.
And Wigrom, the ultimate entertainer.
Team Mentor Mile chose
Peem, an intense young musician.
Gluf, a smart and dapper young man.
Manyoo, a pageant-ready national athlete.
Leo, a highly talented Korean Oppa.
And Jacob, biracial with a sweet face.
As for Mentor Off, he chose
Fox, a charming Thai-Australian.
Rome, a professional model.
Mew, a good-humored rapper.
Pom, a gold-medalist athlete and model.
Bonus, intense, tan, and fit.
Which mentor will lead their team through
the campaigns to become the next Face?
Let's find out.
The winner
of The Face Men Thailand Season 4
will collaborate with Clear Thailand.
He will receive a one-year supply
of Clear Ice Cool Menthol
and Clear Men Cool Sport Menthol.
And get the chance to work
with Vaseline Thailand.
Plus, he'll receive
Vaseline SPF50+ PA++++,
Gluta Hyaluronic Acid,
Photoage Defense UV Serum
free for an entire year.
He will also collaborate with AXE.
And receive a year's supply
of personal care products.
Bearbeary, only the wearers feel it.
Premium wear for every style,
featuring top design and innovation.
They'll award a 100,000-baht gift voucher.
Strive for perfection
with a membership to Hotman Fitness.
Including an 18-month
personal training program.
Plus a 200,000-baht package
from V Design Clinic.
Get ready to step onto the national screen
through a collaboration
with Channel 3 HD, Thailand.
And sign an acting contract
with Kantana Group Public Company Limited,
Thailand's leading producer
of dramas and films.
Welcome to The Face Men Thailand Season 4.
You're all part of The Face family now.
From now on,
you'll carry The Face last name,
just like the contestants
from the past nine seasons
who've made their mark
in the entertainment industry.
Additionally, you'll be living
in a space fully furnished
by Boonthavorn LIFESTYLE furniture.
They make the whole place feel warm,
highly functional,
and as comfortable as your own home.
So, congratulations again.
Give yourselves a big round of applause.
Amazing job.
What's today's master class?
What will we be facing today?
It's exciting and new for me. I love it.
We're heading into the first
master class of the season.
Please give a big round of applause
for Mentor Pancake and Mentor Off.
- Hello.
I walked out with Pancake.
I didn't feel pressure
because she has
a really solid theoretical foundation.
She's probably studied this a lot.
What year did she start modeling anyway?
No idea, but it's been a long time.
Right. We'll have to wait and see.
For our first master class,
we'll discuss something crucial
for being professional models.
That is your look.
As professional models,
you must be able to adapt your look
to fit any brief and situation.
Therefore, today's master class is…
A look isn't just about
being handsome or beautiful.
It's about being able
to adapt to whatever character
the client wants.
I think, first of all,
it's about keeping your own identity.
You must know what you're doing.
You have to understand the assignment.
What character are you portraying today?
What are you here to do?
Are you an actor, a model,
or a host today?
You need to understand
the brief and your role.
First, you have
to interpret the assignment.
You have to figure out
what your character is for the assignment.
Once you understand the character,
your charisma will naturally show.
Because you know yourselves,
and you understand the assigned character.
I want you all to be unique
and have your own style.
My uniqueness is a combination of things.
My hair, face, body, and height.
It's very distinct.
I think I'm quite unique.
Today's task is not difficult.
We have five hats for you to try on.
We want to see how you adapt
your character to match each hat.
Having a story in mind
helps you communicate your inner feelings.
You have to blend in with your wardrobe.
If these two go hand in hand,
it works well.
You'll be memorable.
Go ahead and pick your hats.
- Don't fight over it.
- Try them on.
When I saw the green bucket hat,
I instantly knew it was mine.
It fits my vibe.
Please step forward.
So cool.
He seems to already understand this hat.
He wears it often.
- I aimed for it.
- Yes.
Easy. I wore it and posed naturally.
Being the first,
I set the standard effortlessly.
The hat suits him best.
Bonus looked totally relaxed.
I think he already had an image in mind
before he even picked it up.
That's why he did well
and looked so natural.
Kimhan, your turn.
Oh, a construction foreman look.
Actually,
Kimhan took the hat that I wanted.
I think I would be better
at portraying that look and posing.
It's a shame that Kimhan took it first.
It's beige, yes.
Fox had a story in his head like,
"Hey, today is a chill day.
I might wear this to the beach."
- He kept in character.
- He built it up.
He built up the mood
to make the concept clear.
- It works.
- Keeping it cool.
- You came with a story.
- Thank you.
Okay, next is Lincoln.
For the master class, I wasn't sure
what to do. It was so fast.
So I put on the hat and thought,
"Okay, I'm Michael Jackson now."
MJ?
- You can't do ordinary anymore.
- Yes.
Lincoln understood the assignment.
Anyone could tell he was portraying
Michael Jackson.
Lincoln had a clear story in mind.
That made us feel,
"Yes, he nailed it with this hat."
Next, Pom.
Pom chose a difficult hat,
but he handled it well.
It's a pass for me.
I'm very surprised.
They did better than expected.
There wasn't much confusion.
I got to see how each of them performs.
Most importantly,
maintaining your identity
while adapting to different things
should go hand in hand.
That's how you bring out
your full potential
while staying true to yourselves.
Mew.
At first, I had…
a magazine cover in mind
with the outfit and everything.
But it turned out looking like
a soybean on my head.
I was confused. Perhaps not.
Next person.
Peem.
Is this…
a photoshoot, or is there a story?
It was a hiking vibe.
- Fashionable.
- We know it's a photoshoot.
But the story wasn't clear.
- We should feel it.
- And understand what you're doing.
You can have a story,
but you need to portray it.
You don't want people to be confused
about what your story is.
Some got it, some were confused.
Some didn't get it, some only had a story.
But you need to have it all.
I know I overthought it during class.
But I won't disappoint you
when the time comes.
It's time to begin our master class.
Today's master class theme
is "Freedom to Move."
Your face must be able
to adapt to various looks
depending on the situation.
Your task today is a photoshoot,
but it's more special
than any still photoshoot.
We want a '60s retro fashion shoot.
A photoshoot? Personally, it's…
a piece of cake.
Please welcome Puii, Wanisa Duangjinda,
Managing Director of Bearbeary Group.
A fashion brand owner
who understands the design
and lifestyle of the new generation.
She makes jeans
into more than just clothes,
but a look that enhances your true self.
- Hello.
WANISA DUANGJINDA
MANAGING DIRECTOR OF BEARBEARY GROUP
Hello everyone, and congratulations
to these 15 young men.
I'm very honored
to co-create the challenge
for the first master class
of The Face Men Season 4.
Bearbeary has prepared
a fashion editorial photoshoot
to test your ability to pull off
different looks with our jeans.
Previously,
Bearbeary only made women's jeans
and received great feedback.
This year, we're launching
our first men's collection
right here on The Face Men
for the first time.
I feel so lucky to be among the men
launching this collection.
Wearing their jeans is very special.
We're the first, so I have to brag a bit.
I'm going to win today
and take a pair home for sure.
Today, Bearbeary brought our first series,
the Relax series,
for you to wear in this photoshoot.
These jeans use
special weaving technology.
The fabric is smooth,
sleek, and well-fitting.
The fabric offers superior stretch
compared with regular jeans.
This allows it to fit any body type
and create a variety of looks.
For today's master class,
we have a professional photographer
joining us to shoot your campaigns.
Please give a big round of applause
to Oak, Napat Gunkham.
NAPAT GUNKHAM
EDITORIAL PHOTOGRAPHER
We'll be shooting a fashion editorial.
All contestants will take
both duo shots and group shots today.
Let's get to work.
But there's a special twist.
You'll be taking your duo shots
with professional female models.
Wow, okay.
Now, I'm totally motivated for the shoot.
I'm a bit nervous
about shooting with women.
I guess it will just be
business as usual, right?
I can't wait. It's going to be fun.
Please give a big round of applause
for our professional female models.
MellaMay, Gail, Lita, and Palmy.
The girls from The Face Thailand Season 6.
I'm so excited.
The energy was at 100% just now.
I was feeling tired,
but once they walked in, I was wide awake.
It's getting hot!
It's getting hot in here!
As for the group shots,
we'll divide you into four groups
with one female model each,
featuring one series of Bearbeary jeans.
The duo shots must look cool, relaxed,
and masculine.
The group shots must clearly express
the character of each series.
Here are the rules for this master class.
Each contestant must take one duo shot
with a female model.
You'll only have one minute.
After that, you must take
one group shot per team.
You'll have two minutes per team.
You must direct the poses and composition
for all four female models.
They're all so beautiful.
I want to work with all of them. Yes.
Each female model today represents
a different series of Bearbeary jeans.
Palmy will present the Relax series.
The fabric is sleek, well-fitting,
and comfortable.
For this group shot,
we have Jacob, Kimhan, Bonus, and Rome.
You must portray a relaxed look
and show how breathable the jeans are.
I can definitely do this.
I'm confident I'll win this master class.
Lita will present the Soft series.
This fabric is soft and flowy,
but holds its shape.
We have Donut, Peem, Mew, and Gluf.
For this group shot,
you need to portray
a soft and lightweight look.
Gail will present the Comfort series.
These jeans are designed for daily life,
offering high mobility.
This group includes PP,
Lincoln, Fox, and Manyoo.
You must show
a comfortable and agile look.
I'm feeling quite anxious.
It seems difficult.
I've never done a shoot with women.
And lastly, MellaMay
will present the Cool series,
featuring cooling denim technology.
This group includes
Pom, Wigrom, and Leo.
You need to portray
a cool and breezy look.
Please stay tuned.
If everyone is ready,
please go get prepared.
I'm definitely ready.
I'm 100% prepared.
Bring it on. I'm ready to slay today.
I'm ready. Bring on anyone. I'm so ready.
Welcome back to our master class.
The theme is Freedom to Move.
In this round, contestants
must showcase various looks
to present the unique qualities
of the Bearbeary Relax series,
making each look as clear as possible.
Is everyone ready?
- Ready.
If you're ready,
let's meet our first contestant.
The Soft group,
with model Lita…
and Donut.
I'm the first one, so I'm really nervous.
I wasn't sure
how close I could get to the model.
- You have one minute.
- I'll hold your hand like this.
- Like this?
- Yes.
- Okay, got it.
- You look at me.
- Okay.
Start the clock. One minute.
Ready?
I felt a bit hesitant during the shoot.
I didn't know if I was allowed
to carry or hug her.
I didn't think about going that far.
I'm not used to being
that close to someone.
Let's push our backs down and squat.
Squat.
Will the photo turn out okay?
Donut might be too stiff.
He might be going for a calm, cool style.
He does only one expression.
I think Donut needs to give a little more.
All right, let's move on
to the next contestant.
Peem, please step up.
Softness is about
being gentle and delicate.
I need to exude softness and comfort. Yes.
Do you mind resting on my lap?
Sure.
I want you to lean on me.
I'll sit like this,
and you lie on my lap here.
Then I want you…
- to lift your leg.
- In the middle.
- Good, good.
- Okay, like this. Got it.
- Ready?
- Yes.
- Oh, wow.
Peem clearly planned this.
He has a vision.
He communicates well.
Communication is key.
If they communicate,
they'll share the same goal.
It makes things easy.
Next up, Mew.
- What do you want to do?
- You have only one minute.
I want a scene where we…
- Together?
- You…
- Put your hand in my pocket…
- Okay.
Move a bit left.
Where is it?
Then look at the camera.
Mew looks uncertain.
Why put your hand only halfway
in her pocket?
Put it all the way in.
When it comes to a photoshoot…
You're in charge now.
You have to make it work.
Let's move on to the last contestant
from the Soft group.
- Gluf.
- One, two…
Good. I'll count for you. One, two, go.
- Twenty seconds.
- Gluf fits the brief well.
Light and comfortable.
Last ten seconds.
- Pull me.
- Okay.
Okay, that's it!
As we approached the last 30 seconds,
there was some pulling back and forth.
Gluf did a great job.
Up next, please welcome the Relax group.
Our model is Palmy.
And the first contestant
for the Relax group is Jacob.
I've already planned out the shoot.
I want a vibe like
we're in a garden, on the grass.
Basking in the sunlight.
Start the timer.
There you go.
My body is my weapon, so I have to use it.
Girls, come on. Don't tease them.
Thirty seconds have passed.
This is nice.
He's not overposing, which looks great.
But the options for the client
may be limited.
Perfect. He doesn't need to do much.
Just a little effort, and it's so good.
Next up, Kimhan.
The previous group…
- Hello.
My theme is Relax.
I want to showcase
the flexibility of the jeans.
Show how stretchy they are.
Oh, wow. It stretches this much,
but my face still looks relaxed.
This guy is good.
He got the shot in the first 30 seconds.
And he's fast.
Please turn your back.
We can make a photobook on this.
Beautiful.
I think I did pretty well.
I'm really proud.
Everything went according to plan.
Kimhan is actually quite intimidating.
He nailed the brief.
This is pure talent. He's good.
Bonus, your turn.
When I got there,
I didn't know what to do.
She was confused too.
So we both just winged it.
Freestyle.
We should talk, right?
- Communicate with the model…
- Freestyle.
Hold hands? And walk.
Okay. One, two. Good.
- Use the same leg as me.
- One more time.
One, two, and walk.
- Got it.
- Right leg.
Last ten seconds.
One, two, walk.
Good!
- Right leg.
Three, two, one, zero.
Time's up.
Thank you.
Yes, that's us. Keep it natural.
I'm done.
If I win, I win. If not, whatever.
You still have a chance.
Honestly, without the model's help,
the photos wouldn't look this good.
I feel like I really have to thank her.
She brought the whole concept together.
And now, the last contestant
of the Relax group.
Rome, you're up.
Hello.
I'm sticking to the brief for the mood.
I want a comfortable vibe
while keeping the photos cool and strong.
- Like this?
- Can I hook your arm?
Point at something. Like this.
Just move around.
Fifteen seconds down.
- Come here.
- They're not connecting.
They have to communicate.
- If they're in sync, it's perfect.
- Yes, exactly.
But if they aren't…
If you have an idea
but can't communicate it clearly…
- You'll lose it.
- Tough.
Rome might do better solo.
His direction wasn't clear,
so they just went with the flow.
But there were some good moments.
You could clearly see the jeans.
He got some good shots.
Ten seconds left.
Good.
Believe it looks good.
- Believe.
- Five…
- Four, three, two, one.
- Good! That's it.
- Time's up.
- Yes.
The final stretch was great.
He did well.
The photos turned out surprisingly good.
I didn't expect to see those moments.
They're nice,
but we'll see who the client prefers.
Moving on to the Comfort group.
Gail, you're up.
Can I lean back?
- First up, PP.
- Yes.
You can brief the model however you like.
You only have one minute. Time starts now.
Touch your shoes.
- Lean on my shoulder.
- Okay, got it.
Gorgeous!
I didn't know what to do.
I had some poses planned out.
But once the camera was on,
the first two poses went fine,
then my mind just went blank.
I'm not sure why.
Maybe I was just nervous
because we had so little time.
- Hold the pose, then move.
- Then twist like this.
Okay. Can I turn around?
- Like…
- I'll keep shooting.
- Good. Gorgeous!
- Fifteen seconds left.
He's got it now.
- Show off those long legs.
- Keep going.
Move your leg in a bit more.
Step forward. Good! Keep moving! Gorgeous!
I think PP had a clear vision.
He knew exactly what he wanted.
He just improvised at the end.
It turned out great
because Gail is such a pro.
Thank you, Gail.
Next up, Lincoln.
Are you dancing?
Oh, wow!
Lincoln just charged right in.
He didn't talk to anyone.
He knew what poses he wanted.
He just went for it
and expected her to follow his lead.
He was so worried
about his lack of experience.
But honestly,
he did better than people with experience.
Like me, maybe?
- Thirty seconds.
- What is he…
Lincoln has some great ideas.
These young men are impressive.
They keep surprising us.
I told you, I'm a very shy person.
But when it comes to work,
I work like a pro.
Next up, Fox.
I'm so nervous. Seriously.
I have no idea if the others
are doing the same pose as I am.
I tried to come up
with something completely unique.
Time starts now.
- Actually…
- Good.
- Oh, my god.
Gail really trusts him.
- Easy!
- She completely trusts him.
- Yes.
- Gail rules.
Give me some laughter.
I can't believe
Fox wouldn't let Gail touch the floor.
He kept carrying her.
He did squats over and over.
I hope we got a good shot.
Sometimes, you don't need to overthink it.
We want something easy to understand.
Simple communication,
but visually captivating.
Let's move on to the last contestant
from the Comfort group.
Manyoo.
- Oh, wow.
He took his shirt off.
He's really confident.
He probably leaned out just for this.
If you're ready, start the timer.
- Okay, lift my leg.
- Again?
It's always Gail.
Give me some laughter.
I feel so bad for Gail.
She's in the Comfort group,
but she didn't look comfortable.
It involves doing the splits.
It's about being flexible
during activities.
You need to do more than that.
Now, for the last group, the Cool group.
Please welcome our model, MellaMay.
Our first contestant in this group is Pom.
I briefed MellaMay
on the mood and poses I wanted.
And we only had
a limited time of one minute.
I was a little frantic.
Time starts now.
Beautiful. No kidding.
Here we go.
- You guys can talk.
- Ten seconds left.
- Communicate.
- Fun to watch.
We talked at first, but we found our flow.
We finally clicked.
We really synced up towards the end.
Next up is Wigrom.
They seem a bit disconnected.
They're doing their own thing.
Right.
Come together, pose together.
- Communicate, Wigrom.
- Twenty seconds left.
You need to interact. I can't see…
It's like you're in separate shoots.
To be honest,
Wigrom was a bit confused too.
He didn't know what to do.
He didn't have a clear idea
for the female model.
He couldn't communicate
exactly how to pose.
The ultimate goal is to sell the pants.
To sell the pants.
"To sell the pants." That's it.
I panicked
because my arm got stuck in the shirt.
But I think I did the best I could.
I really tried.
Let's move on to the last contestant
in the Cool group.
Leo.
Leo Oppa has a great body, obviously.
He showed off his body
more than the pants.
Crew over there, keep it down, please.
Since Leo came out,
the crew has been so annoying.
They seem to be cheering him on
extra hard.
Calm down, girls.
Time starts now.
- Oh, wow!
Oh, wow!
None of us thought a deep squat pose
would look good.
I couldn't imagine how it would turn out.
Beautiful.
- Oh my god.
- Goodness.
Oh, it's raining!
The Cool style is very simple.
You don't have to overthink it.
Can you do splits like me?
And now, we're moving on
to the group shots.
The first group, Soft, you're up.
You only have two minutes.
If you're ready, time starts now.
Going first is definitely stressful.
But we already planned out what to do.
- Get in behind.
- Give me a hand.
- Can you lift your leg? Lift it up.
- Lift my leg?
Like you guys are carrying a Naga serpent.
- Old photo that they carried the Naga.
- I wouldn't dare say it.
I think the shot of them carrying Lita
was a bit too much.
The composition might not look
beautiful or perfect.
Let's move on to the next group.
The Relax group.
- Relax.
- You can brief her now.
- Okay, let's go.
- You have two minutes.
- What do we do?
- Start.
Interact with whoever you pick.
Good.
- Good.
- For the group shot,
my initial strategy was to plan the levels
of who stands up and who squats down.
You guys are out of frame.
Only 50 seconds left.
- What is this?
- You're blocking each other.
Guys, work together.
Do you want to sit? Should someone sit?
- Come on, guys, do something.
- Thirty seconds.
- Good.
- Now, laugh.
It's not really working, I'm afraid.
I still feel that…
Maybe it's the time limit,
the teamwork, or other things.
It just didn't click. It looked confusing.
Next up is Team Comfort.
Our model is Gail.
Time starts now.
- That's it.
- Ten seconds.
Oh, no.
Obviously, that doesn't look comfortable.
It's obvious.
It's an uncomfortable comfort.
But towards the end,
they started dividing into groups.
Having the model stand in the middle
was refreshing.
But I still don't see the "comfort" in it.
Next up is the Cool group.
- Here, in the middle.
- Time starts now.
Right in the middle, then pose.
What kind of pose?
Hey, that looks good.
Before coming in, we planned our poses.
Time was limited,
so I wanted everything to be…
Let's just have one leader to avoid chaos.
Don't just stand there.
- A group of four is easy to arrange.
- Great.
Since there are four of them,
composing the shot is easier.
I think they'll have plenty of cute shots.
Can he carry you?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Aww!
- Oh, wow.
- Great squat.
- Give me something.
- Last 20 seconds.
We had high hopes for Pom
and wanted him to win.
But once I saw Leo's pose,
it was a clear win for him.
I couldn't imagine how squatting
while carrying a woman…
could possibly look cool.
But Leo pulled it off.
Our contestants just showcased
a variety of looks
presenting Bearbeary's Relax series jeans.
Let's take a look
at the judge's decisions.
Our judge has selected
the three best photos
from the duo shot round.
Let's take a look.
Jacob, Rome, and Leo.
I'm thrilled.
Honestly, I expected
to make the top three.
The shot came out
exactly as I pictured it.
Honestly, everyone did well
given the limited time.
There were a few hiccups,
mostly due to the time crunch
which made some
of your poses look a bit off.
But overall, it was great.
I agree with Puii.
Each photo gave off a different vibe.
But they all
clearly highlighted the jeans.
The main goal was to showcase masculinity.
It really shone in the photos.
I think these three photos
perfectly captured that essence.
All right, it's time
to announce the winner.
And today's winner
gets a prize, right, Puii?
Yes, a 10,000-baht prize from Bearbeary.
All right, it's time.
Who was the most outstanding
in this master class's duo shot round?
The most outstanding contestant is…
Rome.
See? I told you I could do it. Period.
He touched my heart.
He really met my expectations. Yes.
That's not all.
We have one more prize
for the most outstanding contestant
in the group shot.
Here are the group shots
from all four groups.
- What do you think of the group shots?
- They're good.
I think they look cute,
and you can really see the teamwork.
Even though you guys struggled
with the posing at first…
everyone managed to pull it together…
and take great, cohesive team photos.
You guys were great and very lovely.
Nailing a group shot
in two minutes isn't easy.
They all did an impressive job
for their first try.
Let's take a look at the best group shot.
The best group shot goes to Cool group.
Great composition.
Everyone's eye contact
with the camera was spot on.
Only one word comes to mind, "cool."
Puii.
Who was the most outstanding contestant
in the group shot round?
The most outstanding contestant
for the group shot is…
Leo.
Our first master class was a lot of fun.
A huge thank you to Puii
for joining our master class today.
As for the challenges that you will face
in the next campaign…
Good luck, everyone.
My kids didn't lose.
If they just hit the brief,
they'll win for sure.
We'll do better.
Ready or not, you just have to do it.
I believe in my team.
We're prepared for the first campaign.
Let's see what we're up against.
We lost the master class,
so we can't lose this.
Welcome to the first campaign
of The Face Men Thailand Season 4.
Yes!
Today, we're at Cloud 11.
The new Creative Destination
in South Sukhumvit.
A space for creators.
Aiming to elevate Thai content creators
to the global stage.
Cloud 11 has a huge courtyard.
I think it can be our runway.
For the first campaign of this season,
you'll be walking the runway.
Right up my alley.
Right here at Cloud 11 Park.
The largest canopied rooftop garden
in Bangkok.
In a campaign called
The Creative Cloud Canvas.
Now, let's meet the person
who will give us today's brief.
Noom, Apiwat Yosprapan
APIWAT YOSPRAPAN
RENOWNED THAI FASHION STYLIST
How does the brief
for The Creative Cloud Canvas go?
- I see this place as a blank canvas.
- Right.
We need to add colors to it.
You'll have to use your creativity
to paint on this canvas.
Express yourselves to the fullest.
Show your courage and attitude.
How you use your body language
and manage the space
to leave a lasting impression.
I'm great at runway walks.
Victory is mine. I can already smell it.
All right, it's time
to pick the performance order.
Rome.
Since you won the master class
from the duo shot round,
which team would you like to start first?
I'll choose…
Mentor Pancake's team.
He picked us to go first
to see the favorites in action.
I won't hold back. Just wait and see.
And the second team, Rome?
Mentor Off's team.
So the third team is Mentor Mile's.
Thanks, Rome. I get more time to prepare.
That's not all the surprises
we have today.
Because we have special guests
who will be working alongside you.
Please give a big hand
for the professional models
from The Face Thailand!
They walked down like
it was Victoria's Secret Fashion Show.
All angels.
Bursting with creativity and energy.
- Palmy.
- Palmy is the first pick.
Gail.
Gail is the second.
And the last one?
Minnie is his last pick.
My team gets Palmy, Gail, and Minnie.
It's like… wow.
Watch out for Mentor Mile's team.
When he turned around,
I was like, "Oppa, here, oppa."
Mentor Off's team.
Love you, Oppa. Thanks.
Team Off, which three models
do you want to pick?
- Gwang.
Gwang is the first.
Everyone knows whoever has Gwang
will definitely win.
Fah.
The last pick?
Maaprang.
All three are absolute icons of The Face.
They'd better prepare
for elimination this week.
That means Team Pancake-Ananda
will get Rima, Lita, and June.
We didn't even get to choose.
The ones we wanted went to other teams.
For today,
mentors must create
a creative fashion show
to present the clothing brand, 37°c,
and utilize
the Cloud 11 space effectively.
Your team members
will have 20 minutes to rehearse on set.
The judge will look for
the most captivating show
that best answers the brief.
It's a lot of pressure today.
But my friend is here
to help me out today.
Hold on, Mentor Off.
You didn't come alone?
I brought some help.
That's JingJing. Oh, we're screwed.
JingJing Prariyapit Yu,
Thai Supermodel 2012.
She's my helper today.
That's cheating.
Honestly, I just stick to the games.
I don't like cheating.
The rules didn't say that I couldn't.
So I brought her in. End of story.
Our team only has one mentor.
The others have two.
Two heads are better than one.
It's not fair.
Hey.
- Hello.
- Hello, Mentor Pancake.
I was teary when I saw her face.
It's so reassuring.
I know I'm not
a professional runway model.
And the kids feel reassured too.
Diva is here!
Such a relief.
It really feels like our mom is here.
Mentor Mile is all alone today.
What?
I'm not saying they're playing dirty.
I'm just confused.
I was told for Team A&P,
Pan would only be here for one week.
But this is like our third shoot.
What about me?
I've never directed a runway show.
Call Yoghurt.
Is there time?
JingJing said, "Mile, call Yoghurt."
Yoghurt, what should I do? But…
Three seconds later, they announced
the first team's coaching time.
My Yoghurt just melted away.
Let's flex and be confident. Come on.
Timer, please.
First off, today's concept is about love.
I'll group you guys up.
In the real world,
love comes in many forms.
Women love women.
Men love men. Men love women.
Mile straight up asked me
if I could do Boys' Love.
I had to say yes, right?
I want you two to be Jack and Rose, okay?
Jack and Rose.
Rose opens her arms.
Jack doesn't hesitate.
He steps in, boom.
Cue one. Cue two, look at each other.
- Don't be shy.
- I won't be.
Don't be shy.
Give me Titanic.
I felt a bit awkward.
But doing it gave me a new experience.
If you ask if I'd do it again…
I would rather not.
I mean, I know it's just acting.
I trust whatever Mile decides.
Okay, let's start.
Walk out one by one as planned.
I'm happy with it. Remember,
I had very little time to talk to them.
There's a roleplay element to it,
and they need to get it.
- Time's up.
- Okay, that's a wrap.
I'm so nervous.
I hope none of us gets eliminated
in the first Black Room session.
- Hello.
I told Pan that once we're settled,
I would give her a call.
She was only here briefly
for the rehearsal.
But she helped tremendously.
Our first pair is…
You'll pair up with June. Okay.
We have so little time.
Everyone in Team Panda wants to win.
Nobody wants to be sent
to the Black Room, right?
Go upstairs. Remember your partner.
- You two are going last.
- Got it.
At first, I thought 20 minutes was plenty.
But it actually goes by so fast.
Faster. Faster than that.
You're walking too slowly.
I was a bit worried about myself.
I was afraid I would look too stern.
But I didn't want to force it.
I kept it as natural as possible.
PP and Rima.
You two are already fine.
Fifteen minutes have passed. Let's go.
What can you do in 20?
Waking up and saying good morning
already takes 20 minutes.
Last pair, let's go.
It was a total cardio workout.
Running up and down.
I was getting dizzy.
I saw Ananda sweating bullets.
We were panting.
We ran around, and it was over.
Everyone, remember your places, okay?
Okay, guys. Let's do a dress rehearsal.
Give me some energy.
Get to the back.
Now, I get why 20 minutes go by so fast.
You can barely get anything done.
Start.
Wait for my cue.
We opened with a male-female pair.
I figured Lincoln
wouldn't get overshadowed.
Okay, walk.
Cross paths.
Exit the same way you came.
I admit, I'm a perfectionist.
This is a fashion show,
and I'm focusing on that.
Keep it simple, but do it right.
Look alive, Donut.
Keep the energy up.
Mentor Ananda, I can't keep up.
Watch your shoulder, PP.
It's still tough
walking up and down those stairs.
I've barely ever done it.
So it's difficult.
Come on down for the finale.
Utilize the space.
The brief is all about spatial movement.
Hit the brief,
so we can focus on the models.
We didn't have the time.
Whenever we tried to adjust
or focus on them,
time was up.
- Hello.
We'll start the pattern from the top.
Head upstairs.
It was stressful because I didn't prepare.
It was my first time doing this too.
Rome should be up front. Yes?
The two tall ones in front.
Honestly, I was thrilled.
I've never walked as an opener before.
We have different strengths.
JingJing excels at modeling,
while I'm better at placements,
and show concepts.
When we combine those skills,
it works out perfectly.
Maaprang will strike a pose.
Make it a big one.
I wanted the poses
to really engage the audience.
Eight minutes passed, then ten.
Off and I looked at each other,
"Okay, stick to the plan."
Off went up to brief the team,
and I stayed to watch from down here.
Everything flowed smoothly.
We managed to run through
the whole pattern twice.
Have fun with it! Keep the energy up!
Pick up the pace a little.
Guys. Smile! Use your eyes.
"Look at me. I'm gorgeous."
"Look at me. Buy my outfit."
During the blocking rehearsal,
everything was crisp and clear.
It was all very easy to understand.
Today is our day.
Both mentors helped
draw out our full potential.
Strike a pose.
We're stressed, and we tried our best.
I saw everyone's devotion,
not just the team members,
but the crew who helped too.
They worked hard
because they wanted us to win.
Upstairs, start.
Five minutes.
I felt everyone giving it their all.
The 20 minutes we had to practice
flew by so fast.
Enough for one more run-through.
Hurry! Last three minutes left.
Come on out!
Here we go. What are you trying to sell?
Off told me right from the start,
"Jing, have it your way,
but I want you
to stand up there at the end."
Get everyone together.
Go dance up there and wait! Go!
Once you're in position, start dancing!
Great job! Very good!
Energy! Have fun!
Interact with your partners!
It's looking good. Perfect, actually.
What do the other teams have?
I don't know if this exactly meets
the brief they gave us,
but this is how I'm doing it.
Welcome back
to The Creative Cloud Canvas campaign,
here at Cloud 11 Park.
And joining us to judge this campaign,
our first guest
is a leading designer
who is legendary across the industry.
He's also a former mentor
here on The Face.
He was my mentor.
Moo, Asava founder, Polpat Asavaprapha!
- Hello, Daddy.
- Hello.
POLPAT ASAVAPRAPHA
PERSONAL STYLIST, ASAVA FOUNDER
Our second judge is a true styling icon.
He's the creative director
for the brand 37°c,
whose clothes
our contestants are wearing today.
He brought us a collection
called The Equator.
Give a big round of applause
for Pu, Chamnan Pakdeesuk.
CHAMNAN PAKDEESUK
LEGENDARY FASHION DESIGNER, 37°C FOUNDER
And of course, we have two other judges
who need no introduction.
Master Mentor Adam and Royal Mom!
Welcome to today's campaign.
This is the very first campaign
of the season.
If everyone is ready,
let's begin
The Creative Cloud Canvas campaign!
Starting off with our first team,
Team Pancake-Ananda!
My thought for today
was just to keep it simple.
We focused on the fashion
and doing it right.
That's exactly what I wanted to see
from the team.
Choosing Pancake
and Ananda's team to go first
was a very smart move.
This is the first campaign.
We shouldn't go first.
We opened with a man and a woman.
June walks really well.
All the women have actually been
professional models for a while.
I feel like Lincoln won't be overshadowed.
He's naturally confident.
He could handle himself well.
I've never walked
or done anything like this. It's fun.
- They're heading down.
- Keep them coming.
Don't leave a gap.
Why use the walkie-talkie?
How will it help
when you already told them to go?
Cue three is heading down.
I feel so proud.
The energy is great today.
Hey, this is actually good.
Don't talk.
I can barely breathe.
This is great. You're happy.
Wigrom…
Expectations for him aren't very high.
Plus, he's an extra member on the team.
I'm usually lazy and stay home.
I've never done this.
But I like this kind of pressure.
It's challenging. I'll fight.
Cue four is heading down.
During the actual walk,
we didn't follow the practiced route.
And that made me anxious.
- What's his name?
- PP.
He should walk tall.
We chose PP
because he can utilize his acting skills.
He's charismatic.
But he looked pretty stiff when walking.
It's stressful since we're the first team.
And I'm not sure if our route will work.
PP has a very calm personality.
That might make his walk look soft.
So his presence just faded.
It's undeniable that…
a crucial part of being The Face
is the runway walking.
Kimhan really raised the standard
for Ananda and Pancake's show.
Without Kimhan, they might have struggled.
Kimhan keeps improving.
From the day everyone wondered
what was wrong with him.
He did great. He didn't disappoint anyone.
I feel relieved. I'm sure
I didn't walk the same way as before.
And I genuinely feel better.
So annoying.
Just kidding.
He's really talented.
That's why I wanted him,
but he chose otherwise.
What can you do?
Okay, get ready for the finale.
Tell Kim to speed up a little.
Beautiful. The walk was decent.
I'm starting to wonder if we'll win.
Will my members stay or go?
Going first is risky.
It can either be great or terrible.
- They need to use the space well.
- Right.
Mentors should know how to use the space.
It's like two separate parts.
They felt disconnected.
With eight people,
managing the space is tough.
It is.
- Plus, there are stairs.
- Right?
The scaffolding was distracting.
Honestly, a real fashion show
wouldn't have scaffolding.
There was also a tree.
I wanted to cut it down so bad.
Leave the tree. Just put a camera there.
So the judges can see.
Oops, I'm so sorry.
Out now, Kim, walk out.
Wow, you said you were stressed.
I can't breathe.
Okay.
Overall, our team did better
than I expected.
They were perfect. But in their own way.
That's the first team.
Let's check out the second one.
Team Off.
Our theme is Creative Cloud Canvas.
We made it as creative as possible.
No ordinary walk.
Give it energy. Be happy.
Yes. The mentor is hyping them up now.
Off did a great job boosting their energy
before the walk.
It really boosted their energy.
We started with all of them
walking out together.
It was pretty nerve-wracking
since they're rookies.
We had to plan who would open and close.
Rome is such a natural model.
He looks fluid and agile.
Perfect. The clothes look great too.
My team's outfits were the best.
They fit the vibe perfectly.
I like it. It's very colorful.
I've always liked colorful things.
They had everyone
walk down together first.
Then I noticed how well
they balanced the stage.
Good pace.
That's fabulous.
Fabulous.
If they don't mess up.
We had different walking styles,
swapping positions. And the fountain.
Good, good.
Walking was very easy for me.
So I thought I did well.
Pom turned out to be
a surprisingly great catch for me.
Wow, crisscrossing
like this is pretty cool.
So perfect, as if they practiced for days.
- Mew is good.
- His vibe is right.
The skills aren't quite there,
but the vibe is right.
I was terrified.
Just a little bit,
but I was mostly confident.
Do not take your jacket off, kid.
The energy was so high today.
We did better than in rehearsals,
so I'm happy.
No, don't do that.
This isn't a motor show.
Off's team wasn't that strong.
I think there were some gaps.
There was dead air at times.
Bonus.
I personally like him
and thought he would stand out.
I feel like
he was under too much pressure.
You could see
the lack of confidence on his face.
It helps that the women are there.
- The guys are…
- Complete rookies.
No.
I'm not worried about Rome and Pom.
The rest are a concern.
Honestly,
I don't have much runway experience.
Rome and Pom are good.
They have a lot of experience.
As for me, I just tried to focus
on my walk and my poses.
I couldn't see
the big picture like they could.
We were at the stairs for a short time.
Then we had to walk up the stairs.
Fox, who are you looking at?
Yes. He was…
I want them to succeed.
I want them to be good.
I feel like they need to push
themselves more.
All five of you have to stand out,
not just two.
They're dancing too.
The story is about having fun
and enjoying ourselves.
How do we get them to buy into us?
My team was the most fun.
Our team was just so good.
The characters were very clear.
Bam, bam. One, two, three.
- Does it end like this?
- Maybe.
Wow, they're dancing on the scaffolding.
It was being blocked.
Our judges today have X-ray vision.
They can see right through it.
Right through the tree.
Walking up in heels was hard.
Fah walked up and seemed to trip a little.
Was I afraid? The stairs were this narrow.
It's quite hard for women in heels.
The stairs have gaps,
and the heels could get stuck there.
I was going to help,
but they fixed it so fast.
It's normal. There were no accidents.
Beautiful choreography.
The only things that stood out
were the mistakes.
I can't lose. We hit it perfectly.
We will win, a hundred percent.
One hundred and ten percent.
Off, how did you make this in 20 minutes?
They did so many things.
It was a mix of everything.
It's good, but I'm not sure.
It felt more like an event.
I don't know if it fits the brief or not.
But it was my version of Cloud 11.
Next team, please.
Mentor Mile's team.
The Creative Cloud Canvas.
I interpret it as love.
Or heaven on earth.
And based on the location's style,
we should go with something romantic.
I feel sorry for Mile.
Mile has never put on
a fashion show before.
And he's working alone.
He has no one to consult.
We can only count on ourselves
to push ourselves.
Freedom of thought and freedom to live
are important to me.
What is this?
There's a scene.
- What is it?
- At the top.
There's a storyline.
This team is storytelling.
It's Titanic.
A grounded romance
about two men finding love.
Jack and Rose.
Oh, it's like a performance.
That's a surprise. Very abstract.
New. This is really new.
I respect their bold move.
I thought we had it.
But this is the real deal.
- Way better.
- How did he come up with this?
Magic would happen
when the timing was right.
We had to do it.
And it turned out great.
I'm not sure if they noticed
when our eyes met.
So beautiful.
- The pose speaks for itself.
- Yes, exactly.
- Perfect attitude.
- Yes.
We wanted the show to be striking.
We were so lucky to go last.
The light hit this angle perfectly.
Way better than spotlights.
It made everything look natural.
They showed off the location
and the clothes at the same time.
Wait, who's this?
He's Korean. His name is Leo.
He's a native Korean.
- He doesn't speak Thai.
- Oh, okay.
- This one?
- He's handsome.
Cinderella and the glass slipper.
Cinderella?
I thought her heel just broke.
What made her a Cinderella?
Because he held the shoe
and put it on her like in Cinderella.
I thought it would be cute.
Sorry. I really couldn't tell.
- Is that Palmy?
- She's talented.
She's a pro. She can do anything.
We got lucky.
Palmy really connected with Leo.
That's destiny.
Oh, they have Minnie.
- She's from last season.
- That's Gail.
It's so Broadway.
Let's see.
No offense,
but when you put it all together,
I don't know where to focus.
It doesn't really flow well.
Everything was fighting for attention.
Personally, I'm not feeling it.
- It's visually overwhelming.
- Agree.
Maybe there's too much going on.
No one told me it was a stage play.
It's a fashion show.
- Like…
- It's up to what the judges prefer.
That was so fun.
There was zero stress.
Friends, we were born to be happy.
So, enjoying every single moment
of every day is essential.
Loving yourself is what matters.
I liked the energy.
I liked the dancing.
It didn't look awkward.
Hey, it was fun.
It felt like Broadway.
Like watching a stage play.
I was surprised
by Peem and Manyoo's look and energy.
And they created it
without me saying a word.
I'm lucky. I have to thank them.
The main part
was a pure fashion show runway.
I really loved it.
Everyone hit their mark perfectly.
Mile's team is looking like
the frontrunner.
Their looks are very strong.
Some of them
we're seeing for the first time.
Gluf is Mile's weak link.
He still has a lot to learn.
I'm not sure about the result,
but I did my best and had fun.
Gluf is very mature for a 16-year-old.
He's from the new generation,
but he's genuinely respectful.
He listens, understands, and answers
honestly from his heart. That's important.
There was some dead air, huh.
Yes, a lot.
I'm very confident in my team.
It's up to the judges now
to decide who wins.
I hope once Moo sees my walk,
he might let me walk
in an Asava fashion show.
His final pose is great. I like it.
To each their own.
Personally, the message about love
was practically perfect.
Okay.
If they win, we'll know…
- what they expect.
- Yes.
If it's so abstract,
you have to explain it.
Eventually, people won't get it.
It's too deep.
Way too deep.
- They went in opposite directions.
- Yes.
It's up to the judges now
to see which style they prefer.
Were they focusing mainly on the walk?
Did we go wrong with our creativity?
Judges, we've just seen the presentations
from all three teams.
Now, let's watch the finale show
for The Creative Cloud Canvas campaign.
The finale felt like a real fashion show.
Like we were really modeling the clothes.
I felt like a professional model.
It was so cool.
The lighting right here is gorgeous.
Damn it, Leo is so handsome.
Very handsome. He's a dark horse.
He's no dark horse anymore.
- He's the front-runner.
- Everyone agrees he's handsome.
Mew is being too much. See?
Yes. I see.
That was his best shot.
The energy was so high today.
I feel like I did better here
than in the master class.
Better than practice. Way better.
I'm happy.
Wow, the finale on the stairs.
Four girls, elegant in brick-hued dresses.
The finale had great color coordination.
I liked it.
The people on the scaffolding
were already color-coded.
They were perfectly on mark.
Everything was seamless.
Kim is okay. He keeps getting better.
- To me, Kim is the most intimidating.
- He keeps getting better.
He's like…
He's always ready.
Kimhan was great.
He didn't disappoint anyone, I think.
He also stood out in the finale.
I had a new look today, and I felt cute.
- Pu, the outfit is absolutely elegant.
- Thank you.
They just stood out from the rest.
All right, that was
The Creative Cloud Canvas campaign.
A grand opening
for The Face Men Thailand Season 4.
Before we get to the results,
let's hear some comments from our judges.
Starting with Team Pancake and Ananda.
Doing a catwalk on a massive outdoor space
is not an easy task.
The three teams
had very different perspectives.
Like Team Ananda and Pancake,
they took a very high-fashion approach.
The choreography was crucial.
When the poses didn't fit the space,
it caused the judges to feel disconnected.
With each model's unique style
and the vast height differences,
you need to walk as a cohesive team.
The entire show has to survive.
They didn't listen to the music.
When they ignore the music,
their focus shifts to
"What should I do? What's my next move?"
Kimhan was the one
elevating the whole show.
He was the MVP of the team today.
One person totally lost it,
and that was Wigrom.
His anxiety ended up
dragging the show down.
But he's very open-minded
and ready to fight.
If we can just get him
to go with the flow, it will be fun.
Agree.
Wigrom was the least prepared.
He really just lacks experience.
Let's move on to Mentor Off's team.
- Pu?
- The choreography is fun.
If perfected,
I can easily adapt it and build upon it.
And you were lucky
to have someone carry the whole show.
In any fashion show, there are strong,
standout, and weak models.
But making the whole show flow
is incredibly important.
But I loved the energy.
Speaking as a former Mentor.
More importantly,
you were smart today for bringing in help.
He knows how to play the game.
Mentors need to know how to play it.
I wanted my team to learn something.
That's why I brought in
a professional model.
But some guys were doing too much,
which was a shame.
When the activities you gave them
went beyond just walking.
You have to be careful.
Mew, for example. His look was strong.
- He looked forced.
- Right.
He was trying too hard.
It made that whole section feel awkward.
It just so happens
you had two leading men.
- Rome and Pom.
- Pom.
They made certain moments
look extra special.
So that part was pretty satisfying.
But it's a double-edged sword.
Because when they stood out,
others faded away.
- I just asked Moo, "Where did Bonus go?"
- Yes.
- "Out collecting debts."
- Indeed.
And where did Fox go?
Fox and Bonus both completely disappeared.
We couldn't find them.
Honestly, I don't know
what criteria the judges use to score.
Do you feel the same way?
And finally, Mentor Mile's team.
- Yes.
- How was it?
I have to be honest,
I couldn't keep up with everyone.
You need to guide the audience's eyes.
They lack experience.
They missed their cues.
Which ended up creating dead air.
I loved the storytelling.
I really loved Peem and Gluf.
- It was Peem and Manyoo.
- Sorry, it's Peem and Manyoo.
That was spectacular.
I felt there was movement,
energy, and vibrancy.
I never thought
they would pull off being up there.
One title came to mind, West Side Story.
It gave that vibe,
and it was perfectly balanced.
I was amazed by that part.
The brand owners loved it.
I was over the moon.
I must say, Mile is here
all alone today without any help.
What a gentleman.
- I loved it.
- Thank you.
Your creativity
and interpretation were fresh.
It's exciting and interesting.
The movements perfectly sync
with the models.
But amidst all those movements,
there are flaws
where it feels like dead air.
There's a hidden story there.
For the first week, especially
for the inexperienced young men,
anxiety held them back
from fully expressing themselves.
Let me give you a tip.
We'll have similar challenges
like this again.
So, keep this in mind.
I might have been too harsh,
making them do this on the first campaign.
We've heard all the comments.
It's time for the results.
Royal Mom. Which team won
The Creative Cloud Canvas campaign?
The winning team is…
Team Off.
Yes!
He deserves it.
Congratulations to Mentor Off's team.
Thank you!
You're the winner
of The Creative Cloud Canvas campaign.
I understand the mentors now.
My heart was pounding.
I'm so glad I chose JingJing
to join us today.
Having a partner to brainstorm with
made the game fun.
That's amazing.
But that also means the other two teams
must send at least one member
to the elimination room.
And Mentor Off,
you must eliminate one person.
Two heads are better than one.
That proverb rings true today.
Mentor Mile might be new to this game.
You know what to do now, right?
- Eliminate one.
- Sure, either yours or Ananda's team.
Off, you want anything?
Pan, if there's another runway challenge,
I'll force you to join us.
I'll drag you here.
I won't take no for an answer.
For today, a big thanks to Cloud 11
for providing the venue
for today's challenge.
Also, thank you to our four judges
for joining us today.
Thank you.
I won't be able to sleep tonight.
Honestly, you never know
what will happen on The Face.
Those who underperformed just need
more practice. It's that simple.
I'm practically accepting my fate.
Welcome to The Face Thailand.
I get it now.
- Hello.
Hello.
When Mentor Pancake walked in,
I felt the vibe…
completely drop.
My heart sank when…
Pancake walked in.
You look serious.
- Not just my bold makeup.
- I meant your mood.
Right. My mood too.
The result is…
we lost.
For several reasons.
Based on the judges' feedback
and personal preferences.
It's quite stressful.
I don't know who she'll send
to the Black Room.
Let's video call Ananda.
You need to hear
what Ananda and I will discuss,
and decide who will be sent
to the Black Room.
Who has to fight for their spot to return?
Hey.
- Yes!
- What's up?
Hello.
When Mile walked in,
I was waiting to hear one thing,
"We won."
- You want to know the result?
- Yes.
Do you think we won or lost?
We were just talking,
and we're fairly confident that…
We have a chance. At least we…
stand a chance of winning.
We definitely do.
All right, I'll announce it.
Team Off won.
When Mile had to pick someone
for the Black Room,
I went completely pale.
He was staring right at me.
I'm definitely going to the Black Room.
There he is.
I knew it.
They all did well in the last round.
But you should know
that some of you still have weak points.
Do you think you did your best
in the last campaign?
- 100%.
- Really? 100%?
- 120%.
- 130%.
130%.
- 90%.
- You look stressed.
I gave it my all.
Everyone praised Rome and Pom
for a great opening.
Everything was perfect.
That leaves three of you.
Fox,
Bonus, and Mew.
Man, our team was so stressed out.
I heard the cheering screams.
So I knew my team was screwed.
Someone was going home.
Tell me the biggest mistake
you made that day.
Explain what happened.
I posed too much.
And it got repetitive.
I was stressed.
I knew I didn't do my best.
Honestly, I didn't give
my 100% when posing.
I just moved slightly,
thinking people wouldn't notice.
But I can't do that.
I have to give it my all.
I learned my lesson.
If I do it, I have to go all out.
- You have to be completely confident.
- Noted.
I get it. My confidence was just gone.
That day, I felt that
I didn't have as much energy as I wanted.
- You knew it, right?
- I knew it.
I need more focus and confidence.
I should have more confidence.
The three people I'm picking
are Fox, Mew,
and Bonus.
Three people?
That leaves only two on the team?
Everyone turned pale.
You don't have to go because we won.
I'm super happy. I'm thrilled.
What? We won again!
I'm exhausted.
I'm more stressed than you guys.
Honestly, I couldn't tell you.
Oh, brother.
Stressed?
Hey, don't cry. Why are you crying?
I think I revealed it too soon.
I shouldn't have done that.
Because Mew was tearing up too.
When I mentioned the Black Room,
he started tearing up.
First of all, I'm proud of everyone.
It's a perfect example
of how to make the most of an opportunity.
I'm not ready to let anyone go.
I still want to get to know all of you.
I feel like everyone has more potential.
Everyone is highly talented, but…
I hope I'm not the worst.
And I felt…
It feels unfair
to eliminate someone this early.
But for this week,
I choose…
Wigrom.
I understand that I might be the weakest.
My team is full of talented people.
Everyone has experience.
I'm the youngest.
- Wigrom, are you ready?
- Yes, I'm ready.
Don't be afraid. Take a deep breath.
I'm not sending you in
because you're the youngest or the worst.
That's only part of it.
But I believe you're a fighter.
You can achieve anything you want.
Whether it's asking for a chance
or proving yourself.
Talk to him.
And I believe Mentor Off
will send you back.
He'll be back.
I'm confident
that Wigrom will put up a fight.
And he'll succeed.
Since we didn't win, someone has to go.
Any volunteers?
Someone has to go.
No one wants to go.
I don't want anyone on my team
in the Black Room.
I have to make a choice.
This is a really tough decision.
I couldn't sleep for the first few nights.
I kept wondering what to do.
Listen carefully.
I'm sending you to fight.
So I'll pick someone who…
has a fighting spirit.
I see that in him.
I think he can handle this.
Are you ready?
Hey, remember to breathe.
Don't hold your breath.
Gluf, can you fight if I send you in?
I'll try my best.
I was completely numb. I was speechless.
Before and after it happened.
I think the others
are highly skilled. And…
even though I lack experience,
I have a fighter's spirit.
Honestly,
I think I can win Mentor Off over.
You're a cat with nine lives.
Tawanchai never dies.
Yes.
One, two, three.
- Go Team Mile!
It might not be the best play,
but I think it's…
the most appropriate strategy
for this round.
Hello.
- Hello.
Well…
First, I have to thank both mentors
for actually sending
their weakest members.
What are your weaknesses?
Why did they send you here?
To the judges, I seemed
a bit absent-minded.
Shifty-eyed and anxious.
And awkward.
I think I still lack experience.
I haven't been through enough.
I just don't have enough experience.
The mentors probably already know
who belongs in the Final Walk.
Maybe they just
don't picture you two there.
Mentor Mile said he chose me
because he believes
I can fight my way back.
- Did they tell you their reason?
- They chose me so I would fight.
They believe I can make it back.
Really? So the game is on then.
Mentors sent in the members
who are likely to make it.
That's what Mile told me.
- And do you believe him?
- I do.
I can do it. I can fight.
If he believed in you, why send you here?
- Shouldn't it be someone else?
- I believe Mile.
- Oh, you do?
- Yes, he's my mentor.
Okay. And you believe Pan too.
I was eliminated once before
for the same reason.
When I found out I had a second chance,
I used that time to improve.
I did everything to get better.
And I showed everyone that I've improved.
Since coming to The Face,
I got the chance to show off
and improve myself.
"Show off"?
I'm sorry. I…
I got the chance to improve myself.
Do you think your improvement is enough?
I believe I can grow even more.
My whole life is
about constant self-improvement.
He says he can still improve,
but so can I.
I also believe I can keep improving.
If I get to stay, I believe I would learn
many things from The Face.
So that I could become the man
The Face Men is looking for.
But this is Season 4.
Before applying, shouldn't you have known
you needed to be ready?
How do you think
you can compete with the others?
You can't. It's too exhausting.
I feel like there's still a lot
the mentors haven't seen.
I have a strong sense of self,
yet I am adaptable.
I'm flexible and can handle any situation.
There's a lot I still lack
in the entertainment industry.
I want to learn from The Face.
I just started here in The Face.
But it feels like I've been
in the industry for ages.
I believe my personality and Gen Z nature
can show people what I'm capable of.
I think you're a bit
too confident, Wigrom.
Being overly confident
doesn't really do you any favors.
I see it in everything,
like how you speak to the crew.
You might need to tone it down.
I apologize for that.
I promise to improve.
If I'm eliminated,
I won't have any regrets.
Because I feel I've done my best.
I'll keep pursuing my goals.
From what he's said,
I think I can do that too.
I really understand Gen Z,
if given the chance.
Gluf, I've seen you
since the very first team selection.
You looked like a real fighter.
Honestly, I want both of you to stay.
Because that benefits my team.
Then let me stay.
I have to eliminate one person.
I'm just making the decision
after your mentors did.
These two kids are inexperienced.
And they're both contestants
that their mentors didn't even pick.
If I eliminate them, deep down,
their mentors will be glad.
I was anxious. Off walked out first.
He didn't chat with anyone.
Went straight to Mile.
Mile, what you said earlier…
I just feel like
you shouldn't have done that.
The rules never stated whether
I could or could not bring any help.
I brought in JingJing to help my team win.
What? What's going on with these two?
It felt weird.
When Off walked over to Mentor Mile,
I was shocked.
I had no idea what they were discussing
when they met earlier.
What's up?
No, I just…
When you had your helper coach your team,
I just felt it was a bit unfair.
I don't want to send anyone
to the Black Room.
But the rules already state
you must send at least one person.
- Let's talk to Tae.
- Okay.
I must speak up
because it doesn't just affect my team.
Is there anything I should know?
- Yes, Pan.
- Oh, hello.
- On the competition day…
- Yes.
- Just for this campaign.
- Okay.
I feel it's unfair to the contestants.
Secondly, I didn't know we could do that.
Mile thinks it was unfair
when he did the campaign by himself.
Mentor Off had someone helping him.
If I wanted to do that, I could.
I have already asked the producers.
Okay, I get it's a game.
But sending someone
just to be eliminated isn't fair.
He feels disadvantaged.
And it affects everyone on our show.
Why did it turn out to be my fault?
It might not be wrong to someone,
but to many others, it is.
Mile, you should have
discussed this earlier.
Bringing it up today doesn't fix anything.
It's up to you,
but I must respect the Black Room winner.
Someone has to go either way.
Once the judges have decided,
we must respect their decision.
Right. Then send someone in.
I understand.
If you want to balance fairness,
you should eliminate the weakest
based on performance.
- Don't worry.
- That's all.
Our show needs stricter rules…
- Much stricter.
- Definitely stricter.
I understand, but why bring it up now?
It feels like you disrespected me.
I was pretty annoyed
because I did my homework.
I wanted to do well
and have it turn out okay.
You need to watch more
of the previous seasons.
Ask Pan how she prepares.
I didn't plan to do things
the way The Face used to.
I came here to bring
my own style to The Face.
Otherwise,
you'll be begging every episode.
That just won't work.
I get it, but here's the thing.
I wasn't begging. That's not what I meant.
I spoke up because I didn't want
my supporters watching the show,
or anyone else watching,
to think it's okay to exploit loopholes.
Loopholes in the methods
that let you take advantage of others.
Things are the way they are
because we keep cutting corners.
Mile, you know that on this show,
people want to win.
It can start with us.
It really starts with small things.
I didn't mean that you cheated. No.
It was such a cute scene.
Cute argument.
It feels like a TV drama.
The vibe was so tense.
I just want to know
whether Wigrom made it or not.
Fight for him. Where is our boy?
I really want to keep watching, but…
I want to know
whose contestant gets to stay.
I'll bring him back to you.
Off walked back there.
Then we had to wait and see
if Wigrom would return to the team.
At that moment, I just hoped
Wigrom would come back.
If he wants to play the good guy,
he has to save both of them.
For the one who doesn't advance,
I have to return the portfolio, right?
Therefore…
You are not The Face.
I fight my own way.
Everything I said came from my own words.
Gluf took a lot of what I said.
He merely repeated my points.
I felt it was never really fair.
Or maybe he was just afraid
I would be a threat to his team.
So he chose to eliminate
the tough competitor first.
I understand that.
I couldn't explain it then,
but I was angry.
I felt angry, which is fine.
My boy came back, so I'm relieved.
If you two just argued
and ended up eliminating Wigrom,
that's ridiculous.
At first, I secretly hoped he would return
since Mentor Off said,
"I'll bring him back."
I'm sad and disappointed.
I wish I had the chance
to know Wigrom better.
He has many sides we haven't seen yet.
Wasn't he the contestant
you didn't pick from the start?
Whether I picked him or not,
he's on my team, so he is my team.
It doesn't matter
whether I chose him or not.
But I'm the winner.
Honestly? You're probably glad
I helped eliminate him.
He's my kid now.
There's no doubt about it.
He's 100% on my team.
Wow, that moment was terrifying.
I didn't know what Pan was thinking.
I didn't know what Off was thinking.
There were two choices. And I chose one.
- How did he fight?
- He spoke better.
Wigrom said he came to show off.
That's useless.
Go elsewhere. Don't do it here.
That's one of the reasons
I didn't keep Wigrom.
Did he really say that?
Do I even need to tell you?
Shouldn't I know? You eliminated my guy.
I'm pretty sure Wigrom
at least tried to fight.
That's not necessary for me.
My job is to eliminate, not to explain.
Do I have to explain myself to her?
Is it in the rules?
Of course, I need to know.
You sent my guy home.
Does the winner have to sit and explain?
Not at all.
There was no explanation.
Okay, fine.
Then I won't explain
when I eliminate someone either.
Sure. Just win first.
I'll just cut. My word is final.
No questions.
No explanations.
Oh, crap. I'm screwed.
Are you happy?
No, I'm not. I told you I talked to Off.
I'm not saying Off was fair or unfair.
I just talked to find a middle ground
for him to decide.
I get that Pancake
has probably been through a lot too.
Probably more than I can imagine.
Is it because Mile asked
about rules we weren't aware of,
so you helped his team instead?
- That is not it.
- Is there something I don't know?
No. I'm being honest with you.
- I don't make deals to save my team.
- I don't know.
A game is a game.
I just have to play along.
Making demands when a decision
is about to be made…
I think that's truly unfair.
It's up to you, but I'm not like that.
Mentor Pancake is taking a big hit.
Is Pancake upset? Can someone ask her?
Is Pancake upset?
Honestly, I can tell
she's acting sometimes.
Sometimes it's a performance, sometimes…
You probably didn't picture Wigrom
in the Final Walk anyway.
I did you a favor by eliminating him.
Whether you pictured him or not,
that's my business.
But now, he's completely
out of the picture.
Our mentor is so confident.
We have to win next week.
Confidence is fine, but don't get cocky.
I'll be 115% confident.
We still have to give it our all.
Good. My four contestants
are all top quality.
Hope your team won't mess up.
Let's go.
It shows she loves all of us.
It makes me trust her even more.
It means she really cares.
I love that word. It's so…
hungry and powerful.
Bring the heat, we'll fire back.
If they fight, we fight back.
I'm not scared either.
Thank you. It is what it is.
No, your boy really fought.
I felt it had to be Gluf.
I feel like Mile is more on our side now.
Like Mile really understands us.
Okay. See you.
All right. Enjoy the game, guys.
Enjoy the game.
Peace.
Just making peace, that's all.
I don't know if Mentor Off used this…
as a reason to save Mentor Mile's team.
She's probably annoyed that she lost.
This is how the real world works,
but not for me.
He's probably happy for this team.
It is what it is.
If you're happy, I'm happy.
Keep watching.
Is your whole team going shirtless?
I have a shooting pain
radiating down my entire leg.
For today's campaign,
we'll be shooting underwater.
It's a trauma for me.
I almost drowned in a pool once.
Beautiful. Good.
They're awkward.
Like they're trying too hard.
First time in my life. Going all out.
Subtitle translation by: Sarunpon T.