Ladies and gentlemen,
I now present to you,
Mr. and Mrs. Jordan Manansala!
Bad omen.
Why?
Is it stupid to love you?
You shouldn't have let
your husband have a good
time with another woman.
And in your own house?
Mom, they're just friends.
Did you really have to gift them
with a honeymoon package?
Why not?
So, they can enjoy their little
time together as a couple.
Okay. We're ready.
Are you single?
Sorry, there's just a lot about
you that I don't know.
There's this guy that I like.
But we can't really be with
each other.
I think I know who you're
talking about.
Huh?
Hurry, that way!
Babe, let's go.
Come on, let's go!
Where do we go?
You, come here!
Stop!
Go there!
Move over there,
Congressman!
Gather everyone!
Sit!
I said sit!
Sit down, sit down.
Sit down!
Excellent, comrades.
Who are you?
Just let us know
what you need.
Don't hurt our guests.
Do you want them to pick up
your brain on the ground?
Do you?
They might catch us.
Let's stay here.
Where?
Babe, this way. Come on!
We are the Kalasag!
We are the brotherhood
that fights abuse and greed.
And we're all here. for
Congressman Rodriguez.
The one who stole every
farmer's land!
Wait.
Jordan, we shouldn't
have gotten in here.
We'll get stuck.
We can't stay outside.
We'll get caught easier if
we do.
What about Shaira
and Leslie?
I hope nothing bad happens
to them.
Babe, wait. I'll call
Mom and Tori.
Not now, babe. They'll just get
worried.
We need to focus on how to
help others.
We should let the police know.
We have to contact them.
The police? What if those people
get angrier?
I don't want to die, Jordan.
They might kill us.
No one will die.
We'll go home to Tori.
Babe, call the police.
Okay.
They are the group I see
on TV.
They cut off their
hostages' heads when they
can't pay the ransom.
Hey!
Who told you to chitchat?
Shut your mouth if you don't
want us to blow your
heads off!
Buwaya!
Get a bag.
Get those that will fit in
their heads!
Shut up!
Give me your cell phones!
Cellphone.
Include your jewelry, too.
Cell phone, faster!
Put it there, put it here.
Your jewelry. Move!
Jewelry.
Put it there.
Give all your cell phones.
Try to hide your phones, and
we'll blow your heads off!
Hello, Sir?
Sir, hello.
Please help us.
They might kill us if you don't
come here.
Please, have mercy on us.
Save us.
Are you sure no one escaped?
Leave our guest alone. Just get
what you need!
Igat, Bakulaw... Search
the entire resort!
Bring some of our men!
What did they say?
They say they'll come here.
But they'll come from the
neighboring island.
Hurry! Hurry!
There's another one over there.
Gather everyone in the center.
Sit! Sit!
- Sit down!
- Leon is waiting!
- Hurry up!
Take care of them.
We'll go to Leon.
- Walk.
- Walk!
I'll just use the restroom.
I can't hold it in anymore.
Make it quick.
This mission is so easy.
We got the fool politician
without breaking a sweat.
We can finally exchange heads.
I'm sure Leon will be glad.
What?
This is not the time
for chitchat.
Do you want to lose your
tongue?
Move.
And you, hey!
I'm coming!
I can cut that off.
Hurry up.
I'm done.
You took so long.
Babe.
Looks like they're gone.
Careful. We'll go out.
Okay.
Hurry up!
Move!
Leon.
Why aren't we leaving yet?
We already have the Congressman
with us.
I want to make sure no one will
report us.
And I want the authorities
to be surprised that we
have something against them.
Bring some of our men.
Search every room.
I don't trust Igat.
Make it quick.
What do you need from us?
Please spare us.
We didn't do anything wrong
to you!
I'm willing to pay if I'm the
one you need.
How much do you want?
I have money!
I will pay you no matter
the cost!
Just let me go!
And then what?
You will give us the money
you stole?
Is that it?
Don't worry, Congressman.
You will know everything
we want.
So, shut your mouth for now.
If not, I will show everyone
what we're capable of.
Do you want that?
Hey!
Stop!
Hello, Cristy?
What's up?
Is Jordan already giving you
a headache?
Jeff... Jeff, help us.
Some rebels invaded the place.
Jordan and I got separated.
What?
Jeff, I couldn't believe it
at first, too.
Help us, please.
I don't want to die.
Don't tell Mom, okay?
Don't tell Mom.
Take care of them while we're
still away. Until we escape.
Wait, wait.
Hold on.
You're going to escape?
Isn't that dangerous?
Where's the police?
I don't know.
I hope the police arrive.
But... Okay, okay.
I'll find a way to help you.
Okay.
Just don't lose hope, Cristy.
Jordan is strong.
He'll come back to you, okay?
Thank you, Jeff.
Bye.
Jordan?
Jordan!
You, monsters!
What did you do to him?
Jordan, Jordan, get up.
I'm fine.
Your clothes are so clean.
Are you tough?
Where did you get him?
In the men's restroom.
Oh, really?
Where's the one with you?
I'm alone.
What did we do wrong to you?
Answer my question!
I don't have anyone with me.
I really am alone.
You're alone?
You're alone!
Jordan.
Are you okay?
Cristy... Cristy, can
ask for help.
She can ask for help.
What are you staring at?
What are you planning
to do with us?
Stop.
Do you want to know?
Do you?
That's enough.
Stop, please.
Please.
We'll do whatever you want.
Just don't hurt him.
Please.
I like your girlfriend.
She knows her place.
Be like her.
Because if not, I will blow
your head off.
Hey.
What are you still doing there?
I'm done searching that area!
Let's go back.
I don't know what Leon
is looking for.
Let's go, come on.
Leon.
Yeah?
The first floor is clear.
Are you sure?
Yes, we are.
I'm okay. Just keep hiding.
Love you.
You jerk!
You really are stubborn!
Stop!
That's enough!
Don't hurt him! Please!
Don't hurt him.
Stop.
- Won't you let go of it?
- Jordan.
This is his wife.
If your wife is here, who is
this woman?
It's none of your business.
It seems that you like
that animal.
You know... I feel bad
for your wife.
She's worried for you.
Let's call her.
Don't.
Don't!
Jordan?
Jordan, where are you?
Jordan...
Come here.
Listen.
Where are you?
Jordan!
Babe, don't say anything!
Babe!
Babe?
Babe, where are you?
Where are you?
Babe, don't!
I'll give you five minutes
to show up.
If you don't come, I will blow
your husband's head first.
I'll give you five minutes
to show up.
If you don't come,
I will blow your husband's
head first.
Cristy, don't say anything!
Think of Tori!
Jordan?
Jordan.
Go ahead.
Make him shut up.
Bakulaw, Igat!
What will you do?
Stop!
Don't hurt him!
I'm begging you!
Please stop!
Stop!
I said stop!
That's enough!
Let go of him!
Jordan!
Jordan.
Stop!
Monsters!
Animal Jordan!
Jordan!
That's enough!
Stop it!
Aren't you going to shut up?
Won't you shut your mouth?
Won't you?
I'm sure that the police will
arrive in a few hours.
And you will pay for everything
you're doing!
Aren't you really going to stop?
Let go of Come here.
Shai, Shai!
What now?
Come here.
Shai!
I will make this animal shut up.
- Shai...
- Where are you taking me?
Let go of me!
I'm not scared of you!
What are you going to do?
You're a monster!
Animal.
I can't breathe!
Are you really going to kill me?
Brother!
What's the matter with you?
I told you to just get Cristy.
I didn't tell you
to hurt Jordan!
Why do you put your itch first
instead of the group?
I helped you!
I helped you, didn't I?
We agreed that we'd both benefit
from this!
They have transferred Dad
to Camp Crame.
He can no longer escape.
That's what they thought.
Will Congressman Rodriguez still
go to your resort
next month?
Why? Are you planning something
against Congressman?
What if we do?
I thought you were not
interested in the group?
What if I help you?
I can give you the blueprint
of the resort.
So, you'll know the place.
And why would you do that?
I want you to get someone, too.
What?
Whatever you plan to do with
Congressman,
bring that woman with him.
What? Is it because of this man?
I don't care what you do with
that woman.
I want her out of my life.
I did everything you needed.
You owe me that you got
Congressman Rodriguez!
I only want you to get Cristy
so I can have
Jordan to myself!
Fine!
Tell your man to behave
if he doesn't want
to get killed!
Do you understand?
Leon, don't hurt him.
Don't hurt him.
What's that for?
I'm just making it believable.
So, it will be convincing.
Come on.
- Leon, what are you doing?
- Get your act together!
Move.
Shai.
Okay. Let's do it again.
Hello? Shaira?
Cristy. So?
What?
Is the traffic bad?
It seems that your
husband's life doesn't
matter to you.
That's not true.
That's a lie.
Don't touch my husband!
I told you,
your husband's
life lies on you.
One minute left.
You'll pick his brain on
the ground if you don't come.
Don't, don't. I'll go there.
I'll go. Don't hurt Jordan.
I'm begging you, please. Please.
Even if you kill me...
Its enough for me to know that
my wife is safe.
No. Don't!
Don't!
Jordan!
Jor Cristy
called me earlier.
Is she safe?
No one will shoot!
I'll take care of her.
Cristy!
Jordan!
- Jordan Jordan!
- They will hurt you!
No! No!
Jordan!