Who are you?
Let me go.
I beg you, let me go.
Please, let me go.
Let me go. I beg you.
What a fine body.
Why be a prostitute?
And defile yourself?
Please spare me.
Let me go.
Please, let me go.
I beg you, let me go.
I'll give you whatever you want.
Please let me go.
Don't kill me.
Mmh.
Spare me, I beg you.
Let me go.
I am doing this to help you.
To help you cleanse the filth of the flesh.
Those who defiled you...
...also deserve to die.
All deserve to die.
This annoying rainy weather...
...has finally stopped.
What is this?
Guess what Big Brother...
...brought for you to play with today.
Which one do you want?
I want this one.
Then you take this one.
I'll find one for you too.
How about this one?
Okay.
Children, breakfast is here.
Time to eat.
Put the toys away properly.
Eat up, eat up.
Me too, me too!
There's enough for everyone.
Everyone gets some.
Don't fight over it.
Big Brother Liu Tong.
The things you brought last time are still here.
Making these takes time and effort.
You don't have to go to such trouble.
Because of my appearance...
...only you...
...and these children don't despise me.
Being able to do something for them...
...is the least I can do.
As for you...
...at such a blooming age...
...revolving around these children every day.
These children...
...were either left behind by the dead...
...or left behind by criminals.
My sworn brother was afraid they'd have nowhere to go.
I'm considering this as helping my sworn brother out.
Then your sworn brother...
...how is Junior Minister Yao's investigation going?
Another victim appeared this morning.
Dismembered.
Another rainy night.
I fear it was done by the same person as the night before last.
We were still a step too late.
Such inhumanity.
It is truly an outrage to gods and men.
The killer clearly could have...
...dumped the body parts in the mountains.
Why dump them here?
This is a place where commoners gather.
Is the killer trying to cause panic?
He doesn't just want to kill.
He wants to instill fear in people's hearts even more.
He wants to disrupt all of Chang'an.
Perhaps he enjoys this feeling.
Give the order.
All gathering places in Chang'an...
...search for body parts.
East and West Markets, Pingkang Ward, Vermilion Bird Avenue.
Chongren Ward, the city gates.
Lord Vice Minister.
Body parts found on south Vermilion Bird Avenue.
Confirmed.
My Lord, body parts found in Pingkang Ward.
My Lord, body parts found in the East Market.
My Lord, body parts found in the West Market.
My Lord, body parts found at the East City Gate.
My Lord, body parts found at the South City Gate.
Old Yao
It's been a whole day.
You haven't had a drop to drink. Rest a bit.
If I rest, I'm giving the culprit time.
Not bad, Vice Minister.
You have the style I had back in the day.
You...
Vice Minister.
Shut up.
Mm.
Based on the portrait you reconstructed,
the identity of the deceased is confirmed.
Chun'er, the Top Courtesan of Hundred Phoenixes Pavilion.
Another prostitute.
Also on a rainy night.
Mm.
Also not sexually assaulted.
A total of thirty-seven body parts.
The lungs are missing.
Yet the torso remains intact.
The second painting has appeared.
Appearance stems from the mind.
Vicious, cruel, heartless.
Derives pleasure from the act of killing.
Capable of killing through the night,
and dumping bodies all across Chang'an.
Given his agility,
he cannot be a heavy man.
His targets are all prostitutes,
yet the victims were not sexually assaulted.
He is not driven by lust.
The money earned by prostitutes
is held by the Madam,
so he cannot be after money either.
He destroys their faces...
Is it out of inferiority?
Is he ugly?
Or does he have scars on his face?
If he has scars on his face,
he would surely cover them with his hair.
It's another rainy night.