♪Light, etched on the old wall♪
♪Shadows dancing like memories♪
♪Don't be afraid
of life's uncertainties♪
♪With you by your side♪
♪Destiny, mere scattered coins♪
♪Traded for bolts of red silk♪
♪Wait, love braving the stormy tides♪
♪To take me far away♪
♪Perhaps in this world, only you♪
♪Can warm my soul♪
♪With you here,
spring stays kind even as time flows♪
♪Yet I stand unshaken♪
♪Life, too fleeting♪
♪Fortunately,
we turn yearnings into bonds♪
♪Trust the end that it will bloom♪
♪No longer alone♪
=Spring Burning=
=Episode 20=
How's it going?
Here's the payroll from accounting.
Take a look.
(Anshi Shantou Town Steel Factory Payroll)
Li Jianguo, Li Jianhua, Li Jianzhong...
A whole family working at the factory?
I remember only one family member
is allowed to work in the factory.
If they're all actually working, fine.
But I checked
some just collect pay
without doing any work.
How bold.
I'm planning an audit,
but we can't tip them off first.
Let them stay complacent.
Good. Also, Qian Fugui has been
causing trouble lately,
planning to lead a protest.
With the new factory director
and more layoffs coming,
people are nervous
without full details.
A perfect chance to see
who's pulling strings behind the scenes.
How are machine repairs?
Going well.
Director Li's team arrived early
and joined the repairs
immediately.
They're excited and motivated
with great efficiency.
Good.
That was smart of you.
Helped Director Li
and sped up our repairs.
When will you start the production?
In a few days.
The priority is to
win back the steel factory's
biggest lost contract.
(Mom and Dad, Shanshan misses you.)
What's wrong?
Recently, when we come home,
Shanshan's already asleep.
When we leave,
she's still not awake.
We haven't seen her properly in days.
If I were Shanshan,
I wouldn't like parents like this.
When I was busy before,
I was rarely home too.
We should spend time with her.
I remember when I was little,
my parents often took me out.
Short trips,
but
precious memories for me.
After they passed away,
I'd think back...
I'd also think
if I
ever became a mom,
I'd make sure my child
was happy and carefree.
Let's finish up quickly
and spend time with Shanshan.
Take her out for fun.
Deal.
Mr. Wang.
You again?
I've made myself clear.
About your small mold factory,
we can talk about cooperation,
but the steel factory is off the table.
Mr. Wang, I know your company needs it.
I do need it.
But can the steel factory produce it?
Do you know how huge the trouble you caused
last month?
Mr. Wang, I guarantee
this will never happen again.
Guarantee?
With what? Tell me.
We'll sign a high penalty clause.
The original contract had penalties in it.
But the account was empty.
What good was that?
Besides
I don't want penalties.
I want the goods.
Mr. Wang, take a look.
This is all the assets
the steel factory can mortgage.
If the factory fails to deliver,
my workshop will cover it.
If my workshop can't either,
all this goes to you.
- What are you doing?
- Get out! Out!
Go!
Hurry up!
You'll regret this!
Just wait!
Master! Master!
- Trouble!
- What?
The new director's team
are at the accounting office.
Hurry!
Get the poorest workers
- to protest.
- On it! I'll gather them.
Hurry! Let's go!
Follow me! This way!
- Go.
- What?
- They didn't pay us!
- You can't go in!
- It's them!
- Don't force me!
What's going on?
Everyone, calm down!
If you can't run the steel factory,
the Shuguang Group can!
At least they'll pay our wages!
Exactly! They promised us salaries long ago!
Our families are starving!
Just pay up already!
Watch your words!
Everyone, calm down! Settle down!
I've received the name lists.
I'm fully aware
of the situation.
Once the accounting team
finishes accounting,
everyone will get paid.
Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- All talk no action!
You've been promising salaries!
Within one week at most,
you'll all get paid.
What does a woman like you know about it?
Hey!
Watch your mouth!
Accounting is simple.
I know you,
Liu Shishuai.
Two unexcused absences this month,
plus two late arrivals.
Instead of getting the monthly bonus,
you'll get a five-yuan deduction.
Guys, you should thank him
for contributing to our payroll fund.
This is the new head of accounting
and deputy director of the factory.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Lu Ran.
Top accounting graduates
from Anshi University
will conduct a full audit.
Attention, please. Attention please.
The steel factory has resumed production.
The accounting office is finalizing payroll.
Salaries will be issued in seven days.
Wages in seven days!
Did you hear that?
Stop crowding here.
- You can go.
- Please, leave.
- Leave.
Would the PA system lie?
Back to work, everyone!
- Ran.
Let's go inside and talk.
Come on.
(Accounting Office)
Teacher Wang,
thank you so much for helping us.
Don't mention it.
This audit
is a valuable practical experience
for our mathematics students.
I should be thanking you.
Teacher Wang.
You're being too polite.
Have some water.
Thanks.
We're planning to audit
all the factory accounts
from the past ten years.
No problem.
Let me go make arrangements.
Alright, thank you.
Take care, Teacher Wang.
Do you think we'll get caught
moving the account books out?
Don't worry, it's fine.
Ma Qiang moved them overnight.
Right inside the factory.
Those people probably still think
the books are in the office.
Good.
Here, and here...
I thought you'd fallen asleep.
How could I?
With this audit going on,
half the factory wants me dead.
Someone tried to burn down
the accounting office.
Got caught.
Sent to the police.
It's handled now.
You must be exhausted.
Should I take you home to rest?
No.
Where you go, I go.
Brother Qi, Ran.
Trouble!
- What?
- Explain slowly.
About today's shipment.
Our transport team
abandoned the trucks halfway.
Workers are protesting
and blocking operations.
Don't worry, it's handled.
Brother Qi, Ran.
Those transport scoundrels
dumped loaded trucks on the roadside,
but Brother Shenggong sent two groups.
One is guarding the goods.
One seized the transport team
and took their keys.
About the transport team?
Fire them all.
Brother Qi,
the repaired machines
have greatly improved efficiency.
This week's output equals
a whole month's production before.
Exactly,
all machines are fixed.
And the transport team is back.
Production can resume fully now,
both manufacturing and
logistics.
What's next?
After the audit finishes,
we'll start personnel restructuring.
- Got it.
- Yes.
Then we'll expand production
to secure more contracts.
We'll head out now.
- Go ahead.
- On it.
- Got it.
- Bye.
Let's get back.
Back to work.
How are we supposed to survive?
No wages for months.
Exactly! Just bullying us workers.
Yeah.
I heard
many got taken away recently.
Probably all the corrupt ones.
The director's been interviewing people.
Many left jobless afterward.
Are we...
the next?
What should we do then?
Can't leave empty-handed.
Gotta take something.
Why fire me?
I'm their supervisor!
I've worked here for over ten years!
More like idled for ten years.
How could you idle that long?
Never did any real work,
just bossed us around all day.
None of your business!
Exactly!
Just leave already!
Collecting pay for no work.
The director made the right call firing him.
Indeed.
Quality Control Director was taken away.
You know about this?
I know.
He's trying to reduce his sentence
by reporting
that you bought subpar materials,
took bribes from him.
That's why our steel
passed factory inspections
but had crazy return rates.
Director Qi, that's... that's his story!
It was him colluding with
Mr. Sun from Logistics.
He's dumping the blame on me!
Director Qi, it's not true!
Don't believe him!
Then tell me the truth.
Fine. I'll explain everything.
Making this big of a scene,
even involving city officials.
Isn't this too...
Why hesitate now?
I've arranged everything.
Old Sun, you'd really let
some random blacksmith
treat us like dirt?
The whole management
backs my plan now.
As long as we workers strike
and halt production,
Qi Shengfeng won't stand a chance!
If you side with him,
you're betraying all of us.
Think carefully.
But...
No "buts"!
They're auditing the books.
Your family needs those wages.
Fine. I'm in.
Mr. Sun! Mr. Sun!
What?
Police are here. They want to talk.
Let's go.
Ask your questions quick.
I've got no time for delays.
Luo Guoqiang.
Lately, several staff
got taken in by the police.
You know this?
Yeah. What's it to me?
Someone reported you
selling factory steel as scrap,
pocketing huge profits.
The arrested man already confessed.
He said you masterminded it.
He just assisted.
Lies!
Ma'am,
I didn't do this.
Our investigation shows
your family's struggling.
We doubt you could lead such a scheme,
so we're offering you a deal:
Confess everything voluntarily,
provide physical evidence,
and you'll get leniency.
I have proof.
My own ledger.
I'll hand it over.
Mr. Fang!
Who sent you?
Trouble, Mr. Fang!
Qi Shengfeng's up to something.
The police just took away
dozens of people from the factory.
All our plan participants.
Keep calm.
Don't panic about minor disturbances.
However many they arrest,
what proof links them to you?
He's auditing the books...
If they...
It's actually good for us.
We want workers paranoid.
Those laborers understand nothing.
We need manufactured chaos,
make them feel besieged. Understood?
These workers have no clue
what's happening.
They just know
the director is investigating them.
I can throw the fuel on the fire.
At least you're acting like
a deputy director.
Stick to the plan.
- Leave. Now.
- Yes, I'm leaving.
(Worthless fool.)
(Deputy director?)
(In your dreams.)
Listen, everyone!
You've all seen it.
Ever since Qi Shengfeng
took over the steel factory,
he's ignored us workers
completely.
Worse, he's purged dissenters
and installed his cronies,
showing no mercy.
Now he's having police
arrest our colleagues.
Months without pay,
what's wrong with taking supplies?
- Right!
- Exactly!
Isn't it? It's!
I only took three stools!
They arrest us for that?
- Still no wages!
- Right?
- Exactly!
- Yeah!
Has anyone been paid yet?
- Not a cent!
- Nothing at all!
Families going hungry!
Let's go demand our wages!
- Confront them now!
- We will get our pay!
Move out!
Accusing us of nepotism?
Fine.
What's your name?
Everyone,
this is Qian Ronghua,
nephew of Chief Qian Fugui.
Qian has eight relatives in our factory,
four just collecting paychecks without work.
How does she know?
Not just Chief Qian.
We've checked
all the ghost workers.
(Folder)
116 in total.
116?
- That many?!
- Unbelievable!
97 clocked in
but never worked.
8 unqualified
'managers'.
Should they earn money
like you?
- No way!
- Hell no!
- Why them?
We've worked so hard.
These days,
we've been auditing
the factory's old accounts
and verifying the employees.
But shockingly,
someone tried to
burn the ledgers with people!
It's so vicious.
What is this called?
Murder and arson!
After the audit,
serious cases went to the police.
For the rest?
Director Qi says
clean slate and a fresh start.
Let's rebuild this factory
together!
Seriously?
No consequences at all?
I don't buy it.
We haven't even been paid!
Since when can we trust her?
Are you accusing me of favoritism?
Lately,
the factory keeps having strikes.
I want to tell everyone,
these shipments don't just
appear out of thin air.
It's these few people
working day and night,
working overtime to get them done.
Once the payment arrives,
we can pay everyone's wages.
From now on,
all employees keeping production going
will get a pay raise,
plus an extra 100 in bonuses.
This won't do. We need a solution.
What can I do?
We'll issue payments today.
From now on,
20% of annual profits
will go to worker bonuses.
More work, more rewards.
Bonuses? Unheard of!
Unheard of!
What they're holding
are the audited ledgers.
Today's promise is sealed
by burning the old books.
The books.
It's burning. It's burning!
Yes!
This...
It's really burning!
And they're just letting it go?
They lit it up!
It's burning!
It's really on fire!
Look! It's really burning!
Shantou Town Steel Factory Balance Sheet.
Good! Good!
There's hope now!
We'll get wages, plus bonuses!
Good! Good! Good!
Finally, real action!
We're getting paid!
We'll have money at last!
- Good!
- Great!
There are bonuses too!
(Shantou Town Steel Factory)
Mr. Fang! Mr. Fang! Mr. Fang!
It's been so long. What happened?
They're already rioting!
- Go in!
- Let's go!
(The steel factory is in chaos.)
(Qi Shengfeng…)
(Your downfall is finally here.)
Good! Good! Good!
There's hope now! There's hope now!
Pay back our hard-earned money!
This factory ruined our jobs!
(Work and a living!)
Pay us back!
Pay back our hard-earned money!
Pay back
- our hard-earned money!
- Director Qi!
You've been accused of
firing staff without cause.
How do you respond?
Director Qi, you favor cronies here.
Doesn't this betray
your promises to the workers?
Director Qi, you still haven't
paid back wages.
What's your explanation?
♪Under the dim streetlamp, lane's end♪
♪Two shadows stretch endlessly♪
♪Those unspoken words that day♪
♪Are you still waiting for my reply♪
♪Since you stormed into my journey♪
♪Chaotic years hold no more fear♪
♪Look back, I'll always be here♪
♪Don't be afraid of the distance♪
♪Believe I'll race to where you stand♪
♪Around us♪
♪The spring breeze is blowing♪
♪Tugs my sleeves skyward♪
♪Toward the warmth of your embrace♪
♪Around us♪
♪The spring breeze is blowing♪
♪Nears hearts leaning close♪
♪How blessed that our paths entwine♪