♪Light, etched on the old wall♪
♪Shadows dancing like memories♪
♪Don't be afraid
of life's uncertainties♪
♪With you by your side♪
♪Destiny, mere scattered coins♪
♪Traded for bolts of red silk♪
♪Wait, love braving the stormy tides♪
♪To take me far away♪
♪Perhaps in this world, only you♪
♪Can warm my soul♪
♪With you here,
spring stays kind even as time flows♪
♪Yet I stand unshaken♪
♪Life, too fleeting♪
♪Fortunately,
we turn yearnings into bonds♪
♪Trust the end that it will bloom♪
♪No longer alone♪
=Spring Burning=
=Episode 14=
What is the universe?
It is so cold upon the imagination
that we must try every month
to explore it.
- One of today's wonders.
- Sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law.
Second Brother, why are you here?
Shengfeng's workshop is about to collapse.
What's going on?
No time to explain. Let's talk on the way.
Okay.
Second Brother, slow down.
Slow down.
Shengfeng,
why are you here?
Second Brother just told me.
Has the specification been confirmed?
This should be it,
but it's just a guess.
What's the delivery deadline?
Yesterday.
So we've breached the contract.
Why are you sitting there?
Quick, show me the order
from Zhou Huacheng.
This is it.
If we lose this order,
the deposit, the penalty,
and the costs of manpower and resources
will be enough to crush us.
No way.
We must get the order
from Shuguang Group back.
I'll go to Shuguang Group first.
No matter what,
you need to
bring the correct goods
to Shuguang Group to find me.
Alright.
I'll check the goods
and see if I can adjust them.
Alright.
Brother Qi, Brother Qi.
Brother Qi.
Brother Qi, Ran,
something happened.
I got the latest specifications,
but I heard another supplier
started to supply today.
They used
the batch of goods we delivered yesterday.
This is exactly the same as Zhou Huacheng's.
Ran!
Everyone,
let's adjust the process
of the previous goods
for secondary processing.
Zhou Huacheng's order is still in progress.
It's not enough.
Let's modify the wrong batch
and send it to Shuguang.
Ms. Bai, please sit.
Manager Fang,
why hasn't the batch arrived?
The supplier who was supposed to deliver
breached the contract.
I found another one.
Another one?
The previous one was too unreliable.
Luckily, I found
a better one in time.
Alright,
can the samples arrive on time?
Rest assured. They'll be here soon.
Manager Fang, you should be well aware
that Chairwoman Bai values this project.
Don't worry,
I take it even more seriously.
How much longer do I have to wait?
Lu Lan?
Mr. Zhou, you have a poor memory.
Lu Ran.
Ran, Ran, Ran.
Maybe one day you'll go to jail,
and your memory will improve.
I'm waiting, I'm waiting.
You're here to deliver goods too?
What?
Only you can have cooperation,
not me?
Are you the supplier?
Yes.
I'll go call the bosses.
Hurry up.
Ms. Bai, Mr. Fang, the supplier is here.
They're downstairs.
Ms. Bai, after you.
They're here.
Mr. Fang.
Long time no see.
Lu Ran.
Mr. Zhou,
this is the project leader,
Ms. Bai.
I thought she was a fairy.
Zhou Huacheng.
Ms. Bai.
This is...
Lu Ran,
the one who breached the contract.
Hello, I'm Lu Ran.
I'm also here to submit samples.
I'm already aware of your situation.
You breached the contract.
So we won't look at your goods.
Our legal team will contact you later
for the penalty.
Ms. Bai, this time it's really...
I don't want useless explanations.
- Let's see the goods.
- Okay, come on.
Make way, make way. Come on.
Take a look.
We guarantee the quality is absolutely fine.
Aren't these samples?
Why so many?
It's about sincerity. The more, the better.
Come on, I'll open one for you.
Take a look. Absolutely no issues.
The goods are fine.
See?
(The quantity is much more than
what's on the workshop's delivery list.)
Since the goods are fine,
Ms. Bai,
let's sign the formal contract
with Mr. Zhou today.
Okay.
Only the top layer?
Why not check deeper?
This...
Mr. Zhou's goods will pass any inspection.
As for you,
- delayed the delivery.
- Check the rest.
Your boss isn't here yet.
Is this your attitude?
Well...
You don't need to check the rest.
Let them inspect.
No, this... this...
Ms. Bai, there's a problem.
What problem?
Only the batch on the top is qualified.
The rest are all substandard.
Well...
Well... It's a misunderstanding.
Sell shoddy goods as quality ones.
Fang Hongyang,
is this the supplier you found
for such an important project?
Is this what you call reliable?
No, Ms. Bai, let me explain. He...
Things have come to this.
This is the result.
What's there to explain?
- Ms. Bai.
- Ms. Bai, let me finish.
Please take a look at our samples.
I know,
we indeed failed to
deliver the samples on time.
That's indisputable.
But the current problem is
the steel factory can't take the order,
and no factory can handle
such a large volume in the short term.
If we customize it in other provinces,
the transportation cost will be high,
which is not good for Shuguang.
Why not give us a chance?
Please give us a chance.
Shut up.
Ms. Bai,
we brought samples,
and we've pre-produced a batch as an apology.
If you're willing
to give us this chance,
you can inspect the goods first,
then pay the deposit.
If you're not satisfied,
we'll pay the penalty based on the contract.
I know,
the purpose of signing the contract
is to supervise production
and ensure the production efficiency.
It's not just about the money.
Where are the goods?
Outside.
Let's go take a look.
Follow me.
Ms. Bai.
Didn't you promise me
everything was fine?
I thought it'd be okay to add a little...
Get out!
Okay.
Let's go!
Ran.
We're here.
Here, the goods.
Did we make it?
Impressive.
The goods meet our specifications.
Excellent craftsmanship, up to standard.
Coordinate with my staff
to move the goods to the workshop.
I need the next batch in five days.
No problem.
I hope the delivery will be on time.
Got it, Ms. Bai.
Where should we put them?
Okay, that's fine.
Lu Ran, I need to talk to you.
Come inside with me.
Lu Ran,
you're about to go back to study.
Why are you still entangled with them?
Helping them secure orders, negotiating...
Senior Fang,
why don't you tell me first
why you're using such underhanded methods
to harm Qi Shengfeng?
Lu Ran, I did all of this for you.
For me?
I like you.
I don't want you to stay connected to him.
I want him to disappear from your world.
I don't want to lose you again.
I want you to come back to me.
Even if...
you've been married, I don't mind.
Who are you to mind?
Let me tell you again,
Qi Shengfeng is my husband.
Harming him is the same as harming me.
Lu Ran, you are a college student,
dignified, knowledgeable, and cultured.
You have a bright future ahead of you.
Why would you be with
a rural blacksmith?
I know what I want.
I don't need anyone
pointing fingers at my life.
Listen,
I am very happy now.
You're not part of my life.
Please stay out of it.
Lu Ran, I understand you.
If you're voluntary,
tell me, and I'll help you.
I'll help you continue your studies.
Who said I'm not here voluntarily?
Yes,
I do want to continue studying,
but choosing to be with someone I like
doesn't conflict with it.
What did you say?
You like...
You like Qi Shengfeng?
Yes,
I like Qi Shengfeng.
I stay with the Qi family
because I want to be with him.
I have never regretted marrying him.
Lu Ran, you worked so hard
to get into college.
Why would you want to be with him?
You're throwing your life away.
All your studying is wasted!
Fang Hongyang,
it's your studying that's wasted.
Haven't I been good to you?
Where am I inferior to him?
I am the son of a city leader,
a college student,
the general manager of Shuguang Group.
- I'm...
- Just one thing,
Qi Shengfeng would never use dirty tricks
to harm others.
Lu Ran, I can explain it.
- Let go!
- Lu Ran.
Listen to me.
Manager Fang,
Lu Ran has made it clear.
Please stop pestering her, okay?
Lu Ran.
(Lu Ran,)
(you're an orphan with no parents.)
(How dare you turn me down?)
(How dare you talk to me like that?)
(Qi Shengfeng, Lu Ran,)
(two overconfident fools.)
Lu Ran,
did you hear everything?
No, I didn't.
Let's go back to the workshop.
You told me not to meddle in it.
Now you're asking me to go back.
You've helped us so much.
Everyone is waiting for you there.
Alright.
I can go back to see them.
Then I'll take you back.
No need, I've got legs. I'll walk.
Lu Ran, don't walk. I have a car.
Does it make you special?
Thanks to Ran,
(Shenghua Mold, Pursue Excellence)
we've made it.
Otherwise, our factory
would've been finished.
Indeed.
Ran,
how did you know
Zhou Huacheng sold shoddy goods
as quality ones?
I'm also wondering.
Before I left,
I checked our delivery notes to Zhou Huacheng
and compared them
with the quantities on site.
They didn't match.
They can't produce
products of our quality.
Yes.
Ran, you're really smart.
- Indeed.
- Yes, Ran is clever.
Although we've secured
the order from Shuguang Group this time,
the delivery time is very tight.
You must ensure both the quality and quantity.
Let's get to work quickly.
I'll head off now.
Take care, Ran.
Brother Qi,
did you upset her?
She doesn't seem to want to deal with you.
None of your business.
Go check the quantities.
See how many are missing.
Modify the goods
or melt down and recast them.
I'm just concerned about you.
Do I need your concern?
We don't have much time.
Take shifts if you're tired,
- but quality must be ensured.
- Okay.
Aren't you confident in our work?
- Good.
- Let's go.
- Go ahead.
- Go, go.
Ma Qiang.
- Brother Qi.
- Sit down.
Brother Qi,
this time it's my fault.
It's all my fault.
If something happens,
the workshop will really be gone.
I can't face staying here anymore.
Once this order is done,
I'll leave the workshop.
The problem isn't solved yet.
Instead of thinking about how to fix it,
you want to run away, huh?
Brother Qi, I really don't mean it like that.
I know.
Don't forget,
we're brothers.
Brothers face problems together
and find solutions together.
What's most important now
is figuring out how to make up for it.
Brother Qi,
got it.
I'll work hard.
Such a thing won't happen again.
I'll get back to work.
Wishes within the sunlight become warm.
And the heat causes most materials...
Lu Ran,
Lu Ran.
Why are you here?
I need to talk to you.
Can you open the door first?
Just say it here.
I like you.
You say you like me,
but why won't you let me
handle your affairs?
You even found a place for me to move out.
What do you mean by saying all this now?
I just wanted to find you
a quiet place to study.
I was afraid we would disturb you.
Are you upset because of this?
Did you discuss
this matter with me?
Did you ask for my opinion?
I wanted you to realize
your wish to return to school.
I didn't think that much.
Then why are you coming to me now?
Just because of the order from Shuguang?
Are you here to thank me?
Of course not.
Actually,
what you said to Fang Hongyang...
I...
I overheard it.
If you hadn't, you wouldn't have come.
I would definitely come.
I had decided long ago
to come find you after your exams.
Can you open the door first?
Promise me something first.
Promise me, then I'll open it.
Open the door first.
I'll agree to whatever you say.
Go... go ahead.
Can you promise me
not to shoulder everything alone
in the future?
Discuss things with me.
Let's face any difficulties together.
Okay, I promise.
♪With you by your side♪
Lu Ran,
do you like me?
Are you a blockhead?
Whether I like you or not,
didn't you hear it all that day?
♪To take me far away♪
♪Perhaps in this world, only you♪
♪Can warm my soul♪
♪With you here,
spring stays kind even as time flows♪
♪Yet I stand unshaken♪
Then,
will you marry me?
♪Fortunately,
we turn yearnings into bonds♪
We need to date first,
then get married.
Date?
How do you date?
Dating means
you become my boyfriend first.
It's like a trial period before marriage.
Got it. Okay.
You're supportive of me
going back to study.
Aren't you afraid that after that,
I might leave you?
Everyone says
I tried to escape the wedding,
and once I'm at university,
we won't last long.
No.
I've told you before,
you're free to make any choice you want.
I'll support you.
When you go to university,
I'll keep working hard
and make our business bigger.
♪When we gaze into eyes deep and true♪
♪All sorrows fade♪
Then let's pack our things.
Pack what?
Pack our things and go home.
We're dating now.
Why go home?
Mom said she wants to
have a meal with you.
Then I'll go back.
During the dating period, please behave well.
Otherwise,
I won't go home with you.
♪Fortunately,
we turn yearnings into bonds♪
♪Trust the end that it will bloom♪
♪No longer alone♪
♪Under the dim streetlamp, lane's end♪
♪Two shadows stretch endlessly♪
♪Those unspoken words that day♪
♪Are you still waiting for my reply♪
♪Since you stormed into my journey♪
♪Chaotic years hold no more fear♪
♪Look back, I'll always be here♪
♪Don't be afraid of the distance♪
♪Believe I'll race to where you stand♪
♪Around us♪
♪The spring breeze is blowing♪
♪Tugs my sleeves skyward♪
♪Toward the warmth of your embrace♪
♪Around us♪
♪The spring breeze is blowing♪
♪Nears hearts leaning close♪
♪How blessed that our paths entwine♪