Doctor!
It's not what you think!
- Prem!
- Wait, Pat!
Why was the doctor here?
And what's the matter?
Prem!
Prem...
Let me explain!
Pat,
let go of me.
Prem, pull yourself together and listen to me.
Nothing happened.
I swear.
But I saw what you two were doing!
You got it all wrong!
I got it all wrong?
Friends...
aren't as intimate as you two were.
I wasn't intimate with her!
I was sleepy.
I didn't even know when I fell asleep.
Once I woke up, I saw you at the door!
Do you really think what you're saying
is believable?
Well, it's the truth.
What I saw was also the truth.
I trusted you, Pat.
I did it for your friend
who just went through a miscarriage.
You did the right thing.
Nothing truly happened.
Stop saying nothing happened!
Don't you understand
that I'm not comfortable with what I saw?
So what do you want me to do?
I don't know.
I don't know!
Can you give me just another chance?
I would never cheat on you.
Please trust me.
Trust...
is easily given the first time,
but once it's broken,
it's hard to earn back.
♫All I can do is hold back tears,
knowing our last days are near,♫
♫Even though the end is what we both fear♫
♫I keep telling myself I need to face reality,♫
I think you'll have to find a better way.
♫It's painful going against my heart♫
♫It's painful that we have to part♫
♫All I can say is a tearful goodbye♫
What happened, Pat?
I can't stay here with you tonight.
Was I the reason you and the doctor fought?
I can kinda tell.
I don't have anything against you dating her.
It's your personal choice, after all.
Thank you for getting it.
Earlier, Prem misunderstood us.
It was me.
I'm sorry.
My top was falling off,
so I leaned in to wake you up.
That's probably why she took it the wrong way.
I can tell her
my side of the story if you want.
It's fine.
I'll handle it.
Ow!
What's wrong, Nam?
I'm suddenly getting a cramp, Pat.
Ow...
Ow!
It'll take a moment.
- Hang in there.
- Ow!
I already called the nurse.
It's fine, Pat.
I'm okay. Just go.
Ouch...
- Ow...
- It's fine.
I'll stay for now.
It's okay, Pat.
Ow, ow...
I'm fine on my own...
Ouch!
Hang on, I'll get the nurse.
Ow!
[You have a new message]
Prem, are you feeling better now?
I'll stop by tomorrow.
Let's talk then.
[RAM2 Hospital]
Why the long face?
You were happy yesterday.
By the look of it,
you're mad at each other, aren't you?
That woman
had a miscarriage.
Hm?
Which one?
The one Thawat got pregnant.
Are you serious, Prem?
I am.
She's in recovery just upstairs.
Pat's taking care of her.
Right, because they are best friends.
Pat also had feelings for her.
And you're jealous?
I don't know what happened to me.
I've never been like this before.
That's how it is.
The more you love, the more jealous you get.
Talk it out nicely, Prem.
You're certainly
not the type to have a catfight over a lover.
You think that's funny, Tan?
He's right, though.
Just sit still, look pretty
as long as she doesn't do anything suspicious,
like Bow always does.
Sita!
I can't help you with that, Bow.
Just kidding.
It's good to be on the lookout, though.
Old flames die hard.
Don't let that woman
steal another lover from you.
Thank you for keeping me company, Pat.
Don't sweat it.
You're not cramping anymore?
Mm,
it's better.
I'm sorry
that I kept you from seeing Dr. Prem.
It's probably better
to give her time to cool down
so that we can reason with each other.
I don't mean to stick my nose in,
but I don't think
Thawat is giving up on her that easily.
Prem already left him behind.
How come you're so sure?
I trust her.
No matter what,
she's not going back to that douche.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
I'd prefer not to.
This time...
I'm not here to make excuses.
I just want to apologize.
So can we talk?
I want to apologize
for everything.
I admit I made a mistake,
but I'm now free from that woman.
Free?
Yeah.
I have no ties with her anymore.
How can you say that?
You're the reason she had a miscarriage!
You're supposed to take care of her now!
How did you know she had a miscarriage?
Did someone tell you?
It doesn't matter how,
but you can't just brush off
your own responsibility like that!
Prem...
I don't love that woman!
I love you!
Can you give me another chance?
There's no such thing anymore.
Marry me, Prem.
Let me go!
I'm not marrying you!
No, we have to, Prem.
I don't love you!
No, that's not true.
Get off her right now!
What don't you get about her not loving you?
And what does that have to do with you?
This is between Prem and me!
Prem's business is also mine!
I gave you a chance, Prem,
but you refused to choose me.
Don't come crying to me later.
Wait here, Prem.
Hey, you!
If you get any closer to her...
Why?
A woman like you is just a freak toy
that comes into her life.
Prem's just in a phase,
but once she comes to her senses,
she will know that I'm the real stuff!
Why do you still have the guts to meet him?
You know how he is!
You have the guts to go back
to your old flame, don't you?
Prem!
You're one to talk
when you still haven't dealt
with your problems?
I was gonna do that,
but I didn't think
I'd find him assaulting you!
What would happen
if I were here a little too late?
Too late?
You didn't even come last night.
Do you know
that I waited for you?
Nam had a stomach cramp last night.
It was beyond my control,
so I was planning to talk to you today.
And how did that turn out?
Was it as convenient as you thought?
Why are you so unreasonable?
So now I'm unreasonable?
I love you,
and I give you my sincerity,
yet you still don't trust me.
Have you done anything to earn that trust
apart from sending that one text
and disappearing for a night?
Maybe I set my expectations too high,
thinking you would put your trust in me
the same way I did in you.
Maybe I also set my expectations too high
that you would care more.
Everything I did all this time
is not enough proof?
That's a separate issue, Pat.
Do you want me to just cut her off?
I'm not saying that.
But it seems like you want me to.
I'm just gonna say this.
Nam is a lot more trustworthy than that jerk.
The one who should be jealous
is me
after seeing my own girlfriend
talking to her ex.
If you still don't get what I'm saying,
then we'd better not talk now!
Prem!
Get back to our conversation!
I want to be alone.
♫A forbidden love of two souls,♫
♫The more I suppress,♫
♫The more it unfolds♫
♫It's gonna cut deep, I know♫
♫I'm not supposed to yield,♫
♫But the closer to you, the more I feel♫
♫As much as I want to hide,♫
♫I run back to your sight♫
♫Heavenly, yet it's hell,♫
♫Luring me before I fell♫
♫Into your loving realm,♫
♫No way to tear it apart♫
♫Like the thorns
that pierce through my heart,♫
♫Your love sinks me to the bottom♫
♫It's agonizing, yet alluring♫
♫Like the sweetest poison,♫
♫The more I resist, the more I yearn♫
♫In the end, to you, I always turn♫
♫Forbidden to the touch,
though the distance insists I must♫
Pat.
♫Like a moth to a flame♫
♫A tether meant to claim,
pulling on my soul,♫
♫Chaining me tight, no matter where I go♫
♫A bitter love that stings♫
♫Tastes so sweet to the tongue,
its irresistible poison clings♫
♫Heavenly, yet it's hell,♫
♫Luring me before I fell♫
Do you know why I gave you this dollhouse?
It's because I want to spend
the rest of my life with you.
♫Like the thorns
that pierce through my heart...♫
These are heart-shaped,
just like your pendant!
Exactly,
I gave you my heart,
so we can match.
♫Like the sweetest poison,♫
♫The more I resist, the more I yearn♫
Pat.
I don't know why you're sad.
But you still have me.
♫Like the thorns
that pierce through the heart,♫
♫Your love sinks me to the bottom♫
♫It's agonizing, yet alluring♫
♫Like the sweetest poison,♫
♫The more I resist, the more I yearn♫
♫In the end, to you, I always turn♫
Pat,
I want some orange juice.
Can you get it for me?
[Prem]
- Gosh!
- Oops...
It's all messy now!
I'm sorry, Pat!
You...go change upstairs in my bedroom.
There are some of your blouses.
Okay...
[Prem]
I'm leaving.
Pat, slow down.
Stay the night, Pat.
I can't.
Why?
Do you...
not want to be close to me anymore?
I have errands.
What errands?
What can be more important than me?
Please spend the night, Pat.
I miss you...
very much, even.
We're friends, Nam.
But I don't want to be just friends.
I know
that I brought you down,
but can I please get another chance?
This time...
I will make it up to you really nicely...
Don't do this, Nam.
Why not?
You have feelings for me, don't you?
That was all in the past, Nam.
It's over.
I'm with someone I love now.
Don't make me uncomfortable being around you.
Pat is mine.
You're just a rebound.
Doctor!
Yes?
You were my patient yesterday, right?
You got that right.
You provided the best treatment yesterday,
so I want to show
my appreciation with this dessert.
This is for me?
It is.
Here.
Thank you again, Doctor.
Dr. Melanee,
a word, please.
Thank you.
Please excuse me.
I can't take my eyes off you, can I?
What do you mean?
The patient bought me a gift,
so I accepted it.
Is that all?
It is.
I thought you didn't like sweets?
I don't.
I prefer the taste of something else.
This tastes a lot better.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I had to take care of something.
It's alright.
What did you want to talk about?
She seems like a piece of work.
She is.
I didn't think she would dare send it to me.
Judging from the hidden camera
and how Pat looks reluctant,
I think Nam's intention is pretty clear.
At first, I was blinded by jealousy,
but I have just realized
that she's being manipulative.
How long have you been fighting?
Five days.
If you want my suggestions,
I'd say that you two fighting doesn't help;
it only makes things worse.
Then...
what should I do?
Take it from someone
who has an excessively charming girlfriend,
I think you need to make her realize
that Pat is yours, no matter what.
♫You can only fall for me♫
So, have you made up with the doctor?
What? Why not?
Are you still mad at her?
I'm tied up by Nam.
Nam...
When will this name disappear from your book?
I don't want anything to do with her anymore,
but I also feel bad.
Also, we've been friends for so long,
yet I let that man
hurt her so bad she miscarried.
You feel pity for her, right?
Pat, it's okay to feel that way,
but you gotta understand Dr. Prem.
You're jealous of her and her ex,
so why couldn't she be jealous of you and Nam?
You're right...
But I was just hoping that
she'd trust me more.
Pat,
you're probably used to
being the youngest child
who is always spoiled
by the people around you.
But in a relationship,
you need to put yourself in her shoes.
Let me put it this way:
you can keep that huge ego
and avoid Dr. Prem all you want...
but are you happy with that?
No...
I miss her,
her face,
and her voice so, so bad.
There!
So what are you waiting for?
Did you seriously forget
how hard it was for you two to be together?
Do you realize what to do now
if you want her in your life?
Prem,
I'm sorry.
I didn't know my spoiled girl could say sorry.
I'm sorry
that I behaved so horribly,
but I never, ever thought
about cheating on you.
I love no one else but you.
I'm sorry, too,
that...I was quick-tempered.
No need for you to be sorry.
It was my own fault.
No more blaming yourself, alright?
I'm not mad at you anymore.
Then...
Can we make up?
I'll spend the night here, then.
Don't you have to be with your friend?
Well, I want to cuddle you to sleep.
Fine,
but you gotta go take a shower.
You're full of germs now.
Are you saying I'm a breeding ground?
You're not,
but you were with one.
Fine,
I'll go wash up real good.
Pat only went back to you
because I let her.
Just for a fling, not forever.
I smell good now!
- Tickle, tickle...
- Pat!
Tickle, tickle...
I think the tickler is getting tired.
Can she fall asleep next to you?
Isn't she all grown up now?
Not yet.
Let me sleep next to you, please?
Let's cuddle.
Mm.
[Nam]
Hello?
Pat...
I don't want to live anymore.
Nam, why would you...
Why would you say that?
I mean it, Pat.
No one loves me.
I don't want to live like this.
I want to die, Pat!
Nam, I'll come over right now.
Why do you smell so good today, Pat?
Prem, I have to go.
[Nam]
Pat?
Pat!!
[Nam]
I hate you, Dr. Prem!
It's all because of you...
Because of you...
Nam!
Nam,
I'm begging you,
can you please not do this again?
Don't leave me again, then.
But I can't be with you all the time!
Why not?
Do I disgust you now?
No...
Or do you hate me for real this time?
No wonder...
you don't care if I live or die.
It's not like that!
When I miscarried,
I was all by myself.
And now, you're leaving me again?
You don't have to love me
the same way I love you,
as long as we're together.
Can we please go back to the way we were?
Can you do that for me?
Or at least...
until I get better.
Please, Pat...
Prem,
Sita told us that Nam
is harassing you?
Tell us everything now.
Whoa...
This is hella creepy, Prem.
Wait...
she's been sending you all these?
Not to mention the ones I deleted.
I don't think this can go on.
What are you gonna do, Bow?
Do whatever a princess like you has to.
We'll play the fairy godparents.
[You have a new message]
I want to talk to you about Pat.
I'm tired of competing with you.
Pat,
I'll go out for some errands.
Wait at home, okay?
Can you go out alone?
I can.
It won't take long,
but you have to be here when I get home.
Mm.
I'll get changed, then.
Please.
You finally have the nerve to confront me,
Dr. Premsinee?
Why wouldn't I?
I thought you were a coward,
considering how you enjoy
stealing other people's partners.
I don't have to steal anyone
because people...
love approaching me.
Unlike someone here
who's desperate enough to do anything
just to keep their lovers trapped,
only to have them running for the hills.
Hey!
I'm not talking about you,
but I don't mind
if the shoe fits.
Just say what you have to say.
No need to act all angelic
with that mouth spitting snide comments.
If what I'm doing is spitting snide comments,
then what should we call your behaviors?
Who in their right mind...
would do what you're doing?
She doesn't want you,
yet you're desperate to have her.
Pat belongs to me!
Pat is not a property!
She can decide
who makes her happy.
Stop talking!
If she'd been happy with you,
she would've left me long ago.
But I'm sure you heard
how ecstatic she was with me.
So, who do you think is a fling?
What the hell are you doing, Nam?!
Prem, are you hurt?
I'll tell you right here
that I'm not yours.
I belong to Prem,
and I love her!
No,
you don't love her.
Don't you see she set me up
to provoke me!
But you have no right to hurt her!
Are you saying
she's more important than me?!
Yes!
She's the most important person in my life!
That's not true.
But it is.
It's time for you to wake up.
No,
I gotta be the one you love the most!
I don't love you anymore!
Stop being so delusional!
It's because of her, right?
She's the reason you changed.
I hate her!
I'm gonna get you back!
You can only be mine, Pat!
Only mine!
Pat's gotta be mine!
It's you!
Let go!
Let go of me!
It's because of you!
It's all because of you!!
Pat...
Pat?
I have given you so many chances,
yet you throw them down the drain.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you, Pat.
You can hurt me all you want,
but don't lay your hands on Prem.
I'm sorry...
I...
I just lost it.
I really didn't mean to, Pat.
Please don't be mad at me.
From now on, we're strangers.
No...
I'm... I'm sorry...
Pat, please don't be mad at me...
I didn't mean to.
I really didn't, Pat...
I really didn't mean to.
Pat,
everything I did
was out of my love for you.
I really do love you.
You don't;
you just can't bear the thought of me
loving someone else more than you.
Pat...
Please don't leave me.
Come on, I'll treat your wound...
Enough!
Don't make me hate you more than I do.
Please...
get out of my life.
And if you don't want
to be charged for assault,
don't show your face to me or Prem again.
Prem,
let's take Pat in for her injury.
Let's go to the hospital.
I'm sorry...
Pat!
[RAM2 Hospital]
Tan,
what do you think
the end of that woman will be?
What, Bow?
Haven't you already had one in mind?
So why are you asking?
Whatever.
Let's say, the plan
to have the princess bullied
in front of the knight
was a success.
Pat,
this is Bow.
We have to talk.
Where are you? I'll come find you.
Look at what your friend did to mine.
This is not all of it.
Look.
Bow,
can we consider ourselves the good ones?
We rented out the restaurant
just to set the whole thing up.
Princesses don't always have to be the victim.
Nam,
what took you so long?
I had to take care of something, Pat.
Well, then, let's find
something yummy to eat.
Mm...
Prem...
Is there anything you want to say?
I'm sorry
for how completely clueless I was.
You even got hurt because of me,
not to mention those crazy texts and videos.
Bow already showed everything to me.
Those videos were deceptive.
Nam edited them.
I genuinely could never love
anyone else, Prem.
I know.
I can't believe
that Nam could do
all those horrendous things to me.
I always thought
she was a good friend.
Sometimes,
you might think that
you know something really well,
when, in fact,
you don't know anything at all.
You're a woman,
so you must know
how complicated our emotions can get.
Please just be angry at me.
I feel horrible.
What are you saying?
It's better this way, right?
But...
in the soap opera, when the leads
fight because of a third party,
they usually end up in bed.
I want that kind of experience.
Be careful what you wish for.
Go take your meds.
Hurry.
Come on, let's get you the meds.
Alright?
Come on,
sit.
This is an anti-inflammatory pill.
It's a capsule, so it's not bitter.
Hold out your hand.
Please?
I can't take it.
My arm hurts.
Don't be so stubborn.
Take it.
The capsule's not gonna be bitter.
Give it to me, please?
My arm really does hurt!
♫You're the love I'm longing for♫
♫The heaven-sent one I adore♫
♫The final answer to my prayers♫
Drink some water.
Don't hold water in your mouth!
Thank you.
Get well soon, alright?
From now on, if something happens,
you gotta tell me
everything about it, okay?
Let's not have secrets anymore.
I'll tell you everything.
♫My heart will belong to you forever♫
What business do you have?
The same as last time.
If so,
the answer's the same.
We decided to leave it to Prem.
If she doesn't want to give you a chance,
then we can't help you.
Father, Mother,
hasn't it crossed your minds to change her?
What are you trying to say, Thawat?
So you don't know
that your sweet little daughter
likes women now?
Why are you doing this?!
I don't mind
that Prem's going astray.
I still want to marry her.
That's too bad.
Are you rejecting me, Father?
Exactly.
Now, get out of my house.
Thank you for letting us know
what an incompetent man you are,
failing to earn her love.
Incompetent...
Am I incompetent,
or is your daughter a freak?
Hey!
That kind of manner
won't be tolerated in this house!
When you cheated on her,
we never thought
to ask you to pay for what you did.
And now, you're pressuring us?!
Just leave my daughter alone.
Then, you can go around
parading your freak of a daughter.
But don't ever think
that someone like me will beg for her back.
And if people know that
your sweet Prem is a dyke...
who would want her?
Get out!!
Now!!
I'm getting out, alright.
But just remember
what a revolting being she is.
Why don't you look
at yourself in the mirror?!
Bastard!!
Leak the photos.