I always believed in you.
But you're the one who destroyed that.
How many times do I have to tell you
to stop seeing me as the one who died?
Do you not trust me,
or are you just jealous?
I did what I love.
You too. We just found
what we love in different ways.
If I ever see your face off the track again,
I'm running you over.
Bring Charlie back.
And get rid of everyone around him.
I didn’t lose on purpose.
I just never managed to beat you.
To the victory of X-Hunter.
- Cheers.
Hey North, you were killing it today.
What was your nickname again?
North Hot Speed, right?
Man, Dean.
With that performance...
He’s now been promoted to
North the Next King.
If he didn’t spin out first.
No idea. Whoa.
If Willy didn’t block my rise...
I would've finished side by side with Babe.
So intense.
My heart was about to explode.
Willy’s really leveling up.
Yeah, true.
Mhm.
Same here.
I thought we were done for.
Good thing Babe and Charlie made it back.
I'm telling you,
if we keep working as a team like this.
No one can beat X-Hunter.
But... are Babe and Charlie good now?
Aw, kid. Don’t worry.
If those two vanished from the after party.
Where else could they be?
Except...
It has to be for sure that...
That...
Drink.
I think you're drunk. Are you?
Someone’s heartbroken, huh?
I really hate it when we fight.
But I'm glad we could make up.
Babe.
I think we shouldn’t
get back together just yet.
Why?
I just need some time to think.
How much time do you need, Charlie?
Until I’m sure.
That I’m good enough
to really be by your side.
Please give me a bit more time.
What are you still unsure about?
You've stayed by my side
and looked after me.
You made me a better person.
We work well together, Charlie.
You saw it today, didn’t you?
What more do you need?
Or am I not good enough for you?
You are good enough, Babe.
But I just don’t want us to fight again.
About Willy, about the test laps...
Maybe it'd be better
if we had a bit of space.
It’s up to you then.
Why haven't you brought Charlie back yet?
And you even lost to him on the track.
Completely useless.
I just couldn’t find the right timing.
So I had to stay cautious.
Feels like he knows I have powers.
So what? I have to waste my time
just because you’re too scared to act?
You're afraid of him.
But you're not afraid of me.
Let me remind you of something.
Someone I raised with my own hands...
I still killed him.
So someone I brought back
from the dead like you...
Why would I keep you?
Don't bother trying.
Who the hell are you?
The one who brought you back from the dead.
And turned someone as ordinary as you...
into an alpha with special senses.
What the hell are you on about?
Let me go. Let go!
Fiery, huh?
You really do fight like a warrior.
But just so you know,
the chip in your body...
It could explode at any time.
If you work for me...
I'll let you live.
Yes.
I haven’t forgotten.
You’re the one who gave me a second life.
I’ll do whatever it takes to get Charlie back.
Good.
Let’s hope next time I see you,
you’ll bring good news.
Weird vibe in here.
North?
Sonic?
You guys fighting?
He’s fighting by himself.
He won’t talk to me.
He’s avoiding me too.
I’m not fighting anyone, uncle. I’m fine.
I’m just focused on training for the race.
You two, seriously...
If something’s wrong, just talk it out.
Don’t act like kids.
Jeff, is he helping Dean with the car?
Haven’t seen him, uncle.
Huh?
He left home since morning though.
- Where’d he go?
- Alan.
I finished the car setup.
Babe isn’t showing up today, right?
What about Charlie?
If Babe isn’t coming,
I doubt Charlie will either.
Want me to try calling them?
Yeah, give it a shot.
Okay.
No need to call, uncle.
Thought you weren’t coming.
Ever since you made up with Babe,
you’ve been totally gone.
Come on. Since you’re here, let’s train.
I’m not here to train today.
I came because there’s something
I want to tell you all.
What is it?
I want to resign from the team.
Charlie, you still haven’t made up with Babe?
I even gave you two alone
time in the locker room.
You didn’t show up to the party either.
This has nothing to do
with our relationship, uncle.
Right now, I just want to
focus seriously on my lab work.
And you’re quitting in the middle like this?
Can’t you wait until the season ends?
Racing is a team sport, you know?
I’m really sorry, bro.
I do love racing, I really do.
But the lab work just can’t wait.
I tried doing both,
and it just doesn’t work.
So I have to focus on the lab first.
Please try to understand me.
Alright, whatever.
You’ve already made up your mind anyway.
What’s your deal, seriously?
Just suddenly quitting the team?
Why are you mad? I quit uncle’s team...
Not the one you’re running, you know?
How can I not be mad?
I haven’t seen my boyfriend
this pissed in a while.
The garage vibes are already tense...
And you still had the guts to come find me?
Come on now.
This is more important
than your boyfriend’s mood.
The other day I raced with Willy.
I think he might be
an alpha with special senses.
But I don’t know what his power is.
So you’re not sure either?
Then that means everything
Babe suspected is true?
Then go apologize to him.
If I could tell him, I would’ve.
But I can’t say anything yet.
Because the one who sent Willy... was Tony.
Tony? Tony again?
That day, I followed Willy.
To figure out what his power really was.
Tony ordered Willy...
To take out everyone around me.
And he said...
He wanted me.
Probably to use me for something.
So it’s just like before all over again.
Only difference is...
it’s not Babe this time, it’s me.
By now, I’m sure he already knows
what my power can do.
Tony probably wants this power.
So that’s why you pretended to quit the team.
And won’t go back to Babe.
Even though...
you actually want to make up, right?
It’s better than putting
everyone else at risk.
You really think you’re a hero?
Solving everything on your own?
I can’t drag anyone else into this.
If anything goes wrong...
It’ll be just me who doesn’t make it.
Think it through.
Even if you die... how can you be sure...
That Tony will stop hurting others?
Is the path you’ve chosen
really the best one?
Hey, kid.
Where’ve you been?
Had some stuff to take care of.
Sorry I didn’t tell you first, uncle.
It’s alright. I get it.
Things at the garage have been messy lately.
If it’s too much, you have to let me know.
You too, uncle. If the pain's still there,
don’t forget to see a doctor.
- Gotta take care of your own body, you know.
- I know, I know.
- Babe.
What’s going on?
You’re here kinda late.
Sorry for dropping by so late.
Can I crash here tonight?
You good?
Charlie packed up and left.
I can’t sleep there alone.
Everywhere I look, I think of him.
You okay?
At first I really thought
we were gonna make up.
Things were finally going well.
Then he told me...
We can’t go back to how we were.
Kid, have you talked to Charlie lately?
Even Babe… Charlie won’t talk to him either.
To me? He doesn’t say anything at all.
Jeff, can you check my future for me?
See if Charlie and I will ever be together again.
Babe...
Come on, just check for me.
Please don’t lie to me.
I’m begging you.
Babe, my powers aren’t stable right now.
I don’t think I can read your future.
I’m sorry.
I’ll head inside first.
You two can talk more privately that way.
Then stay here tonight.
Take your time
and go back when you're ready.
Make yourself at home.
Thanks, uncle.
No worries. I’ve been the one
tying up every loose end anyway.
Come on, get some rest inside.
Don’t overthink. Just rest.
You woke me up early...
Just to watch you shadowbox in my room?
Kim, tell me honestly.
Can you not go back to Korea?
Can you come back and race for X-Hunter?
You already know why I left the team.
Because I want to be number one.
I was born to be
the main character, not a sidekick.
Sit down.
I think your back’s in trouble.
Take it easy or you’ll hurt it even more.
It’s fine. I’m okay.
If the team I built
half my life is falling apart...
A busted back isn’t that big a deal.
Alan, why are you getting all dramatic?
Now I feel bad, man.
What do you guys see my team as?
Come and go whenever you feel like it?
You and Charlie—where did I go wrong?
Sorry for ranting.
I just really don’t know what else to do.
If it’ll make you feel better...
Go ahead and yell. I can take it.
But if running the team...
is stressing you out this much...
Maybe you should take a break.
You can take a break from life too, you know.
If I step back,
what will everyone else do?
Racers like you still have a way forward.
But what about the rest of the crew?
They’re like family to me.
I’ve got a responsibility
to make sure everyone’s okay.
Whoa whoa, hey—wait up!
You care about everyone so much,
you forgot your own happiness.
You’re bottling up too much.
Be careful or you’ll end up like Kenta.
That’s not good.
That’s why I came to unload in your room.
And you, man...
You were the first one to leave my team
and stress me out.
You owe me for that.
So what did you call me out here for?
Don’t tell me you’re having problems
with your researchers again.
Why don’t you trust Chris?
Because he’s shady.
Just one look at that face and
you know to stay away.
But you still wanna mess with fire.
It’s not like I want him to replace Way.
I’m just not sure about myself yet.
So that’s all you needed?
I’m heading back.
Wait a sec.
I recovered the data
from the hard drive you gave me.
There’s someone listed
in the Unlock the Power of Change project.
His name is Kawin.
He was a former athlete who got
injured and couldn’t compete anymore.
Disappeared from home once.
The neighbors even called the police.
Then one day,
he just came back out of nowhere.
But what changed was…
Kawin started having mental issues.
You think it’s from the experiment?
I’m not sure yet.
Then just send me the rest of the info later.
I’ll take care of the rest.
Okay.
That look on your face—
did you and Pete have a fight?
What look?
Never mind.
Thought it was some
love drama or something.
Quit racing, dragged
your suitcase out of the house...
All I asked for was time.
Did you have to go this far?
Charlie, at least give me
a reason that makes sense.
Do you really think what you’re doing...
Is actually good for us?
I put all your meds in the pill box already.
Don’t forget to take them.
And your doctor’s appointments,
practice schedule, race schedule...
I added them all to your calendar.
That’s not what I want to hear.
I also cut up fruit and left it in the fridge.
While I’m gone,
please don’t drink too much.
If you really can’t sleep while I’m away...
You can always call me.
Charlie...
You love me that much?
Then why are you leaving me?
I still want to be your boyfriend.
Not your ex—someone you
just drop by to hook up with.
Please trust me.
Us living apart...
It’s better for both of us than forcing it.
Charlie...
I really do love you, Babe.
But I can’t be
the same person for you anymore.
Take care of yourself, okay?
Excuse me.
Is Kawin, the former
national swimmer, around here?
Does he live nearby?
He lives right next door.
Thank you.
- I need to talk to you, Mr. Kawin.
- Sir—
Mr. Kawin.
Please calm down, Mr. Kawin.
They sent you here to take me, didn’t they?
You’re Kawin, right?
I need to talk to you.
I’m scared. Please let me go.
Calm down, Mr. Kawin.
- Sir, Mr. Kawin.
- Mr. Kawin.
Mr. Kawin.
Just calm down.
Please calm down, Mr. Kawin.
What do you want?
Calm down.
You were part of the project—
What do you want? I’m scared!
They locked me up.
They stabbed me with a knife.
I’m not going back!
Please calm down. Can you remember
where they kept you?
They locked me in a building.
There were people in masks.
I'm scared. Demon snake. I'm scared.
Mr. Kawin.
What? What is it?
I think I might know...
What that demon snake really is.
Kid, that’s enough for now.
Everyone, gather up for a bit.
- North. Sonic.
- Yeah?
What’s going on, uncle?
Someone else quitting the team?
Nope. Just Charlie.
I’ve made up my mind.
I’m letting Dean race in Charlie’s place.
Me? Uncle?
Wait, are you being serious?
You sure about this?
Well, I agree.
Dean’s already got skills as a racer.
Honestly, he should’ve been
on the main lineup instead of me.
If he didn’t screw things up.
Hey, come on now.
I’m the captain, and I’ve decided.
Unless Dean doesn’t
want to race in the main league.
I’m in.
I’ll go with whatever you say, Alan.
If you believe in me...
Then I’m ready to prove myself to you.
Good. Let’s go over the race strategy then.
Come on. You too, North.
Hey, congrats, man.
Why are you avoiding me?
Why would I avoid you?
Exactly.
So what are you hiding from me?
Or is there something
you’re keeping from me?
Jeff...
You and Charlie—
what are you two hiding from me?
I...
I didn’t want to do this either.
Why?
What is it that I’m not allowed to know?
Actually, I was the one who told him.
Charlie became Tony’s target.
And Tony is planning
to kill everyone around Charlie.
Come in, Jeff. The door’s not locked.
Babe, how did you even get here?
So the reason you ran was because of Tony?
It’s like you let him come
ruin everything we have, Charlie.
If you’re afraid being
with me will get me killed,
Then I’ll be the one who stays close to you.
We agreed we should
keep our distance, didn’t we?
Charlie...
You made that decision all on your own.
I never wanted to be apart from you.
Here, I’ll add the noodles.
Just sit and wait, I’ll handle it.
But after you eat,
you really should go back home.
This isn’t going to work, Babe.
Please wait over there properly.
Mama just wants to know
how strong Papa’s will really is.
You really gonna stop here?
Mama came all this way to make up with you.
Papa, you’re not going soft on me at all?
You’re seriously stone cold.
What’s wrong?
I just want all of us
to stop going through this.
If there were no special senses or anything...
That might be the best way out.
Alright.
Let’s go with that then.
We don’t need to get back together just yet.
But Papa, please don’t push
Mama out of your life, okay?
Mama loves Papa so much.
You know that, right?
I should go finish cooking.
I’ll leave the ring here.
Wear it if you want.
If not, that’s okay too.
But I’m not going home just yet.
Why that face? Stressed?
Or… want me to go
with you to see the doctor?
It’s okay. I’ll just be out for a bit.
You sure?
Yeah.
Drive safe, okay?
Uncle.
- Haven’t eaten anything.
- What do you feel like eating?
Hmm… maybe something noodle-based?
Alright, not sure if they’re open though.
Papa.
Blow my hair for Mama?
The hairdryer’s in the room, babe.
Go grab it and do it yourself.
Papa, pretty please?
Just blow it for me?
Please? Pleaseee?
Fine. Wait here, I’ll go get it for you.
Mr. Alan has a chronic neck
spinal compression issue.
It’s been there since his racing days.
The doctor thinks it may likely get worse.
Surgery is recommended.
Please excuse me for a moment.
Hey kid, what’s up?
Hello? Hello, Uncle?
Uncle, I think my condition’s getting worse.
It’s… it’s more intense than before.
- Where are you right now?
- I don’t know.
It’s like I’m seeing double…
everything’s overlapping.
Kid…
Yes, Alan?
What did you say?
Okay, I’m on my way, Alan.
What happened?
Kid.
How are you feeling?
What happened to me?
You crashed the car.
Luckily, no brain damage.
No broken bones either.
Alan told me everything.
The side effects of
your power got worse, didn’t they?
You really can’t control it anymore?
Jeff.
Did you hear what I said, Jeff?
Jeff, can you hear me?
Kid.
Are you okay?
I’m seeing everything double… all over.
It’s okay. You’re okay.
I’m right here. You’re going to be fine.
I’m here. Don’t be scared.
Alan, is Jeff’s condition really this serious?
That ability-reversing
drug you’re working on—
There’s still hope, right, Charlie?
You okay, Uncle?
Yeah, I’m fine.
Have you seen the doctor yet?
Yeah, I already did.
- Chronic spinal compression in the neck.
- What?
They say I need surgery.
Is it that serious?
Yeah, but I’m not doing it yet.
Don’t worry about me.
But you should take care of yourself too.
I can’t.
I need to be here for Jeff.
Jeff’s in serious condition.
I can’t even help him right now.
If I go in for surgery…
I’d be leaving Jeff. Leaving you guys.
Leaving X-Hunter.
I’d hate myself even more.
It’s my fault.
I wasn’t strong enough to protect any of you.
Hey.
If we didn’t have you—
things would’ve been even worse.
But you’re still here, and that means a lot.
So stop blaming yourself.
Yeah. Thanks, man.
Charlie, what are you doing?
So you won’t have to suffer anymore.
Not like this, Charlie.
Not like this. Let go.
Charlie!
If you start experimenting on Charlie again,
won’t it make him worse?
And who gave you
the power in the first place?
Who told you to come here?
It’s your indecisiveness
that’s the problem. So annoying.
Lucky us, huh?
Getting to hug like this.
Stay here. I’ll distract him
and draw him away.
- But…
- Trust me.
Did you miss me, Babe?
And now… we reach right in.
Don’t pull down my pants! Ow!
Just place it gently, that’s all.
(Take it easy, Pel Pel.)
It’s just pretend, right?
I’m heading in now.
(Your audience awaits.)
- Watch out for wind monkeys.
- Wind monkeys incoming!
Get up, get up, get up!
(Brotherhood of men.)
A ghost ship?
(Captain’s going full drama mode.)
A ghost ship on the Chao Phraya?