The new researcher at
Pete's lab looks exactly like Way.
Please, come on in.
Right now, I just want
to earn back all your trust.
Just wait and see the person I sent in...
They’re gonna totally wreck X-Hunter.
So, Pit Babe,
wanna do something fun with me?
I'm a huge fan! Can I take a photo with you?
What the hell are you doing?
Is the bar seriously that packed?
Why do I smell alpha on you?
Call Babe, quick!
What?
Babe? Are you serious?
Alright, I’ll tell Charlie.
Touch.
Can you switch off the stim device?
Nobody's allowed to turn it off.
But I’m the one
who gave the order to shut it down.
Babe just had an accident.
Charlie needs to get to the hospital right now.
But the brainwave scan isn’t finished yet.
No one’s allowed to shut down the stim device.
Not even you.
Mr. Chris.
The one in the accident...
He’s Charlie’s boyfriend.
Even if the skill eraser is important,
it’s not more important than someone’s life.
Touch.
-Please shut down the stim device.
-Okay.
Charlie.
Charlie...
Charlie, wake up.
It’s a car accident case.
The guy who looked kinda cool.
Which room?
Let me check that for you.
How’s Babe doing, bro?
He's safe. Just a strained tendon.
The doctor’s gonna run a few more checks.
If all’s good, he’ll move to recovery soon.
So who hit Babe? Do we know yet?
The cops said it was a hit-and-run.
They haven’t caught the driver yet.
The crash was that bad...
How could the other guy still be okay?
Didn't they get hurt at all?
No idea, honestly.
Cops already checked the CCTV.
But they couldn’t tell where the car came from.
A witness said that...
It looked like the car ran
a red light and never even braked.
It was on purpose.
I saw this future coming.
What do you mean, kid?
Didn’t you say you had your
sense under control for a year?
I just started seeing again.
The first time I saw it...
I didn’t know what it was about.
Until today happened.
The car that hit us...
It looked like it hit on purpose and drove off.
So that’s when you called me?
To come see Babe?
Yeah.
When did your sense come back?
Just recently.
At first...
I thought I could still keep my power in check.
Until suddenly...
I felt pain.
Pain?
Yeah.
I felt pain.
Like I got hit by something
when I saw the vision.
I only realized today...
It was the same pain.
The same pain Babe felt when he got hit.
Jeff.
If seeing the future
physically hurts you like this...
That’s not exactly a good sign, man.
Exactly.
I think your special ability's
gotten stronger than before.
Now you actually feel
what’s going to happen too.
Something this serious...
You didn’t think to tell me?
Even if I did tell you,
you wouldn’t have been able to help me.
But I’m fine now, really.
I just felt it
it's not like I actually got hurt.
So what, you’d wait until
something actually happens
or you die—before telling me?
Uncle.
Jeff.
Why are you just standing there?
Go after Alan!
Did I die or something?
Yup, you did.
And a handsome angel...
has come to escort Babe to heaven.
Ow...
Was that supposed to be funny?
Well, I thought you were making a joke.
Are you in a lot of pain?
It hurts, but I can handle it.
And I'm totally ready to leave the hospital
and punch whoever hit me.
So, did they find out
who the driver was yet?
You just woke up and already acting tough.
I think you should just rest for now.
What about the others?
They all came to see you already.
But you weren’t awake yet.
So I told them to go home for now.
Can you tell Alan I’m sorry
I missed practice?
Alan wouldn’t blame you for that.
As for the CCTV footage...
Alan already spoke to the police.
But they didn’t see anything.
So they still haven’t caught the culprit.
But don’t worry.
Whoever it is, I’ll take care of them myself.
Oh wow.
Little puppy turned into
a full-on Rottweiler now, huh?
Ouch.
If it hurts, then rest, okay?
So you can heal faster, alright?
That’s not enough.
I want a magic kiss.
Get some rest.
Oops—wrench dropped.
Hey, kid.
You okay?
Hold on, Uncle.
Can’t we just talk first?
When we should’ve talked, we didn’t.
So what’s the point now?
Come on, Uncle… I know you overthink stuff.
That’s why I didn’t wanna be a burden to you.
The word “burden”...
Shouldn’t even exist in a relationship.
Love is about two people walking together.
But what you did...
It’s like you just pushed me out of your life.
Uncle...
Think it over properly.
What does being someone’s boyfriend...
really mean to you?
Something serious going on?
Hey.
What do you do when Babe’s mad at you?
Alan’s still not talking to you?
This time he’s not just ignoring me.
He won’t even look me in the face.
I’ve never seen him this mad before.
Can you blame him?
If Babe kept something that big from me...
I’d feel the same way.
Enough whining already.
Just tell me what you usually
do to make up with Babe.
Me and Babe aren’t
the type to hide how we feel.
When we make up...
We don’t really talk about it.
We just have sex.
But I’m not sure
that’ll work with you and Alan.
Right now, anything that works with him—
I’m willing to try it all.
Before you go beg for forgiveness...
You better get that checkup done first.
Go on, then.
It’s an evolution of Jeff’s power.
But the scary part is...
We have no idea where it’ll end up.
Meaning, if the person Jeff
sees in his sense gets hurt...
Jeff would feel the pain too.
And what if that person dies?
Then Jeff might...
I don’t want to die.
We can’t ever let that happen.
From what I can see...
It’s still in the expansion phase.
And like I said—
What’s scary is we don’t know where it ends.
And we have no idea what it’ll do to his body.
So our only option is the skill eraser.
I think we need to speed things up.
For Jeff’s safety.
Sir.
Babe is in the hospital right now.
If Mr. Manit’s men messed up the job...
Should I take care of it?
No, they did the job.
Mission accomplished, sir.
I just kinda missed him.
I didn’t plan to kill him.
If I wanted him dead...
One move... and he’s gone.
But the best kind of revenge...
Is watching them suffer.
Not dead...
But might as well be.
I’ve ordered all the evidence to be cleared, sir.
They won’t be able to trace anything back to us.
What would you like me to do next, sir?
Nothing.
I’d rather see him squirm.
You’re not leaving yet.
I need a word with you.
You mean… me?
What did the boss talk to you about?
Mr. Tony told me to shadow you.
I’m gonna take Kenta’s place
as his right hand.
Working for Tony
isn’t exactly a walk in the park.
That’s true.
You might be an asshole...
But you’re not quite asshole enough.
Keep trying, alright?
Stick with me long enough...
You’ll get there.
Got it.
You’re back, Papa?
Papa’s home.
What the hell?
Who told you to come in here?
Well, I’m already here.
No harm done, right?
Brought you flowers.
I’ll just leave them here.
Then get out.
Your boyfriend’s not around?
You’re this badly hurt and he’s not even here?
What a waste.
Will it kill you to mind
your own damn business for once?
With that attitude...
Did your boyfriend ban you
from being with others?
My boyfriend didn’t say anything.
I just don’t wanna be with you.
So that means...
Your boyfriend hasn’t seen our pic
at the bar that night, huh?
Came out great, by the way.
Looks like we were on a date.
What pic? I never took any with you.
This one.
Tons of likes on it too.
And I even tagged you.
You sure your boyfriend won’t see it?
Can you stop messing around?
If he saw it, he’d say I was already asleep.
Now get out.
You’re annoying.
How can I leave...
When I’m trying to flirt with you?
Listen up.
-Me and Charlie are never breaking up.
-Never breaking up.
I know what you're gonna say.
But your boyfriend's not here right now, is he?
Let me take care of you for now,
just as a stand-in.
Get lost already.
Why are you in such
a rush to kick me out, Babe?
What are you doing?
Charlie.
I’m here as a rep from ETA to visit Babe.
Same industry
we gotta support each other, right?
Hope you don’t mind.
Looks like you’ve got
someone to look after you now.
As promised.
I’ll head out now.
Yeah, just get lost already.
You’re annoying.
Bye then.
I shouldn’t have left your side.
I could’ve helped you sooner.
It’s okay.
I know you had things to take care of.
But I’m not going anywhere.
I’m not leaving you.
Charlie.
I know you’d never leave me.
I’m more afraid you’ll leave me.
What are you even saying?
Why would I ever leave you?
What if someone better comes along?
Smarter than me...
Has more time for you...
Like that Willy guy who’s been all over you.
That night you went to the bar...
You saw Willy, didn’t you?
Why didn’t you tell me...
That he’s still trying
to hit on you off the field?
So what if he is?
I didn’t flirt back or anything.
Besides, I beat him that night.
Is there anything else I don’t know?
Am I being annoying?
I’m really not feeling confident right now.
Charlie.
Okay.
I get annoyed by people easily.
But I mean it, alright?
You’re the only one I’ve ever had eyes for.
Got it?
But...
But I just don’t care about him.
If I don’t care,
then there’s nothing he can do, right?
Charlie.
Willy...
He’s got nothing on you.
You know that?
Hey, come on.
What’s with you?
I love you, Papa.
Come here.
Don’t overthink it.
Alright?
Kenta.
You probably heard we’re outta prison, right?
So who are you working for now?
I’m not working for anyone.
That’s why I ran here.
You’re running away?
I don’t wanna be involved in this stuff anymore.
But the reason I’m here...
Is ‘cause I figured the ones in real danger...
Are you guys.
What’s that supposed to mean?
You might not believe what I’m about to say.
But the scariest one of them all...
He’s back.
No breathing.
What’s the pulse?
Did you check?
Go check now.
Sample c153 has failed.
Bring in c154.
Yes, sir.
Have CEF put out an urgent recruitment call.
Pete, is something wrong?
Why did you call us here?
It’s something really important.
Otherwise, I wouldn’t have asked Babe
to come here right after leaving the hospital.
Kenta?
How did you get out?
What do you think you’re doing?
If it wasn’t serious,
I wouldn’t be getting
involved with you guys again.
But all of you need to know this.
Tony is back.
At first, I didn’t believe it either.
Because I was the one
who killed him with my own hands.
But after I got out of prison...
Someone took me to see Tony.
He looked like he was
recovering from serious injuries.
Are you sure...
That this whole thing isn’t some made-up story?
Kenta’s not lying.
Because right now,
he’s just as much at risk as the rest of us.
Or does Tony...
have some kind of power
that helped him survive?
I’ve never heard of any
special ability like that before.
But we all came from the Chen family.
None of us knew everything, right?
Did anyone know if Tony had powers?
Even if he comes back a hundred times...
I’m not afraid of him.
I just came to warn you all to be careful.
Because if I’m right...
The reason you’re like this now...
It’s probably because of Tony.
Are you worried about Tony coming back?
Not really.
Are you scared of him?
I’m not scared of Tony.
I’m just scared we won’t get to stay together.
We don’t know what Tony’s planning next.
What if he comes back
and takes you away again?
But I don’t have sense anymore, Charlie.
Why would he want to take me?
And besides...
Someone like Tony...
All he wants is revenge.
And me?
I’m not letting him touch either of us.
We’re both gonna be safe, no matter what.
That line...
Shouldn’t Papa be the one saying it?
Well, Mama’s still injured, you know.
Oh please.
It’s just a scratch.
Papa’s been taking care of you so well...
Doesn’t he deserve a reward?
What kind of reward, Mama?
I just got out of the hospital, you know.
You want it already?
What kind of reward are you thinking about?
Well...
Exactly the kind
you’re thinking about right now.
Go ahead.
Jeff.
You’re still not making up with Uncle?
I’m trying, I really am.
Trying?
Trying what, exactly?
I haven’t seen you do anything.
I just don’t know how to start.
But I did ask Charlie for advice.
And what did Charlie say?
He said I should use—
Use what?
Never mind.
Are we gonna have
an actual conversation today?
Alright, how about this?
If you’ve run out of excuses,
just use work as one.
Here—take the charger.
Trust me.
Take the water too—give it to Alan.
Trust me. Go, now.
Uncle.
Are you still mad at me?
Yeah.
But I can still separate work
from personal stuff.
Why?
You still hiding something from me?
I’m not hiding anything from you.
What about Tony being alive?
You didn’t know about that in advance?
I really didn’t know about that.
Come on, Uncle.
Don’t lump me in like that.
Can’t help it.
I just don’t know
what I can believe from you anymore.
Telling us this info...
You might be putting yourself in danger too.
Let’s just say...
I’m doing this to make up
for what I did to you guys.
So where are you gonna go now?
I don’t know.
But don’t worry about me.
I’m not going down that easy.
But I’m worried you’re the one who’s not safe.
Let me help you.
Help how?
If I stay here with you guys,
Tony’s just gonna target you too.
But I might have another way to help.
Hey, Alan.
Hey, Uncle.
How did it go with the police?
Any leads on who hit Babe?
Nothing yet.
All the CCTV footage got wiped clean.
The cops aren’t doing anything useful.
Tony, that bastard...
He just woke up and already—
He’s got connections with the police?
The fact he could hide
his “death” and all that for years...
Which means...
His connections are still just as strong.
And the fact he hasn’t shown his face...
Might just mean he’s waiting for the right time.
But I’ll tell you this—
Someone like Tony...
He wouldn’t run Babe over himself, right?
Uncle.
I think we need to figure out...
Who he ordered to do it.
Exactly, Uncle.
Why don’t you ask Jeff?
He’s seeing the future again now, right?
Tell him to focus, maybe he can—
Get a glimpse of the culprit’s face.
Even just a silhouette would help.
I couldn’t see the face.
But...
I remember seeing...
The driver was using only one hand.
What?
Damn, that’s bold.
He hit that hard—driving one-handed?
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
Just a little drained.
Hey, Uncle.
What’s the plan for the next race?
It’s just me and Charlie.
I don’t think we can pull it off.
You’ll have to. No choice.
Charlie.
You need to clock your best time in the next race.
We don’t know when Babe can come back.
Got it.
Actually...
I’ll race in the next one.
Babe, wait up!
Why would you race?
You just got out of the hospital.
There’s something I need to prove, Charlie.
Prove what, exactly?
I have a feeling Willy...
might be the one who hit me.
I’m not totally sure yet.
But from what Jeff told us...
Something about it reminded me of Willy.
So I wanna see for myself—on the track.
But that’s way too risky.
If you want something proven, just tell me.
I’ll do it for you.
No, I can’t let you.
Aren’t you supposed
to test the ability-nullifying drug?
That’s important too, isn’t it?
Charlie.
I can’t just let you deal
with everything on your own.
Okay.
You sure you’re fit enough to race?
I don’t want you pushing yourself.
I can handle it.
I’m Pit Babe, remember?
Did you forget?
Then make sure you get plenty of rest, okay?
You treat me like I’m your kid or something.
No, I treat you like my boyfriend.
Boyfriend, huh?
Someone might see us.
No one’s around.
Why should I help you guys?
I’m in the middle
of transferring back to Korea.
That’s exactly why.
You’re no longer part of X-Hunter...
And you’re about to leave the country.
So you’re the least likely to be targeted.
Still, it’s risky for me too.
We’re not asking you to keep Kenta forever.
Just give him a place to hide...
Until the timing’s right.
Once I figure out a safe escape route...
I’ll come get him myself.
You’re the only one...
I trust to help Kenta right now.
How’s Charlie doing?
Nothing’s changed.
Everything still looks exactly the same.
You haven’t gone home yet?
What about you?
Don’t you have a home to go back to by now?
I figured someone like you, a total workaholic,
probably hasn’t eaten yet either.
Here—sushi.
Can you eat this?
I’m not picky, you know.
If it doesn’t kill me, I’ll eat it.
So you’ve lived in the States your whole life?
Just like I told you—
I only came back here
because of the ability-nullifying drug.
Actually, I’ve had to...
run off to another country too, once.
In the end, I had to come back.
Because of Daddy.
Daddy?
Yeah, Daddy Tony.
He’s like a godfather to all the Chen family kids.
Honestly...
I think I’ve seen some news about him before.
But didn’t he already die?
Most people probably think that, yeah.
By the way, you’ve worked with
a lot of people with special senses, right?
Have you ever met anyone...
with a sense that makes them immortal?
Pete, come on...
Even the most powerful Alpha...
can’t escape death.
Or wait—Pete,
have you actually met
an Alpha with a power like that?
No, not at all.
I just asked
because I was curious, that’s all.
What the hell are you doing, North?
I’m praying, obviously.
At this point, we need
some divine help, don’t you think?
Didn’t you say you were fully prepared?
Training is one thing...
but keeping your cool during
the actual race is another.
Sonic, this is my debut race
as a full team racer, you know?
Then take this with you.
What’s this?
Some kind of charm?
If calling it that helps you
feel better, then sure.
You’ve got this.
I believe in you.
Alright then.
There you go.
Thanks, man.
How are you feeling, Babe?
I’m better now.
No need for anyone else to butt in.
I’m already taking care of Babe.
You just focus on your race prep.
My racer needs to focus.
Maybe you don’t realize it,
but what you’re doing...
feels like you’re playing dirty.
No need to be so negative.
I’m just concerned for him
as a fellow racer.
Charlie.
See you on the track.
Time to gear up.
We’re back with
The Hollow Super TG Speed Thunder!
This is Race 2, folks!
And now just 1 minute left...
It’s Willy from team ETA in the lead,
followed closely by Babe from X-Hunter,
as they approach zone A!
And they’re off!
Still neck and neck—Babe and Willy.
As expected, no changes in position just yet.
Looks like it’s going to be a long battle.
This is definitely not an easy one.
Willy’s in the lead!
It’s fine—it’s just the start.
Now we move into Zone B...
...the container zone!
Drivers need extra caution here...
and lots of experience.
Willy from ETA still leads the pack.
Babe and Charlie are right behind.
Willy’s holding strong—smooth cornering!
Babe’s closing in hard now!
But Willy’s still defending well.
Charlie keeps pressure from behind.
North, the new racer from X-Hunter...
...is doing great for his first race!
Go, North! You got this!
Willy’s still defending the lead well.
Babe’s looking for a way around...
But Willy’s still blocking tight.
Back to Zone A now!
Pit Babe’s speeding up again!
And it looks like North
is pushing into 4th place!
Yes! He made it—he’s in 2nd now!
Back in Zone B
Charlie’s accelerating hard!
He just passed Babe!
But Willy’s not letting anyone through just yet.
Babe pushes back and overtakes again!
Current standings
Willy, Babe, Charlie, then North.
Babe’s trying to find a way around Willy—
—but it’s not the right moment yet.
And now Charlie overtakes Pit Babe!
He cuts in front and is now tailing Willy!
Right on him! Right on his tail!
Willy from ETA is still defending like a pro.
Charlie’s not backing down though!
He’s closing the gap!
Now it’s a straightaway!
Looks like Charlie’s about to overtake!
Come on, Charlie—keep pushing!
Closer! Closer!
Charlie’s right on Willy’s tail now!
But his car’s starting to wobble...
Hey, Charlie’s car spun out!
Charlie, man!
-Uncle!
-Whoa, hang on!
Babe, focus! Stay calm!
Charlie’s car should be okay.
North, it’s just you and Babe now.
-You gotta cover for Charlie.
-Alright, let’s go!
It’s up to North to catch up now.
Babe just overtook Willy!
They’re neck and neck now!
And now they’re on the final straight!
Babe’s picking up speed!
It’s super close right now!
And Babe crosses the finish line!
Babe’s first! Then Willy and North!
Dean, go get the rescue car for Charlie!
Got it! Sonic, stay here, okay?
Charlie!
Come out first!
You okay?
You alright?
Is Charlie okay?
Sense...
I think I lost my sense...
So when’s Charlie waking up?
He’s been out like 4–5 hours now.
To you guys, is he just some lab rat?
It’s the same compound
we used for the skill-nullifying drug.
Tony didn’t make a skill-nullifier.
He’s actually making something to boost skills.
You're sweating like crazy...
But you still smell nice, bro.
I’m starting to wonder...
What’s going on in your head
While having dinner with
someone who looks just like your ex.
Happy Birthday, Mama!
Make a wish, quick!
So smoky in here.
(Grilled fish 100 baht each)
Super grilled.
Maybe 199 baht for that tilapia or whatever?
Can I kiss your cheek?
How about a nose kiss? Super cute.
Once I get the kiss, I’ll ask for more!
(Sneaky moment)
Then I’m like—wait, who even is this?
It’s a big deal and you didn’t think to tell me?
Tell me for what? What could I even do?
(That hits deep...)
I’m fine now, okay?
You gonna wait till I’m actually
dying before saying something?
Whip that bob and walk away—yeah, just go.