♪Destiny is so mysterious♪
♪Hazards appear in piles♪
♪Reflected in the mirror of mortal♪
♪Reincarnation repeats itself♪
♪I'm so forlorn and no one responds♪
♪Twilight falls on the deserted path♪
♪Beautiful old memories♪
♪Echo under the eaves♪
♪I don't want my soul to perish♪
♪Or disappear♪
♪Always live the life, happy or sad♪
♪Get rid of the glory♪
♪Reveal the destiny♪
♪Absorb the luck of heaven and earth♪
♪And prosper perfectly♪
♪When young dream chasers♪
♪Travel together♪
♪And shine brightly♪
♪I keep them company for mankind♪
♪Waiting to emerge♪
♪However the world changes♪
♪I've never been afraid♪
♪Even if everything collapses in the end♪
♪I will hold you in my arms♪
♪Brambles pierce through me♪
♪Tears roll down your cheeks♪
=The Last Immortal=
=Episode 39=
(Gate of Tribulation, Nine Palace Tower)
(If the devil army doesn't show up
before entering the Nine Palace Tower,)
(then devils are likely among these people
who enter the Tower.)
There is another world
in the Nine Palace Tower.
The light gate ahead is
the first Heavenly test,
specially used to inspect
the immortal foundation.
When passing through this gate,
countless heavenly thunders will descend,
just like those that appear
when you ascend to a higher level.
Everyone, who will go first?
What about Yu Xiazi and I go first?
The cultivation of you three is higher
than mine, I'd better be the last.
What difference does it make
to go first or last?
Is it that there are some
inexplicable concerns?
Of course not.
I will go with you first.
(Reverse Immortal Power?
He is not a devil.)
You cultivate against the norm
to improve your cultivation.
What a shame.
Reverse training is strictly prohibited
by the Heavenly Palace.
Since you made this mistake,
you can't move forward anymore.
Do you think my words don't count?
Go and receive your punishment.
Thank you for saving him.
It's nothing.
Since you have passed
the Gate of Tribulation,
you can go ahead now.
(Realm of Forgetfulness,
Nine Palace Tower)
(Why are these cloud steps
going up endlessly?)
Martial Aunt.
- Yin.
Come over here.
Where have you been for so long?
Finally you came.
If Qing Yi didn't go to find you,
I really couldn't find you.
You, as a girl, should stay away
from the Forbidden Valley.
There are many beasts.
It's dangerous. Do you know?
I think it's the beasts that are in danger.
This girl is always fierce.
Those beasts in the Forbidden Valley
run away as soon as they see her.
What's wrong?
I was just joking.
Why are you staring at me?
Jin.
Master.
You bullied Yin again.
I didn't.
If so, why are Yin's eyes red?
Yin, I ask you here to tell you that
you are my closed-door disciple
from today on.
That's great.
- Great!
That's great!
I never expected that I would
have a junior sister one day.
I am a senior brother from now on.
- That's great!
- I am a senior brother.
- Great!
- Yes.
Yin, I will grant you this
sword tassel today.
Let me do it.
Come, let me grant you the sword tassel.
What's wrong? Are you unhappy?
No.
I am willing to see Master,
you,
and Daze Mountain.
But I cannot indulge in this.
You must be Feng Yin
from Wutong Island.
You are…
Qing Qiong.
Your Lordship. I heard that you have
been traveling around the world.
Why are you in this Nine Palace Tower?
It's important to choose
the Heavenly ruler.
The second pass of this Tower
is called Realm of Forgetfulness.
It needs an immortal who is proficient
in illusion to guard the entrance.
I came back to help.
Little girl.
(Lord Qing Qiong)
How did you see through the illusion?
Xian Shan had always shown
respect and courtesy.
He wouldn't let Jin take the sword tassel.
Jin respected Master and Xian Shan.
He would never take the sword tassel.
It's just so?
It is more than that.
The scene in front of me
was so beautiful,
but I only felt sad in my heart.
At that time,
I didn't remember anything.
But when I heard them
calling me Martial Aunt,
the scene when Daze Mountain
was destroyed
seemed to reappear before my eyes.
So I can no longer indulge
in the illusory beauty.
There is only one Daze Mountain.
It is my sect when it's prosperous.
It can't be replaced when it's perished.
What I need to do now
is to prevent the Three Realms
from suffering from such a disaster.
Good. You passed this test.
If you become the Heavenly Empress,
remember your original intention.
Go ahead.
The position of the Heavenly ruler
is mine.
Three chimes announce
the arrival of the groom.
Shu.
Lan Feng.
Is it really you?
It's me, Shu.
Today is our wedding day,
please don't cry, okay?
Shu, it's time.
After we exchange jade tokens,
we can complete our ceremony.
Lan Feng.
Lan Feng, where have you been?
Come back, okay?
Lan Feng.
Hua Shu, it's wrong for you to use
the Illusion Veil to enter the Tower.
And you can't see through the illusion,
you're not the chosen Heavenly Empress.
Leave the Tower now.
Why did you end the illusion?
You have long seen through the illusion?
- Why didn't you…
- A thousand years have passed.
I've been fantasizing
if Lan Feng walked up to the hall
and married me that day,
what would I be like after that?
Today I finally saw it.
But why did you take away all of this?
Why?
You all deserve to die.
You… You fell into the devil path.
All of you will
accompany Lan Feng in death.
Ling Feng? What happened?
The devils invaded Wanyi Mountain
last night.
Hua Shu killed my father and took away
the Illusion Veil of Wanyi Mountain.
So, the Maser of Wanyi Mountain
is actually Hua Shu in disguise.
Illusion Veil can change forms
and transform into gas.
It's the best concealment tool,
and no one can see through it.
With this treasure, Feng Yin
may not see through Hua Shu.
What should we do?
Nine Palace Tower is closed now.
No one can enter it.
(Jianwu Hall, Nine Palace Tower)
It seems that only you and I
have arrived here.
Is that the Seal of the Supreme?
Yes.
I have met you several times.
Now, only you and I are vying for
the position of the Heavenly ruler.
It's quite fate.
Since we are destined to compete,
I'll let you try first to see if you
can take the Seal of the Supreme.
Thank you.
I heard that the Seal of the Supreme
has its destiny to choose its master.
I will give it a try first.
You have made no progress in a thousand
years and still can't be patient.
How did you recognize me
from the Illusion Veil?
(Wanyi)
One of you is a God and
the other is the Phoenix Queen.
You are born to be a perfect match.
People like you are born esteemed.
You have a smooth road ahead
and a way out behind.
Naturally, you can be
carefree and desireless.
But do you know how much effort I have
put in just to not be inferior to others?
Do you know what will happen to
people like us
with ordinary qualifications?
You hate others for their noble birth,
but you are born as
the Princess of the Peacock Clan,
the prettiest immortal at the peak
of Senior Immortal.
You'd been the Acting Heavenly
Empress for a thousand years.
But you turned around and
suppressed inferior immortals.
Are such acts not despicable?
Hua Shu, I advise you to turn back
and not be obsessed with greed.
Ask me this when I get
the Seal of the Supreme
and change the Heavenly Palace
into Lan Feng's mourning hall.
Hua Shu is indeed inside.
They are coming.
Yuan Qi had guessed your trick long ago.
You are now trapped in the
Devil-trapped Formation. It's a dead end.
The Purple Moon shines on the Three Realms.
The Devil God will come visit.
Are you alright?
The Seal of the Supreme is mine.
Hua Shu, your father is here.
Think it over.
You'd better hand over the Seal
and retreat the devil army.
Shu, haven't we come all the way to
today just to unify the Three Realms?
You must not hand over the Seal.
Shu, take out the
Demon-gathering Banner that I robbed.
Demon-gathering Banner?
It's the most powerful object for demons.
The Demon-gathering Banner is here.
Let's see who can trap me.
So it was indeed you who stole my sword
and killed the Demon King Lin Sen.
So what if it was me?
Lin Sen is dead.
But the immortals and the demons
are still fighting each other.
It's really ridiculous.
The source of the sins a thousand years
ago has finally been found.
Killing you will bring good results
to the Three Realms.
That depends on whether
you have the ability.
Shu, activate the Demon-gathering
Banner. Open the Demon-release Gate.
Summon all the devil soldiers
in the Infinite Cave.
Stop dreaming.
The Demon-release Gate is the most
powerful tool in the Demon Realm.
Without god power, it can't be opened.
You are far from being doing it.
I can't do it, but Shu can.
Move.
Hua Shu, if you do this,
you can never correct it.
Shu, don't listen to their nonsense.
For the sake of me and Lan Feng,
kill them all.
Stop Hua Shu.
Hua Shu, take a good look to see
who deceived you.
The one who killed Lan Feng
was concealed in the black mist.
Now take a good look at
who this person is.
The killings of Lan Feng and Lin Sen
were a set of interconnected schemes.
The ultimate goal is to provoke a battle
between immortals and demons.
Now, the Demon-gathering Banner
is in his hands.
How could he not know
who killed Lan Feng?
What does Lan Feng's death have to do
with me? Don't try to instigate Shu.
Why did you remove
Hongque's immortal bones
and descend her to the Mortal Realm
immediately after Lan Feng was killed?
I didn't do this.
I was descended to the Mortal Realm
by the Peacock King.
Hongque, you are still alive.
Your Highness.
Father said you blamed yourself
for Lan Feng's death.
So you asked him to remove your bones
and descend to the Mortal Realm.
You died of depression soon.
No, Your Highness, it's not like that.
On the day of your wedding,
I saw Peacock King went to Lingyu Hall
to find His Majesty Lan Feng.
After he went in, Lingyu Hall
was separated by a barrier.
Then, His Majesty was killed.
Later, Peacock King used the excuse of
me not taking good care of the Emperor,
descended me to the Mortal Realm.
Your Highness,
I followed you for many years.
How could I not know your affection
for His Majesty?
But I haven't had the opportunity
to talk to you in these years.
Hua Shu, we all know that
you want to save Lan Feng,
but Lan Feng has been dead
for a thousand years.
How could it be possible for him
to come back to life?
Lan Feng should have been able to
come back to life. It's because of you!
Should have.
Now I will show you his true state.
How could it be?
Even if Lan Feng couldn't come back to
life, he should not be like this.
This ice coffin is nothing
more than an illusionary coffin.
What you see are all illusions
created by Hua Mo for you.
Hua Mo, His Majesty Lan Feng
was kind and upright.
Just because he loved Hua Shu,
you took the opportunity to kill him.
If he could be buried in the ground,
he should have been reshaped
and reincarnated.
But he was covered by your ice coffin,
exhausted all his immortal spirit
and can never be reincarnated now.
Father, is that true?
In front of the enemy, you and I should
unite against them.
Is that true?
Yes, it was me.
If I didn't provoke a conflict between
the immortals and the demons,
how could the Peacock Clan stand out?
Look at these immortals,
who shows respect to us?
Are you willing to be trampled
by them forever?
Shu, activate the Demon-gathering
Banner and summon the devil army,
then we will be the ruler
of the Three Realms.
Only one step left, only this last step!
But so what?
What's the point of doing all these
without Lan Feng?
I knew that even you couldn't be
relied on at the critical moment.
Fine. Since you refuse to take action,
I will help you.
Stop Hua Mo!
I asked the Devil God
for this Mind-Blowing Spell
to avoid this.
Listen, activate the Demon-gathering
Banner. Open the Demon-release Gate.
- This…
- The gate is open.
The gate is open!
Feng Yin!
What are you going to do? Come back!
If you still respect Lan Feng,
please trust me this time
for the sake of Lan Feng.
Shu!
Let's make the Three Realms
disappear forever!
Father,
what should disappear forever is us.
Shu!
Hua Shu from the Peacock Clan
is unforgivable.
Please exhaust my immortal spirit to
seal devils in Demon-gathering Banner.
I don't ask for any forgiveness,
but my fellow clansmen were
forced to practice devil power.
Now I have extracted the devil energy
from their bodies.
Please consider that they are forced,
and don't exterminate them.
I will guard the Demon-gathering Banner
forever to redeem the crimes for the clan.
You have passed the Nine Palace Tower,
and become the new Heavenly Empress.
You decide what to do and give the order.
The crimes of the Peacock Clan
have been cleared by Hua Shu.
From today on, no immortals shall
make trouble for them.
Any violator will be severely punished.
I will obey Your Majesty's order.
No need for formalities.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Feng Yin.
A thousand years ago, I caused
your immortal spirit to dissipate,
now, I am here to reap what I have sown.
It is a retribution.
Our resentments are settled today.
Rest assured, as long as I am alive,
no one will touch the Peacock Clan.
Thank you, Feng Yin.
I'm afraid we will never see
each other again.
Before I leave, I have some words
to tell you.
Many years ago, I envied
your background,
and admired your talent.
But now I realize that
I don't need to admire you
for one thing.
Because I also have someone
who can give up everything for me
and considers me more important
than his life.
That's…
It's devil energy.
It can come and go freely
in the Three Realms. It's Ming Qi.
Let's follow the Demon-gathering Banner.
Go.
(Ruins, Bainiao Island)
Why is the Demon-gathering Banner
landed here alone?
Because the true devil energy
has been extracted by me.
It is useless now.
Ming Qi?
No, that's not his true form.
Don't worry. We have plenty of time
to talk after I open the Abyss.
He is absorbing the devil energy
suppressed here.
He wants to make his true form appear.
Stop him!
Yuan Qi, you are really clever!
Unfortunately, it's too late.
The air in the Three Realms
still smells so good.
Force him back!
♪Kill the demons and devils♪
♪Go to the three worlds
and the eight wastelands♪
♪No one can stop me♪
♪The world is unpredictable♪
Three sealings merge into one!
♪See the love and the hate♪
♪I told you not to be stubborn♪
♪If you're crazy, if you're oblivious♪
♪Just treat it as a dream♪
♪It's an endless cycle♪
♪I always remember his stubbornness♪
♪If we never stumbled through the storms♪
♪How can we resist it♪
♪Even if I can't come back, I'll fight alone♪
♪If we never had a story to tell♪
♪How can you call it madness♪
♪Looking back, the world is so vast♪
The fusion of three energies makes
the Chaos Power of the God Realm.
You can't escape. Ming Qi.
You are dead. Why are you laughing?
I'm laughing at you, Ao Ge.
Do you know that Xiu Yan
sacrificed himself to seal the Abyss?
If you don't release the previous sealing
and add a new one to seal me again,
Xiu Yan will never be able to leave,
like me.
If you stop your sealing
for a moment now,
Xiu Yan can escape in this instant.
Why don't you give it a try?
Ao Ge!
Ao Ge, sober up!
♪Flowers bloom, hands hold♪
♪I look into your eyes♪
♪Life after life, I search♪
♪Reminiscence and nostalgia♪
♪Your smile is my sweetest dream♪
♪On a chilly night, leaves gyrate♪
♪Your face emerges♪
♪Life after life, I get disappointed♪
♪Old dreams come back to me♪
♪Your heart is where I stay alone♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I water the withered with the ocean♪
♪Make vibrant changes♪
♪And rebuild love♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I bid farewell with blood and tears♪
♪Unshackle the regret♪
♪And rush to you forever♪
♪Forever♪