♪Destiny is so mysterious♪
♪Hazards appear in piles♪
♪Reflected in the mirror of mortal♪
♪Reincarnation repeats itself♪
♪I'm so forlorn and no one responds♪
♪Twilight falls on the deserted path♪
♪Beautiful old memories♪
♪Echo under the eaves♪
♪I don't want my soul to perish♪
♪Or disappear♪
♪Always live the life, happy or sad♪
♪Get rid of the glory♪
♪Reveal the destiny♪
♪Absorb the luck of heaven and earth♪
♪And prosper perfectly♪
♪When young dream chasers♪
♪Travel together♪
♪And shine brightly♪
♪I keep them company for mankind♪
♪Waiting to emerge♪
♪However the world changes♪
♪I've never been afraid♪
♪Even if everything collapses in the end♪
♪I will hold you in my arms♪
♪Brambles pierce through me♪
♪Tears roll down your cheeks♪
=The Last Immortal=
=Episode 8=
Martial Uncle Xian Zhu,
why did you suddenly borrow so many books
from the South Heaven Cave?
Books! The books!
This is where the strong wind circulates.
The books must have fallen
to the Mortal Realm.
You go back to Daze Mountain first.
I'll get a permission
for going to the Mortal Realm
and retrieve the books.
Martial Uncle Xian Zhu,
be careful!
(Mortal Realm)
Don't run!
Stop!
Where are you going?
Let's go!
Miss,
are you okay?
(Wan Yue)
Your clothes are torn.
Let me mend it for you.
No need.
I can mend it with immortal power.
My method is different.
Let me do it.
Wait a moment.
I'll get some needle and thread.
Miss Wan Yue.
Look.
This embroidery.
I really like it.
(Daze Mountain, the Immortal Realm)
Martial Uncle!
I need your help! It's urgent!
What's going on?
The Heavenly Palace's messenger
brought rewards for the Trial Assembly
and needs someone to sign for them.
You call this urgent?
I was just about to leave for the Guanxin Valley
for closed-door cultivation,
waiting for the ascent.
Find someone else to do it.
Martial Uncle,
Master is busy with the sect affairs
and doesn't have time.
Martial Uncle Xian Zhu hasn't returned.
It'll only take a little while.
Martial Uncle,
please help me out.
- But my luggage...
- Come on, let's go.
Only in this kind of situation,
I can remember that I am an elder
of Daze Mountain.
This time, the first prize
is the newly formed Yin Fire Yang Ice.
That's why the messenger said
it must be personally received by an elder.
Yin Fire Yang Ice?
Our foxes' cores are special.
It's extremely Yin fire.
Ordinary herbs
are ineffective.
Only Yin Fire Yang Ice
has miraculous effects.
If we can find a piece,
I don't have to consume
Yin's immortal power then.
(With Yin Fire Yang Ice,)
(Yin no longer needs to)
(consume her internal core every day)
(to heal Jiu.)
How can the Yin Fire Yang Ice
be obtained?
Naturally, by winning
the Trial Assembly.
Jin.
What are you doing here?
Why haven't you gone
into seclusion for cultivation?
The Thunder Tribulation is approaching.
Xian Zhu left these elixirs
before leaving.
If you find it difficult to endure
during the Thunder Tribulation,
take a couple of them,
they can help you.
How could I not make it through
a mere Thunder Tribulation?
Thank Xian Zhu for me.
I don't know why you're always happy.
Let me tell you,
the Trial Assembly is about to begin.
Pay attention to your demeanor.
You don't look decent this way.
So what?
I'm mainly worried that
people from Bainiao Island
will despise you.
Why?
After I marry Hua Shu,
there will be a few days each year
when I have to accompany her
back to her family.
In our Daze Mountain,
you can be casual and carefree,
but if you go to Bainiao Island
and are looked down upon,
I'll have to stand up for you.
You also need to change your temper.
Alright, you will go with me
to Bainiao Island.
I won't go to Bainiao Island with you!
Why should I
go to Bainiao Island with you?
I'll stay in Daze Mountain,
and sleep in!
Focus on your cultivation!
You are really angry?
I was just joking.
Thank Xian Zhu for me.
No!
(Wutong Island, the Immortal Realm)
Feng Ming,
you've been coming here
to take care of the ancient tree
every night for many years, haven't you?
Yes, Elder,
it has been a hundred years.
The ancient sycamore tree
nurtures our Phoenix Clan.
I just
want to contribute
to the entire Phoenix Clan,
leading Wutong Island
to prosperity for generations.
You
want to become the Phoenix King?
According to the rules,
the throne of the Phoenix Clan
should be passed on to Feng Yin.
But now, Feng Yin's immortal spirit
has already dissipated,
her life and death are unknown.
If Feng Yin doesn't wake up
for thousands of years,
our Phoenix Clan
will be without a leader for that long?
News has come from Daze Mountain
that Gu Jin has found four portions
of Feng Yin's immortal spirit.
Sooner or later, she will return.
Feng Ming,
your efforts for the Phoenix Clan
are indeed well-intentioned.
However, the Fire Phoenix
is the first heir to the throne,
that's an unbreakable ancestral rule.
Just wait patiently for Feng Yin's return.
(I've been in seclusion for ten years,)
(breaking through the great formation
on Wutong Island.)
(I consider myself)
(the most outstanding disciple
of the Phoenix Clan.)
(The throne)
(should rightfully be mine.)
The rules of the Phoenix Clan
are really fusty,
leaving such a capable person unused
and insisting on waiting for
someone who is
practically a lifeless shell.
How dare you come here?
If the Phoenix Clan finds out
that I'm colluding with you...
Rest assured,
I used the secret way you told me
to get through the barrier.
Nobody will find out.
Where is the Fire Phoenix Jade?
Has it been destroyed?
The Fire Phoenix Jade contains
a prohibition formed by
the immortal veins of Daze Mountain.
I can't enter the forbidden area
of Daze Mountain
to explore the veins.
This is the Star-Seeking Compass.
With this tool,
you can find the location of the veins.
You plotted against me and failed.
Why do you think
I will still believe you?
Perhaps
you've already revealed your true colors.
Once Gu Jin gathers
all Feng Yin's immortal spirit,
you may never have another chance.
My master said that
Daze Mountain's trial assembly
is a great opportunity for you.
You are a demon,
but I cannot see through
your true identity.
Who is your master behind you?
You don't need to know these things.
Just understand that
we all want the Fire Phoenix Jade
to be destroyed.
If we succeed in our cooperation,
it will be beneficial for both sides.
Think about it.
This is your last chance.
(Daze Mountain, the Immortal Realm)
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
here is the list of participants for this year's
Trial Assembly.
Please take a look.
Qing Yi,
did you see Jin?
No, I didn't.
The list of participants
for the Trial Assembly is here.
Everyone whose names are called,
please come to receive
your immortal artifact.
Wanyi Mountain, Ling Feng.
Kunlun Mountain, Lian Yue.
Leize Mountain, Lei Che.
Wutong Island, Feng Ming.
(Yantian Hall)
Yihua Island, Jun Yu.
Daze Mountain,
Gu Jin.
What...
Your Majesty,
Gu Jin
could be a mistake.
Is there a problem?
No problem!
I am present!
What are you doing?
You might meet the Thunder Tribulation!
Are you crazy?
He won't participate!
I will!
- Don't go.
- Why not?
Practical experience
is beneficial for ascent.
Honestly,
what are you up to? Tell me.
- Nothing, nothing at all.
- You...
Hua Shu is here.
I arrived late.
I ask Your Majesty,
Master Xian Shan,
and all immortals for forgiveness.
(So he came for Hua Shu.)
You are injured, Princess Hua Shu.
If you didn't come,
it would be reasonable.
As the Salary-Managing Heavenly Official,
I should fulfill my duties faithfully.
How could I delay the selection
because of personal reasons?
If that's all,
let's begin.
Alright.
Just wait for me to come back.
I...
This Trial Assembly
is for selecting war-managing positions
for the Heavenly Palace.
I hope all of you
will compete for the positions
with your full efforts.
Yes.
Wow. That is...
This is a thunderbird
from the Heaven Realm.
All of you need to use
your immortal artifacts
to collect a strand of
purple lightning from it.
The first two immortals
who successfully collect it
will be the winners.
Please remember that
this is only a competition.
Never harm each other
and ruin the harmony.
If there is any life-threatening danger,
immediately stop the competition.
The Trial Assembly
begins.
Jun Yu,
are you alright?
Catching the thunderbird is difficult,
but catching you
is a piece of cake.
You even want to win?
In your dreams!
Your Highness, are you okay?
Thank you, Jin.
I'll wait to see you win.
Hua Shu.
Did it affect
your internal injuries just now?
Thanks for your concern, Your Majesty.
I'm fine.
If you don't take
your injuries seriously now,
they might lead to
hidden ailments in the future.
The crisis on Bainiao Island is urgent,
I don't have the energy
to care about my injuries.
I've already sent mediators to intervene
in the war between the Peacock Clan
and the Eagle Clan.
It's just that both clans
refused to cease the war,
resulting in the current tragic situation.
I have issued an order,
I'll give you a month.
If both clans still refuse to stop the war,
I will hold the two
clan leaders accountable
according to the laws
of the Heavenly Palace.
This is also for the sake
of Bainiao Island.
At least the Peacock Clan
wouldn't be harmed fundamentally.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I overstepped.
Please forgive me.
Ling Feng, you only need to use the hypnosis
spell to collect the purple lightning.
There's no need to harm it.
Feng Ming, take your hypocrisy back!
- You alright?
- I'm fine.
Thank you, Gu Jin.
Gu Jin,
the thunderbird is curious.
Let's use Lin Powder
to attract it,
then use the hypnosis spell to catch it
and collect the purple lightning.
Okay.
He got it.
Quite impressive.
What should he do?
How should he escape?
Oh no.
Are you kidding me?
Thunder Tribulation!
Why is there a thunder tribulation?
It's Gu Jin.
Gu Jin is about to ascend.
Yin, what are you doing here?
No time for that.
Set up a formation
to block the heavenly thunder.
Get back down there now.
With your current spiritual power,
a single thunderbolt can easily kill you.
Set up the formation!
(Yin, as Jin's)
(immortal beast,)
(might be able to help him.)
♪I don't want my soul to perish♪
♪Or disappear♪
♪Always live the life, happy or sad♪
♪Get rid of the glory♪
♪Reveal the destiny♪
♪Absorb the luck of heaven and earth♪
♪And prosper perfectly♪
♪When young dream chasers♪
♪Travel together♪
♪And shine brightly♪
♪I bury my feelings♪
♪Embrace fearless♪
♪Leaving scars in my heart♪
♪No matter how many devils I face♪
♪I can drink heartlessly♪
♪Even if my frozen heart♪
♪Worries about you♪
♪I also talk to myself sometimes♪
♪I keep them company♪
♪For mankind♪
♪Waiting to emerge♪
♪However the world changes♪
♪I've never been afraid♪
♪Even if everything collapses in the end♪
♪I will hold you in my arms♪
♪Brambles pierce through me♪
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
- Martial Uncle! Martial Uncle!
- Gu Jin!
Good thing you're okay.
It was really scary just now.
Congratulations, Gu Jin, on successfully
ascending to junior immortal.
Gu Jin,
your ascension during the trial
is truly admirable,
displaying exceptional
mental fortitude.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Gu Jin's Thunder Tribulation was so powerful.
It knocked me unconscious.
The Trial Assembly
has come to an end.
Feng Ming
was the first to collect the purple lightning,
and Gu Jin
performed even better
by capturing the thunderbird.
They're about to enter the Heavenly Palace
for official duties.
Any objections from the other immortals?
Congratulations, Gu Jin.
Congratulations, Feng Ming.
Feng Ming, Gu Jin,
you two can now choose your positions.
Capturing the thunderbird
was no easy feat.
So Gu Jin should choose first.
Congratulations, Immortal Gu Jin.
You can choose a position
between the Combat God of the South Pole
and the War God of Yunling.
I choose neither.
I came
just to win the trial.
- Martial Uncle.
- Jin.
Jin.
Yin, can't you be gentle?
It really hurts.
Even the heavenly thunder couldn't kill you.
A bandage would hurt you that bad?
I'm hungry.
I want some food.
What's this? Food?
Change fresh dressing for yourself later.
Then what about food?
I don't have time to find food for you.
Go find it
yourself.
Come back.
What are you busy with?
Looking after me is the most
important thing right now, isn't it?
Don't try to control me
with the master-servant contract.
I want to look at flowers, grass, and the sun.
I don't have time to look after you.
What are you doing?
I'm your master.
My injury requires bed rest.
How could you leave me unattended?
Don't you have any conscience?
No.
My conscience
was already gone
when you were blinded
and smitten by a beauty.
All gone.
Going through a Thunder Tribulation
could be extremely dangerous.
Why didn't you tell us you were going
to the Trial Assembly?
Besides, you grabbed that thunderbird
and wouldn't let go
because you wanted to impress Hua Shu.
Was that necessary?
If you were really
- struck by the thunder…
- Take it.
What is it?
Yin Fire Yang Ice,
the prize of the Trial Assembly.
Jiu said
with this,
you don't have to consume your own
spiritual power to heal him anymore.
So… So…
So, you participated in the Assembly
in order to get this?
Or what?
I have plenty of opportunities
to impress Princess Hua Shu.
But you are my personal servant.
You almost died for healing
that stupid fox.
Alright,
now you can go appreciate the flowers
and the sun.
I'm going to take a rest.
I wonder
if Princess Hua Shu saw me
when I was successfully ascended.
As it turned out,
he tried that hard
to help me.
Yin,
Jin is very nice to you.
How could you
be so petty?
He likes Hua Shu.
So what?
You shouldn't be upset about it.
Then
should I help him as well?
I'll help him win Hua Shu's heart.
(Inaction)
Go make the soup.
Put more pork liver in it.
Or,
you can put yours in it.
No.
Jiu.
I wasn't bullying Qing Yi.
Listen,
I'm here to ask you something.
Ask me something?
How to chase a girl?
Chase
a girl?
You?
Not me.
Why would I chase a girl?
I want to help Gu Jin.
Help him chase Hua Shu.
Gu Jin.
That's easy.
I can teach him the Bewitching Spell
of our Fox Clan.
I want to help him chase a girl he likes,
not trick a girl.
Besides,
the Bewitching Spell can't last forever.
Then let him give the Bainiao Island
several carriages of spiritual items.
Daze Mountain is wealthy anyway.
No, that's not gonna work.
Hua Shu is an immortal princess,
not a slave.
She wouldn't be impressed by those things.
Moreover,
true love can't be bought.
Give me another idea.
Go straight to the point.
Let Gu Jin restrain Hua Shu.
Do you know how to chase a girl or not?
All the ideas you gave me
are bad.
Of course…
- Of course, he doesn't know.
- Before…
I'm afraid
Jiu has never even held a girl's hand.
You know everything, don't you?
Qing Yi,
- you should mind your own business.
- I…
Have you done cooking?
Forget it. What a waste of time.
I thought since you foxes
can cast Bewitching Spells,
you must have a lot of ideas
for wooing a girl.
Looks like
I can't help Jin after all.
Hold on.
If you want to help Martial Uncle Gu Jin,
I do have an idea.
When I was in the mortal world,
I read a story book
about a scholar
spending three years
growing a grove of peach blossoms.
When the petals started to fall,
he invited the girl he liked to the grove
and confessed his love for her,
then the two got married.
It's such a good
and unique idea.
So, are you going to let Gu Jin
grow peach blossoms
in Daze Mountain?
There's a pear tree
by the hut in the Forbidden Valley.
It may look like an ordinary pear tree,
but actually it's Chiluo,
a very rare pear tree species.
Chiluo?
But it looks just like
an ordinary pear tree to me.
You don't understand.
The Chiluo flowers won't show
unless you nurture it
with immortal power for 20 hours.
Rarely do people care
to spend that long
for nurturing a tree.
Tomorrow is the Qiqiao Festival,
and it's such an original idea.
Good. I'm going.
Confess my love for her
under the Chiluo tree on the Qiqiao Festival.
What a good idea.
Anyway,
I've told you what to do.
It's all up to you now whether or not
you are able to ask Hua Shu out.
But just so you know,
if she rejects you
when you ask her out,
it'll be your own wishful thinking only,
and it can be very embarrassing.
I don't think so.
I'm going.
I'll go ask her out right now.
Actually, this idea
isn't that good.
I think you should give it another thought.
It's perfect.
Thank you, Yin.
I'm leaving.
(Young Hua Shu)
(Heavenly Palace, the Immortal Realm)
(Young Lan Feng)
Who are you?
Why are you crying here?
You don't recognize me either?
I'm Princess Hua Shu
of the Bainiao Island.
Should I know you?
Sure,
all you can see
is Princess Chen Min,
who's like the light of the sun and the moon,
outshining me who's insignificant like stars.
I'm much more beautiful than her,
but she was born to be above me
because she's the daughter
of the Heavenly King.
One day,
I'll let all of you see
that our Peacock Clan
is not a second-class immortal clan,
and as the princess of the Peacock Clan,
I'm not a foil for anybody.
What's this?
When I passed by the Venus today,
it shined so brightly,
so I collected some sparkles of the star.
Look at them.
Although they aren't as bright
as the sunlight and the moonlight,
they do flash beautifully in their own way.
No one can outshine your beauty.
(The sparkles of the star
from 200 years ago.)
(I can't believe she's been
carrying them with her.)
Your Highness,
Immortal Gu Jin is here.
Gu Jin?
I see. You may leave now.
Jin,
how's your injury?
It's fine.
Your Highness,
tomorrow is the Qiqiao Festival.
I'm here to ask
if you'll be available tomorrow.
There's a rare Chiluo tree
in the Forbidden Valley
of our Daze Mountain.
So, I'm thinking…
If you don't have time,
it's okay. Then…
Since you are inviting me,
of course I have time.
Good.
Then I'll wait for you
in the Forbidden Valley tomorrow.
See you then.
See you.
Your Highness, I thought
you weren't fond of Gu Jin.
He asked you out on the Qiqiao Festival,
apparently, he wants to go after you.
Why did you agree to see him?
Gu Jin's cultivation base is so-so,
but his origin is quite mysterious.
He shattered the immortal spirit
of the young Fire Phoenix,
yet he could still get away with it.
I'm afraid he's got
someone powerful to back him up.
Besides, he has
the Sky-shrouding Umbrella.
The more days I keep him around,
the longer I can use the Umbrella.
Then what about
Heavenly Emperor Lan Feng?
Lan Feng
is an upright and fair-minded man.
He's not as easy to manipulate as Gu Jin.
Although he's been at the peak level
of the Senior Immortal for years
and hasn't ascended as a god yet,
he's after all the Acting Heavenly Emperor,
whom no one can outpower
throughout the entire world.
I'm just not sure
if the pouch of star sparkles
I dropped on purpose would work.
Your Highness, you are brilliant indeed.
I think it worked already.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
I found an item that belongs to you,
so I came to return it.
I…
I dropped it by accident.
Sorry for the trouble.
I didn't expect
that you'd been carrying it
with you for all these years.
I first met you 200 years ago.
Back then,
I was still
an ignorant little girl.
It was kind of embarrassing.
I wish you could forget that.
Hua Shu,
tomorrow is the Qiqiao Festival.
May I invite you
to appreciate the view
on the bridge of magpies with me?
Actually, ever since
I met you 200 years ago,
I've been
thinking of you.
Your Majesty, please let me think about it.
Sure.
I'll wait for you.
It's been a whole night,
the Chiluo flowers still haven't shown.
Maybe you should take a break.
In case your immortal power runs out
before you could make the flowers show.
It'll harm your body.
Today is the Qiqiao Festival.
I invited Hua Shu
to be here to appreciate the flowers.
How can I make her disappointed?
You take a break.
Let me try.
Forget about it.
With your weak immortal power,
it's not gonna work.
It's working?
Let's do it together.
Try again.
Come on.
It really worked.
You've got your flowers.
Now we can go back and take a rest.
Hold it.
Do me another favor.
Come here.
- Why?
- Sit down.
Since I'm going to confess
my love for her under the tree,
I came up with some lines,
and I'd like to hear your opinions.
Ten years ago,
I first met you,
and I've been thinking of you
ever since.
Every time I see you,
I want to look at you more.
Every time I hear people talk about you,
I want to hear more.
Today is the Qiqiao Festival.
I want to tell you something
that I've been keeping from you
for ten years.
I like you.
What do you think?
I thought about it for a long time.
I had no idea what else to say.
But I think it'd work.
Yin.
Tell me what you think.
I don't feel well.
I'm not worthy… I… I…
Figure it out yourself.
I have to go.
What are you talking about?
You are stumbling.
So weird.
Martial Aunt.
Martial Aunt, what's wrong?
Are you feeling unwell?
Martial Aunt.
Martial Aunt,
you finally woke up.
Yin,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
The master-servant contract acted up,
so you fainted.
It acted up
because you were thinking
of something against the contract.
Yin,
let me ask you,
and you must be honest with me.
Were you trying to hurt Gu Jin?
Of course not.
How could I hurt him?
Then
do you have feelings for him?
♪Flowers bloom, hands hold♪
♪I look into your eyes♪
♪Life after life, I search♪
♪Reminiscence and nostalgia♪
♪Your smile is my sweetest dream♪
♪On a chilly night, leaves gyrate♪
♪Your face emerges♪
♪Life after life, I get disappointed♪
♪Old dreams come back to me♪
♪Your heart is where I stay alone♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I water the withered with the ocean♪
♪Make vibrant changes♪
♪And rebuild love♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I bid farewell with blood and tears♪
♪Unshackle the regret♪
♪And rush to you forever♪
♪Forever♪