♪Destiny is so mysterious♪
♪Hazards appear in piles♪
♪Reflected in the mirror of mortal♪
♪Reincarnation repeats itself♪
♪I'm so forlorn and no one responds♪
♪Twilight falls on the deserted path♪
♪Beautiful old memories♪
♪Echo under the eaves♪
♪I don't want my soul to perish♪
♪Or disappear♪
♪Always live the life, happy or sad♪
♪Get rid of the glory♪
♪Reveal the destiny♪
♪Absorb the luck of heaven and earth♪
♪And prosper perfectly♪
♪When young dream chasers♪
♪Travel together♪
♪And shine brightly♪
♪I keep them company for mankind♪
♪Waiting to emerge♪
♪However the world changes♪
♪I've never been afraid♪
♪Even if everything collapses in the end♪
♪I will hold you in my arms♪
♪Brambles pierce through me♪
♪Tears roll down your cheeks♪
=The Last Immortal=
=Episode 19=
(Gallant and Formidable)
Bad news! Bad news!
The Heavenly Punishment Officer
is coming to arrest Yin!
Me?
The Energy Protection Arrow exploded
and hurt Lord Zhen Yi's finger bone.
What?
You were watching over the Arrow, huh?
And you were the last to touch it
before it was put into the Secret Storeroom.
They think it's your responsibility
and will catch you for interrogations.
That's not true.
I checked it before that.
Nothing was wrong with the Arrow.
It doesn't matter.
I'll explain it to them.
Yin!
(Gallant and Formidable)
It's not time to explain anything.
Jin.
Yin.
We all trust you in this.
But the demons are furious
and forcing us to answer to them.
If we can't figure out what happened
and they insist on a solution,
you're very likely
to be used as a scapegoat.
But I didn't do anything.
- If I don't explain it now...
- Oh, no.
They're breaking in.
You come with me.
Come on. Say no more.
Leave through the back door.
- Go.
- Hurry.
Hi, Officer.
The Heavenly Palace is
so glorious and vast.
I really can't find my way.
Please walk with me and show me the way.
But...
I'm in some haste.
It won't take long.
Lead the way.
This way, please.
Yin.
What happened
when you delivered the Arrow?
Tell me if anything was unusual.
Or I couldn't vindicate you.
You don't suspect me?
Don't be silly.
I brought you up.
How can I not know
what kind of girl you are?
What's wrong?
Had anyone hurt you before I got you?
I'm just thinking. Why am I stuck
in this kind of thing
and put you in trouble?
This isn't trouble.
You're under my protection.
Whoever gives you trouble
will be provoking our sect and me.
If you don't believe it, ask Qing Yi.
He won't let anyone hurt you, either.
Anyway, before we find out the truth,
you have to glue together with me.
You will be seen unless you wear
the Heaven-shuttling Garment, understand?
Last night in the Secret Storeroom,
I saw a ring-shaped weapon fly out.
I thought I saw it wrong.
But considering what happened today,
the ring-shaped weapon must be fishy.
So, who's behind all this?
Now, immortals and demons
are at loggerheads.
I think someone is
taking advantage of this thing
to start a fight between us.
If this is true,
we should tell
the Heavenly Palace about it.
We can't.
We don't have any proof.
Our conjecture alone isn't convincing.
Besides, Jiu is a demon.
If we point out what happened last night,
he may be exposed
and get into unnecessary trouble.
I prefer to investigate secretly
and catch them off guard.
I don't care who's behind this
or what he wants.
Since they've framed Yin,
I won't let them go.
The ring-shaped weapon followed us
into the Secret Storeroom.
But Jiu noticed it
before it approached the Arrow.
How could it do anything...
Can there be a mole?
That's exactly what I was thinking.
And that's why I hurriedly
took you away from the Hall of Arms.
If you had been caught,
you would be tortured.
Oh, look.
This is a fragment of the Arrow
I found where it exploded.
Yin, check if you can find anything.
Blood-sucking Sand?
I didn't use it to make the Arrow.
This is a fake arrow.
The smell... I smelt it before.
- Where?
In the last place
I found Feng Yin's immortal spirit.
Let's go, then.
We should go.
But we can't bet everything on one clue.
Now we know
the Blood-sucking Sand is the key clue.
All the fragments are kept
in the Hall of Wind
for the Wind Lord's inspection.
Jiu, you keep a close eye
on the Hall of Wind
and see if anyone suspicious gets in there.
Besides, one couldn't fake an arrow
unless he had the drawing.
Yan Shuang,
you should check the list of recent shifts
and investigate anyone who had access
to the drawing and manufacture.
Yin and I will search for more clues
where the Blood-sucking Sand was found.
I had meant to ask the Immortal Realm
for more Blessed Caves.
Unexpectedly, they silenced me
with the Nirvana Wheel.
The Wheel is so useless to me.
But if I had rejected
the sacred weapon of the Fox Clan,
they may suspect me.
But Master, what do we
need the Blessed Caves for?
My devil army is growing bigger
and it's harder to cover the devil energy.
Without suitable places to settle my army,
others will find them sooner or later
and I will fail in the end.
Unless I have the barrier-breaking stone
of Ningyun Mountain to cover the devil energy.
But I can't get the Stone
until I have the mastership
of Ningyun Mountain
from the Heavenly Palace.
No wonder you took so much trouble.
As our scapegoat,
Yin diverted the investigation direction.
This is a wonderful surprise.
But just in case,
all traces of the fake arrow
must be cleaned up.
But now, the Heavenly Palace
is heavily guarded.
I really can't break in.
Don't worry.
Someone else is more anxious than you.
(Weird.)
(There's a strong smell
of the Blood-sucking Sand.)
(But why can't I see any of it?)
Jin, I found him!
Stop running!
Yin!
Gu Jin, Yin.
Wind Lord.
What are you doing here?
Who's that man in black?
For your information,
Yin and I came here for some clues.
That man in black is to blame
for the loss of Lord Zhen Yi's finger bone.
(Heavenly Palace, the Immortal Realm)
Your Lordship,
the Blood-sucking Sand is really found
on every piece of the Arrow.
Your Lordship,
because of the Sand,
the fake arrow exploded
at the Spiritual Trigram Assembly.
But when Yin made the Arrow,
she didn't use this material.
Anyone who manufactured
or inspected the Arrow can verify that.
So, Yin is falsely accused.
Someone else is behind this.
Your Lordship, hope you can
report this to His Majesty soon
and clear Yin's name.
Don't worry.
I will honestly report to His Majesty,
repeal the hunting order on Yin
and vindicate her.
If you hadn't insisted on trusting her,
we would nearly wrong this innocent girl.
By the way,
the man in black
detonated the Sand at short range.
He must have been burnt, too.
Give out my order.
Screen out anyone in the Palace
who was burnt.
Anyone regardless of his rank.
Thanks to you, Jin.
So, I will give you a huge present.
You don't need to.
Your problem is mine.
This is a very important present.
You lost it a long time ago.
I hope you can get it back.
What?
Tell me about it.
Not until I find it.
All right.
(There it is.)
(This is great.)
(I'm sending Gu Jin a message
and give Yin a surprise.)
Feng Ming,
what happened?
When I was patrolling here,
I saw this man doing devil cultivation.
I fought him, then.
Unexpectedly, he scattered
some explosive powder
and I was unfortunately burned.
But luckily, he failed to run away.
It's the Blood-sucking Sand.
Yan Si.
He's the man in black you met, huh?
We were late.
Your Ladyship,
His Majesty found out the truth
of the finger bone case.
Knowing a devil cultivator
was behind all this,
the Demon King agreed to let it go.
He accepted our precious
compensation offer,
250 kilometers of unclaimed territory
and the Nirvana Wheel.
At the command of His Majesty,
we've brought you the Nirvana Wheel.
Thank you.
Leave me.
Gu Jin and Yin ruined my plan!
Ningyun Mountain isn't
among the unclaimed territory.
What about your plan?
Luckily, Hua Shu, the Deity of Fortune,
takes care of the land distribution.
Under such circumstances,
we have to use Hua Mo.
Father,
why was the Arrow case
totally different from what you told me?
Shu, you got me wrong.
I thought that was
just a small deal with the Fox Queen.
I didn't know
she even colluded with devils.
Demons are rather cunning.
You shouldn't have trusted demons.
If people know we were involved,
we can hardly vindicate ourselves.
Yeah.
Luckily, you were clever enough
to remove the scene in the Truth Mirror
with the Peacock Feather Pure Water.
So, in no case can they come after us.
Hong Ruo kept her promise, anyway.
She told us the secret of the immortals.
It'll help with your application
for the Cloud Lord.
Sadly, the female immortal
named Yin survived.
We had meant to kill her in this case.
To our surprise, she got away with it.
Even if we failed to kill her,
we should give her a lesson.
You said she applied
for claiming Ningyun Mountain, right?
After she hurt my son,
how could she wish for a mountain?
Why don't you give
this mountain to the demons, too?
(Heavenly Palace, the Immortal Realm)
Why is Ningyun Mountain
also given to the demons?
According to Princess Hua Shu,
there isn't a lot of unclaimed territory
within 250 kilometers in the south.
So, she had to pick some from the north.
The document has been sealed
by both sides and delivered.
Any problem, Your Majesty?
Forget it.
Your Majesty, Yin is here.
You don't need to curtsy.
Thank you for finding
out the truth in time
and resolving the misunderstanding
between immortals and demons.
I never expected
an immortal to do devil cultivation.
And the devils dared to stir up trouble
and intensify our contradictions.
Your Majesty,
I have something else to tell you.
In the Secret Storeroom,
Jiu found a suspicious ring-shaped weapon.
The Nirvana Wheel saw it through
and it fled in panic.
When Jiu caught up, it was gone.
Seriously?
It happened in a fleeting instant.
Without evidence, we didn't dare to judge.
But considering the fake arrow case,
there must have been some relations.
The Heavenly Palace is heavily guarded.
Without organization or premeditation,
how could anyone fake the arrow
and replace the real one?
And a ring-shaped weapon from nowhere
ended up in the Secret Storeroom.
Are you saying
there's still a mole of the Devil Realm?
Yin, thanks for reminding me.
I'll immediately have the Palace
thoroughly investigated.
Yin,
I invited you here
because I wanted to apologize.
Because of the devil's trap,
you were falsely accused.
I'm certainly to blame.
It doesn't matter.
We found the real killer, anyway.
Don't blame yourself, Your Majesty.
You found out the devil killer
and settled the dispute
between immortals and demons.
A special merit for you.
And I'll make you
a fourth-rank Official of Arms.
What else do you want? Tell me.
I... I want nothing else.
Your Majesty, please allow me
to claim Ningyun Mountain.
Ningyun Mountain?
(Ningyun Mountain)
What?
Ningyun Mountain was given to the demons?
Upon hearing this, I hurried to you.
Yin was summoned by His Majesty.
I don't think she's aware yet.
I'll go tell her.
(The pear tree on Daze Mountain.)
(Something urgent about Yin.)
(Gu Jin, come immediately.)
Three-life Stone?
Something about Yin?
Go check it out.
I'll take care of Yin. Don't worry.
All right. I'll be right back.
Sorry, Yu.
I still failed to get Ningyun Mountain.
I don't know when I can wake you up.
I came here and started
as the lowest official
just to become a fifth-rank official
and claim my own place.
I thought it was the fairest rule
in the Heavenly Palace.
But why did they
take away Ningyun Mountain?
Is it because I have a low status
that I can't even protect my home?
Don't be too sad, Yin.
There must be another way out.
Jiu is a demon, right?
We can ask him for help.
Maybe he can convince the Demon King
to allow us to trade Ningyun Mountain back
with some other treasure.
It's too early to give up.
Moreover, I have good news for you.
I'm sure it'll make you happy.
I found Gu Jin's affection ties.
Really?
You bet.
Gu Jin is going to find
Three-life Stone now.
You should go too.
Hurry.
Three-life Stone.
Gu Jin.
What's up?
This is a gift from Yin.
What gift?
These are your affection ties.
Your affection towards Yin.
Someone removed them
with the Memory-erasing Flute
and buried them here.
It took me a long time to find them.
My affection towards Yin?
Actually, Yin already fell in love with you
when you were bound
with the master-servant contract.
Because of that, she was punished
by the contract quite a few times.
Now, please open it. Let me show you
how close you guys used to be.
(Gu Jin, Yin)
I'll lock it now.
Done.
(Gu Jin, Yin)
Gu Jin and Yin.
We are bound together now.
You loved it so much.
I want to give it to you as a betrothal gift.
I'm thinking instead
of the master-servant contract,
we can make a marriage contract
so we can be together forever.
Yin,
let's go to Yantian Hall tomorrow
to make the contract.
I'd love to.
Wait.
Not the master-servant contract.
It should be a marriage contract. Let's do it.
What marriage contract?
Marriage contract is not something
to be made casually.
You read too many story books.
Who removed your affection ties anyway?
It'd take a lot of effort to do such a thing.
Could it be
the two senior brothers of yours?
Well, His Majesty will go back
to the Nether Realm soon.
I'm leaving now.
Take your time and think about it.
Please think twice, Your Lordship.
Do you know when you answered
for the tribulation under the Heaven Stone
to get back the immortal spirit
of the Fire Phoenix,
the tribulation emerged?
And that was Yin.
Donghua predicted that before he left
and made the master-servant contract
so that you could avoid the tribulation.
Now, the contract is
unexpectedly terminated.
Your love with Yin
will only make the tribulation
more terrifying
and put you in more danger.
Your Lordship, why do you
want to see me in a hurry?
Your Lordship, don't be mad.
I can't watch a tribulation
befall you and do nothing.
That's why I took it upon myself
and went a little far.
Aunt, you watched me grow up.
You know my temper
better than anyone else does.
Just because I respect you
doesn't mean you can remove
my affection ties in secret
and manipulate my feelings!
Even if Yin is my tribulation, so what?
We should be responsible
for our own relationship.
No one else has the right
to interfere and meddle in it.
No matter what I do,
it's for your own good.
I knew you'd be angry with me,
but I still had to do it.
For my own good?
So, are you going to continue to interfere
and separate me and Yin?
I'm worried that you'd regret it one day.
You may not care about yourself,
but you do care about Daze Mountain.
How does it have anything to do
with Daze Mountain?
Blessed by your god parents, Daze Mountain
is now more prosperous than ever.
But, anything comes with a price.
Donghua predicted
that something would happen
to the master-servant contract,
so he had a backup plan prepared for you.
Although I made a master-servant contract
for Gu Jin and Yin,
not everything in the world
will go as we designed.
If the contract fails by accident one day,
there's only one way left.
We'll have to link Gu Jin's tribulation
to Daze Mountain,
hoping that the spiritual energy accumulated
for 70,000 years can keep him safe.
But, it's really unfair to the rest of you.
What?
Your master-servant contract was severed
by the dragon in the Mortal Realm,
so your tribulation is bound to happen.
Therefore, your two senior brothers
made the decision
that when it comes,
Daze Mountain will fend it off for you.
Staying with Yin will harm
not only yourself but also Daze Mountain.
In that case, do you still insist
on being with her?
Why have my senior brothers
never told me about that?
Your Lordship, if you don't believe me,
you can see it for yourself.
Bearing Donghua's order,
Xian Zhu and Xian Shan
can't tell you the truth.
But I know you very well.
I think you should know the truth.
Otherwise, if that day came,
how could you deal with it?
It's not like we'll end Yin's life.
We just need you to stop loving her.
It won't do much harm to her anyway.
Which is more important? Your affection,
or the lives of all the disciples
of Daze Mountain?
It was my fault
that I wanted to make a decision for you.
And now, I'll let you
make your own decision.
I'm sure
you'll do the right thing
given the gravity of the situation.
I've put my soul mark on Yin.
Even if she's in danger,
I'll be there to protect her.
We still have the Worry-free Immortal Fruit.
All you need to do right now
is take a good rest.
I will.
I still need to make the contract
with you tomorrow.
It was my fault
that I wanted to make a decision for you.
And now, I'll let you
make your own decision.
I'm sure
you'll do the right thing
given the gravity of the situation.
This is my gift for you.
Your affection ties.
Do you recall it now?
Yes, I do.
Yin,
I was too immature before.
I shouldn't have behaved like that.
I guess you know now that I'm a True God.
I should carry forward the will of
the ancestral gods and protect the Three Realms.
I can't waste my energy
and time on one person only.
In fact, I had my affection ties removed myself.
I didn't expect you'd find them back.
Sorry for the confusion.
I don't want to spend my whole life
waiting for someone like Xian Zhu did.
Love and affection don't matter.
I have more important things to do.
Do you understand?
But you told me
I was also important to you.
Yes,
you were.
But it was before, not now.
To me, all lives
in the Three Realms are equal,
including you.
Are there any unspeakable reasons?
Or, is it because Lady Hong Chou
told you that you and I…
It's okay.
Lady Hong Chou is only
the Chief of Qingchi Palace.
I am the head of Qingchi Palace.
She has no right to order me around.
♪Flowers bloom, hands hold♪
♪I look into your eyes♪
Yin,
you are my junior sister,
so I'll be straight with you.
♪Life after life, I search♪
There's a huge status gap between us.
♪Your smile is my sweetest dream♪
You and I are not gonna happen.
You should give up.
♪Your face emerges♪
♪Life after life, I get disappointed♪
♪Old dreams come back to me♪
♪Your heart is where I stay alone♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
So, my love for you
is just a joke in your eyes, right?
Or, you've never really loved me?
Yes, I had feelings for you first,
but you did say that you'd
make a marriage contract with me.
Yes, I'm of humble status,
but I don't think it matters
when it comes to love.
I had no idea you are this type of person.
Yes, I am this type of person.
Fine.
There's no better time
than now to end our relationship.
♪Forever♪
♪On a chilly night, leaves gyrate♪
♪Your face emerges♪
♪Life after life, I get disappointed♪
♪Old dreams come back to me♪
♪Your heart is where I stay alone♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I water the withered with the ocean♪
♪Make vibrant changes♪
Don't.
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I bid farewell with blood and tears♪
♪Unshackle the regret♪
♪And rush to you forever♪
♪Forever♪
(Ningyun Mountain, the Immortal Realm)
As it turned out, Ningyun Mountain
has been hiding here over the past
tens of thousands of years.
I heard the rumor about the secret barrier
in Ningyun Mountain.
Now that I see it today,
it's indeed spectacular.
Without the barrier stone,
the landform of Ningyun Mountain
wouldn't have been kept intact like this.
After the extinction of Water Divine Beasts,
this piece of stone is the only
valuable thing left in the mountain.
Wait.
You want to challenge
an expert cultivator of our clan?
Yes.
According to your rules,
the winner can get the thing that he wants.
This is the Cradle Boat,
the only demigod tool in the entire
Three Realms that can nurture the young,
and it's the only one in the whole world.
I'll challenge an expert of yours
using this as the prize.
Win or lose, you can get this Cradle Boat.
But if I win, I want only one thing.
I hope you and the Fox Queen
can give me Ningyun Mountain.
Ruo,
it's a no-lose deal.
We have no reason to refuse.
General You, you go.
Ruo, You Tu is a Senior Immortal.
If we send him to fight Junior Immortal Gu Jin,
it's a little unfair even if we win.
He's Donghua's favorite disciple.
How do you know he didn't come prepared?
Since he wants to challenge us,
let his strength be the final judge.
So, my love for you
is just a joke in your eyes, right?
Or, you've never really loved me?
I was wrong about you.
I can't protect my own home,
and I don't deserve a True God's love.
I didn't expect you could be this powerful.
I underestimated you.
Stop it, Ruo.
Though he's a Junior Immortal,
he defeated a Senior Immortal of our clan.
According to our rules, he won.
(If I fight Daze Mountain)
(and cause a lockdown,)
(it'd actually affect my plan.)
(I've got the barrier stone anyway.)
(Ningyun Mountain)
(is no use to me anymore.)
Fine.
If you want Ningyun Mountain this badly,
I'll let you have it on account of Hong Yi.
(Tablet)
(Heavenly Palace, the Immortal Realm)
After negotiation, the Demon Clan
has agreed to return Ningyun Mountain.
I'll approve your application
and give the mountain to you
your residence.
But, the Fox Queen took the barrier stone.
I hope you don't mind.
I don't.
Getting the mountain back
already makes me happy enough.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
(Tablet)
Why don't you give it to Yin yourself?
Your Majesty, please keep it a secret for me.
I don't want her to know.
I finally got back to Ningyun Mountain.
But it feels like everything has changed.
Yu will hatch soon.
Hope when she grows up,
she won't fall for the wrong person
or chase the wrong dream.
Yin,
you've always despised
such thing as status discrimination.
How could you say that about yourself?
I thought he didn't care about it either,
but as it turned out,
he does.
Gu Jin is such a jerk.
Yin, stop drinking.
Don't use wine to punish yourself.
He left you, and it's his loss.
That's right, Yin. Drinking will only
make you feel more miserable.
Stop drinking.
Your health is more important.
I'll consider today a closure on the past,
which seems insignificant,
but it cost all the love I had.
But time will heal.
Sure. Everything will be fine.
Yin, we'll always be there for you.
♪Flowers bloom, hands hold♪
♪I look into your eyes♪
♪Life after life, I search♪
♪Reminiscence and nostalgia♪
♪Your smile is my sweetest dream♪
♪On a chilly night, leaves gyrate♪
♪Your face emerges♪
♪Life after life, I get disappointed♪
♪Old dreams come back to me♪
♪Your heart is where I stay alone♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I water the withered with the ocean♪
♪Make vibrant changes♪
♪And rebuild love♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I bid farewell with blood and tears♪
♪Unshackle the regret♪
♪And rush to you forever♪
♪Forever♪