♪Destiny is so mysterious♪
♪Hazards appear in piles♪
♪Reflected in the mirror of mortal♪
♪Reincarnation repeats itself♪
♪I'm so forlorn and no one responds♪
♪Twilight falls on the deserted path♪
♪Beautiful old memories♪
♪Echo under the eaves♪
♪I don't want my soul to perish♪
♪Or disappear♪
♪Always live the life, happy or sad♪
♪Get rid of the glory♪
♪Reveal the destiny♪
♪Absorb the luck of heaven and earth♪
♪And prosper perfectly♪
♪When young dream chasers♪
♪Travel together♪
♪And shine brightly♪
♪I keep them company for mankind♪
♪Waiting to emerge♪
♪However the world changes♪
♪I've never been afraid♪
♪Even if everything collapses in the end♪
♪I will hold you in my arms♪
♪Brambles pierce through me♪
♪Tears roll down your cheeks♪
=The Last Immortal=
=Episode 35=
Go to the Demon Realm and bring
your Phoenix Queen back.
Yu.
Come over.
Lady Hong Chou.
You do know who I am.
You are so happy on
Wutong Island these days.
Have you forgotten your identity?
When His Godship proposed to
marry into Wutong Island,
why didn't you try to stop him?
It's a good thing that His Godship
marries my sister.
Why should I stop him?
My sister said that Wutong Island
has no cliché.
So, as long as His Godship is happy,
I have no objections.
Unbridled!
How dare you talk nonsense like this!
(Fengyi Palace)
Follow me back to Qingchi Palace
and reflect on your mistakes.
How mighty Your Ladyship is.
Your hand has reached
my Wutong Island.
Yu belongs to Qingchi Palace.
What's wrong with me
to teach her as the Chief?
I recognized Yu as my sister.
She is somewhat famous and respected
on this Wutong Island.
Furthermore, Yuan Qi has given
Qingchi Palace to me as a betrothal gift.
I can be considered the true owner
of Qingchi Palace.
You, as the Chief, should also
listen to my commands.
I was sent by True Goddess Yi He
to the Immortal Realm
to take care of His Godship.
Besides True Goddess Yi He and His
Godship, who dares to boss me around?
His Godship was raised by me
from childhood.
Not to mention Yu, even you
should be treated as I wish
since you married His Godship.
How do you plan to treat me?
Do you want to treat me like
what you did to Yin before?
Throw her into the hurricane of
Wujin Cliff and let her perish on her own,
or remove His Godship's affection ties again?
How could you know these things?
I experienced all these.
How could I not know your methods?
You experienced these?
Are you…
Water Divine Beasts have a short life,
but we are not lowly.
Impossible!
Absolutely impossible!
My immortal spirit scattered back then.
A portion of my immortal spirit entered
the body of the Water Divine Beast,
and awakened the dormant
Water Divine Beast.
You are Yin?
I thought Your Ladyship is
so proud and mighty
that you have long forgotten about
the insignificant pawn Yin.
I am Yin.
Hong Chou came to find Feng Yin's trouble?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Hong Chou is notorious for being
difficult to deal with in the Three Realms.
I'm just afraid that Lady Feng Yin
will be wronged.
According to my understanding
of Feng Yin,
no one in the Three Realms can
make her back down except Yuan Qi.
Your Majesty, what you said is true.
But if she is wronged,
wouldn't you feel sorry for her?
The Three Realms have a manner of
treating others based on their positions.
I had already experienced it before,
so it's nothing special.
When I was a Water Divine Beast,
you considered my life insignificant.
Now I have returned, you came to
propose marriage on behalf of Yuan Qi.
This changing face is really ridiculous.
It's not like that.
I hated Yin and tried to kill her
only because...
Because she would bring
a tribulation to His Godship.
So?
Did she have to die
just to keep His Godship alive?
In your eyes, can Water Divine Beasts
be abandoned so easily?
Lord Donghua and my senior brothers
tried everything they could to protect us.
But you remained supercilious,
thinking you're the noblest.
Who are you to judge Yin's life?
Why can you decide
who lives and who dies?
You thought you saw through everything.
Did you see this coming?
You just had your view overshadowed
and you're such a snob.
I thought everything I did was
for the sake of His Godship.
But unexpectedly, it turns out that
I was presumptuous.
Fortunately, the Heavenly Empress is here.
I want to ask Your Majesty,
the Divine Envoy of Qingchi Palace
intentionally hurt a Fire Phoenix.
How should she be disposed of?
The God Realm should not interfere
in the affairs of the Three Realms.
Not to mention slaughtering
living beings in the Three Realms.
You persecuted the Phoenix Queen
under the guise of loyalty.
If True Goddess Yi He knows it,
she will expel you from the God Realm.
Expel me from the God Realm?
You should be grateful that Feng Yin
is safe and sound this time.
If she is willing to forgive you,
you may be exempt from punishment.
I have only knelt in front of
True Goddess Yi He and God Yuan Qi.
I consider myself worthy of
the God Realm.
But I turned out to be self-righteous,
shallow, and narrow-minded.
I am not afraid of being
expelled from the God Realm,
because I only cared about
the well-being of His Godship.
But today, I know I was totally wrong.
I kneel in front of the Phoenix Queen here,
not asking for forgiveness.
I am willing to pay any price
and accept whatever punishment.
Forget it.
Whether you are sincere or hokey,
at least you helped Yuan Qi
take care of Yu.
If you dare to mention your so-called
rules of honor and hierarchy
in front of me or bully Yu again,
I will let you know that it's not difficult
to bully others using power.
Your Godship.
I thought you had prejudices against Yin
because you cared too much about me.
But I didn't expect you really
wanted to kill Yin.
I lost my head at that moment
and made a big mistake.
I'm sorry to disappoint Your Godship.
I'm sorry to the Phoenix Queen.
I'm sorry for betraying the trust of
True Goddess Yi He and Your Godship.
I can forgive you for any other matters,
but I'll never forgive you
for what you did to Yin.
The person you're most sorry for
is not me, but Yin.
Chang Que.
Bring Hong Chou back to Qingchi Palace
and wait for Phoenix Queen's decision.
If the Phoenix Queen
won't forgive you in the end,
go to the God Realm
and resign from your position.
Your Godship.
Your Godship!
I'm sorry.
I didn't know Yin had suffered
these grievances.
In fact, what Hong Chou did
was all for me.
If it triggers any of
your unpleasant memories,
you can blame me as you want.
It's all in the past.
Don't mention it again.
I didn't expect you are willing to let
Hong Chou grow old in Qingchi Palace.
She did all this for you.
She can't be considered
completely wrong.
Let's sleep now. We will go find
the Purple Moon tomorrow.
Is there anything unusual about them?
They get along the same as
an ordinary couple.
They are affectionate.
His Godship loves the Phoenix Queen
very much.
Lady Hong Chou had a conflict
with the Phoenix Queen,
and was confined in Qingchi Palace
for life.
Yuan Qi has always respected Hong Chou.
He punished Hong Chou so heavily
just because of a conflict.
This is a bit strange.
You did a great job.
Keep watching them closely.
The reward is abundant.
Thank you, Your Lordship.
(Immortal House on Xuan Pond,
the Immortal Realm)
The source of Ruoshui River.
The Ruoshui River is difficult to cross.
I didn't expect
there is such a dense mist here.
Ordinary immortals and demons
cannot reach there.
No wonder no one can find traces of
devils in the past thousands of years.
This time, it's all thanks to Hong Yi.
This is the Abyssal Prison?
Don't run around.
As long as we are together, the
Heaven-shuttling Garment can protect us.
Let's go.
Be careful.
The concealing barrier
of Ningyun Mountain.
The Purple Moon is indeed here.
Using the concealing barrier of
Ningyun Mountain here.
How tricky the Devil God Ming Qi is.
I have searched through the Three Realms,
from Dawu Mountain in the far west
to the Liyuan Sea in the far south,
even the islands in the North Sea
have been thoroughly investigated,
but I have never found
any trace of the Purple Moon.
It won't be long before
the barrier is broken.
There is no need to waste energy.
Join me in opening this barrier
and overturning the Three Realms.
Isn't it more interesting?
Do you feel the fluctuation
of spiritual power?
Yes, I do.
Wait a moment.
There is something wrong
with this barrier.
This barrier cannot be broken.
They have connected this barrier
to the barrier of the Abyss.
If we forcefully open this barrier,
it is very likely to impact the barrier
of the Abyssal Prison.
It seems that the devils want to
break the Abyss's barrier in this way.
The strange fluctuation of
spiritual power just now
should be some kind of force
colliding with the barrier.
Is it possible that there are
other passages besides this one?
It is difficult for immortals and demons
to come to the source of Ruoshui River.
It seems that Hua Mo is trying to use
another passage to impact the barrier.
It's an urgent task for us to quickly find
another passage and block it.
Otherwise, it would be dangerous.
Let's leave here first.
What's wrong?
It turns out that Hua Mo had colluded
with devils a thousand years ago.
What happened back then must have
something to do with him,
Lan Feng, Daze Mountain,
and what you have suffered.
I wish I could crush him
into powder right now.
We have found the Purple Moon.
As long as we regain control
of the Abyssal Prison,
we can settle the problems with
the devils and Hua Mo.
I have come up with a solution.
Perhaps we can use Fu Chen to find
the passage connecting to the Abyss.
This is the spiritual power on the barrier
at the source of Ruoshui River.
You want to do what you did
to sense the Purple Moon,
using the spiritual power collected by
the parasol tree leaf to feel the passages?
That's right.
Now we know the fact that
Hua Mo has colluded with devils,
but we don't know whether the Peacock
Clan, even the entire Immortal Realm,
contains his followers.
We should not alert him before
finding other passages.
What I'm worried about most now
is Hua Shu.
She came to our wedding.
She should not have become a devil yet.
I hope she won't be too silly.
Feng Ge did have contact with Hua Mo.
(Fengyi Palace)
(Feng Ge left Wutong Island to deliver
invitations and candies to Bainiao Island)
(Daily Records of Immortal Maids
in Fengyi Palace)
What are you doing?
We will sleep together from now on.
Why?
Don't think too much.
I am considering the overall situation.
You see, we are suspicious
of Feng Ge now.
We need to be more cautious
in our actions.
In case she finds out that
we sleep in separate beds,
what we did before will all be in vain.
We'll use the water bowl as a boundary,
one person facing the head of the bed,
and the other facing the foot,
no trespassing.
Can we sleep now?
We can,
but I...
Why do you have wounds on your back?
I accidentally bumped into
the Primordial Ancient Vine.
It's nothing serious.
I'll help you apply the ointment.
Does it hurt?
No.
I'll be gentle.
Honey, you're quite concerned about me.
Don't call me that.
I do this for you
because Chang Que is not here.
Why is this ointment not working?
Is it truly a stab wound?
Why does it look like a punitive sign
by a magic weapon?
- Your wounds…
- Primordial Ancient Vine
has been chosen to smelt
magic weapons since ancient times.
The wounds it causes are like this.
But…
Honey, you are so gentle.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Let's sleep now.
Why do you come to
Qingchi Palace today?
His Godship is not in the palace.
I don't come for His Godship.
I heard that Your Ladyship
was embarrassed by the Phoenix Queen,
and you were confined in
Qingchi Palace, so I came to visit you.
You have never made any mistakes
in the past thousands of years.
How could His Godship punish you
for such a trivial matter?
Could it be that the Phoenix Queen
is causing trouble?
What does Your Highness want to know?
I am not afraid to tell you the truth. It is
because I didn't respect the Phoenix Queen.
I deserve this punishment.
His Godship and the Phoenix Queen
love each other.
His Godship is affectionate
toward the Phoenix Queen.
No one can be instigated.
I know that you
can't forget about His Godship.
I don't want to say much about love,
but I want to tell you that
His Godship doesn't like you at all.
He loved the Phoenix Queen a thousand
years ago and still loves her now.
I advise you to give up early.
Don't end up losing face completely.
Farewell.
Hong Chou said that His Godship loved
the Phoenix Queen a thousand years ago
and still loves her now.
It's simply nonsense.
Wasn't the one Yuan Qi loved
the Water Divine Beast Yin?
Who is there?
How dare you eavesdrop here?
I didn't eavesdrop.
I was just hiding here to calm down.
It's you who don't behave yourself and
speak ill of Aunt Hong Chou.
You're just a humble beast
favored by His Godship,
how dare you challenge me?
I will take you to Qinglong Platform now
and teach you the principles
of respect and hierarchy.
Hua Shu, if you want to discuss
hierarchy, why don't you come to me?
By qualification, I am a demigod, you
are just at the peak of senior immortal.
By status, I am the Phoenix Queen,
you are just an Acting Heavenly Empress.
By territory, Qingchi Palace is
the residence of His Godship.
Now, His Godship is mine,
so is this Qingchi Palace.
How dare you act recklessly here?
Don't you apologize to me?
You love Qinglong Platform, huh?
Is this where you did evil
for your own selfish desires?
A thousand years ago,
you failed to kill me there.
Now, you want to hurt my sister?
You really think Water Divine Beasts
are pushovers, huh?
So, it's really you.
Yin, the Water Divine Beast!
Why? This is unfair.
I'm going to kill you to avenge Lan Feng!
For Lan Feng's sake,
I tolerated you as far as I could!
But now, I'm no longer Yin
who showed kindness everywhere.
So, I won't let you run amok anymore.
Hua Shu, having evil ideas isn't horrible.
But you should wake up in time.
If you still thwart
the investigation of Yuan Qi and me,
I won't show mercy.
But let me remind you, by that time,
what you lose will not only be
the position of the Heavenly Empress.
Your Majesty.
(Landscape of Ponds and Mountains)
I apologize.
I was eager to protect His Godship
and repeatedly went against his will,
cutting off your fate with His Godship.
It caused His Godship to suffer a lot
and he still cannot sleep soundly now.
This is not what I wanted.
There is no need to mention the past.
No. There are some things
that you should know.
His Godship has always loved you.
To protect you,
he left a soul mark on you,
preventing me from hurting you.
I had to take away his affection ties
while he was healing.
His Godship knew nothing
about these things.
He held the responsibility of his sect
and wanted to protect his beloved one.
I knew His Godship was affectionate
and righteous, but kept pressing him.
Bearing Donghua's order, Xian Zhu
and Xian Shan can't tell you the truth.
It's not like we'll end Yin's life.
We just need you to stop loving her.
It won't do much harm to her anyway.
Which is more important? Your affection,
or the lives of all the disciples
of Daze Mountain?
In fact, I had my affection ties
removed myself.
There's no better time
than now to end our relationship.
♪Flowers bloom, hands hold♪
♪I look into your eyes♪
♪Life after life, I search♪
♪Reminiscence and nostalgia♪
♪Your smile is my sweetest dream♪
(Tablet)
♪On a chilly night, leaves gyrate♪
♪Your face emerges♪
♪Life after life, I get disappointed♪
His Godship loved you deeply,
(Landscape of Ponds and Mountains)
but he dared not implicate Daze Mountain.
He had to destroy his affection ties
to push you away.
Everything he said at that time
was all insincere.
He was not like me. He didn't think
Water Divine Beasts are worthless.
Even if I took away his affection ties,
he still fell in love with you again.
He wants to spend his whole life
with you.
He was even willing to give up
becoming a god for you.
Even if Yin can't go to the God Realm,
I always have a way to not
return to the God Realm.
I don't want this
True God's identity anyway.
If I can't stay with the person I love,
how could I become a God
and protect the people?
When you returned from the Nether Realm,
you were at the point of death.
He used his blood of chaos
to prolong your life.
He was afraid that you would refuse
to use this method to prolong your life.
It's not a long-term solution after all.
He finally asked for a way to help you
reshape your immortal body.
Then he began to search for those rare
immortal materials in the Three Realms,
and refine the Spirit-nourishing Elixir
for you.
He begged Hua Shu for
the Peacock Feather Crown.
So, His Godship felt indebted
to Hua Shu,
gave her the jade seal and
did his best to fulfill her request.
He even sacrificed
half of his God power.
♪On a chilly night, leaves gyrate♪
♪Your face emerges♪
It is precisely because of the existence
of the Spirit-nourishing Elixir,
His Godship believed that he could
use his Chaos Power
to seal your immortal bones and
internal core, without hurting you at all.
But who would know
things took a wrong turn.
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
Spirit Sword! Withdraw!
♪I water the withered with the ocean♪
♪Make vibrant changes♪
Since then, he has gone throughout
the Three Realms
and the Nine Regions to search for you.
♪Who said♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I bid farewell with blood and tears♪
♪Unshackle the regret♪
♪And rush to you forever♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I bid farewell with blood and tears♪
♪Unshackle the regret♪
♪And rush to you forever♪
♪Forever♪
I'm telling you these today
just want to let you know that
His Godship never thought of
giving up on Yin, and you.
Even Daze Mountain was destroyed,
he still wanted to protect you.
(He did so much,
but I knew nothing about it.)
You are awake?
I caught a few fish from the river.
I'm roasting them.
We can eat them later.
What's wrong?
Where am I?
You are confused?
We are in the Forbidden Valley
of Daze Mountain.
(Leisure)
We just found Fire Phoenix's immortal spirit.
You took a long sleep after we came back.
You can't remember this?
It seems you are really tired.
Come on. Sit on the swing for a while.
We can eat the fish soon.
Have fun.
♪The past is stained♪
♪The past in dark in light♪
When shall we go back to
Daze Mountain to find the others?
We are in Daze Mountain now.
♪Diluted in the moment of looking back♪
Why do I feel so sad?
It will be fine, Yin.
Everything will be fine
in Daze Mountain.
♪Expecting to travel together♪
- Osmanthus cake.
- Is it delicious?
I haven't tasted it yet.
Try it.
Delicious.
What do you think?
That's interesting.
Look.
Yin.
♪A tear is tied under the river of hope♪
♪It's a trip to the seasons♪
♪The years are like a dream♪
♪The wind rises,
the thoughts are in the way♪
What's wrong?
♪The ink is thick, the past is stained♪
Where did you go?
I thought I couldn't find you.
I went to buy some snacks for you.
Hey, young man, you'd better
keep an eye on your wife.
She couldn't find you and
was about to cry just now.
I didn't.
Don't cry. I'm here.
Follow me.
I'll take these two.
Okay, okay.
♪I wish for a next life of love♪
Here you are.
This is very effective here.
Do you know what it means to buy
intertwined hearts in the Mortal Realm?
Yes, I do.
Didn't you like…
Yin,
I realized that I had been loving
the wrong person all these years.
(Leisure)
I told you that
Hua Shu saved me on Wutong Island.
I thought my gratitude
towards her was love.
But later, I discovered that the person
was not Hua Shu, but Feng Yin.
What does it have to do with me?
I haven't finished yet.
Later, I realized that I not only
made a mistake on the person,
but also misunderstood my feelings.
My feelings toward Feng Yin
are gratefulness.
As for love,
Yin, you are the one who
has been with me all these years.
You are also the one who has
accompanied me through life and death.
You are more important to me.
You are the one I truly love.
What are you saying?
I won't say it again.
How can I say such words a second time?
I heard it clearly.
Happy birthday, Jin.
I hope I can accompany you
on your every birthday in the future.
♪The night breeze blows♪
♪Look at the moon in my dream♪
♪With your eyes in my heart♪
♪How can I not think of you♪
♪Luckily in the world♪
♪You and I witness how time goes by♪
♪We continue to enjoy an ordinary life♪
♪All I want is to visit you often♪
♪And see the world with you♪
♪All I want is to walk around with you♪
You are awake?
Why are you in my dream?
I saw that you fell asleep here.
I just wanted to
bring you into the house.
But I didn't expect your consciousness
to invite me into your dream.
What's wrong?
You got angry?
Sorry.
- Next time, I…
- I'm not angry.
It's fine.
You just said that you are not angry.
Hong Chou told me everything,
the things about the affection ties,
Daze Mountain,
and what you did to refine
the Spirit-nourishing Elixir for me.
You knew everything?
Let's forget about what happened before.
I have learned a few dishes
of the Mortal Realm.
I can make them for you to taste.
Wait a moment.
What shall we forget about?
It's just like what you think.
Which one?
♪All I want is to visit you often♪
♪And see the world with you♪
♪All I want is to walk around with you♪
♪And watch the moon on the roof♪
♪Don't let the story wait for no reason♪
♪It's just like a dream♪
♪Finally I see the moonlight♪
♪Flowers bloom, hands hold♪
♪I look into your eyes♪
♪Life after life, I search♪
♪Reminiscence and nostalgia♪
♪Your smile is my sweetest dream♪
♪On a chilly night, leaves gyrate♪
♪Your face emerges♪
♪Life after life, I get disappointed♪
♪Old dreams come back to me♪
♪Your heart is where I stay alone♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I water the withered with the ocean♪
♪Make vibrant changes♪
♪And rebuild love♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I bid farewell with blood and tears♪
♪Unshackle the regret♪
♪And rush to you forever♪
♪Forever♪