Master, you are here.
-Master--
-Is she
the temptress
who lured you to elope with her?
I--
Bear with it!
For the sake of Master and Weining.
I thought it was because
she's exceptionally pretty.
She turns out to be ordinary.
Master, Gu Xiang is not a temptress.
Although she comes
from the Ghost Valley, she--
she is innocent and kind.
She has gone through a lot
together with us in Mount Qingfeng.
Master, you don't know because
you didn't spend time with her.
-But Master Fan does.
-Shut up!
Temptress, you're something.
You can even delude my disciple.
Huaikong knew I would come
and he put in so many good words for you.
Cao Weining, think twice.
Do you really want to fall
into the evil ways just for this girl?
Master, I've made up my mind.
I once made a vow
that in my whole life,
from now until death,
including every second,
I will never fail Gu Xiang.
Master, you told me
since I was little that we must
honor a promise in good faith.
I can't break
the promise I've made with a girl.
Enough!
You--
you're not willing to fail the girl,
but you can stand that the sect is turning
into a joke of the martial arts world.
Great.
I've made so much effort to bring you up.
But this is how you repay me!
I know my sins.
I'm unfilial and disloyal!
Master!
I will uphold justice
with my wife in the future
to mend our ways!
Master, please show some mercy
and agree to our marriage!
Master.
All right.
Do it!
Weining.
Look.
Hasn't this become…
a festive bereavement?
Kill them!
-Go!
Why are they hitting the drum again?
I want to buy you a meal.
May I ask
what your name is, miss?
After telling my master,
I'll prepare the dowry
and a proper marriage.
In this life,
if I can't be with you,
I won't be happy anyway.
Don't worry because I won't leave you.
Let's leave the martial arts world.
We can open a dessert shop
or a cosmetics shop.
We can raise cows and a farm.
We can do anything.
What do you say?
Gu Xiang!
Go and find Prince Qi!
Yu Qiufeng, are you insane?
Have you really
forgotten about me?
Qianqiao!
All of them are fighting
for the Glazed Armor
at the cost of their lives.
But none of them knows
that I've got all the pieces
of the Glazed Armor,
including the key.
Father.
Why are you staring at me?
Don't you believe me?
Since Wen Kexing didn't die,
the body falling from White Deer Cliff
must be fake.
The key found with the body
must also be fake.
The real key
was given to me by Wen Kexing
in exchange for my cooperation.
All are here.
This is
the Glazed Armor that you gave me.
This used
to belong to the Window of Heaven.
Now, Mo Huaiyang
has practically fallen into my hands.
So he'll give me the remaining
three pieces of the Glazed Armor soon.
Father.
The things you've desired
for more than 20 years
fall into my hands…
in just a flash.
There is something
in my heart
and it's called ambition.
While in others' hearts,
it's called illusion.
When it comes to you,
it's called--
I almost forgot.
You have no heart.
Stop!
Wen Kexing.
One more move
and she's dead!
If you want to save her,
hand over the Glazed Armor
and the key to the armory.
I can give anything to you
as long as you let her go!
She is just a little girl!
"A little girl"?
This temptress is so excellent
in deceiving others
that both my disciple and my junior
have been bewitched by her!
I have no choice but to cleanse my sect!
You killed them?
Shut up!
This is the true
last war.
Coveting gains ahead
without being aware
of the danger behind it.
But none of them knows
that I am
the real hunter.
Run!
Where are those things?
Hand them over!
Fine, I'll give them to you.
What's that sound?
What tricks are you playing with me?
Drug Men army?
It's the Drug Men army!
Retreat! Quickly!
Retreat! The Drug Men army is here.
Gu Xiang!
Retreat! Quickly!
I'm going to kill him.
I'm going to kill him!
Gu Xiang.
Master!
I'm going to kill him!
I'm not your master.
I'm your elder brother.
Kexing.
Kill him for me.
I've never begged you for anything.
Kill him for me!
I'll kill him for you.
I'll kill him for you!
Thank--
thank you, Kexing.
Please take good care of yourself.
From now on,
I can't take care of you anymore.
I'm going
to meet Weining, that fool.
Gu Xiang.
Gu Xiang!
Master.
Master!
Master, how are you?
Are you still feeling dizzy or hungry?
Shall I cook for you?
My good master.
I'll be fine after some rest.
Master, you're a bastard.
See? This unruly servant
is bullying her master.
Master,
are you leaving me?
Scorpion King.
How can we be set up by Scorpion King?
Chief Mo, I was entrusted
to see you off!
Damn brat.
I'm sorry, Gu Xiang,
I let him die an easy death.
Wait for me.
I'm coming to you.
Chief of the Ghost Valley,
it has been a while.
My ally.
You were high-spirited when we last met,
but now,
how did you end up like this?
I'm taking Mo Huaiyang's three pieces
of the Glazed Armor
if you don't mind.
Just take them and get lost.
Don't disturb me
while I'm enjoying the sun.
Your Majesty,
I've admired Chief Wen for a long time.
May I see him off?
For a great figure
such as the chief of the Ghost Valley,
I should do it myself.
Any help from others
would be insulting.
How dare you hurt
someone from the Four Seasons Manor?
Chief Zhou,
you have made
so much progress in your martial arts.
Idiot.
Why are you here?
To die with a lunatic like you.
Chief Zhou. Chief Wen.
Why bother?
Today, no one can walk
out of the Ghost Valley alive.
My children
are everywhere in this valley.
Today, even if I have to die here,
I will drag you down with me.
You two can die together.
Why bother taking me with you?
The netherworld is so boring.
We are both clever men.
Isn't there a second choice?
All right.
You can have the Glazed Armor,
but I'm taking him with me.
Just go then.
How boring.
Wen Kexing!
On your body…
there is light.
I want to take a look at it.
Chief.
We've found all the bodies
of the Ten Devils.
None of them were missing.
The three traitors were detained
in the cold pool's jail.
I've killed them.
Tragicomic Ghost, Ghoul, and Beauty Ghost
have all died in the fight.
Beauty Ghost, Liu Qianqiao?
Yes.
-Scorpion King, is there any problem?
-No.
It's nothing.
Chief, we're still keeping records
of the bodies of those sect leaders,
but we haven't found the bodies
of Mo Huaiyang,
Fan Huaikong, and Mo Weixu
of the Gentle Wind Sword Sect.
I've gotten rid of Mo Huaiyang.
His body is outside the valley.
Fan Huaikong was killed by Mo Huaiyang
and Mo Weixu is still missing.
Don't bother with them.
Didn't you hear what Scorpion King said?
Go.
Yes.
I'm so surprised that the Drug Men army
showed such tremendous power
on the first try.
With these amazing troops,
His Highness will find no difficulty
in forging ahead.
Opening the armory
is no doubt a first-class merit,
but the attack on Mount Qingya
has brought great damage
to the martial arts world.
So many people have died.
It'll take 20 to 30 years to recover.
It's great merit too.
Scorpion King.
You and I are perfect partners!
Ever since Evil Bodhisattva
introduced us to each other,
I've enjoyed rapid advances in my career.
How strange.
Many people have died
in the Central Plain.
Why does it matter to you?
Mr. Duan.
You harm others
without benefiting anything from it.
You're happy for nothing.
My lady,
you're still inexperienced.
Since ancient times,
martial artists tend to violate bans.
They always hunger for fame and credit.
His Highness is coming
for this piece of land.
Sooner or later,
these bandits will be taken care of.
This fight is an act of killing two birds
with one stone, isn't it?
Bullshit. Then why did you cooperate
with Zhao Jing before?
Nothing is too deceitful in war.
I don't believe it.
You old men are always up to no good.
All you do are plotting, cheating,
and setting up traps for others.
Aren't you tired?
Master.
It's me, Gu Xiang.
I met Mother and Father.
They would like to thank you.
They want to talk to you.
I'm not feeling well now.
Maybe another day.
Have a cup of tea then.
I'm so tired.
Get out.
All right.
I'm leaving then.
Kexing.
Please.
Take good care of yourself.
Gu Xiang!
Prince Qi.
Great Shaman.
Zishu.
Thank you for your help
in getting them out.
You're so thoughtful.
It's beautiful here.
Master, Prince Qi asked me just now
what to write
on Weining and Gu Xiang's tombstones.
Yes.
Since they haven't held
the wedding ceremony,
Ms. Gu Xiang is still a girl.
I don't know whether we should write
her name or Lady Cao on it.
It should be Lady Cao.
Gu Xiang would like that.
Master, is Master Wen still unconscious?
I used the Drunk Like a Dream on him.
I don't know how to face him.
Chengling.
I hope you
take good care of Master Wen.
Can you do that?
Master, where are you going?
I thought I could settle down,
but maybe roaming all over the world
is my destiny.
Lord Zhou.
You've pulled out
all those nails in your body?
Zishu.
How could you do that to yourself?
You--
When did you do it?
Before the Heroes Conference,
I have to recover all my power
to avenge him.
I must do one last thing.
I have to stop Prince Jin
from opening the armory.
I don't have much time.
What do you mean?
Master, it can't be--
Wu Xi, is there any other way?
Look at Zishu.
He is still in high spirits!
Will any treatment work for him now?
Mr. Wen--
For Mr. Wen's injury,
we can find Master Ye.
He is a peerless master.
With the help of his martial arts skills
-and Wu Xi's medical treatment--
-It's too late.
I've taken the elixir from Nanjiang.
We can refine another one.
I'll give my all to find
the rare and valuable ingredients.
Zishu.
There must be a way.
Beiyuan.
It's too late.
Even if the chief
of the Healer Valley is alive…
we've done everything we could.
Now that my days are numbered,
don't bother getting anything
beyond our reach.
The Healer Valley.
And the Yin Yang Book.
Master, there must be a way!
It's life for a life, right?
I can exchange my life for you!
Master, let's look
for the Yin Yang Book now!
Idiot.
With your thoughts for me,
I'm already content.
Be good.