Deng Kuan,
tomorrow is the Heroes Conference.
Father said
he would announce
my marriage to Chengling
at the conference.
I can't disobey my father.
If you wake up one day,
will you blame me?
Who is it?
Gu Xiang, it's you?
What happened to you?
What happened?
Why are your hands so hot?
Hurry up and lie down.
Why were you so careless?
Be careful.
Slowly.
Silly Ah Xiang.
You should be more careful.
At this distance,
I can surely freeze her
with the Unfaithful Nail
that Qianqiao gave me.
It does feel a bit hot.
Don't go.
All right, let me check your pulse.
Gu Xiang.
Don't panic.
I have to freeze her in one move.
Only then will I have the chance
to exchange her for Madam Luo.
Ah Xiang!
They said you are sick
and came to see the doctor.
What's wrong?
How did you get sick all of a sudden?
Xiaolian, is it serious?
Not particularly.
I'll fetch her some medicine.
Ah Xiang.
Go away. Don't touch me.
What are you doing, Cao Weining?
I…
I wasn't doing anything.
I bought you some snacks.
Gosh, he's so clingy.
Why did he have to choose
this moment to barge in?
Ah Xiang, the medicine will be bitter.
Here, have something sweet.
No.
-I don't want it!
-It's delicious.
Try it.
Really, look.
It's delicious.
From now on,
if Mount Tai Sect has any demands,
the Five Lakes Alliance
will do our best to comply,
even if we have to risk our lives.
Very well.
Mount Tai Sect's only request
is for the Five Lakes Alliance
to punish the murderer immediately!
Punish the murderer!
-Yes!
-Yes! Punish the murderer!
-Punish the murderer!
Of course the murderer must be punished.
As long as everyone works together,
we'll catch the demon of Ghost Valley
and cut him into a thousand pieces
to comfort the spirit of Master Ao Laizi.
You are messing around!
He killed my master!
Did you see Chief Shen kill him
with your own eyes?
Or did you see Chief Shen
order his murder with your own eyes?
So you saw neither, did you?
Everyone knows
that Master Ao Laizi was killed
by Ghost Valley.
Many friends and families
of the martial arts world
were murdered by the Ghost Valley.
The reason I arranged
the Heroes Conference here
is to avenge the dead!
But everyone, you must remember,
don't fall for the instigation of others!
Don't fall into chaos!
Or else, you will step
right into the trap of the evildoers!
Elder Huang, what do you think?
You're right.
The most important thing right now
is to crusade against Ghost Valley.
The lost Glazed Armor of Master Ao Laizi
has most likely fallen into the hands
of the murderer from Ghost Valley.
As the saying goes,
evil does not suppress righteousness.
The Five Lakes Alliance
will destroy the Ghost Valley
and return peace
to the martial arts world!
Crusade against Ghost Valley.
Restore peace in the martial arts world!
Gao Chong is quite eloquent.
Crusade against Ghost Valley.
Restore peace in the martial arts world!
Chief Gao.
A few days ago at Renyi Hall,
you promised to explain
the whole story behind the Glazed Armor
to everyone at the Heroes Conference.
Over half of the heroes
who are joining the conference are here.
When are you going to tell us the truth?
Huang He.
Do you want to know the truth
about the Glazed Armor
or do you want to know
the whereabouts of it?
So what if I do?
Don't the present heroes
deserve to know the truth?
That's right!
That is the reason
why the Iron Fist Clan came here today!
The Iron Fist Clan bore the brunt
of the Battle of Mount Qingya.
We suffered heavy casualties.
Chief Gao.
You still owe us an explanation!
Chief Gao!
I lost an eye on Mount Qingya
and my son!
I paid such a high price,
yet I didn't garner the lost secrets
of my Eagle Claw Clan.
Isn't that enough reason to ask
the Five Lakes Alliance for the truth?
-Chief Gao! Explain it to us!
-Explain it to us!
-Hurry up, answer us!
-Answer us!
-Hurry up, explain yourself!
-Explain yourself! Answer us!
-Hurry up, answer us!
-Answer us!
Hey, friend.
It's getting exciting.
Where are you going?
It's you?
Scorpion Sect?
Fine. I shall tell you the truth today.
The Glazed Armor
is in the possession
of the Five Lakes Alliance.
Gao Chong!
The Five Lakes Alliance did everything
only for the peace and tranquility
of the martial arts world.
As the martial arts world suffered heavily
after the Battle of Mount Qingya
and couldn't withstand
an even bigger calamity,
we five brothers divided
the Glazed Armor between us
to secretly protect them
and wait for the right moment.
Chief Gao!
You make it sound so reasonable
as if that was your only choice!
The World's Armory contains secret records
of martial arts from all over the world.
What right does the Alliance have
to keep all heroes in the dark?
Chief Gao!
Every one of us contributed
to defeating Rong Xuan!
How could you keep
the Glazed Armor a secret?
-What rights do you have?
-That's right!
Hand over the Glazed Armor!
We will redistribute it!
-Yes. Hand over the Glazed Armor!
-Hand it over!
-Redistribute it!
-Dear heroes,
-Hand it over!
Please listen to what I have to say.
Years ago, the Glazed Armor
caused great bloodshed
among the martial arts world!
It almost caused a catastrophe.
Right now in Yueyang City,
the fake pieces of Glazed Armor
are being spread by the wicked.
It once again caused countless deaths
and injuries in our world.
This item is a curse
to the martial arts world!
Chief Gao, stop being a hypocrite!
The turmoil within
the martial arts world 20 years ago
and the dispute caused by
the fake Glazed Armor right now
were both planned
by the Five Lakes Alliance, weren't they?
Only someone who is
very familiar with the Glazed Armor
could have made
such real-looking fake ones, right?
What are you trying to say?
Why do you keep slandering Chief Gao?
What is your purpose?
What do you mean?
Did the Five Lakes Alliance
make fake Glazed Armor pieces?
How vicious!
Feng Xiaofeng! You're full of nonsense!
Feng Xiaofeng, shut your mouth!
If you dare spread any more rumors,
I will kill you!
Feng Xiaofeng!
You'll be the first one I kill!
Get down here.
Ah Xu.
Just say come down,
you didn't need to hit me.
Would I dare to disobey you?
Ah Xu, it's good you came.
Drink.
Where did you run off to?
I saw Pretty Arhat just now.
With Scorpion Sect involved in this,
nothing good will come of it.
Things are bad
whether Scorpion Sect is involved or not.
As long as the fire
doesn't reach our Chengling,
what does it matter to us?
I was thinking about how Scorpion Sect
abducted Chengling back then.
There's something strange about it.
Wasn't that for the Glazed Armor?
Ah Xu, don't worry about it.
Just relax and watch the show.
If you ask me,
this big show of Chief Gao
fighting the heroes with his words
will entail a shocking twist.
Let's wait for the highlight.
I saw him build a big building
I saw him feast with his guests
I saw his building collapse
Gao Chong, the Beggar Gangs,
the Ghost Valley, the Window of Heaven,
and the Scorpion Sect.
From beginning to end,
in this fight for the Glazed Armor,
the shadow of the Scorpion Sect
lingered around.
What role does
the Scorpion Sect play in this?
"When you know where to stop,
you have stability.
When you have stability,
you can be tranquil."
Godfather.
Everything you've planned
has been arranged.
It's your turn now.
It's time to end it.
If I'm right,
the Ghost Valley and the Scorpion Sect
must have joined hands.
The incident of the theater corpses
harbors the shadow
of Scorpion's assassin Qin Song.
And the strange Drug Men
driven by evil spirits
at the Zhao family's coffin home
also appeared in large numbers
at the base of the Scorpion Sect.
Lao Wen.
Someone is manipulating the show
behind the scenes.
This person is scheming
with malicious intent.
Is that not good?
It's precisely because there are
so many twists and turns
created by conceited people
that you and I have such a wonderful time
watching it play out.
What you call a wonderful time
entails the blood of innocent people.
Is that what you wish to see?
"Innocent"?
Which of these people
dare call themselves innocent?
But Ah Xu, you are right.
This kind of exciting blood-filled play
of starving animals fighting over food
is exactly what I want to see.
You go on and on about the Ghost Valley.
Stop beating around the bush.
Chief Gao,
please take out the Glazed Armor.
Open the armory!
Every sect will retrieve
their secret records that were lost.
Then we shall fight
against the Ghost Valley.
Wouldn't that be perfect?
-Yes. Open the armory!
-Hand over the Glazed Armor!
-Open the armory!
Everyone!
It's not that I am unwilling
to hand over the Glazed Armor.
Even if I hand it over,
you can't open the gate to the armory.
Enough!
Stop telling us one lie after another.
We've heard enough.
Just hand over the Glazed Armor!
Chief Gao is quite clever and fickle.
There's someone who can testify for me.
Let me see
what tricks you have left.
Put her down!
Whatever it is,
let's take this woman away first!
-Master.
-Go!
Let's go.
How strange.
Why haven't I seen anyone on the way?
Where are the disciples on patrol?
WORSHIP OF LITERATURE
How strange.
Why are all the people here gone?
Where did the doctor and pharmacist go?
Ms. Gao, come with me!
You both should go first, I'll stop them!
As if you could!
Cao Weining!
You old witch! How dare you hurt him!
Watch out!
Cao Weining!
Weining!
Don't die!
I don't want
to owe you my life for nothing!
Right.
Why did I choose you in the first place?
If I knew, I would have found another way
to get inside Yueyang Sect.
Why did you treat me so well?
Silly girl.
Will you waste the life-saving tablet
I gave you this way?
Madam Luo?
LONG XIAO
YOUNG CHIEF OF LONGYUAN CABINET
-Who is this person?
-He is…
Didn't you see the carriage's mechanism?
That must be the legendary
Chief of the Longyuan Cabinet.
He is the only one
who can create
such brilliant mechanics.
In the old days, even the emperor
showed Longyuan Cabinet his respect.
There were rumors 20 years ago
in the martial arts world
that the Longyuan Cabinet
could open the armory.
Open the armory?
The chief of the Longyuan Cabinet
is an old man!
Who is this kid?
I think you all recognize him now.
This is Long Xiao,
the Young Chief of Longyuan Cabinet,
the one and only Master of Mechanics.
I invited him here today
so he can tell everyone
the whole story behind the armory!
Chief Gao is right.
No one knows the story behind the armory
better than my father,
the half-genius Long Que.
-The demon Rong Xuan used clever means
-The half-genius Long Que?
to steal countless secret records
of martial arts from various sects.
He knew he had committed many wrongdoings.
For fear that others will steal from him,
he deceived my father and tricked him
into designing the World's Armory for him.
Young Chief Long.
Gao Chong just said
that even with the Glazed Armor,
the armory cannot be opened.
What the hell is this nonsense?
Chief Gao is right.
The armory is highly complex.
It is indeed impossible to open it safely
with the Glazed Armor alone.
Just tell us,
can you open the armory or not?
-Yes, can you open the armory?
-Can you open it?
-Can you?
-I am sorry to disappoint you.
I did not inherit
the true teachings of my father.
I cannot open the armory.
-Can't open it? Stop wasting our time!
-Why say all this if you can't open it?
However, the mechanics
were designed by my father.
He must know how to open it.
Chief Gao.
I came here in person today
to convey my father's attitude to you
with everyone as my witness.
No matter how much you bribe us
or coerce us,
we will never help you open the armory
and satisfy your selfishness!
Young Chief Long.
The armory is the armory of the people!
No one can claim it for themselves!
-That's right!
-Well said!
The armory is the armory of the people!
-That's right! Well said!
-Well said!
I knew you wanted
to make the armory your own!
-No one can claim it for themselves.
-You all heard it, didn't you?
Gao Chong wants to take
all the treasures in the armory!
How despicable!
Long Xiao!
When has my brother
ever bribed or coerced your father?
Spewing such nonsense
in front of so many people,
do you think I won't kill you?
What the hell are you saying?
Why did you lie to me?
What are you scheming?
Everyone, please don't believe him!
My brother has never harassed
the Longyuan Cabinet!
Gao Chong, haven't you played us enough?
Your witness already told us the truth.
How much longer
do you still want to deny it?
Hand over the Glazed Armor quickly!
-Hand it over! Hand over the Glazed Armor!
-Hand over the Glazed Armor!
-Hurry up and hand over the Glazed Armor!
Gao Chong, I'm sorry!
I couldn't find the Longyuan Cabinet,
no matter how hard I tried.
He found me instead.
He said he would testify for me.
It's all my fault.
I got you into this mess.
Zhao Xuande?
How did such a weak and stupid fool
become one of the five sons
of the Five Lakes Alliance?
Shen Shen was not an idiot then.
Aren't your apprentice’s father
and Lu Taichong not much better?
What a Five Lakes Alliance.
Lao Wen,
why do you hold such extreme views?
Don't let hatred blind your eyes
and affect your judgment
on the Five Lakes Alliance.
Can't you see it with your talent?
Someone deliberately set Gao Chong up.
I know that of course.
That's why I can’t wait
to applaud this guy.
Ah Xu, don't speak.
Let's see how Hero Gao
will manage to turn the tide
and respond to this scheme.
Quiet down!
Hurry up and hand it over!
Everyone, quiet down!
There may be some misunderstanding
between Young Chief Long's father and me.
But I can promise you this,
I do not hold
any selfish motives regarding the armory!
What misunderstanding?
Don't confuse the crowd anymore!
-Hurry up and hand over the Glazed Armor!
-Yes, hand it over!
I swear to Heaven!
Once Ghost Valley is wiped out,
Young Chief Long and I
will distribute the secrets
of the armory among all sects.
If I am insincere,
I shall be cut into thousands of pieces!
If there is no objection,
this matter has thus been decided.
Young Chief Long,
you've had a long journey.
You may go to rest now.
Yes!
Get up.
Get up!
Chengling.
Don't be afraid.
Come.
Mr. Gao.
There's one more thing
I have to tell everyone.
This is Zhang Chengling,
son of my fourth brother, Zhang Yusen.
He is the last descendant
of the Mirror Lake Sect.
I have decided
to betroth my daughter
to him!
In the future, he will be my son-in-law,
and together with my daughter,
they will lead Mirror Lake Sect
and Yueyang Sect.
After that,
I shall become a monk
and walk my path with Buddha.
I will no longer
handle the matters
of the mortal world again.
Gao Chong, don't do this!
I have made my decision.
You don't need to stop me.
You brats!
How dare you force my leader
into becoming a monk!
Are you satisfied now?
Ah Xu.
Gao Chong dragged
your apprentice down with him.
Do you still think I was wrong about him?
No.
Doing this
doesn't benefit him at all.
Ah Xu,
why do you insist on contradicting me?
Gao Chong has always pretended to be
the paragon of virtue.
He must be using Chengling
for some tricks of his!
Gao Chong announced this in public.
There is no return for him.
Chengling has handed over
the Glazed Armor.
What would be his value to Gao Chong?
Everyone, please look.
What is this?
This is the Token of Honor!
-What? What is the Token of Honor?
-What is that?
This is the token
of Mount Changming Sword Immortal.
The Sword Immortal once swore an oath,
if the Ghost Valley harms
the martial arts world,
the holder of this token
can order the world to eradicate
that cancerous evil
in his name!
TOKEN OF HONOR
With this token,
what doubt could you possess?
I'm willing
to return the armory to the people!
I don't need power and might!
I only have one wish!
Which is…
to destroy Ghost Valley,
to avenge the deceased brothers,
and to return peace
to the martial arts world!
Our Five Lakes Alliance
and the Ghost Valley can't mutually exist!
It is imperative to attack Mount Qingya!
What else do you have to say?
Bring the wine.
LONE ARE THE TAIYUE AND DANYANG SECTS
EMPTINESS THE WORLD REMAINS
Those who are willing to work with me
to wipe out Ghost Valley
may have your blood mixed in it.
Whether we were friends or foes,
after drinking this wine,
we will be brothers
who can die for each other.
Before Ghost Valley is destroyed,
this oath will not be broken.
Those who take the oath may stay,
those who wish to leave,
I will not stop you.
Hero Gao.
You really know how to fool people--
Chief Gao.
The Gentle Wind Sword Sect
and Ghost Valley have a blood feud.
Today I, Fan Huaikong,
entrust my life to you.
I shall follow your orders.
Thank you.
Chief Gao!
My Jujing Gang looks forward
to your leadership.
What Chief Gao said was good.
My men and I swear to follow Chief Gao.
Cao Gang will also follow you!
Chief Gao, I didn't listen clearly.
I wish to confirm something with you.
You said that
after Ghost Valley is destroyed,
you'll open the armory
and give the secret records
to each sect, right?
I will not go back on my word.
Good. Chief Gao is an upright man.
There's something I'm curious about.
The Combined Six Cultivation Method
and the Yin Yang Book
belong to no one.
How do you plan on settling that?
That's right!
Who will get
the Combined Six Cultivation Method
and the Yin Yang Book?
Will these unowned items
end up in your pocket?
You people!
You haven't even cleared up
the most critical issue yet
before anxiously pledging your allegiance.
This is Hero Gao's usual trick!
Who says
the Combined Six Cultivation Method
and the Yin Yang Book
don't belong to anyone?
Rong Xuan had his own sect.
Once I open the armory,
we will return
the Combined Six Cultivation Method
to his sect!
As for the Yin Yang Book,
it belongs to the Healer Valley!
It will naturally be returned.
Chief Gao, stop joking around.
They are all dead, how will you return it?
The chief of our Feisha Gang is
a close friend of the Healer Valley.
This Yin Yang Book should be given to us.
You brat!
Stop kidding!
What kind of friendship would that be?
Why don't you say that your leader
is the long-lost grandson
of the chief of the Healer Valley?
That's right!
Dear heroes,
if you ask me,
our Five Tigers Broken Knives Clan
suffered the worst casualties
in the Battle of Mount Qingya.
Speaking of meritorious deeds,
our Peng family should be awarded
the Combined Six Cultivation Method
as compensation.
Is it that glorious
to have a high death count?
You call that meritorious?
You!
Feng Xiaofeng is right.
We should distribute according to merit.
Our Twelve Chain Cove
rendered the most merit.
The strategy of besieging Mount Qingya
was our leader's idea.
You bunch of robbers
are just idiots!
What idea?
You…
Chief, are you guys
from the cove even literate?
Even if you get the book,
can you read it?
He is right.
Everyone,
our Funiu Sect has a long history
and long heritage!
This Yin Yang Book should be ours!
Fight.
Why aren't they fighting?
Lao Wen,
who are you exactly?
Do you want to test
my martial arts skills?
Why not? I'm not afraid! Come on!
Come!
They want to fight but don't dare to.
Cowards.
Lao Wen.
Do you hate the Five Lakes Alliance
or the whole martial arts world?
You're still trying to tell me
you aren't Rong Xuan's son?
Ah Xu.
Whether you believe me or not,
I have never lied to you
from the first day we met.
In that case,
why bother with these ignorant people?
"People"?
How are they even human?
The righteous clans
of the martial arts world?
The difference between them
and the Ghost Valley
is that one is blatantly evil,
while the other is wearing a cover
of benevolence, justice, and morality.
Yet as soon as they see flesh,
they can't wait
to tear off their human skin
and start barking and biting!
Exciting.
How exciting.
All right.
We walk different paths.
I can't persuade you.
Do whatever you want.
Let's go our separate ways.
Everyone's gone. I'm all alone now.
There are only so few people locked up.
What's the point of watching them?
Deng Kuan, you're awake!
That's great!
YUE
I'm Deng Kuan,
the first disciple of the Yueyang Sect.
Rewarding the evil and punishing the good,
such is the impermanence of nature.
It's my turn to appear.
Everything shall be done
according to Master's arrangement.
Ghost Valley came at the right time.
Let's work together.
Let's destroy these ghosts.
Their blood shall be
the sacrifice for our banner!
Chief Gao, no true man is without cruelty.
What a cruel mind you have.
That idiot Long-Tongued Ghost has just
destroyed the Mirror Lake Sect for you.
Now, you turn around and kill him?
Tragicomic Ghost trapped
and killed Danyang Sect's disciples.
Happy Ghost killed Ao Laizi.
Weren't all those instructed by you?
Gao Chong, it really was you!
You bastard!
We agreed on dividing up
the armory's treasure equally
after collecting the Glazed Armor.
After you got three pieces of it,
you immediately turned around
and betrayed us.
You want to destroy Ghost Valley?
Who are you?
Stop slandering me!
"A wise man won't believe rumors."
There's no use in saying more!
Do you think Ghost Valley
will let you do whatever you want?
Kuan'er?
Yueyang Sect's first disciple, Deng Kuan?
Isn't he dead?
-Enough, Master.
-He is still alive.
Kuan'er.
Everyone.
-What's going on?
-I am Deng Kuan,
the first disciple of the Yueyang Sect.
I'm not dead!
I was kept imprisoned by Gao Chong.
It was him
who instructed me
to sneak into the Mirror Lake Sect
and help Long-Tongued Ghost sneak inside
to extinguish the Zhang family.
Kuan'er,
what are you talking about?
Gao Chong!
You abandoned the Five Lakes Alliance!
Such disloyalty!
You murdered your own brothers!
Such disrespect!
You harmed the lost orphan
of the Mirror Lake Sect.
Such inhumanity!
You colluded with Ghost Valley
to disrupt the martial arts world.
Such injustice!
I assisted you in your cruel ways,
I am too ashamed to live!
I shall end my life to maintain justice!
I will die with you!
Kuan'er!
Deng Kuan!
You can't believe him!
This kid is crazy!
Kuan'er.
Who wants me to be dead
by controlling you?
Changing Ghost.
So this is where you're making your move.
Sure enough,
a dog that can bite doesn't bark.
Congratulations, you abandoned the dark
and cast a bright future.