Twenty years ago,
when the evil Rong Xuan
was killed at Mount Qingya
by the Five Lakes Alliance
and other heroes,
he left behind
an armory that could let someone
become invincible overnight.
In order to open the armory,
one must find the Glazed Armor.
Afterward, as a nursery rhyme spread,
many forces began
to secretly search for the Glazed Armor
in order to control the armory.
Prince Jin in the north
is also starting to make his move.
MILITARY GOVERNOR'S MANSION
-What happened?
-Look.
Over there too!
Archers, get ready!
Shoot!
CHANGSHA PREFECTURE CHIEF
NANNING PREFECTURE CHIEF
Prince Jin is secretly training assassins
in the Window of Heaven
to kill the officials of the Court.
He has intentions to revolt.
OFFICER LI
SWORDSMAN IN GREEN
Master, the assassins are here.
Hurry and come with me!
JINGYI RESIDENCE
Who are you?
Hand over the confidential letter.
No way!
ZHOU ZISHU
CHIEF OF THE WINDOW OF HEAVEN
Officer Zhou.
You--
you are from the Window of Heaven?
I'm here to see Officer Li off.
Zhou Zishu.
What you do to others
will be inflicted on you later.
You are helping the bad guys.
The disaster in the future
begins today.
I die without regret.
Officer Li,
I'm sorry.
PRINCESS JING AN
THE MILITARY GOVERNOR'S DAUGHTER
Zhou Zishu.
Princess Jing An.
This is--
The Military Governor
conspired with corrupt officials
in an attempt to revolt.
He has been killed.
It's impossible.
My father gave everything to the country!
It's a pity,
but his actions must be punished.
I came to visit today
to give you a choice.
I want to thank you for bringing back
my junior Qin Jiuxiao's body to me
in chaotic circumstances.
I will never forget your kindness.
Your Highness, you have a high status.
Committing suicide
will save you from humiliation.
Am I supposed to thank you?
You killed my entire family.
And you are letting me die with dignity.
Where did you
bury Jiuxiao?
Four Seasons Manor.
He was laid next to our master.
The flowers blossom in all four seasons,
knowing everything in the world.
QIN JIUXIAO
YOUNG LORD OF FOUR SEASONS MANOR
It's so ugly.
Give it to me.
Give it to me!
You are so annoying.
Jiuxiao.
If you find a girl you like,
I will be happy for you.
He told me
that after he retired from his position,
he would
live with me there.
I--
Everything is taken care of.
Only a few stubborn generals
tried to resist.
I've killed them all.
Chief, Bi Changfeng
made a huge mistake in the mission
to assassinate the Military Governor.
And he wants to leave
the Window of Heaven.
It infuriated Prince Jin.
Prince Jin ordered you
to deal with it in person.
Mr. Bi.
BI CHANGFENG
GUARD OF THE WINDOW OF HEAVEN,
FORMER MEMBER OF FOUR SEASONS MANOR
My lord, you are here.
Mr. Bi.
Four Seasons Manor
only has you and me left.
Eighty-one of our brothers
came to Jin with you.
Now, it's just you and me.
Even Jiuxiao is dead.
What Four Seasons Manor can there be?
Why haven't your wounds healed?
"Shadows without traces.
Entry without exit.
Know everything.
Be everywhere."
Prince Jin requested me
to accomplish these four things
when I created the Window of Heaven.
Once you enter
the Window of Heaven,
you can't leave.
You know that.
I know
that I can't walk out.
Can I not be carried out?
Even if I can only live freely
for one day,
it's still better
than being Prince Jin's dog.
You would rather become a cripple
than continue working for me?
Over the years,
we have been through thick and thin.
I did everything you asked me to.
But our people from Four Seasons Manor
were continuously persecuted.
So I began to question
Prince Jin's intentions.
Now,
I really can't do it anymore.
Not to mention seven nails,
I'm willing to take a thousand cuts
in order to quit!
I know you can't help it,
and I don't blame you.
If our relationship over the years
still matters to you,
please give me the nails.
That's true.
All I can do is send you off
with my own hands.
Don't worry.
I will take care of your family.
Whether it is worry
or relief,
I won't know about it.
My lord, please go ahead.
HAN YING
COMMANDER OF THE WINDOW OF HEAVEN
DUAN PENGJU
DEPUTY CHIEF OF THE WINDOW OF HEAVEN
Mr. Bi
is really a tough man.
No ordinary person
can endure the Nails of Seven Torments.
Mr. Zhang.
What are the Nails of Seven Torments?
Nails of Seven Torments,
death in three years.
Once you've taken the nails,
not only will you lose
your martial arts skills,
but you'll also begin to lose your senses.
In the beginning, you can't speak.
Then you can't hear, smell, or see.
You'll turn into a vegetative state.
This is the only way
that you won't expose
the secrets of the Window of Heaven.
Although you become a cripple,
you'll still remember what happened.
You'll live in torment for three years
before you actually get to die.
Why would anyone want to take it?
Isn't it better to just die?
Well.
Will they let you die so easily?
This is the rule of the Window of Heaven.
They scare you
so that you won't consider leaving.
If one day,
you don't want to stay here anymore,
pretend to accidentally fall
on your blade during the mission.
You'll die quickly without torment.
If you die during a mission,
our lord
will even take care of your family.
No, I dare not.
I will be loyal to the Window of Heaven
and our lord for the rest of my life.
What did you call me?
My lord.
No, Chief.
I'm sorry.
I thought the elders called you that.
The last person
from Four Seasons Manor is gone.
Don't ever say
"my lord" again.
GUIYUN PAVILION
It has been ten years.
Ten years on this path of no return.
I remember each face of the people
from Four Seasons Manor who died.
They're all dead.
Except me.
Why?
Because I don't even deserve to die.
It serves me right to keep living.
Chief of the Window of Heaven.
I am above hundreds and thousands of men
and only below one
and yet I live like this,
boastful of this power,
but I can't even save
a single person I want to protect.
LICHUN PALACE
Why isn't Zishu coming to see me?
Has he still not recovered?
Your Highness.
The traitor has rallied many people
who are skilled at martial arts.
The chief hasn't fought anyone
for a long time.
It must have aggravated
his injuries this time.
He has been resting
in isolation these days.
Ever since he spat blood and fainted
at the news of Qin Jiuxiao's death,
how long have his injuries lasted?
About a year, right?
Your Highness.
Yes.
He became like this just for Qin Jiuxiao.
He won't be of great use.
Tell him to come to see me
as soon as possible.
Yes, Your Highness.
CHONGMING COURT
THE FLOWERS BLOSSOM
IN ALL FOUR SEASONS
"The flowers blossom in all four seasons,
knowing everything in the world."
Eighty-one of our brothers
came to Jin with you.
Now, it's just you and me.
Even Jiuxiao is dead.
What Four Seasons Manor can there be?
In order to leave the Window of Heaven,
I spent a year and a half
putting the Nails of Seven Torments
in my body.
There are actually two ways
to put in the nails.
If you put all seven nails in at once,
the person being tortured
will quickly lose his senses,
and he can only live
for three years as a cripple.
But if you put in one nail
every three months
to let the nail
get into your body gradually
and become part of your body,
although you will still have
three years left,
you will retain half of your martial arts
and your senses
will only disappear in turn slowly
until death.
You just have to endure the extreme pain
that will last for 3 years and 18 months.
Zhou Zishu.
Don't do that.
Jiuxiao?
Why are you crying?
What's there to cry about?
It's what I deserve.
The 81 brothers
from Four Seasons Manor
all died
in my hands.
Our heritage has been terminated.
I couldn't protect any of you.
I even killed
your lover.
I--
After I die,
how can I face you?
I wonder
if you've met Princess Jing An
over at your side.
She must be telling on me, right?
How could there be
such a cruel senior like me?
How could I give
a bottle of poison to my sister-in-law
as a first gift?
The guard Zhou Zishu is here!
Come in.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Please rise.
You really
don't look well.
Take a rest.
You are a pillar of this country.
I need your help to achieve my goals.
I am an ordinary man,
only fit to be your weapon.
Now that Hedong is peaceful,
you need people who know
about governing a country.
I can only fight
and can't be of great help to you.
Zishu,
what do you mean by that?
Zishu!
My spirit is broken.
My wounds are not recovering
and I can't do much now.
I want to return to my hometown.
I've already left the Window of Heaven.
I asked for the punishment
of the Nails of Seven Torments
and allowed it myself.
I've already
put six nails in.
If I put in one more,
I'm afraid that I won't get
to say goodbye to you.
I hope you can consider my hard work,
even without any achievements,
and fulfill my wishes.
Good.
That's very good.
Zhou Zishu.
No wonder you are
the chief of the Window of Heaven.
You are cruel and decisive,
even willing to hurt yourself like this.
Your Highness, please calm down.
If you don't want to live,
I can let you die!
Why go through all this trouble?
You saved my life.
If you allow it,
I can then drag this crippled body along
for two more years.
If you don't,
then take my life.
You all lied to me!
Yunxing left.
Beiyuan.
Beiyuan is gone too.
I'm really alone in this world now.
Zishu,
you were lying to me, right?
If I spare you,
are you willing to help me
achieve my goals?
Please give me
the last nail.
You would rather be a cripple
than be my trusted official?
Fine!
I understand your intention.
Nails of Seven Torments,
death in three years.
Zhou Zishu,
you have to stay alive.
Three years.
Within three years,
I will definitely go there
and ascend the throne!
I'm going to show you
that I am the chosen one,
and I will be successful no matter what!
I will try my best.
Pengju.
Do as he says.
From now on,
you are the chief of the Window of Heaven.
Chief.
His Highness means…
congratulations to us both.
Both of us got what we wanted today.
"The rivers flow.
The window leads to the underworld.
Rumors endanger justice.
The clouds hide the sun."
You just wait, Zhou Zishu.
I will let you go for now.
HANGED GHOST
ONE OF THE TEN DEVILS OF GHOST VALLEY
GHOST VALLEY
That treacherous Hanged Ghost
suddenly jumped off the cliff with a vine.
We weren't quick enough
to stop him.
Useless!
We need to see him if he is alive
and his body if he is dead.
Where is his body?
There wasn't a body under the cliff.
CHANGING GHOST
ONE OF THE TEN DEVILS OF GHOST VALLEY
Good.
Very good!
It's my fault.
Chief, please forgive me!
Please spare my life!
Chief, please forgive us. Kneel down.
-Chief, please forgive us.
Hanged Ghost stole my Glazed Armor!
Glazed--
-Glazed Armor?
-Order all 3,000 ghosts in Mount Qingya.
From now on,
I want everyone to go out
and kill the traitor.
Whoever can get
the Glazed Armor back for me
will be the head of Ten Devils!
-Kill Hanged Ghost!
-Retrieve the Glazed Armor!
THREE MONTHS LATER, YUE
FUDING PAVILION
Whoever has been a beggar for three years
won't want to exchange his place
even with an emperor.
Master, look!
That beggar is pretty optimistic.
WEN KEXING
GU XIANG
He doesn't even have a bowl before him.
He didn't get any money
and is still happy.
Maybe he is a fool.
He is enjoying the sunshine.
Enjoying the sunshine?
What's there to enjoy in the sun?
He is already so skinny.
If he keeps sitting in the sun,
he will really dry up!
Master,
don't look down on me
for not having as much experience in life.
He looks like
he hasn't had a full meal for three years.
He may die anytime.
Am I wrong?
I bet that he is definitely a beggar.
What's the stake?
If I win, you have to play cards
with me for three days!
What if you lose?
Then I'll play cards with you
for three days.
Little girl,
are you trying to trick me?
ZHANG CHENGLING
Wu, give him some money.
Master, look! Someone gave him money!
I won.
Why doesn't he want the money?
Young Master, look at him.
He didn't even thank us.
No wonder he is a beggar.
Who told you to throw it on him?
FUDING PAVILION
Hey, you!
I'll treat you to a meal, all right?
Kind lady.
How about
you treat me to a drink?
Master, he called me a kind lady.
A kind lady!
Let's bet.
All right.
I'll treat you to a drink.
Here.
Are you not afraid that it's poisoned
and you'll spill your guts
after drinking it?
This is good wine.
It's worth it even if I die from poison.
A toast to you!
Thank you, kind lady.
"Kind lady."
Here.
Miss, your martial arts are really good!
Let me ask you.
Why don't you want their money?
You want wine but not money.
You are so picky for a beggar.
Who says I'm a beggar?
I'm just here to enjoy the sunshine.
You tricked me into giving you wine?
Give it back!
I can't give you back the wine,
but you can have my life.
Do you think
I don't dare to take your life?
Miss, how could you bully a sick person
with your good martial arts?
Martial artists
should help the poor and the weak.
-You should be righteous and just!
-Little idiot.
Are you lecturing me right now?
Be careful. I might cut off your tongue!
-She has such good skills.
-Kind lady.
You look sweet,
but you're fierce.
I don't believe you!