Cowardly bastard.
Shut up before I expose the truth.
I'm thinking of that too. How could I waste this horrible school.
It would be really fun if the others found out what you did.
Shut up you murdering bastard.
Do you want to die, you punk?
Are you crazy?
Calm down!
What is this?
Rascals!
Song Dae Hwi.
And Hyeon Tae Woon.
You two performed serious violence against each other
in a classroom setting.
Do you admit?
Yes.
Yeah.
T-teacher... I only tried to stop them, you see...
Ra Eun Ho, even though you knew about them you didn't report it to the school.
This is a sin!
What?
Teacher, Ra Eun Ho really didn't do anything wrong.
Right! I just ran in there to stop them.
Do I need to talk to you about sinning again?
This is a serious misdeed within the school!
I will give you guys a special opportunity.
I will open up the school committee for violence or
you guys can receive punishment.
Song Dae Hwi. Hyeon Tae Woon. Do 50 laps in the gym.
And Ra Eun Ho, 20 laps.
You will be doing this for 10 days starting today.
Go!
You two were the ones fighting, why should I run-
I'm sorry. But no matter how much we tell him,
he won't listen.
You go and talk to him.
- Shut up.
- Come on.
You could just use your dad to get out of this again.
This bastard just wants to die. Don't talk rashly, you jerk.
Quiet.
That day, those two acted very strange.
They were indeed not nice to each other, but their running
seemed like they were bothering themselves.
The two of their edged stories
the fact that it was also hurting me,
I didn't know back then.
School 2017 - To meet on the way
Amazing!
Korea University
Episode 4
Teacher, is it real? It's not a prank, is it?
I didn't know you were this good.
[Korea University Webtoon Media Final Examination Information]
Omg! Omg!
To think that you can get early admission privileges by placing in the top 3.
Transcripts: 25%, Student Records: 35%
Eun Ho, it seems like you can go to Korea University.
Well about that...
There is a problem.
Teacher, please help me.
If she gets in the top three of the competition, she can attend Korea University.
The reference ratio of portfolio and school records is quite high.
Please, please remove the demerits.
I really need to go to Korea University.
So, catch that guy.
You said that you will.
That didn't turn out the way I wanted either...
If you don't catch X or whatever his name is,
don't dream about removing the demerits.
Eun Ho. There's still ten days before the deadline.
Let's think about another way.
How?
Huh?
I mean, I don't think you guys are on good terms either.
R-right.
Anyway, let's think about it.
But what about your portfolio? You said that was important as well.
Portfolio?
I should talk about that.
I must be crazy. Teacher, I'll go get it.
Did it dissapear? My sketchbook?
No way, Teacher! I'm in big trouble if I don't have that.
Come find it when you have graduated.
It's not me.
You must have come to get it because it wasn't you.
It looks like he took off with it when he broke into the teacher's office.
X or whatever his name is.
That bastard, seriously...
Ra Eun Ho.
Don't forget to go to the gym with Hyeon Tae Woon and Song Dae Hwi.
I will kill Hyeon Tae Woon and Song Dae Hwi.
My life is so twisted because of some two guys.
I keep getting punished. It's annoying.
Hey. Think of it in a good way. Let's use this as our opportunity.
Find out who the real X is as you stick close to them.
Starting from today and 10 days onward, you will clean every nook and cranny of the school.
The punishment is your responsibility.
Once you're done, the three of you guys will be reviewed.
If any of you run away, it's nullity.
Can't I just get my punishment and be done with it.
Are you crazy?
The punishment is a little harsh...
You could just tattle to your father and get out of this situation.
If you just want to continue living off your father,
you are free to do so.
What are we going to do? What am I doing in this situation, all because of you two?
I'm sorry. Don't do any cleaning, I'll do it.
You shouldn't have tagged along, Dummy.
What?
Cleaning...
Then,
you guys should help me.
Let's find X together.
- Are you crazy?
- X?
You guys heard it right? I got to the final acceptance process for Korea University.
but because of my school records that's all out of my reach.
Also, that X bastard has my sketchbook.
What about that childish sketchbook...
Childish? It contains all the different ideas.
Why would X do that...
It's probably childish rebellion,
since they don't have the guts for their age.
Rebellion?
Maybe they have a childish inferiority complex
In my opinion
he's a psychopath.
X blends in with other students, and act normally.
But, X stores the corpses in school.
What does that have to do with X's doings?
To divert attention
Isn't a psychopath a little...
Oh really? It's not to that bad, right?
Yeah, right.
What? Are your feelings hurt? Why?
My feelings aren't hurt. Does that even make any sense, a psychopath?
Why not! He could really be as bad as I imagined!
Wow, your imagination's really running wild. Seriously.
That's why you should help me catch X.
You understand how desperate I am to be asking you?
Will you go out with me?
- What?
- You don't want to?
Then how about a kiss?
Are you...crazy?
I probably am.
That's what my heart is like, unbelievable and flustered.
Why do I have to suddenly find X with you?
Don't you dare leave!
Don't you know we have joint liability? You will die.
What am I supposed to clean with then? My hands? I need a broom!
Why do you throw?
- What are you doing?
- Ah, I'm sorry!
Come here!
I told you to wait outside!
What is that there?
That's just a storage room.
A storage room?
Do you have the key for it?
I'm not sure. It hasn't been used in a long time and is supposed to be demolished soon.
I think it got thrown somewhere in the study hall.
Try to find the keys for this.
Are you an elementary student? Why did you guys even fight...
Hey.
- What are you doing?
- Wait a second.
You're bleeding.
Blood?
When did that happen?
You were dilly dallying everywhere...
You scraped it badly.
I did...
Here.
It's not like you to carry around this stuff.
My friend bought it for me because motorcycle accidents can get you badly hurt-
A friend? Your friend rides a motorcycle too?
I'm going.
They were best friends.
- Best friends?
- Yeah, they were in the same class together in 1st grade.
They were totally best friends but after a big fight they separated.
Why'd they fight?
The rumor said that it was because of Im Joon Gi.
Im Joon Gi?
What? What is it?
That, that,
That Im Joon Gi guy died.
It was during that bus accident you experienced.
431?
The three of them were best friends but- was it the day of the funeral procession? They got in a huge fight that day.
Yeah so why'd they fight?
This was a rumor too,
but that accident was apparently caused by Hyeon Tae Woon.
But Hyun Tae Woon's father pushed it all onto Im Joon Gi.
Really?
Tragic Bus Accident's Main Culprit Is Dropout Student
One Year Ago
F-Father...
Joon Gi and I got into an accident...
What? Speak properly, what are you saying?
Joon Gi...
He...
Where are you? Where?!
Joon Gi. Let go of me... Im Joon Gi!
Tae Woon! Hyeon Tae Woon!
I said let go of me, Tae Woon, Tae Woon.
Hyeon Tae Woon!
Why do you keep looking at a picture of someone dead?
That family must have gotten a lot of compensation money.
I mean, I heard that the kid that was riding with him and survived was the chairman's son?
Every mention of him was taken out of the papers.
Since they ended up putting all the blame on the child who died.
They must have gotten a ton of money for it, huh?
Leave, I have to study.
What are you getting all prickly for?
You study every day!
- Do you really have to go this far?
- If I don't I'll be trampled on.
Because if you don't have power,
you take the blame for everything.
Take it easy, okay?
Teenage Dropout Takes Lives Of Citizens Through Reckless Speeding
There really is,
no mention of Hyeon Tae Woon.
Even though he's a rude jerk,
he didn't strike me as a bad guy.
What he didn't? He slipped out with money and his background.
Then what about what X did? Why would a bad guy like him do those things?
Just a joke for killing time. Anyway his father will protect all.
You can just use your father to get out of this, too.
This punk wants to die. Don't blabber anything, you jerk.
Ugh, having to clean cause of these jerks
That's right,
That guy and justice?
Nope. No way.
By the way, the upcoming demerits presentation event,
When was the presentation?
I think there's a week left.
Anyway, I want X to appear and flip the principal off. Real big.
-Big flip off?
- Secretly take a picture of the bad deeds he does..
and give him demerits just like us.
Don't you think it would be super funny if we made this into a video?
Oh yeah, it would be funny.
Song Dae Hwi is X?
I doubt the egotistical Hyeon Tae Woon would fight for justice.
If that's how you're going to look at it, Song Dae Hwi's not much different.
Song Dae Hwi does so much for all the kids though
Was it the funeral procession day? Im Joon Gi's coffin was brought to the school.
But Song Dae Hwi was taking a test and showed up for not one bit of it.
Really?
Yeah. Hyeon Tae Woon totally blew a gasket over it.
It's not even like it was someone else. His best friend was the one who died.
Could you take a test after that? Honestly? I think he's a bit like a monster.
What good did Tae Woon do to be able to cause such a fuss?
Something definitely went on between the two, but no one but them knows what it is.
But if Song Dae Hwi is X,
why would he do that? He who already doesn't have enough time to study.
To relieve stress? It must be stressful being number 1 in the school.
Hey, since we're talking about this, doesn't he kind of seem like a pervert?
I guess he wouldn't really fight for justice either.
Can we believe Song Dae Hwi?
We're desperate
We have to fix it quickly.
Ra Eun Ho - 55
If it goes on like this, I'm going to end up with 100 points.
I think this reward and punishment system won't go away until you catch X.
Class 2-1's current demerit points
Everyone, be quiet!
Kids, keep quiet.
Kids!
Keep quiet.
Ki- Demerits for everyone!
If I do that,
will you quiet down?
I'd like it if our class didn't report demerits from now on.
Really, Teacher?
Secretly accusing your friends...I'd like it if at least our class didn't do that.
How can we believe this, Teacher?
I believe in you.
So from now, for every report that someone from our class submits,
I'm going to run laps around the field.
I'm going to do it until not even one report is submitted.
Ehh that's nonsense.
The choice of whether or not to do this to your friends
is up to you all now.
Teacher!
Yes, Eun Ho.
Thank you.
Are you really going to run?
If you all don't report anything, it's possible I won't have to.
All the other classes are going to continue doing it. If only our class doesn't do it, what's going to happen?
Adults are pretty awful for making this kind of problem.
If you keep being like this...
Is finding X going well?
I'm close to getting him but... not yet.
Will you report your friend?
Teacher, if I end up not being able to go to college because of him,
the rest of my life is going to be ruined.
If I don't go to university, I won't even be able to find a proper job. So...
So I didn't do wrong...
Right?
Come get it when you graduate
Yes, the final.
My Eun Ho only has her final acceptance process left for Korea University.
What do you mean a prestigious college? Okay, I'll treat you.
"Let's make up." Doesn't it mean that?
They know you're looking for their contacts, so they're scared.
Makes sense. Those two are the only ones who know how badly I needed this.
I'm sure X is one of those two though.
But, you know, both of them are kind of disappointing.
One of them pushed his wrongdoings onto his dead friend
And the other had his nose stuck in an exam during his friend's final sendoff.
Why would such selfish people do what X did then?
He did a big harm to the school, and rescued me with the drone.
I thought it was for justice...
"Justice", my foot! One of them was relieving stress from studying and the other was playing a joke!
Where? Where are you going?
You need to make a delivery!
Mother, I have a very important meeting with friends today.
I have a business too.
You're kidding. Have you been drinking with those unemployed punks again?
Mom..again, you're so precise. I'll be back!
Hey, hey! He never comes to his senses.
I'll be back.
Where are yo going?!
Ugh those punks. My orders are all delayed. I'm going crazy!
Is there a delivery to be made?
Where is it?
Really. I really mean it. Starting next month,
I'll pay the rent on time without missing a single one!
You actually have the nerve to say that?
Would I fall for this lies again?
Pay what you owe in full and vacate this shop by the end of the month!
Please wait! If you act like this all of a sudden- where are you going? Please overlook it just this once! Please just onc-
Mom!
What are you doing?!
Oh my, student. This isn't a time for a student to be raising his voice.
Why did you come out instead of studying? Hurry in and study.
Is that what's important right now?!
You must have been really shocked.
It's okay. Even my dad misused his house collateral.
It's always chaotic. They all live like this.
- Thank you.
- What for?
I mean, you even brought up your dad in order to make me feel better.
But still, you study well.
You're set for life. What do you have to worry about?
I wish that were true. Not having to worry about money just by studying.
I'm sure it'll work out that way. You're the most hard-working person I know, after all.
Hard-working...
Can you really break out of something just by working hard?
Even if you sprint like your life depends on it,
is it possible catch up to someone when your starting line is so different?
Total number of reports 62
Sixty-two demerits ...
I will be back.
Will he really run?
Ah. I told him not to do it...
He really will?
62 points
How is he going to run that much?
Hey, guys. The teacher is running so fast..
How many laps has he done so far...
36 and a half laps.
Isn't he going to pass out if he continues?
I doubt it. He'll stop soon.
Let's go out there fast.
Come out?
Why are they like this suddenly?
This wouldn't disappear by doing that.
Hey Eul..
You're not going to go out? Your boyfriend is over there.
I just feel like sitting back and watching for once.
- He looks like he'll collapse.
- He really does.
How many laps now?
He really did a lot.
He may be utterly exhausted.
He is already exhausted.
He really needs to stop.
Wow he finished
It's over.
Should he go to the hospital?
Please stop.
Teacher...
Ah, what to do?!
Oh my!
I think he's dehydrated.
Should we call a doctor?
Stupid
Ah, Teacher...
Why did you purposely suffer in this hot day?
Right?
But it's surprisingly not hard at all, Teacher.
What did you say, you punk?!
Say it again. What are you going to do? Turn youself in?
Is that lousy kid that great?!
"Lousy kid"?
Because you keep acting like this, Father, I can't even honor Joon Gi's memory.
I feel like even just the act of thinking of him is a crime. I feel so sorry towards him-
I did all I could!
I protected my son, and I took moral responsibility too. I paid enough compensation.
If you're going to live under me and my methods, then live as I tell you to.
Your methods? You mean buying off everyone?!
This punk...
Hyeon Tae Woon!
Hey! You said you found an awesome restaurant. Let's head over there fast!
I'm starving.
Hello!
Are you okay?
Would I be okay? I got beaten up by my dad.
Let's just tell your mom.
Mom's rank is way higher than dad's..
Are you joking about me not having a mom?
You don't have one... I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
If you just pity me so directly like this, I feel so miserable.
No, no. What is the pitiful?! You have huge money and you have huge rudeness as well.
Ru-
Get on.
- Huh? Where?
You said "let's go". I know a great place to eat.
Our summer days are passing by
Whatever you do, you're full of fighting spirit.
This is seriously really good. Can I have another?
Of course. Since you're paying for it.
Hey, what do you...
The dazzling blue sky
Eww, gross.
Trees dancing outside of the window
You said you were buying!
- When did I do that?!
I said it'd be delicious.
"If that's unfair, I'll pay for it." You can pay for it thinking that it's me.
I hope every wish come true
I saved you from troubles.
Bully...
Bully? I was going to buy you a good hand-made ice cream..
Hey...
Who do you think I am?
Do you think I will just fall for a hand-made ice cream... Where is it?
Let's go. Yay!
Do you want to eat ice cream with me that much?
Lose weight.
What?! What...
Over there. Did you fix it?
What?
That watch from earlier... It's broken, isn't it!
Just buy a new one.
It will be more expensive to get it repaired.
Just do it. He has a lot of money.
I'm not sure if we have the right faceplate for it.
Wait a minute.
I've seen this before.
You saw it at the class room.
On the bus...
Bus?
Hey Geum Do High School! Geum Do High School!
Wake up! Geum Do High Schooler! Geum Do High Schooler!
Come to your senses! Geum Do High Schooler.
You were saved by Joon Gi, huh?
Then when he saved me he...
Song Dae Hwi
Tae Woon! Are you okay?
I'm fine but the bus...
Please help me!
Are you alright?
Help!
Are you okay?
Geum Do High Schooler! GeumDo High Schooler!
Try to wake up!
Mister! Please wake up!
Joon Gi! Hey! Hey, Joon Gi!!
You nee- you need to get out!
Come back out!
HEY! Get the hell outta there, you bastard!
Oh no, what do we do...
No! Joon Gi! Joon Gi! Come out!
You have to come out!
Please!
Please come out! Please, please come out!
Are you okay?
My friend is in there
You have to come out, Joon Gi!
You bastard!
It must've been painful. Very.
You, too. It must have been painful.
Class 2-1 number of reports total: 48
If he continues, he will faint.
Still a lot left.
That's so much running
Teach! Hang in there!
Teach, Fighting!
Fighting!
Fighting! Fighting!
You're almost done!
Fighting! Fighting! Fighting!
Fighting!
What to do...
Ah, I feel so bad...
- Teacher, no matter how wrong it seems,
- Hang in there, Teacher!
- no matter how much I don't like it,
- Fighting, Teacher!
- turning in the culprit is the right thing to do, right?
- Fighting!
Don't faint!
I have to live too, don't I?
Eun Bbal! Get your head on straight! Is this any time to worry about Tae Woon and Dae Hwi?
I only have two days left until the turn-in date.
No matter which of them is X,
I feel like they both have their own legitimate reasons for it.
Have you forgotten what you've been put through already?
Because of those punks, your mother even had to beg on her knees!
You're right...
Korea University
Being in the 6th level in school,
it's a level where you even deserve to be treated like a human.
Drop out?!
Please let go of it this time. Please!
Why did you have to go into the Teacher's office and make this complicated mess just to annoy everyone!
You must have a death wish.
- It wasn't me!
- I oughtta!
Demerits.
Because of demerits or whatever, we're suffering..
Apparently it's all because of you! So you can catch that X or whoever he is.
You perfectly set a trap, right?
There will be no excuses whatsoever. Please watch, they'll perfectly get caught.
The student X .. will definitely show up on a day like this.
It's not even chasing some Bridal Mask.
What was that?
It was nothing. Let's go in.
This rodent-like rascal. Just wait till I catch you.
Let's go.
I should just stomp on him to death.
Starting now,
the students with the most demerit points, when you hear your name called,
please move to the edification chairs.
The one with the most demerits, 62 points: Ra Eun Ho. 51 points: Hwang Myeong Geun
Ra Eun Ho!
Come out immediately! What are you doing?!
Hwang Myeong Geun
Total of..
forty-five demerits..Park Jeong Hye.
Forty-three demerits...Bang Mi So. Forty-one demerits ... Chae Yeong Jeong.
Forty-one demerits.. Yeo Seung Won.
Forty demerits.. Jeon Ho Seong.
Thirty-nine demerits.. Jeon Sang Gil.
Thirty-nine demerits.. Han Na Rae.
Thirty-eight demerits, Do Si Ho
He took the bait!
Guards
Let's instroduce the one with the most demerits and Guemdo High School.
Leaving leftovers
10 demerits
Oh!
Do not laugh!
Apologize! Don't laugh!
Dress Code Violation
10 demerits
I told you not to laugh!
Unauthorized speculation: 15 demerits
fly-tipping 15 points
Total demerits: 85 points
Principal
You're expelled!
What is this..
You're laughing?
You're laughing?!
Hahahahaha Funny, isn't it?
But, how are you any different?
What is different?
You abandoned friendship
To all images of friends,
Are you happy, now that you've gotten merits?
He's over here!
Catch him.
You need to catch him! Catch him immediately! Hurry!
Why aren't you running?
Stop right there!
He went this way!
Catch him!
Hey!
I'm sure he went this way. You didn't see him?
I was debating.
If I just lift this fabric up, I will be able to prove my innocence and reveal who X is...
It was the perfect timing.
Come this way.
If you ask why I didn't catch X, which I very much looked forward to,
Do it, do it!
Could it be because in the process of finding X,
I gained friends first?
It's not a bold hero who bravely put the school through hell
Shut up, you murdering bastard!
They're just 18-year-old friends with pain and hurt.
Eighteen. An age where you can become friends with anyone.
Could we possibly gain true friends in this school?
What are you doing?
What is this?
What's that teacher doing?
Why's he going up there?
What's going on?
What is he doing?
Are they newly putting that up?
What?
Is the reward and punishment system over?
I think it's over!
Wow, that's awesome!
Have you lost your mind?!
You call yourself a teacher? All you do is do what the kids want.
Put the demerit chart back up immediately.
E-excuse me, sir
Put it up already! Don't do anything useless.
I can't do that.
What?!
I can't put that demerit chart back up.
Are you crazy?
Yes. I'm fine with being called crazy.
I can't teach the kids to rat out one another so they can be rewarded.
Above all, I'm a teacher.
Nice catch.
I will write an official apology if you tell me to do so.
Gosh, school's environment is so messed up!
The students and teachers are the same! Write an official apology immediately!
You're so foolish.
Board of Education
You lost a good opportunity.
I'll be chosen for this competition.
This time, I'm first. I have a feeling.
You're such a positive person, really.
I wonder who X really was.
Song Dae Hwi
Really?! Song Dae-
Why? Why is Song Dae Hwi X?
He did what I asked him to do.
But during the reward and punishment system announcement this time,
I really wish X would appear and put the principal through sh*t.
Sh*t?
Film the principal doing bad things, and then we can give the demerits.
Wouldn't something like this be so funny to make as a film?
Yeah. It sounds like fun.
Huh?
He's here!
Hurry! Hurry! It's X! X is here!
Hey. Hey!
I knew it! Song Dae Hwi is X!
Do you think I won't know just because you aren't wearing your hood?
You're really getting on my nerves.
♫  Believing now in this moment I ♫
♫  Sometimes feel insecure and uneasy but ♫