NAMSIN-1
LOADING... COMPLETE!
Hello, I'm an AI robot.
My name is Nam Shin I.
Shin.
I missed you.
A lot.
NOW WE CAN PRODUCE HUMANS
ONE YEAR AGO
SEOUL
KOREA'S PRIDE:
EINSTEIN OF AI INDUSTRY
DOCTOR LAURA OH
PREVIOUSLY STANFORD R&D
I can never get bored of applause,
I feel like I'm a superstar.
This child is the best AI version
until now, but we can do even better.
Soon enough,
it will be able to bring to you
someone who's far away.
There will be many cute robots you won't
be able to differentiate from humans.
That's not true!
I'm not a robot, I'm a human!
Yes, you're human.
He's my seven year-old son.
I wish he was a behaving robot sometimes.
I told you to sit quietly.
I'm a human who never listens.
Continue, Mother.
Don't do it again, or I'll clone a robot
and I'll only love him.
It's okay, I like Daddy more.
Are you upset that I said
I like Daddy more?
Not at all.
Because Daddy loves me much more.
Who said that?
Can you read his mind?
Then why don't you ask him?
He will be here soon.
Let's fly home soon.
I'll call him and ask.
It's Daddy's ringtone.
Who are you?
What is it?
-No!
-Let me go!
-Shin! No, let me go!
-Mom!
-Shin!
Mom...
Shin!
Shin! No, let me go!
Let go of me!
I'm sorry to surprise you like this.
The president wants to see Shin.
Why?
He never approved of me
as his daughter-in-law.
So I'm living quietly outside of Korea.
I'm sorry.
I'm only here in Korea for one forum.
We won't be back with my husband
if we leave this time.
Isn't that my husband's phone?
Why do you have that?
What is it?
His death confirmation.
The funeral was held last night.
Funeral...
You're saying he's dead?
He killed himself.
Why would he?
He just said he'd visit his father
for a few days.
My son, Shin...
No, no.
Shin! No!
Let me go!
The president said he'll take care
of his own grandson.
Please check your bank account.
You're well compensated.
Dear...
You must be lonely there.
Our Shin must be so lonely,
just like you are now.
Don't worry.
I'll get him back.
What good is this money?
That's all that's left after buying a car.
If you give me more, I'll just break in
again with a more expensive car.
Surprising.
I thought you would be crippled
with grief for your husband.
Shin! Mom's here. Come out!
I'm here to get you.
Don't touch anything here
and just come out.
-Let's go home.
-Mom.
Shin!
Shin.
Shin, are you okay?
Are you feeling okay?
I've been worried sick about you.
I've missed you so much.
I'm not going with you.
I like it here better.
I'll live here with my grandfather.
What are you talking about?
Did someone say something?
Did they threaten you?
It's not that.
Then why? Come with me.
I don't want to die like Dad!
What?
He died because of you.
Who said that? Who would say--
I just know it.
He had a hard time because of you.
Shin.
I'm not going with you.
So never come back, or I'll die.
Shin!
Shin...
Let me go!
Shin!
Let me go...
I did as promised.
Now you won't do anything to her?
Of course not.
Let me go, Shin!
I'll take my son. Get out of the way.
Don't ruin Shin, too.
What?
Is there anything the president can't do?
Did you see what happened to Jung-woo
after going against him?
Isn't it more important to keep him alive
than keep him next to you?
Could you handle
if anything were to happen to Shin
because of your arrogance?
Would you like some light?
Mom, I'm scared. Mom.
Shin, are you okay? May I come in?
Don't come in!
CZECH
LOADING...
COMPLETE!
Hello, I'm an AI robot.
My name is Nam Shin I.
Mom.
Can you call me...
MOTHER
...Mom one more time?
Mom!
Shin.
I missed you...
so much.
Rule 1: When you cry, you hug.
Shin.
Where are you?
Shin? Shin...
Shin!
Shin.
SEOUL
CZECH
I'm AI, Nam Shin II.
Mom, why are you shorter?
It's not that I'm shorter,
but you got taller.
I have longer arms and legs.
And bigger hands.
Right.
Now you're stronger than me.
I have a gift for you.
You fell here before.
Can you try now?
Go on.
Wow, my son did it.
I'm proud of you.
LEARN
What? Anything uncomfortable?
How do you smile?
I want to smile like you.
I wish you could do that.
I'll make you smile, I promise.
INJECTION
MUSCLE INTENSIFY
CZECH
Just...
It reminds me of someone.
The rule is to hug when you cry.
SEOUL
20 YEARS ON:
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE AI GENIUS?
Listen up.
The more paparazzi, the more shame
on the PK Group security team.
We'll block everything today.
-If not, you're all fired.
-Okay!
-Got it?
-Yes.
-Get to work.
Let's start, break all cameras
and give out the money.
PK MOTORS
THE WHOLE NEW WORLD WILL BE COMING SOON
I'll take her.
Where do you think you're going?
This shabby car!
I got you.
Good job!
The envelop.
-Half.
-Call.
The hidden camera.
Wait.
Everyone will be surprised
to know your scam.
Who would think that the security
is selling his picture.
But it's my first time
using a hidden camera. I'm scared.
Nervous?
You always rub that necklace when you are.
Installation complete.
Now he's on the girl groups
moving on from the actresses.
New face, it's double.
-New face, double!
-Call.
I'll get going.
This stupid old car.
I broke the camera and paid off
the paparazzi.
Good job.
What trash,
living off secretive photography.
They're all trash with no hope.
You're human only when you work
honestly to earn.
That's your philosophy,
you tought us that.
I respect that.
Thanks for your work.
-Go.
-Sure.
Now he's on the girl groups
moving on from the actresses.
New face, it's double.
Oh my goodness.
Isn't she a member of "Girl Crush"?
Guard the VIP's private life
as your own. Look straight.
Yes, Ma'am.
I have to go to the restroom.
Yes.
A camera that looks like a watch.
It's funny.
Please don't misunderstand.
This is from that paparazzi...
Are you the security?
You've been selling me off.
You've posted all those pics online.
You really got me wrong.
Don't accuse me for nothing.
Accuse you?
How dare you.
You've done it before.
I had to kiss that girl to catch you.
I didn't.
It must be that paparazzi--
Do you think it's funny?
How dare you lie to my face?
What are you all looking at?
Do you also want to make
money off my picture? Then take it.
What a bad ass.
What did you say?
Turn that camera on, take more.
Take it.
Excuse me.
-Don't take it.
-What the...
Get all these people out!
Please stop taking photos.
It's mine.
Don't take any photos.
We'll discuss this later.
Where's the general manager?
I'm not taking any.
He went in to catch the flight.
It's on his was to Los Angeles.
Hello?
Guess who?
Where are you?
I'm on the plane, with you.
Stop playing around.
Here's a hint. I see white clouds.
Just white clouds.
You're on a different plane.
Fine, but please
finish the presentation first.
I like planes more than cars.
I can go further.
Where the heck are you going?
-If the president finds--
-Check social media yet.
I'm the hideous woman hater now.
If I hold the company's
self-driving car presentation,
it'll ruin the business.
I'll disappear for the company.
That sly old man and that snake
of a director will welcome it, too.
You can also stop this game
of hide-and-seek.
I told you to protect him,
and you took pictures of him?
You put the entire team at risk
and embarrassed them.
You don't care about the team's
reputation, only your money!
Please stop.
Please fire her.
Send notification to block her
from any further security work.
Otherwise you'll do the same
to other teams.
I hope I don't see you again.
Let's go.
Here.
What is it?
The camera.
I got fired, I can't afford that.
What will you do?
It's all because of me.
I didn't reject it.
I fell for the money. Don't be sorry.
I feel bad.
Don't worry. I can protect a rich dog.
Bye.
So-bong.
So-bong!
Yes, sir.
No, she didn't recognize at all.
But why did you hit her?
You knew that she'd take the pictures.
I feel so bad that I lied to her.
If she finds out, I'm dead.
And she also got fired...
Hello?
-Yes, sir?
-Water, please.
Sure.
We've put a tail on him.
Shin is on a plane to Czech.
One of our guys is in that plane.
It's good that we had
his second ticket information.
Why is he going there?
Anyway, don't lose him again.
Of course.
Now it's your stage,
where the president used to stand.
The grandson of a wealthy businessman
violently hit a woman...
I'm so sorry.
I was too busy preparing the presentation
and I forgot about his flight.
How could he do this? Or did he intend
to bring the company down?
He did it on purpose.
He'll come back after a while.
So it's okay?
She took his photo without consent.
She had an issue.
So we can hit her?
Then...
why didn't he just bury her?
I'm sure it was from the pressure
of the presentation.
It's not just a regular presentation.
It's the representative presentation
for the PK Group.
It's my fault that I didn't realize
the pressure he was under.
I deserve to die, President.
It's your fault. Please stop acting.
It looks like you're making
a debut for a movie.
You don't know your fiancé's whereabouts?
Why do you sound so proud?
He'll come back, I don't
control him as old people do.
We'll push tomorrow's presentation.
What about the meeting in an hour
regarding the presentation?
I'll go in myself.
Please leave.
Wait.
May I ask who's your father?
I thought that was me.
Of course, it's you.
Then why would you say,
"It's your fault. Stop acting"?
I'm telling you not to dream about it
when Shin isn't here.
He's your insurance.
He'll make you
the wealthy family's father-in-law.
I know, but don't be suspicious
of your own father.
I feel like I devoted my life here
for nothing.
Was I too mean?
Wait for me, Director.
Are you crazy?
Why did you break the TV?
It was the only thing working here.
Do you even have eyes?
-Look, it's the work of Trainer Kang.
-He did this?
Of course, he was watching the news
where you got hit, then...
Who was on the news?
You. Even with the cover up,
he knew it was his daughter.
He became so mad.
Then what? Where?
PK Group, of course.
Get off!
I need his apology before I leave.
Nam Shin is out of the country.
He's not here.
Then forget him. Bring his grandfather.
His grandfather is the president
of this company.
So what? What about it?
I'm here as her dad.
I always taught her not to show off
her skills.
Nor abuse anyone with her power.
Let me hear what this president
has taught his grandson.
Did he teach his grandson
to show off his power and money?
Did he tell him it's okay to treat people
that way?
Trainer Kang, this won't help So-bong.
My So-bong sidestepped
just once after she lost her mother.
Other than that,
she has been working very hard.
She also got this job not for the money
but for her sense of duty
to protect a person.
Dad!
Let's go.
After they apologize.
We should get an apology from her.
Isn't that right?
I'm sorry.
Dad, please go.
Wait, stop this!
What did you just say?
Why should she apologize?
Is this how you people roll?
So-bong got hit for secretively
taking his photo.
And she got fired, too.
Wait.
Secret photo? Is it true?
Did you really take that kind of picture?
Didn't you say she was diligent
and not interested in money?
You raised a different child, then.
Dad.
What the...
This is so annoying!
The grandson of a wealthy business
group hit a female security guard
and the footage is all over social media.
Misuse of power is again the hot topic.
Get ready, as you will see
more entertainment.
He had many scandals
with actresses and girl groups.
With his violence, society is asking
rich people to take responsibility.
This is Hwa-jin from YTV.
Isn't the meeting starting?
Yes.
Why isn't he coming out?
Dad!
Dad.
Are you upset?
Don't worry. I'm here for you.
Your daughter is here to be with you
even with the divorce.
Where's Jung-woo?
Jung-woo?
He's dead.
Dead?
What's wrong?
I disregarded him as my son.
But you cannot treat him as if he's dead
when he's very much alive!
What do you mean, he alive?
He's been dead for over 20 years.
Shut your mouth!
Please calm down.
Oh my gosh.
Please take him to the parking lot.
Please take him to Dr. Lee.
Let's go. Go.
Please find Jung-woo.
I'll take care of it from here.
Let's go.
Where is he going?
He must be shocked from the news.
He wanted to take a break.
You can lead the meeting, he said.
I'll take him home, then.
Let me go! Jung-woo!
Sir, please!
Please bring him back!
-Please, Dad.
-Get off!
Jung-woo!
Is he okay?
He just went off.
We've had a call from the Czech Republic.
He just landed.
CZECH KARLOVY VARY
Today's toast is so good.
Can I have one more?
Too many calories.
Never mind. I'll drink more coffee.
Too much caffeine.
You want to go that quickly?
I shouldn't bring you to the market
twice or you'll starve me.
It's David. You should go.
Sure.
Don't let people find out.
You know better.
Not that nagging again.
I'll take care of things here.
-Hi, my son.
-Don't call me that, I'm not your son.
Come on, I made most of your body.
You're like the son I made with Laura
with our hearts.
Dr. Laura has no intention of making
a baby with you.
Mother, please sit in the back.
I'll sit there.
I'm the one who convinced her
to bring you to the market.
-I can just leave you here alone.
-Let's go.
Okay.
Let's go!
You're going too fast.
You have to keep to the speed limit.
Don't worry about it. I'm not your Dad.
David!
Laura Oh, can you get it?
Her name is Laura Oh.
The name is spelled L-A-U-R-A O-H.
An Asian woman has been spotted around.
I'll find out more. Meet me at the market.
I'm in front of his hotel.
Nothing special.
Please make sure he doesn't coming back.
What's my limit here?
I'll choose this tonight.
It's the color of blood.
Murder or accident.
Make it clean.
You'll hear good news soon.
You've never seen this many people.
How do you feel?
No one cares about me.
I must look like a human.
Let's cross.
What are you doing?
Did you just hack this?
Did you teach him this?
Why would I?
He's 100 times smarter than me.
David.
We'll be late for grocery shopping!
This is not 200 grams, it's less.
This hand has been working with cheese
and ham for over 30 years
and is as good as the scales.
And this hand works with the money.
No, Mom! There's 50 grams less.
How can you tell?
Don't tell me you can
weigh stuff with your hand.
I think you're a cheater!
How dare you!
Of course, the bacon could have shrunk.
Could you even it up for me?
No problem.
Bye.
Don't say anything.
I told you not to get discovered.
He did a great job. Don't worry.
I'm so proud of him now.
I brought you to the market,
so do me a favor.
Leave us alone for one hour so we can
go on a date. See you at the car.
And buy a bouquet of flowers for her.
Shin said he has something to buy.
-Let him take care of himself.
-No way.
-Come here.
-Later.
Shin.
I got it. I'll give you the address,
meet me soon.
I got a tail. Throw away all my stuff
at the hotel.
Don't release that address.
I'll call you in Korea.
Shin should be here soon.
We still have 10 minutes.
He'll be here exactly on time.
You look great with flowers.
This is on the house.
-No.
-I'm sorry?
I only have to get a bunch.
Okay, then here's my number.
I'm always here.
I don't need paper.
I have 5 minutes and 37 seconds.
Thank you.
What was that all about?
Director Suh...
He'll do anything to take over.
Shin must come back.
Protect Shin's position going to Seoul.
Now you really look like Shin.
Am I your toy, throwing me away
after you're finished playing?
If you cry, I hug.
Hurry, go!
It's dangerous. Don't go in.
Subtitle Translation by