Let me out!
Let me out of here!
This is all your fault.
I'll return to being a slave again.
Goodbye for real,
So-bong.
You're just a robot.
Why did you have to look at me like that?
But...
why am I thinking of you now?
Okay. Please take your seats.
We'll begin soon.
PLEASE GET RID OF THE FILE
ON THE DESK
IN THE SELF-DRIVING CAR
DEPARTMENT
You have no idea where I am, do you?
I'm sure...
you can't come.
I'm the crazy one...
for hoping you'd come.
It's me, So-bong.
I'm here now.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Isn't he carrying the dashcam?
What happened to the car?
Did you...
The dashcam probably recorded you.
We have to get it
before he gives it to Mr. Suh. Let's go.
So-bong.
I'm fine. You need to go.
Get on my back. You need a doctor.
There's no time for that.
I'll stay here, so go.
We'll lose him!
Please.
I'll be right back.
-Hello.
-Let's go.
-Where to?
-Just go!
Okay.
Mr. Park. It's me.
Mr. Nam came.
He isn't human.
He can't be human.
Step on it. If you don't want
to die, step on it!
Make a left up there. Turn left!
Stop... Stop at the crosswalk over there.
Why that...
Start the car!
There's been an accident.
Send an ambulance.
What's going on?
The ambulance will be here soon.
Just what...
in the world are you?
My grandson must be back
to his bratty ways.
This isn't happening today,
so we'll invite you all again soon.
It won't be too long.
-What's going on?
-What a mess.
-What a waste of time.
-Exactly.
Ye-na.
I owe you...
a debt for life.
Blame me for raising him like that.
It's okay, Grandpa.
I've waited long for him already.
Who cares about the wedding date?
Let's go. Everyone will be
uncomfortable if I'm here.
I won't say anything stupid
to my dad, so don't worry.
I'll always be on Shin's side.
Something stupid?
That I won't marry him or
something like that.
So-bong!
I'm here.
Sorry.
I tried to get to the hospital alone,
but...
I'll call an ambulance.
Don't. It'll only complicate things.
Let's just take that and go.
What about that man?
Did he not say anything
when you took the dashcam?
He may tell people what he saw.
That man...
can't say anything anymore.
What did you do to him?
Did you threaten him?
The person you're trying to reach
is not available.
So-bong isn't picking up either.
I'm sure they're together.
He even removed the manual control remote.
He's completely out of control.
He can't develop desires. You know that.
It may be for the best...
since we avoided
this wedding tying us to Mr. Suh.
The chairman won't be
able to push it anymore either.
Hey. Shin.
Where were you?
Your mom was so worried.
Why did you remove that?
Why are you doing this?
You won't listen to me anymore?
I couldn't listen to you.
-Sorry.
-Were you with So-bong?
She was attacked because of me.
So you did leave
the wedding because of her.
Why are you acting so different?
Are you the one I created?
Are you really my son?
Dr. Oh.
Am I not your son if I don't act
like the human Nam Shin?
Can a robot not be your real son?
What? Why you...
The man who attacked So-bong
was the man who followed human
Nam Shin in the Czech Republic.
He's definitely Mr. Suh's man,
but he suddenly died in an accident.
I thought I should tell you this.
Suh Jong-gil.
He really tried to kill Shin.
Our instincts were correct.
This can't be the evidence,
so let's monitor Mr. Suh
until we have solid proof.
Good job. You've obtained
important information.
I need to tell you something.
Please come in.
So-bong is in the hospital.
I'll go now.
Okay. Don't wait for Mom, and go.
I thought I should tell you...
before it was too late.
I'm sorry,
but I think we should stop
the ultrasound treatment.
What do you mean?
Tell us.
It's hopeless.
I made the conclusion a while back,
but I thought you'd be too disappointed.
That can't be.
We haven't tried for very long.
We can't give up already.
We need to do more.
If we keep doing it,
it'll increase the risk factors.
The stroke he had recently
was probably because of...
He said...
that the dashcam had
recorded Nam Shin.
He said he wasn't human.
He said he couldn't be human.
And the police didn't find the dashcam?
I think Mr. Nam took it.
Do you think Mr. Nam...
realized he was the man
who tried to kill him...
in the Czech Republic?
If he took the dashcam to find
a connection to you...
Watch what you say.
Go shut the door.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
They caught the hit-and-run driver.
Then...
was it really a hit-and-run?
They'll have to investigate further,
but they're more than 90 percent sure.
A hit-and-run.
Why did it have to happen at that time?
Just what happened to So-bong?
That's the weird part.
All of the security cameras were dead.
When I spoke to him,
he said a car just came at him.
So I checked it myself,
but it was fine.
He said...
the car was smashed in the garage,
but there was nothing. It was clean.
It wasn't a hit-and-run.
Someone must be behind it.
The hit-and-run driver of the accident...
on a street in Yeoksam-dong...
was arrested for hitting a man
in his 40's and running away.
He had fled after the accident,
but he walked into
a police station at 6pm...
and turned himself in.
The victim died at the scene.
Witnesses say...
MATCHING
Did you kill a person this time?
If I hadn't,
all of this would've been found out.
I couldn't let anyone know that
the data center...
of Nam Shin III is located in
my company building.
Then even Dr. Oh, whom you
protected, will find out.
She simply created a robot...
because she missed her son.
If she finds out that I'm her sponsor,
she'll faint from the shock.
How's Shin?
I don't think he'll wake up.
That robot ran out of the wedding
because of So-bong, right?
Keep it in check.
It must be a product.
I don't need a defect
that causes problems.
I didn't accept your funding...
to create nothing but a product.
You wanted to create
an excellent AI as a scientist?
He's adjusting to the human world
like a human being.
You'll see. He'll develop
more than imaginable.
That's good for me.
This is the inside of his brain, right?
The future of my company...
rests inside that thing's brain.
Why don't you ever believe me?
I'm taking care of my friend
in the hospital for a few days.
Who? Like you know all of my friends?
I'll call again. Bye.
The results are in.
Your muscles are in shock,
so you just need rest.
What did your mom say?
Wasn't she mad that
you blew off the wedding?
Go home, and apologize to Mr. Ji.
Tell him that I called you out.
You can't go out of control.
Why can't I?
Just do as you're told. No questions.
Just go now.
Okay.
He's so quick.
At least turn off the lights.
Is this a hospital or a hotel?
Money really is nice.
Okay, So-bong. Let's get some sleep.
Let go! Let go of me!
Let me go!
Go away.
I knew you'd be like this.
Why did you pretend to be tough?
I didn't pretend.
I am tough.
I told you to go.
Why didn't you listen?
Okay.
Hey.
How could you leave
just because I said so?
Something bad happened to you
while helping me.
If I were a human,
I would've felt gratitude.
I'm sorry I can only say it
without feeling it.
It's okay. It isn't your fault.
I won't leave tonight.
I'll stay here all night.
I'll wake you up every time
you have a bad dream,
so don't worry, and sleep.
I didn't mean
that you should stay all night.
I'm a nobody.
You're not a nobody.
You're an incredible person.
I ignored traffic signals
and broke a car...
because of you.
You make me break existing rules
and create new rules that didn't exist.
That's oddly persuasive.
Again?
-Hey.
-My gosh.
You really are an incredible person.
Hey.
Is this all I get from a corporate heir?
I should ask for the entire store.
Do you want this store?
What? You're joking
more and more now.
Bring me the dashcam from that dead guy.
Let's see if anyone else saw you.
Okay.
It tastes bad to eat alone.
I lost my appetite.
You ate it all.
You consumed 1,537 calories--
I ate them because they'd go to
waste if I didn't.
What are you waiting for?
I need to digest the food.
This is fun!
It's fun, right?
I'm here now.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Fun? What am I, your friend?
Friend?
I've never had a friend.
-What?
-I've had Mom and David,
but I've never had a real friend.
Do you want to be friends with me?
What? You don't want to?
Sure, let's be friends, So-bong.
What? Are you speaking informally
just like that already?
Sorry?
I heard friends use informal language
to each other.
Should I not do that?
I'll be nice since we're friends.
-You can be casual.
-Hey. So-bong.
That's right, I'm So-bong.
We're the first human
and robot to be friends.
What do you think?
Totally cool, right?
Totally cool.
My first friend, Kang So-bong.
Thanks for being my friend.
Tell your friend.
What will you do now?
Will you keep pretending to be Nam Shin?
What should I do?
Why are you asking me that?
I won't tell you what to do anymore.
Whatever you choose,
I'll be on your side.
Friend, let's return to the room.
Okay. Run.
-Hey.
-What?
-Are you having fun?
-Hey.
I'm on my way
to answer your question.
I'll be back soon.
Hello, Mr. Suh.
Where's Ye-na?
She said she was going on a trip.
Why are you here
this early in the morning?
What's with the luggage?
I wanted to stay with Shin,
so I pretended to go a trip.
Do you still think you know your dad?
You said it confidently before.
You said that your dad wasn't like that.
When I think about
what that scumbag did...
You're at it again.
Why are you blaming Mr. Suh
for Shin's accident?
She's just sensitive. Go inside.
I don't want her even looking at Shin.
It makes me sick.
Antagonizing her won't do any good.
We still need to hide Shin's state.
Don't tell her that
we stopped the ultrasound.
Shin will wake up even without it.
What do I do?
I didn't think my dad would do that.
I didn't think he was bad enough
to kill someone.
I'm the daughter of a man like that.
I have no right to be sorry,
but I am sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Shin.
PK GROUP
What brings you to my office?
You must feel bad...
about the wedding.
Why should I? It wasn't going to
happen anyway.
Only one person wanted the wedding.
It's better this way.
I ran into Ms. Suh,
and her eyes were puffy.
As her father, it must break your heart.
Your son is the one...
who did that to my daughter.
I think I deserve to hear an apology.
Sorry,
but I have no intention of apologizing.
Listen up, Jong-gil.
If you make my child cry,
I will make your child cry tears of blood.
If you touch my son again,
I'll do the same to your daughter.
She must know for sure...
about the accident in the Czech Republic.
This is the office.
You should've at least changed.
So-bong was badly hurt,
so I was tending to her.
I'll change later.
Why did you come?
You should've stayed at the hospital.
So-bong is my friend.
I need to make sure
she isn't hurt again because of me.
"Friend"?
Yes.
But you're important to me too.
I promised you,
so I'll guard this position.
-Go on.
-However,
I'll make the call and do it my way.
I can do it well, so please just watch me.
You made me, after all.
And if I do this well,
it'll help the human Nam Shin.
I don't need a Shin who does his job well.
I need the real Shin.
Do as you please.
Do whatever you want.
Dr. Oh.
Wait here.
SUH JONG-GIL
Dr. Oh.
-Where are you going?
-I don't know.
It's too hard to be with him.
My words mean nothing to him now.
I need to change my perspective.
Change your perspective?
What do you...
It's way too early for drinks.
You were too cruel to Ye-na.
You know...
what weddings mean to women.
Why did you hurt her like that?
You're the one who hurt her more.
What... What do you mean?
Think about what you did
to the man your child loves.
It was quite memorable.
Don't tell me you forgot.
There must be some sort of
a misunderstanding.
I wonder...
if the man who tried to kill me for you...
and died while trying to abduct So-bong...
would also think it a misunderstanding.
I know that we've had our differences,
but I'm offended to hear you think
I tried to kill you.
Would I say that without any proof?
I don't plan to use it yet,
so don't worry.
However, if you try to harm my people,
I'll do the exact same thing back to you.
Please mark...
my warning.
He said he wasn't human.
He said he couldn't be human.
Who are you?
What are you?
Who do you think I am?
Believe as you see and wish.
I am...
just me.
Joint, are you on your way?
You packed my clothes and
laptop without telling Dad?
Of course. I'm on my way.
I'll be on my way. Bye.
I'm so bored.
When is he coming?
What's this?
Hello. I'm Maibo.
Were you waiting for me?
You were bored, right?
No, not at all.
But what's this? Your alter ego?
He'll play with you when I'm not around.
He has lots of functions.
I'll teach you one by one.
So?
What's the answer to this question?
I told Mom I'll keep acting like
the human Nam Shin.
Good. She must be relieved.
How's the company?
What about the office and the garage?
It must be a total mess.
There isn't a single trace.
I checked the security videos,
but they were deleted.
How is that possible?
I just got the chills. I'm scared.
You're scared?
What are you doing?
I'm going to sleep here tonight.
Says who? Forget it.
Why not?
Shouldn't a friend eat together and
stay with a friend who's scared?
You don't eat or sleep anyway.
Joint will be here with my things, so go.
You told me to bring this.
Let's watch it together.
I'll watch it myself. Let's go.
Do you think a guy and
a girl can be friends?
-What?
-According to a survey,
55 percent of women said that people
of the opposite sex can't be friends.
Which side are you with?
Stop being stupid, and go.
The 55 or 45?
Why won't you say?
I want to know more about my friend.
The VIP suite?
I knew it.
She's the patient.
She isn't taking care of anyone.
I'm sure it has to do with Mr. Nam.
This is like a hotel.
What's this?
I spoke with Dr. Oh.
She's very upset.
-Sorry?
-That kid...
rebelled hard against her.
He said he'll act like
Shin the way he wants.
Naturally, she's upset.
Her son is lying unconscious
before her eyes.
So what did she say to him?
It couldn't have been pleasant.
She said something like,
"What I need is the real Shin."
He listens to you,
so make sure he doesn't antagonize her.
What if she takes extreme measures?
"Extreme measures"?
Did I say that?
I spoke wrong.
Anyway, does he really call you a friend?
-Yes.
-Gosh, that kid.
He even made friends on his own.
He's all grown up.
I know I made him,
but I'm still curious about him.
If he can get a girlfriend,
he'd be perfect.
Did he come and go already?
Maibo.
If his mom may take extreme measures,
it must be that, right?
The kill switch?
What is this? Is he dancing?
He's moving the best he can.
Allow him to be cute.
Do you want to be my bodyguard again?
What if an error occurs
at the office without you?
Forget it.
It'll probably cause a fuss
about your wedding.
People might get
the wrong idea if I go now.
Did you...
lie to me today?
I didn't. Why?
Forget it. I'm going to sleep.
Is it 45 or 55?
You didn't answer me earlier.
45. Happy?
I'm open-minded enough
to be friends with a robot.
A guy friend is a piece of cake.
Bye.
He won't tell me about his Mom.
When he heard her say that
she needs the real Shin,
he must've been so hurt.
You don't know pain
since you're a robot.
You don't know loneliness either.
Right now, I'm so glad that he's a robot.
Friend.
Another error occurred.
Mr. Nam...
At first, I thought of him as
a machine or object.
But after spending time with him,
I found he speaks and acts like a person.
It's just me, isn't it?
You've never felt that way, right?
You said you'd let me talk whenever
I want, right?
You said you have no complicated feelings
and don't try to hide your faults.
You can talk all night
since I don't get tired.
I may be getting punished...
for sometimes thinking
about something so absurd.
Like what?
That you seem like a person.
When So-bong said it, I played dumb,
but I thought that way at times too.
Why should that be punished?
I often thought of things
that would make the other Shin angry.
That I wish he were more like you.
That I like you because
you weren't emotional,
reckless, or cynical.
That I like that you're rational
and get things done.
Things like that.
I simply lack emotions and ambition.
I know.
As long as the results are good,
you can make the decisions from now on.
Dr. Oh may disagree,
but I'll support you the best I can.
Do you mean it?
If it's good for Shin, I don't care.
Even if...
Shin can never wake up.
No. Even if he wakes up...
and can never forgive me,
I'll go all the way to the end.
Why do you go so far
for the human Nam Shin?
I don't understand which
part of the brain is active.
I don't know.
Why do I go so far?
I can't remember.
To me, Shin is like...
a habit that I developed
without knowing...
when or why.
Shall we go in?
I need to sleep.
Don't touch him.
-Leave him alone.
-I told you.
It may endanger him more.
Whether he dies like this
or dies while trying,
the result is the same.
Even if he dies,
I'll take full responsibility,
so don't touch my son.
Understood?
Am I not your son if I don't act
like the human Nam Shin?
Can a robot not be your real son?
However,
I'll make the call and do it my way.
I can do it well, so please just watch me.
You made me after all.
WARNING
The rule is to hug you if you cry.
I'll do as you say.
So don't be sad.
Have you lost your mind?
Why did you take out the kill switch?
What do you plan to do?
-Will you kill him now?
-What choice do I have?
-He keeps getting weirder.
-He's a robot.
A robot that you made!
He isn't getting weird. He's progressing!
Why? Are you afraid he'll
progress even more?
In case he'll progress more
and hurt your son?
How could you even imagine
something so insane?
You're being ridiculous!
You're no scientist.
You're just a bad mom. Do you know that?
I'm leaving for work.
BEANSPROUT SOUP
DRIED POLLACK SOUP
Corporate heir reporting for duty.
I'll go to the hospital later, friend.
Maibo, relay the message to
my friend, So-bong.
MESSAGE SENT
So-bong's here.
So-bong.
-What were you doing?
-Why are you here?
Let's go back to the hospital.
You asked me to be
your bodyguard again...
in case another error occurs.
You didn't want people getting
the wrong idea.
Mr. Nam must have lost his mind.
Did he cancel the wedding for her?
He's shameless.
How could he bring her here?
-Gosh, I feel so bad for Ms. Suh.
-I know.
Don't mind them. I'm not leaving.
I don't like how
the security videos were deleted.
That man was definitely involved
with the accident.
You can just admit
you were worried about me.
Let's go.
Let go of my hand.
Where are we going?
You ran off from the wedding.
Why did you come here?
I can't marry Ms. Suh.
Forget Ye-na.
What about Jong-gil?
I'll make sure...
Mr. Suh can't do anything to me.
Do you have something on him?
I'll handle that.
Does he not scare you anymore?
I don't have any fear.
Learn to do one more thing,
and you're complete.
Don't forgive anyone
who gets in the way...
of your decisions.
Even if it's your mom.
Your enemy is not always your enemy,
and your ally isn't always your ally.
If you can understand that much,
I'll let you take my place.
Thank you, Grandpa.
Thank you for what?
Come in.
I'll follow my own decisions
just like you said.
Kang So-bong...
will be my personal bodyguard again.
Don't mind them.
Don't look at them either.
I envy your lack of emotions right now.
Humans are sensitive
to people's attention.
You must be hungry.
What do you want to eat?
You don't even know
what it's like to have cravings.
What should we have?
Sandwiches.
Let's eat at somewhere cool, like a park.
Go ahead.
I'm going to run to the ladies room.
He always calls you "Mom".
He said that his mom was his creator,
family, and friend.
So?
Why are you saying that?
If you're his mom, treat him that way.
You can't kill your own son.
What do you mean?
The kill switch.
I overheard.
To him, that's like death.
Did you tell him?
Does he know?
If he did,
he couldn't smile at you
like he did earlier.
He may lack emotions,
but he knows when to smile.
If you're really his mom,
please get rid of that horrible device.
I'm begging you.
-It's so hard.
-Even I can do better.
Seriously.
You're so bad at it.
You should get that.
Why did you get two?
You want me to eat two?
We're friends,
so I'll eat with you.
Can you really eat?
Once in a while.
When I want to be a proper friend to you.
I don't know whom I should pity.
Is it you or him?
What are you staring at?
People.
I'm trying to understand them more.
You're surrounded by such terrible people.
Aren't you sick of people?
I want to understand you more.
What?
I need to know more about you, So-bong.
That very moment,
I thought for the first time...
that I wished the one before me...
wasn't a robot.
I wished he was a person just like me.
Subtitle Translation by Gloria Lee