This human looks just like me.
I just spotted him
46 minutes 43 seconds ago.
MATCH
You guys are twins!
You both are handsome. Who's older?
NAME: NAM SHIN
AGE: 28, PK GROUP'S GRANDSON
Nam Shin.
I'm also Nam Shin.
SEARCHING
NO DATA
You should protect the life.
Save first, think later.
-Hello.
Thank you.
Please help saving the earth.
What does it mean to have...
the same name and face?
Who the heck are you?
Shin.
It's me, your mother. Open your eyes.
I now know.
That's human Nam Shin.
He's my mother's son.
Shin, it's me, your mother.
I hug when she cries.
Not now.
Get out of here before anyone sees.
Shin.
Please open your eyes. I'm your mother.
You mother is right here.
Please open your eyes.
Shin.
Please.
Shin...
I couldn't give Mom the flowers.
It's okay.
We can give them to her anytime.
I saw another man tailing human Nam Shin.
-He had a gun.
-What?
Guess who I saw?
There was someone who looks just like--
Good. Please come back
before you get caught.
It's all done.
Dad is insisting to go to work.
Bring Shin right away.
You went to find Shin, right?
Call me.
Is it true that the director will
do the presentation?
Hello?
Open up!
I know you're here.
I know you're here to see your mother.
Who are you?
Are you serious?
How did I find you?
I searched all the hotels and your calls
to the private investigator.
Do you have any idea
what's going on at work?
Of course not.
I'm Nam Shin, but not that Nam Shin.
Are you crazy?
-The president has dementia--
-Don't misunderstand.
I'm not human.
What?
Who are you?
-Why are you here--
-I know him.
He's a new assistant,
Shin's only close friend.
How is he?
The bleeding has stopped, but...
he could suffer from edema.
I don't know when he'll wake up.
Did you find the truck driver?
We did, but he was already dead.
Shot in the head.
Something is going on.
I just need Shin next to me.
We've been apart for 20 years
because of that old man with dementia.
He even got into a car accident
in front of me.
I'll take care of him.
If Director Suh finds this out...
Who? Suh Jong-gil?
You know him well.
If he knows his condition,
he'll do anything to kill him.
It will endanger him even more.
Suh Jong-gil.
He killed my husband,
and now my son.
Shin can stop this.
We need Shin back.
There's no way.
There's no trace of that man
who was tailing Shin.
-You didn't get anything either?
-Right, no data.
Let's keep it a secret from Mom.
She has too much going on already.
How's your human son doing?
Shin.
I have a favor to ask.
What is it? You look so serious.
Please go to Seoul
and keep Shin's place.
Seoul? What are you saying?
You're sending him to Seoul
instead of your real son?
Are you insane?
I'll do as you say.
Hey.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Don't be sad.
Shin doesn't bow back.
-Why not?
-He's cocky.
Chin up, look down.
Let's try something else.
He avoids the president.
He doesn't talk much.
The director is our enemy
but your fiancée's father.
You can greet him.
Ye-na is like your sister.
No touching.
He doesn't button up.
Now you really look like Shin.
Even I get confused.
MRI, CT, brainwave, blood test.
We've looked through again.
It is the early stage of Alzheimer's.
You have to continue to take the medicine.
I will, but let me do the presentation
myself.
Are you out of your mind?
Do you want to advertise
that you have Alzheimer's?
You'll look for Jung-woo
in front of Director Suh again.
Be quiet.
She's right.
I think you should let him
do the presentation.
He's too lucky to have that chance.
It's all because of Shin!
Is this okay so far?
Yes, right there is fine.
When you finish your sentence
the self-driving car will come in.
Why don't you be in that car
when you come out, sir?
I think our plan is more dramatic.
But we should put all the spotlights
on him
to help with the presentation.
Is the main presentation about him
or the self-driving car?
Let's go with the first plan.
Sure.
Let's do some more adjustments.
How do I look?
Looks cool, right?
Sorry to break it to you,
but I wish it was Shin looking cool.
Not you.
I'm going to him.
What?
Did Shin call you?
I managed to find out
Young-hoon's business trip destination.
He must have gone to bring him back.
I'll help him out.
Oh, sure. Bring him quickly.
So I don't feel all this pressure on me.
Let me know if you need anything.
Sure, will do.
My bags should be here by now.
Bye.
What?
I'll just ask once.
Why did you get fired from the PK Group?
That's because...
He hit you for secretively taking
his picture, right?
You took out that part from your CV.
Do you think we're
that much of a pushover?
You told me to work from today.
I can work 7 days, not 5 days.
I also don't need an employee discount.
Why? Will you sell the pictures
of our VIPs?
What can I do to earn your trust?
I can write a contract.
I can bet my hands on it.
Up! Get out now!
Just bite the ear. Or poke the eyes.
When the referee isn't looking
that's when you cheat.
Go on.
You come out.
Give me my soju back. Come on.
I thought it was your first day.
Why are you back?
Did you make trouble again?
Is it a hidden camera
from the mall's restroom this time?
Stop it. I got fired for that
and won't be able to work at all.
So are you sad?
What kind of security takes
a photo with a hidden camera?
How many times do I have to tell you?
I won't do it again.
How can I trust you when you tell
the students to cheat?
What does that have to do with this?
A lot!
Once you become trash,
you stay trash.
What? Trash?
Fine.
I'll sue that jerk and get the money.
I endured it for you, but I won't anymore.
What, again?
Sue me, too for raising a girl like you.
Get out of the way.
PK GROUP
There's nothing but PK Group around you.
Is Korea a PK Group or something?
What kind of global group
tries to block my career?
I'm sorry.
Stop it, I'm talking about PK, not you.
Hey.
I knelt down on the street
in the middle of Hong-dae.
I have a confession.
That hidden camera...
was Nam Shin's idea!
What did you say?
He wanted to make himself
look like trash, so he used you.
And all the money you got was from him.
He just beat me like that
knowing about the camera?
That was all show. I was surprised too.
Who is this jerk?
I'm barging into PK Group.
Wait, please don't.
You're also out of my life. Bye!
Hello? Where are you? You okay?
Just drink up and feel better.
I'll buy you beer and beef.
I just need to borrow both of you.
The self-driving car project was planned
and carried out by Nam Shin.
Due to personal issues,
I'm here on behalf of him.
I'm PK Group's Director, Suh Jung-gil.
PK MOTORS
The 4th industrial revolution is a magical
change that turns imagination to reality.
PK Group would like to start that magic
with this self-driving car.
It drives by itself.
It helps humans to rest.
Introducing The M Car.
As you can see,
there's no one in the driver's seat.
Of course, none in the back either.
-I'm sorry, I'm late.
-Oh, my.
Are you crazy?
I'm sorry.
He wanted a dramatic appearance.
KIM MYUNG-HO, CHA SANG-HYUNG
SUH JONG-GIL'S RIGHT/LEFT HAND
NAM HO-YUN, FASHION DIRECTOR, ENEMY
NAM GUN-HO, PK GROUP PRESIDENT
SUH JONG-GIL, GENERAL DIRECTOR
EAGER TO TAKE OVER
Director.
Thanks for all your work.
I'll take it from here, please enjoy.
Please give a round of applause
for the director.
I'm glad I made it on time.
I'll do the rest of the presentation.
I am Nam Shin, the General Manager
of Future Development.
SELF-DRIVING CAR
NEW INTRODUCTION
I'M NOT THE SWINDLER HERE.
STOP THIS ACT AND APOLOGIZE, SHIN.
HE USED HIS POWERLESS EMPLOYEE.
How long do we have to do this?
My arms hurt!
Do they hurt already, Joint?
Don't call me that.
My name is Jo In-Tae.
Don't be a weak baby.
I'm good.
I'm the robot cop.
So-bong.
You're too much, just go.
So-bong, please stop.
If Shin sees this, it's even more trouble.
What? That jerk is inside there?
This car doesn't feel anger,
compulsion nor fatigue.
It doesn't drink and drive,
have road rage, or nod off at the wheel.
You can watch movies, shop,
or love your lover
like you've seen it on TV in the car.
Just don't forget the window
is in manner mode.
When there's a car accident,
what should we do?
Accident?
Why would you ask him
that hard question?
Before a journalist asks,
it's better we clear it up.
Let's say the car is going
into a narrow street.
And there are two motorcycles
coming from the opposite side.
One rider is wearing a helmet,
another one isn't.
If a crash is inevitable,
which rider does the car hit?
It should be the one with the helmet
as he or she will get hurt less.
But that's the one who followed the rules.
It's not fair.
I think it should be the one
without the helmet.
Mr. Nam, which decision should we make?
That's hard.
Should we decide it with rock,
paper, scissors?
Let me rephrase the question.
What if the helmet rider is 100 years old.
And the one without is in his teens.
The teen should die because
he didn't abide by the law?
Which life to save, the decision
is in human's hands.
Now humans are within the reach
of God's control, deciding people's lives.
God has given us destiny
and coincidence so far.
But PK Group will be the one
that wins over any human decisions.
PK's godly upgrade
to a different level starts with...
this M Car.
You jerk!
President...
Isn't she the one who got hit by him?
-I'll get help.
-Let Shin take care of it.
You made me take the pictures. And you
hit me even though you knew about it.
I did?
Don't pretend you don't know.
Are you going to deny it like this?
SEARCHING
I kept quiet because
I did the wrong thing.
I sucked it up when everyone
treated me like garbage and fired me.
Then I heard you played me.
Am I some toy for you to use like that?
How fun was it for you?
It must have been fun watching me
run around without knowing anything.
If you cry, I hug.
Why are you blanking out?
Did you get hit again?
What did those crazy people do to you?
I'll go and...
You go home.
I'll call you later.
You didn't see him?
What did you do inside?
I'm sorry but...
whether you met him or not
where's the beef you promised?
Beef my ass, go away!
Do you want to be on the fire
with the beef?
You told me you'd treat us.
If you had shut your mouth,
we'd have eaten it.
Hug when you cry?
Pretending to be an angel?
Oh, I see. Now you're using me
to change your public image?
Wait!
It was a touching moment to see
your reconciliation with that lady.
Was it planned?
No way. He's been regretting it a lot.
He's acting weird.
He never hugs anyone.
He must have grown up this time.
No way. Humans don't change that easily.
You always act how you want.
Why didn't you hide longer?
You should've come back after I'm dead.
Avoid the president.
Shin doesn't talk to him much.
What was that cute show all about?
What a hypocrite.
Sneer at her.
You're also a hypocrite
in front of grandfather.
What?
It's a big day, no need to fight today.
Welcome back, Shin.
It means it's a lie.
The sensor in your hands will read
a person's heart beat,
breathing pattern and blood pressure
to figure out if that person is lying.
The lie detector is an addition.
It's a lie when I wink.
Yes.
People lie, although it seems
like they are telling the truth.
Don't get fooled by people
like Suh Jong-gil.
What a lie.
You didn't want Shin to come back.
I know it, I have a lie detector.
Mr. Nam...
A lie detector?
What an interesting way
to make me laugh.
Shin.
Be careful what you say.
I must have wronged him in some way.
For him to make such a joke to me.
That was a bit over the line, Mr. Shin.
Seoul has changed a lot.
You must have been gone for a long time.
Why didn't you visit your hometown?
I'm here now. Where's Shin?
You should focus on the other Shin.
Make sure he's okay
with the new environment.
Okay, hanging up.
I'm sorry for you,
you're in a new environment, too.
Wake up already.
Before everyone gets
into bigger troubles.
Get up.
I'm sorry.
Do you even realize
what you've done to me?
I'm sorry.
Find out what and how it went wrong.
If that killer betrayed us, find him
and cut him into pieces.
He's been working for you for a long time.
He wouldn't--
If he didn't betrayed me, why is he alive
after being hit by the truck?
Then he came back alive
to embarrass me in front of everyone.
I'm sorry, I will double check.
You mentioned that there's something
Shin can't find out.
Do you think he might have come back
after finding that out?
His route in Czech has nothing to do
with that.
Isn't it about his father?
-I'm sorry.
-Don't you dare ask questions.
Just go check with that killer.
Yes, sir.
Don't smile like that.
Hugging So-bong and talking
about the lie detector were dangerous.
-If you cry, I hug--
-I know it.
But why are you here?
Because Mother asked me to come.
She asked you to become the real Shin.
You said your mother is your top priority.
You can't be caught as a robot
for the sake of your mother.
Especially in front of them. Am I right?
You did fairly well today.
Thanks for doing as I taught you.
You know how to smile.
I guess I can relax now. I feel relieved.
Dr. Oh Laura should be here by now.
Really?
I'll call the car, go and meet her.
I'll finish up the rest here.
Let's go.
Sure.
It's really you.
My Shin.
Where are you going?
I want to go with you.
Was it really Shin?
Don't follow me.
Please, let's talk. Just once.
Do you want some more?
Which type of attack do you want?
No, no.
With my journalist name tag,
we can go meet Shin at the reception.
So you'll be off the blacklist.
Don't forgive me.
You don't have to see me again.
But I need to make sure
you're working again, so I feel better.
I will also give you all the money
I got from Shin.
What if Shin denies you as well?
Just follow me.
Stop drooling.
You never change.
You cherish me too much.
You're like my sister.
Don't worry,
I'll be your sister-like wife.
Stop having pictures taken of you
with other girls. Let's get married.
No.
Never.
No?
Why not?
Which girl are you looking at this time?
CLUB IN BRAZIL ON FIRE,
THE CAUSE WAS THE FIREWORKS
No fireworks. It's dangerous.
Okay, you stay here.
I'll go talk to them.
I'm old enough to know
that you don't play with fire.
This is what all clubs are doing.
Get out, you wrinkly old lady.
Don't.
Let it go.
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
You're the crazy one.
Why are you even here, you swindler?
What did you call me?
I'm here to see someone.
I'm sure that's Shin.
Who the heck are you to--
I'm the Marketing Lead of PK Group.
And Shin's fiancée.
Oh, you're that pushover
who's fine with everything
her boyfriend does, even cheating.
Pushover?
You'll never see him. Get out.
Who are you to tell me that?
You're only the fiancée.
You can break up at any time.
What...
Stop making stories up.
He did plan it, he played me.
Don't blame us that you got fired
for your wrongdoing.
I'm not blaming anyone.
Let me check, bring him in.
Mr. Nam?
Who are you?
Journalist Jo.
You know me.
I knew it.
I told you, he'd deny you.
I knew it. He says he doesn't know you.
Stop fooling around.
Are you Journalist Jo?
Yes.
-Let's talk.
-What?
I know all about Shin,
but I've never seen you.
You said it's absolutely secret
and sounded like you weren't coming back.
Why are you back here?
You did well before pretending
that you don't know me.
The world will be fussy about you
again if they knew about our plan.
But think about poor So-bong.
She's a scapegoat.
Please let her work, at least.
I'll take care of it.
Here's more.
You little...
What?
Who do you think you are, anyway?
Fire!
It's fire.
Fire! Come out quickly!
Save us!
-Let us out!
-Excuse me.
I'll do it.
What are you doing? Stop!
It's not here. Get out the other way.
Wait, my phone. It's in the restroom.
You can't go back there again.
Use this and go.
Hurry up!
Hurry, go!
I think we should go now.
Oh, sure, go.
Then I'll trust your words
and let So-bong know...
There's big fire in front of the building.
Please come out and see.
Shin!
Where have you been? I thought I'd die.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not.
Let's go check up later.
Shin.
Where is he going?
Slowly.
It's dangerous. You can't go in.
-He's in crisis mode.
-Crisis mode?
He won't remember anyone
at the moment.
His energy is focused on rescuing people.
Other functions are off.
Save me first. They'll all die anyway.
What was it?
Hurting an ankle won't kill you.
Save yourself.
DAD
Don't get it wrong.
It's your heartbeat.
I don't have a heart.
No one touches Shin.
What is she planning behind my back?
You can't go in.
I said don't go!
This is Shin?
He's totally different.
He doesn't even remember
his comment.
Accept me as your security.
Nam Shin.
You better not get caught.
Subtitle Translation by