[BANGING]
- [CHURCH BELL TOLLING]
- Ling's sister was also in the area.
Her sister Bettina.
Ling, aren't you taking a break?
No, you two go ahead.
You won't get extra pay
even if you don't take a break, Ling.
- Come on.
- It's alright.
I just wanted to talk to Ling.
It's working hours, Bingo.
I'll just wait for her break, ma'am.
If you got blinded
by your anger towards Edward…
I would do the same.
- You're unbelievable.
- Sorry. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to say that.
There was a nail found
at the scene of the crime.
Is it Bettina's nail?
The most damning evidence is that nail.
So what if you saw her sister?
I don't know, boy.
I just feel like I have to let her know.
- Bougie.
- Where are you?
We've got problems here.
What?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Koriks, what's this? This is wrong.
That's why I'll fix it.
The address should be Quezon City,
not Quezon Province.
My goodness.
Aside from the mystery box,
we're also selling underwear
so it's confusing.
[SNOOP] You can't be confused.
It's your job to double-check the items.
You're unbelievable.
[KORIKS] Fine. It's my fault.
- Well, yeah.
- Hey.
What's going on?
Stop fighting.
Let's just find a way to fix this, okay?
There's no use blaming each other.
[BOUGIE] Hey! We're not scammers!
We don't know what's
inside the mystery box.
- It's not our fault you're unlucky!
- Alright. We'll take a break.
- We'll be right back.
- [GRUNTS IN ANGER]
Turn it off.
- Hey!
- Bougie.
[GRUNTS]
We've been over this already.
We should be as tolerant as possible.
People are bashing us online.
They're saying
the mystery boxes are a scam.
Well, we know that's not true, right?
Don't let those bashers affect you.
They don't know what they're saying.
Koriks, we'll call the customers
that have concerns about the waybill.
I'll help you, okay?
Boy.
You handle the freebies for the customers.
- Freebies?
- Yes, to make up for this.
We're already losing profit
due to shipping costs
and we don't know if the
customers will return the items.
We'll get our profit back.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on, guys.
We can do this, okay?
Let's work.
- Let's get started.
- Fix this.
- We got this.
- I'm calm now.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[CLEARS THROAT]
[CATHY] So, what's your favorite food?
Auntie!
May I help you?
- Did you miss me?
- No!
Oh, I'm sure you did.
You just won't admit it.
Anyway, Auntie, I'm here because I'm back.
- Yay!
- What?
Your back hurts?
No, I'm back here to work.
I'm back and ready to be trained again.
What makes you think I'd train you again?
Auntie. Auntie, please.
No, Auntie. Please take me back.
Auntie.
I need to train to represent
my siblings in the business.
Auntie.
Auntie, I like your hair and your outfit.
Auntie, listen to me, please.
- [WAITER] Excuse me, ma'am.
- Okay, fine. Go.
- Sorry, Ma'am Irene.
- Go, go, go.
Auntie.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Am I going to jail?
Listen to me.
Your father and I won't let that happen.
You're not going to jail, okay?
Over my dead body.
- Bettina, you have to get up.
- [SNIFFLES]
You have to be strong.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You can do it.
- [MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CATHY] Oh, why are you here?
You're not on the closing shift.
I'm not yet tired, Auntie.
You're not going home?
I should control my emotions
or they will control me.
I'm glad you remembered that.
If you're doing that to distract yourself,
then do it well.
Do your job properly.
Take charge of closing
and make sure that you
don't forget anything.
Back to work.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GRUNTS AND HUFFS]
I've arranged everything
according to size and style
to avoid confusion and make
the inventory more organized.
This is arranged from
lowest to highest price, okay?
As for this one,
I labeled them "Metro Manila,"
"Luzon," and "Visayas."
Come here, Koriks,
so you can see it better.
Put all the items that need
to be shipped in these boxes.
- Boy.
- Hm?
If I'm not around,
double-check the waybill
before we release it for shipping.
Got it.
Bougie.
Get some rest so you won't get cranky.
Are we clear?
- Yes.
Very good.
Things are different when you're here.
[SNOOP] Tell me about it.
Bingo is suddenly acting bossy.
- Oh, really?
- Just kidding. [CHUCKLES]
Let's just continue this tomorrow.
Let's go.
- I better get going.
- We're good now, right?
- Yeah, let's go.
- Bye.
- Is holding hands necessary?
- [CHUCKLES]
- I'll help you here.
- [BINGO] No need, Bougie.
- Go to bed. I got this.
- Are you sure?
You need rest. I'll be fine.
Good night.
- Good night.
- Get some rest, too.
[SIGHS]
Alright.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, shoot!
I forgot the fish stew.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HUFFS]
It's closed already.
I'm going to be in trouble.
Grandma, don't get mad at me, okay?
I forgot to give the food to Ling.
I'm telling you now so
you'll be calmed down
when I get home.
[LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS]
["YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING]
[MUFFLED] Ling.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Ling.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KNOCKING ON GLASS]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BETTINA] How dare you do this to me!
[EDWARD] Bettina!
- How dare you!
- Stop, please!
[SCREAMING]
- [EDWARD] Bettina, please!
- [BETTINA] The wedding is off!
[EDWARD] Bettina!
Bettina, please!
Bettina!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBBING]
[RING CLATTERS]
[BETTINA SNIFFLES]
[SIGHS]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES]
- [BARMAN] Good afternoon, ma'am.
- Whiskey on the rocks, please.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [EXHALES]
- [GLASS THUDS]
[BREATH QUIVERING]
I figured you're stressed
so I booked a masseuse,
so you'll be stress-free tomorrow.
Hey, Bettina. Hey.
[GASPS]
Your nails.
This can't be happening.
Your wedding day is tomorrow.
Wait, I'll book a nail technician.
Bettina.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're in charge
of closing the restaurant?
[KEYS JANGLING]
How are you?
I sent you a text.
I haven't checked my phone.
Why?
Uh…
It's about your sister… Bettina.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Remember the day we were
looking for your brother?
I didn't get to tell you I saw Bettina.
I saw her drinking at a bar.
At first, I wasn't sure if it was her.
But it was definitely her, Ling.
She was at a bar.
It might mean nothing,
but I feel like you should know.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know, Bingo, there's just
so much going on right now.
Bettina almost got implicated
in Edward's death.
How?
Hold on.
Is it because of the vlogger
claiming it was murder?
That can't be possible, Ling.
I saw your sister at a bar.
I remember it well,
because the church bell rang.
The bell strikes at exactly
5:00 p.m. for the mass.
That's how I knew we were
at the venue past 5:00 p.m.
It was past 5:00 p.m.
How is it that Bettina became a suspect?
She wasn't there…
when Edward died.
Well, Papa is taking care of everything.
But I'll tell him what you told me.
I have to go now.
Oh. Hey.
Are you okay, Ling?
Here. Sit down first.
- It's okay. I'm fine.
- No, have a seat.
- Sit down.
- Thank you.
Have you eaten already?
You look pale, so obviously no.
Here.
Grandma cooked some fish stew for you.
I was supposed
to give this to you earlier.
It's no longer warm, but it's still good.
No, thank you.
Oh.
You should thank Grandma, not me.
Here.
Mm. It smells sour, right?
But, it's not because it's spoiled.
As Papa would say,
Grandma's fish stew is deliciously sour.
Try it.
Here. Hold this.
I'll check it first.
Let's see.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
It's still good.
I'll take that.
There. Now, the fish.
Here you go.
Eat up.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm not in the mood to eat.
I'll just bring that home.
I'm telling you, Ling.
My grandma will scold me
if this container is not empty
when I get home.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh. Wait.
I almost forgot.
Let's add some soup.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh.
It's from Papi.
What's this?
It's an ointment.
He said it relieves headaches
and calms nerves.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BINGO] Oh, another thing.
I'm sorry for--
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
But we're good, right?
I washed it well
and dried it under the sun,
so I'm sure it's germ-free.
And you'll need it
after you're done eating.
Here.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BINGO] Oops.
I also brought something for you,
aside from Grandma's fish stew
and Papi's ointment.
That's from me.
Bon appetit.
Did I say that right?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Is it good?
I don't eat fish.
Mm.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
What the hell is your problem?!
I lived here, you know?
Auntie Cathy is my relative.
I'm really sorry, ma'am.
Ma'am Cathy instructed us
not to let you in.
So you know me?
[RECEPTIONIST] Yes, ma'am.
She told us not to allow
the snobbish girl with bangs
inside her house.
But I left my bags here.
I'll just get them and leave right away.
Ma'am, I'm very sorry,
but I can't let you in.
You're just a receptionist. I'm Irene Tiu.
- Come on.
- Ma'am!
- Ma'am, wait!
- What?
Ma'am, Cathy said I can have you arrested,
together with your bodyguards,
if you insist on going inside.
[GRUNTS]
How annoying!
[BINGO] It's delicious, right?
I'll take that.
I will take this container home
because Grandma will need it
when she cooks for you again.
Please thank Grandma Nene for me,
and tell her the fish stew is delicious.
But she doesn't have to prepare--
No, no, no, no.
We can't stop her.
You know her, Ling.
She's going to cook for you anyway.
By the way…
[BINGO] Yes?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma'am, are you ready to go home?
Your curfew is 1:00 a.m.
if you're working the closing shift.
I have to go.
Okay. Good night.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Good night.
[EXHALES]
Did Ling like it?
- She finished all of it?
- Yes, she did.
That's great.
[MONCHING] She must be really hungry.
What about the ointment? Did she use it?
She put it in her pocket.
- Her pocket?
- Yes.
You mean she didn't use it yet?
- I don't know.
- [MONCHING] She didn't use it?
Oh no.
She might drop it if it's in her pocket.
What if when she drops it,
it ends up in the drain,
or gets picked up by someone else?
- Then, she gets a headache.
- [YAWNS]
She suddenly remembers
the ointment I gave her,
only to find out that it's gone.
How is she supposed to
relieve her headache now?
Plus, it was 150 pesos.
- It's pricey. I shouldn't--
- [BINGO SNORING]
Quiet.
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BINGO SNORING]
He fell asleep.
He must be really tired and sleepy.
Poor dear.
- [SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BINGO SNORING]
[THUD]
[NENE] Good night.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
We're here for Bettina Tiu.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
We need to take her to the station.
Let's go.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Bring the bags.
Give this to Ling, okay?
Yes, Grandma. I'll give it to her.
If your DNA matches the nail
found at the crime scene,
you'll be in trouble.
So it's best you confess now.
[HONKING]
Bingo I need you. Papa and I need you.
Are you the Bingo who saved Caroline
when she was kidnapped?
So, Bingo, are you willing to testify?