What are we doing here?
Why'd we get a room?
Take a shower.
Why?
Just trust me.
Girl! Who's that?
Is that your boyfriend?
It's not what you think, okay?
Who's that?
- [KNOCKING]
- What the hell?!
I'm getting impatient.
Tonight.
I promise I'll give it to you.
Here's our plan.
Liv likes men.
Tall, dark...
Handsome?
So you're going
to make me a thief.
Discreetly, of course.
Can you please leave?
But I have to see--
I'm uncomfortable.
I'm not used to people
watching my every move.
I told you, I'm going
to get my money.
Can you please relax?
The important thing
is that Caroline is gone.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLICKS TONGUE, INHALES DEEPLY]
Irene?
We need to talk.
It's okay.
Oh. Why'd you let her in?
Sir, you can't go in.
What about her?
We can't let you in. Sorry.
It won't take long.
- No, sir. We're sorry.
- Boss.
It's not allowed.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Psst!
Psst! Bingo!
Oh my gosh.
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MOUTHING]
Was that her? Should I go?
[CAROLINE WHISPERING]
No! It's not her.
- Hi, Miss Liv.
Hi.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUFFLED SCREAM]
It's not Liv.
I almost offered myself to her.
Now you're telling me
it's not her?
It's not Liv.
Nor is it Edward.
Then who is it?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUFFLED SCREAM]
Babe!
- You scared me.
- I'm sorry.
I just really missed you.
That's a pretty dress
you're wearing.
Thank you. I missed you too.
Give me a kiss.
[LIV GIGGLES]
- [UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [LIV GIGGLING, MOANING]
[EDWARD] I like this.
- [LIV] Thank you.
- [EDWARD] So sexy.
[LIV] Thanks.
Babe.
[EDWARD, LIV MOANING]
[LINE RINGING]
Dear.
Are you coming back home?
[CAROLINE] Nanny.
I need you to report to me
all of Irene's moves.
Dear, what's going on?
(In Fukien) Is that Caroline?
Ma'am.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Tell her...
if she's ready to apologize
to the Liaos and to Bettina,
that's the only time
she can come home.
Yes, ma'am.
Dear. Hello?
Dear?
What now?
Shall I take you home?
No.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LIV] You caught me off guard.
I didn't know you'd be there.
[EDWARD]
I can surprise you again later.
[LIV] Don't do it again, okay?
Hold on, I need to call--
What?
Babe, my phone!
- I left it upstairs.
- Forget your phone.
No, no, no, no. Wait.
Let's just go.
[GIGGLES]
Wait, I'll just get it.
I won't take long.
I'm sure it's upstairs.
Okay, fine.
Okay? Just a minute.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
- [THUDS]
- [GROANS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Who's the mastermind, then?
Irene.
[BINGO] Irene?
You mean your sister, Irene?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
How did you know?
I heard it straight
from the horse's mouth.
Horse's mouth?
You heard it from her?
How?
She was there.
[BINGO] She's the mastermind?
Not Liv?
She had her own sister
kidnapped?
Because she's Irene.
She can do it.
And this is not the first time.
That witch.
She never runs out
of evil plans.
[CAROLINE] Sir.
Sir, I'm talking to you!
Please!
I didn't do anything wrong!
[WOMAN] It's not her.
[OFFICER] But her name
is in all your transactions.
[IRENE] What the--
[CAROLINE] How dare you?!
You've got some nerve
to use my name.
What? I don't know
what you're talking about.
- Aah!
- What's happening?
I know you're using my name
to scam other people.
What name are you protecting?
You're just a bastard!
Caroline, stop it!
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- [IRENE] Aah!
Aren't you going to stop?!
Where are you hiding it,
you little rat?!
[GASPS]
Drop it.
Why? Is this yours?
That's my mom's.
No!
Oh no.
[CAROLINE] No.
[IRENE]
Just remember, Caroline,
you don't belong
in this family.
[SNAPPING FINGERS]
What evil plans
are you talking about?
What did Irene do to you?
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
It was that bad?
Can you try to recall it?
You know, Grandma said...
family members
should love each other.
We're different.
How?
Ever since,
we've always been rivals.
[WILSON] As you both know...
Bettina and Carlo...
After they graduated
from college,
they started training
in the company.
And the two of you,
that's what
you're going to do.
I will need
a new management trainee.
Someone who'll always be
by my side
to see firsthand
everything I do.
I am so ready, Papa.
I know I'll learn a lot
from you.
(In Fukien) No.
Irene, I'll assign you
to the marketing department.
I know you're good
with people,
and you're going
to excel there.
I want Caroline to be
my new management trainee.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay.
You don't have
to share the details.
Another time, then.
But Irene...
She's your rival.
I thought you didn't have
any feuds with your siblings.
They are angry with me.
But I never thought of them
as enemies.
But they see me as their enemy.
To the point
that they had me kidnapped.
that she wants me gone.
Maybe you should talk
to her first.
[CAROLINE] What for?
She wants war...
I'll give her war.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
You deserve this, you bastard!
Why didn't you just die?!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ma'am, where are you
taking that?
It's none of your business.
That belongs to Ling.
Ugh! Ling, Ling, Ling!
It's all about Ling!
She's never coming back!
- She is.
- This is mine!
She'll be back. She--
Can't you just go?!
Do the laundry or something!
Get the hell out of my way!
But, ma'am--
Go!
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[EDWARD] Let go of me.
Do you want money?!
I'll give you money!
Let's go to an ATM!
I'll withdraw cold hard cash!
[GRUNTS] Let go of me!
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
You.
Are you nuts?
You think you'll get away
with this, huh?! Let go of me!
[CHARLESTON] Why, Edward?
Do you think you can run
away from this, huh?
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
No.
I'm not scared.
I'm not scared of you.
I know you're scared, Edward.
It's okay.
You should be.
You can act tough later.
If you come out of this alive.
Go ahead.
You're an asshole, Charleston!
You'll pay for this!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [EDWARD GROANING]
[EDWARD BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [EDWARD GROANING]
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GROANING]
[COUGHING]
Bingo borrowed my motorcycle,
together with two helmets.
- Oh?
- You know, Kap has a point.
I think the girl
is three months pregnant.
- Ouch!
- Really?
- It's too tight!
- You're exaggerating.
She can't be pregnant.
You see, these days,
getting pregnant
is like making popcorn.
Come on, guys.
Can we please stop gossiping
and start working?
If that is possible.
I think we should meet
that girl,
so we can find out
if she's prettier than you.
Ow. My Tweety bird.
Makes sense. Don't you think?
Hmm.
- Looks good.
- Let's apply mascara.
- [ADORA] Bingo!
- [KORIKS] Bingo!
[KORIKS] It's Bingo!
Bingo! Where's the...
- Uh.
- ...key to my motorcycle?
OMG!
Here.
Thank you, Koriks.
- I've filled it up.
- O to the highest G.
Here are the helmets.
You smell good!
And you look fresh!
Did you get a trim?
He just used gel.
You look like a leading man
in a K-drama.
The son of a rich CEO!
Just like Park Seo-joon!
What do you think, Bougie?
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
He's got a lot of free time
to go out.
Where do you go these days?
Riding a motorcycle, check.
Wearing gel, check.
Nice outfit.
Probably went on a date.
What a heartthrob!
You went on a date?
No!
What date? It's a side hustle.
I'm taking care of something.
What about you?
How was your sales today?
Why don't you tell us
about the girl?
Don't act like we're strangers.
Tell us about it.
It's getting late.
I'll go ahead. Good night.
- Hey!
- Another day, another hustle!
- Bingo!
- Hey!
Did he just walk away?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Why do you hate me so much?
Why?
Why?!
- Why?!
- [THUD]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GROANS]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing?
I was just looking for cotton.
Oh. You're bleeding.
Let's clean it up.
- It might get infected.
- No need.
This is nothing anyway.
Are you sure?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why is this here?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What's that?
News clippings.
I always keep this.
Because of Wilson Tiu?
No.
Because of this.
A grant from GL.
I applied for it before.
- [CAROLINE] Really?
- [SIGHS DEEPLY]
I actually reached the finals.
Too bad. I almost won.
What happened?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll tell you another time.
Back to the crime board.
We have a mystery to solve.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LINE RINGING]
[OPERATOR] The subscriber
cannot be reached.
Charleston.
Charleston, what happened?
[CHARLESTON EXHALES DEEPLY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHARLESTON] Bettina.
You're my sister.
I just want you to be happy.
You deserve better.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
We need to follow Irene
everywhere she goes.
We need to know and track
her every move.
What's the point
of following her?
I'm certain
that one of these days
she'll meet up
with the kidnappers.
So what if she meets
with the kidnappers?
[CAROLINE]
Then you can identify them.
We'll call the cops
and have them locked away.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Boo!
What was that for?
- The live stream ended already!
- [CHUCKLING]
Sorry.
- Oh well.
- [SIGHS HEAVILY]
Are you okay?
I'm just tired.
Really? Tired?
Why don't you believe me?
It's annoying.
You know, if I were you,
I'd talk to him.
What's the real issue?
Nothing.
Really?
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hello, Thea. What's up?
[THEA] Miss Caroline.
Thank goodness
you answered my call.
Your dad has a request.
What is it?
Your dad is requesting
all of you
to attend the family meeting
tomorrow.
Sure.
I'll be there.
Really?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Absolutely.
Thank goodness.
Alright, Miss Caroline.
Take care.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Where's the money?
- I have something better.
These are Caroline's bags
and heels.
I need cash!
You're driving me home?
- It's dangerous.
- Thank you.
- Wait.
- No need to walk me in.
No, hold on.
- What?
- The helmet.
Your father has an important
announcement to make.
I'm opening up the opportunity
for all my children
to inherit my position
as chairman.
As if you have a chance.
Well, you're the one
standing in my way.
Is that why you want me gone?