Where are you going?
Away.
What are you waiting for?
Are you expecting me to stop you?
Where exactly are you going?
I don't know.
Can I stay at the Eclipse?
That's how old people are,
so just leave me alone!
We have to get your eyes checked
before things get worse.
We don't have the money.
Who told you that?
Two hundred thousand pesos
for a pair of eyes.
Are you sure?
Give me 200,000 pesos
and you'll get what you want.
I never thought I would
actually use this money.
Are you nervous? Relax.
We might get in trouble because of you.
You know, it’s dangerous out here.
Especially when you're alone.
-Come with us!
-[SCREAMING]
Snoop?
-Let’s get out of here.
-Why are you here?
Come on! Let’s go!
Hey!
She's getting away!
Sorry, I need to do this.
[COUGHS]
Since you're such a busybody,
I'll bring you along, too.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHISPERING] Ma'am?
Ma'am, are you okay?
Hey!
Ma'am.
I'm just waiting for their advice
on what to do with the girl.
For now, get rid of the boy.
[BERT] Felix, I only agreed to
kidnap the girl for the money
because I need it
for my child's hospital bills!
Now, you're not sure if
her family will pay the ransom?
Killing that boy wasn't even in our plans!
Didn't you hear what I said?
I'm just waiting for our boss' advice.
So, will you just shut up and do as I say?
Or do you want me to shut you up?
[FELIX] Get moving!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[METAL GATE RATTLING]
[HUFFS]
[BERT] You.
-Come with me!
-What?
-[GRUNTS]
-What about her?
Hey!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Bingo, answer the phone!
[PANICKED BREATHING]
-[LINE RINGS]
-Please pick up!
-[PANICKED BREATHING]
-[LINE BUSY]
[BREATH QUIVERING]
[LINE RINGING]
Pick up, Bingo!
Please!
[LINE BUSY]
Sir, maybe we can talk about this.
You need money, right? I have it.
-Shut the hell up!
-I have money.
I heard you didn't want to kill anyone.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
You can have my money.
Just let me have the girl.
Where's the money?
It's in my bag.
Go on, sir. Take it.
And then you can go.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EXHALES LOUDLY, SNIFFLES]
Bert's taking his time.
You're right.
-I'll go take a leak.
-Alright, boss.
[MAN] I'll keep watch here.
-[FELIX] Try calling Bert.
-[MAN] Okay.
[FELIX] Tell him to hurry.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAN] Hello, babe?
[KEY RATTLING]
[MAN] Yeah, I'm still at work.
I can't clock out yet.
I'll call you when I'm on my way home.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MAN] Yeah.
[GRUNTS]
Yes.
Alright, alright.
Yeah. I have to hang up now.
I'll just message you when my shift ends.
Alright, bye.
What did he say?
That wasn't Bert.
I was just about to call him.
Geez, man!
Hurry up and call him!
Hang in there, ma'am.
We're almost outside.
[PANTING]
You're quite heavy.
[MUSIC STING]
Where’s the girl?!
She escaped!
Get up!
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
Let’s go!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAN] She couldn't have gone far, boss!
[FELIX] Get the car!
Come on! Hurry!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAR ENGINE]
[BINGO EXHALES LOUDLY]
[SIGHS IN RELIEF]
Ma'am? Ma'am.
If you don't wake up,
we'll both end up dead.
You're okay, right?
Ma'am?
Are you still breathing? Huh?
She's breathing. Phew!
Okay, that's good.
[GRUNTS, GROANS]
Let’s go.
[MUSIC ENDS]
Where’s Caroline?
She hasn't apologized to the Liaos.
She took her bags and left.
I tried to stop her,
but she still took off.
Right, nanny?
That's right, sir.
Miss Caroline left.
You know your daughter.
Whenever the situation
doesn't favor her, she leaves.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome, ma'am.
I have to talk to her.
I'll make sure she comes back.
I'll freeze her cards.
When she realizes she has
no more money for shopping,
I'm sure she'll come crawling back.
Believe me.
What if…
What if she doesn't come back?
Then that’s good!
That means she can manage on her own.
Wilson, think of it as part
of her training in handling our business.
Isn't that what you're trying to do?
She's your trainee, right?
Not Charleston,
not Bettina,
and definitely not Irene.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
Cindy, she’s still my daughter.
So you must find her
and make sure she’s safe.
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello, Bingo?
[BINGO] Why did you do that?!
[SNOOP] My aunt really needs money
and my family is getting
evicted from their place.
[BINGO] Why didn't you tell me?
[SNOOP] I'm sorry, alright?
But what if she wakes up
and reports me to the cops?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNOOP] We should've left her in a hotel.
[BINGO] A hotel?
You think they'd let us leave
an unconscious woman there?
You should've asked her where she lives.
Dude, she’s unconscious!
How would I ask her?
What about her friends?
She has friends, right?!
We don't even know her name.
How would we know her friends?
Get the keys. It's under that pot.
Hurry.
[KEYS JANGLING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNOOP] You should've left her
in an abandoned lot…
[DOOR CLOSES]
…or dumped her in the river.
[BINGO] Are you crazy?
I can't do that.
Besides, she still owes me
200,000 pesos for her life.
That money was for Grandma!
But how would you explain this to Grandma?
You brought home a girl
you don't even know--
[NENE] Bingo!
Is that you?
-[LOUD THUD]
-[NENE] Oh!
What was that sound?!
Who's that with you?
That… That was just Snoop!
-His… His knee just hit…
-[SNOOP GROANS]
some of our items for delivery.
[SLURRING] I'm sorry, Grandma.
I'm kind of…
I'm kind of drunk right now.
You two are unbelievable!
Why did you stay up drinking again?
-We got carried away.
-[NENE] Fine.
I'll make you some coffee.
-No!
-Don't!
-Huh?
-Uh…
No… No need, Grandma.
You see…
Um…
It’s too early for coffee.
Just go back to sleep.
-What?
-Go on, Grandma.
Just go back to bed and stay in your room.
It's still dark outside.
Okay?
Goodnight!
Goodnight, Grandma!
Snoop will go home in a bit.
[SNOOP SLURRING]
Thanks for having me, Grandma!
I love you!
-What do we do with her?
-Lift her up.
-I'll hold her legs.
-One, two, three.
-[GROANS]
-Up.
Okay.
-Where should we put her?
-I don't know.
Let's take her to the room.
-Which one?
-My room.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNOOP, BINGO HUFFING]
Here?
No, that's Papi's bed. Over here.
Where is he anyway?
He'll be back in the morning.
I hope she wakes up before Papi returns.
Are we done here?
I better go.
Hey, are you serious?
You'll leave the two of us here?
It's not like I'd be of any help.
Besides, if she wakes up
and recognizes me, I'll be dead meat.
-Dude, come on.
-No, no. Good luck, man.
Don't leave! Snoop!
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
Ma'am.
Ma'am?
[SNAPS, CLAPS]
Hey, ma'am!
Hello!
[CLAPS]
Ma'am?
Ma'am.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma'am?
You're still alive, right?
Hey.
[SNAPS]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
She’s still breathing.
[SIGHS]
What the hell did you take?
Why won't you wake up?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
-[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
-[GROANS]
As a good chairman,
I should let my constituents
know about it.
But should I just
trust Bingo to do it himself?
Or should I do it myself…
…as a good chairman?
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE CHIMES]
Guys! Good morning!
There's a new face in town because…
Bingo brought home a girl!
A girl?!
Bingo?!
Oh, no!
How lucky!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[KETTLE WHISTLING]
Mom, hasn't Bingo gotten out of bed yet?
He and Snoop stayed up late drinking.
Mom? Mom?
What are you doing?
I'm trying out these cosmetics
before selling them.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You're my kidnapper!
No! No!
No.
And I'm in your hideout!
No! What hideout?
We're… We're at my place.
Help!
-Somebody, help--
-Hey!
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
-[CAROLINE SCREAMING]
-A girl?
-[MUFFLED SCREAMS]
-Don't shout please!
[GRUNTS]
[CAROLINE] Help me, please! Help!
Can you please stop--
-It's really a girl!
Don't shout!
Stop that! They might get the wrong idea!
-[MUFFLED CRIES]
-Can you please not shout?!
[BINGO] They'll hear you! You're so loud!
[BOTH GASPING]
-[BINGO GASPS]
-[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
-Why are you on top of her?!
-No, Dad, um…
It's not what it looks like.
-But, why are you…
-Get off of her!
[BINGO] She was shouting.
Don't talk, okay?
Promise me you won't talk.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You're the mastermind!
Huh?
[LAUGHS AWKWARDLY]
No, no, no!
-No!
-Hey!
Who are you calling a mastermind?
[BINGO] They're my grandma and my dad!
-Yes.
-Will you just relax?
Who is she?
Just who is she?
I'm the victim of your grandson.
He kidnapped me!
-Huh?!
-You… You kidnapped her?!
No, no! Kidnap?!
I saved her from her kidnappers!
I didn't kidnap you!
And you expect me to believe you?
Yes, because I'm telling the truth!
-There you go.
-[BINGO] I swear!
-See?
Listen,
if I really did kidnap you,
don't you think I would've
tied you up at least?
-He's right!
-Correct!
What for?
I don't even stand a chance
against all of you.
[SCOFFS]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
-Mommy…
-We're not bad people!
Heck, I just got here!
What are you talking about?
Okay, if I were your kidnapper,
shouldn't I have brought you
to a discreet place
instead of my house?
-He's right!
-Didn't you realize that?
-[BINGO] We're in my house!
-Right!
-Yes!
-This is our house!
-She's not thinking straight.
-Yeah.
But what if you're lying?
What if this is really your hideout?
-Huh?
-Hideout?
This has been our beloved
home for 30 years now!
Come here!
Follow me!
-Go with him!
-Come here!
After compromising my marriage,
she'll just disappear on us?
What can I do? She left on her own.
Caroline will show up eventually.
By then, I should have a plan
on how I can force her to apologize.
Bettina, you don't have to do anything.
I've already cut her finances.
And you know her.
When she gets desperate,
she'll do anything.
Okay?
So, please relax.
Thanks, Mom.
[BINGO] Come here! Look!
We have a legitimate business!
We sell clothes and underwear,
both in Ongpin and online.
And here's my graduation picture!
My medals, photos of my dad
and my grandma…
Our family pictures.
What do you think?
Is there a hideout that
has family pictures?
Still,
they don't prove anything.
You guys could be paid actors, right?
-Oh?
-[BOTH LAUGH]
How I wish!
We got a lot of offers, but we're too shy.
We're not paid actors!
Your imagination is so wild!
And your excuse is too lame.
That last thing I remember
was me getting kidnapped,
and you were there.
Because I happened to be there!
That's why I saved you!
But what were you doing there?
Why were you there?
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Grandma, um…
I was supposed to meet someone
there, but he didn't show up.
How convenient.
I'm telling the truth!
I heard you shouting while
you were being kidnapped.
You fell down into the water,
so I jumped in there to save you.
Huh?
Wow, you're my hero!
So, you fell down into the water.
Don't you remember that?
It's all hazy to be honest.
But it must be coming back to you now.
I don't remember you saving me.
Well, of course.
Because you were unconscious
after falling into the water.
Hold on…
Could they have drugged her?
That's possible, Dad.
That's why I've been telling you…
that I'm not your kidnapper!
Besides, you're the one who owes me!
-I owe you?
-[BINGO] Yes!
I paid one of the kidnappers
200,000 pesos for your release!
You have that much money?
Had!
So, you have to pay me back!
-You had 200,000 pesos?
-Where did you get that?
[CAROLINE] You see?
Even they can't believe you.
That's right, Grandma, but…
it doesn't matter how I got it.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hmm…
So…
Is this the new mode of
operation for kidnappers?
Hmm…
You'll get kidnapped,
then, they'll say they rescued you.
You should've just made it
a two-million ransom,
so your story will be more believable.
Whatever. I'm done with you!
This is so frustrating!
From the start, you just
decided we're bad people,
despite the fact I helped and saved you!
Because it's all not adding up!
Let's switch places, okay?
Would you believe that I saved you,
just because I said so
without having any proof?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma'am, I saved you.
Cross my heart.
[NENE] I believe you, Bingo.
Thank you, Grandma.
Look, I'm not asking for
your gratefulness.
But the money… I need it back.
It's for something important.
My gosh!
This is so ridiculous!
[SIGHS]
[CAROLINE] But fine! Okay!
200 thousand pesos, you said?
Okay! I'll get it.
-Let's go, then!
-Okay! Let's get to it!
Hold it!
[NENE] Um, young lady…
Don't you want to freshen up a little?
Don't you want to wash
your face or shower?
How about coffee?
So you'd feel better and…
-fresh.
-Mm-hm.
How about it?
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
-Wait… Wait…
-Follow me!
Didn't I tell you to wait for me?
Where's the money? The donor is ready.
About that…
You didn't show up.
Also, something happened.
Are you messing with me?!
Look, I really want to help my grandma.
But something came up,
and I had to use the money.
Listen, boy, I don't like jokes.
-I don't play games!
-[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay. Just give me some time.
I'll just collect the money
from the person I used it for.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're the mastermind!
-Huh?
-What?
You're the mastermind!
Huh?!
They were trying to kidnap you
when you fell into the water.
And I saved your life.
I don't remember you saving me.
I'm not your kidnapper!
In fact, you owe me!
I paid one of the kidnappers
200 thousand for your release!
Is this the new mode of
operation for kidnappers?
Fine. 200,000? I'll get it.
I need one thousand.
That much for your cab fare?
Just put in on my tab.
-How will I know you'll return?
-Because I said so.
["YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE"
BY JANINE TENOSO PLAYS]
-Who's that man?
-Oh my god, it hurts!
Where are you going?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]