[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Get me more.
There's no need for a tip.
I'll get you another.
Welcome, everyone,
to Edward and Bettina's engagement party.
Isn't the girl in black
the third wife's daughter?
You just can't help it, can you?
Wearing that stupid, ugly dress.
I'm just honoring my mom's death.
Why don't you just do what she did?
Kill yourself.
[SCREAMS] Ah!
Don't talk about my mom like that!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
-What the hell?
-Oh my God.
Caroline?
You're even trying to steal my fiancé.
Why would I be surprised?
Your mother was also a snake!
Well, if you really want to know,
I saw him kissing your best friend.
You're making up stories again!
Who do you think you are?!
-Caroline!
-She's gone.
Find her!
Caroline does this every November 17.
She acts out during
her mom's death anniversary.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
-Congrats, Bingo!
He was hit by a bus.
-What?!
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
I don't need money.
I only want you to be healthy and alive.
It pains me to see you getting hurt.
[SLAPS]
Bettina! Stop that!
Caroline! Apologize to the Liao.
Let's put an end to this.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
-This one? Alright.
-They want this one.
This item will make you feel sexy.
You will surely catch
everyone's attention.
-Look at that.
-Mm!
-What are you waiting for?
-Order now!
Just comment "Mine Fuchsia"
if you want this item.
If you can't spell fuchsia,
just comment "Mine Pink."
-"Mine Pink."
-Go type "Mine Pink."
Monda69 got the item.
Monda69, this item is now yours.
Thank you.
Please take a screenshot
-in three, two, one.
-Take a screenshot.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, Monda69.
[BOUGIE] Okay.
-[ADORA] Okay, next item!
-[BOUGIE] There you go!
-[BOUGIE] Let's keep going.
-[ADORA] Alright.
-[BOUGIE] Wow!
-[ADORA] Wow!
[BOUGIE] This is so pretty.
-[ADORA] Of course.
-[BOUGIE] Super.
[BELL RINGING]
Oh! [CLAPS] There it is!
Our bell has rung.
It's…
-Bundle time!
[CLAPS]
Bro, I heard your gig didn't go well.
Does that mean I can't
borrow money from you?
Bro.
You still owe me.
-[LIVE SELLING ONGOING]
-[SCOFFS]
You see, my mother needs extra cash.
We're in a tight spot.
Is it for your mom, or…
is it to take Florencia on a date?
[SCOFFS] Well,
of course that's part of it.
[SNOOP] Come on.
[LIVE SELLING ONGOING]
[CHUCKLES] I got another side hustle!
-Really?
-[SNOOP] Yeah.
So you'll pay off your debts?
[BOUGIE] Someone posted "Mine!"
It's Monda69!
-It's Monda69 again!
-You're not paying attention!
-Hang on!
-Monda69, this is yours now.
-Pay attention!
-[ADORA] You get this bundle.
Please take a screenshot
in three, two, one.
Thank you so much.
Monda69 has bought a lot already!
-Thank you so much.
-Thank you.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Where are you going?
Away.
Are you running away?
Basically.
What are you waiting for?
Are you expecting me to stop you?
Go.
[CINDY] Prepare my jasmine tea.
The new one.
-[MAID] Yes, ma'am.
-[CINDY] Thank you.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey, miss!
-I'm offering you a good price.
-Adora!
-[ADORA] Over here. Set it up inside.
-[HORN HONKING]
[BOUGIE] Bingo! Bingo!
Grandma! Let's take a break.
Excuse me.
-[MAN] Okay, okay.
-Let's eat! Do that later.
-[BINGO] Is it delicious?
-[BOUGIE] Of course.
-[BOUGIE] Come on, let's eat.
-[BINGO] I'll buy drinks.
[BOUGIE] Get me coconut juice.
Bingo! Bingo! Bingo!
-Yes?
-Get me a jelly cooler.
Alright.
-[CROWD NOISE]
-[HORN HONKING]
-[GLASSES FALL]
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
Ouch!
Grandma!
-Grandma!
What happened?
-Let us help you.
-Where are my glasses?
-I'll take that.
-Let's get up.
You should've asked for our help.
-One, two, three, up.
-Careful.
[BOUGIE] Bingo!
-Bingo! Bingo!
-Yes?
Your grandma got into an accident!
-What?
-[BOUGIE] Come on!
-Hurry!
-What accident?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[DRIVER] To the airport, ma'am?
Yes.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BINGO] I keep telling you
to have your eyes checked.
Look what happened, Papi.
We have to get her checked.
You're just overreacting.
What do you mean?
Let me remind you, Ma.
At your age, you should
take your health seriously.
It's a good thing it wasn't serious.
[BINGO] That's right.
Why can't you accept the truth
that I'm already old?
That's how old people are!
So just leave me alone!
[BINGO] What are you saying?
We have to get your eyes checked
before things get worse.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Grandma, just rest for a while.
Papi and I will do the work. Right, Papi?
Bingo, we don't have any money.
Who told you that?
You know me.
I'll find a way to earn money
for your eye check-up.
Okay?
I'll find a way.
Whatever.
[MUSIC FADES]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Dude.
You're Bingo, right?
Yes.
I heard you're looking
for a donor for your grandma.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why?
[MAN] The airport system is down, ma'am.
All flights are delayed.
All flights?
[SIGHS]
My gosh, how third world.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHARLESTON] Oh. How are you?
[CAROLINE] I'm fine. I left home.
Well, you've been planning to
for a while now.
Yeah.
Can I stay at the Eclipse?
There's a power outage at the airport.
They're delaying all flights.
Where exactly are you going?
[CAROLINE] I don't know.
Anywhere.
Two hundred thousand, final price.
If it's an eye you need.
Are you sure?
It's the cheapest you'll get.
Where is it from?
No questions asked.
As long as you have 200,000 pesos,
you'll get what you need.
Find the money.
Once you have it, let me know
so we can get things ready.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[LUGGAGE ROLLING]
[MAN] We've prepared the yacht, ma'am.
Okay.
You can leave once we arrive.
Don't tell anyone I'm here.
Okay, ma'am.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Slowly, Ma. Take it easy.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
Does it hurt?
I'll get going, Grandma. Papi.
Join us for dinner.
-Where are you off to?
-I'm going.
-Take a seat here.
-Where is he--
Where is he going? What is he up to?
He withdrew some cash earlier.
What for?
He said he'll get you new eyes.
What?!
Where? On the streets? Or online?
[CHUCKLES]
Let's eat.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[NEIGHBOR 1] How unfortunate that boy is.
To have that kind
of irresponsible parents.
His mother left him.
And his father was a drug addict.
[NEIGHBOR 2] What will happen to him?
We should get help from social services.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hold on, mister.
[SNIFFLES]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HAMMERING]
[SOBBING]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Andrei…
Keep this, son.
It's the only thing I can leave you with.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I never thought I would
actually use this money.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
Where are you? I'm here now.
Give me a minute. I'm on my way.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
Hey.
Do you have a lighter?
No. I don't smoke.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you alone?
Huh?
I'm waiting for someone.
You know…
It's dangerous here.
Especially when…
you're alone.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGING]
Sir Edward,
Miss Bettina is here.
Yes, sir.
Ma'am!
I'll accompany you to Sir Edward's office.
He's just in a meeting right now.
You weren't taking my calls,
so I decided to come here.
Edward…
I was thinking about
what Caroline said, and--
How many times do I have to tell you?
Please…
stop getting the wrong ideas.
But then, why would Caroline say--
So, you'd rather believe your sister…
than trust me,
your future husband.
No, no, no. Of course not.
Papa is forcing Caroline to apologize.
Then, good.
My dad told me…
to postpone the wedding.
Bettina, I’m sorry.
Unless your family apologizes to mine…
we have to hold the wedding.
Do you understand?
Yes.
[SIGHS]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
What's up?
[KNOCKS ON WINDOW]
Meet Snoop.
Boss.
Are you sure we can trust him?
Didn't we agree that
he'll just be our driver?
[LINE RINGING]
Paps, we're good.
We're all set.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay.
[CLEARS THROAT] Let's go.
Come on.
Hey. Are you nervous?
Relax.
We might get into trouble because of you.
Sorry, boss.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[METAL GATE CLANGS]
[GATE OPENS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
-Let's go.
-[COCKS GUN]
Come on!
[DOOR LOCK CLICKS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GASPS]
-Come with us!
-[SCREAMS]
Stop resisting!
[CAROLINE] Help!
Hey! Don't just stand there!
-Help us!
-Hurry!
[CAROLINE SCREAMING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CLICKS TONGUE]
-[CAROLINE SCREAMING]
-[KIDNAPPERS GRUNTING]
[KIDNAPPER] Snoop!
Bro?
-Bro, let's get out of here!
-What are you doing here?
Hey! Answer me! Why are you here?
[PANTING]
I got myself into trouble.
Let's get out of here!
What do you mean? Hey!
-Focus!
-Let's get out of here!
Snoop, what’s going on here?
[CAROLINE SCREAMING]
Hurry! We gotta leave now!
[KIDNAPPER] Hey!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
-[CAROLINE GRUNTS]
-Ah!
[GRUNTS, SCREAMS]
Ouch!
[KIDNAPPER] Hey!
She's getting away!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC RESUMES]
-What are we going to do?!
-Damn it!
We're in big trouble!
Jump into the water and look for her!
I'll deal with that boy!
What? Why me?
You let her get away, so you find her!
This isn't looking good!
Never mind, let's go!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WATER SPLASHING]
[GROANS SOFTLY]
Ma'am?
Ma'am, are you okay?
Ma'am? Ma'am?
Ma'am, wake up!
Ma'am!
What happened to you? Hey!
Ma'am, wake up! Hey!
What happened to you?
Ma'am!
[PANTING]
Wake up! Hey!
Ma'am!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Sorry, I need to do this.
[BLOWS AIR INTO MOUTH]
-[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
-[PANTING]
Ma'am!
[COUGHS]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
Since you're a busybody,
I'll bring you along too.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma'am, wake up!
Sorry, I need to do this.
[COUGHS]
Since you're a busybody,
I'll bring you along too.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I need money! My kid's in the hospital!
I heard you don't want to kill.
Just take my money and
return the woman to me.
He escaped!
Hang in there, ma'am!
After them! Let's go!
["YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE"
BY JANINE TENOSO PLAYS]
Help! Please!
Help! They kidnapped me!
[MUFFLED SCREAMS]
-A woman's voice?
-They'll hear you!
What's going on here?
What are you doing to her?!