Hey, Bingo! Why did you
bring home a girl like that?
-Why? What happened?
-Who does she think she is, huh?
Grandma, where's Ling?
She's not here.
I've already looked around.
She probably went out for some fresh air.
You startled me! What are you doing?!
I thought you were someone else!
Babe, I'm sorry, okay?
I won't do it again.
Come on, Ling!
Didn't I tell you not to go out?!
What if something bad happened to you?!
You know someone's after you!
That Edward is despicable!
What are you gonna do now?
For goodness' sake, Koriks!
-Who owns it?!
-He's a big shot!
-Tell us who!
-General!
-General?
It must be Irene.
It's Irene.
Where does Irene usually hang out?
She's an alcoholic.
She loves getting wasted.
And that's when you come in.
Nothing good ever comes
from drinking alcohol.
Just let her talk, or get her phone.
You're really turning me
into a thief, huh?
For Irene, alcohol is her savior.
That's why we're going to practice.
Here's what we're gonna do.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Take note of the private
helicopter I requested.
It's non-negotiable. Don't forget.
Mr. Liao, I surely won't forget
because you've mentioned it
many times already.
[LAUGHS] Okay.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Good morning, everyone.
My apologies for the wait.
But I'll keep this short.
I'd like to announce…
that we're ending our
partnership with the Liaos.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
That would be all. Thank you so much.
Have a great day.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
And who do you think you are?!
It's purely business, Albert.
[ALBERT] I can destroy Charleston
and Bettina,
your useless daughter!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Never speak about my family
in that manner!
[LAUGHING]
Wilson, Wilson, Wilson!
You talk as if
you're such a good family man!
You know what's funny?
You're a womanizer, just like my son.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
But the thing is,
I didn't use them.
I wonder who influenced Edward
to use them to his advantage,
especially in business.
I will make sure
that Charleston will rot in jail!
Go ahead.
File a case.
Let's drag this out in public, Albert.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Put it there where everyone can see it.
Hey, hey. It's slanted. Adjust it.
-Perfect!
-Grand drinking party?
He'll treat everyone in
Barangay 143 to drinks?
They drink alcohol like it's water.
-Gee, that's so generous of Mr. Cortez.
-Yeah!
It was really nice of him
to invite everybody.
It's his thanksgiving for his second life.
Are we also invited?
Yeah. Just bring some gifts.
Oh, I see. He wants gifts.
I see what it is now.
The gifts aren't for Mr. Cortez.
They're for me.
It's my birthday, remember?
-Oh!
-[BIERNA LAUGHS]
-I forgot.
-Me too.
-So, it's a gift-giving event.
-Get ready because…
we'll be drinking all day.
-Wow!
What are we going to drink?
Anything! Sky's the limit!
[BINGO SIGHS]
What's this?
It's gin.
I thought you were a drinker.
I never said that.
It's cheap,
but it hits hard.
Fine, this will do.
[NENE] Hi!
-Hey!
-Hey! What's that?
Why are you drinking?
Do you have a problem?
Come here. Let's talk about it.
It's too early to be drinking!
Grandma, Papa, it's not what you think.
Um… We just want to try it.
There's this new trend, you see.
Alcohol with… candy.
Ling, you forgot about it.
She forgot to buy candy.
There's no candy.
Candy? Goodness…
[NENE] Oh, you two.
It's too early to be drinking.
I can do the task,
with or without alcohol.
I got this.
-[NENE] Kids these days…
-I don't think so.
Are you sure?
What kind of trend is that?
If you're gonna drink,
you should know the drill.
Here… let me show you.
Listen up. First,
add freshly-squeezed
lime juice to your booze
and to your drinking glasses.
And then, pour--
-What are you doing?!
-Ouch!
You're teaching them to become drinkers?!
I'm just teaching them the proper way--
What proper way?! This isn't allowed!
They shouldn't be drinking yet!
Stop this, you two.
If you have a problem,
let's talk about it.
Let's settle it instead of drinking.
Put those away! No drinking allowed!
[MONCHING] You heard your grandma.
[NENE] Stop it.
Instead of drinking in broad daylight,
just help me sort out these things.
Ah, it hurts…
Pa.
Edward! Come here!
-Come here!
-[MARIETTA] Albert!
Albert! Stop!
You deserve worse than that!
-Stop!
-Stop! Stop!
You had one job!
One job!
You're so stupid!
Bah!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm sorry.
[CINDY] Everything will be alright.
Wilson.
We've fought so many battles.
But look at us.
We're still here.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[JERSEY] So, I just need to
get Irene to notice your guy?
Is he the same guy I lent clothes to?
Yes, and yes.
They only need to meet.
Ugh… Fine.
Where is he?
He should be there by now.
Where?
You won't miss him. He's…
tall,
[CLUB MUSIC PLAYING]
dark,
and…
Handsome! Spotted!
Really?
Really, really, really!
Okay.
[CLUB MUSIC PLAYING]
[WOMAN 1] Girl, look!
[WOMAN 2] Oh!
-[WOMAN 1] OMG.
-[WOMAN 3] He's cute.
[PHONE RINGING]
-Hi!
You look cute!
[WOMEN GIGGLING]
-What do you think?
-He's cute!
-Let's go?
-Let's go!
[CAROLINE] Again, remember
not to talk too much.
[CAROLINE] Let her talk.
Play hard to get.
Hi, baby!
-Oh, he's taken.
-Sorry.
[BINGO] I'm talking to my babe.
What?
Let's go, girls.
He's taken.
Sorry about that.
I had to make those girls leave me.
Oh, wow.
Anyway, remember all
the information you'll gather.
Better yet, get her phone.
Sure, if I can get it
without feeling guilty.
Because that's theft.
Are you nervous?
Don't be nervous.
You're telling me to
snatch someone's phone.
Why wouldn't I be nervous?
But…
Do you think she'll remember me?
Don't worry. Once she gets wasted,
she won't remember a thing the next day.
Also, Jersey will be there for you.
Jersey? Where is she?
Anyway, I'm hanging up.
[CAROLINE] Wait.
Thanks.
What was that, baby girl?
-[CLEARS THROAT]
-Thanks for doing this.
[CLUB MUSIC PLAYING]
Anything to get my money back.
Oh wait, last thing.
[BINGO] What now?
Can I see your…
teeth?
Huh?
You're creepy.
Come on. Let me see.
-There might be…
-Particles?
[COMICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
-Okay. Good.
-I've got none.
Irene gets turned off easily by bad breath
and poor oral hygiene.
Just ask Jersey for a mint.
I don't have bad breath either.
Okay.
I hope this works.
I have a favor to ask.
Don't go out.
Hopefully, I'll be back…
with all the answers to your questions.
Okay.
Thanks again.
Okay, baby girl. See you later.
Bye.
So…
You're Ling's man?
Jersey?
The alluring Jersey.
So, how do we pull this off?
Just leave it all to me.
All I have to do is
make you and Irene meet.
[HOST] Ladies and gentlemen,
Queen Irene!
[CROWD CHEERING]
What's up? Hi!
Hey, just have fun. Don't worry about me.
The witch has arrived.
What am I supposed to do?
Just trust me.
Is that your tagline
or your best friend's?
[CLUB MUSIC PLAYING]
-Are you ready?
-No.
[IRENE] Have fun, have fun!
I'll see you later.
Oh my gosh!
You naughty, naughty boy!
-Is that Jersey?
-My dress!
Bettina, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. Please.
Please, just forgive me.
I swear, it won't happen again.
I swear to God!
If you want, let's get married.
We can do it now.
I'll do everything for you. Please.
No!
That's not for you to decide, Edward.
From now on,
you will never lay a hand on me.
Yes.
Never.
I will never do it again.
I swear, Bettina.
Well, what about Liv?
Liv?
I'll forget about Liv.
She's out of my life now.
I swear. I promise.
Good.
Then the wedding is on.
[EDWARD] Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[IRENE] Jersey!
You're here! Again.
-[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
I thought I already talked
to security about this.
Leave.
If I'm leaving,
so is he.
No.
He can stay.
-[CHUCKLES]
-[BINGO CLEARS THROAT]
If he's staying, then I'm staying.
And he's all yours.
Perfect.
[JERSEY] I'm going to be invisible.
Have fun.
Have fun!
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello, Ma. What's up?
When are you coming home?
I told you I'll be home at Christmas.
Just wait for me.
Can't you come home sooner?
I might die before
we see each other again.
Don't joke about that. It's not funny.
You're going to be okay.
Just don't forget to take
your meds and vitamins.
Alright.
Make sure you're eating properly, okay?
[SNOOP] Yes, Ma.
I'm just a little busy here.
You see, my friend needs me.
But I promise I'll be home soon.
Bye, Ma.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNOOP] Follow that car.
[ENGINE REVVING]
-[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
-[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hi.
Can I have your name?
Ramon.
[CHUCKLES] Ramon? Really?
You don't look like a Ramon.
What's your full name?
Ramon…
Devilla.
I'm from Quezon City.
I work as a--
Skip it.
What do you want, Ramon?
Do you want anything?
Do you want a chip?
I'm good, thank you.
-Are you sure?
-All yours.
Okay.
[ALLURING MUSIC PLAYING]
You know what?
Your name really throws me off.
It sounds so tacky.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm going to call you Ram for short.
[ALLURING MUSIC CONTINUES]
So, what do you want, Ram?
I want a bad girl.
[LAUGHS]
Why is your face like that?
You're so weird!
-Are you a bad girl?
-Oh, yeah.
But you wouldn't want know.
You might throw me in jail.
So, my lips are…
[LIPS SMACK]
-[KNIFE SHARPENING]
-[WATER RUNNING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GLASS CLINKING]
[SIGHS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WOMAN] Hey. I'm back.
Miss Melba let me in.
What brings you here, Pato?
I got these for you.
I'll cook your favorite.
Wait.
You're alone? Where are the kids?
I sent them on some errands.
They're on their way back.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Then I'll get cooking.
[CHUCKLES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[LINE RINGING]
[LINE BUSY]
I want to party and get drunk
until I'm wasted!
If your boy is trying to get
Irene drunk, he's failing.
You said you don't drink,
but it seems you're having fun.
Why do you keep calling?
I want an update.
Are you jealous?
Where are the kids?
I sent them on some errands.
The GL Bank app was hacked.
Many accounts have been compromised.
Did you manage to trace the hacker?
I'll make you coffee.
Where's Bingo? He didn't come home?
He's young and single.
Maybe he went out to have fun.
-You're drunk and--
-No.
Just admit it! You don't want me.
You're just like everyone else!
-No, no--
-You don't want me!
Wilson Tiu is your father?