Do you really think you can find Pato?
In life, there are things
I didn't try to search for.
But that Pato, I'll find her.
Are your eyes still open?
No. I was about to close them.
You have to step down as president
and CEO of your company.
Why don't I replace Wilson?
You are a mistress.
No one in this family will replace Wilson.
Her nickname is Pato.
She's a bit jumpy. Is that her?
That's her. That's her, Bingo.
Where can we find her?
All I know is she's staying
on Urbiztondo Street.
But what's important is that now I know
that the Pato who lives in that apartment
is the Pato I'm looking for.
Let's talk later. Miss Cathy is mad.
- What?
- Tony!
How much longer do I have to wait?
I'm sorry for being late.
Miss Cathy, wait!
- Ouch.
- Ah!
- [GROANS]
- Oh!
Are you okay?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[CATHY] Caroline!
What are you doing?
Are you training or not?
You weren't here when I arrived.
Miss Cathy.
I gave her permission.
Bingo.
What? It's true.
Auntie, I know I'm late,
and I'm sorry for that,
but Bingo wouldn't have gotten
hurt if you hadn't done that!
And if that's the kind
of training you want--
I was mad because problems
have been piling up
here in the warehouse.
Sales are down.
If it doesn't improve,
we might have to close down.
I came here to discuss your presentation,
because you had brilliant ideas.
And since you're young,
you might have new ideas that could help.
But you weren't here.
Never mind.
Just go back to work.
Bingo, you come with me.
I want to talk to you before I leave.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
This is preposterous.
What will people think?
That no one from this family can step up?
We need someone compassionate,
good-looking, charismatic.
One who can garner sympathy.
[LAUGHING SARCASTICALLY]
Why don't you get an actor, then?
That will fit every one
of your qualifications.
Because as far as I'm concerned,
everyone here has their own secrets.
And one day, they might come to light.
Enough!
Gina, will you please cooperate?
We're talking about family business here.
And whatever decision we make here,
it also concerns you.
[CINDY] That's why I suggest…
that you and Carlo refrain
from causing a stir.
[GINA] Cause a stir, you say?
Why don't you ask your child?
Because for sure,
there's another big surprise
that's about to come.
What are you talking about?
Who are you referring to?
Gina, come back!
Wilson, let her go.
She's like an empty can.
Her words are nothing
but meaningless noise.
Let her be.
Where did she go? Why is she late?
Um…
It's a long story, Miss Cathy.
But she went to meet this person
who might know things about her past.
And?
Did she learn anything?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Did she get an answer to her questions?
[TONY] Um, Miss C.
Yes?
- You tell her.
- You do it.
Go ahead.
Bingo, you know that I didn't hire you
to solve Ling's personal issues.
I know that, Miss Cathy.
But when I saw her scared and in tears…
I wanted to know what was going on.
What really happened to her.
And also, since there was a chance,
I wanted to show her that I care for her.
Isn't that the best example?
The best training?
Be the best example of companionship.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Is there something you want to say?
Actually, there is.
But this may not be
a good time since he's--
No, no. I think
it's the perfect time, Miss C.
Um…
We would like to thank you.
And to apologize as well.
For judging you harshly
after the theft incident.
And for other things.
[TONY] But if it weren't for that,
and for what you did,
maybe there would still be other victims
of Kida's schemes aside from Neco.
She could've used other
people and lockers too.
That's why we would like
to thank you, Miss C.
Thank you, too.
We'll return to our station now, Miss C.
We'll get back to work.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE STARTING]
- [BINGO] Take care.
- [CATHY] Okay.
Let's go. We're leaving.
[GROANS]
- [DRIVER] Are we leaving?
- Yes, we are.
Didn't you hear me? Come on. Let's move.
[DOOR ALARM BEEPING]
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
Ma'am, it won't start.
I think it's a battery problem.
What?
Try it again.
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
Ma'am, it just won't start.
[DOOR ALARM BEEPS]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing here?
Car problems?
Hey, can you step outside?
[DOOR ALARM BEEPING]
I already warned you to stay out of it.
But you just won't listen.
I don't care
if you're my brother's mother.
If you won't stop…
you might end up like Divine.
- I can sue you for this.
- On what grounds?
Don't use the law to scare me,
because we're all in this together.
Even Carlo, your son.
So, if I were you…
I would shut the hell up.
[DOOR ALARM BEEPS]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GROANS]
Bingo.
Are you okay?
Yeah, of course.
It's nothing. Don't worry.
Where did Auntie hit you?
Ling, it's nothing.
It's no big deal.
- Is it here?
- Ouch!
As I thought.
Can I see?
Ling, this is nothing. I'm fine.
There might be a wound
or a bruise. Let me see.
- I said it's nothing.
- Just let me check, Bingo.
Come on.
Please.
[SIGHS]
- Seriously?
- Just let me check, Bingo.
It's nothing. See?
["YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING]
- See?
- I can't--
- I can't see.
- There's nothing to see.
You know what? Just take off your shirt.
What?
Take off your shirt.
- Bingo.
- Okay, okay, fine.
Taking it off now.
I'm telling you, it's nothing.
No wounds or anything. It's no big deal.
Look.
See? There’s nothing.
- "Nothing"? What is this?
- It's nothing.
It's red.
It's just minor.
It's not minor.
It might turn into a bruise.
You have to put ice on this.
Does it hurt here?
Or here?
A little.
So it hurts?
[SIGHS]
It might bruise.
["YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE"
INSTRUMENTAL CONTINUES]
Why are you holding my hand?
- I'm not holding it.
- Yes, you are.
- I am holding it.
- Then why are you holding it?
- Pato?
- Pato. Pato. Um…
- Huh?
The…
The landlady? Have you talked to her?
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, uh, about that,
you don't have to worry.
It's a dead end anyway.
But we should keep looking.
I'll help you.
Bingo, I'm really thankful
for all your help,
but I'll take it from here.
Okay, just wait for me.
I'll get you some ice.
What?
Ling, why?
Because I don't want
to cause you anymore trouble.
- Ling--
- Look what happened with you and Auntie.
You're not causing me trouble.
And you're most certainly
not a burden to me.
["YOU'LL BE SAFE HERE"
INSTRUMENTAL PLAYING]
Ah, what I mean is…
it's no trouble at all.
That's it.
That's what I mean.
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- Well, okay.
I'm grateful for all your help.
Really.
But, Bingo, I can do it alone.
Wait for me. I'll get you some ice.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
There.
Miss Cathy wants you to clean them.
Everything?
[STAMMERS] Here,
why don't you just kill me?
That'll be so much better.
Oh, spare me the drama.
They're just octopi.
Wha… Octopi?
What's octopi?
Yes. Oc-to-pi.
And this octopus says…
- "Clean me!"
- [QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
- [LAUGHING]
- No, no, no, no.
I can't. I can't.
Sorry, I really can't.
Gosh, quit being so fussy.
That's what Miss Cathy ordered.
- Now, get to it. I'm busy.
- No, no, Cristine, help me.
You'll be fine.
Hey, hey, hey, you do it.
- I'm on my break.
- It's my break, too!
I need a break!
[SHRIEKING]
Oh, no, no, no.
[IRENE WHIMPERS]
Smells so bad.
[SQUEALS]
I can't, I can't, I can't, I really can't.
No way, I can't. I can't.
I'm going to die.
I'm going to freaking die.
[PUFFING]
[PHONE RINGING]
[CHUCKLING]
What?
Now, you're calling me?
Poop. Poop, I need my cognac now.
Like, right now. Bring it to me now.
They're staring at me, Poop.
I thought you didn't
want to see me ever again?
You're just going to buy.
I didn't say we need to meet.
Just do it. I'll pay you.
[SCOFFS] Pay?
You still haven't paid me from last time.
Poop, please.
Please, Poop, I'm like, imploring you.
I'm begging you. Don't be so heartless.
[SCOFFS] You have the nerve
to say I'm heartless.
Look, you're just going to leave the booze
in the location,
and I'll leave the 5,000 there.
And then another 5,000 for today.
How about that?
No.
No way.
I have a part-time job, okay?
And you're not my priority.
You know, just pay me
the 5,000 you owe.
Then we're all good.
Fine.
I'll pay you what that
part-time thingy of yours pays.
Whatever that costs you,
I'll double it. How about that?
[LAUGHING]
You're crazy, you know that?
You think I'm that desperate for money?
Yeah.
You're like, really poor.
You're almost a beggar.
Poop, I know you need the money, right?
Money.
Whatever! Forget you!
Poop!
[ANNOYED GRUNT]
Where is Carlo? Is he here yet?
Not yet, ma'am.
Damn it!
- [GLASS BREAKS]
- Ah!
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BREATHING DEEPLY]
[CHARLESTON] I already
warned you to stay out of it.
If you don't stop,
you might end up like Divine.
[SOBBING]
[LING] What do I do with these?
I need to sell you all.
Because if what Auntie said is true,
this warehouse will probably close down.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Right. Bingo's the answer.
[BINGO] Why is she looking at me?
[LING] Right. Right.
He's an expert.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BINGO] Is there dirt on my face?
Is my hair in place?
[CLEARS THROAT]
[LING CLEARS THROAT]
Ling.
What's up?
- I need you.
- What?
I need you.
I know you know a lot about it.
Well, you have to teach me.
Why is she looking at me?
Is there dirt on my face?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Ling, what's up?
- I need you.
- What?
The witnesses' descriptions
matches Pato perfectly.
What if the reason
we didn't meet up before
is because either she was
taken away or she's dead?
Don't use the law to scare me,
because we're all in this together.
If you don't stop,
you might end up like Divine.
I saw that feather the day
I was supposed to meet Pato.
And I also saw the exact same feather
the day Edward died.
What if the person who killed Edward
is the same one who's after Pato?