Yingying, come eat.
Dad.
Your return should have been a happy occasion.
But look at you now.
The way you dress.
I barely recognize you.
This is all I can wear now.
Since the Japanese occupied Sanzao Island,
I often told your mother's photo
to rest assured,
that I would hold on until you returned,
to see you living a happy life.
And now you've finally returned.
Yes, returned indeed.
But with a Japanese person.
And your behavior
confuses me greatly.
Tell me honestly,
what have you been doing all these years?
I went to Shanghai.
Didn't you go north?
Why did you go to Shanghai?
Dad, please don't ask.
Trust that I have principles in what I do.
Everything I do
is to help more people
survive.
Is there something you want to tell me?
Dad.
Is there something about our family you're hiding from me?
Come, let's eat.
I'm done eating.
I need to go out for a while.
I didn't say anything.
I'm finished too.
What's today's mission?
Reporting, Colonel.
Today's mission is
to attack the Yue-Han railway line and Jiangcun Bridge.
Go.
According to the plan,
Wumu must scout out the island today,
mapping all the terrain
and the deployment of troops on the island.
Meanwhile, Ye Biying
should be visiting relatives and friends on the island.
We were secretly tracking down the messenger
but the sentries that suddenly appeared last night
disrupted all our plans.
Search this area again.
How can we not even find the body?
What is it?
Is Major Wumu here?
What?
Wumu.
Go away! Step back!
Miss Ye.
You're just in time.
Can you ask him
if Major Wumu is here?
Sure.
Excuse me.
This is Miss Ye,
Major Wumu's assistant who came to the island with him.
She needs to see Major Wumu.
Is the Major at the airport barracks now?
No.
He's not here? I...
Then can you ask where he went?
Where did he go?
He said he was going out for a while.
He didn't say where,
but the car was heading toward Paotai Mountain.
Thank you.
He said Major Wumu
went in the direction of Paotai Mountain.
Paotai Mountain.
Wumu knows
this is the location arranged by Director Shen
for the second evacuation plan rendezvous.
But Director Shen doesn't know
there's a hidden anti-aircraft gun position here.
Colonel.
Bring me the binoculars.
How far is it from here to Macau?
Reporting, Colonel.
13 nautical miles.
In that direction,
you can see the lights of Macau at night.
Good work.
Yes, sir.
What happened?
Can you promise me something?
No matter what happens,
you'll protect my family's safety.
My father,
Fourth Aunt and my brother.
If it helps you work with peace of mind,
I will definitely do that.
You promised.
I did.
This is a portable disposable
morphine injector needle from the US military.
Produced by the American company Squibb
Syrette needle.
Where did you find it?
At Fourth Aunt's hometown.
Can we assume that
your Fourth Aunt rescued that American pilot
and hid him in her home?
That doesn't make sense though.
With such a large-scale search by the Japanese army,
how could they not find him?
It wasn't just my Fourth Aunt, was it?
Let's go to your house now.
I need to talk to your father.
Wait.
I haven't had a chance to tell you that
my father took me to see the mass grave this morning.
The Japanese army carried out a massacre on the island.
Over ten thousand villagers died.
Not just my father,
but Fourth Aunt and my brother too.
They all hate Japanese soldiers.
Everyone in the village does.
My father won't help us.
You have me.
Sasaki.
That's the situation with the missing sentry.
I've heard about it.
Listen carefully.
Organize the police unit immediately
and the garrison to search the entire island.
But Captain, you're still here.
Don't worry about me.
I can't leave right now.
You're the only one who can handle this now.
Take some men with you.
Your main task isn't to find
that missing soldier.
What's important is to use this opportunity
to go to Ye Degong's house again
and uncover the secret behind that wall.
If you actually find a secret room
or
capture that American who landed on the island,
send someone to inform me immediately.
Let's begin the operation.
Yes, sir.
First squad, move out!
About face!
Double time!
Wumu never expected
to obtain information
about the American messenger so quickly,
and in his own assistant's home.
But he knew well
that making the Ye family hand over the messenger wouldn't be easy.
It's not that simple.
Don't take off your clothes in front of my house.
No way.
Fine.
Don't let him in.
It's okay.
I brought him here.
He needs to talk to Dad.
Hello, Mr. Ye.
I'm Wumu Yilang.
Nice to meet you.
Let's go.
The sentry is dead.
I'll visit you another day.
Go back to bed.
You don't understand what I'm saying?
Put down your weapon.
Mr. Ye,
Dad.
we'd like to have a word with you.
Mr. Ye,
we were in a rush yesterday.
Today,
I'm formally paying my respects to
the father of my assistant, Ye Biying.
My name is Wu Muyilang,
an investigator from the Emperor's Chamberlain Office.
I have nothing to say to you.
Go back.
Mr. Ye.
I need to have a formal conversation with you.
I hope you'll give me a chance.
To talk with you properly today.
We have nothing to discuss.
Please stop pursuing my daughter.
Cats and mice don't sleep together.
Tigers and deer don't walk the same path.
There's nothing to talk about between us.
Dad, I...
Between Biying and me,
it's not what you think.
I also promise you.
I have never done
anything to harm Chinese people.
I have nothing to say to Japanese people.
I can swear to you.
I would never hurt your daughter.
Please believe me.
But you're standing here as an invader,
on
invaded soil.
Did I invite you in?
Get out.
That uniform of yours won't convince me.
Colonel.
What are you doing here?
We're ordered to search this place.
Since I arrived on this island,
Commander Fujita has expressed
his respect for Mr. Ye.
If you find anyone here,
I'll execute their entire family for you.
If you find no one,
I'll shoot you dead.
Or you can explain yourself to Commander Fujita.
Dad.
I'm sorry, Mr. Ye.
For disturbing you.
Thank you for your help
in keeping us from being harassed.
However,
regarding my daughter's matter,
I think we have nothing more to discuss.
Dad.
He's not here to discuss me.
Don't be so stubborn.
Mr. Ye,
this is important.
I hope you'll give me a chance.
Xia'er, see him out.
Dad.
Mr. Ye.
I, Wu Muyilang, will visit again another day.
Goodbye.
This is my assistant's home.
From today onwards,
without my orders,
no one is allowed to disturb them.
Is that clear?
This puts me in a difficult position.
Unless your superior
has his approval,
tell him to speak to me directly.
Didn't perform well?
But I still gained something.
I can now basically confirm
that your father and that American are connected.
Isn't that obvious?
But the key question is,
are they in any danger?
Inoue is now locked in solitary confinement,
so the American is safe for now.
Tonight, Lieutenant General Fujita
has prepared a welcome dinner for us.
If we attend as scheduled
and you perform well,
managing to handle things smoothly,
your family will be safe for the time being.
Is this even reliable? Seriously.
So to make this more credible,
since we still have some time before the banquet,
I need to give you some special training.
Special training?
Really? Training?
Is your Military Intelligence
always this last-minute with preparations?
No, no.
Just cramming at the last minute.
How did it go?
The search failed.
Why?
The Colonel wouldn't let me search.
At that time,
Colonel Muki was talking with that old man.
They were arguing intensely.
What were they discussing?
I don't know either.
I see.
You probably interrupted
a negotiation between a future son-in-law and his future father-in-law.
It seems Colonel Muki
is really taking this Chinese woman seriously.
He also said...
What else did he say?
If there's really a need to search the Ye family home,
my superiors must negotiate with him first.
What did you say?
That bastard.
[Salute]
This colonel is taking advantage of
his minor position in the imperial palace
and doesn't respect anyone on the island.
Can't we do something about him?
I'm curious who could make
Captain Inoue, who always annoys others,
so angry.
Long time no see.
What are you up to?
Carrying out my mission.
My eyes.
I've finally waited for your return.
Don't cross this line.
It stinks.
How many days since you last showered?
Sorry.
Just talk to me from over there.
A sentry went missing yesterday.
But that missing American
still hasn't been found.
Many strange things have happened lately.
That woman the colonel brought
is very suspicious.
That strange colonel and his strange woman
whether those people pose a threat to us,
we need to investigate further.
This arrogant guy,
what's his purpose for coming to the island?
He even prevented
Sasaki from searching the Ye family's home.
Also,
as soon as the American plane crashed,
the colonel and his woman entered the island right after.
As soon as they arrived, someone died.
This is all too damn convenient.
I've probed him about the lookout's death.
He really has no motive for the crime.
It could actually be the work of someone from Macau.
Besides,
that woman, as soon as she arrived on the island,
was interrogated by us.
But soon after, the Colonel took him away.
I understand what happened now.
Scream louder!
Let everyone outside hear you.
Let them all know you're in special training.
Let me tell you something.
I don't like you acting this way.
I don't like the way you're acting either.
Don't start taking this act seriously, okay?
We're just putting on a show.
What kind of girl do you like then?
I like someone fun.
How fun?
More fun than you.
I thought what just happened was quite fun.
Remember this.
As a dancer,
first,
she's already used to physical contact.
Tonight at the party,
Japanese officers will definitely ask you to dance.
If you treat them like you treated me,
we're both finished.
What are you doing?
What are you looking at?
Is there something up there?
Why do you keep looking up?
Look at me, will you?
Look at me.
Second.
As a dancer,
your eyes should never waver.
Look at me.
Whether you pass tonight
doesn't depend on me,
but on you.
What are you doing?
Point number 3.
Remember this.
A dancer
has a thousand ways to refuse her clients,
not like this.
If you do this tonight,
we'll both be finished.
Mr. Wumu,
your hand is in the wrong place.
Not good.
Mr. Wumu,
please be gracious.
That's not right either.
Mr. Wumu,
why is your hand moving faster than your heart?
Hmm, it's getting somewhat interesting.
Remember this.
Always keep smiling.
A smile is your best cover.
Your profession
is being a dance partner at a dance hall in Shanghai.
Is that so?
These days,
it's a decent profession.
You're at the Cathay Grand Ballroom on Edward Road
working as a dance hostess.
I've been to that dance hall.
The lighting is nice.
It's just that
the marble dance floor is a bit too slippery.
On Metherst Road.
The Cathay Ballroom is on Maxwell Road,
not where you said it was.
Also,
it has a spring dance floor,
not marble.
Our ideal takeoff zone
is 400 miles east of Tokyo.
I suggest on the 19th,
one plane takes off three hours before dusk.
The other planes will take off at dusk.
After flying for 2 hours,
we'll drop bombs on Tokyo at night.
Before the Japanese wake up,
we'll be on our way to China.
By dawn on the 20th,
we'll land at Quzhou Airfield.
After refueling,
we'll continue flying to
Chongqing, China's wartime capital.
I've heard many stories about your exploits, Doolittle.
Everyone here knows that
Pearl Harbor
was the greatest humiliation of my life.
Nothing would please me more
than striking back at those damn Japanese.
But this is a crazy plan.
The Navy and Army have never collaborated like this before.
General,
we are indeed doing what others wouldn't dare to imagine.
I still have doubts.
Sir, that's why I'm here today.
To eliminate the Navy's concerns
about our Army pilots' capabilities.
Listen up, Jimmy.
If your test flight succeeds today,
within three days,
you'll load your planes onto the Hornet.
Then,
on the morning of April 2nd,
Captain Mitchell will lead
the Hornet and Task Force 18
departing from Alameda.
I'll meet you near Midway Island aboard the Enterprise
for the rendezvous.
Then under my command,
we'll merge as Task Force 16.
Task Force 16,
including 'Hornet' and 'Enterprise',
4 cruisers, 8 destroyers,
2 submarines and 2 tankers.
We need 18 days to cross the Pacific.
When we reach 400 miles east of Japan,
your B-25 bombers will take off.
Once you're airborne,
the task force will turn back to Hawaii.
You'll be on your own then.
Sir, we've been ready.
Let me emphasize one more thing.
This combined fleet
is all the naval power we have left after Pearl Harbor.
If we're discovered before
reaching the launch point,
the bombers will have to take off early
for Midway or Tokyo.
That way, 'Hornet's' deck
can be cleared for the fighters.
Protecting the ships is my primary concern.
Understood, sir.
One last thing.
We won't have lights at night.
The deck will be completely dark.
Take off after sunset.
Sir, we'll continue with the takeoff tests.
Jimmy, are you ready?
Yes, sir.
I'm excited
to see
what you can do with that big machine.
Jimmy.
Our mission depends on
whether you succeed today.
I certainly don't want to see you fail.
The aircraft has arrived on deck.
General,
let's wait and see.
7701 ready.
7701 cleared for takeoff.
Roger that.
Lieutenant Cole,
it's time to show what your training has accomplished.
Yes, sir.
Flaps down.
Full throttle.
Tower to 7701.
Copy that.
Prepare for takeoff.
Roger.
Ready. 7701 requesting takeoff.
Cleared for takeoff. Good luck.
We're on the deck.
With at least 30 yards to spare.
Unbelievable.
Jimmy, congratulations.
My fleet is at your disposal from now on.
Thank you, General.
Lieutenant Cole.
Take the plane back.
Yes, sir.
I'm Arnold.
Hap, this is George Marshall.
I just saw the footage of the B-25s
taking off from the Hornet.
Doolittle did a great job.
I never doubted him, George.
Has the President seen the footage?
Yes, and he's very pleased.
He just gave final approval.
Any questions, Hap?
No.
Doolittle is the best,
though I hate putting him at risk.
But I trust he'll complete the mission.
Yes. Talk to you later.
I'll make you proud.
Looks good.
Why does the Commander
always host these Western-style parties?
Perhaps the Commander
enjoys this Western style of entertaining.
I see.
Country bumpkin.
When the Commander was at the New York consulate,
he attended these kinds of gatherings
and ate this type of food.
Colonel, the Commander is waiting for you.
Colonel.
Miss Ye.
Translator Luo.
Please wait.
I'll ask the Commander to come down.
Thank you for your hard work.
What are you looking at?
I grew up here as a child.
I know this place better than anyone.
As soon as I stepped in,
I felt the rage of having my home invaded.
It's like my shoes
are covered in dirt
and I don't know where to go.
I really want to set fire
and burn this place down.
Control your emotions.
Only then can you drive out
all the filth from your home.
There were countless parties here since I was little.
I never imagined
that I would be dressed like this,
coming to my own home
to attend a Japanese party.
Control yourself.
What perfect timing. Our main character has arrived.
Yes.
You must be Miss Ye.
Commander,
this is Miss Ye Biying.
Miss Ye,
I am Commander Fujita.
I am a friend of your father.
She is indeed beautiful.
The Colonel has good taste.
Your father and I are old friends.
Though we have different views on current affairs,
we share the same interests.
Tea ceremony, history... I respect him very much.
We both served as diplomats.
Your father was my senior.
He even let me have this place to live.
I'm very grateful for that.
I'm sure, Miss Ye,
you're very familiar with this place.
Please make yourself at home.
Let me introduce everyone.
This is the Emperor's special envoy,
Colonel Takegi Ichiro.
The Colonel is here
to carry out a very important mission.
If the Colonel requires cooperation from unit commanders,
please give him your full support. Understood?
Let me introduce them to you.
What's this about?
Please wait.
Director Shen: Zhang Songwen
Tang Ju'er: Lin Cheng
Takahashi Nobuo: Wang Longzheng
Inoue Kamakura: Otsuka Masayuki (Japan)
Sasaki: Nakaizumi Hideo (Japan)
Akino Kawami: Chai Yao
Fukuda Hirakawa: Takashima Shinichi (Japan)
Wang Yanwu: Zhang Wei
Lao Yi: Dong Zhao
Haozi: Zhao Shuai
Yumiko: Liu Yi
Mommy Wang Zheng
Fen Ni Zhao Tongtong
Song Meiling Shi Chunling
Wang Shihe Shen Xuewei
Shakawa Kaneo Yao Weiping
Old Fortune Teller Shang Tielong
Tang Chuananfu Saito Hiromi (Japan)
Hui Hui Yang Jingyi
Jie Xinliji Jiang Kun
Li Qufeng Li Yatian
Li Baoshan Liu Jian
Supervisor Wang Chen Xuming
Wu Mu's Mother Zhou Ling
Zhenshan's Mother Feng Jun
Chongren Guo Jiulong
Young Ye Biying Liu Zhimiao
Young Ye Longxia He Yucheng
Director Zheng Zheng Xiaozhong
Xianger Jiang Xinxin
Captain Matsumoto Zhou Zhengran
Hasegawa Yokoi Tetsuya (Japan)
Town Chief Yang Zhang Wentao
He Yangling Song Gongkui
He Shaoying Wu Shoujing
Ding Shijie Lu Lei Yuan Chenghao Liu Chengbin Wang Xuefeng Zhang Hui Gong Fan
Zheng Yanping Li Xinlei Wang Pin Zhou Qi Duan Lanjuan Shi Jia Zhang Yan
Li Quanyou Wen Chundi Chen Jiaolong Yang Changqing Zhang Lin Yu Xiaodong Jiang Yixuan
Zhang Xiaoqing Wang Jiayi Deng Lizhen Xu Jiacheng Wang Bo Zhang Dabao
Director Zhao Yilong
Executive Directors Li Xiaolong Xiong Bo
Assistant Director Zhang Yaqi
Editors Sun Qingzhu Dong Chuanhui
Lighting Director Wang Chuanmin
Lighting Assistant Guo Wenju
Costume Supervisors Bai Dapeng Yuan Shuzhen
Makeup Design: Liang Haiman
Makeup Artist: Li Rui
Art Directors: Mao Huaiqing, Gao Huliang
Wu Zhiqiang
Jia Ruibo
Production Manager: Liu Wenpeng
Assistant Production Manager: Yu Haitao
Post-production Coordinator: Guo Ziyan
Marketing and Distribution: Wang Jie
Procurement: Sun Tianyong
Military Advisor: Gao Wei
Still Photography: Yang Songlin, Zhao Wanyi
On-set Producer: Wang Chunsheng
Set Manager: Wang Kangning
U.S. Production Team
Cast
Mitchell: Jeff Fahey (USA)
Trainee Pilot Curry: Nicholas Walker (USA)
Co-pilot Hamilton: Dallas Hart (USA)
Lighting Assistant: Franklin Melendez
Costume Assistant: Chantal Filson
Art Director: Christian Ramirez
Production Manager: Amy Ma
Translator: Ruo
Martial Arts Director: Yu Xiaohua
Assistant Martial Arts Directors: Chai Ruitao, Yu Zhangzhen
Sound Recordist: Zhang Qing
Sound Assistants: Liu Xing, Cao Mengchao
Costume Designer: Yan Xiaoli
On-set Producer: Wang Yuguo
Set Manager: Gao Yuhua
Music Supervisors: A Kun, Tang Yi
Conductor: David Sabee
Orchestra Supervisor: Brooke Vlahos
Music Coordinator: Sam Rosson
Composer/Arranger: Liu Xuandou
String Performance: International Principal Philharmonic Orchestra
Recording/Mixing: Tong Xinyu
Featured Song: "Life and Death Together"
Vocalist: Lin Cheng
Harmonica: Liu Xuandou
Producers: Liu Jing, Liu Xuandou
Executive Producers: Liu Jing, Yang Yu
Sound Design: Wang Chong
Audio Supervisors: Wang Chong, Wang Yiwei
Xu Yuehao
Pre-mixing: Wang Yiwei, Wang Chong
Stereo Mixing: Wang Yangbing, Wang Chong
Title Sequence Editor: Xing Weiguo
Packaging Supervisor: Zha Xi
Administrative Reception: Su Jun
Dubbing Director: Gu Fangbing
Narrator: Bai Ma
Computer Special Effects
Chuanshi Visual Media
Model Team Leader: Fan Xiang
Lighting Team Leader: Zhi Li
Special Effects Team Leader: Fu Hao
Acknowledgements
Xiangshan Film and Television City
Zhejiang Dongyang Hengdian Film and Television City Management Service Co., Ltd.
Shanghai Film Production Company
Xiqiao National Arts Film Studio
Sanhe Film and Television Props Rental Company
Xin Yingyuan Film and Television Props Studio