Why are you asking about this?
The only thing I'm certain of now
is that Colonel Wumu
graduated from Shanghai Tongwen Academy
and was likely a protégé of former Prime Minister Konoe Fumimaro.
I see.
Prime Minister Konoe's investigation agencies
all belong to the Cabinet Intelligence Bureau.
Some others belong to
the Konoe family's private investigation agencies.
For example,
there's the one located in Shanghai Broadway Building,
the East Asia Political and Economic Research Institute,
and the one on Sichuan Road,
the Shanghai East Asia Investigation Association.
Also,
the Nishu Research Institute headed by Fukamachi Sakuji,
president of the Mainichi Newspaper,
and the Yamazaki Research Institute
run by Tateishi Shunzo.
All these institutions belong to them.
What about the Cabinet Secretary's Office system?
The system?
These are all just rumors.
The Shanghai Koua Patriotic Association,
the East Asia Common Culture Association Shanghai Branch,
the Tokyo Common Culture Academy Investigation Association,
the Shanghai Municipal Research Association and others,
are all said to be
Prime Minister Konoe Fumimaro's
privately controlled investigation agencies.
I'm not quite clear about their missions.
The intelligence from these agencies
is never reported to the military or the Imperial Headquarters.
I see.
Mr. Oshima.
I think you might be
overthinking this matter.
Let me give you an idea.
Do you remember the Ministry of Finance's
Deputy Secretary Tae Shuichi?
Section Six.
He currently
oversees all budgets for Tokyo Metropolitan Police Department.
He's the money man for the police department.
Send him a telegram
asking him to dispatch an official
from Section Six of the police department.
Wouldn't that get this matter off your hands?
Section Six.
Counterintelligence Division.
If this Colonel Takeki
really has issues,
it would be the police department's achievement if they uncover it.
If the investigation is wrong,
then it's obviously their mistake.
I see.
Eat more.
All right.
Everything tastes good.
I was careless.
I didn't notice his motorcycle
parked in the yard.
Can your body handle it?
No problem.
Is it okay?
Come with Ju'er
and help me push the vehicle.
JUN08596
Sit tight.
Push harder.
Yes.
Open the front for me.
Help me hold this side.
Yes,
hold it here.
What are you looking at?
Hurry up.
Yes.
Close it.
Go help me push the vehicle.
Put some effort into it.
Find a safe place to hide.
Wait for us here.
We'll be back as soon as possible.
Comfort Tang Ju'er.
Tell her to be brave.
I'll be back soon.
Let's go, Weite.
There's an aircraft signal tower on the mountaintop.
It's staffed during the day but not at night.
Behind the mountain is a camp barracks.
This place is relatively the safest.
Can you hold on?
I can manage.
Come on.
I'll go get Xia'er.
No need, Auntie Si. Please sit.
This Xia'er...
He has no appetite at all.
Hasn't eaten a single grain of rice since morning.
I'm worried he'll make himself sick.
Auntie Si.
Look at that flower.
People are just like flowers.
Take this flower for example.
If you don't water it daily,
don't take good care of it,
with just a little neglect,
it will wither away.
And then,
you'll regret
not cherishing it
when it was in full bloom.
I understand Xia'er's thinking.
He always sees the bigger picture,
always thinking of others first.
But,
regarding his feelings for Ju'er,
he's overthinking it.
However, neither I
nor Tang Bingchen
have the right to interfere.
Young people's affairs
should be decided by themselves.
Sir.
Why don't you tell Long Xia that?
A young man
needs to grow on his own,
experience life himself,
only then will he understand.
Your son
is someone only you truly understand.
Eat.
Why aren't they back yet?
I hope nothing's happened.
Don't worry.
Wumu is the most reliable person
who knows exactly what he's doing.
Wumu is great.
If only
he weren't Japanese.
Ju'er.
Don't take what my brother said
last night to heart.
He didn't mean it.
How can I not think that way?
He doesn't like that
I work at a Japanese hospital.
He doesn't like my father
being the chairman of the Puppet Council.
But what choice do my father
and I have?
Your brother can't treat me like this.
After he said those things,
he deeply regretted it.
He...
He really didn't mean it.
Those were just words spoken in anger.
Words in anger?
How can you treat
this matter so lightly?
My father was wrong to make such a scene.
But he shouldn't have agreed so easily.
If he truly cared about me,
he wouldn't have so readily agreed
to break off our engagement.
Without our engagement,
there's nothing
between us anymore.
Ju'er.
Don't say such things in anger either.
Let's do this.
I'll go back and talk to my brother.
He really didn't mean it.
You have to believe me.
Don't you believe me anymore?
[Star 08596]
It's them.
They're back.
Are you okay?
Come up quickly.
Thank you, Nurse Tang.
When we go back to the hospital later,
try to relax
just like usual.
Is that okay?
Let's go.
Be careful.
Looks like the talk went well.
Let's go.
Are they all asleep?
Help me, please.
Thank you.
Nurse Tang.
Can I talk to you?
Are you still thinking about
what happened this afternoon?
Yes.
My mind is filled with images from today.
No matter how busy I am,
scene after scene
keeps flashing through my mind.
Are you scared?
You're a nurse.
You should know that
when people are under extreme stress,
the limbic brain mobilizes
all body systems
to freeze your memories.
Those scenes flashing
through your mind
will make you even more panicked
when you encounter others.
Yes.
I know.
What should I do?
I need you to
forget what happened this afternoon.
Forget that hateful Jingshang Kancang.
I want to forget too,
but I just can't.
Nurse Tang,
do you know what we use
to strengthen our memories?
We rely on association.
If
we need to quickly forget
certain things,
we also rely on association.
We force ourselves
to think about family,
parents,
and the people we love.
Or our future.
We imagine every step
and every detail of what we'll do.
This way we can gradually forget
the things we want to forget.
But I don't want to think about my father.
Thinking of him
also troubles me.
Brother Longxia,
we have many reasons
why we can't be together.
Nurse Tang, listen to me.
Don't think about those
reasons keeping you apart.
Force yourself
to imagine
your future together.
Think about your life
after the Japanese leave.
The more detailed, the better.
This way you'll gradually forget
what happened this afternoon.
Ye Longxia,
I've met him.
He's a good man.
You'll be happy together.
I can see you really like him.
Since you like him,
don't worry about those reasons.
You should bravely pursue this.
I hope you can have this love.
I'll be wishing you well.
I also hope
to have such a chance.
You will.
Someday.
If I have other questions
can I come to you as well?
Of course.
If you have any questions,
you can come to me anytime.
Get some rest then.
All right.
Thank you.
Colonel.
The reason I came to see you
is that I have another matter to discuss.
What is it?
We've made a plan.
The plan is for April 12th,
which is six days from now,
under the pretext of lifting the fishing ban.
What are you doing?
Planning to let over 260 people from Sanzao Island
go fishing at sea.
Our plan is
to eliminate all these people at sea.
Getting rid of so many at once,
won't that cause public outcry?
No.
We've done this several times on the island.
This is the last batch.
After eliminating these 260 plus people,
the island will be peaceful.
So,
what do you need me to do?
Sasaki.
For our Navy's 6th Air Base,
threats come from three sources.
Please take a look.
First, those
radical and strong young natives on the island.
Second, the Macau gangsters from District Eight.
Over the years,
they've been raiding our island.
More than 40 of the Emperor's soldiers
have died because of this.
Third, those ships after the Humen Naval Battle.
The gunboats of the Chiang regime
that escaped to Macao disguised as merchant ships.
Our plan is to kill three birds with one stone,
solving all these problems at once.
Tell me what you need me to do.
Colonel,
in your telegram a few days ago,
you mentioned capturing an informant from Anlan Hall.
Yes, there is such a person.
I need
to secretly pass our intelligence to him.
The families of Anlan Hall members
are still on the island.
If we let them know about our intelligence,
they will definitely come to rescue them.
We'll seize this opportunity to wipe them out in one strike.
This can be arranged.
One more thing,
it would be best
to find a way to let those Chiang regime ships hiding in Macao
receive some information as well.
I can figure something out for this too.
Another thing,
how does Anlan Hall in Macao
communicate with those troublemakers
on the island?
I can work on all of these.
Thank you very much then.
I'll do my best to help you.
Mr. Oshima,
it's getting late.
Let's head back to the hotel early today.
This plan of yours...
I'll study this carefully tonight.
Thank you for your hard work.
We'll discuss the rest tomorrow.
Then I'll take my leave.
Take care.
Yamaguchi.
Yes.
Take them back to their hotel.
Thank you for today.
This way, please.
Take care.
Thank you for today.
Please rest early, sir.
I'll come pick you up first thing tomorrow morning.
Thank you for your trouble.
Yes.
Oshima Hiroshi.
Great!
Where are you going?
Are you sure you didn't make a mistake?
Boss Geng.
Years ago, they massacred people on the island.
I crawled out from a pile of corpses.
There's no mistake.
It's definitely Oshima Hiroshi.
My wife and children
all died by his hand.
I'd recognize him even if he were burned to ashes.
How many people came with him?
Two.
One was the driver
who left after dropping them off.
You're sure it was two?
Positive.
Boss Geng.
I don't want any reward.
I only ask that you kill that monster
to avenge my wife and children,
to avenge all our dead countrymen.
I'm willing to serve you like a beast of burden.
Get up.
You may leave now.
I'll handle this.
Help me with a few things.
First,
go to the
Lisboa Hotel tonight personally with some men.
You must find out about that Oshima Hiroshi:
how long he's staying,
why he's in Macau,
how he got here,
and when he's leaving.
Second,
send someone tonight to find Haozi.
Tell him to bring his gear
and a few men to see me.
His marksmanship and fighting skills are excellent.
This time
it's his chance to show his skills.
I'll arrange for people to find him right away.
This time,
we can't let those two guys
return to the island alive.
Sir,
don't worry.
I'll go arrange it now.
Is doing this
really going to be safe?
Not necessarily.
Oshima Hiroshi will soon discover
that Inoue Kamakura might have died first
before being pushed off the cliff.
If that happens,
he'll investigate Inoue Kamakura's
movements throughout the day.
Soon,
the hospital will come into his view.
And when Inoue Kamakura was at the hospital,
we were there too,
creating a point of connection.
So we'll become the prime suspects.
But there's no need to worry too much.
Because someone can testify
that Inoue Kamakura left
the hospital on his motorcycle.
If that's the case,
Inoue Kamakura left the hospital alive.
Then the significance of this meeting point
no longer exists.
You're talking about that sentry.
What are you looking at?
Hurry up.
The sentry's testimony will be in our favor.
But Oshima Hiroshi might not completely believe it.
He will also investigate
everyone who had contact with
Inoue Kamakura today.
Including me and Juer.
Tang Juer is our weak point.
She's honest and timid.
If she panics,
everything will be in trouble.
That's what I'm worried about too.
She's on night shift today.
Why don't we go back and have a good talk with her?
Absolutely not.
That would just provide evidence for Oshima Hiroshi.
The Major tonight
will handle her.
He is a professional agent.
I believe he will take care of it.
Can I tell my father and brother
about what happened today?
Yes,
let them be mentally prepared.
Tomorrow when Juer gets off work,
have your brother bring her over.
We'll talk to her in detail then.
Don't think about it.
So many things happened today,
you should get some rest.
Right here.
You guys keep watch here.
You've seen this person before,
keep your eyes wide open,
no sleeping.
Don't let him get away.
Don't worry,
I won't let him escape.
Hello.
Good day, sir.
What service do you need?
My master
has a guest staying here.
I'd like to see
your guest register.
Of course.
No problem.
Take your time.
What are you thinking about?
A generation of vicissitudes cannot be washed away,
yet the three martyrs of Yaishan still leave their legacy.
Are you going to lecture me on 'History of Song' again?
Well, well.
It seems lately
you've been reading more than just 'Water Margin.'
What you just recited
is the couplet from the Yaishan Three Martyrs Temple hall.
It's recorded in the 'History of Song.'
It's not that I don't like reading such books,
I just think they're useless.
How can they be useless?
History is like a mirror.
Reading history makes one wise
and helps us learn from the past to predict the future.
The future?
But what good is the future?
Your reading these books
may make you a civilized person,
but we're living in a barbaric era.
Look at these Japanese on the island.
Can we drive them out
with civilized methods?
In front of savage invaders,
many people only seek self-preservation
and are willing to give up everything.
We've now reached the critical moment
for our nation's survival.
The Japanese have blocked China's passages.
They have almost
cut off all channels
for the Chinese government to get foreign aid.
Chiang Kai-shek can only
hold out in the southwest corner.
If this continues,
China will be in danger.
Tell me,
Wu Mu and Ying'er,
are they working for the Kuomintang
or for the Communist Party?
She doesn't want to say,
and I don't want to ask too much.
But honestly speaking,
I do hope
she's working for the Communist Party.
This party
has vigor
and conviction.
I don't care about the outside world,
nor can I do anything about it.
I'll just stay with you.
When people die,
they become stars.
Those who miss them,
if they see a star shooting across the sky,
it means someone who misses them
is thinking of them.
Ju'er.
In the sky above our Sanzao Island,
not a single star is sad.
When the Japanese leave,
everyone in the country will be free.
We can truly be together,
never to be separated again.
War is an invention of mankind.
Brother.
You're back.
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
I'll ask Mrs. Si to prepare something for you.
Major Weite will
replace him at the hospital.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Jingshang's disappearance
is a serious matter.
The Japanese will definitely investigate thoroughly.
You need to remind Wumu
to be careful
and not show any suspicious signs.
To prevent their retaliation.
I understand.
You need to be careful too.
Ying'er,
is Ju'er alright?
Can I go see her now?
She was frightened,
but
it was a close call.
This Jingshang,
he was so evil.
He deserved to die.
Please take this to my brother's room.
I'll eat there.
I need to talk to him.
No need.
Just leave it here.
Okay.
Don't bother Mrs. Si.
You two talk.
Remember what I told you.
Don't forget.
Take care of yourself.
I will.
Good night.
Good night, Dad.
Dad, get some rest early.
Ying'er,
is
Ju'er still angry with me?
No, she isn't.
She's still worried you don't want her.
Did she ask you
to talk to me?
Is this the first time
in your life that you've felt
so worried about someone?
A little bit, yes.
Before, I only thought about
staying on this island with Dad
and being filial to him.
If someday I could leave this island,
I'd surely make something of myself.
On this island, apart from Dad and you,
there wasn't anything
worth missing or caring about.
But now there's another person
I worry about,
and that's Ju'er.
Before,
I was always avoiding
the feelings between us.
But she kept helping me,
risking her safety again and again.
I don't want
to involve her in my troubles anymore.
But sometimes
when I think about her father,
I feel I should just give up.
But now you see
I feel really troubled.
What?
I think you've truly fallen in love with Ju'er.
Not because of the engagement.
Then tell me,
what should I do now?
If I step forward,
I'm afraid of putting her in danger again.
But if I step back,
I can't back away anymore.
If I do,
she'll truly think I don't want her.
Stop with those fancy excuses.
All that talk about fearing for her safety.
You just can't swallow your pride
and don't want to apologize.
Let me tell you.
Ju'er is much braver than you.
If it weren't for her today,
the consequences
would be unimaginable.
Sir.
Master.
Sir,
Rat's associates are all here,
but we can't find Rat himself.
Fulong Street's Xin'an Teahouse.
Have you checked there?
We went there.
He wasn't there.
Send more men
to keep searching.
Yes, sir.
Go quickly!
Yes, let's go!
What's the situation on your end?
Sir,
we've gathered all the information.
They indeed only sent two men.
One is Oshima Hiroshi
and the other is Sasaki.
They booked a suite with beds in both rooms.
They plan to leave tomorrow afternoon.
We'll make our move tomorrow.
Don't you dare fall asleep.
Keep your eyes wide open.
Don't let him slip away.
Don't worry.
Boss.
Keep it down.
Where's Master Geng?
Master Geng.
What have you been up to lately?
You're nowhere to be found all day.
I had people looking for you all night yesterday.
Where were you?
I had a few too many drinks last night.
I stayed at the one on Fulong New Street.
At Liangji House.
I've kept you around for this moment.
Now it's time to put you to work.
Can you handle it?
If not, I'll find someone else.
Fine.
Rest assured.
Whatever you ask.
When have I ever not handled
your rat problems perfectly?
Tell me.
Here's the situation.
One of our enemies
has arrived in Macau
and is staying at the Lisboa Hotel.
Which enemy are we talking about?
The boss means...
I figured out last night
their accommodation and travel route.
Their hotel room
is booked until this afternoon.
So...
I expect this afternoon they'll
go to the fishing pier
and leave on a ship owned by Japanese Fuda Company.
The boss wants
to make sure these two don't leave alive.
What's his name?
His name is Oshima Hiroshi.
He was the head of the Japanese
special police unit on our home island of Sanzao.
The massacre a few years ago
and the recent deaths
of the Tiger brothers
were all his doing.
This is our chance.
He's delivered himself to us.
I want to use this villain's blood
to honor our dead villagers
and our brothers.
Boss Geng.
Where do we make our move?
The hotel has too many people watching.
Wait for them on the way.
As soon as they appear,
shoot them dead.
Got it.
Boss Geng.
I'll take them there.
Success is the only option.
Failure is not permitted.
Cast
Oshima Hiroshi, Kobata Ryu (Japan)
Wei Te Chen, Shao Tong
Luo Zhiyong, Liao Wang
Sasaki, Nakaizumi Hideo (Japan)
Commander Fujita, Kobayashi Shigeo (Japan)
Dr. Ozu, Ouyang Wangjia
Takizawa, Chen Weixu
Akanishi, Matsuura Kei (Japan)
Haozi, Zhao Shuai
Yumiko, Liu Yi
Inoue Akira, Mori Hiroyuki (Japan)
Shazi, He Zhilong
Director Li, Zhang Zhizhong
Qiu Gang, Wang Zheng
Rongtaku Sakusha, Matsukaku Yohei (Japan)
Kimura Shoichi, Oyanagi Shinichiro (Japan)
Yamamoto Isoroku, Miura Kenichi (Japan)
Kai Nobuyoshi, Jiang Kun
Elder Chen, Luo Shiping
Chen An, Gao Haishan
Supervisor Wang, Chen Xuming
Director Yan, Huang Wenhao
Chen Qiao, Li Jinfeng
Bing Yi, Yue Junling
Captain Zhong, Zhou Jie
Dahu, Zhang Junyi
Xiaohu, Jin Guangzheng
Yuan Dai, Ma Yan
Old Qin, Zhao Haiying
Cigarette-buying Girl, Yu Li
Qing Mu, Liu Fenggang
Ye Tian, Feng Pu
Yongye Yang Chengming
Secretary Zhao, Shi Yifu
Zheng Caifu, Chen Jun
Xu Chuansheng, Xue Conghai, Zhang Xiaolei, Xiao Yang, Li Yu, Liu Haibo, Zhu Chaoqun
Yang Xiaomei, Jing Chao, Yin Xin, Jie Lei, Ding Yong, Yan An, Zuo Longqiang
Zhang Menglian, Liang Xiaoxia, Li Qinyang, Wang Jingru, Ding Zhiyuan, Dong Xiaoya, Zhang Dengyun
He Guiling, Liu Youlin, Li Jiawei, Ji Xiang, Yin Zhefei, Jia Shuyi, Zhang Haifeng
Assistant Directors: Ma Yunbo, Zhang Yi
Casting Coordinator: Wei Tianci
Editing Assistant: Zhai Kai
Director of Photography: Gao Wei
Lighting Director: Wang Chuanjun
Sound Director: Lin Xin
Set Design Lead: Guo Baojun
Deputy Set Design Lead: Liu Shusen
Effects Lead: Wang Tao
Props Lead: Ma Yulong
Deputy Props Lead: Liu Junqing
Deputy Production Director: Yu Haitao
Production Coordinator: Su Kewen
Liang Tinghui
Procurement: Sun Tianyong
Production Assistants: Yang Haiqun, Zhu Quan
Legal Advisor: Sun Shouheng
Translators: Qian Lei, Luo Yu'e
Script Planner: Wu Tian
Location Manager: Wang Kangning
Pilot Lawson: Skyler Hart (USA)
C-46 Pilot Jefferson: David Blue (USA)
Charles McRoll: Desmon Aldridge (USA)
Japanese Commander: Taishi Mizuno (Japan)
Spoons: Jeff Rector (USA)
Navy Dancer: Marshall Watson (USA)
Japanese Officer: Takashi Yam
Alexander Garcia: Kevin Joy (USA)
Colonel Cooper: P.J. Marino (USA)
Cadet Pilot Curry: Aaron Wilton (USA)
Cast and Crew
Assistant Director: Luis Felipe Delgado
Production Assistant: Cheryl Su
Martial Arts Team
Martial Arts Director: Liu Jie
Assistant Director for Actors: Gao Haishan
Director of Photography: Li Wenhao
Sound Assistants: Liu Xing, Cao Mengchao
Li Chenghe
Zhong Yanhe
Music Editors: Dai Tingting, Liu Zongyun
Music Production: Akun Music Studio
Sound Engineer: John Kurlander
Music Coordinators: Zhang Xiaoming, Qiu Yunbing
Theme Song: "Moon Opens Its Eyes"
Performed by Duo Liang
Recording/Mixing: Tong Xinyu
Producers: Liu Jing, Liu Xuandou
Executive Producers: Liu Jing, Yang Yu
Lyrics: Zhao Jun, Zhang Jingyi
Composer/Arranger: Wang Tianyin
Post-Production
Beijing Paihua Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Project Manager: Wang Yiwei
Environmental Effects Editors: Wang Keyu, Jiang Zhiyu, Liu Dige
Special Effects Editors: Wang Yangbing, Wang Ying
Dolby Atmos Mixing: Wang Chong
Color Grading: Li Yang
Narrator: Bai Ma
Japanese Dubbing Director: Qian Lei
Voice Actors: Takahashi Nobuaki, Chikai Masahide
VFX Supervisor: Shan Zijia
VFX Director: Liu Bing
Model Team Lead: Fan Xiang
Lu Haowei
Documentary
Chief Director: Miao Lei
Li Siying
Zhejiang Broadcasting Shanhaishang Legend Park
Guangzhou Panyu Yuyin Mountain Villa Tourism Service Center
Guangdong Kaiping Diaolou Tourism Development Co., Ltd.
Guangzhou Shawan Ancient Town Tourism Development Co., Ltd.
Zhongshan Film and Television City Co., Ltd.
Xin Ying Yuan Film and TV Props Studio
Beijing Huixin Yijie Film and Television Planning Co., Ltd.
Costume Sponsor: Jiangsu Qianyu Environmental Engineering Co., Ltd.