[Episode 2]
♫ You follow behind me, but I'm only running forward ♫
♫ I'm just around the table you're sitting at, I don't care ♫
♫ If you touch me you won’t be able to handle it. I’m hot hot hot hot fire ♫
♫ Someone please stop me before I flip something over ♫
♫ I open my closet and put on the freshest outfit ♫
♫ I carefully check the reflection of my face in the mirror ♫
♫ Right now it’s 8 p.m., I’m supposed to meet up at 8:30 p.m. ♫
♫ Tonight I set out with bold steps ♫
♫ I am the best ♫
Look at her go.
What's this?
♫ Whoever looks at me can see I’m kind of fabulous, all right ♫
♫ Even if you were me... ♫
Why aren't you picking up?
♫ Right ♫
♫ Guys keep on staring at me, girls always copy me ♫
♫ They keep eyeing this spot I'm at; it gets so tiring ♫
♫ This clumsy player keeps pretending to be a pro ♫
♫ I'll dump you as if you're a flat tire ♫
I think he saw everything.
♫ I'm incomparable to anyone else; I'm being humble ♫
♫ If you want to know my value, I'm a billion-dollar baby ♫
Why are you here?
Why didn't you pick up my call?
I was working.
You were dancing.
I was working too.
Why are you here? You said you were going clubbing.
That's why I'm here.
I came clubbing to kill time, but the crowd isn't so good.
Woo!
Woohoo!
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ What's wrong with my age? ♪
♪ Age is just a number when it comes to love ♪
Yeah!
♪ This is my only heart ♪
♪ This is my one true feeling ♪
♪ You are my one true love ♪
♪ I have tears in my eyes ♪
♪ What's wrong with my love? ♪
♪ I'm the perfect age to love ♪
That one is mine. It's mine.
Move, move.
Woohoo!
♪ I walked into the night ♪
♪ In the early morning... ♪
I finally managed to get out.
You haven't finished yet, right?
I'm almost done. Don't worry, go in. Thanks for going.
This is so much faster this way.
It was taking me so much time to pack and tape these individually.
It is, isn't it?
You're supposed to use your head.
Is that right?
Gosh, was that a boulder just now? So heavy.
Sorry, I was wrong.
Seriously, you...
Once I catch you...
What the heck!
I got you.
- Section Chief!
- Oh my. Oh no.
- Section Chief Yun!
- Yes!
- Where are you?
- Ye Eun.
- You're still here!
- Yes.
- Section Chief Yun.
- Why did you come here?
I thought you'd still be here alone.
No, I'm fine.
I'm almost done. It's so messy there. Come here.
I'll help you. We can talk while we wrap up.
No, you're being too ambitious.
I can clean up once I get to work tomorrow.
What?
Karaoke wasn't a great time, was it?
It's so annoying. He kept touching me.
I thought I'd die. It was so creepy.
It's my fault for leaving you there.
It would've been worse if you were there.
Senior Manager Gong acts up when you're around because you don't say anything.
Gosh, I'll cover for you next time.
Shake it off and forget it.
You should stop letting him off the hook like that.
And they keep bringing up the fact that you broke up with your boyfriend.
Why don't you say anything? I would never let that go!
You're already having a really hard time. You really liked him.
When did I?
Well...
It's just...
It isn't like I liked him to death or anything.
When most people date, they have their good times.
Yes, so what I mean is...
- I really, really love you.
- Yes, Ye Eun.
But I think you're really drunk.
- I'm not.
- Stand up. Do you think you can stand? Try standing.
Section Chief Yun, I want to help you though.
- Can you go?
- I came to help you.
Let's go, let's go. Don't move and stay here.
I'll be back soon.
- Are you doing that all alone?
- No, no.
I'll finish it tomorrow morning.
Oh, I'll turn off the lights.
I'll do that. I can do it. Wait!
Gosh.
You don't need to... turn off the lights.
My back.
The alarm has been set.
I'm okay, Section Chief Yun.
Try to pull yourself together.
- I'll call a car.
- No, I'll do it. I'll do it.
- I can do it.
- I have somewhere to drop by.
- I have to drop by my friend's store.
- Oh, that place.
The franchisee there is named Seo Gyeong Seon.
That's right.
You must be very close.
I guess so.
This is Sangam-dong, around DMC.
- Yes.
- Yes, Yeongdeungpo.
- And the other car...
- It's cold.
I'll call you back.
Yes.
- Are they coming?
- Yes. Let's hurry.
Oh, Section Chief Yun.
- Pull yourself together.
- You know I like you a lot, right?
Yes. I really, really like you, too.
I'm going crazy here.
Get in now.
- Section Chief!
- Yes, why?
I'm going to become a cool career woman just like you.
- Okay, you do that, but go home first.
- Are you getting in or not?
Hold on! Why do you keep trying to send me away?
I like being with you.
The driver is waiting.
- You must not like me.
- You should go home.
I like you so much, so much. But you should go home now.
Oh, okay.
Mister.
Section Chief Yun, I love you. I love you.
Me, too. I love you, too.
Please go.
Goodbye!
♫ You can dance ♫
♫ Every dance with the guy that gives you the eye, and let him hold you tight ♫
♫ You can smile ♫
♫ Every smile for the man that held your hand beneath the pale moonlight ♫
♫ But don't forget who's taking you home and in whose arms you're gonna be ♫
Jun Hui!
Hey! Where are you?
Where is he?
Jun Hui!
♫ Like sparklin' wine, go and have your fun ♫
♫ (Yes I know) Laugh and sing ♫
What took you so long?
I came as fast as I could.
Yeah, right. You must've crawled here.
♫ Don't forget who's taking you home and in whose arms you're gonna be ♫
♫ Please darlin', save the last dance for me ♫
I got home safely.
Good night.
♫ Can't you feel it when we touch ♫
♫ I will never ever let you go, I love you oh so much ♫
♫ Save ♫
♫ Save the, save ♫
Are you coming in or going out?
Can't you tell? I'm going to work.
You come and go whenever you please. I can't figure it out.
You should acknowledge the hard work of your brother who works all night.
How would I know if you were working or partying at a club?
I did both.
Paying rent to leave your place empty half the time is such a waste.
Let's live together to save.
Are you crazy?
Do you have to be crazy to live with me?
We may be siblings, but let's keep our privacy, Noona.
- Do you have a woman?
- "A woman"?
Which woman are you talking about?
I'll get into an accident.
A car accident isn't the only kind of accident you can get into.
Do you know how shocked I was when you pretended to call the police as Jin Ah's boyfriend?
I thought you got into a fight with some guy over a girl.
I felt like my insides were turning inside out.
I'd win, of course.
Don't joke around and listen carefully.
The day you bring around some rude and thoughtless girl to marry,
you'll both die by my hand.
But what if she's very pretty?
If her looks can compete with mine, I'll think about it.
I think my ears are rotting from hearing that.
Ouch! All right.
Section Chief Yun, come see me.
Do you expect me to read this or look at it like it's a picture?
I worked hard on it. Does it not meet your standards?
Section Chief Geum, bring me a ruler.
Standby.
Do the lines meet or not?
The content changed, so we had to replace it.
Are you a novelist?
Don't focus on such useless things.
Focus on the original goal of the report.
Standby.
Hey, do you call this a Powerpoint presentation?
We went with the method most commonly used in the past three years.
Who said to copy that?
Didn't you consider making it original at all?
If you were going to use a template and just change the words and numbers,
all you did was press Ctrl-C and Ctrl-D.
It's not 'D'. It's Ctrl-V.
You're so knowledgeable about that, so why was this done so poorly?
Do it all over again.
Make it original and new.
Standby. Come here, Section Chief Kang.
Yesterday...
our young friends like Dong Wu and Ye Eun stayed until the end of our dinner.
You should be convincing people to come, but you were all missing.
What's the purpose of a company outing?
It's to create a bond and devotion.
You should know better.
Working in an organization means that you shouldn't just think of yourself.
There should be a sense of camaraderie.
Speaking of which...
does our company discriminate based on gender?
Do we force you to drink?
We all get along, as equals.
You don't even have the basics down.
What are you doing? Go!
Take this with you!
Let's go eat.
[What a bastard.]
Let's go. Dong Wu, come on.
Yes.
If I just sat at a desk all day like them,
I would want to go to company outings, too.
The stores are constantly expanding and we are out all day.
How would we have the energy to go out?
I know.
It's getting harder to wake up lately.
I must be getting old.
What's with you two?
We aren't that old yet.
You don't know how much difference a year makes.
Don't bring up age when we are colleagues.
Should I start calling you Unnie?
I welcome that anytime.
Old or young, we need to energize ourselves.
How about some healthy food?
Sounds good.
Rice noodles.
What?
How is that healthy food?
It's all the same if it's good.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Please enjoy.
Hey, hook me up with her, please.
Welcome.
If your friend is lonely every night, he will end up sick...
Hello.
Oh, Noona.
Oh, you were here.
Please sit.
Where do you live?
Me? My parents live outside the city.
So I live in Mok-dong.
- I live alone.
- That's the best.
No, I meant...
You live in the best area. Yes.
Where do you live?
- Bundang.
- I live in Bangbae-dong.
I have somewhere to be.
Enjoy your food.
Bye then.
You're paying for the noodles, right? I helped you yesterday.
Be quiet.
Thanks for the meal.
How do you two know each other?
I transferred schools when I was in second grade.
Wow, it's already been over twenty years.
Yes, his older sister was my classmate.
Oh...
You're practically family.
Maybe you know my sister. She's a franchise owner there.
Oh, really?
Where?
Which one?
I thought you left already.
Why? Is something going on?
About Seo Gyeong Seon's store, since you're in charge of it,
I'll take over from now on.
That will be a problem.
I think my friend would get upset.
I'll treat her well so that she isn't upset.
You took over the Gasan store.
I did that because of trouble between you and the owner there.
This is a different situation.
So do you not want to?
It's not that I don't want to. It's just a little difficult from my point of view.
All right. Never mind.
I'll handle it.
Why would he mention that his sister runs a franchise?
Did he really have nothing else to say?
Who are you talking to?
Oh, I was just spewing nonsense.
I'll get going first.
If that plane leaves the ground
and you're not with him
you'll regret it.
Maybe not today, maybe not tomorrow, but soon.
And for the rest of your life.
We'll always have Paris.
What did you buy?
Look at this later and get me some water. I'm so hot.
Is it hot outside?
It's because I'm so upset.
We will end up broke giving people money at weddings.
This is for the youngest son of my youngest sibling.
They seem to like the girl he's marrying.
Sister-in-law was showing off so much, I thought she was from a great family.
She had nothing going for her except that her dad is a district representative.
That's something.
Forget it.
This must be your friend.
Seocho-dong, their second child is getting married.
Their in-laws are in banking and finance and have power there.
She shows off every time I see her.
You should see how she acts when someone says they envy Jin Ah.
She goes on and on endlessly about how great her in-laws are.
I guess she has the right to.
From what I heard, they're a really successful family.
We can marry Jin Ah to a good family, too.
That's what I'm worried about.
If we just believe in Jin Ah, there will be no hope next year either.
Why don't you call Gyu Min and talk to him?
- Me?
- Aren't you going to get her married?
Will you just give other people wedding gifts?
Okay.
Don't just say okay and do nothing. All right?
For goodness' sake.
You better do it.
He has to.
What is it? Don't you like it? Should we go somewhere else?
Have you been here before?
I came here with work colleagues before. It wasn't bad.
We can go somewhere else if you don't like it.
I don't mind it.
You're here, Sir. I'll take you to your seat.
The employees here must have a really good memory.
Can we sit over there?
Yes, sit where you'd like.
Do you want something to drink?
What should we drink?
Something you've had before.
- What?
- You must've had something recently.
I wasn't here recently.
What is it?
I'm going to the restroom.
Okay.
Hey, I wouldn't want to sit with him for even one minute.
Why are you even dealing with him at all?
Just pour the wine, throw it in his face, and leave!
What do you mean you're going to see?
Are you going to date Lee Gyu Min again?
If you won't, then why are you dragging things out?
You better not do anything stupid.
Okay.
Who is it?
Why bother asking? It's Yun Jin Ah.
Lee Gyu Min came to see her again. Seriously.
Why?
Why else? He's playing games to start dating her again.
Doesn't Jin Ah know he's playing games? Why does she keep seeing him?
That's what I...
Who says she's seeing him? He's the one who keeps showing up.
That's because she keeps giving him an opening.
She'll make things clear today. She couldn't possibly...
I doubt it.
But why are you getting annoyed?
I'm not.
I'm trying hard to make things work again.
You won't stop being angry, so it's really hard.
Is it hard?
Of course, I don't know what to do.
Are you shameless or thoughtless?
What?
How could you come here?
Especially when you're trying to make things work.
Lipstick, stocking...
What? Do you want to sue me? Let me add assault to that.
Jin Ah.
I came here to try and end it with good memories.
You're cruel.
You're truly the worst.
I'm not the only one who cheated.
Who was the guy who took you away in front of your office?
Seriously?
You see.
You met someone else, too. Why am I the only bad one?
We both did wrong. Can't we just call it even?
It's not you. I was the worst for dating you!
How can you leave like that?
What? Do you need cash for the valet again?
Oh, you drank. Do you need money for a designated driver?
Are you upset about something?
Hello.
Oh, hello.
Your outfit today is... wow.
Thank you.
You look like you're in a bad mood today, Jun Hui.
Right? I told you.
No, I'm fine.
You said you live in Mok-dong, right? Where in Mok-dong?
Five minutes from the subway stop.
The famous five minutes from the station?
Yes.
Hi.
- Hello.
- Yes.
There's a hot oven pizza place by the subway.
Do you know it?
Yes, it's quite good.
They have a location in this area.
Oh, really? Where?
Then could you take us sometime?
Why not?
Speaking of which, how about having lunch there today? Do you have time?
Yes, of course.
Even if we don't, we will have to make time.
Is this the army?
Oh, by the way...Your phone number.
Oh, mine?
Noona, do you want to come, too?
Where?
I didn't hear what you were talking about. I was texting.
I'll get going now.
Goodbye.
I'll message you later.
Stay seated.
I have something to say before the meeting.
Did you see the news yesterday?
There's no way you would have.
The size of the coffee market was 6.4 trillion won last year.
Wow.
How much of that do you think was our company's share?
I'm not hearing about any new stores.
Business Development Team, don't you have anything?
I'm sorry. We will work harder.
That doesn't mean that existing stores can feel safe.
We need development.
If we only open the doors and do nothing, will customers just come in?
- What is it?
- There is a store that hasn't opened yet.
And we still can't reach the owner.
How can they not be open at this time of day?
- Where is it?
- The Gasan-dong location.
If it doesn't open in thirty minutes, everyone here is fired.
Everyone, get out!
We suddenly had something come up at another store.
Yes, hello.
- Yes, Sir.
- Yes, Senior Manager.
- I'll contact you again.
- Sorry about that. Yes.
We will be there in about seventeen minutes.
Hello, this is Geum Bo Ra.
About our appointment at 11:00 a.m...
- Yes, I understand.
- Can we reschedule?
Yes, Senior Manager.
- Yes, yes.
- It's an urgent head office matter.
- We need to handle a matter.
- Seventeen minutes.
Then, perhaps, after work?
Jun Hui, hello. This is Kang Se Yeong.
Yes. What do I do?
An urgent matter came up, so I'll be at a store today.
Sorry, I know I suggested lunch first.
I feel worse if you say that.
I'll make sure to treat you to a big meal within a few days.
Yes, please contact me.
Yes. It's fine.
I'm sure there will be another chance.
Yes. Thanks.
What next time? Call her right now and tell her tonight is okay too.
She says she's busy. Why are you being so pathetic?
Hey, I'm not being pathetic. I'm being straightforward.
This is why you're bad at dating.
Hey, let's see how good you are then.
I think he's screwing with us because of the report.
All the required products are here.
We will get what we need from the manager, so let's decide on our positions.
I'm on the POS.
Section Chief Geum is on pastries, right?
Who can do better than you who has a SCA license?
(T/N: Specialty Coffee Association license)
Is that a compliment or a joke?
You two can divide the work on your own. Two and three.
- Three covers the back room.
- Okay.
Welcome!
She was supposed to pay for these out of pocket, so why is the company paying?
Even Chairman Jo told Yun Jin Ah to take care of it.
It's because it wasn't Yun Jin Ah's mistake. I feel it was settled unfairly.
What? This matter was already settled.
What do you mean, "unfair"?
Who will pay for it then?
Someone needs to pay for it.
What are you looking at?
I... let many things go without saying anything.
I'll fix it and hand it in again.
She is subtly arrogant.
Someday... I have to deal with her.
Where is Director Nam?
He's inside.
Were you looking for me?
Let's have lunch together if you don't have plans.
Yes. Let me just get my shoes.
Manager Jung, you should come, too. I have something I want to ask you.
Yes, Sir.
How is the Gasan store doing?
Oh, right.
It seems to be doing well.
I heard from them.
Well, all the players are there, so it should do well.
It seemed like Yun Jin Ah was diligent.
Why do I keep hearing about her lately?
Yes, I know.
Well, I guess you really can't judge a book by its cover.
Gosh.
What caused the payment issue for the promotion last time?
I have yet to figure that out. I'm sorry.
Are there times when you procrastinate your work too?
I'll find out as soon as possible and report it to you.
Investigate it thoroughly.
Manager Jeong... one moment.
Just one moment.
Let me see.
About the report to Chairman Jo, what are you going to say?
Like you said, Yun Jin Ah would pay it.
I have to tell the truth about the payment.
What do you mean, "the truth"?
To find errors easily, we make copies of all settlement requests.
I looked into it and sent in that request.
I thought about it and...
she's only a section chief.
How would she have that kind of money?
It's like a company dinner.
I'll think of it like treating you all to a company dinner.
Wouldn't that work?
A hundred lipsticks is 2.1 million won.
A hundred mobile coupons is 320,000 won.
That's a total of 2.42 million won.
Okay.
I can do the math, too.
So, to confirm, I will report to the chairman–
I'll do it.
[Coffee Bay]
Gosh, you all worked hard.
Our team works quite well together.
I worked until my nails broke.
You only worked on the POS. I think I dislocated my shoulder.
What about tomorrow?
I'll have to meet the franchise owner.
The company will have to use its reserves depending on the situation.
If they don't, I don't know,
- but I won't come tomorrow. Bye.
- Goodbye.
- Thanks for working hard.
It's our job, too.
You should feel apologetic to me.
- I'll be off.
- Bye.
You two should get going. I need to return the car to the office.
I have to go look for the owner. I'll use it and return it.
- You two worked hard, too.
- Should I come with you?
Stop making me feel worse. Go home and rest.
- See you tomorrow.
Yes. You worked hard.
Oh, my legs.
Mister Franchisee, Avoiding me is not the answer.
Please call me.
[Coffee Bay]
He said you were like this, right? That punk.
"That punk"?
Should I call him brother-in-law?
Now that you're in love again?
What are you talking about?
Did Gyeong Seon say that I'm dating him again?
Well, your relationship was so intense, it must be hard to end.
As if!
You sure are funny.
What do you know to assume such things?
I heard everything, okay?
What kind of relationship was it that even your junior feels bad for you?
When dating someone, do you just ask how they're doing?
It should be hot.
Otherwise, you're the weird one.
It isn't right to the person you date. You mistreated that person.
You should be crazy, passionate, and intense when you like each other.
That's normal. Do you know that?
Oh, really?
You're also a professional when it comes to love.
I'll make sure to remember that and use it.
Why do you keep speaking so sarcastically?
Who? Me?
Even that tone right now.
I wasn't.
Again.
I apologize if I made you feel bad.
Sorry.
It's raining.
Yes, it is.
They didn't say it would rain.
You don't have an umbrella, right?
I don't.
I'll just get rained on.
Why would you get rained on for no reason?
Because you've made me upset so I'm burning up.
I've said I'm sorry. Stop being angry.
Fine.
I should be the one who's sorry.
I kept you from eating hot, hot oven pizza with Kang Se Yeong.
It couldn't be helped, so please forgive me.
No need for forgiveness.
You could come, too.
Why would I go when I'm being included against your will?
What do you mean, "against my will"?
What do I mean?
Didn't you say, "Noona, do you want to come, too?"
It wasn't even, "Let's go." It was, "You want to come."
Did I say that?
I was making plans without thinking, so I misspoke.
Yes, I'm sure you couldn't focus.
Hey.
Do guys like girls just because they're pretty?
We do.
So annoying.
You're prettier, Noona.
It doesn't look like it will stop.
Let's call a taxi here.
How will we get to the street?
Stay here. I'll buy an umbrella.
Oh, we should just go...
How much?
What?
Come here.
You said I shouldn't get rained on.
I got rained on a bit.
Geez, why did you only buy one umbrella?
A red one, at that?
Don't you know? Buying umbrellas and lighters is the biggest waste of all.
Okay, rich man.
We will both end up half-wet like this.
There's a solution for that.
What?
Like this?
♫ Sometimes it's hard to be a woman ♫
♫ Giving all your love to just one man ♫
♫ You'll have the bad times ♫
♫ And he'll have the good times ♫
♫ Doing things that you don't understand ♫
♫ But if you love him, you'll forgive him ♫
[Parking Lot Entrance]
♫ Even though he's hard to understand ♫
Should we get a taxi?
Well...
I think it's best I sober up first.
Then we better walk a bit more before getting one.
I think so.
♫ Stand by your man ♫
Noona, you're really small.
What?
I didn't know because your punch is so strong, but you're so small.
Hey, I'm not small. I'm average.
Hey, what do you take me for?
I know a lot about women...
Really...
Is that right?
I'm joking.
I see.
♫ Keep giving all the love you can ♫
♫ Stand by your man ♫
Do you want to see a movie this weekend?
I haven't seen a movie in a hundred years.
Isn't that what moms say?
Hey!
♫ Stand by your man ♫
It's late.
You should get going.
After I see you go in.
I think you're using all your manners today.
I have some left.
What?
A present.
Why? You bought it.
That's why it's a present. Here.
Thank you.
Go on in.
Okay.
Bye.
Go.
Sleep well.
You, too.
I'll give you three days.
If I don't hear from you, we will close your store.
- Hello.
- Are you at work?
Not yet. I had to stop by somewhere.
I wanted to drink some morning coffee made by a professional.
Sir, that'll be difficult without an appointment.
You're playing hard to get.
I am hard to get. Didn't you know?
You aren't sober yet, are you?
Just you wait.
[Corporate Law Firm]
Yes, Father. Please go on.
Oh, no. It's all right.
It's nothing.
I was wondering if you had time tonight.
Yes.
Tell him he has to come.
You must be busy if you have a big case.
Yes, you must be busy.
Yes.
Really?
Okay, then. I got it.
What did he say?
I called him while he was busy.
- Can he come or not?
- What?
He's coming.
I couldn't breathe for a second.
Hold on. Seung Ho's coming, too. I wonder if we have enough meat.
Shouldn't we tell Jin Ah that Gyu Min is coming?
I'm sure they'll tell each other.
I think you got a message.
Se Yeong, should we have hot oven pizza today?
Should I make a reservation tonight?
Do you have plans?
Yes...
Jun Hui, he wants to eat together tonight.
I would've skipped lunch if I had known.
My body feels heavier lately.
I've gained some weight, haven't I?
I don't know. I never looked carefully.
I'll be leaving first.
What are you doing tonight, Ye Eun?
I have to redo my menu analysis.
You should eat dinner. Come on. My treat.
Really? All right.
Where should we go?
Somewhere that sells both food and alcohol.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
I'll be leaving now.
Aren't you coming with us?
- I have plans.
- He's going clubbing.
Clubs... I like them, too.
Really? We can all go together next time.
I have other plans today.
Okay, take me to a good place next time.
You can have other plans next time too.
I'll keep that in mind. Escort her well.
I should escort him well.
- Should we get going?
- Yes, let's go.
See you again.
Yun Dong! Are you back already?
Is something wrong?
No. I suddenly felt like drinking.
You still think about your ex-boyfriend a lot, right?
You'll say I'm lying if I say no.
The best medicine for a break up is a new love.
Hurry and date someone new.
No, thanks.
Why? It's best to keep the time between relationships short.
Because you won't have forgotten your past mistakes yet.
So you'll act without regrets in the new one.
We have a player here.
I'm not so good at it in real life, but I'm good with theory.
I'm proud of you.
But...
how much of a man's words and actions should I believe?
They're all lies.
"Lies"?
"Hey, what can't you say or do when you're seducing a woman?"
I studied engineering.
That's what I heard the most, surrounded by men for four years.
But if the guy tries to woo the girl,
doesn't that mean he likes her?
That's true.
But like my mom used to say, "A man doesn't say no to available women."
He will just keep them all in his pond and choose one.
[Dog: Gyu Min]
Hold on a minute.
Hey, why do you keep calling me?
It's your dad.
"Dad"?
Why do you have Lee Gyu Min's...
Dad, you met Lee Gyu Min?
[No Smoking]
This doesn't really seem like something Seo Dong bought for me from the U.S.
Have you been fooled all your life?
It's the first time you've done this.
Hey, how can you get a doctorate with that brain?
It's my first time back since I left.
Oh, that's true.
Hurry and play.
Did you know that your sister and I work in the same building?
Really?
Don't you care?
Do you care a lot about Gyeong Seon?
I have better things to do.
What about it?
I was going to tell you to come over to our house.
But Noona's boyfriend is coming over, so I came out.
"Boyfriend"?
Oh, you don't know.
There's a guy that my mom is totally crazy for.
His job and family are no joke.
Is he at your house?
He comes by often.
I'm at school, so I don't see him often. It's a relief.
When the two of them are together, oh I could vomit.
It's quite a spectacle.
Gosh, seriously.
- Sorry.
- Hey, Man.
What's with you?
Come on, you punk.
Jin Ah.
Why are you standing there like that?
Gyu Min bought me and your dad some couple scarves.
You don't know how nice they are.
- Come look.
- I need to change.
Hey.
Gyu Min, eat up. There's lots of food.
Why would you do something like this?
Be quiet.
We heard from Gyu Min that you fought.
"A fight"?
When you date, you can fight once in a while.
He made a decision to come and yet you glare at him like that?
I don't know why you're getting more indifferent.
Did you drink?
How can I not drink?
He's made it so that I can't be sober.
- How old am I that you and Dad are–
- Exactly.
How old are you that you can't even keep a man?
Why must your parents get involved?
Aren't you embarrassed at all?
Be better, would you?
I keep telling you this.
Where do you think you'll meet another guy like Gyu Min?
He works at one of the top law firms, and look at his family.
His parents went to Seoul University.
There's nothing more to hope for.
Your future husband is important,
but your future parents-in-law are also important.
It's a great fortune for you to meet someone like Gyu Min.
You should be incredibly grateful.
You should know that before you act up.
You better not frown when you come back out.
- Bye.
- Goodbye.
Come home with me.
It's okay.
Is it because of my sister's boyfriend?
Why does it matter? We will be in my room.
It's fine.
I should meet your parents sometime, though, so I'll make time for another day.
I was going to ask you to put games on my console.
That's why I'm not going.
Bye.
Seung Ho!
What is taking her so long?
Oh my.
Mom, Dad.
Don't be surprised.
It seems like Gyu Min wants me to look this way.
He says that I'm too much like konjac jelly.
He's saying I'm too bland.
Honey, why are you just sitting there? You should look at me.
How do I look?
Do you like it?
It's not enough for you, is it?
Should I have worn something shorter?
Should I have put on redder lipstick?
Net stockings!
- I don't have any, so...
- Hey!
Right, Mom and Dad are here.
That's a bit overboard, right?
Yes. Sit down, sit down.
Sit down, okay?
I'm craving wine, though.
Aren't you dating anyone?
No.
Wow. How unusual for you.
Not even a little something with anyone?
So you do have something. Tell me about it.
What do you want to know?
Oh, something's not going well.
Is she difficult?
She's scary.
Why? Who is it? How old?
Twenty-three? Twenty-four?
Thirty-five.
You crazy punk. Are you crazy?
You've become a psycho after coming back from the U.S.
What? Thirty-five years old?
That's the same age as our sisters.
Can you actually have something with her?
To put it simply, it'd be like dating Yun Jin Ah.
Oh, I'm getting goosebumps.
Hey, don't go any further and end it.
Don't get chained down and suffer.
Mom.
When you were dating Dad, did he ever cheat on you?
Come on. What kind of person do you think I am?
For me, Kim Mi Yeon is my one and only.
Here's looking at you, kid.
"One and only"? Yes, right. I even caught him.
Really?
Why would you bring that up?
So what did you do, Mom?
Did you let it go?
Let it go? Why would I? I hit him on the back of his head.
- Like this?
- Ouch!
- That hurts.
- Hey.
There's a limit to joking around.
Why are you acting like that?
Honey, stay put.
Gyu Min.
Yes, Mother.
You had another woman besides Jin Ah.
This is so absurd.
I never saw you that way. How could you betray us like that?
Did you really? You punk...
Dad!
He's probably still there, right?
Gosh, they're probably making such a scene.
You said your parents are home.
Mom and Dad encourage them.
You should just use words.
Goodness. Really?
Honey, my gosh.
What kind of a punk...
Honey, you'll get hurt.
I... I admit I was wrong.
But it wasn't just me.
She cheated, too. She has another man.
Lee Gyu Min!
What? It's not like I'm making things up.
Is this why you came here? Is this why you came?
Do you think it was easy for me to come?
Then why did you come?
Your parents told me to come. Am I supposed to say no?
You should have.
If you had any respect for me or my parents,
you should have politely declined.
If I had drunk more today, it wouldn't have ended with just one hit.
- Jin Ah, what's going on?
- Fine, fine. Hit me.
If that will make you feel better, I'll accept it, so hit me.
How pathetic.
I'm trying to make it work and go back to how it was.
Dream on. That will never happen!
Are you saying that you're really going to break up with me?
Didn't we break up already?
Yun Jin Ah, what's going on here?
I'll explain it all later.
Why later? Do it now.
Should I say it in front of your parents?
Who was that guy who took you away in front of your office?
Who was it?
You pretend.
You just turn me into the trash that cheats, but what about you?
Does it make you feel better to twist things that way?
Then why can't you tell me who he is?
You have no reason to fool me if you didn't cheat.
I'm going crazy because you won't tell me!
I like him!
Yes, he's someone I like. So, what?
Oh my. What do I do?
I'm home.
Seung Ho's home. What am I going to do?
Oh, Jun Hui.
Oh, dear.
Oh.
What's going on?
What happened is...
Oh, it's him!
What do you mean, "It's him"?
Who? Jun Hui?
Tell them!
Let go of that hand.
Hey.
- Hey, hey.
- What are you doing?
Oh my, my son.
Hey, Seo Jun Hui!
- Hey, hey!
- Oh no.
♫ You can dance ♫
♫ Every dance with the guy that gives you the eye, and let him hold you tight ♫
Jin Ah said she liked him. She said she likes him.
I heard you came to my place.
I'm asking if you came to me.
You keep being cute, Noona.
Don't you know how old I am?
Doesn't that depend on who's looking?
Relationships between men and women are about timing.
What if the timing is always off?
I better move fast.
Make things hot.
Noona, you know...
If by chance...
"If by chance"?
If by chance, I...
You what?
If...
If I asked you to buy me food tomorrow, would you?
♫ And don't forget who's taking you home and in whose arms you're gonna be ♫