Zhu Niannian
You
transferred to
our class
That's right
Tian Ye
From now on, we'll be desk mates
Going to the bathroom
I just transferred here
I thought you were Deng Shasha
Sorry about that
You scared me to death
Tian Ye
Switch desks with me
No way
My desk mate is the Chinese class representative
You can copy his Chinese homework from now on
Besides
Isn't Chinese your worst subject?
You're mistaken
Physics is my worst subject
And I can copy from the school beauty
Tian Ye
Then switch seats with me
From now on, physics homework
how about I do it for you?
Don't think
I don't know what you two are up to.
With you two looking like that,
the school beauty would never like you.
She wouldn't like you either.
Your comeback
has no effect on Tian Ye at all.
Tian Ye
just say yes.
I give up.
Just say yes.
Tian Ye
What are you guys doing?
No, no, no.
It's nothing, really.
How come after just a few days apart
your relationship has progressed this much?
Report.
Nian Nian, you're here.
Nian Nian.
You suddenly switched subjects.
You really caught me off guard.
I don't know if it was just a moment of impulse,
or
if there was some other reason.
I still want to try to keep you.
Teacher.
I've already moved to Class One.
I know you've already moved.
But I still want to leave you a way back.
Think about it.
The joint exams are coming up soon.
You weren't doing well in science before.
It's hard to get good grades.
I think
before the joint exams,
you should think it over carefully.
Class Eight will always welcome you back.
Teacher.
Don't worry.
I definitely won't regret it.
As for my science subjects,
I'll take them very, very seriously.
You really don't need to worry.
Stand up.
Good morning, teacher.
Good morning, students.
This in-class quiz
I have finished grading.
Everyone has made overall progress.
However,
only one student
got a perfect score.
It must be you.
Zhu Niannian transferred to another class.
You're the best at history in our class now.
It's her.
Chen Jing'an.
Let's give her a round of applause.
Actually, when Chen Jing'an
first transferred to our class,
I was especially worried
that you might not keep up with the grades.
But
now I see there was no need to worry.
All I can say is
Chen Jing'an
is truly talented in the humanities.
Come here.
Congratulations.
Thank you, teacher.
I will keep working hard.
Go back to your seat.
Whose is this?
I accidentally bought too much.
It would be a waste if I can't finish it.
If you don't mind,
I don't mind at all.
You can even do it like this?
This is way too advanced.
Oh my god.
You’re not going to snitch to the teacher, are you?
What are you talking about?
How did you learn to be just like
Chen Jing’an?
Here, take it.
The school beauty really gets special treatment.
Shasha
From now on, we'll be classmates.
Do you want some water?
No, thanks.
Before Nian Nian switched classes, she specifically told me
that you are her best friend.
She wanted us to get along well too.
Really.
I just can't figure it out.
She was doing just fine,
so why did she change her major?
I asked her, but she wouldn't say.
Maybe she just
simply didn't want to study liberal arts anymore.
Look,
there are plenty of people who switch majors in the second year.
Isn't that pretty common?
I don't think it's that simple.
Lately, it seems like
she's always hiding something in her heart.
Something's off.
You...
Don't overthink it.
She's totally normal.
I'm her best friend.
I definitely know her better than you do.
At home,
how do you get along with Chen Changning?
We just get along as usual.
So what's he like at home?
Is he very different from how he is outside?
Let's not talk about Chen Changning anymore.
Let's talk about something else.
Then I'll ask one last question.
Does he like any girl?
I don't think so.
No, he doesn't.
That's great.
Let good things stay within the family.
I think Nian Nian and Chen Changning
are actually a good match.
What do you think?
Let's do a good deed.
Let's try to set them up.
It would be a shame if two such great people aren't together.
That would be a pity.
Keep your voice down.
Don't let others hear.
So it's settled then.
After all, you're Chen Changning's sister.
And also Nian Nian's friend.
You'll have plenty of chances to set them up.
We've agreed on this, okay?
Nian Nian.
You told Chen Jing'an you were worried about me?
Chen Jing'an already told me.
We're getting along pretty well now.
Nian Nian.
It's Chen Changning.
So childish.
I heard from Chen Jing'an
that you transferred to the physics class.
Are you getting used to it?
It's okay.
Chen Jing'an.
She's really something.
She actually helped Nian Nian and Chen Changning get together.
I heard from Chen Jing'an
that you've helped her a lot.
If you have anything going on at school
or need any help,
you can always let me know.
Senior Chen Changning,
our Niannian
switched from liberal arts to science.
Although she works extremely hard,
but
her foundation in physics, chemistry, and biology is still a bit weak.
If you have time,
could you help our Niannian
with some tutoring?
Deng Shasha, what's with you?
My grades are good enough to tutor him!
Niannian,
don't pretend to be shy at a time like this.
This is
a chance to be alone
and a great opportunity to build your relationship.
You can't miss it.
Forget it.
Chen Changning definitely won't agree.
Senior,
please think about it.
Sure.
Then it depends on when Zhu Niannian
has time.
This Chen Changning must be fake, right?
Senior.
That's how it is.
What about Nian Nian?
Her family is pretty strict.
If she wants to go out,
she has to tell her parents in advance.
Otherwise,
we'll wait until she confirms the time,
then we can make plans.
Okay.
Alright.
Nian Nian.
Do you think Chen Changning
is interested in you too?
Otherwise, why would he start a conversation with you?
But next time, you shouldn't
be too reserved.
What if he misunderstands
and thinks you don't want to talk to him?
What would you do then?
What nonsense are you talking about?
I'm being serious.
From my intuition,
he definitely likes you.
Impossible.
Nian Nian, be more confident.
You're so outstanding,
good-looking,
gentle,
and have great grades.
If he gets to know you,
he'll definitely like you.
Nian Nian.
Don't be shy.
Changning is here.
Come in.
Earlier, you
asked me about
the issue of memory exchange, right?
I’ve gathered some information.
Take a look.
Sixi Maruko
Yes.
These
are all from Sixi Maruko’s
science fiction novels.
I compiled some sci-fi concepts from them.
I think
some of the principles in there
are related to memory exchange.
See if
they might inspire you.
Although science fiction novels are fictional,
the knowledge points in them
are solid and real.
If you don’t believe me,
you can go read Sixi Maruko’s novels
and study them carefully.
Also,
I recommend a few movies for you to watch.
They’re all listed above.
Teacher,
this Sixi Maruko
isn’t that you?
Sorry.
I’ll return the book to Teacher Fan.
Okay.
Teacher Deng
Let him know later.
I left it here for him.
Okay, no problem.
By the way, Teacher Deng,
You
Is it really Four Happiness Meatballs?
Teacher Yu
has also read my book.
I've heard a little about it.
See,
the history teacher
has read the science fiction novel I wrote.
During break time,
you should read it carefully too.
It will definitely help your studies.
Okay.
Chen Jing'an
You're really great.
From now on,
besides Nian Nian,
you're my best friend.
Did something good happen to you?
Something amazing!
Thank you so much this time.
That's all I'll say.
The joint exam is coming up soon.
I'm going to study hard now.
Put away all the books on the table.
If there's no space, put them in my office.
Come on.
Hurry.
Nian Nian
Do you want me to help you?
No need.
I'm very strong.
It's fine.
Come here.
You should go back.
Jingan
The exam is over.
All examinees, please put down your pens immediately.
Zheng Chuan
Come to my place to watch a movie later.
Let's invite Chen Jing'an too.
Sure.
After three days of exams,
we can finally relax.
Got any new movies?
Yeah.
Japanese ones.
What kind?
You wouldn't like them.
They're not suitable for you.
Let's go find Chen Jing'an.
Okay.
Let's go.
I'm Chen Jing'an!
You won't show me the good stuff.
How did you do on the exams?
Zhang Fenglai from Class 2 made a statement.
She said she wants to surpass you.
Not bad.
The English reading section was a bit beyond the syllabus this time.
There were a lot of rare words I hadn't seen before.
The average score probably won't be very high.
The one about aerospace.
Last year, the US reported new achievements in aerospace.
It was an excerpt from a magazine article.
I've read it.
No way.
You even predicted the topic?
My aunt sent me the magazine.
I just happened to glance at it.
Boss.
Let me see it too.
I want to see how many points I got.
No time.
Where are you going?
Got something to do.
Tianye
That Korean movie last time was so boring.
Today's one has to be more exciting.
Don't worry.
The exciting part is coming up soon.
Look, look, the exciting part is about to start.
Stop pretending, stop it.
Come on, Zheng Chuan.
Can we not watch horror movies?
Stop messing around.
Since when have you ever been scared of horror movies?
Tianye
Is someone here at home?
My mom's here, my mom's here.
My mom's here.
Why is it so dark? Why didn't you turn on the lights?
Hello, Auntie.
Auntie.
Jing'an is here.
What were you two just doing?
Watching a movie.
At night.
Stay for dinner.
What do you want to eat? I'll make it for you.
No need, Auntie.
My brother is still at home waiting for me to eat.
Auntie, I have something to do too, so I'll head out.
Uh...
Wait.
I'll deal with you later, kid.
Jing'an
Hello.
I saw you mention in your post
that you've experienced a swap.
Yeah, that's right.
Do you know what triggered the swap?
How did you switch back in the end?
How long did it take to switch back?
Did it cause any harm to your body?
Big brother,
I was just bragging online.
Is it really necessary to dig so deep into this?
No way.
My son has grown up.
He even dares to watch those adult movies.
Back in the day, we were only twenty.
What are you saying? What are you saying?
Kids at sixteen or seventeen
are the most curious about this.
Your son might be the same.
Very curious.
But the key point is,
he even watched it with Jing'an.
Do you think there's something wrong with his head?
If you put it that way, this is kind of serious.
How could it not be serious?
You should have a good talk with him later.
What can I even say?
I'm an adult, talking to him about this...
It's not exactly comfortable.
It's the 21st century.
Why are your ideas still so old-fashioned?
Are you going to talk to him or not?
Talk about what?
Come here.
Your dad wants to talk to you.
Come on, come on.
I have something to tell you.
I need to talk to you.
What's up?
Shameless.
Be honest.
Say it.
Movie.
At your age,
watching this
isn't appropriate.
And you even watched it with Jing'an.
No,
we just watched a horror movie together.
Son, I've been through this.
Who watches horror movies so sneakily?
We really just watched a horror movie.
Last time,
my mom
got so scared she cried, right?
It's just that
I didn't want her to lose face in front of my classmates.
Do you know what time it is?
What are you all chatting about?
Go to bed, now.
I'm exhausted.
You sold me out again, didn't you?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Oh my god
Chen Changning is first in the whole school again this time
Definitely Tsinghua or Peking University material
Don’t be jealous
She won the physics competition last semester
She’s already got a guaranteed admission
Nian Nian, did you hear that?
Chen Changning is really amazing
Let me check your score
Let’s go, let’s go
Look at Chen Jing’an and Zhu Nian Nian’s grades
Didn’t they just switch majors?
They actually made it into the top ten in the grade
Zhu Nian Nian is first in physics again
These scores are almost inhuman
Good-looking and good grades
How are we supposed to compete?
Nian Nian, you’re incredible too
How did you do it?
Keep it low-key, keep it low-key
You’re amazing, a perfect score
A hundred points
Chen Jing’an
Why are you here?
To celebrate, of course
Impressive, Chen Jing’an
Just switched to the liberal arts class and already scored so well
Teacher Lin in Class One
Keeps praising you to the skies
Your favorite snacks
I bought you a lot
Thank you
I don’t eat spicy strips
I mean
Recently
I’ve got pimples, so I can’t eat spicy food
It’s okay
Then
When you don’t have pimples
You can eat them again
You go back to the classroom first.
Thanks for the spicy snack.
Thank you, thank you.
Look at this new book I bought.
Thunder Assault
The writing on it is so good.
We are the long sword of the People's Air Force.
We are the shoulders of our motherland.
I've wanted this book for a long time.
The packaging isn't opened yet, don't open it for me.
Tian Ye
What's wrong? You look so down.
How many times has it been now?
Still can't face your own grades?
I feel like Chen Jing'an has no feelings for me.
I think I'm about to lose her as a friend.
What's wrong with you?
She used to ignore me before.
She didn't even tell me when she changed departments.
I just gave her
her favorite spicy snacks, but she didn't want them.
Don't feel too bad.
A woman's heart is impossible to fathom.
A forced melon
is never sweet.
Some people
are destined to just pass through your life.
I feel really upset.
It hurts.
Xinyi,
at the beginning of next month
is our school's 60th anniversary
celebration.
You're the class president of Class 8
and also the arts committee member.
It's a good chance to organize your classmates.
Prepare some talent performances.
I heard people from the TV station will come to record.
It's just right,
after the joint exams are over,
you all can relax a bit.
No problem.
Teacher.
What's wrong with you?
No.
I've had a friendship with Chen Jing'an for over ten years.
I can't just let it end like this.
So what can you do about it?
I'm going to talk to Old Lin.
I want to switch departments.
Dude,
don't be impulsive.
I've thought it through.
I'll just say
that when I saw my entrance exam results,
I reflected deeply on my failure.
I realized
I'm not cut out for science.
Maybe
if I join the liberal arts class,
I'll have a chance to start over.
Looks like you're really going for it.
Chen Jing'an,
I didn't expect
you'd be so talented in liberal arts.
You really should have joined our class earlier.
But it's not too late now.
Sorry, teacher.
I need to borrow Chen Jing'an for a moment.
Let's go.
I want to tell Tian Ye about us switching places.
Why?
Didn't you say
we can't let anyone else know?
Tian Ye thinks I want to end our friendship.
He said today that he wants to transfer to the liberal arts class.
I'm about to go crazy.
I'm just afraid of being exposed.
That's why I didn't dare get too close to him.
I'm not blaming you either.
I just don't want to lose him as a friend.
He can be trusted.
Do you agree with me telling him?
If you want to tell him,
I support you.
That's fine then.
I'm leaving now.
Chen Jing'an.
Hurry to class.
Zhu Niannian.
You brought me here
for what?
Tian Ye.
What I'm about to tell you
you might not believe.
But you have to trust me.
What I say
is all true.
Actually,
I am Chen Jing'an.