Not
You fall into myλέflige and express your secret to me
Are you angry or not? You have to say goodbye to me
In my arms, who are you?
How can you hide in my soft heart?
I want to see you closer
From your little heart
The sky is gentle and you are not in use
I want to see you closer
I will keep your secret and look for you
I am waiting for you
I want to see you closer
From your little heart
The sky is gentle and you are not in use
I want to see you closer
I will keep your secret and look for you
What's up? When are you coming back?
Tomorrow, the afternoon
The wedding gown is ready
Do you want to show it to you?
No
You are professional with these things
But remember this
You must be a machine
Don't worry
I will show you
These things are too easy for us
Since it's ready
Tomorrow morning
I will send the wedding gown
I can go to the morning
To get the money
I will watch you
If you do well
There is an external reward
Good bye
Go
Nanxi
I know this game
I won't go
He is the one who is looking for you
If you join
You have a great chance to win
I don't care about winning
I just want to do my job well
I heard
The competition now
Is very good in China
It has a great impact
It's even more effective
I can't go there
I can go there as a cannon
You must join this time
I won't go there if you go there
Listen to me
You forgot how the doctor told you
What's the relationship between you and the competition?
Nanxi
Think about it
If you join
If there is no name
There is no effect
If there is a name
It must be helpful to you
And if you get your disease
That's not perfect
Go
Gu Nanxi
Hello
Qin Shijie
Where are you?
Ximen, did you see it?
I'm in Chunzhou
I'm back after the show
What news?
Hurry up and take a look
I'm here
What are you doing?
No
You said it slowly
I don't know what the news is
I'm afraid Ximen will send you a phone
I hope you can explain to me
Okay
I'm here
He's doing quite well
Let things continue to fall
Continue to grow
Let's go.
Nanxi,
don't think too much.
There must be a misunderstanding.
This is what the ugly kid's truth report said.
Look, I won't kill him.
Nanxi, believe me.
I promise you,
Qin Shiqi is definitely not like this.
Why are you laughing?
You should take a look at it.
Is there any familiar thing here?
He really is so creepy.
He must be stretching his legs so much.
He's just very energetic.
He's my kind of person.
There should be a足.
And I don't know either.
Could voices such as
the legacy of the dare 필 worship
be true to you?
Are we talking about laughs?
Why is An Keke in the crew?
I think it's because of work.
Then,
is Shiqi and An Keke...
It's okay.
They're fine.
Don't worry.
What a pity.
We should worry about Shiqi now.
When the crew is shooting,
the news about her
will be very influential.
I don't know
who's actually doing it.
What's the purpose?
But we must find a way to help her.
I'll call Shiqi and ask her.
Shiqi's phone.
Hello, Shiqi.
Hello.
Nanxi.
You saw the news, right?
Don't.
I saw it.
You don't need to explain it to me.
I understand.
Thank you, Nanxi.
How about this?
I'll go back to the company right now
and study the solution.
See you later.
Jin Zhiqi.
I know you don't want people to be upset.
But you're too much.
Dawei, don't worry.
I'm not worried.
You know the company
and the money you paid for it.
How much did you spend?
You know my position.
I can't do this.
I believe in the money.
I want to trust my friends.
I want your fans to trust me.
I want you to trust me.
Let's explain it to everyone.
What do you mean?
You're so unfair.
Who believes you?
How's the crew now?
Is there any impact?
It seems...
It seems to be still on the scene.
What's the rush?
We have to finish the work
of the film first.
And then we'll
slowly solve it and discuss it.
That makes sense.
Such a big boss
can't do anything.
Who are you?
I didn't say you.
I'm going back to the crew tonight.
You're the one who's on this side.
I'm leaving.
Be good.
I'll leave.
Come back.
I really am sorry
that I kept you on this side of the movie.
I don't know anything.
When you were playing with the Guo Jia family,
you said you wanted to,
but you said you didn't want to.
But I told you not to hurt Shi Qi.
Miss An Da, I'm not your subordinate.
I don't have any obligation to do anything for you.
So you didn't plan to work with me at the beginning?
I'm smart. I'm a little smart.
Why?
I just praised you for being smart.
Why are you making a mess again?
You want to know that?
Fine.
Then I'll tell you that
you're the only one who has and isn't you.
But you're in my sight now.
Because you and Qin Shi Qi's relationship
will make my plan more sweet and simple.
Aren't you afraid that I'll be too serious about what I did to you?
So you changed.
Because of Qin Shi Qi's scandal,
the company will open a shareholders' meeting tomorrow.
At that time,
Li Na will be the father.
You can be the real controller of the treasure of Kai Ge.
At that time, no matter what happens, you don't care.
Smart.
But you have to get Kai Ge in many ways.
Why do you want to hurt Shi Qi?
Like you,
I don't just want to be Kai Ge.
I also want to be Gu Nan Xi.
Xiao Ru.
In fact, you're also a pitiful person.
Me?
Yes.
Just like the previous me,
I understand this now.
We can't hurt anyone with the name of love.
Do you think you'll return to your side after you get the treasure of Kai Ge?
No. Love is not materialistic.
I can't get Qin Shi Qi's heart in Qin Shi Qi's hands.
That's just an excuse for your failure.
No matter what you think,
Xiao Ru, I'm telling you, you touched my bottom line.
The person who hurt Shi Qi is my enemy.
You're just a coincidence.
Just you?
Let go of yourself.
You've been in the industry for so many years.
You don't know how to be careful.
How do I know that I have eyes?
You're reasonable.
Stay away from An Ke Ke.
Luckily, Nan Xi is generous.
Otherwise, you'll explain.
Enough. Let's not talk about it now.
Let's think of a solution.
Shi Qi, shut up.
Shut up.
You know what to do.
How do you solve it?
I've asked someone.
The news is about a famous dog team in the industry.
Since they can report the first news,
I believe there will be other news in the future.
Qin Shi Qi, what are you doing in the crew?
I didn't do anything.
Enough.
I think they've reported the photo.
Then we'll have to wait for them.
Then there must be a reason.
I think they're all doing it for money.
They've been using it for so long.
Someone will contact Shi Qi or his company
to talk about the payment.
Don't be anxious.
Then we can solve it quickly.
No.
Why should we give money?
I didn't do anything wrong.
When is it?
Can we solve it with money?
Isn't it good?
Yufan,
we can't solve it with money.
If we spend money,
it's like we've forgotten that this news is true.
We can't spend it.
This is a physical problem.
What do you think we should do now?
How about this?
I'll be the one to face it.
Okay.
Let's face it together.
We'll admit our love relationship.
Not together.
It's myself.
What do you mean?
Shi Qi,
you're still in the upper class.
The public love is a big blow to your career.
You can't be publicized.
Dan Xi,
what do you mean?
I mean,
I'm Shi Qi's sister.
So,
will it really work?
Of course.
There are two girls in the picture.
I'm her sister.
Another girl,
even if she's in a normal relationship with her,
it's not a boat to her.
Then the company will be publicized.
This thing will go on.
Yes, yes.
That's how it will end.
No.
This thing is so unfair to you.
Shi Qi,
calm down.
What do you mean?
Gu Dan Xi,
you're my girlfriend.
Why should I make you suffer?
You said a lie,
and you're a liar.
Do you understand this?
Shi Qi,
your current mission is to shoot a movie.
You can't share these things.
Okay, I don't need you to do that.
Then we'll really break up.
No one will say that.
Break up?
You're so clear-headed.
Do you want to say that
you're my sister?
Shi Qi,
can't you hear me?
Is this for your own good?
Now,
the most important thing is to solve the problem first.
You go back and make up.
Look at you two.
Let's talk about something.
How about this?
Let's keep the southern west's plan in mind.
Let's see the development of the future.
We'll make a deal.
Okay?
Yufan,
talk to the southern west first.
I'll send Shi Qi to eat.
Okay?
You're crazy.
I know it's hard at the novice level,
but he wouldn't either.
How do you know this?
You said we were always one when Master Shi Qi inside.
It's a meaningful moment.
men
I knew he'd get nervous.
The more Nan Xi says this,
the more it proves that he doesn't want to be separated.
Shiqin,
I was quite worried that you two couldn't make it.
I'm getting more and more envious of you two
after this.
Look at your brother-in-law.
You and my brother-in-law are good.
Okay.
I'm happy to see you two.
Brother-in-law,
I'm begging you.
Stop it.
I know.
I'm helping you to keep Nan Xi safe.
Don't let her do anything stupid.
Yes.
She really doesn't know the power of netizens.
Once she does that,
the secret will be revealed.
There's nothing left.
What are you going to do?
I'm not quite sure yet.
Please look at me.
Wait.
Let's go first.
講报告MAE
Guys.
Wait.
I'm so worried.
Now the situation in the idol's room
is getting worse.
How can the company
sign the contract with the director?
Right.
The company has invested in the film industry.
This is the field
that the company has never touched.
It's so big.
Now that it's out of this,
I guess it's a flood in eight cities.
Linan, how can you handle it?
Uncle.
Before the company makes all the decisions,
the directors usually vote for it.
I think
it's not the time to be in charge.
Linan,
although Li Chunlin has some problems,
he did say something right.
You're not suitable to be in the position of the president.
It seems that you all have a background today.
Linan,
I suggest you to let go as soon as possible.
Otherwise, the company will be in your hands sooner or later.
Do you all think so?
Linan,
you really don't want to be in this matter.
And recently,
you've been busy with work in the company.
It's too hard.
You should take a good rest.
Xiaorui,
I really want to see you.
Linan,
I did this for your own good.
I suggest you
you should let Xiaorui be your main villain.
Before that,
how old were you
under the leadership ofómissing President Xia?
Director Wang, you're wrong.
But you should
make the final decision about this.
I believe that
everyone's eyes are white colored.
OK,
Forget my voters.
You were able to kill
my uncle?
I'm leaving.
Don't mind him.
Li Na is still in a good mood.
Let's give him a break.
It's good to have a break.
Well, President Xiao.
We are a group of five.
You are the substitute.
I think you have no opinions.
Well,
I'll be more respectful.
From now on,
I'll take all the blame for Li Na.
I'll be more respectful.
And,
I've decided
to stop the background information of the crew.
And end the cooperation between Qin Shiqi and him.
President Chen.
Yes, Qin Shiqi.
It's okay.
Director.
What's going on?
Why didn't you start the work today?
Shiqi.
I think you should know something.
What is it?
It's because of you.
Kaige's jewelry
has been decided to withdraw the money from us.
Reject the money?
You know all the inspections here?
That's right.
Many decibels here still exist.
Is it right?
Big brother,
please give me some information check it up.
Hello?
You areammed, are not you?
What is that?
I'll pass on my love only to you.
No, I don't want to face you.
This way.
This way and this way.
Let me ask you about this letter first because you said you were hungry.
Sister Lan Xi.
KO?
Why are you here?
Sister Lan Xi, can you look for me to give you完了 advice?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry? Why?
If it wasn't for me,
it wouldn't have been like this.
Don't say that.
We're all victims.
Someone must have planned this.
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry.
I should have told you earlier.
It's all Xiao Rui.
Xiao Rui made a mistake.
She made me confused and I'm with her.
If I told you earlier,
I wouldn't have...
I didn't expect
it's all Xiao Rui's fault.
Sister Nanxi,
how should I make up for it?
We're in a hurry to help Shiqi.
Yes.
I'll do whatever you say.
How about we help her make a statement?
Okay.
I have experience in this.
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
What's wrong, Grandpa?
Disgusting.
Is it that serious?
Okay, I get it.
What's wrong, Sister Nanxi?
Brother Kai withdraws his money.
Shiqi is taking the film break.
It's all my fault.
Don't say that.
The money must be in Xiao Rui's plan.
Sister Nanxi,
I have a way.
What way?
It's all my fault.
Don't worry.
I'll take responsibility for it.
Wait for my good news.
Xiao Rui.
I was going to look for you.
But I found you weren't here.
So I waited for you here.
Nanxi,
I prepared this for you personally.
No need.
I and Li Na are done.
It's over.
Nanxi,
I promised to hide things from Li Na before.
But you have to believe me.
I did this
for the future between us.
Li Na has left Kai Pavilion.
Now Kai Pavilion is my fault.
As long as you're here,
you can come back anytime.
Nanxi,
you're my love.
Love?
Love is not worth it
to say it out loud.
Don't say that.
Then what do I say?
Thank you for your love.
I love that boy so much.
Gu Nanxi,
are you that heartless?
Heartless?
Is there any problem between us?
You've always loved yourself.
You've never loved me.
An Keke has told me
what you did before.
Whatever you want to do,
just do it.
We won't give up.
You can do it.
Step down,
to two,
hurt yourself,
and hug.
Episode 7
Grandpa.
I have something to ask you to help me.
It's the information about the investment of Qin Shiqi.
You already know?
I've read the news.
So you agreed?
Actually, Qin Shiqi's crew is poor and not enough.
You see, there are many things in society that need help.
Why should I invest in Qin Shiqi?
Yan Yan, if it's not because of me,
won't it turn out like this?
Keke, I am your grandfather.
But now you are already old.
You should solve your own mistakes.
Yan Yan.
If you don't give me a good reason today,
I won't help you even if you say you are a big man.
I like Qin Shiqi.
Didn't she already have a girlfriend?
Yan Yan, I've been thinking a lot lately.
Sometimes, I don't necessarily have to do it.
I can also be a little bit of a burden.
I like Shiqi.
I just want to see her happy.
Then I am satisfied.
If she is unhappy with me,
then why should I force her?
Yan Yan, actually, I am doing this not only for Shiqi,
but also for Yi Hai's jewelry.
Yi Hai's jewelry has always been a big problem.
Actually, our cash flow is very strong.
It is a lack of market.
I used to keep looking for a good propaganda environment.
But the effect is not very ideal.
You want to promote our Yi Hai's jewelry through Qin Shiqi's play.
But now, in addition to this matter,
whether the new play can be released or not,
I don't know if the risk is too high.
I have already thought about it.
This matter is because of me.
I will let the company release a new article tomorrow
to clarify my relationship with Shiqi
and to fight for the lowest public opinion.
As for Sister Nan Xi,
I think Shiqi will have a way.
It seems that you have already planned everything.
Isn't that so? I will do everything in my power
to help you get this winter wind.
Yan Yan, you...
I have already known about it since the incident happened.
You will find me.
It is still so difficult for me to do this before the cold.
Sit down.
Ke Ke, I am a businessman.
I am not like a charity.
But after hearing what you said,
I suddenly felt that my granddaughter
has grown up.
She is all over the country.
Go ahead.
Here is the investment.
It's yours.
Thank you, Yan Yan.
If you say it again,
this is the investment.
I will ask the responsibility.
Don't worry, Yan Yan.
I didn't expect that the one who sent the charcoal in the snow
would be Ke Ke.
But Ke Ke is quite good.
The previous things
should be too much for Shiqi.
My brother is a little charming.
Of course.
I have a lot of eyes.
Okay.
The crisis of Shiqi has been solved for the time being.
Let's think about the competition.
You really want to participate?
Of course.
I tell you,
this matter is not discussed.
I heard from the internal news that
you are also participating in the treasure hunt.
Don't you want to defeat Xiao Rui?
Okay, I will participate.
I am very happy to be a part of this project.