Not sleep yet?
i had a bad dream.
Here.
Your eyes are puffy.
I cried…
i dreamt
about you.
And you cried? what for?
Just a bad dream.
When is your next appointment with the therapist？
I got no clue
or I have to check the info on the receipt.
Why?
I…
I just…
I just have bad dreams a lot lately.
Want to solve my sleep problems.
I need you to tag along with me
What? Are you a kid when you're in love?
You really need someone to be with
even when you drink water or go see a doctor?
Do I need to escort you to
bask in the sun when we are old?
Yeah, I’m a kid, okay?
I need to be accompanied like hell.
Is it a yes or a no?
Gotta check out my meds.
I’ll go with you after I finish taking them.
OK?
Go check out for the receipt.
You can do it tomorrow.
The receipt won’t fly away itself.
You didn’t notice the remaining pills?
I still got some left.
That’s fine. Let’s go to sleep.
Raccoon Chao.
What?
Did take your meds?
Of course I did.
I did it every day!
So, where did you go?
I…
My friend just texted me.
We had a chat outside.
It was nothing.
Come on. I’m sorry.
Don’t be mad at me.
It’s ok. You don’t have to apologize to me.
But I will take you to the therapist.
I told you I still have my meds.
But…
Your episodes are much more serious than I thought.
I need you to go to the clinic.
Just have another check.
It’s nothing to do with chatting with a friend.
Why should I go to the clinic?
Raccoon Chao!
What?
Your friend is not even exist.
You were the only person there.
You were soliloquizing.
You are out of your mind.
My friend was definitely there.
I’m out of my mind?
You were the only person in the laundry.
You spoke to no one and my mind is just fine!
What are you talking about?
My friend was there.
He was there.
Fine.
Call him right now.
Let me comfort him.
Fine.
I can call him.
(Mom)
It’s late.
He should be asleep now.
I wan to be alone and clear my mind.
You were the only person in the laundry.
You were soliloquizing.
Story telling is over.
Still don’t want to sleep?
Or do you want the magic to sleep with open eyes?
Why does it must be
square and intact?
It’s special because of the
missing pieces.
Humans are dangerous. Haven’t you learned your lesson?
I was not the only one there.
Why’d you said that?
Why…
(Dolphin)
(It’s been a long time, Raccoon.)
(Raccoon)
(Who are you? Why do you have my childhood picture?)
(I met you when you were a child.)
(Why do you have this one?)
(I don’t even have this. Who the fuck are you?)
(You don’t recognize me? I’m Dolphin.)
(You used to call me Big Bro. I live in Nanfang'ao, too.)
(You wanna go out sometime?)
(I’m not there. It’s just a region setting.)
(Don’t be kidding me. You really know me?)
(I just can’t remember.)
I’ll celebrate your birthday the day after tomorrow. Come to meet me.)
(Maybe you will remember then.)
Raccoon Chao.
You are…
I’m Big Bro. The one who sent you the pictures.
Do you recognize me now?
I think I do…
But I don’t remember any detail.
Human brain is amazing.
Just take a break.
You might recall everything later.
How’s that?
Get any better after seeing the ocean?
Every time I go to the aquarium,
I would sit in front of the biggest glass wall.
By staring at it and doing nothing,
I can get tranquility.
But it’s different from an aquarium to the ocean.
You can hear waves from the ocean.
I think it’s better.
I can’t get better
when I hear the waves.
I would be frustrated.
You won’t be when I’m with you.
so why do you have my childhood pictures?
I just told you.
Give your brain a chance to rest.
No rush.
Oh…
Do you remember the fried shrimp cake?
The vender you loved when you were little
is now a famous shop right now.
I do remember.
So it is not a vender anymore?
A famous shop, huh?
I remember that your mom hate you for
eating too much fried shrimp cake at that time
You would lie down on the floor.
And you would cry and make a big scene.
He wouldn’t stop until your mom
give you the permission to buy it.
such a crying baby.
Wanna try the fried shrimp cake later?
Sure, I miss it.
It’s weird that when you were a kid,
you didn’t like to stay at home.
you preferred to come to the beach.
You used paper board
to build a funny house
and you always liked to do role playing.
Tried to assign who could be the right family members.
I think it’s the same even if you are an adult.
You save money to buy a house.
You find somebody to make a family.
It’s like a formula which you need to be strictly followed.
Like it’s a path to having a perfect life.
But…
It’s also boring when you are alone.
After detaching your family,
you could be losing focus.
You alone now?
Not really.
I met a boy who I care about.
But…
Still losing focus?
We. Are not exclusive.
All we have is intimacy.
That’s not what I want.
so what do you want?
Have you discussed with him?
I want…
Play with water.
You must get wet
if you come to the beach.
Go.
Let‘s play a game about holding breath.
Sure.
1 2 3
Get out!
Stop playing!
Get out of the water!
Just get out!
Shut. I was terrified.
What? Worried about me losing you
and sinking into the sea?
You’re insane. Don’t do that again.
I was playing with you.
Why so serious?
Because I would be afraid.
Of what?
I’m not a treasure box
I won’t be sinking into the sea.
Raccoon Chao!
Where are you?
(Kangaroo)
(The password is right. I’m in.)
(He is not home. What should I do?)
(Tina)
(Have you searched everywhere?)
(Kangaroo)
(Everywhere.)
(Tina)
(He had never gone awol.)
(He hasn’t reply my message. What happened to you?)
(Kangaroo)
(Do you know the therapist thing?)
(Tina)
(Why? Is it serious?)
(Kangaroo)
(Serious now.)
(I’m worried about him. Any place he would go?)
(Tina)
(Let me contact his father. Keep in touch.)
(Kangaroo)
(Thanks, Tina.)
Good boy, it’s okay.
You met me just at that time.
You can remember, right?
You can now also remember the
bad dream you had.
A deep deep dream.
About the bottom of the sea.
There’s no sunshine in the bottom of the sea.
And there’s only a secret treasure box there.
It’s the only thing can glow in the dark.
Staring and sparkling.
It’s interesting.
You passed the area every time
when you took a bus.
It was like you can see through the sea.
You cried because of
the shine from the treasure box.
It’s just too bright so that your eyes got hurt.
However you just can’t help going back to the area.
Because you felt when your tears dropped,
you left a part of yourself
to stay with the shiny treasure box.
So what is in the box?
It’s the 18th anniversary that you know me.
Wanna come with me
to open the treasure box?
You know what?
I was really upset.
You didn’t leave any word to me
before you left.
I was so upset.
How could you left me behind?
The people in your dreams were so real.
But they were still bogus.
I was the real one to you.
But I’m afraid of you lying to me.
Like my ex.
My mom abandoned me.
Maybe that’s because I don’t deserve to be treated well.
I want to go to Okinawa.
Okinawa?
Nice place.
I want to eat the food there.
Okinawa onigiri.
Ishigaki Gyu.
Agu pork.
And one thing special.
Red bean sweet ice chips.
You can go to Okinawa to shoot reels.
Full of food in your mind.
I didn’t even get to say my opinions.
Are you a pig?
Okinawa aquarium is nice , too.
Aquariums are everywhere.
It doesn’t have to be Okinawa.
It’s different.
I want to meet cute guys there.
I’m done with your face.
Okay.
Done with me, huh?
Just open your dating App.
You can pick anyone you want.
You still use the dating App? While we are together?
What? You cheater?
I’m not the one who are going to use it.
I offered you a solution for
being done with me.
And you must know one thing.
There’s an awesome function on the App.
You can set your region
to anywhere you like.
Then you can check out the local boys.
Busted!
You picked a lot of guys on that, right?
I did, but I’ve never met them.
Another function for you.
If you are really in the region you’ve set.
You can check out the activity label.
There are many events showed on the list.
Some of it would even give you a link
to purchase the tickets.
Isn’t that convenient?
Sounds great!
I’m going to book the flight ticket.
Can’t wait to meet cute guys on that App.
You mean guys in Okinawa?
Let me check out my day off plan.
What? It’s none of your business.
I want to go alone.
Say that again, Raccoon Chao!
Okay, okay. I’m joking!