（Delete for good in one day.)
(Unblock)
(Search Result: Raccoon0802 not found)
(Do you want to unblock Kangaroo Dai?)
(Kangaroo: Can we meet and make it clear?)
(Kangaroo: I’m really sorry that I hurt you.)
Yes?
Are…
Are you Raccoon?
Yeah, hello.
You are so handsome in the flesh.
I love your reels so bad.
I love you for not showing off your figure
or not playing as stupid influencer.
I love you for being yourself.
I can see the innocence in you.
Thanks.
Um…
Is filmmaking
taking a lot of effort?
You have to buy a fancy camera,
or a nice microphone or something?
Can you teach me
how to be a popular guy like you?
Every time I read your post
I can hear a voice inside my mind.
I just want to be like you.
Such a nice-looking guy
who are loved by everyone.
I’m just a lucky guy
who happens to be loved
by people on the internet.
Who told you that?
Good-looking is an advantage to be an influencer.
You have innate advantages.
You don’t need to do weird things for effect.
People follow you spontaneously.
I bet that many people confess their love for you.
You got no romance issue at all,
right?
Most people like me
for the Raccoon identity.
They do not LOVE me for real.
They just like the image
that a guy smile in front of the camera
when the food is great.
And
they like to have
different positive Raccoon to see in their cell phones
However, that’s not me.
Being Raccoon is not my everything.
You are still liked by many people.
Sometimes being liked
is also terrifying.
Once
I got a message.
Someone sent me a pic of me eating ice.
The picture was took without asking me.
I had no clue.
I found it offended.
It’s like someone staring at me all the time.
Recording everything I do.
I just can’t figure out who
are taking pictures of me right now.
Or even more…
some people would gaze at me.
But instead of talking to me,
they compare me with the photos in their phones.
and even whisper to each other in front of me.
I would rather they confront me.
That’s even better.
Better than the social torturing.
Can you understand?
I got cheated a lot.
You?
I got cheated twice by guys in relationships.
Does that count?
Usually you wait here
or you go for a walk
and then come back later?
I go back home and come back here again.
For real?
You just  come and go
in this short time?
I always wait it here.
Until the dryer finishes its job.
And I found it interesting to stay here.
Got a game for myself.
A game?
Role playing.
What does that mean?
Look over there.
There are clothes wait for reclaiming.
I would wear them
and assign them different characteristics
which I will play.
You just don’t
want to buy new clothes
so you wear them.
It has nothing to do with the money.
I make the clothes alive.
Alive?
Each of them has its specialty.
But it still needs someone to wear it.
Look at me.
If we never have a conversation,
you would judge me by my appearance.
That is to say…
The clothe.
My face, my body.
And my acting.
All of them construct a whole person.
But you ARE a person.
I think you mean “a role.”
You’re right.
A role.
People live
to play different kind of roles.
We played nice kids.
Good students.
Wonderful lovers.
They are characters.
Well, since you have been playing the roles,
Why would you
wanna play and create more of them?
I take it as a life-training.
I trained myself to deal with different kind of things.
So it would be much easier for me
to face my real life.
I don’t remember the story exactly.
But back to my high school life,
A notorious senior student
ran into my classroom.
He wanted to beat me.
I was skinny,
and I would never win the fight.
So I ran away and hide myself.
One day, it just occurred to me.
If I can’t be brave
Then at least I can play like I am.
If my figure is too skinny to compel people,
then I could train myself to be a hunk.
If I’m a well-behaved guy,
I should make myself
look like those douche bags.
So no one dares to provoke me.
Well.
Why didn’t you just tell your family
about the bullying?
Because I don’t have a family.
Makoto: My friend got me an empty room,
so I will live with him.
Makoto: I don't know how to distribute
the furnitures.
Makoto: I don't need them anymore.
Makoto: You can keep them.
Makoto: Do you remember how much
you need me and my
advices before?
Makoto: But you can handle things now.
Makoto: Seems like you don’t need me anymore.
Makoto: So why did I cheat on you?
Makoto: All I want is a guy who needs me.
Makoto: Still. Thank you for taking care of me for eight years.
Makoto: I’m the one who should be blamed.
Makoto: I did hurt you.
1 2 3
Action
Listen, I met an idiot.
He occupied the training equipment
and he kept using his phone.
Shit. I got so upset.
You know what?
While he was using his phone,
I threw his towel away.
And I started to work out.
He was going to have a fight with me.
You know what I said?
“Fuck you,
go get a room with your phone!”
He just got terrified and fled.
Hilarious.
CUT!
Nice job.
1 2 3 Action
Sir, I’ve finished the report.
I sent it to your mailbox.
Please check it out.
Ok. No problem.
I’ll amend it later.
I’ll send it tomorrow morning.
You want it done now?
But I have an appointment today…
Ok. I’m sorry…
I’ll do it now.
OK, 1 2 3, action.
Why?
Why did you leave without saying anything?
Is saying goodbye to me so hard for you?
Why did you left me behind?
Why…
Please just tell me.
Is it because
that I look like
a guy who can suffer all of that?
Are you okay?
Stop crying.
However have you been?
Why me?
Why do I got to deal with this every time?
Why…
I’m sorry.
It’s all my fault.
Please tell me what’s going on?
He had moved out.
It’s not gonna ever happen again.
Please have faith in me.
Raccoon.
I miss you so bad.
Death is not scary.
Life is scary.
Are you alright?
Your heartbeat was so loud
that I thought you’re going to die.
I’ve been about this.
The Sleeping God makes everyone asleep.
Everyone can have his happy journey in the dream.
What about the Sleeping God?
Isn’t he lonely?
You’re not sleeping.
You want a magic to sleep with open eyes?
Is he a performance artist?
Maybe.
He’s really good.
I can tell what he is acting.
Interesting.
What kind of role did you play?
The one inspired from the suit.
When I got that suit.
I can sense a feeling of integrity.
So I thought about a friend.
His job is a manager.
Manager?
He is doing showbiz?
No.
The managers work in a
LGPTQ friendly insurance company.
Sometimes we have misunderstanding
about insurance managers.
Actually their duties are quite diverse.
Not only selling people single insurances
but also selling full-coverage cases.
The managers can bring you
different kind of products.
They give us better plans to manage our lives.
Got it.
And you know what?
There are so many cute gays in the company.
Always makes me feel so great.
Well… you just gave me a huge pause.
Even though we just made it up
I still can feel jealous
when you praise someone.
You just end your last relationship today.
I’m not even mad.
You got jealous now?
I’ve ended up over a year.
How long was the lease?
Over a year?
I don’t think so.
I’m telling the truth.
Are you sure?
YES.
Really?
I promise.
How do you promise that?