Okay, let’s imagine this.
What would you do if you are
a six years old kid facing a unexpected rain.
I would put my yellow raincoat and boots on.
Holding my umbrella.
Doing some puddle jumps.
Well. I said “unexpected” rain.
But you’ve got your gears on.
And even prepared an umbrella.
That’s because…
He has prepared for the accident.
He wants to take care of himself.
Why would he think this way?
He is only a child.
Where’s your mother?
She…
You didn’t answer my message the whole weekend.
You didn’t pick up the phone calls.
I’m sorry.
What happened to you?
Nothing.
If it’s really nothing,
should I know why you didn’t come?
I’m sorry.
I waited for you for a long time that day.
Stop saying that.
That’s not what I need to hear now.
I just want to know what happened.
I’m worried about you.
We should start meeting each other.
No appointment, no waiting.
And no disappointment.
Why’d you say that?
Because you want an answer.
I’m giving you one right now.
Raccoon Chao.
All of a sudden, I just don’t want to answer the phones.
All of a sudden, I wanted to cry.
I don’t even have the strength to get up.
I am this kind of asshole.
I don’t deserve you to treat me well.
Please don’t ghost me.
Please don’t push me. - Please don’t ghost me.
Please don’t push me like this.
I’m scared.
Just go away. - Give me a break.
OK? -What did I do?
Please don’t push me.
Just tell me what happened.
What are you doing right now? - Please don’t push me.
What are you doing？
Just don’t push me.
Stop doing this to me.
Here.
Thanks.
Look.
Isn’t it ugly?
So stupid, right?
Why do you…
wrap yourself like this?
I feel so wrong when the episode comes.
Then I won’t get hurt when I slam myself
onto the wall.
Smart guy, right.
You’re very smart.
You’re taking care of yourself very well.
At first, I thought I just having insomnia.
I didn’t know why I became like this.
It’s okay.
You are in a struggle.
I do take my medicine.
You know I can take care of myself.
No worries.
Look.
Fine, go take a rest.
You don’t have to go back?
I can…
I can stay.
Can I?
But I want to be alone.
I can stay in the living room.
Is that okay?
You still don’t believe me?
Just today.
Okay?
I haven’t seen you for days.
I wanna be with you.
If you are tired you can go to the guest room.
Alright?
Sleeping now?
It’s still early.
It’s just one o’clock.
Why are you here?
I have your keys.
What? Don’t want me to come?
Stop it.
Kangaroo is in the living room.
Don’t make him confused.
You so bad.
Taking a date home.
Meanwhile, you are messing with me.
Shut up. I’m not messing with you.
I don’t want him to misunderstand.
Misunderstand what?
About my importance?
Or about me having your keys?
Give it back.
Who told me that
he’s afraid of dying at home alone
so that he gave me the keys.
You got a new sweetheart now.
So you want to get rid of me?
Are you insane? It hurts.
Smash the wall doesn’t hurt?
Moran.
Turn over.
Come on.
Count on three. - No.
Count on three.
123 456
Come over and let me bind you up.
Go out with me.
No.
If you don’t do that,
I’ll tell him I have your keys.
You are such a dick.
A very huge one.
To where?
Just follow me.
But Kangaroo is in the living room.
How do we make it?
Raccoon Chao.
How much does he know?
It’s none of your business.
You won’t keep a relationship well if it’s full of lies.
How about your boyfriend not knowing
You’re here today.
Did he blow you off?
Where did he go?
He didn’t blow me off.
He said he wanted to prepare his essay.
He wasn’t in the mood of going out.
You could just go to his house.
He didn’t want me there
because he would be thinking
if I would be boring.
It may turn out to be
nothing is finished and no one’s happy.
So, here I am.
What the fuck?
Where should we go to play?
Let’s do things he would never do with me.
Another.
I want this.
This.
Again.
What happened?
Wait…
Not ready, wait.
Wait!
I’m not sure about happiness.
Does it taste sweet and sour?
I’ve got you in my phone.
You’ve got me in your phone.
I feel joy and happy.
Slide back the notification.
Who’s that?
Why does he care about your whereabouts?
I’m gonna tell you about my episodes.
I’m the honest one.
Where have you been last night?
I have no idea.
Are you hearing yourself?
I don’t know.
Don’t push me.
I want more drinks.
More drinks.
There are only karaoke bars are open.
Do you want to sing?
Nah. I don’t feel like to sing.
How about some movies at my place?
Sure. What will we see?
A drama adapt from a movie named One Day.
Have you seen that?
It’s on my top three list.
The Mandarin title is…
Jen Ai…(Love to)
Eat bananas.
Or you try the right answer. - No.
You go.
Jen Ai…
Eat dicks?
What’s wrong with you?
Jen Ai Mei Yi Tian.
What?
Nope.
That one is a sci-fi drama
about jumping between times.
It’s Jen Ai…
Jen Ai…
Tiau zhi Tsu.
Shit. You made it.
What’s the reason do you like it?
I adore Anne Hathaway’s beauty.
And the guy is
so blue to be a prince charming
to me.
Can I say you are shallow?
Fine. I’ll tell you another reason.
It’s hard to love someone for a long time.
True.
Fall in love in the first sight,
and love him as a friend.
It’s really hard.