It was your Jin family who made a mistake
I asked you to prolong my daughter's life
It's not too much, is it
It should be so
Don't blame me for being cruel
I just don't want to lose my daughter
Then say so
I don't have to die
Could you take that box away
It's scary to put it there
You can keep it for your own use
Jujube soup
Really
Is really my good daughter
Don't run around in the future
Stay by my side and spend more time with me
The father emperor
Can you let Jin Jiu go
You mean the fake waiter
His manners are short-tempered and his body is not clean
I sent him to banishment
To banish the army
No, no, no
I forbid him to leave
A clever waiter has something to do
You drink the medicine first
Father will arrange for you again
What a fishy smell
The imperial doctor added a blind pig blood as a medicine guide
New formula
Wrong
Jin Jiu must still be in the palace
Another meal. You feed pigs.
Why are you here
Father really lied to me
You wait. I'm gonna get you out of here
Unexpectedly
You're the one I'm looking for
But you were so clever when you were little
How did you change when you grew up
How has it become
Become
Saskatchewan
It's not what you said
You said you should protect yourself in the future
Orb
To see you again
How nice
What are you doing
I can't go
Why
You'll die if you stay here
Only I can relieve the cold poison in your body
What are you gonna do when I'm gone
If you unlock the lock again,
I called someone.
You
Somebody, someone broke the prison
Somebody, please
I don't care if you love it.
Idiot
Shu De
Sister Huang, why are you here
I have something to ask you
What's on me
Help me save Jin Jiu
Save Jin Jiu
But my father said
It is a great crime to release prisoners privately
Don't piss me off
And
Why don't you save yourself
Father looked at me closely
I went to save it once
Jin Jiu didn't cooperate
The size of this palace
You're the only one I can trust
But Sister Huang
My mother said
The two of us are not the same
And my mother said
She and your mother's concubine
Two people are at odds
What do you have to struggle with
Long Shude, let me ask you something
Who am I to you
You
You are my most admired emperor sister
Then who are you to me
I
I'm your loveliest sister
Then don't you have to
Sister Huang is wrapped around me
What do I need to do
Carp soup
Isn't it too much
I donate blood, not milk
True fragrance
As heavy as a pig
You said you
What thick cloak do you wear in summer
I was mistaken for the little princess
I spent a lot of time with Baozhu
Who stipulates that you can't wear a thick cloak in summer
This is a trend. Do you understand
Why did you get me out
I'm not that kind
It's just that someone asked me
Since it wasn't your intention
Then take me back
The orb needs me
You're crazy
You will die if you go back now
I'm not going back
Baozhu will die
No, no, no
I promised Sister Huang that I would take you out
I can't break my word
What are you doing
Take me back
You let go, let go
Now that Sister Huang has said it,
I hope you live well
Don't let her down
Orb
Why are you so stupid
Without you
So what if I survive
Since I chose to come back,
You won't leave her
You can only delay her toxicity
But it can't save her life
Even if it's just to delay her for a little longer
I'm happy too