What happened?
After Ye Ru Yi escaped the marriage last night,
someone followed her and tried to kill her.
Did you find out who it was?
It seems to be Shangguan Kyung-moo's subordinate
Shangguan Kyung-moo
He even killed his foster daughter.
He's getting more and more crazy.
But why is he doing this?
He insisted on giving you his adopted daughter.
and now he wants to kill her.
Everyone knows that Shangguan Jingmo
won't kill his own family.
Then the murderer
could only be me, the husband who was forced to marry.
Why is she like this?
Yesterday, on the 15th,
didn't take the antidote from Shangguan.
and fainted.
He's also a pitiful person.
Can the fruit detoxify?
It can alleviate the poison.
Feed her.
Save her life first.
Now we have to do it accordingly.
Don't let this pot of dirty water on me.
and affect the business here.
I'm incompetent.
He’s gone.
Phoenix.
You are my most valued subordinate.
You can
You can do it, right?
Don't worry.
I will never make the same mistake again.
Punish you.
to punish you.
But the Shangguan family has a clear punishment.
After receiving the punishment,
he went to find Ye Ru Yi's body.
Then throw it into the yard of the dethroned Crown Prince.
Yes.
Thief!
Are you looking for this?
Yes.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Last night...
Yes.
You detoxified me?
The one who detoxified you is our boss's ears.
I'm his subordinate, Cang He.
One ear. One ear.
Oh.
Such a strange name.
Is it the handsome guy
wearing a mask last night?
Mask?
The shopkeeper is wearing a mask.
Cane River, right?
Yes.
I'm hungry.
You eat first.
I'll go down first.
You just detoxified.
You'd better not wander around.
Call me if you need anything.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're so beautiful.
Your hands...
You're so annoying.
You must be very interested today.
The task arranged by the higher-ups is finally done.
Of course I have to be happy.
My lord.
Hey, beauty.
Yes.
Here.
A toast to you.
Okay.
Here.
My lord, do you know where General Wang is locked?
I can't tell you.
who did it
Who did it?
Yes.
The Crown Prince of the previous dynasty.
Shangguan Jingmao.
Yes.
It's him.
Your Highness.
What is it?
A secret letter from the princess.
I've sent someone to rescue General Wang.
Continue to collect evidence of Shangguan's rebellion.
Go.
Continue to collect evidence of Shangguan’s rebellion.
Yes.
Who?
I... I heard nothing.
Please spare my life.
Warrior Zhao.
Since you saved me,
don’t kill me.
What are you up to now?
I'm not on Shangguan's side.
This
This is a secret letter from Shangguan Jingmao.
I don't know if it will help you.
Warrior Zhao.
Since you have accepted my stuff,
we are good friends.
Between good friends,
between good friends.
Right?
It's an honor
to be Miss Ye's friend.
Okay, goodbye.
The letter has been received. It's true.
We are outnumbered. We need to know ourselves and our enemy.
There must be more letters.
Ye Ru Yi is still useful.
Has she left?
Yes, she left.
But it's less than half a month.
Good.
You may leave.
Master with one ear.
Since we are friends,
I wonder if you can protect me.
What do you want?
I want to live here.
Why are you haunting me?
Maybe you can use me
in the future.
Sure.
You've been here for so long.
I finally had a good sleep.
Luckily, I'm smart.
I hid a few letters.
Then I can continue to carry this thigh.
Can you stop now?