Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Guards!
Someone!
Ye Ru Yi.
You're here.
It seems different from what you expected.
But what can you do on your own?
She's not alone.
She's just an ant.
No need to be afraid.
Who are you?
Cut the crap, Shangguan.
Go to hell!
Humph!
Do you think you can change anything
can change anything?
What if you add me?
Phoenix,
You’ve let me down for all these years.
Without you,
without you.
A dog that I don't know well.
It's fine to lose it.
Dear.
Why are you here too?
Traitor Shangguan Jingmo.
Still not repenting?
The Liu family's court
Who are you to speak?
Guards!
Arrest them all!
You are indeed my best son.
If I don't kill them,
You're the one who deserves to die.
You overestimate yourself.
Humph.
No!
Dongmo Chen.
Ruyi.
Don't give up.
Bye.
Thief Shangguan.
I'll kill you!
Max.
We will win.
Zuo Qianchen.
Sorry.
I'm late.
Zuo Qianchen.
Ye Ru Yi.
Don't you understand?
I am the master of this world.
A nobody like you
should die in this world.
Shangguan Kyung-mo.
We are all small characters in your story.
in your story.
We don't have golden fingers.
We don't have the halo of the protagonist.
But I've told you.
no one wants to see you become the emperor.
No!
Congratulations on passing through the blind boxes.
The comic has been modified successfully.
and returned to the real world successfully.
It's finally done.
The company is down.
Yes.
I heard that the boss is not capable.
plagiarized her assistant's work.
He was sued and lost a lot of money.
That's it?
This boss is too much.
It's fine that he deducts our salary,
but you bully little girls.
What kind of ability is that?
That's right.
I've seen her before.
She's very pretty.
Yes.
What's your name?
Yoo Shi-won.
That's right.
Are you Ye Ru Yi?
Can I buy you a cup of coffee?
Hello.
Enjoy.
Ye Ru Yi, you may not know me.
No.
I know you.
I know you are the real author of the God of War Sword.
Congratulations on winning Wang Mao.
Thank you.
Actually, I found you this time
because I read your popular comic.
I don't know.
are you interested in joining our studio?
Yes.
They're here.
Hi.
Let me introduce you briefly.
More money is our boss.
His boyfriend Cang He is our marketing manager.
This is Phoenix.
our operating director.
His fiance is in charge of the market.
Dong Mo Chen.
There's one more person.
is also my brother.
Just like us,
an illustrator.
Hey, he's here.
Hello, I'm Zuo Qianchen.
Hello.
I'm Ye Ru Yi.
Nice to meet you.