Guards!
Someone reported that he didn't know about gambling.
Therefore, Nanfeng Pavilion is more unscrupulous.
I'm here to seal it.
Nonsense.
Nanfeng Pavilion has never had any dirty activities.
Have you found any evidence?
Ruyi.
It depends on you. It depends on you.
depends on you.
It's between you and me.
between you and me?
It's just some unimportant people.
You must
come with me.
If you leave,
what should we do?
Unknown people are illegally running it.
The evidence is solid.
Smash it!
Stop!
I'll go with you.
Let them go.
Ruyi.
They're still useful.
We can't be smashed by them.
Don't worry.
He won't do anything to me.
Don't you understand?
She said she's coming with me.
Your Highness.
How can you let Miss Ye Ruyi go with Jin Buyi?
You know who Ye Ru Yi is.
No one can change her mind.
But...
It's okay.
Tell the princess
Find an excuse to get Jin out of the capital.
Yes.
But after this
the guests won't dare to come again
Then do something
to restore the unknown place as soon as possible.
That way, we can collect information.
Also,
make more money.
The provisions at the border are in danger.
Yes.
I don't know
I don't know what happened.
Is it so painful to be with me?
Ruyi, I have something to do in the court.
I'll be back later.
What do you think?
Do you think my idea works?
The manager said we can try.
That's good.
Are you ready for the divination wine?
Yes.
Do you need to pick an auspicious day?
No, it's better to pick another day.
Just today.
Wait for me.
Take a look.
A new Fortune-telling wine
Come and take a look.
Sir.
Okay.
This is our new divination wine.
What new stuff is coming out?
This is Fortune-telling Wine.
There's a spirit stick in each pot.
You can see it after you drink it.
Bring me a pot when you're in trouble.
I promise everything will go well.
It works.
How much is this pot?
Let me try.
to see if it works.
Ruyi, the manager said it's dangerous outside.
Why don't we go back first?
Sir, what's wrong?
Do you not like the food?
No, no.
It suits your taste.
I came here today
to
I want to
with Mr. Qian.
You must be joking, sir.
I'm just a woman.
I need men to decide my business.
Why don't you go to my father?
Business is not physical work.
There's no difference between men and women.
What's the difference?
Thank you for not despising me as a woman.
Just say it.
Here's the thing.
We don't know
Something happened recently.
The food is decreasing.
However,
we launched a new wine.
called Fortune-telling Wine.
It's been sold for a few days.
It worked well.
I'm impressed.
I was wondering
to sell the wine
to sell it?
Of course.
You look like a businessman.
Don't be modest.
Okay.
Let me pour you another cup.
It's getting late.
Why don't we go back first?
Okay.
How about this, Miss Qian?
Next time,
We'll have a good drink next time.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
How are you?
I'm fine.
He didn't give me a hard time.
I wonder how he is doing.
Thanks to your Fortune-telling Wine, we got in.
That's good.
By the way,
the military pay hasn't been settled yet, right?
It doesn't matter. I'll think about it.
Jin Buswaang will be sent out for a while.
So please bear with it for a while.
I know how to make money.
Don't look at me like that.
He'll be back soon.
Let's go.
I'm leaving.
Let go of me.
If Jin Bubei sees it,
I don't know what will happen.
You are my wife.
Why do you have private meetings every day?
What private meeting?
Don't be so harsh.