♪ A scene of you suddenly appeared ♪
♪ When I close my eyes ♪
♪ I can see ♪
♪ A specific time and place ♪
♪ Sometimes I peek at you ♪
♪ Hiding behind the wall ♪
♪ Let me be frank ♪
♪ I was the one who first noticed you ♪
♪ My Valentine I love you so ♪
♪ I want to tell you
that I love you more ♪
♪ A small action makes me happy ♪
♪ I love you more every day ♪
♪ How long did it take
for us to be here? ♪
♪ My kiwi is sweet ♪
♪ Anything is okay
as long as you say it ♪
♪ I love you more every day ♪
♪ Love you more ♪
♪ My Valentine I love you so ♪
♪ I want to tell you
that I love you more ♪
♪ But you were shocked
when I knelt down ♪
♪ You smiled and cried ♪
♪ How long did we wait
for us to be here? ♪
♪ Will you be my Valentine? ♪
♪ Anything is okay
as long as you say it ♪
♪ I love you more every day ♪
[About is Love]
[Episode 13]
Is there anyone here?
Can anyone help me?
Editor He.
There was nobody in the fitting room.
I heard you shout, so...
You won't blame me, right?
No, this is my problem.
Wait a minute.
I'll do it.
Take it.
I don't think that's good.
I think it suits you more than me.
Really?
Moreover, this brand...
suits you too.
Really?
I'm meeting the director
of this brand on the 6th.
Do you have time?
Me?
I want to introduce our model to them...
and see if there's a chance
to collaborate.
Do you have time?
Yes.
What about the location?
Give me your phone.
My phone.
I think this is more convenient.
I'll contact you later.
Okay.
And, next time when we meet,
can you stop being so nervous?
I think,
you look the best
when you act naturally.
Okay.
He really knows how to flirt.
That brooch should be expensive, right?
Fei Fei was staring at it
since 30 minutes ago.
I think, it's not that
the brooch is expensive,
the person who gave her that brooch
is valuable
What are you talking about?
I heard everything.
She has a fever.
Who has...
He said you have a fever,
but you seem like you have...
I'm fine.
You don't know,
but He Wei is really...
the same as rumours about him.
Although I know he was flirting,
he did it...
naturally.
Especially when he isn't talking...
and smiles at you,
his eyes...
are filled with stars.
My heart was thumping.
He's too handsome.
No, I met He Wei before.
He wasn't like what you said.
This is the first time seeing you...
infatuated with a man.
No, yesterday I saw...
Saw who?
This is a new flavour, it's delicious.
Let me tell you,
He Wei bought all of these.
You should thank him.
You can do it...
the next time you see him.
I'll have to wait until the 6th...
to meet him.
How old are you?
It's all over your face.
Why did you ruin my makeup?
How dare you do that?
Why did I suddenly think of that person?
No,
since when did you become so close?
No.
I'm disciplining him.
He was spoiled by you.
Don't touch my chocolate stick.
Can you steal it from me?
You can play this way?
I'm afraid they'll make it real.
Don't just talk about me.
Well, what about...
you and Wei Qing?
There's nothing between us.
I think we are friends.
Friends?
Look, even Xiao Fei lost his appetite.
Do you know how wrong you are?
Did you think it through?
I thought you wanted to escape from him?
Actually, to think about it,
although Wei Qing lied to me,
he didn't harm me.
Moreover, he did...
repay my dad's gambling debt.
I should thank him.
I think you have...
Stockholm syndrome.
The more others torture you,
the more you like them.
No, he's quite pitiful.
He doesn't have friends.
I don't know what happened
between him and his mum.
His mum seems to hate him.
So, I pitied him and...
Since you've thought it through,
we can't say anything.
But, you have to be cautious,
don't be fooled by him again.
Don't worry. I'm not a fool.
I won't be lied to again.
Shut up.
It's extremely easy...
for Wei Qing to win your heart.
If you can't control yourself,
then your Brother Ming Cheng...
If you didn't mention him,
then I would've forgotten.
I haven't thought about
what should I draw for him.
Quick, help me think about it.
-Quick...
-Wait...
Stop eating!
You can eat yourself slowly.
I'm going back to my room.
Miss Xue Zi, this time...
you won't be going back
to the States, right?
Yes.
The company assigned me...
to oversee the management
of the China market,
find a suitable collaborator...
and expand the market in China.
I just got here recently.
I'll appreciate it if you'll
help me in the future.
You're too courteous, Miss Xue Zi.
Yun Ma really wants to collaborate
with Snow Group.
What do you think...
about the collaboration proposal...
proposed by Yun Ma?
We are interested...
in Xun Ran's designs.
I believe you know,
even in the international market,
Xun Ran is a popular designer.
Many large companies are
willing to spend money...
to sign him on.
But, unexpectedly
he signed on to Yun Ma Artwork.
How did you...
persuade Xun Ran?
We are simply acquaintances.
I didn't expect that...
the biggest chip for Yun Ma
to collaborate with Snow...
is Xun Ran.
Xun Ran is one of the reasons.
It's also important to see...
who's our partner too.
Looks like we have to collaborate more.
I remember when we met last time,
you were wearing gloves too.
I have mysophobia.
Excuse me for that.
People who have a strange habit
are more interesting.
But now, there are only
the two of us here.
What are you worried about?
If I want to take Xue Zi down,
I'll have to cure my illness soon.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
[Yun Psychological Clinic]
I slept soundly.
This is a psychological clinic,
but you treated it like a hotel.
I paid the fee.
You took my money but
didn't do anything. Isn't that good?
That means,
I have to thank you?
How are you recently?
Do you still have nightmares frequently?
Two to three times per week.
But even if I didn't have nightmares,
I can only sleep an average of...
four to five hours per day.
Then, what is the content...
of your nightmares?
Can you remember them?
The usual.
Screams, blood and my mum.
Will you consider hypnotherapy?
No, I don't want you
to be in my head...
where you can see whatever you want.
Okay, then...
Then let's talk about Zhou Shi.
How is it going?
Is your relationship going well?
It has improved.
We are friends now.
Friends?
This isn't your usual style.
By now you should be...
She's different.
I have to go slowly.
Moreover, it's good to be friends first.
At least we can get to know each other.
Why are you laughing?
I've known you for 10 years.
This is the first time I've heard you...
talk about friends.
Moreover, this is
my first time seeing you...
talking about someone...
in a relaxing manner.
Do you remember
what did you look like...
the first time you came to me?
Of course I do.
Every time, after he...
had skin contact with others,
red rashes will appear...
on that part of his body.
Although the rashes...
will disappear after a few hours,
it will recur when
the same thing happens again.
This doesn't look like vasculitis.
I think it's just a normal...
skin allergy.
You can go to the hospital
for an allergy test.
Then, get some histamines.
You should recover by then.
The same thing again.
Look,
I said it isn't necessary to come.
Yet, you didn't believe me.
Mysophobia.
How long has he been like this?
Around six months.
Although he had
slight mysophobia previously,
it wasn't that serious.
I don't know the cause exactly.
He never told me about that.
I saw many mysophobia patients.
But this is the first time I saw...
a patient with allergic reaction.
18 years old.
No family history for allergic reactions
or a history of psychological problems.
So, this is an acute allergic reaction.
Did he undergo an allergy test?
Surely he's not only
allergic to people, right?
He thinks that the hospital is dirty.
He wouldn't go there for tests.
If your clinic wasn't just...
a psychological clinic,
he wouldn't come at all.
18 years old.
Then you have to contact his parents...
to arrange for a full
psychological check-up.
No need.
In my mum's eyes,
a stray cat is more important than me.
What about your dad?
Don't bother, okay?
Just check...
and prescribe medicines.
As long as you can cure me,
you will get your pay, okay?
Party? Of course I'm going.
Wait for me, I'll pick you up.
You're going to a party?
What's wrong?
Do you know
a severe allergic reaction...
will trigger shock and disseminated
intravascular coagulation?
You're going to the party
with your condition?
Because I'm in this condition,
I have to go to the party.
Maybe there will be...
a woman that won't...
trigger my allergic reaction.
Let me tell you.
Don't bother about my private life.
Just cure my illness, get it?
Okay?
You were like a...
small hedgehog.
Other people couldn't go near you.
So what?
It was just a front I put on.
But, you did a great job.
You went through it yourself.
Look, you even have a friend now.
Zhou Shi is your lucky star.
Whether or not we can be friends...
depends on...
me passing her test.
What do you mean?
I came over this time...
not to just sleep,
I also need your help.
Okay.
In a situation without spending money...
nor giving presents,
how can I treat a girl well?
This is her test?
She is interesting.
You're a female too.
Speak nicely.
As a female, help me out.
It's all written in the Internet, right?
Men shouldn't tell women
to drink more water...
whenever there's a problem.
Just do that.
Okay, I'll be serious.
Compared to men, women...
are more fickle.
For example,
they might like something a minute ago,
but the next minute,
they might already hate it.
Women want men to...
pay attention to them.
So, you can try...
paying attention to her.
For example,
you can try to understand
what she needs the most.
Even if the outcome is not desirable,
but your sincerity...
can touch her.
But, women won't..
make it clear...
about what they want, right?
How can I guess that?
Women want...
men to guess what's on their mind.
But, this doesn't mean that...
they won't tell their friends...
about their feelings.
Can you take that pair down
for me to try?
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Miss, have you decided on
which pair to buy?
I'll look around first.
Wrap them all up.
Li Ming Cheng's birthday?
Miss Zhou is planning to confess
her feelings during his birthday party.
Again?
Why won't she give up?
Find out what Li Ming Cheng likes.
Buy that for Zhou Shi.
Miss Zhou has already
prepared a present.
Then, book...
a romantic restaurant for hm.
I think compared to external factors,
Miss Zhou would care more about...
whether or not
her confession will succeed.
Then, find a few staff from
the publicity department...
and send them to their college.
Okay.
You're here?
What is this?
The second present in your list.
A model of the solar system.
Really?
But, this is a 2D version.
You don't get it?
You drew...
the solar system before, right?
Yes, but what does that
have to do with this?
Focusing on the scaling aspect,
that diagram you drew
was completely wrong.
In fact, to draw the solar system...
on a piece of A4 paper
using the correct scale...
would be an impossible task.
Yes.
But, that was just a normal diagram.
In reality,
nobody can draw it using
the correct scale, right?
Is this the attitude...
of a scientific researcher?
You're a top physics student.
Can you see this?
This is a speck of toner.
Of course, you can't see it
with the naked eye...
as it has a diameter of 4µm,
This is the smallest printing unit...
on paper.
Imagine this speck of charcoal
is the moon.
How many papers
do we need approximately...
to print out the whole solar system?
Wait, let me calculate.
If one speck of toner
has a diameter of 10µm,
then the diameter of
the moon is 3500 km.
The ratio is 1:35x10x^11.
The distance between Neptune
and earth is 10 astronomical unit.
One astronomical unit is 1.5 billion km.
Then, according to
the scale I'll need...
-One...
-169 sq.m.
If we calculate the size of A4 paper,
we'll need more than
2700 pieces of paper.
Which is the number of papers
you have in your hands.
So?
You're giving me
more than 2700 pieces of paper...
to let me draw by myself?
Of course.
Didn't we agree that...
the time and method
would be decided by me?
My present is...
pointing out your logical errors.
You don't have to thank me.
We are both in science stream.
It's should be an exciting thing...
for others to point out
your logical error.
I've never experienced
this happiness before.
I really envy you.
I'm defeated.
Isn't this normal?
Aren't you used to it yet?
Don't think that...
I'll keep losing to you.
So what if you lose?
I lose to Zhou Shi in cooking.
I lose to Ning Fei in drawing.
I also lose to Lin Fei Fei
in dressing up.
But, so what?
Will remembering
all of that make me happy?
But,
what if I have to win once?
Up to you.
If the opponent is boring,
what's the point...
of winning 100 times?
You're a bore.
He doesn't suit Zhou Shi at all.
I don't get what he likes.
Hello, friend.
Can I interview you?
Sure.
Why did you ask me to come in a hurry?
I have something to show you.
My name is Li Ming Cheng.
I'm a fourth year student studying
physics in Guang Hua University.
Brother Ming Cheng?
Watch it carefully.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
Do you have someone that you like?
No, why are you asking this?
We just want to know...
about the relationship status
of university students.
Then what is your...
ideal type?
My ideal type?
Smart.
What about her appearance?
Normally, she wears glasses.
She has no makeup or light makeup on.
Her hair is short, until this length.
She has fringe.
Normally, she likes
to wear casual clothes.
She has a big heart and is direct.
Just like a guy.
So?
What do you mean?
Aren't you going to confess your feelings
to Ling Ming Cheng...
on his birthday?
How do you know that?
You don't need to know that.
Let me ask you,
do you want to succeed or not?
Of course I do.
Follow me.
What are you doing?
Are you done?
It feels strange.
Come out. Let me see.
Why are you laughing?
Don't I look good?
What is this?
Not bad.
I think this is simple.
This is too plain.
Why would Brother Ming Cheng like
someone like that?
That's hard to say.
Maybe Li Ming Cheng
likes girls who are natural.
I won't trust you.
I think this is better.
What do you think?
She looks youthful.
Really?
I think I look good in this.
Don't you know it yourself?
Change it.
Okay, take a look now.
Wei Qing.
What are you doing? You're a bear!
Wei An!
How do I look?
Almost done.
Look at the mirror yourself.
Why does this look familiar?
Your image is done.
Do you know why did you fail last time?
Because you lost...
my ring and letter.
No, it was because
you weren't confident enough.
From tomorrow onwards,
I'll arrange a special
training session for you.
Quick, change back to your clothes.
I'll send you home.
Okay.
Are you really helping Miss Zhou
to pursue Li Ming Cheng?
Li Ming Cheng doesn't like Zhou Shi.
But, if I don't let her...
try it herself,
I'm scared she will regret it.
Sister Zhou Shi.
You're alone at home?
I'm hungry.
I'll cook for you later.
Okay.
You're drawing? Let me take a look.
You draw really well.
I can't be compared to you.
I have always wanted to ask you.
Your drawing style
is similar to Xun Ran.
Are you imitating him?
Yes.
You're good at imitating him.
I imitated him too.
But, I can't imitate his essence.
But your drawing...
is similar to his.
You must have been
imitating him for a long time.
By the way, I heard that...
you learnt drawing from Wei Qing's dad.
Yes.
Can you tell me about him?
Uncle.
You can draw well.
Xiao Fei,
if your dad is still alive,
he'll be proud of you.
Wei Qing.
Look at Xiao Fei's drawing.
What do you think?
Although Xiao Fei's technique
is still amateur,
you can feel passion...
in each of his drawings.
Although he doesn't like to talk,
drawing became his only way to
communicate with the world.
I hope you can reach this level too.
Now, you can draw well,
but your drawing...
lacks passion.
Looks like Xiao Fei will be...
inheriting my talent.
Thank you, uncle.
You're doing a good job.
Here, if...
Senior.
What's wrong?
If your senior...
can use his anger...
to draw, that will be great.
Uncle thought highly of him.
So, he was strict...
to get the most out of him.
But, Wei Qing...
never understood his intentions.
Then what about him and his mum?
Why does his mum hate him?
Because uncle's death...
It's all your fault!
You caused your dad's death,
do you know? You're an unfilial son!
Chairman He...
You caused his death!
Why do I have a son like this?
Auntie thinks that...
uncle's death was related to him.
So, she hates him.
Then, how did...
Wei Qing's dad die?
Auntie didn't tell me about it.
I didn't expect that Wei Qing's family
will be this complicated.
Do you like him?
What are you talking about?
Impossible.
Actually, he isn't that bad.
He's only bad some times.
I know.
Okay, I'll go and cook for you.
I'm back.
You're back? I'm going to cook.
Come and help me.
Okay.
Normally, she wears glasses.
She has no makeup or light makeup on.
Her hair is short, until this length.
She has fringe.
Why does this look familiar?
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
Aren't you going to cook?
I'll go and change.
Okay.
Brother Ming Cheng...
likes her?
Someone that I like?
Yes, do you have one?
Why is this question popular nowadays?
What?
Nothing. Why are you asking this?
I'm just asking.
Brother Ming Cheng,
you aren't young anymore.
You should consider...
about your relationship.
You,
if you use your brain to study,
you'd have pass the CET-4 ages ago.
Do you have one?
Tell me.
-No.
-Really?
You've been in college for four years.
You didn't fall in love with anyone?
No.
Okay.
By the way, do you remember Bi Qiu Jing?
Bi Qiu Jing?
Yes, what's wrong with her?
What do you think of her?
Both of you are top students.
You should have many common topics.
Her?
Compared to her,
I'm not a top student.
She's much more smarter than me.
Moreover, she's more
open minded than me.
This is the first time I've seen you...
compliment someone like that.
Then, is she your ideal type?
What ideal type?
You're saying it like
we're on a dating show.
If I have to say it,
she's a rival...
that I want to catch up to.
Just a rival?
Of course.
Although she often laughs at me,
I want to win at least once.
You can do it, Brother Ming Cheng.
I believe that you can win one day.
You don't sound confident at all.
You think she's better
than me too, right?
No. You're the best to me.
Let's go to class.
Okay.
Do you have class later?
Yes, one more class.
I don't have class later.
Can I come along?
It's a physics class.
Can you understand?
Yes...
I like physics.
When did you like physics? Good.
Where is the class?
Great.
From today onwards,
you'll be the queen
of Li Ming Cheng's heart.
Be confident.
Confident...
Then, what should I do next?
Confess your feelings.
To whom?
To me, of course.
From now on,
I'm your Brother Ming Cheng.
-You can start now.
-Are you joking? This is embarrassing.
Do you want to succeed?
You can begin when you're ready.
Brother Ming Cheng.
Are you going to bite me?
Can you be more natural?
Brother Ming Cheng.
Are you awake?
Put more feelings into it, okay?
Brother Ming Cheng.
Are you going to a fight?
Can you be more gentle?
Gentle, get it?
I won't practise anymore!
I couldn't do it well.
You kept laughing at me.
I'll stop laughing at you, okay?
Let's do this again. But,
you have to treat me like...
your Brother Ming Cheng.
Be more passionate, okay?
But, I can't do that.
I know...
why I can't.
It's because you don't look
like Brother Ming Cheng at all.
Then, what should we do?
Why don't you dress up like him?
Impossible.
Then, I won't practise anymore.
Why are you laughing?
Didn't I do this for you?
Okay, thank you.
But, actually you look good...
in this outfit.
Don't use that tactic.
I changed my outfit.
You don't have an excuse now, right?
Can we start now?
Go ahead.
Brother Ming Cheng.
I liked you...
since we were in primary school.
Do you know that?
Thanks to you,
I got my first full marks.
I was delighted.
I wanted to tell you about that.
But,
I fell into the river.
My test paper was soaked.
That was the first time
I failed in confessing my feelings.
Later on...
Later on, I never got
100 marks in exam anymore.
So, I never tried to
confess my feelings anymore.
I was afraid that
you'll think I'm foolish.
I was afraid that I'll disappoint you.
So, I tried my best to catch up.
I hope that one day,
I could catch up to you.
But, I realised...
you drifted apart from me.
I was tired of chasing after you.
Maybe because I was too foolish.
But, I still like you.
I forced myself to catch up.
I hope that one day,
I can catch up to you,
pat your shoulders and say,
Brother Ming Cheng,
I finally caught up to you.
Am I good?
That way...
That way you'll like me.
But, I can't keep on running anymore.
Can you stop,
wait for me and hug me?
♪ The "us" that I yearn of ♪
♪ Was "you" as stated by her ♪
Stop running.
You're good enough.
Then, will you like me?
I like you.
♪ Tell me firmly to trust you ♪
♪ My fringe isn't listening to me well ♪
♪ It isn't like me ♪
♪ It's like you instead ♪
♪ My fringe isn't listening to me well ♪
♪ It isn't like me ♪
♪ It's like you instead ♪
♪ The hot weather is annoying ♪
♪ My mood is like the rain ♪
♪ It may be cloudy or sunny like you ♪
♪ The "us" that I yearn of ♪
♪ Was "you" as stated by her ♪
♪ I was the only serious one ♪
♪ The "us" that I yearn of ♪
♪ If you didn't tell me firmly... ♪
♪ to trust you ♪
♪ My fringe isn't listening to me well ♪
♪ It isn't like me ♪
♪ It's like you instead ♪
♪ The hot weather is annoying ♪
♪ My mood is like the rain ♪
♪ It may be cloudy or sunny like you ♪
♪ The "us" that I yearn of ♪
♪ Was "you" as stated by her ♪
♪ I was the only serious one ♪
♪ The "us" that I yearn of ♪
♪ If you didn't tell me firmly... ♪
♪ to trust you ♪