♪ A scene of you suddenly appeared ♪
♪ When I close my eyes ♪
♪ I can see ♪
♪ A specific time and place ♪
♪ Sometimes I peek at you ♪
♪ Hiding behind the wall ♪
♪ Let me be frank ♪
♪ I was the one who first noticed you ♪
♪ My Valentine I love you so ♪
♪ I want to tell you
that I love you more ♪
♪ A small action makes me happy ♪
♪ I love you more every day ♪
♪ How long did it take
for us to be here? ♪
♪ My kiwi is sweet ♪
♪ Anything is okay
as long as you say it ♪
♪ I love you more every day ♪
♪ Love you more ♪
♪ My Valentine I love you so ♪
♪ I want to tell you
that I love you more ♪
♪ But you were shocked
when I knelt down ♪
♪ You smiled and cried ♪
♪ How long did we wait
for us to be here? ♪
♪ Will you be my Valentine? ♪
♪ Anything is okay
as long as you say it ♪
♪ I love you more every day ♪
[About is Love]
[Episode 21]
Don't tell me you didn't hear
what I was talking about?
I did.
Repeat what I said.
Something about response...
and something about
the questions?
I'm sorry.
I was absent-minded and didn't hear it.
Can you explain it again, Chairman?
Mr. Wei.
I said, I'll show you
all the exam questions...
and create a framework.
Lastly, we'll practise
your adaptive response to stress.
What's adaptive response to stress?
To make it simple,
it's like training a dog.
You'll have to do 20 sets
of questions per day...
until you're tired of it.
You don't have to remember
with your brain,
but with your body instead.
Once you see the questions
you can write the answers immediately.
Do you have to be so cruel?
Do you know how a circus trains a tiger?
By hitting it?
By starving them.
Hunger is an animal's natural instinct.
Most of the time, people would
do anythng just for food.
I'll train you in the same way.
My goodness.
Are you ready?
I am.
Louder!
I'm ready!
What is this?
This?
I found it two days ago.
When I was a kid, if I did something wrong,
my father would beat me with this.
Look. My name is on it.
It's worn out. I'm sure
you got beaten a lot.
Now, I'll use it on you.
Why is also a word here?
Okay.
I don't care how other people teach you.
As long as I'm your teacher,
I won't be merciful.
For today, you don't have much to do.
Just memorise everything here.
If not,
you don't get to sleep.
How can I memorise all of them?
[Long time no see.]
[I'm sorry. I'm quite busy lately.]
[Did you settle your things already?]
[Yeah. Luckily, I got some help
from my friend.]
[You must thank your friend then.]
[Yeah. She's unique.]
[ If I thank her directly,
she'll think that I'm boring.]
[This is interesting.
Is she interesting?]
[She's the most interesting person
I've ever met.]
[You regard her highly.
I think she's your special one.]
Did I say something wrong?
Never mind.
[Yeah.]
I think he's shy.
[Does she know that?]
[I don't know. I'm afraid that
she'll think I'm boring if I say this.]
[Confession is boring.]
[But staying undecided is more boring.]
[Just try.]
[You're right. It's late now.]
[Rest earlier. Good night!]
[Good night.]
Time to wake up.
Where are you going?
I'm going to work.
What time did I sleep yesterday?
Around 3 a.m..
I slept for less than five hours?
You can go to work.
But I don't need to work, right?
Wake up, revise your homework.
These are the papers
you need to do today.
it is too much
Assistant An, I'm so sleepy.
Can I just sleep for a while?
Just for an hour?
Why did he give this to you?
Wei Qing is overdoing !
He doesn't want me to rest.
Assistant An, why are you
against me by his side?
It's all for you to pass the exams.
You have to go through this.
Wei Qing.
Chairman slept at the same time with me.
Why is he not sleepy at all?
When Chairman first
took over Yun Ma Group,
he stayed up the whole night for a few days.
He's not sleepy at all.
the more work he does, the more energetic he is.
He's a monster.
Perhaps only a monster...
could help Yun Ma Group
to be successful in a short time.
But now, even if he wants to sleep,
he can't.
Why?
Didn't he tell you this?
He always had nightmares.
I think I've heard about this.
He looks glorious on the outside.
But in reality, it's hard for him too.
Yeah, that's why you must work hard.
I can do it!
This is?
Chairman,
For this season, the galaxy series
jewelries designed by Xun Ran...
has been booming in sales
since the pre-booking stage.
When the series got launched,
they sold all out at once.
Now, the series is out of stock.
But we've notified the factories
to hasten their productions.
By next month,
the second batch will be out.
We've discussed this with the
marketing department as well.
We think that we should create a
second series while the hype is around.
We've developed
some new designs as well.
Chairman, please have a look.
Are you done?
Yes.
Stop the factory's production first.
And delay the launching
of the second series.
-Why?
-Why? They're popular.
Did you guys think about Xun Ran?
He's a popular artist now.
The galaxy series is his masterpiece.
The galaxy series
had such a good sales...
because they have artistic value.
If you mass-produce them,
their artistic value will be lost.
By then, they would be worthless.
You guys don't even know this?
Publicity department.
Chairman?
Put Xun Ran's exhibition on our agenda.
And hold it at Xun's Galleria.
Yes. I'll arrange it immediately.
About Director He...
I'll speak to her.
I'm not sleeping!
I just took a nap.
Ask Assistant An
if you don't believe me.
Is that true?
Okay, I'll forgive you this time.
You can eat now.
eat!
This is your meal.
What do you mean by this?
Are you discriminating me?
You only did three sets of questions
for the entire morning.
You should be thankful
I gave you something to eat.
You are bullying me!
You're not eating?
Wei An, take it away.
Okay! I'll eat!
What expression is that?
I have something for you
in the afternoon.
You're giving me work again?
Mind your attitude.
Chairman, do you have any orders?
Your beloved Xun Ran is
holding an art exhibition soon.
Really? Is that true?
Yeah.
He drew many paintings already.
He should hold an exhibition.
How did you know that he...
He told you, right?
That's better.
Saves me from all the trouble.
Just call him then.
Ask him to go to Xun's Galleria.
And arrange his own exhibition.
His exhibition will be there.
I'll go immediately!
Does she need to be so excited?
He's holding an exhibition for Xiao Fei?
Yes. Chairman told me
to pass this message.
Director He,
you'll arrange the exhibition.
And our company will
surely cooperate with you.
Why didn't he tell me this personally?
Chairman is afraid that...
you won't talk to him.
If you need to talk to him, I...
No need for that.
By the way, Director He,
I don't know if I should say this...
Don't say it then.
I know what you're trying to say.
But it's our family affair.
How can an outsider know the truth?
Aunty.
Xiao Fei, you're here?
Have a seat.
Xiao Zhou, you can sit too.
I didn't expect that Xiao Fei
told you this already.
I didn't expect that I could
be around my idol as well.
Oh yeah,
I still remember what
you said to me when I came.
You said I would meet Xun Ran someday.
That really came true.
Yeah. Fate is a mysterious thing.
Xiao Zhou.
Xiao Fei doesn't like to talk much.
He doesn't have any friends either.
I'm quite worried about him.
I encouraged him to go out often.
But he doesn't listen to me.
But now, you guys are good friends.
I feel relieved.
Not just me,
my housemates like Xiao Fei too.
Xiao Fei is sensible.
He's talented as well.
I'm really happy.
I've always hoped that Xiao Fei
could be someone normal.
I hoped that he can
interact with someone else.
When I saw you guys together,
I'm really happy.
Xiao Zhou.
Please take care
of Xiao Fei in the future.
If you need any help or money,
just tell me.
No problem.
Xiao Fei is just like my brother.
I will take care of him.
Xiao Fei, did you hear that?
You must listen
to Xiao Zhou in the future.
Okay then.
Let's talk about the exhibition.
Director He is quite kind.
I was afraid of her in the past.
But now, I think she's kind.
Aunty is a kind person.
She's just not happy with my senior.
Nice painting.
You like my paintings so much?
Of course! I would buy all of them,
if I had the money.
I'll give them to you then.
All of them.
You can't do that!
You need to sell them.
I don't want to sell them now.
I want to give them to you.
Silly boy.
I appreciate your sincerity.
Besides, you drew
a painting for me already.
It's a special one for me as well.
I'll draw them for you next time.
Sure.
By the way,
why does the word 'Ran'
appear in all of your paintings?
And why are you called Xun Ran?
Because my brother is Ning Ran.
I want to find him.
This is Ran. It's my name.
Remember that.
Write it for me.
Good job.
Did you notice anything about the word?
Here! It lacks a dot here.
He wrote the wrong word.
Only you two know about this?
What happened after that?
How did you guys get separated?
Xiao Fei? Xiao Fei!
Why are you hiding here?
The headmaster is looking for you.
Your foster parents are here.
Come on! Come with me.
I don't want to!
Why?
Xiao Fei, be obedient.
Your foster parents look rich.
You can leave the orphanage
if you follow them.
Do you want to be trapped
here forever?
Why didn't you go with me?
My father asked me to wait for here.
You've waited for more than
one year already.
They would've come by now.
Be obedient. go with me.
If you don't want to go with them,
I'll go with them then.
I don't want to stay here anymore.
I want to leave.
I want to lead a good life.
Big Brother, please don't go.
Xiao Fei, I'm sorry.
I'm leaving now.
Please don't go.
Big Brother, please don't go.
Xiao Fei, if I lead
a good life in the future,
I'll come back for you.
If you do leave here in the future,
remember to find me.
And don't forget my name.
Did your big brother come for you?
After about a month,
my uncle came for me.
You've been searching
for him ever since?
Don't worry. I'm sure you can find him.
Besides, you're famous now.
If he sees your works,
he'll come to you.
Senior.
I'll leave first.
How is it?
I've settled it already.
Director He said that she'll
send the proposal soon.
I think Director He has
a different view of you now.
Because you hold
an exhibition for Xiao Fei.
She's quite touched by that.
And I told her that you stopped
Xiao Fei from designing jewelries.
She smiled because of that.
Is that true?
Why are you telling me this?
I'm not interested.
You just don't want to admit it.
I've done a good job.
Shouldn't you reward me?
Fine. I'll give you an extra
ham for tomorrow's sandwich.
You're so stingy!
I want to sleep!
Did I make many mistakes?
Mistakes?
Why didn't you ask me about the
number of questions you got right?
You can't blame me for this.
When I don't sleep well,
I can't memorise things.
When I can't memorise them,
I'll do bad in the exam.
Where did you get all these?
I've bought every related book
from the market.
Don't worry. You'll do a large amount
of them every day.
And I can make sure that
you won't repeat a question.
Just kill me already.
You must finish them by tonight.
If not, you can't sleep.
♪ My fringe isn't listening to me well ♪
♪ It isn't like me ♪
♪ It's like you instead ♪
♪ The hot weather is annoying ♪
♪ My mood is like the rain ♪
♪ It may be cloudy or sunny like you ♪
♪ The "us" that I yearn of ♪
♪ Was "you" as stated by her ♪
♪ I was the only serious one ♪
♪ The "us" that I yearn of ♪
♪ If you didn't tell me firmly... ♪
♪ to trust you ♪
♪ My fringe isn't listening to me well ♪
I'm so hungry.
I don't want to do them anymore.
Time to eat noodles.
I haven't finished them. I won't eat.
Why shouldn't I eat them?
I'll eat them now!
♪ The "us" that I yearn of ♪
♪ Was "you" as stated by her ♪
♪ I was the only serious one ♪
It's okay if I fail.
I've finished my noodles already.
You can do whatever you like.
You got 48 marks even though
you only completed two-third of them.
You have one-third of them left.
As long as you don't make
too many mistakes,
I think you can pass your exam.
Looks like...
your efforts are not wasted.
Good luck.
There are more noodles upstairs.
If you want them, you can go and take.
Yes, Mr. Wei.
Why do you bring me here again?
Your body is used
to the questions already.
Now, it's time to train your brain.
Although there are not many collections here,
it has everything you need.
Just look at them.
It's beneficial to you.
Do you know about Pu Yi's story?
I don't.
Pu Yi and Wang Guo Wei, the collector,
were best friends.
Wang Guo Wei had
collected some antiques.
And he asked Pu Yi to view them.
After viewing, Pu Yi said
that the antiques were fake.
Wang Guo Wei was upset about that.
He used various evidences and viewpoints
to prove that they were not fake.
Pu Yi didn't say much about that.
After that, Wang Guo Wei
examined them closely.
He discovered that
the antiques were fake.
He asked Pu Yi.
how did you differentiate them.
He wanted to learn something.
Guess what Pu Yi said to him?
Pu Yi said,
I don't have the theories
and evidences like you,
I just feel like your antiques are
different from the one at home.
That's why, sometimes,
having direct contact with something...
is better than reading books about them.
-Look at them.
-Okay.
My painting?
I didn't do a good job.
Why did you buy my painting?
Look at the paintings beside you.
And think of the place you're in.
Do you think I would put
worthless paintings here?
Although your foundation is weak,
you're not as useless as you think.
You're very talented.
In painting and designs.
I bought your painting
before I knew you.
Is that true?
Although you don't have
great techniques and vast experiences,
you can become better if you
work hard in the future.
I'm sure you'll be a great painter
in the future if you work hard.
That's why, with my professional view,
I bought your paintings.
I'll use them in the future
when they are valuable.
In the end, you bought them
for the money.
Money is a good way of determining
the worth of something.
If someone bought something,
it doesn't mean that it's good.
But if no one bought that thing,
I'm sure it's not a good thing.
Appreciation give art their lives.
But money gives art their worth.
It's all nonsense.
That's why,
you must be more confident.
Although you're not as good as
Bi Qiu Jing or Li Ming Cheng,
in art,
you're the clear winner.
You can even compare yourself
with Xun Ran.
Do you mean that?
Or do you just trying to motivate me?
I promise you with my professional view.
You will become a great painter.
I know that.
Fine. Stop praising yourself
in front of your painting.
View some other paintings.
I'm in the storage room.
Okay, I'll send it to you now.
I need to do something.
Take a look around.
Go then.
Be careful.
This is different from last time.
These are all the real deals.
I understand.
It is so much!
There's a secret room here?
Wei Qing?
Wei Heng?
Do all these belong
to Wei Qing's father?
Are you done?
I didn't do it on purpose.
Get out.
But the pictures...
Get out!
[I'm sorry.]
You're back?
Wei Qing said
I'm almost done learning them.
I can just do my revision
with the questions.
Let me look at your face.
You look okay.
Your face is still chubby.
I almost died of starvation.
I can only eat sandwiches
these few days.
He doesn't allow me to sleep either
I'm so hungry.
Fei Fei, I want to have a nice meal.
Okay. I'll buy some food later.
We'll have hot pot tonight, okay?
Fei Fei is the best!
These comments are written by Wei Qing?
Yeah. Everyone thought
he only knows about business...
and he is clueless about art.
Actually, he's very knowledgeable.
Let alone he reads extensively
he knows about the history of
the paintings and the painters as well.
He's smarter than our professors.
If he taught me in the past,
I wouldn't have to resort
to cramping myself with books.
Now you're worshiping him?
I'm not worshiping him.
I just think that he's amazing.
When you talk about him,
your eyes is glowing.
Just like when you talk about
Li Ming Cheng and Xun Ran.
So, do you know...
his position in your heart?
But this time, he's serious.
I thought he was just playing with you.
Yeah, I thought of that too.
I thought he just wanted to
monitor me when I was studying.
I didn't expect him to make
the notes for me personally.
Zhang Shuai made some notes for me too.
But he only highlighted
the important parts.
Wei Qing is different.
Besides highlighting them, he also
made some charts and diagrams.
He's so busy.
How did he find the time for this?
Silly girl.
Of course he made them
when you didn't notice him.
Maybe he made them during your sleep.
Maybe he's making them
for you right now.
Anyway, you must thank him this time.
He did put a lot of effort into it.
I should thank him.
Okay then. I'll go and buy food now.
You do your papers, okay?
Goodbye.
I slept at 4 a.m. these few days.
Now, I can't sleep when
it's not that time.
Silly girl.
Of course he made them
when you didn't notice him.
Maybe he made them during your sleep.
Maybe he's making them
for you right now.
Anyway, you must thank him this time.
He did put a lot of effort into it.
Get out.
-But the pictures...
-Get out!
Who's there?
I'm coming.
Did you sleep well?
You're here?
What's wrong?
Do you think you have revised
your homework already?
No. I thought that...
You thought what?
Change your clothes now.
And go upstairs.
Okay.
Now, your professional knowledge
is good enough already.
For the next task,
we'll focus on CET-4.
Of course.
I'll spend two hours per day
to help you do revision as well.
So that you can remember them.
Are you sure you want to write that?
What's wrong?
Did it wake up your inner trauma?
Did this remind you of the horror?
which the College Entrance Exam brought to you.
You look very excited about this.
I didn't take the  the College Entrance Exam.
I can experience it with you this time.
Besides,
it can awaken the memories inside you
It's good for you.
When you're reminded of that,
you can learn better.
Anyway,
we don't have much time left.
You will have a hard time.
Are you ready?
I'm ready. I know I won't get to sleep.
It's best if you know that.
There's no shortcut in learning English.
But we do have shortcuts
in memorising words.
There are many methods
available in the market.
To sum them up,
they're the affixes mnemonics,
categorization mnemonics,
associative mnemonics,
and pictogram mnemonics.
I'll try to combine all of these
methods for you to learn better.
What is this?
I've asked the technical department
to total up the words used...
in the last 10 years of the CET-4.
And categorised them accordingly
so that you can understand better.
This is amazing.
You should've teach in the
New Oriental Group.
Please go ahead
Besides memorising them,
you need to answer questions.
But you've done that before.
I'll skip that then.
When you wake up in the morning,
you have the best memory.
We'll focus on memorising.
Although you may be tired
in the afternoon, I can help with that.
During the night,
we're the most focused.
I'll give you pop quiz during that time.
Do you have any questions?
Tell me.
Do...
I need to starve again?
If you're full, you're easy to get tired.
My goodness.
Director He.
Do I have anything in the afternoon?
You don't.
I'll confirm that later.
No need for that.
Just help me cancel everything.
Later, you must go to an event with me.
Okay.
Director He, I thought we were
going to a shooting event?
You'll know that shortly.
This is...
Today is the first month
since we've known each other.
In this month,
we knew each other,
we had misunderstandings,
and we had feelings for each other.
No, I had feelings for you.
Honestly speaking,
I had never fell so deeply in love
with someone.
Although we didn't
spend much time together,
your every actions and words...
were deeply imprinted in my heart.
Fei Fei, will you be my girlfriend?
Director He.
I think I need some time.
Of course.
As long as you don't reject me.
I'll wait for your answer.
Let's go. I've booked
a restaurant already.
We can go there now.
What's wrong?
You don't want to go with me for dining?
It's not true. Let's go then.
-Let's go.
Time to wake up.
to resist.
Withstand.
W- I-T-H-S-T-A-N-D.
A workshop or a factory.
Workshop.
Workshop!
To injure someone.
Where did you get these two guys?
Yun Ma Group is a big company.
Is it very difficult to find
two foreign employees?
But there is no oral test for CET-4.
I'm training your listening now.
Isn't this too much?
Can't I just listen to the recordings?
Recordings are dead,
but humans are alive.
I hired them because
I want you to learn faster.
If you do well, during your exam,
you will have images in your mind.
And it's good for your memory.
Start! Let's begin.
♪ My fringe isn't listening to me well ♪
♪ It isn't like me ♪
♪ It's like you instead ♪
♪ The hot weather is annoying ♪
♪ My mood is like the rain ♪
♪ It may be cloudy or sunny like you ♪
♪ The "us" that I yearn of ♪
♪ Was "you" as stated by her ♪
♪ I was the only serious one ♪
♪ The "us" that I yearn of ♪
♪ If you didn't tell me firmly... ♪
♪ to trust you ♪
♪ My fringe isn't listening to me well ♪
♪ It isn't like me ♪
♪ It's like you instead ♪
♪ The hot weather is annoying ♪
♪ My mood is like the rain ♪
♪ It may be cloudy or sunny like you ♪
♪ The "us" that I yearn of ♪
♪ Was "you" as stated by her ♪
♪ I was the only serious one ♪
♪ The "us" that I yearn of ♪
♪ If you didn't tell me firmly... ♪
♪ to trust you ♪