=Adventure behind the Bronze Door=
(Adapted from the original novel
"Zang Hai Hua" by Nan Pai San Shu)
=Episode 17=
(This story is purely fictional)
I didn't expect Wu Xie
to really complete the mission.
It seems we underestimated him before.
Of course you did.
My master is very capable.
I want to learn from him.
I want to beat the Night King.
Good.
He was the first
to pass Wang Jinyuan's test.
Our patriarch did choose the right man.
Enjoy your drink. I'm going home.
Where are you going?
No, you can't leave.
I can't drink anymore.
I am
friends with Qiling,
and you're childhood friends with him.
This time, we've gone to hell and back
for his sake.
So
I guess we're friends now.
Here's to you.
If I get drunk, Haixing will be mad.
- I have something important to tell you.
- She's not here right now.
Speak of the devil.
Who's here?
This little guy wants
to make a toast to you.
He's too embarrassed to do it himself,
so he dragged me along.
Zhang Xiaoguo, you're embarrassed?
When you met me before,
you looked like you weren't afraid
of anything.
Master.
He's heard of you before.
But at that time, you were just
a symbol,
a name to him.
But when you appeared in front of him
and accomplished something
that others thought
was impossible,
he realised
that the hero was right next to him,
visible, tangible and real.
At this point,
he's too embarrassed
to approach you.
When did you become so understanding?
Back then,
after Zhang Qiling got the Heavenly Staff
and sacrificed himself
to succeed the patriarch,
we realised
how great this person
who had adventures with us was.
Master, here's to you.
You're amazing.
Xiaoguo,
it's not that I'm amazing.
I'm sure your patriarch
doesn't think he's that great of a man.
It's only because we dare to do
what others think we can't do.
You're so little now,
but you're so brave.
When you grow up,
you'll be better than all of us.
Come on.
Wait.
I've never seen you smile before.
If you're happy today,
can you show me your smile?
Come on.
Cheers.
Mr. Haike,
here's to you, too.
Haike.
The last one.
Cheers.
Goodbye, Master.
Bye.
Isn't Fatty usually quite energetic?
Why is he so abnormal today?
He's hurt. Just let him rest.
Haixing,
give him the key you got.
Why?
Give it to me.
Give it to whoever you want.
You never listen to me anyway.
She's used to such a way
of doing things.
You have the key now.
I've given you
everything I can.
I hope we won't be suspicious
of each other
in the days to come.
Otherwise,
we can't accomplish it.
You don't have to stress about it
because it's from the patriarch.
It's up to you
how you use it.
I have no right to ask.
If you decide
to fulfill the duties of patriarch,
I will do everything
in my power to help you.
Have a seat.
There's something
I've always wondered about.
Well, what happened
after your family
came to Dejia
that made Zhang Nian and Zhang Jiuri
so powerful?
When the patriarch entered
the Zhang Family Ancient Tower,
all the Zhangs
were given their long-awaited freedom
and scattered all over the world.
You know how powerful
the Zhangs are,
but we used them with restraint
and didn't expose them to the world.
But at that moment,
we're going into the world
of ordinary people,
and you know what that means?
I know.
The Zhangs' powers
are like a double-edged sword.
Once unrestrained
and coupled with the desires of some,
they may be used without restraint.
That would be an indelible disaster
for the mundane world.
Back then, the Zhang family
was divided into two kinds.
One kind is the ones you see here,
we chose to live in seclusion
and stay out of the world's affairs.
And another kind, like Zhang Nian,
who couldn't control his own desires
and abused the Zhang family's power
to plunge the world into more crises
until the patriarch
solved the Night King's case
and came to Dejia.
Those Zhangs were scared when they heard
the patriarch was coming,
so they've restrained themselves.
But there were others
who wanted to fight back,
so they joined forces
to assassinate the patriarch.
But they vanished
and never showed up again.
No one knows what happened.
The patriarch stopped Zhang Nian
and
went to the old underground city of Dejia
to hide the Heavenly Staff and the key
before leaving.
And he hasn't come back since.
I heard that he entered the Bronze Door
of Yunding Heavenly Palace
to guard the ultimate secret
of the world.
After that,
Zhang Nian got someone
to pretend to be you,
and I realised
that the patriarch
had entrusted such an important matter
as the Night King Devours The Sky
to an ordinary person.
I was curious about you at the time
because the patriarch never
left his duties to others.
It's the first time.
I always wondered
how capable you were
of making the patriarch
give you the job.
So
you tried to test me many times before.
I looked into you earlier,
and the results showed
that you're very ordinary
indeed.
But I didn't believe it then.
I thought you'd been pretending,
or else
the patriarch's choice
would have been too hasty.
But I can now understand
why the patriarch
gave you such an important task.
In his mind,
he's experienced too much betrayal
and abandonment.
He's lost all trust
in the Zhangs.
And you
made him feel
that there was someone else in the world
who would fight to the death
to walk alongside him.
♪We've lost ourselves♪
♪In the unknown destiny they expected♪
♪No one had the chance
to tell us all the stories♪
♪And you never found yourself
in all the secrets♪
♪How can I break the maze?♪
♪How can I read the trail you left us?♪
Come on.
Drink up.
Are you my buddy?
Fatty.
Come on,
I'm looking for you.
Naive,
come on.
You...
You're ignoring me. I'm coming for you.
Come on, let's drink.
Are you my buddy?
Are you going to drink?
Drink up.
I won't drink,
and you'll have to stop drinking, too.
You dislike me!
I don't.
Why are you upset?
I was just talking to Zhang Haike,
he told me
a lot of things about Qiling's past.
Things about Qiling?
That's a good thing.
Listen here, Naive,
you've got the key.
You're one step closer to Qiling.
You should be happy.
Have some chicken wings.
Come on, have some chicken wings.
Fatty, stop it.
Be good. Good boy.
Take those keys out, put them together
and see if they fit.
Don't let Zhang Haike fool you
with a fake key.
Look, I'm still looking out for you.
It's a real key.
That's great.
I've finally got it.
All right, leave it with me.
Give it to me.
You're drunk. Don't lose it.
You don't feel at ease, do you?
I trust you.
You don't trust your buddy.
You don't trust me with it.
You don't care about my feelings.
- It's because you're drunk.
- Have you ever cared about me?
You just left me there.
You let me sleep.
Weren't you afraid I'd freeze?
- Seriously. Give me the key.
- I've been so nice to you.
Fatty.
Thank you.
Thanks for getting me the key.
Wu Xie,
you need to think about
when you
started losing.
Wu Xie,
we've finally met.
I've waited a long time for this moment.
From the first step you took,
I knew all your tricks.
I just watched you play.
It was long and dull.
You're too careless.
The Zhangs are familiar
with all kinds of poisons,
so I used
a very special kind of psychedelic,
colorless and tasteless,
enough to make most
of the Zhangs pass out.
Before they wake up,
I'll finish it off.
Stop looking.
Zhang Haike,
Zhang Haixing,
all Zhangs,
Fatty,
everyone must die,
but you don't have to.
As long as you take me
to the place where Zhang Qiling went
and find him,
I won't kill you.
Someone's spiked the wine.
We've got to wake everyone up.
What's going on? Where are
Zhang Haike and the others?
Wake them up.
I feel terrible.
Hang in there a little longer.
Who are you?
You go in first.
What about them?
You're the most important.
We need to protect you.
I've never been the most important.
We've got to get up there and save them.
Zhang Haike has been captured,
Zhang Haixing is nowhere to be found,
and Wu Xie has disappeared.
Find Wu Xie.
I want him alive.
Yes.
Mr. Zhang,
why did you kill those people?
You're making putting an end
to this very difficult.
Our purpose is to get the Night King.
Killing those people
won't do us any good.
Mr. Feng,
it seems you don't approve
of my actions.
You're doing things too rough.
And you impersonated Wang Fatty
and acted on your own
without informing me in advance.
I have to thank you
for providing me with the information
so that I could disguise myself
as Wang Fatty seamlessly
and fool everyone.
Even though Wu Xie is brainless,
he's not stupid.
If I leak the plan ahead of time,
there's no guarantee
it won't get out.
I must put on a good show.
I need to be sure that it works.
Besides,
as long as we get the key,
it doesn't matter
if some insignificant people die.
Mr. Feng, I'm sure you understand
that what I'm doing
is for the sake of our cooperation.
Since Wu Xie's body can't be found,
don't worry, he won't die.
Let's go.
I know where the Heavenly Staff is.
Zhang Qiling's key is really ingenious.
I didn't expect it to be engraved
with a map
of the underground drainage system
of Dejia City.
Mr. Zhang,
Is this where the Heavenly Staff
is kept?
(How much time has passed
since I was stabbed?)
(I'm not dead yet.)
(I don't think any organs were hurt.)
(Luck is still on my side.)
(Where's Fatty?)
(I wonder how the others)
(are doing.)
Yes, my name is Zhang Xiaoguo. Master.
Thank you, Master.
Zhang Haike.
(I have to make a call.)
(I have to make a call)
(to...)
(to Hua and the others for help.)
In case you get credit for finding
the Heavenly Staff, you have to make it clear
that the five of us
worked together to get it.
So we're Scorpion Team now.
For better
or for worse.
- Okay.
Mr. Zhang,
it's a messy record.
It's not clear at all.
Zhang Qiling had almost lost his memory
when he hid the Heavenly Staff.
What's recorded here
are some fragmented information
he told Wang Jinyuan.
Wang Jinyuan recorded it
and kept it here.
Is there anything related
to the Night King?
It's all just tattered memories.
These are all
Zhang Qiling's memories.
Don't let Wu Xie get them.
Burn them all.
(1. Call the police 2. Negotiate
with Zhang Nian 3. Save them myself)
Qiling,
I screwed up. I screwed it all up.
(Our patriarch
did choose the right man.)
(Wu Xie,)
(you need to think about)
(when you)
(started losing.)
I can't.
If only I could have...
If only I could have reacted earlier.
No.
(Even if I gave you
another chance right now,)
(you'd still make the same choice.)
(Even if you knew you'd die here,)
(you'd still come.)
(I've never seen you smile before.)
(If you're happy today,)
(can you show me your smile?)
How could this happen?
It shouldn't be.
They shouldn't be the ones to die.
God, I'm begging you
to give me another chance.
Please tell me what to do.
What to do? What to do?
You shouldn't have run away alone first.
You've caused them all to die.
You must remember this day forever.
Zhang Nian is from Zhang's family,
and so is Qiling.
So the only people in Niles
who can deal with Zhang Nian
are the Zhangs.
Who lived in those houses
on the mountain?
The old monsters.
The purest
and longest-lived
of the Dejia's Zhangs
live here in seclusion.
Until now,
those in the back of the mountain
can only accept
those who can bring out the token
as orthodox Zhang family members.
They are the only ones qualified
to enter the mountain.
I have to to get them to help.
(It's the only way now.)
What is this place?
How come there are so many
marks that represent danger
to the Zhangs?
This should be the place
where the Zhangs lived
when they were still in Dejia.
(What is this place?)
(Zhang Jinyuan, Zhang Haiping
Zhang Fuyi, Zhang Zide)
(Looks like these)
(are the Zhangs who tried to go in)
(and didn't come out.)
(Fire.)
(People were being punished.)
(They're all burned to death.)
(A god who masters fire.)
♪Swept into a cold, relentless fate♪
♪Which snow will conceal the mystery?♪
♪Even if the chill is unavoidable♪
♪I’ll ignite my obsession♪
♪Until all the storms and snow subside♪
♪No longer hiding♪
♪That unknown miracle♪
♪Only you will walk towards eternity♪
♪Maybe the colors have long blurred♪
♪Maybe they’ve long dissolved into chaos♪
♪Forgetting the reason,
forgetting the outcome♪
♪Why not forget it all?♪
♪That scar, that shackle♪
♪Let the storm sing praises,
storm, storm, storm♪
♪Witness a brave heart shining bright♪
♪Forgetting the reason,
forgetting the outcome♪
♪But holding on even tighter,
no matter the ease or adversity♪
♪Still stubborn, unrepentant,
storm, storm, storm♪
♪Forgetting the return date,
but not this moment♪
♪Carving an unnamed verse♪
♪Which mountain turned away and forgot?♪
♪Even if time flows endlessly♪
♪It hasn’t erased your trace♪
♪But this path is always rugged♪
♪People gaze at mottled illusions♪
♪Through a door,
glimpsing heaven and earth♪
♪Even if the colors have long blurred♪
♪Even if they’ve long
dissolved into chaos♪
♪Forgetting the reason,
forgetting the outcome♪
♪Why not forget it all?♪
♪That scar, that shackle♪
♪Let the storm sing praises,
storm, storm, storm♪
♪Witness a brave heart shining bright♪
♪Forgetting the reason,
forgetting the outcome♪
♪But holding on even tighter,
no matter the ease or adversity♪
♪Still stubborn, unrepentant,
storm, storm, storm♪
♪Forgetting the return date,
but not this moment♪