GYEONGSEONG CREATURE
What is this place?
Let me out of here. Please?
Please take me with you.
Please!
Please help me.
Don't come close.
I might end up attacking you.
How are you here?
So get away from me, please.
Please!
Tae-sang!
You're awake.
What is this?
I'd like to hear what happened yesterday.
Who did you meet in that old factory?
Where are the others?
Call Yong-gil for me first.
Mr. Kwon is in critical condition.
He sustained a severe head injury,
which led to a brain hemorrhage.
He's currently in the ICU
after emergency surgery.
And where's the ICU?
I have to see him first. Uncuff me.
Not right now.
I need to see for myself what happened
and what condition he's in!
Take this off now.
I'm Yong-gil's guardian, okay?
We found a weapon that we suspect
had been used at the scene.
We only found traces of two people on it.
Hair and blood
seemingly belonging to Mr. Kwon,
and your fingerprints, Mr. Jang.
What are you saying?
You two were the only ones there,
and based on evidence and circumstances,
there is a high possibility
that you're the one who attacked Mr. Kwon.
Don't be ridiculous!
Why would I do such a thing to him?
Was it because of money?
What?
I heard Bugang Company had a lot of debt.
Do you want to start from there?
Look here, Detective.
Who's the woman that was with you?
What's her deal?
Is she the one who murdered
Madam Na and Oh Ki-hoon?
No.
If not, how is she connected
to the serial killer?
There's no connection whatsoever!
Then tell me what exactly happened there.
Ms. Yoon Chae-ok.
Hey!
Stay with me!
Wake up!
Open your eyes!
Hey!
GYEONGSEONG CREATURE
BETWEEN A PRETENSE OF VIRTUE AND VICE
EPISODE 4
THE OTHER SIDE
Is it consciousness or the subconscious
that rules over a person?
What changes fate?
Is it a routine
that is repeated day after day?
Or is it unforeseen coincidence
and hardship?
What is it that defines
the kind of person we are?
Is it disposition?
Or is it ability?
That would depend on the person,
would it not?
Why would it depend on the person?
Because every individual
is quite different.
They all transform in unpredictable ways.
It's not because they are different.
It is because they are imperfect.
Most humans are neither here nor there.
They are but imperfect beings
placed on the borderline.
It may appear as though humans
are ceaselessly seeking life's answers,
but in truth,
they only strive to resolve
the anxiety in themselves.
Therefore,
it is fundamentally impossible
for a human being to hold good intentions.
They make selfish choices
for themselves and themselves only
from the beginning to the very end.
That is why our work
carries so much significance.
And that is why
we must continue
to move forward and evolve.
We do not have time to waste
on failure like this.
I apologize.
We will intensify our efforts.
I'd like you to bring that person back.
But Lady Maeda, he's already--
Bring him back.
Yes, ma'am.
Detective Noh.
How's he doing so far?
He's having a total breakdown.
He caused a scene at first,
demanding to see Kwon Yong-gil,
but now he's just lying down
without doing or saying anything.
What did the doctor say?
His injury isn't that severe,
so he'll be discharged by this afternoon.
Okay, then get him discharged
and bring him straight to the station.
I have so many questions.
Yes, sir.
What do I need to do
to get Jang Ho-jae discharged today?
Please wait. Let me ask his doctor.
Keep it down.
I'm here to help.
Wait, how did this…
We're done searching outside, Captain.
Nothing seems worth noting.
-What are you doing?
-Give me a hand.
Yes, got it.
"Nitrogen."
What is this?
It says "Jeonseung Bio."
Jeonseung Biotech.
-Jeonseung Biotech?
-Yes.
Let's get out of here first.
I have a lot to tell you.
Are you kidding me, asshole?
You can't fool me twice.
Don't you want to find her?
The doctor will be right down.
Please wait in the patient's room.
Okay, thank you.
The suspect has escaped. Call for backup.
INTENSIVE CARE UNIT
Upstairs, quickly!
Mr. Kwon Yong-gil's guardian?
Please put on a mask
and sanitize your hands.
You'll be given five minutes.
He's still unconscious.
You'll have to see him and come right out.
So what happened? Have you found him yet?
Forensics. I found this upstairs.
We are combing through
the whole hospital right now.
We'll keep looking.
Goddamn it!
Yong-gil.
Why did you do that?
For what?
I need to know at least something.
We received a call from the ICU.
Apparently, Kwon's guardian
just came to see him.
Don't go.
How are you feeling?
Can you hear me? It's me, Ho-jae.
Don't go.
Don't go back.
Keep living
as Ho-jae.
Just like now.
Damn it.
This is her scan.
Let me shade in this region here
for a better look.
The way the Najin has settled down
is similar to that of Seung-jo's.
When a Najin enters a body as a larva,
it latches on
nearer to the top of the head.
But these two have settled in the back.
As Seung-jo received
a mature Najin from his mother,
it is highly likely
that it was the same case for her as well.
It won't open.
Who's there?
Do you know where we are
or what it is they do here?
Are you all right? Hey!
They said they would cure me.
They said if I drank it…
I wouldn't have to live
with a disability anymore.
It's a simple experiment.
You just have to empty
the glass of water in front of you.
Then you'll immediately receive
ten million won in your bank accounts.
Excuse me.
Yes?
If the experiment succeeds,
will my leg be cured for sure?
You have infantile paralysis, I see.
That's correct.
If this experiment succeeds,
you'll no longer live with a disability.
All right, then. Let's drink up, shall we?
Ten million…
MY PUPPY
The person you're calling is unavailable.
Leave a message after the tone.
I'll no longer have a disability.
You won't have to suffer because of me.
Help!
Please help me!
They said…
my leg would heal
if the experiment succeeded.
Is there anything more I should know
about myself before the accident?
You're much better off now
than you were before the accident.
I just came to check
if all your memories really disappeared.
Please…
Ms. Yoon Chae-ok.
Sir!
Master Jang!
Sir, what are you doing?
Aren't you going to take a photograph?
You're not waiting
for the sun to set, are you?
We have to take it while the sun's out.
Hurry up. I'm busy!
You'll let me take a photo
on my own later, won't you?
Yeong-chun.
You can go to the studio
and use your own money to do that.
Stop staring at us and come here already!
Hurry up!
Chop-chop!
Come now.
Here I come.
All right, looking good.
-Slow down!
-Sure. As you wish.
Here we go now. One, two…
One, two, three!
Please. I said I'm fine.
We're celebrating, remember?
A little closer. Look friendly.
Give us a smile!
They won't arrest you for smiling.
Show your teeth at least!
That's it. One, two, three!
Do you want something to drink?
Weak.
Too slow, man.
How are you going to find that woman
in that sorry state?
Asshole. Are you going
to keep hiding like this?
Does it look like I'm hiding?
I'm right here, you know.
It's driving you mad, huh?
I'm here, but you can't see me.
When you can see me, you can't catch me.
I don't listen to cowards who hide.
Come out now.
Show yourself, asshole!
Now what?
Can you beat me?
You're gonna get yourself killed.
No one has ever messed with us before,
except one person.
That's you.
Don't you miss those times?
You crazy bastard!
You know what I'm talking about.
Your memories are coming back.
Aren't they?
Don't run from anything.
Look it in the eye
and face it head-on.
Then you'll have a real shot at winning.
Those were your words, Ho-jae.
You have to remember.
Are you okay?
Hey!
Wake up!
He'll stay like that for a while.
Even if he gains consciousness,
he won't be able to recognize anyone.
A massive craving will hit him at first.
But you already know that.
How long have you lived like that?
Tell me where I am first.
As far as I can remember…
the Najin was never leaked to the outside.
Just what on earth are you bastards?
What kind of bastards are you
to be doing such a terrible thing?
How did you survive?
How long have you lived
without being under control?
Are there more of our kind out there
besides you?
Don't tell me…
this is Ongseong Hospital.
Is it?
That hospital closed
when the Greater East Asia War ended.
Most of the building
was destroyed during the war,
and Jeonseung Biotech was built
on top of its ruins.
Its founders are Lady Maeda
and the former chairman, Kato.
Chairman Shin Ji-oh, his son,
has currently succeeded him.
So it's not over, then.
This hell.
Now, answer me.
Who are you?
Out.
Make your choice.
Either go back to the man you used to be,
or…
die here like this.
Don't go back.
Keep living
as Ho-jae.
Just like now.
Come back.
Be it Ho-jae…
or Tae-sang, I don't care.
Go back to the man I once knew.
Let's go back to those times.
Okay?
Long time no see…
Ms. Yoon Chae-ok.