My hand!
Come on.
[Beneath the Undertow]
[Episode 13]
Where is he?
Wasn't he supposed to be in the hospital?
He's gone.
He's gone?
Wasn't he poisoned?
And he was still able to run around?
He could.
He just came back
and took Sui Xiao out.
That's what love can do.
Where is Ao Xiaojie?
What's on your mind?
Just nervous.
Can you let go of my hand now?
No.
This... this kid is so thoughtless,
bringing you here without any notice.
Is... is my place too messy?
It's fine,
not messy.
Quite clean, actually.
He comes over to help me clean
whenever he's free.
I can't even chase him off.
Did he tell you who I am?
He told me on the way here.
I'm just wondering
why he brought you to my place.
He said...
you're his only family now.
And you're
the only girl he's ever brought here.
I don't mean anything else by that.
I-I don't mean
that he's dated many girls before.
He's... You...
you know what I mean.
-He's never had a girlfriend.
-I know, I know.
I get it.
The fact that he brought you here...
means he's really serious about you.
I'll go check on him.
Okay, okay, go ahead.
How did you get this?
From a spiked club.
Got it back when I was
still young and foolish.
I also have knife scars on my body.
That won't put you off, will it?
Aren't you all grown up now?
What are you doing?
Yang,
this is not the place.
You...
In-law.
What are you going to do?
Sit down.
Dad.
Yang.
You walking jinx,
who invited you here?
-Yang, what are you doing?
-Let go! Let go of it!
Don't do this!
What are you doing?
I'm not your dad!
Yang!
Yang, what are you doing?
Get lost!
This is your son's wedding, Yang!
Can you stop causing a scene?
Have some decency!
He has decency.
Go be with him, then!
In...
Get out of here!
I'm a complete joke!
You still wanna drink?
None of you get to drink!
None of you!
Mom.
Let's go back.
Let's go.
-Let's go.
-Tang Juan.
We're better off
not marrying into a family like this.
Let's go.
Yang Baoge!
Keep flipping!
Come on!
Knock everything over!
Kill me.
Kill me!
Kill me now!
Come on!
Flip everything over!
Screw it all!
Sui Xiao is a good girl,
you lucky dog.
What are you talking about?
Nothing, nothing.
Leave these peanuts here.
Now that Ao Xiaojie has been arrested,
I feel like a huge weight's been lifted.
I know.
He helped you, and you see him as a buddy.
But I'm afraid you can't see through him.
He's not like you.
He's calculating and ambitious.
I once tried to help him
get on the right track,
but what did he do?
He thought I was trying to
throw him in jail.
These eyes of mine...
they're very likely his doing.
Dad, what's wrong?
Xiaozhou?
I'm sorry, Xiaozhou.
I'm sorry.
Dad didn't take good care of your pipa.
Dad couldn't protect your pipa.
I'm sorry.
Since yesterday,
Ao Xiaojie hasn't said anything useful—
he just keeps beating around the bush
and dodging questions.
When questioned about the girls
being beaten and sexually assaulted,
he claims it was due to
poor supervision of his men
and that he never personally participated.
As for the murder,
he flatly denies it.
Someone attacked him
before we could get to him.
Yes.
Someone wanted to silence him.
Who would do that?
He probably knows
but won't say.
That Shark,
Sha Hongli, was probably silenced too.
I thought Ao Xiaojie was the one
behind all of this,
but now it seems
he's just another pawn.
He was about to be silenced,
yet he still won't talk?
This only shows
that the real mastermind is very powerful,
with a far reach.
This case
is no longer just a simple murder.
The more we pull at this thread,
the deeper it goes.
Well... what about Dayong, the one
who escaped with Ao Xiaojie?
He's in the hospital.
They managed to save him,
but he's badly injured.
Did Ao Xiaojie witness
Dayong getting beaten like that?
Yes.
But during the interrogation,
Ao Xiaojie
didn't ask about
Dayong's condition even once?
Not a word.
He's just an ungrateful scumbag.
He's definitely not the loyal type,
but not asking even once...
You think...
Sir, Shi Qiangfeng wants to
beat up Ao Xiaojie.
-Stop! You can't go in there!
-What are you doing?
I'm warning you, don't do anything stupid!
That was just angry talk.
I won't beat him.
I just want to ask him something.
No!
You can't!
I won't beat him.
I just need to ask him something.
Interrogations must follow protocol.
Fine, I'll ask after you're done.
But...
I have a request.
Did you see these clearly?
He's badly injured,
but his life isn't in danger.
What's that saying?
"If you do the crime,
you do the time."
The person who beat him should also pay.
You don't need to act like you don't care.
Having someone you care about
isn't something to be ashamed of.
Don't worry,
we've already coordinated with
the detention center.
We'll guarantee your absolute safety.
You're not just saying that, right?
No.
Wait... what's he doing here?
I may be blind,
but I'm still a cop.
You've already retired.
Can you still interrogate me?
After retiring from active duty,
I became a community patrol officer,
and now I'm assigned to
assist with this special case.
You're some kind of big deal now, kid.
Feng.
Feng, I didn't mean to kill you.
That drug wasn't pure—I watered it down.
You know I only sell watered-down stuff...
Cut that out.
I know.
You don't have the guts to kill anyone.
Otherwise, he'd be dead already.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Ao Xiaojie,
how long have we known each other?
I remember...
I knew you
even before I met him.
Back then, you were just a kid,
small in size and small in courage.
You liked tagging along with adults.
You never rush to be at the front
when doing things.
Actually, you aren't a bad kid.
You just lacked affection
while growing up,
afraid of being bullied.
People,
we always need to learn self-preservation.
And you're smart,
quick-witted,
and a fast learner
who knows how to get by.
In this regard, you're better than he is.
That's why you kept making me
go to school back then.
I'm not cut out for that.
You've always been the clever one.
Sharp.
So when you do things,
you weigh the pros and cons,
avoid danger, and see the advantage.
Being the first to stick your neck out
isn't your style.
You never take things too far.
Right?
They told me
what you've done these years.
Just as I thought,
you're still just a sidekick.
Murder?
You don't have the guts for it.
I don't believe
there isn't a boss behind you.
You need to think this through.
Take responsibility for your own crimes.
You're still young.
If you confess,
you might get a reduced sentence.
After you serve your time,
you can still start your life over.
Look at me.
I'm already this old.
Look at the state I'm in now,
and even I can start a new life.
Right?
An accident ruined my eyes.
Xiaojie,
you didn't do this to me, did you?
Tell the truth.
Or was it your boss behind that?
Who was it?
-It really wasn't me.
-Tell the truth!
It was Kun.
He mentioned it to me once.
He said
that no one would bother me anymore.
Who is Kun?
He's the guy who does the dirty work.
The one who wanted me dead this time
is definitely him too.
He's extremely ruthless.
He has a nickname in the underworld,
"Reaper."
But none of us dares to call him that.
Who does he do dirty work for?
Xiaojie,
since you're going to spill,
spill it all.
Li Dada.
Li Dada?
Yeah.
Why does Li Dada want to silence you?
He's the money behind me.
My company
and the KTV business
are both his.
I'm just a street thug.
Where would I get the money
to start something this big?
I'm the front man,
and Kun handles all the dirty work.
My streamers—
I screen them once,
and then Li Dada picks from them again.
If he sees someone he likes,
I take her to attend
those secret parties he organizes.
But I'm not allowed into these parties,
so I don't know what happens there,
and I don't dare to ask.
Those two...
who died...
I know that one of them had been there.
And the other one...
someone took her there.
The loan shark, Shark.
Yeah, I do know too much.
What about Shen Xiaozhou?
Shen Xiaozhou never went to those parties.
She only did a couple of livestreams
before she left.
And I never saw her again.
At that time,
Li Dada made me force that nerd
to delete his post,
and I found it a bit weird.
Why do you think
he didn't want people to know
that Shen Xiaozhou had worked
as a streamer?
Because he didn't want us to
trace it back to you
and then to him.
Shen Xiaozhou was actually...
introduced to me by Li Dada
at Zhang Haoyang's request.
She genuinely wanted to work to earn money
because her family was poor.
But I just don't get
why someone like her exists.
With such a rich backing,
she still insisted on
earning mere pennies.
She was so contradictory.
She clearly cared a lot about money.
When we discussed the commission split,
she haggled over
one or two percentage points
for ages,
calculating everything
down to the last penny.
And then,
she just quit without warning
and didn't take a single cent.
Who else from your company
attended Li Dada's secret parties?
Tell us.
We'll protect everyone who's involved.
No one else.
Whenever someone went to that party...
I never saw her again.
Who is it?
Still awake?
Sorry to disturb you.
What's wrong?
I owe you an apology.
I failed to deal with Ao Xiaojie.
Forget it,
he won't dare speak carelessly anyway.
Ao Xiaojie has no family,
so he's hard to control.
So you need to be more careful
from now on.
You can just be more careful for me.
Ma.
How did you meet Shi Qiangfeng?
I arrested him near the railway.
He was 17 that year.
He got into a fight at the train station
while trying to help someone.
He, alone against five or six of them,
got beaten bloody,
yet still held out.
It took me a lot of effort
to become friends with him.
He only started calling me "Uncle"
after more than a year.
He's good at heart.
He has that heroic spirit in him.
Like a rough diamond—
with some polishing,
it could become a gem.
Look, the police academy did just that.
Let's go, Ma.
You've made a contribution.
Watch it. What do you mean,
"I made a contribution"?
It was all thanks to Lian's arrangements.
Lian, we're heading out.
Ao Xiaojie confessed
that Jia Beibei attended
Li Dada's secret parties.
And Wang Yishan
was probably brought there
by Shark, Sha Hongli.
This Sha Hongli
is very likely Li Dada's puppet too.
Now all the evidence
points to Li Dada.
We should make him our primary suspect
and focus the investigation on him.
Investigate him,
but covertly,
without revealing our intentions.
His father, Li Longhe,
is the boss of Jinhai Group,
a celebrity entrepreneur.
We can't afford a repeat
of the internet controversy
with Zhang Haoyang last time.
We need to get solid evidence
before making a move,
and when we strike, we finish him.
Chief Qiu,
any further instructions?
Even though all the clues point to
Li Dada...
we still
don't know who attended those parties
or what exactly happened there.
Anyone who attended those parties
is a suspect.
But this killer
has his own specific preferences
and signature.
He is a typical...
sexual psychopath.
So we need to continue verifying
and eliminating suspects.
Lian Haiping.
Do you think Li Dada fits the profile?
I've met him twice.
Based on his personality and behavior,
I'd say there's a 70% chance.
Plus, he's predominantly left-handed.
Come here. I won't hit you.
But Shen Xiaozhou...
What about Shen Xiaozhou?
Do you remember?
The morning after Shen Xiaozhou's case,
he hit someone with his car,
and I took him back to the station.
He was extremely agitated at that time.
Yes, very excited.
Actually...
that isn't the state someone'd be in
right after committing murder.
On the contrary,
he should have been relatively calm
after getting the satisfaction.
Are you saying
that Shen Xiaozhou might not have
been killed by him?
I don't know.
Look, to clean the oyster,
from here, like this.
Press down, but watch your fingers.
Don't flick it.
Take two eggs.
See? Two of them.
TV.
Watch me and learn.
You can watch TV after you learn this.
Only after you've learned it.
Come on, look at me.
Crack them.
TV.
Be good.
Weather forecast...
Watch me and learn.
You can watch TV
after you've learned this.
Be good, Xiaohai.
Beating the eggs well.
Watch.
For a small serving,
two spoonfuls are enough.
-TV...
-Like this.
-Watch me.
-TV...
Watch me!
TV!
No TV!
No TV until you've learned this!
What's all this noise about?
Alright, alright, alright.
Xiaohai.
The TV is on.
Come watch.
Meanwhile, as the cold air
moves southward,
heavy rainfall is expected
in Zhejiang and southern Jiangsu...
Xiaozhou...
Possibly accompanied by thunderstorms.
What?
Why do you insist on teaching him this?
When Xiaozhou was alive,
he had someone to rely on!
What should we do now?
One day, when the two of us are gone...
he can only rely on himself.
Beijing...
Xiaozhou...
-Hello, Captain Lian.
My mom made some steamed buns
and insisted that I bring some to you.
Thank Mom for me.
How's Shu doing?
He's being good. Don't worry.
I'm heading to work now.
What?
Nothing. Go ahead.
Talk after the case is solved?
Okay, we'll talk
after the case is solved.
I'm off. Eat the buns while they're hot.
Meeting time.
Let me brief you.
Ao Xiaojie has provided us with the names
of several girls who attended
Li Dada's secret parties.
After our investigation, we found
that they all left Lingchuan
within the past year or two.
We've confirmed the whereabouts of
three of them.
Two returned to Northeast China,
and one went to Sichuan.
The others are still unaccounted for.
Whether Li Dada is a pervert or not,
those people probably witnessed
whatever happened.
So were they scared off,
or were they deliberately sent away?
Go find them.
We've already assigned three teams
and will depart shortly.
Be prepared.
Those girls are probably
even more frightened than Ao Xiaojie.
As long as we can find one
willing to talk,
things will get easier.
Sir,
someone called in,
saying they have information about
the Shen Xiaozhou case.
Who is it?
An elderly couple.
Were you both employees
of the Xuri Factory?
No,
we run a small business.
But it'd be nice
if we were from Xuri Factory.
Why's that?
Didn't Xuri Factory shut down long ago?
That's the good part.
Xuri Factory owns buildings and land,
and when these are demolished, they'll
get oceanview apartments in exchange.
Now, with this murder case,
I'm afraid the demolition
and housing allocation
will likely be delayed.
I heard the boss has changed his mind
and is looking at other locations now.
We don't know much about that.
Is the information you're reporting today
related to Shen Xiaozhou?
What I want to talk about is Yang Tao.
No, not Yang Tao.
It's Yang Tao's father.
Right,
it's Yang Tao's father,
Yang Baoge.
Yang... Yang Baoge...
What's his connection to Shen Xiaozhou?
He has some connection
to Shen Xiaozhou's father.
We've heard about it for a long time.
Well... Yang Baoge
has issues with Shen Huazhang.
At yesterday's wedding,
the way he behaved—
it wasn't just dislike;
it was like they had a real grudge.
Yang Tao's wedding?
Yes.
Yang Baoge
ruined it.
Yesterday, he got drunk
and caused a scene.
He didn't show us any respect
at that wedding.
I'd never let my daughter
marry into a family like that.
Good thing they haven't gotten
their marriage certificates yet.
Then why doesn't
Yang Baoge like Shen Huazhang?
Because of his wife.
Yang Tao's mother.
Back when they were young,
she and Shen Huazhang
had a thing going on.
But that's all ancient history.
So many years have passed,
yet they still hold grudges
like teenagers.
How did you know all this?
Yang Tao came to our house last night
to apologize,
and I got it out of him.
Because their family has
a good relationship with the Shens,
they didn't even set off firecrackers
at the wedding.
All out of respect
because the Shen family's daughter died.
I think that Yang Tao
doesn't look like Yang Baoge at all.
At the wedding yesterday,
Shen Huazhang was present.
And I realized
that Yang Tao actually looks
quite similar to him.
They both have that fair complexion.
Do you think it could be that...
Don't make wild guesses.
But... Yang Baoge
really does have a terrible temper.
H-He's a drunkard,
beating his son whenever he drinks.
The way he beats Yang Tao,
you'd think the boy wasn't even his child.
Yang Tao still has scars
on his back from his belt beatings.
Exactly.
We should stay as far away
from such a family as possible.
If they've really done
something deadly,
how could our daughter live with him?
You think Yang Baoge might have...
Alright.
I understand the situation
you've reported.
Thank you.
Okay.
Oh, right.
Well, I heard
that the Shen family's daughter
was found in the sewage tank
at Xuri Factory,
right?
Before Yang Baoge
was laid off, he worked at
the wastewater treatment plant
of the factory.
Hello?
Hello,
is this Mr. Shi?
Your DNA test results
are ready.
You may come pick them up
at your convenience.
Okay, got it.
You think the information they gave
is helpful?
I think they just want to
break off the engagement.
Still, we can't ignore any leads, right?
There are already many suspicious aspects
surrounding Shen Xiaozhou's case.
It's connected to those other two cases
but also different.
Haven't we seen
this kind of unexpected situation
in previous complex cases
as well?
The least suspicious person
turned out to be the real culprit.
Have we looked into
Yang Baoge's background?
He has a criminal record.
When he was young, he often picked fights
and got into brawls,
serving time twice for injuring others.
If Yang Tao is
really Shen Huazhang's child,
I think we can't rule out
the possibility
that he killed Shen Xiaozhou
to get revenge on Shen Huazhang.
Okay,
then continue with your investigation.
Right now, Li Dada is the main suspect
with many complications.
Zhao Hougang has already sent out
three teams,
so we're a bit short on manpower.
Allocate your men.
Keep what you need,
and send the rest to help him.
One of you follows me,
and the rest cooperate well
with Team Leader Zhao.
Yes, sir.
Don't worry, we'll cooperate fully.
You're not included.
We won't fight with Unit Two.
I want to arrest Li Dada.
Not arrest, investigate.
Investigate, then arrest.
You're planning to join them?
Have you thought it through?
Yes, I have.
You can go.
You follow me.
Captain Lian,
I'm sorry.
It's about Ma, right?
Don't worry,
I won't act impulsively.
Lin Zi has more experience than you.
Cooperate with him well
and avoid any conflicts.
Call me anytime if there are any problems.
G-Got it.
The place we just saw is
a bit too small, isn't it?
Actually, there's another apartment
on the fifth floor.
I'll take you up to see it in a moment.
Okay, I'll take a look.
I'm thirsty.
I'll go get something to drink.
Someone needs to stay in the car!
Bring me a drink,
a cold one.
Okay, got it.
Jia, are you busy?
I need a favor.
Officer Zheng, you're here.
Yesterday,
I don't know
if I caught a draft right here
or slept wrong, but my neck is
really stiff.
Let me massage it for you.
Who all went to
Yang Tao's wedding the other day?
I heard there was some trouble?
You bet there was.
Yang Tao and his father
even flipped over the tables.
But Yang Tao is a good kid.
His father, though, that's another story.
His son was getting married,
and he was causing a drunken scene.
What a joke.
Behaving like an animal at his age.
Yang Baoge was causing a scene...
I-I heard it was because of Shen Huazhang?
He's been jealous for decades.
He couldn't hold back
all that jealousy anymore.
Can't really blame him.
Back in the day,
Shen Huazhang and Ding Shulan
made quite a good couple,
right?
Weren't they on TV together?
Yes.
They were.
In the 1990 city performance,
they represented our factory in the show.
One played the pipa,
while the other performed...
well, a folk dance.
Their skill level
wasn't just local TV—
it was national broadcast quality.
Then, why didn't they...
end up together?
Well, in 1991,
Shen Huazhang's parents both got sick.
So, he
had no time to play the pipa anymore.
And because of that,
he and Ding Shulan
spent less time together.
Plus, Sun Qiuhong was
head over heels for him.
She worked in our factory canteen!
So she brought food
to his parents every day
and took care of them impeccably.
And then later,
Ding Shulan suddenly married Yang Baoge.
So Shen Huazhang and Sun Qiuhong
became a couple.
Tell us something we don't know.
Everyone in our factory knows about that.
Do you know why they really broke up?
What other reasons could there be?
Sun Qiuhong is wife material,
but Ding Shulan isn't.
Who do you think
Shen Huazhang should choose?
That's just you.
You think Shen Huazhang is
the same as you?
When did Shen Huazhang and Ding Shulan
break up in 1991?
It was in the winter of 1991.
My son was just born at that time,
in the same hospital as his parents.
Officer.
Can this case be solved?
Definitely.
Until it's solved,
we won't have peace of mind.
You just want a sea-view apartment, huh?
Cut the crap!
Xiaozhou was one of our own
at the Xuri Factory.
Such a promising young woman...
and someone killed her.
This revenge must be taken.
Yes.
Must be.
If Shen Huazhang and Ding Shulan
really broke up in the winter of 1991...
I remember that Yang Tao
was born in the summer of 1992.
Your memory is quite precise.
It's hot.
I'm getting a bit hungry.
Go get me something to eat.
Twice-cooked pork rice bowl.
He just went in.
What's that?
Why did you buy river snail rice noodles?
Haven't you ever tailed someone before?
This stuff stinks,
with soup and all.
This is the worst food for stakeouts.
With this smell,
everything I eat stinks.
At this distance,
we're bound to get stuck at the red light.
You're practically on his bumper.
Do you have no hand-eye coordination
or something?
Let me drive. Come on.
Can you shut up?
My driving's top three on the team.
Then Captain Lian must be the number one.
He drives like
he's in The Bourne Identity or something.
His driving
is fast and steady.
Especially his keen sense of distance.
He doesn't even need to hit the brakes
and just slips through any gap.
So smooth...
Is Lian Haiping your dad or something?
Hello, this is a residential area.
May I ask whom you're looking for?
Hello, officer.
Which building
does that car owner live in?
He lives in Building 902.
Hello.
I'm tailing Li Dada,
and he just took a girl home.
But I can't get a clear view
of his villa right now.
What should I do?
I'm afraid I won't make it in time
if he makes a move.
Where did he pick up this girl from?
A bar.
None of the previous victims
were taken directly from bars.
Understood.
I'll keep watching.
Li Dada is fast.
It's only been about an hour.
One hour...
and I've got about 100 mosquito bites.
I forgot.
Are they itchy?
Where are you going?
I'm asking you where you're going.
The food is in the pot.
You can eat it later.
Next time when cooking, open the gas valve
and ignite it with a flame.
Otherwise, it won't ignite.
Oil, salt, soy sauce, vinegar, and such—
I've put them all where you can see.
And I've written down all the recipes
of those dishes you like.
They're under the jar at the bottom.
What do you mean by all of this?
Are you going on a long trip?
You know how to use the washing machine.
Xiaozhou already taught you.
Don't use too much detergent.
Hang the laundry out in the morning,
and remember to bring it in at night.
What exactly are you trying to do?
Tell me!
The other day on TV,
I saw a bakery
in the provincial capital
that specifically hires people
like Xiaohai.
I want to take him there to see
if they'll accept him as an apprentice.
How...
how long will you be gone?
If it works out,
we'll stay there.
Fine,
just go.
If you don't want to come back,
then don't!
Xiaozhou's case hasn't been solved yet,
and you're already abandoning this home!
You only care about Xiaohai,
not Xiaozhou.
Wasn't Xiaozhou your child too?
You used to work at
the wastewater treatment plant too?
Yeah.
That Yang Baoge,
he's got a bad temper and a petty mind.
He doesn't get along with anyone.
That's right.
We've all had our suspicions
that his son definitely isn't
his biological child.
Just look at him.
He looks like Black Whirlwind himself,
yet somehow has produced
such a fair-skinned son?
What did his ancestors do
to deserve such luck?
He's a real son of a bitch!
I've got beef with him!
One time, I made a joke about him.
Was it about his son?
Yeah, I'd barely started the joke
when he grabbed me
and threw me into the settling tank.
The same tank where you found
the Shen family's daughter.
If someone hadn't been quick enough
to shut the valve,
I would've been sucked into
the discharge pipe into the sea!
I heard you attended Yang Tao's wedding,
and things got unpleasant.
Yes.
I shouldn't have gone.
Did you have any previous conflict
with Yang Tao's father, Yang Baoge?
No,
never even spoken to him.
You're on good terms with
Yang Tao's mother, Ding Shulan?
Yeah, we're okay.
But what does that have to do with
the case?
I need to ask you a question
that might be... uncomfortable,
but I hope you'll answer honestly.
Is Yang Tao your son?