Fold it for half
Fold it for half and press it
Click on it
Turn it up
Shortly, you will become a small boat
Tiny boat
It has become a small boat
When I graduate, let's go on a trip
To where?
Any place fits
Our family did not go on a journey together before
Go, go wherever you want
Good
Travel costs money
And you haven't started work yet
Yes, it will cost
Let's spend generously this time
amazing
My brother, we will go on a trip
Journey, where do you want to go?
look at me
What do you think of going to Beijing?
Brother, look at me
look at me
The bed
Jing
Beijing
The bed
Jing
Beijing
Let's go to Beijing
Giant panda
Well, let's go
Brother, I will go now
Let's pledge
I will return
I will return to school
Did you take the boiled eggs that I attended for you?
It is in my bag, I will go now
Xiao Chu
When will you return?
In twenty
Dad, my mother, my brother
I am going
Li Dada did not say the truth
His first meeting with Shin Xiao Chu
He was supposed to be at Hancao Club
But he deliberately hidden this fact
You have been fulfilled
Hancao Club is owned by the Jin Hai Group
Do you think Lee Dada did not kill Shin Xiao Chu
And that there is another person?
Why does he admit a crime he did not commit?
I don't know
I want to continue the investigation
Since we discovered
Another abnormal aspect of the life of Shin Xiao Chu
We must get to know the details
Lee Dada case
Zhao Hugang will end it
Regarding his confession
Do not tell the Shin Xiao Chu family yet
Lian Hibing
Investigate
I had returned
Did you eat food?
no
Didn't you say that you will take us
For delicious food abroad?
The waves shine for thousands of miles
What place in the Spring River does the moon shine?
Stop joking my father
My mom actually prepared food
We are the two, we finished eating
Moonlight on flowers and forests is like falling snow
Unreliable.
I want to tell you something.
Do you remember what I told you?
What happened in Yun Province twenty years ago?
That girl
I never knew
She has a child.
Do you want to hear?
My favorite professions are the policeman and the doctor
Because they save lives every minute
And each minute
They make this world a better place.
Trust me, you can.
You will be a great policeman.
If a day comes
And I wanted to go alone
Do not ask me why.
Why did you come here?
Do we not continue to investigate?
Wherever you go, I will go with you.
Leader Ving actually agreed.
Do you not have any questions you want to ask me?
No need to ask.
If you think it should be investigated, let's get true.
We still have some time,
Let's go somewhere first.
The dead cannot speak,
Have you thought about this issue?
There are billions of people in the world,
But the only ones
Those who can speak on their behalf,
And help them restore justice,
They are these few officers who are investigating cases.
Sometimes he is only one person,
No one else.
They are
The only bridge between them and justice,
They are their only hope.
So we must catch the right person.
Since I became a policeman and achieved in the first case,
I advise myself with this.
Was it the first issue I faced?
In 1995
In Yun Province?
She is my mother.
I saw your name in the case records.
The records say that you are
You were in an emotional relationship.
On the first summer vacation after accepting at the Police College,
It was surprising and decisive.
After that, I did not hear about it for three years.
Then I graduated,
I was appointed in the provincial office,
When I went back to visit my family,
With your sharp intelligence
Didn't you check my DNA?
I hesitated.
no.
So how did you exclude me?
Did you examine my DNA?
Frankly, I hated you at first.
I thought I was abandoning my mother.
Because you look
A bit cold person.
But then
I got to know you more.
I started to wish you were really.
This is better.
If so,,
I will not be able to be your student.
How did you get to know my mother?
When you are in the second year of high school,
My mother died.
And that year I got to know Yoon van.
The name of your mother Yoon van.
It was in the third year of high school,
It has re -two years.
She did not come to school much.
Every time I saw it,
I thought it was from outside the school and mixed with society.
She did not like to wear school uniforms.
She did not like long hair.
She did not dye her nails.
She liked to ride a bike like boys.
Sitting on the edge of the road and drinking soft drinks,
Mutal skewers eat.
Her personality was completely opposite.
But I loved her at first sight.
Perhaps conservative people
They are more easily attracted to liberated people,
Because they want to become like them.
What surprised me is
She noticed me.
She knew my name.
You also came to watch the sea.
Your name is Lian Hi Ping, right?
I always see you staring at sea,
However, your degrees are excellent.
After we became closer,
Discover
She was not pretending to be intentionally.
Her family's circumstances were very bad.
She did not have a mother,
Her father was spending most of his time playing gambling.
I think it was very angry with this world.
So
She wanted to show herself as
Bad girl.
In fact, this was a kind of self -protection.
When she was with me it was
Very real.
She was also nice.
Police and doctors love,
She means, right?
No one has been interested in me since childhood,
My nature is that I love to raise problems.
You are a good child.
It's okay, criticize me when you should,
Just stay as you were before.
Was this issue difficult to solve?
It was not difficult,
We soon identified the suspect.
It was a person who had been harassing her for years.
It was and tomorrow does not respect the law.
In short, he was doing all the bad things.
He rarely failed to get what he wanted.
But she did not give up.
When pressed, it was able to resist a knife.
Until a day came,
I jumped in the river to escape from him.
Because of my relationship with her,
I could not participate in the investigation.
But I couldn't give up.
I shared a secret
In his arrest.
Also,
I hit the criminal and injured him.
I shouldn't be so reckless.
I should have done better.
I had to find more evidence
To be sentenced to death.
After that, I did not go to the boycott office.
I chose a new job,
It has reached here, it can be considered a kind of disciplinary transport.
I did not imagine that you have this enthusiasm,
And that you may act recklessly.
I wish you saw you hitting someone.
When you have time, come to visit us at home
And meet my wife
And my younger brother also
Yes
It came to us as a guest
A university student wants to earn some money
He is the son of President Zhang
It was presented to us by the late Sayyid Chang Haw Yang
She plays the biba very well
The reaction of the guests was positive
Perhaps for about half a year
Once or twice a month for offers
Was it just offers
Not any other programs were arranged?
Of course not
Just art shows only
We are a high club here
We do not have these suspicious things
Moreover
Play the biba
It is also enhancing our traditional Chinese culture
Isn't it?
Are there surveillance cameras at the show?
No, there is no
Everyone who comes to us are important guests
We have to protect their privacy
This is contrary to the rules
Even the finest clubs are public entertainment places
How do you not ride surveillance cameras?
Surveillance cameras? Yes, we have
There are some in the external courtyard
Can you take us to see the records?
No, this ...
Sir, the officer
I heard that this issue has already been resolved
Is there a necessity?
Is there a necessity
You are the expert or me?
This is the registration of her first experience when she came
Look
She was wearing modest clothes
Traditional Chinese clothes
All are upscale arts
Bring all surveillance camera records
Please withdraw for a moment
Good
Well, please watch
What do you want to drink?
mineral water
Enjoy your time
decent
It has been kept for three months
Let's see the records of the second of June
I am afraid that we will not find anything
In such places
Bad things happen behind closed doors
Not necessarily, not everyone
They pay attention to the locations of the surveillance cameras
Here she has arrived
It came alone
Here she comes out
She went out less than twenty minutes after she entered.
She did not change her clothes,
It seems that it has not started the show yet.
Twenty -eight minutes.
What is she carried in her hand?
Is it not a money?
What did you do in the car?
This is a Long -hae car.
How do you know Shin Xiao Chu Long He?
Did I have Dada in the car?
There was a driver in the car,
Lee Dada knows how to lead himself.
Looking at their relationship as a father and son,
He will not use this car.
After Shen Xiao Chu left from here,
I went to meet Yang Tao.
According to Liang Tao, her psychological state was very bad,
She also cried.
How many secrets
We do not know it
About Shin Xiao Chu?
Sorry, sorry, sir.
You did not call in advance to tell us,
The Chairman of the Board is not in the company,
You came without interest.
Where is it now?
We can go to it.
Can you tell me what you want first?
I will convey to him the message.
Sorry, this is inappropriate,
Just give me his address.
This is also inappropriate.
What is this talk about appropriate and inappropriate,
We are from the police.
I know that, O officer,
But it is really inappropriate.
My job level is not enough.
Well, ask the manager of your department Chio
To contact the chairman of our board of directors
He asks him personally.
Interesting.
Officer, wait for a moment.
The Chairman of the Board gave personal instructions,
This is his title.
Let's fill fuel first.
Really cool.
They seized all good places,
This place will be demolished sooner or later.
Our Board of Directors.
Lean Leader,
I came.
Your son has just been arrested,
And you are here on vacation.
Prefer, tast this.
Green, organic, pollution -free,
I now eat only the vegetables that I cultivate myself.
What kind of compost do you use?
Ruth, right?
O young man,
What do you think that the word organic means?
It is just like my childhood taste.
Since the Chairman of the Board knows that we are coming,
I will speak frankly.
Maybe Dada Shin Xiao Chu was not killed.
Do you know Shin Xiao Chu?
Yes.
Good.
Were you in the car?
Yes.
It was in the car for twenty -eight minutes,
What happened during that time?
If the tone of your voice is
A little kind,
I will be more ready to answer.
please,
What happened during these twenty -eight minutes?
This question is much better.
A few months ago
Shin Xiao Chu
When she came to the club as a guest
I noticed it immediately.
From a poor family
With high -end ethics
Beautifully beautiful
It is superior to her studies
This is very rare.
The more you know it
My appreciation for her.
Later I wanted to work in our company.
On that day in the car
I gave her a contract.
I told her
If you only fall on it
It will be done.
The contract.
Unfortunately, I refused.
She said it is not her specialization.
It was preferred
Work in its field of specialization.
By the way
I later invited her to visit
This organic environmental garden.
I wanted to hear her opinion.
These tomatoes gave a five -star rating.
Did you return the contract later?
no.
Without signature and seal, the contract has no value.
So in June
I ask you about the nineteenth of June
Any night of the crime
Do you know where I had Dada
؟
I don't know.
I rarely communicate with him
We are very rarely to meet.
Where were you at that time?
Where were you on the nineteenth of June
Check it to me.
On the evening of the nineteenth of June
I went to the company's headquarters
To meet representatives of the sales office employees
This is a video of that time.
The Jin Hi One project sells well
I went to grant distinguished employees
Their rewards.
Then there was dinner
It was also attended by the Chairman of the Board
And ended at eleven o'clock.
Do you have other questions?
no.
Sorry.
I endured all the way
Can I offer your precious place?
A contribution of organic fertilizer?
There is a toilet here
No need.
Inspector Lyan.
I heard about you a while ago
You are one of the best investigators.
I am a person
Heroes always respect
And the police are the heroes of peace time.
This is ashamed of me.
Legitimate
It sells very well.
You can visit it when you find time
And if you like it, tell me.
But we will follow the official procedures
We will not let you make any mistake.
Thank you, Mr. President.
My wife has already gone to see him.
I will definitely go when I find time.
Hey, you.
to stop.
A very strong absence guide
He has a full video of witnesses.
There was a surveillance camera at the entrance to the farm
But it has been removed now
There are still signs on the door
Why was it removed?
For fear of knowing
Who came to the farm
On the nineteenth day
Did Shin Xiao Chu go there?
Not possible
She is dozens of kilometers away
In addition
We don't even know
How Shen Xiao Chu left that street
There is also the contract
We have never seen him
What?
Shin Xiao Chu did not promise me to Lee Long
I did not throw it either
And not in school either
Can it be at home?
We did not pay attention last time
What if it is
It carries it with it on the day of the crime?
Think about it
Why will you carry it with it?
Also, is it really a contract?
What are you looking for?
Did you bring Xiao Chu?
A file in a brown paper envelope
Almost this size?
I have never seen him
Xiao Chu
This was used by Xiao Chu before
She did not want to throw it
She left her to Shayo Hai to play with her
She was made by Xiao Chu when she was young
She was afraid that Xiao Hi lost her
Xiao Hi
Can I take one?
Yes, you can
Xiao Hi
Xiao Hi, Xiao Hai
Did Xiao Chu give you this flash Drive?
Xiao Hi
no
Yes
This flash Drive should be sound
Xiao Chu was using it
To save its research when it comes to the computer
It cannot be abandoned
Did Shin Xiao Zhu put it there on herself?
I don't know
television
Wicked
theft
Television
He says that there are evil on TV
They stole the flash Drive
Are the bad guys stole the flash Drive?
Yes
Xiao Hi, can you go with us to the police station?
Xiao Hi is ...
We need to take fingerprints
We will go to the police station
To the police station
Good
Xiao Hi, let your mother go up first.
Xiao Hi, what do you carry, my dear?
To the police station.
Xiao Hi.
Come on, ride the car.
Your head, pay attention to your head.
Leader Lyan.
We have developments in the Xiao Chu case.
The four -family fingerprints are on the box.
On this flash memory
There are only Xiao Chu and Hayo Hai fingerprints
There are no fingerprints for anyone else.
Xiao Hi never lies.
If Xiao Chu is not given it
He will not take it.
Open it to see.
Good.
It needs a password.
Can we penetrate it?
It will take time.
٠٥٢٦١٨٣٠.
It was opened.
How did you know that?
Xiao Chu.
Do these numbers have any special meaning?
It appears to be
Birth dates of our four family members.
Xiao Hi is the eighteenth day.
Xiao Chu is the thirty day.
Xiao Chu.
Are there any memoirs or records of conversations?
They are only professional materials.
Are there any hidden files?
All files here.
Let's divide it
Let us all search.
Good.
You can return after eating.
Thanks.
Give me a piece of your tea cake.
How there is no discovery.
I feel like I studied half a specialization in environmental protection
I did not understand anything.
Let's go to sleep first.
permission
We can exclude Le Long from the list of suspects.
We still need to investigate.
The guide not to be at the scene of the accident cannot be refuted.
If he wants to do something, will he do it himself?
The relationship between him and Shin Xiao Chu
Not simple as he claims.
Hi Ping.
With your experience
I should not remind you.
Are you
Emotionally involved in this case too much?
What do you mean?
You are constantly looking for
Evidence that Lee Dada did not kill Xiao Chu.
If Shin Xiao Chu was already killed by his hands
Don't you should get out of your own logic
And reorganizing ideas again?
Supreme management presses to close the case.
Pressure pressure, but this has nothing to do with it.
Cheo's director can give you more time.
The problem is that we need a deadline
The hospital.
Give me two additional days.
This is detailed recognition
Li Dada made about his killing Lesin Xiao Chu.
Take a look.
The details are mainly identical.
It does not have what I want to know.
What do you want to know?
I want to know
Shin Xiao Chu.
On the nineteenth of June
From four in the evening until the time of his death at night
What happened?
Unity
When you have time, check
That flash memory carefully
And see if there is any hidden content
Good
I always feel
That there is something
Otherwise, it would not have arisen
Writing this code
Writing it
Perhaps it was a reserve
To reserve
I left it for us to see it
Should the policeman?
To invest his personal feelings in solving issues?
Some old investigators
They never put their personal feelings in the investigations
Not engaging emotionally
It is a kind of psychological self -protection
But can this be controlled?
The more you deepen the investigation
The more emotionally involved
sometimes
In the most desperate and dark places
You need this driving force
To push you to continue moving forward
What is there?
Have you seen this person before?
no
Thanks
Have you seen this person before?
no
Sir, can you look?
Have you seen this person before?
I have never seen it before
Are you sure you did not see it?
sure?
Have you seen this person before?
no
I have never seen it before
my lord
Can you look if you have seen this person?
Have you seen this person before?
No, I have not seen it before
no
no? Look carefully
I have never seen it before
Thanks
Come on, to Qian Long One!
Come on, go!
Is there anyone heading to Qian Long One?
Promising to Qian Long One!
Come on, quickly!
We will start as soon as you ride!
quickly!
Come on, heading to Qian Long One!
Are others heading to Qian Long One?
Promising to Qian Long One!
Brother, do you want to ride a car?
O policeman, is this a public bus?
I...
Yes...
no
Sir, the officer, this is a service to facilitate people's lives
Don't worry, I am not from the traffic police
Do you come with this car every day?
Where do you go?
I...
I am investigating a murder case
Say the truth
That trip to Qian Long One
I do not come every day
I just come once a week
Once a week
No wonder
Yes
It is only to help the villagers and workers of the tourist area
To go to the city to fulfill their needs and shopping
Fifteen yuan for a person, and this is barely enough for the price of fuel
Did you come on the nineteenth of June?
June 10 ...
I, let me check my schedule
The nineteenth of June
nineteenth
Yes, I came
Have you seen this person?
So this is how it disappeared
I really went to search for Lee Long
We need to get a guide
That Shin Xiao Chu went to Lee Long's house
Before we can make sure
Who will go down
Make sure to take your luggage!
Come on, hurry.
Hey, beautiful.
I got out of the car here.
Can I go now?
Go.
There is still six kilometers until the Lee Long HH farm.
Very far, how did you go there?
Let's ask these.
If someone has less Shen Xiao Chu
They will definitely remember it.
Mr., did you take this person?
He says he does not remember.
Hello, we are from the police.
Have you seen this person?
We did not see it.
Look well.
Really, we have never seen it.
Mr., did you take this person?
He says he does not remember.
Hello, we are from the police.
Have you seen this person?
He says he did not say it.
O master,
Did you take this person?
I did not say it,
I never saw him.
Is there any of you who did not go out in his car today?
Yes, Xiang is like our village did not come today.
How many days have he not come out with his car?
Perhaps three or four days ago.
Do you have a phone number?
Hello, the phone you call closed.
The phone is closed.
Can you take us to search for it?
We will pay the car fare.
The police are very polite,
There is no need to pay.
Xiang c.
Stop roads, no one here.
He left early in the morning a few days ago.
I saw, as I said,
He went to the city.
Have you seen yourself that he left?
I saw the car left.
When he left the sky was still dark.
Also, his car is easy to distinguish,
Transformers drew on the front of the car.
What about his parents?
His parents died a long time ago,
He only has a girlfriend working in the city.
Where do you work in the city?
Xiang Ze said she is working
In a luxurious restaurant that sells seafood.
I heard that foreign crabs are sold for more than a thousand yuan.
I joked him saying
This is not a cancer,
It is like paying travel costs, right?
Why doesn't he go to work in the city with her?
What does he do in the town?
Work in the city is tired,
Our tourist area has become famous,
And earns a lot of driving.
Xiang was planning
He said that he will work for other two years,
Then he will return and marry his girlfriend.
It will open a rural restaurant,
It also sells seafood.
Do we not have a lot of seafood here?
Why do we eat foreigners?
It is supposed to have returned now,
It usually goes for only two or three days.
If Xiang Zz is the one who connects Shen Xiao Chu,
I am afraid that they have already found it.
How did they know about Xiang Z?
Have you forgotten,
There were surveillance cameras at the farm entrance.
And Xiang car is easy to distinguish.
Did Xiang fly because of their threats?
We must find it.
You are back.
O leader,
I have some new discoveries.
Flash Shen Xiao Chu.
I reviewed it several times,
Most of the academic research papers,
The titles and contents are clearly classified.
But these two files are different,
So I copied them separately.
These two reports speak mainly about
Soil pollution in a chemical factory,
The titles are unclear,
The content has been deleted parts of it.
Someone deliberately deleted the name of the chemical factory
And the name of the Environmental Evaluation Foundation
From files.
But I discovered.
Look, isn't this familiar?
It is local.
Yes.
This chemical factory
It has not been a chemical factory for a long time,
And it is now a residential complex,
It's now.
Jin Hi number one.
Yes, I also discovered that
The company that made the environmental evaluation of Jane Hi number one
It is Le Qing Environmental Technology.
Le Qing.
The conclusion of these two reports is that
Soil pollution at the chemical factory site
After treatment and reform
It became harmless.
But I feel something incorrect.
I don't understand,
What does this mean?
I also do not understand.
I just feel very suspicious.