STRANGER
We are rolling.
-Microphone check, one, two, three.
-Let's go.
The house you see behind me
is where Mr. Park was murdered
in January this year,
and another brutal crime
just took place here.
It sounds like another person got killed.
-Goodness.
-It was revealed
to the public after a student posted
a photo of the victim on social media.
A group of teenagers has been hanging out
at Mr. Park's empty house since his death.
They posted a photo of the victim
after discovering the body
instead of contacting the police,
-which has shocked many of us.
-The kids are coming out!
-They are coming out!
-There they are.
-Please say a few words.
-Please tell us what happened.
-Block the cameras!
-Say a few words.
-Wait.
-No photos!
No, you can't. Block them!
-Please say a few words.
-What exactly happened?
-Please look at the camera here!
-Please tell us what happened.
-What happened?
-How did you get into the house?
-Officers.
-Let us ask a question.
-Please cooperate!
-What happened?
Please cooperate.
What brings you here?
Is this related to the previous case?
Is it a copycat killing?
Another victim has been killed
despite your promise.
-Do you have anything to say?
-Please say something.
-Is it a serial murder?
-Is it true, Prosecutor?
-Prosecutor Hwang!
-Prosecutor, how do you feel?
-Please say a few words.
FORENSIC SCIENCE OFFICER
Hey.
Try to find her belongings.
Whatever you can find.
Yes, sir.
Where on earth
did the owner of this house go?
She's left like that, yet none of
her clothes are around here.
Pardon?
Not even a purse.
There is nothing here whatsoever.
I know where the owner is.
It wouldn't have been easy to tie her
like that even if she was passed out.
There is no blood on the wall.
-Goodness!
-She is alive!
-She is alive.
-What? What did you say?
She's alive!
-She is alive?
-Hey!
Hey, come on!
-Hurry up and untie her.
-She was dead!
-Scissors!
-Untie her!
Just cut it with scissors.
Pass me scissors!
-Hurry and untie her!
-Untie her!
-Move aside.
-Get her up.
One, two, three. Goodness.
Be careful!
-Where to?
-To outside!
Hey, she is alive!
-She is alive?
-Move out of the way. She is alive!
Hey, wake up.
-Did you see who did this to you?
-Goodness!
She opened her eyes to live,
not to catch the culprit for us.
Paramedics.
Call the paramedics immediately.
Why didn't he finish her?
I mean, after all this trouble.
Also, why here?
What is he getting out of this?
Okay. One, two.
Open the door, please. Door!
-I think she is alive.
-Is she alive?
-Please tell us.
-Is she really alive?
-Is she alive?
-Please say a few words!
The girl is alive.
She will be taken to Namsan Hospital.
There are so many reporters here.
The killer will find out soon.
Please send us backup
right away. Yes, sir.
Try to be more careful, will you?
Detective Kim.
-Yes?
-It is from Chief.
Goodness, we know nothing yet.
Why is he calling? I know nothing.
Name, Min-ah Kwon.
Tell him that she should be around 25.
Who? The victim?
Do you know her?
I don't know her,
but I know where she lives.
-Sorry?
-He is waiting.
You just figure it out.
Prosecutor Hwang, wait.
How can you know where she lives
when you don't know her personally?
She works for an establishment
that got busted
during our prostitution crackdown.
So, is she a working girl?
She got caught again
during another crackdown last night.
She had already fled
when I figured out where she lives.
Now, that was two nights ago.
How did a working girl end up
at this house?
I would also like to know the answer.
And what it means.
She must have seen the culprit.
She must live.
-Prosecutor.
-Prosecutor!
-Prosecutor, please say a few words.
Have you identified a prime suspect yet?
What is your thought on this incident?
-Prosecutor, will there be another...
-Please tell us.
Please say a few words.
-Tell us your thoughts on this case!
-Please comment.
Prosecutor, are you sure
you can catch the killer?
-I will insert it now.
-Move her immediately.
-Bring six more packs. Fluids too.
-Yes, Doctor.
-Has she had a shock yet?
-Yes, she has.
-It is in.
-Move her now.
-She'll live, right?
-It is hemorrhagic shock
with hypoxia and low blood pressure.
She will survive, right?
The puncture in the lung caused
blood loss and exposure to oxygen.
It could have been very dangerous.
She saw a serial killer.
She is the only witness.
Please make sure she lives.
I should do my best regardless
of whether she is a witness or not.
Whether she is a witness or not.
You must live. Don't let him beat you.
You were terrified. It was horrible.
Do not let it become your last memory
of this world.
You have to live!
Ms. Han!
-Sir.
-Hey.
What happened?
She is in the operating room now.
The doctor couldn't guarantee anything.
We got her identity.
The prosecutor knows her address.
He's heading there with Sergeant Kim.
-Do you mean Prosecutor Hwang?
-Yes.
How does he know her address?
The prosecution has been after her
due to a prostitution crackdown.
Mr. Park, hold down the fort
while I am gone, okay?
-You must keep an eye on her.
-Well...
Hey, Ms. Han. Yeo-jin.
IT IS SO FUCKING SCARY.
Honey.
Did something happen?
Why do you ask?
No, nothing happened.
It is nothing.
Good grief.
Goodness.
I would have opened the door for you.
Why did you come in through there?
You are right.
Is there any sign of a struggle?
Did the culprit
go through her stuff?
Don't touch anything!
It is possible she got abducted here.
Hey, it is me.
Send the forensic unit here.
Perfume.
A travel mug.
A makeup brush.
Right, when they are done there.
What?
Mr. Hwang, what is the address here again?
You said she works at a bar.
Goodness, something happened to the girl?
I don't know.
Something terrible must've happened.
Hello, you all are working so hard.
Hey, you made it.
What is going on with that girl?
She is in surgery at the moment.
Mr. Park is there.
Where is the forensic unit?
They can't come here because the scene
in Huam-dong is a total mess.
There are too many of these.
Prosecutor Hwang had no idea
she was abducted from here
and walked all over.
Where is he?
-He just left.
-What? Hey.
Did you get his fingerprint?
Our fingerprints must be all over
the place as we got in through the window.
Why did you get in through the window?
What do you think? Should we have
knocked down the door instead?
You said this is where she got abducted.
Was the door locked?
The abductor kindly locked
the door as he was leaving?
It doesn't have an electronic lock.
It couldn't have gotten locked on its own.
Well. If he used the door,
people would have seen him.
Anyway,
it is a mess here. Don't you think it is
because she felt threatened?
Goodness.
What did I do all this for?
There was no facial moisturizer.
I didn't see anything she would need daily
on her dressing table.
I thought maybe it wasn't an accident
and that she could have packed her stuff
and left home to lay low.
But it happened right here.
Only a few steps from her place.
I was late once again.
It is not your fault.
Who knew she would get abducted like this?
This was planned.
Sorry?
He left the laptop.
The blood was intentionally left there,
and he buried the dog underneath it.
Everything must have been planned
from the get-go.
Do you think it is a message for me?
I also felt
that someone might be leaving tracks
on purpose,
but why would it be a message for you?
I could have caught the culprit
like Mr. Park,
but I was late once again.
Why is this happening?
Who knew that you would be coming here?
If someone keeps harming people
around you,
that person must be holding grudges
against you or want to frame you.
Mr. Hwang, by any chance,
did you get involved with that girl?
The victim. It is like what you told me
earlier, right?
You said Moo-sung was like a sponsor
and that he used money and women.
He used her for that purpose, didn't he?
Is that how he bribed you?
If the culprit
is a man who loves the victim,
he could be holding grudges against you
and obviously against Moo-sung.
Why aren't you answering me?
Is there really something?
No, there is nothing.
Have a look.
I saw it at her place.
Her year of birth is listed as 1993
on her wireless carrier's records.
Some men might like stuff like this,
so it is possible
she was actually born in 1993.
What if this isn't a costume?
But it is her actual high school uniform.
Then, she must have been
a walking time bomb.
To some men, that is.
But it doesn't look like that.
He should've killed her quietly
if he wanted to shut her up.
This looks like he is dying
to advertise it.
I mean, why did he tie her there
of all places?
Let's just catch him.
Now, I really want to see
what this prick looks like.
I will look into this.
Oh god.
Why do you think you are being targeted?
Who would it be?
Why?
Yes, sir. We figured out
where she got abducted.
The serious teenage misbehavior
is shocking enough in and of itself,
but the fact that people without
any authorization were able to sneak
into the scene of an unsolved case,
which has been a mystery for months,
is making us doubt
the competency of the police.
Also, there has been no progress made
even though there is another victim now.
We would like to ask the police once again
if they are actually
determined to catch the culprit.
When will they stop fussing around
only after something happens?
Moreover, how many more lives will it take
for Korea to become safe?
When will Korea be able to dissociate
itself from its bad reputation of being
the country where man-made disasters
kill its civilians on a daily basis?
Thank you for watching Breaking News.
I hope all of you have a great day.
It's your doing, right?
Didn't you stage it as a murder
because you couldn't figure out
what to do after abducting her?
No, it wasn't me.
You mean it wasn't you?
Then, who is the mastermind?
We have each one of you in every room now.
You need to come clean first
if you want a lighter punishment.
I already told you
that we didn't kill her.
Otherwise, we wouldn't have
posted the photo.
You obviously did that
to use it as an excuse like this.
You think you are so smart, don't you?
Sir, I won't be punished
because I am under 14.
How dare you.
Hey, get your facts straight.
That is true in the Criminal Code,
but not the Family Law.
You are still a kid. What will you
be later if you are already like this?
Sir,
-I am not a kid.
-You little...
Hey, be quiet.
-Goodness.
-Stay still!
What are you doing? It hurts.
-Hello.
-Who are you?
POLICE, YEO-JIN HAN
Are you Min-ah's mother?
She is not home at the moment.
What is this about?
Your daughter is at a hospital now.
Pardon me?
Did you say hospital?
Well, she is supposed to be in Japan now.
What happened?
-Japan?
-Yes.
Isn't this your daughter?
No, this girl is not my daughter.
I got so scared for a moment.
PROSECUTOR YOUNG
-What?
-Where are you now?
There is an emergency meeting
at Mr. Kang's office.
Right now?
All right.
You all know the situation.
We have a lot to do.
Let's get started right away.
Mr. Seo isn't here yet.
He'll stop by
Yongsan Police Station first.
The new Huam-dong case.
Will Mr. Seo take it on?
By what standard?
What standard?
What makes you think
that you can question my standard?
Listen up.
I don't care even if you are friends
with some reporters.
Zip up your lips about this case.
The culprit is obviously determined
to make a complete fool of us.
Don't give people a reason to gossip more.
Do you all understand?
-Yes, sir.
Si-mok.
Jin-seob's family has decided
to press charges
against the government,
the jail staff and us.
It is for criminal compensation
and compensation for damages.
We probably won't have to stand trial,
but know that it is your fault
and behave yourself.
Will you go on TV again?
No, sir.
You sure know how to answer.
This is a composite sketch of the suspect.
Name, Hyung-jun Yoo.
He is a member of the Yeongnam gang.
He used to be based in Mokpo.
He got himself in trouble again
right after completing his jail term.
Those who found Min-ah Kwon
They didn't do it?
Hello, Mr. Seo.
We didn't find any bloodstain on them.
If it was their doing,
things would have been so easy.
So, is it turning into a serial case then?
Sixty thousand volts.
What is this 60,000V for?
A permit is needed for that much voltage.
We are looking into that as well, but...
Please excuse me for a moment.
Yes.
What? She's not?
Then, who is Min-ah?
Darn it, the statement
has already been released.
Okay, I have to go. Hey, wait.
Message everyone in our group chat.
-Were you wrong on the girl's identity?
-Well.
That was the social security number
on her phone contract and her lease,
but it wasn't hers.
That is precisely why we were keeping
an eye on this girl.
She must have a connection to those
who supply minors with fake IDs.
But it is...
Things have gotten so complicated now.
I don't know how to interpret all this.
Who is at the hospital now?
Right. We sent an officer there.
He is there by himself,
but he will be sure
to keep a watchful eye on her.
We are always short-staffed, aren't we?
Damn it.
PROSECUTOR KANG
Aren't you in charge of manslaughter cases
with female victims?
I guess he wanted someone more senior
as it has turned into a bigger case now.
Who arrived on the scene first
and who knows the most about the case
won't really matter.
Are you trying to make me feel better
or being sarcastic?
You can rub salt into a wound
only when there is a wound.
You never get affected
by things like this.
I guess you will really behave yourself.
MEETING ROOM
Come in.
They have found out
that Min-ah was an alias.
Why?
-Pardon?
-Why did it have to be yesterday?
The night you went after her
all of a sudden.
Why did we end up with another victim
on that very night?
Why are you asking me, sir?
Do you think
I have something to do with it?
Why are you jumping to conclusions?
Do you feel guilty about something?
You even went to that bar.
Did you notice anything out of ordinary?
Did anyone follow you?
Well.
Si-mok.
He is the one who gave police
the information on the culprit.
He was tailing me,
and he must've followed her to her house.
Sir, don't you think it is strange?
Moo-sung Park died under Si-mok's watch,
and it happened again.
This can't be a coincidence.
You said he tailed you.
How did he figure out where she lives
when you couldn't?
You only went to the bar.
To me, what is more peculiar
than the timing
is why the culprit would target Min-ah.
When Mr. Park was killed,
I thought it must be one
of the many people
who were involved.
But with this Min-ah case,
it is almost
as if an invisible helping hand
gets involved
whenever you could get in trouble.
Have you forgotten her nickname?
I am asking if you have forgotten
what Mr. Park used to call her.
Why do you think
the culprit tied her there?
Why?
Why didn't he finish her?
He probably didn't expect her
to be found so soon.
I bet he had no idea that some teens
would be hanging out at a murder scene.
If it weren't for them,
she would have died already.
Yes, that place was their hangout.
They must have hung out there many times.
The culprit who thoroughly used the scene,
must have known about them.
It could have been someone else.
Or he might have wanted
to mete out a bigger punishment
so that she can't function
even if she wakes up.
That could be what he wanted.
Why did it have to be yesterday?
The night you went after her
all of a sudden.
Why did we end up with another victim
on that very night?
Was it a coincidence?
It happened on the day
Dong-jae chased her.
You even went to that bar.
Did you notice anything out of ordinary?
Did anyone follow you?
Was he following me?
Or did I lead him?
What will you do?
Her address and number.
Garwol-dong...
-That was probably when the culprit...
-behind Suwol Elementary School.
A building called Daejin Villa.
He probably left before I did.
No.
-Taxi!
-Hey!
Min-ah Kwon
It took me 46 minutes.
If he figured out her address
by tailing me,
he must have arrived there roughly
40 minutes after she did.
Would she have taken 40 minutes
when she was trying to run away?
She clearly saw Dong-jae chasing her.
Would she have wasted 40 minutes
at home?
It wasn't even 20m away.
He must have been waiting for her there.
That wouldn't be possible
if he was 40 minutes behind her.
Then, it wasn't me.
He must have used another route.
If he was someone she knows
and they were supposed to meet up,
he wouldn't have had to use a stun gun.
I mean, anyone could have seen them
in that alley.
He would've gotten her
into his car first to get away.
Yes, he already knew.
He must have been waiting there,
knowing where she lives
and that she would be coming.
But...
But he also knew
that we managed to track her down.
He must have been waiting
for her to be spotted by us.
Then, he put all of us on stage
and threw us into the scene
right before the murder.
How did he know about us
tracking her down?
Two days ago?
Well, let's see.
If it was in the evening...
This is it.
Someone on the inside.
The fact that he knew
people from our office were after her
means he is somehow connected.
I don't think he saw us
while hovering around her day and night.
He must either be someone who works here
or someone who is connected in some way.
Why is it so empty?
It is usually...
That's right. At this time two days ago,
Mr. Lee was giving his speech
in the assembly hall.
Why did he have to do that
at the end of the day?
Dong-jae, the investigator in his office,
Mr. Lee, who must have received
a report about it, and me.
In this building, those four people
knew about...
No, five.
Hey, are you not going to
answer the phone?
These people need a lesson.
This is Yongsan Police Station.
Hello? Please go ahead.
Well,
it is okay.
Why are you calling?
Where are you calling from?
Sergeant Kim, we have a big problem.
What now? Did another person get killed?
You need to see what we found
on the weapon.
FINGERPRINT ANALYSIS
RESULT OF ANALYSIS
Hey, are you sure this is right?
You got the fingerprint.
I am certain of it.
Hello?
Hello.
Listen.
It is really okay.
Just tell me why you are calling.
I will keep it confidential.
Well... I think
I saw the culprit.
What is it?
You saw the culprit?
Please go on.
What should we do, Chang-jun?
I just got a call from the chairman.
He called you directly?
What is the problem though?
About the Huam-dong case.
He asked me what is going on with it,
and I ended up telling him.
I couldn't say we haven't even identified
any suspect yet.
So, what did you tell him?
I actually just got a report about it.
I was going to tell you first, but...
Stop beating around the bush.
What?
What did you just say?
All of this?
-Take them to the records room.
-I can go.
Forget it.
What was that about?
Hello, sir.
I am going to the post office.
It is so tense here
every single day. Goodness.
Are you the one with the knife?
Are you the one who stabbed the girl?
No, I didn't.
Your fingerprints
were found all over the weapon.
How will you explain it?
I touched it.
Tell me.
Have you gotten into an alliance
with someone to stop my promotion?
I am sorry,
but I have never seen anyone
who wants to be my ally.
I am not here to joke around with you!
Your fingerprint is all over the weapon
and everything in her house.
There is more. There is now a witness
who is saying you are the culprit.
Thanks to you, not a day here
goes by without problems!
Every piece of evidence
is perfectly pointing to me.
Then, why don't you think
that I am the culprit?
-You piece of...
-I used to be called a psycho,
and even all the evidence is perfect.
Why aren't you suspicious of me at all?
Is it because you know who the culprit is?
-How dare you, son of a...
-Min-ah.
Did you do it, sir?
No matter
how cornered one feels,
one must know what one shouldn't do.
Last October,
Mr. Park sent an underage girl to you.
Then, he threatened you saying he would
disclose it all as you didn't help him,
but he ended up
getting silenced for good.
Also today,
that underage girl was found.
The girl, whom you have been
so desperately looking for,
was found nearly dead.
Can all of this be a coincidence?
Please tell me the truth.
Nothing happened.
Not because I am fastidious to the point
that people question my orientation.
Mr. Park was already going downhill then.
I only opened the door for him
so he wouldn't cause a scene,
but it wasn't him. It was a woman.
No one would have been able to guess
that she could be a minor.
Yes, I admit that I was tempted.
But I told her to leave. Why?
Because I knew that it was a trap.
I knew that it would be
a sure way to a muddy road.
I know you think
no one is smarter than you.
But know this, Si-mok. I am above you.
Min-ah must have blackmailed you
since her source of income, Mr. Park died,
saying that the whole world
would believe her over you no matter
how desperately you try
to plead your innocence.
Mr. Park called her Bell.
What does that mean?
It is because she always showed up.
She is like a doorbell
that is answered right away.
Do you think he rang that bell
only for me?
We are prosecutors.
Some of us accept money
or such forms of entertainment as a bribe.
Some former high-ups expect
special treatment on their cases.
It happens when people like us study
only to gain power and honor.
Some of us are immature
and act up, but we are still prosecutors.
We are here to protect the law
and to fight for justice.
I have a faith.
I believe that there are two types
of people in this building.
Guardians and criminals.
Barrister's robes and prison uniforms.
No matter what the situation may be,
I believe we are different
from those we need to punish.
I firmly trust that we would never
harm others no matter how lax we become.
But what did you just accuse me of?
You didn't answer my question.
I did not kill anyone.
That was discourteous of me. I apologize.
Prosecutor. Prosecutor Hwang.
Prosecutor Hwang, are you there?
It is your turn now.
What is going on?
That is what I want to ask you.
What on earth...
Sir.
I would like to ask him a few questions.
It is for the investigation.
Prosecutor Hwang,
where were you between 11 p.m. and 1 a.m.
last night?
Your colleagues must have been
here too, right?
No, everyone had left for the day.
Does that mean you were alone here?
Oh dear.
We have never dealt
with something like this before.
I touched the knife used
for the attempted murder of Min-ah
with my bare hands ten days ago.
How did that happen?
I tried reenacting the crime at the scene
to see if Jin-seob's claim could be true.
I used a knife I found in the kitchen
that looked similar to the murder weapon
although it was a little smaller.
Can you prove it in any way?
Except for your words...
Was the culprit's fingerprint
not found on the weapon at all?
No. We only found yours.
The way you asked that question
makes it sound like you want to tell me
the culprit's fingerprints
shouldn't be the same as yours.
Let me tell you.
Coming here wasn't easy for us.
The fingerprint isn't the only problem.
Someone called us claiming
that you are the culprit.
You are talking
about the illegal taxi driver, right?
I got Min-ah's address from him.
Dong-jae.
I didn't think it was you.
But the witness said
that you were very violent toward him.
He tried not to give you her address
because of his loyalty to those girls,
but he thought he could die
if he continued to refuse your request.
I didn't believe him, of course.
Everyone must have their reasons.
Well, thinking from the taxi driver's
perspective,
I could look like the culprit
because the incident took place
on the same day.
But what happened after that
is not any different from what I told you
when I took you to the victim's place.
I got her address,
-but she had already left.
-You took him there?
Are you saying we helped the police
confirm the victim's identity?
His chief didn't mention
anything to me though.
I guess they wanted to take
all the credit. Well, it happens.
That being said,
I did some thinking too.
I thought about why you took us there
when you had something
to feel guilty about.
Then, this thought popped into my head.
If your claim that you didn't see her
when you got to her place isn't true,
and if you actually followed that girl
into her place last night,
you must have thought hard
about what to do with your traces
which you left all over her place.
That must be why you went in there again
accompanied by us, the police.
Your fingerprint has been found.
And we have a witness.
You were most likely the last person
who saw the victim.
What would you do
if you meet a suspect like that?
I think I have already explained
everything to you.
Someone also strongly claimed
his innocence a while ago.
But what did you do to him?
I arrested and charged him.
What are you all doing here?
Bring firmer evidence
if you want to take one of my people.
For goodness' sake.
What can be firmer evidence
than fingerprints?
Good grief. How dare he...
They are being ridiculous.
They would have locked him up already
if they were in my shoes.
That is right. We would have put him
behind bars immediately.
What I meant was...
That is why
it has to be indisputable.
Of course.
Here.
This one. It is
Yangkang High School's uniform.
They actually changed the design
last year. We no longer make this design.
Why do you need this?
Did you say Yangkang High School?
Okay. Thank you.
Hey, come down already.
YANGKANG HIGH SCHOOL
Goodness, don't follow me.
Hey, stop. Wait up.
Hey.
You should have been like that too.
I am sorry to interrupt your class.
This student.
You were her homeroom teacher, right?
My goodness, it is Ga-young.
Where did you find her?
Where is she now?
Did she run away from home?
We filed a police report too.
Isn't that why you are here?
She was found unconscious
in Huam-dong early this morning.
Pardon me?
Well. When did she run away from home?
How old was she at the time?
Huam-dong...
I saw it in the news. The incident
happened at Kyung-wan's place.
Is that it?
Kyung-wan? Who is Kyung-wan...
This is my grandson.
I heard you are serving
in the military now.
Excuse me for a moment.
Mr. Park sent about five million won
to Min-ah's account every month
until the end of last year.
Min-ah. I mean, Ga-young Kim.
What year was she born?
She was in 12th grade last year, so...
The 12th graders last year were...
She was born in 1998.
I see.
Thank you.
No problem.
I had no idea.
She said she was born in 1993
and even showed me her ID.
How would I know that she was a minor?
When was the last time you saw her?
Three days ago. At work.
Why didn't she work the last two days?
That prosecutor caused a total ruckus.
Of course she couldn't come.
Is that why you gave him her address?
To whom else have you given her address?
I don't know where Min-ah lives.
How can I give anyone information
that I don't have?
Even if I had known her address,
I wouldn't have given it to anyone.
My numbers would drop if my girls
meet up with customers elsewhere.
You must know this man.
I have never seen him before.
Take a good look!
-You know him, don't you?
-I told you. I have never seen him.
I want names of all the places
she has worked.
-She only started a few days ago...
-Write them down!
We were able to prevent organ damage,
but cerebral hemorrhage is the problem.
She could have hit her head hard somewhere
or it might be caused by the assault.
There is a pool of blood inside.
We will need to open up her cranium
in order to remove it now.
Her body won't be able to handle it.
It will be better to remove it
using tubing later on, but...
But what?
In the worst-case scenario,
her brain may not function afterward.
Well, did you notice additional signs
of assault anywhere else?
No, I didn't see anything else.
Thank you, Doctor.
Goodness, you startled me.
-My apologies.
-It is okay.
Why did it come off?
I would've gotten in big trouble for it.
My daughter, Ga-young. My goodness.
Goodness.
Ga-young.
What should we do?
-It looks like he is in shock.
-Hush.
I have a faith.
I believe that there are two types
of people in this building.
Guardians and criminals.
Barrister's robes and prison uniforms.
No matter what the situation may be,
I believe we are different
from those whom we need to punish.
I firmly trust
that we would never harm others
no matter how lax we become.
Nothing happened.
I admit that I was tempted.
But I told her to leave. Why?
Because I knew that it was a trap.
What should we do?
HANSUNG
HANSUNG SEORAK RESORT
FIND JOY IN NATURE
Yes, hello.
This is Prosecutor Si-mok Hwang
from Western Seoul Prosecutors' Office.
How long do you generally keep
the footage from your security cameras?
Yes, right. But don't you
back up the files
or keep copies for internal use?
Right.
Yes.
Yes, it was October 27 of last year.
At 2 p.m. on the tenth floor.
I just need the footage
from the west hallway.
Yes, last year.
Please try to find it. I will send
an official request right away.
Thank you.
-You are home.
-Yes.
Dad.
I am home.
-It is late.
-I know.
At this rate, my daughter will be
awarded for being a patient, devoted wife.
If that is the case, Mom should have been
awarded a long time ago.
Just coddle your husband.
Don't lash out at me.
I am hungry.
-Go wash your hands.
-All right.
You and your father talked
behind my back, didn't you? Was it fun?
We have other things to talk about.
-That man sure is something.
-Pardon me?
Didn't your friend tell you?
The actor basically came
on stage on himself.
Are you referring to Si-mok?
When I first heard about it from Woo-gyun,
I was just speechless.
I thought, "There will be
a lot of noise for a while."
But...
Everything just seems
to be falling into place perfectly.
The man who announced on TV that he'd be
sure to catch the killer was the culprit.
All other news or scandals will be buried
because people will be so shocked.
If Si-mok is confirmed as the culprit,
everyone will indeed be in utter shock.
He was at the scene when Mr. Park died,
and this time too...
Exactly.
Every time a victim is found, he is there.
People will think that he pushed ahead
with arresting Jin-seob
in order to conceal what he did.
-He hit the bull's-eye.
-But...
The way the girl's body was placed
is quite unusual.
That is true.
If the person who killed Mr. Park
also harmed the girl,
it is not a simple serial case.
He must have a goal.
I don't think murder itself is his goal.
If we make Si-mok or whoever
look like the culprit,
what will we do if it continues...
I don't care even if
there are other victims.
We just have to cut ourselves off
from Mr. Park.
All is good with no connection to him.
Nothing else will happen at that house.
Let's say something happens there.
What is the term "copycat crime" for?
We can say that somebody killed
whom they wanted to kill
and left the body in that house
to avoid getting caught.
If you let such petty worries stop you,
you can never move forward.
Right.
You are not even
at the Supreme Prosecutors' Office.
You are just in the criminal division.
You should be quick to act at least.
When did I tell you to take care of it?
Have you been worrying
about that all this time?
I am sorry.
It is only a matter of time
before people find out
how Mr. Park actually died.
-Get on it.
-Yes, Father.
Goodness, I heated up
everything perfectly.
All right. Let's eat.
Dad.
He acts very quickly
once he sets his mind to do something.
He threatened me by saying
he would kill me and strangled me,
so I had no choice but to give it to him.
I jotted down his license plate number.
I never imagined this would happen.
That psycho is the culprit.
So, did you tell Min-ah about it?
Did you warn her, "A dangerous man
is headed to your place. Run away"?
Then, I would have had to tell her
about giving him her address,
and none of those girls would ride my car.
Car? What car?
Hello? Are you there? Hello?
I can't get over how much
of a douchebag he is.
If only he had called her,
none of this would've happened.
How can he risk a girl's life
to make sure he can continue
earning a living?
We got the plate number.
We must know who it is.
Who is it?
The psycho he was talking about.
Prosecutor Hwang.
Pardon?
Are we really supposed to just sit
around and do nothing about it?
We shouldn't be protecting him
because he is in the prosecution.
Chief told us to wait for now.
Mr. Hwang already told us
that he tried to chase her
from the bar to her place.
He was lying.
He told us that he only figured out
her address,
but it can't be true.
He must have met that girl that night.
I am convinced that is why
he took us there.
He must have wanted
our traces to get mixed
with the traces he left all over there.
How...
Ga-young Kim
Age: 20
Have a look.
I saw it at her place.
Her year of birth is listed as 1993
on her wireless carrier's records.
It was me.
I met up
with Moo-sung Park
the night before he died.
I did it alone.
I'm telling you,
Prosecutor Hwang and that girl
must know each other personally.
I am sure of it.
When did he have time to print
these photos?
He didn't take these when he went in there
with Sergeant Kim. He must have had them
since before the incident took place.
Did he sneak into her place
and meet Ga-young there?
What if this isn't a costume,
but her actual high school uniform?
Then, she must have been
a walking time bomb.
To some men, that is.
Wait, was he talking about himself?
STRANGER
Prosecutor Seo will be there soon
to investigate Kyung-wan.
He and Ga-young went
to the same high school.
I'm asking if you've forgotten
what Mr. Park used to call her.
Bell.
Do you think he rang that bell
only for me?
I heard that song when I called that girl.
The man who was in the room
at the corner in the resort...
-Dong-jae Seo.
-It's his ringtone.
It must've been your perfume that
I smelled from Prosecutor Dong-jae Seo.
Why did he meet up with you again?
-Let go.
-You let go first.
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi