ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
-So you think he's alive?
-He'd better be.
Shouldn't you find out who that was,
and what else they told him first?
Senior Inspector Han Yeo-jin
will be in charge.
And the second team will investigate
Segok Police Station with me.
What? A cop?
Well, this and this…
These two cases are connected… Ma'am?
Our Captain even told me
to leave Sergeant Song alone.
Song Gi-hyeon committed suicide.
"Let's sacrifice one member
and save the whole team."
Is that what you thought?
Our children are waiting
for their father to come back.
Any small detail is important to us.
You got what?
Someone must've leaked that info
with certain intentions.
-Nothing's been confirmed.
-No, it isn't.
If Seo Dong-jae is really found dead…
And let's say the police did it.
What if we're told to hand over
the investigative authority despite that?
It'll be an all-out war.
Yes. The feud between
the prosecution and the police
will turn into a war
between us and the government.
All the prosecutors who've been
holding back due to social discourse
will rise up to protest against it.
But the thing is,
the government won't do that.
Even this administration won't be able to
mess with our investigative authority.
I'm not saying I think
Prosecutor Seo will be found dead.
Chief Woo refused
to shoot straight with me.
I asked him if he had been trying to dig
up dirt on Choi Bit, but he didn't answer.
You asked him that?
Isn't that why you asked me about it?
You asked me if I thought
Chief Woo would try to dig up dirt on her
because you wanted me
to ask him out for you.
-Was it that obvious?
-Do you think I'm an idiot?
I'm sorry, sir.
You're apologizing?
-So you thought I was an idiot?
-No, sir.
Hey, that sounded very insincere.
I also thought it'd be better for me
to ask him personally
if I wanted to find out
what's really going on.
But he seemed to be on edge about it.
-You mean, Chief Woo?
-Is it because he's worried?
His junior went missing without
a trace except for a single bloodstain
while working on something
that was assigned by him.
Do you think
Chief Woo is reacting like that
purely because he's worried?
-What do you think?
-What do I think?
I mean, look at you.
You and him were close,
but you're managing to keep your cool
despite how worried you are.
We aren't that close.
What?
Then do you think
that Chief Woo is just worried?
You see…
How are you meant to act
when you're worried?
-What?
-I need to know what the signs
and symptoms are to figure out
whether or not someone is worried.
How do people behave when they're worried?
What kind of question is that?
They just worry.
We're back!
Here's some food for everyone.
Thank you.
SENIOR INSPECTOR HAN YEO-JIN
Yes, Senior Inspector Han.
We received a message.
A message from the culprit.
2 HOURS AGO
WHO WOULD'VE THOUGHT
THEY'D KIDNAP A PROSECUTOR?
THE PROSECUTOR IS HANDSOME
I HOPE HE'S ALL RIGHT
I wish they'd post something useful.
I WASHED THE DISHES
TOO LATE
This is…
The color of the blood…
Maybe it's because this photo is too dark.
I don't think this is too old.
The blood doesn't look that dark.
Is that the floor?
Did they put it on a
table to take the photo?
-Couldn't they have taken a better photo?
-It's too dark.
Was it taken at night?
It doesn't look like natural light.
And it just looks like
a regular hardwood floor.
We can't tell with this photo.
But the tie is soaked in blood.
Dried blood won't do that.
-This has to be fresh blood.
-Looks like it.
-So he's alive?
-That's what I'm thinking.
The color of the blood
hasn't changed that much.
But what if the photo was taken
by the culprit much earlier
and he sent it to us now?
If that's the case,
why send us these today, of all days?
Maybe he didn't know where to send them
until we posted the video
with Sun-chang's phone number?
If these were taken
on the day that he was kidnapped,
there's no telling if he's dead or alive.
Did you check
the sender's name and location?
The culprit probably didn't use
their own number,
-but I'm looking into it.
-Okay.
Detective Jang, get the locations
of the Segok officers.
-Sure.
-When we get the GPS info,
we'll compare it with those officers'
whereabouts and see if there's an overlap.
Okay. But since they're cops,
they'll know they can be tracked.
If the culprit is one of them,
I'm sure they placed their phone
somewhere else when sending this photo.
Yes. It would've been too obvious
if their phone was turned off.
-We should still look into it.
-Yes.
Do you think the victim is with
the culprit, whether he's alive or not?
Let's say the culprit already buried
or tossed Prosecutor Seo somewhere.
Then why did they cut out
a piece of his tie and send it to us?
-Maybe they took the tie before that.
-That's right.
Maybe this was his plan from the get-go.
Maybe it's for shock value.
They purposely sent us
a part of the blood-soaked tie.
I doubt they're normal.
They're practically out of their mind.
Most culprits don't send us
photos like this to show off.
They must really have it in for the victim
to call it "dishwashing."
Is one of the people Prosecutor Seo
put behind bars trying to get back at him?
Why does he keep coming here?
Were there many comments
criticizing the culprit?
Yes. There are no tips
but everyone's cursing the culprit out.
It means that the culprit
watched the video,
judging by how these were sent to you
as soon as the video was posted.
Given what they did,
they must be watching everything
to see who's talking about them.
They must've read the comments too.
This is their way
of getting their revenge.
They're cleaning out the "filth."
Whether it was because of a grudge
or something that Prosecutor Seo did
that caused the culprit harm.
But everyone's posting
berating comments about them.
Do people like them get upset
by malicious comments online too?
Is he angry?
If that's the case, he must have
taken the photo after he saw the video.
Then does this mean
that Prosecutor Seo could still be alive?
What should we tell his family?
Should we show them the photo?
"I did it.
Too late."
Short, simple sentences.
Everything else is straightforward,
so why use a metaphor?
To show off?
Or does it mean the grudge runs that deep?
Why did he send us this?
I WASHED THE DISHES
TOO LATE
"I'm a victim too.
The prosecutor brought it upon himself."
Is this what they're trying to say?
But why?
They got their revenge.
Why the explanation?
Because what others think matters?
Or just out of anger?
Because people think that the victim
is a good man and a good prosecutor?
Are they anxious because of the video
the police uploaded?
And why the necktie?
If they wanted to prove
that they're the kidnapper…
Prosecutor Hwang.
Where can I see the prosecution's
personnel transfer records?
At the Ministry of Justice.
Hold on.
Why are you asking him about that?
Do you want a list of every office
the victim's worked in?
Well, the victim is a prosecutor.
If the culprit is holding a grudge,
we should go through
everyone he put behind bars
to obtain a lead of any kind.
There will be way too many.
It's not just the convicts.
What about their families?
Exactly. He worked in the prosecution
for over a decade.
How can we comb through
every case he's ever worked on?
Honestly speaking,
what if it's related to bribery?
"I gave you money. How dare you
not keep your end of the bargain?"
If that's what started this,
it wouldn't be on the records.
We know he accepted bribes before.
Even if we had more time
and weren't short-staffed,
-we won't be able to do that.
-That's right.
To narrow down the suspects,
we'll have to comb through
all the cases he's worked on.
Do you think the prosecution
will just hand them over?
Exactly. We'll keep searching the scene
and interviewing the people around him.
And the prosecution should look
into the rest themselves.
Can you send me the photo?
Sure.
-Nice one.
-Well said. Thank goodness.
-Right?
-Totally.
What do you think this message means?
"You can't catch me.
I have something to say.
Here's my message, smeared with blood.
So listen."
This message shows that the culprit
thinks the police are a joke.
How dare they?
Are you not outraged that
some lunatic's treating us like this?
Between people saying that
all cops should drop dead and this,
I can't tell which is worse.
Who in the police force
would say the culprit is a cop?
I doubt the prosecutors would
try to look for us if we went missing.
This means that the culprit
isn't one of the officers from Segok.
It's up to us to prove it.
I've sent you the photo.
Officer Park Sun-chang, well done.
Pardon?
Without that video,
we wouldn't have received this.
We've obtained an invaluable clue,
regardless of the culprit's intentions.
Great job.
I have to say,
the young ones are sharp-witted.
He's not just young.
He's practically a kid.
-Thank you.
-Good work.
-I'm impressed.
-Good job.
This is the Criminal Legislation Division.
Is the deputy chief there?
Okay, thank you.
He's in the office.
Request a full list of every office
Seo Dong-jae's ever worked in.
Tell them I need it.
Yes, sir.
How dare they mess with us?
What did he say?
He asked me to get
Prosecutor Seo's wife's call logs.
Is he on to something?
Yesterday, he asked his wife
why she thinks
the kidnapper hasn't demanded
a ransom yet.
That's possible
if the wife is the culprit.
If she wanted,
she could have forged a ransom note
to evade suspicion.
They don't usually go that far.
Though I've seen a husband crying at his
wife's funeral turn out to be the culprit.
We happened to receive that photo today,
so Prosecutor Hwang is suspecting
if the photo was sent by the wife
to evade suspicion.
But she said she was at home,
with her kids.
I should go over
their children's statements again.
Hey, come with me.
We'll stop by their place first.
-All right, guys.
-See you later.
Okay.
If she had a male accomplice,
she'd intentionally stay home, right?
To make it look like she's unrelated?
Jeez, this is why
missing-person cases are so awful.
It's utterly devastating for those
who are closest to the victim,
yet they end up becoming the suspect.
If we have to keep an eye on the victim's
residence, we'll have so much to do.
But Ms. Han helped us
take a huge weight off our shoulders.
People really listen to her
now that she's moved on to a bigger pond.
-What do you mean?
-You know, earlier.
Because she said we won't be able
to go through all the records,
the job ended up going to the prosecution.
That's not what she said, you fool.
Then…
The prosecution won't
hand over the records
so we won't ask for them.
"Since you love to exert
investigative authority,
you should take care of this. But…
we as police should be embarrassed
that we complained
about getting more work."
That's the gist of what she said earlier.
Didn't you feel it
when she complimented you?
She wasn't complimenting you
as your colleague.
That was a compliment
someone higher up would give.
I thought she was Chief Choi for a moment.
She's now in the policy development team.
I've learned a lot
since joining our team two years ago,
so she must've also learned a lot from…
From all the experience, right?
My goodness.
-You put me to shame.
-Yes, I know.
Well, to tell you the truth…
When she called me
"Officer Park Sun-chang,"
that's the only thing… You know?
I guess you're right.
TOO LATE
I WASHED THE DISHES
"Too late."
"It's too late to find him"?
"You are too late"?
TOO LATE
I WASHED THE DISHES
Which is it?
We received a message,
which is believed to be from the culprit.
It was sent to the tip-off line posted
by a detective at Yongsan Station.
If this is true,
they must have held a grudge
against him for a long time.
Right, which means
it's not one of the Segok officers.
Everything fits together,
but we cannot overlook the risk.
I'll just go public with this.
I have to give an interim briefing anyway.
No, let's hold off on that.
This could be fake.
We'll find out anyway
when we catch the culprit.
We'll figure something out then.
The entire police force is facing
severe criticism right now.
What if one of the Segok officers did this
to make it seem as if he was
kidnapped because of a grudge
because we're closing in on him?
Your biggest concern is
investigative authority,
but I'm responsible for this case.
Finally.
There will be a lot of stone hurling.
Is someone hurling stones? At you?
The Segok officers' written statements.
No, older ones are fine too.
As long as they're handwritten.
Also…
Rumors?
What kinds of rumors?
Have you heard anyone say
that Prosecutor Seo had a sponsor?
Or is there anything you saw
while working under him?
No.
Did he give anyone special treatment
or ever give unreasonable orders?
What about his private life?
His private life?
With the opposite sex.
Did he?
No, she said he never did.
Was she trying to protect her mentor?
It could be true.
I saw him three times
after moving back to Seoul,
and he was always wearing the same watch.
And the same shoes too, two times.
Considering how he used to be…
It's not like him.
Did he look dejected by any chance?
"Dejected"?
The chief of the western office called.
An order came
from the Supreme Prosecutors' Office.
They wanted him to compile a list
of all the cases where Dong-jae
had problems with the defendants
and reinvestigate them.
The current chief
doesn't know Dong-jae that well,
so he called to ask
why he got such an order.
That got taken care of quickly.
Did you request to have this collected?
All the troubles he's caused?
Yes.
-All the offices he's ever worked in?
-Yes.
He'll have to be a lawyer.
He'll be good at it
because he's a smooth talker.
He's worked at six or seven offices,
at the very least.
They'll comb through every case
he's ever worked on.
Even saints have a flaw or two.
And in Dong-jae's case…
Since it's Seo Dong-jae,
his reputation will hit rock bottom
if they dig up his past conducts.
No office will want to work with him.
Are you saying I should have taken
his reputation into account?
All I'm saying is,
his reputation doesn't matter
if he returns safe and sound.
If we can save him
before it's too late, that is.
Jeez.
He wanted to stop by,
but I told him not to.
I told him, "What for? Why bother?"
When was that?
When did he say he wanted to stop by?
I don't know. A little while ago, I guess.
He was just trying to be friendly.
He must have been embarrassed.
I cut him off right away.
Prosecutor Seo said he'd look into it.
That was what our last phone call
was about.
He said he needed more time
and that he hadn't had a chance
to meet the chief yet.
You said you had a question for me.
You must be busy, so go ahead and ask.
I had asked him a favor a while back.
Hey.
Ask away so you can go look for him.
If there's anything we should know
about the eastern district office.
How was Prosecutor Seo…
Because you wanted to see
if there was something you could use
to attack the eastern office?
…after I transferred to Tongyeong?
Did he cause trouble
that you don't know about?
Yes.
I'm not sure.
I ended up transferring him
to Juvenile Investigations.
And I must say,
he did a pretty good job there.
Dealing with child abuse and bullying is
a whole different ball game.
Some of the cases had him fuming mad.
I see.
Thank you for your time, sir.
You're done?
You came all the way here for that?
It's not that far.
It took me 30 minutes to get here.
All right.
You said you interviewed a suspect,
the cop.
Why not interrogate him more?
Like you said, he's still just a suspect.
Woo Tae-ha must be thrilled.
Even everyone here is saying they won't
let it go if the police orchestrated it.
All right.
I may sound a bit subjective
coming from me,
but Chief Choi Bit seemed
rather favorable to me
when I met her this morning.
So what did she say
she'll do about Park Gwang-su?
Figuring that out
is just a matter of time now, ma'am.
I was afraid she might put her guard up.
She is a cop, after all.
But I'll find out soon, ma'am.
They must be on alert
because the culprit might be a cop.
I'm surprised to hear
that she was favorable to you.
Oh, ma'am. Did I tell you?
I'm also meeting with the chief
of the eastern office today.
I should take care of the issues
surrounding Hanjo's lawsuit as well.
That's good news.
I'll have Mr. Park fill me in on that.
Yes, ma'am. I'll call him
as soon as the meeting is over.
Have a good day, ma'am.
The second trial for the fines
has been scheduled.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
NOTICE OF TRIAL
Seoul High Court's Division 3
is handling it.
It's never-ending.
Tell them we need to submit
additional documents and postpone it.
Yes, ma'am.
And I found out why Mr. Lee has been quiet
since the shareholders' meeting.
It looks like Hanjo Engineering
will be audited soon.
I heard the lights from floor twelve
and up have been on all night.
They'll be audited?
Did someone rat on them,
or did they get caught?
The eastern office
started the investigation
and handed it over to the FSC.
Is the Eastern Prosecutors' Office
out to get Hanjo?
Isn't our accounting team on floor eight?
Yes, ma'am.
They'll have to pull all-nighters too.
I'll get our accounting team ready
so we can avoid further audits.
I say one word, and you know
exactly what needs to be done.
Is this your husband's necktie?
Please find my husband.
Yes, we're doing our best.
Save him. Please help him.
I know you have a suspect,
and you've already interviewed him.
Why isn't my husband back yet?
YOON SIN-YEONG SOLO PRACTICE
EUMPA PIANO ACADEMY
I'm sorry, but could you write a statement
stating that you've seen the photo
and verified your husband's necktie?
We need the statement. I'm sorry.
Are you at home?
A detective came by just now.
March 29, 14:01.
YONGSAN POLICE STATION, TEAM 3
FIND OUT WHO THE WIFE SPOKE TO
AT 14:01 ON MARCH 29
Hey, what about the CCTV footage?
-You should see this.
-Why? Do you think she lied?
No, we've confirmed with the kids
that she was home all day.
She did come home around 7 p.m.
on the day of the incident.
But if you see this…
That's her younger kid heading out
to the academy at 7:30 p.m.
But the thing is,
her older kid came home after 10 p.m.
So there's no one to prove her alibi
for that three-hour window?
But none of the footage
shows her leaving the house.
Remember the realtor lady
from two months ago?
She vanished from her home,
but she wasn't caught
on any of the CCTV cameras.
From her children's perspective,
the younger one saw her
at home in the evening
and the older one also saw her at home
later that night.
Maybe that's why they said
their mom was home all day.
I mean, she wouldn't encourage
her kids to lie.
You still believe that all moms are good?
Well, I'm just…
-I'm surprised she touched up her nails.
-What?
I know this because I've seen my wife.
Nail polish usually chips in a day or two.
But his wife must do her nails
every night.
Her nail polish didn't chip at all.
What's it called?
What if she got a gel manicure?
Hang on. I saw her nails during the shoot.
I'm not talking about nail art.
That's when you put on sparkles
and draw on your nails.
Her nails are not like that.
Maybe she just picked a solid color.
It's very durable
so you need a solvent to remove it.
Think about it.
If she went to a nail salon
and asked them to remove it
because her husband went missing,
wouldn't that be weirder?
You think so?
Maybe you're right.
IMMIGRATION
MOVED BACK HOME
SELF-EMPLOYED
Did he quit?
Gosh, you scared me.
What kind of shoes are you wearing?
You walked in so silently.
I heard he was transferred. Did he quit?
Yes. He was transferred to Pocheon
after the incident at Segok,
but he quit after 15 days.
He currently works at his mother's
paper shop in Bangsan Market.
Why do you think the culprit
sent a photo of his tie?
To prove that they're the kidnapper?
But the blood wasn't necessary.
Maybe they wanted to show off.
They're crazy enough to send this.
They could do anything.
There are loads of people
who upload photos on the internet
after hitting someone with their cars.
Captain.
-We got something in the mail.
-What is it?
A show-off…
Bold enough to send
the victim's blood and belongings
directly to the police…
Oh, gosh.
-If the culprit wanted to show off,
-What's that?
wouldn't they have sent us
the tie instead of the photo?
They want to show off, not get caught.
Why are you all entering so quietly?
Sending us the necktie would allow us
to find the post office they used.
By visiting the post office,
they would be giving us a lead.
Many people don't realize it,
but there are many mailboxes
on the street.
Putting a letter in one of them
would only take a second.
There wouldn't be any witnesses.
And if he did that,
he could have given us a fingerprint
or other clues.
Even though there's blood on it,
we can't have anything tested
since it's just a photo.
But here's what I find strange.
I've been a detective for 30 years,
but I've never seen anyone
who's sent a message like this
after committing a crime.
Things like this only happen
in American movies.
Most culprits should be busy hiding.
They won't have time for this.
So why did they send us the photo?
If it wasn't about showing off,
it could be that they were upset
after watching the video we uploaded.
The culprit saw the victim as someone
who needed to be "washed,"
but people are now praising him
and criticizing the culprit.
Maybe that's what upset them.
That would mean they haven't
gotten rid of him yet.
Then we should do legwork,
not look for a body.
Dead or not, they must have
had him close by to have sent the photo.
Unless they have some kind of a fetish
where they collect
the ties of their victims.
Where would kidnappers in Korea store…
I mean, keep their victims?
If they're normal people like us.
It's not like there are any cabins
in the middle of nowhere like in the US.
Where would they keep their victims
in a densely populated country like Korea?
If it's a dead body, the trunk of a car
would be the most convenient.
They could have put him there at first.
But even if Prosecutor Seo
was unconscious at the time,
they would've had to tie him up
and gag him
so that he wouldn't cause trouble
when he woke up.
Would the culprit have done that
at the scene?
No, they'd run first.
They would obviously want to flee
the scene of crime first.
Plus, it was a residential area,
so they could've been seen at any moment.
Then where would they go to tie him up?
Where would they keep him?
A parking lot? That's even riskier.
What if the culprit lives in
a detached house with a separate garage?
That would be ideal for the culprit.
But then we need to add
one more condition.
The culprit would have to live
in a detached house with a garage,
but they have to live alone.
They have to live alone,
and even if they're not,
they don't share their car
with any of their family members.
Or the entire household
could be accomplices.
Like that incident before,
"My father was a victim of a hit-and-run,
but Prosecutor Seo took bribes
from the culprit and let him go."
So the entire family could lock him up
in their house as revenge.
It does seem like a detached house.
There aren't many apartments
that have wooden floors like that.
The wooden floor…
He only got to wear these for a few days…
I couldn't buy him these shoes.
But he said it was okay
and that he'd just get a part-time job.
I was already upset,
but that prosecutor kept
talking nonsense to me.
Do you remember
exactly what Prosecutor Seo said to you?
What if the culprit killed him
and left the scene with his body
in the trunk?
If he died at the scene,
the body would be decomposing by now.
And if they didn't get rid of the body,
they'd be keeping it close
since they would have to hide the smell.
When people kill their families,
they keep the body wrapped in a blanket
in their bathrooms or the closet.
It's hard for us to imagine
having to live with a body like that.
People like that can't even
open their windows
because someone might smell the body
and report them.
So the safest place for the culprit
is a location they have full control over.
I don't think we'll get anywhere
by investigating the scene of the crime.
The fact that the culprit left
the victim's car there
means they fled somewhere far away.
Gosh. Where could they be?
Why was it the necktie?
They could've taken his ear or his finger.
Because people wouldn't know
whose it is from the photo?
Because body parts wouldn't show
that it was the victim's?
But that's the same with blood.
Were they scared?
Was it because of that?
I WASHED THE DISHES
Maybe it wasn't revenge.
Oh, you two were here too.
This won't be enough then.
Order some more.
What is it?
Rhino Dumplings. We ordered
tteokbokki on the way here.
I was really craving that.
Hello. We just ordered…
Wait. We want to order some more.
I want dumplings and skewers.
Get fish cakes and sundae
for Detective Seo.
Two servings of dumplings,
two servings of fish cakes and sundae,
and rice cake skewers…
Prosecutor Hwang, do you want skewers too?
Of course. He'll eat them.
Six rice cake skewers then.
All right. Thank you.
I almost cried a while back
because I missed their food so much.
Why? You can just go there and have some.
So I ran over, but they were closed.
What?
You came all the way here
and left without dropping by?
Jeez. You almost cried
because a restaurant was closed,
but you ignored your colleagues
suffering from a heavy workload?
She won't think of us
as her colleagues anymore.
Oh, right.
I got a written statement
from Prosecutor Seo's wife.
WITNESS STATEMENT
Could I get this printed out?
Sure. Send it to me.
I can do it here.
What is that?
Handwritten statements
of the six Segok officers from 2017.
I got it.
Did the culprit not know
how to print something?
They used the non-dominant hand
to hide their handwriting.
It would've been easier
to type and print it out. Jeez.
Here you go.
WITNESS STATEMENT
Here.
Whose is this? It looks the most similar.
The one who left Korea.
-What if he came back for a short while?
-Right.
-Check his entry and departure records.
-Oh, come on.
Can you get these statements analyzed too?
Okay.
The food must be here.
-Are you here?
-Here. Get the receipt.
All right, I'll be there.
Do you think this is a ceiling light?
It looks like there are
two ceiling lights.
I think there's something written here.
Oh, my eyes hurt.
-Did you send this to Forensics?
-No.
It's not like the culprit
printed out the photo themselves.
I didn't think we'd get anything
from the photo.
Right, but just send it over anyway.
-It'll be better than just looking at it.
-Okay.
Would we have the results by tomorrow?
Why tomorrow?
The interim announcement.
Are you going to announce this?
Are you going to tell them
it was the culprit
-when we don't know who it's really from?
-The food's here.
We need to verify it first.
What's the hurry?
It's urgent. You know why.
I'm Han Yeo-jin, the detective
in charge of this case.
I will now announce
our investigation results so far
on the missing case of Prosecutor Seo
from the Uijeongbu Office.
Around midnight on March 26, 2019,
the blood of Prosecutor Seo from
the Uijeongbu District Prosecutors' Office
was found along with his vehicle
in an alley in Bogwang-dong, Yongsan.
The victim's ID card
and small amount of cash
were found in his car.
The entire Violent Crimes Unit
as well as the Intelligence Crime Team
and Investigation Support Team
at Yongsan Police Station
are all working together
to find the missing victim.
We're currently increasing our range
of investigation,
starting from the crime scene.
Just make the announcement.
Gather all the reporters
who said a cop did it,
and tell them they were wrong
to their faces.
The victim, Prosecutor Seo,
has been specializing in juvenile crimes
for the past few years.
The Uijeongbu District Prosecutors' Office
stated that
he was chosen as
the Prosecutor of the Month
for his diligence
and his investigation skills,
and was to receive an award soon.
Is that true?
No, I haven't heard anything.
-Why are they praising him?
-So they can ruin his image later.
We need to verify it first.
What's the hurry?
It's urgent. You know why.
If we announce this,
people will stop saying
that the suspect is a police.
So did the higher-ups tell you to do so?
We are still investigating the suspects
who were formerly
summoned by Prosecutor Seo.
No, it's not just that.
If this message was intended to
throw us off the track
and I announce it at an official briefing,
the Segok officers will think
that their plan is working.
Then they are bound to make a mistake.
Yesterday afternoon,
our investigation team received a photo
that is believed to have been
sent by the culprit
via text message.
Captain!
CULPRIT SENDS PHOTO MESSAGE
Mom.
No,
it's not about your dad.
The culprit is presumed to be
holding a grudge against the victim.
And despite having been
summoned by the prosecution,
the initial suspect was proven
not to have any motives.
So the investigation team
has decided to investigate
the victim's past actions
for new suspects.
Stop the car.
-Pardon?
-Stop the car.
Captain!
Don't! Captain!
Don't do it.
Go back inside.
Calm down.
Let's just go.
We're currently focusing
on the victim's actions
for the last two to three years.
And we will be moving onwards
with the investigation
based on the clues we find.
We are waiting for any reports you make
regarding this case.
We appreciate your cooperation.
I'll now answer your questions.
Chief Choi's gone too far.
Half the comments are about the culprit,
and the others are about Prosecutor Seo.
The fact that he was under investigation
two years ago comes up
when you search his name,
so many people are criticizing him.
And there are only a few comments
criticizing the police now.
All right.
Thank you.
Why are you thanking me?
I just said I got it.
It's already been days. The chance
of finding him is getting smaller.
It's obvious that we'll be criticized
if we don't find him.
You're right.
It feels like we're wasting our efforts.
That letter shows the culprit thinks
he's something that should be washed out.
Would they keep him alive?
We're also making investigations
based on the possibility that
the culprit buried the body.
We need a suspect to figure out
where the body would be.
It could be anywhere.
It'd be easier if they buried it outdoors.
What if they buried it in their own yard?
What? Is it something related to the case?
It's Detective Jang. About Kim Su-hang,
one of the officers who worked
at Segok Police Station…
Yes, I know. What about him?
Detective Jang got his resume,
and the store he worked at
right after his release
is just 650 meters away
from the crime scene.
On top of that, the store is his uncle's.
-The former Chief of Dongducheon Station?
-Yes.
I thought you checked
both their alibis yourself.
Come to think of it,
only Officer Kim's was confirmed.
Why do you say "come to think of it"?
The Chief worked overtime…
False entry…
Are you saying that was fake?
So he didn't work overtime?
Would it be possible to verify it?
I'll get it verified for you.
It's about him being a suspect or not.
Thank you.
Do it quietly.
It won't cause any trouble.
If he got someone to fake
his overtime work,
the cameras at the Uijeongbu Station
would have recorded him
getting off work early.
They use a different method these days.
Some people go home
and return to work at night,
and record their overtime work themselves.
They could say they had business outside.
How do you know that so well?
I guess officers in the field
still fake their overtime for more wages.
It's not just the officers working
in the field.
Should I make
a full investigation out of it
instead of keeping this quiet?
How could a civil servant do that
for a little pocket money?
This is ridiculous.
He's working at the Administration
Division in Uijeongbu, right?
Yes.
Go to my desk
in the Reformation Unit office.
There's a small cabinet under the table.
It's the second drawer.
Bring the…
Wait. What was that called?
-The Gyeonggi Province organization chart.
-What's that for?
We should interrogate the person
who gets the least amount of overtime pay.
Faking overtime work is a habit,
so people around them always know.
People who work honestly
hate higher-ups who fake their overtime,
so they'll tattle right away
when HQ asks them.
Yes, ma'am. I'll bring the file.
Am I one of the higher-ups that you hate?
What are you talking about?
Do you have anything to tattle--
What's with her?
CHIEF CHOI BIT
The second drawer…
What's going on?
What do you mean?
-The file you told--
-No, I'll do it.
You should go check out
the former Dongducheon Chief's store.
It's near the scene.
Officer Kim should know the neighborhood
since he worked there.
Right. I should head there.
I'll report to you later.
CALL HISTORY
The Uijeongbu District Prosecutors' Office
called and said they sent you an email.
-It's Prosecutor Seo's assisting officer.
-All right.
PROSECUTOR SEO'S BROWSER HISTORY
BROWSER HISTORY.XLSX
It's a list of all the websites
that Prosecutor Seo accessed
from March 18 to March 26,
the day he went missing.
It's organized in the order
of date and time.
PARK GWANG-SU FOUND DEAD
FORMER CHIEF PROSECUTOR OF
DAEJEON OFFICE DIES FROM HEART ATTACK
PARK GWANG-SU, FORMER CHIEF PROSECUTOR
OF DAEJEON OFFICE, DIED ON THE 6TH
FORMER CHIEF PROSECUTOR DIES
ON NAMYANGJU HIGHWAY
PARK GWANG-SU DIES DUE TO ILLNESS
WHILE DRIVING
FORMER CHIEF PROSECUTOR
FOUND DEAD ON NAMYANGJU HIGHWAY
FOUND ON HIGHWAY 45, GEUMNAM-RI, NAMYANGJU
FILTER: PARK GWANG-SU
PARK GWANG-SU'S DEATH
PARK GWANG-SU DIES DUE TO ILLNESS
WHILE DRIVING
FOUND ON HIGHWAY 45, GEUMNAM-RI, NAMYANGJU
DATE OF PUBLICATION
It's from 2018.
Hello, I got the browser history
you sent me.
What are these articles about
the former chief who died in Namyangju?
Let's go have lunch.
-Yes, sir.
Chief Prosecutor Park Gwang-su.
Prosecutor Seo doggedly searched
articles about his death.
-Aren't we going?
-What? Oh, him…
A vacation home area?
He'll join us later.
Is there a possibility…
Hang on. You can go ahead first.
It's fine. Go on.
It's going to take a while.
I'll join you later.
-I'll text you when we get there.
-Okay.
I have to go somewhere.
-Pardon?
-I have to go!
Criminal Division 1 deals with
traffic incidents, right?
Then you must have the dashcam footage.
What? Only the footage from that day
is missing?
How could the footage
from the day of his death be missing?
Hang on.
By any chance, did the driver die
in Geumnam-ri, Namyangju?
SEO DONG-JAE'S GPS DESTINATIONS
Highway 45.
Can you find the case report for that?
I'll be there right away.
Yes, I'm heading there right now.
HIGHWAY 45, GEUMNAM-RI, NAMYANGJU
What the…
What the hell are you doing? Move!
What's going on? Damn it.
Jeez.
Damn it. What are they doing?
What? What's going on?
Are you okay?
What time did you find him?
I'm not sure about the exact time.
I was driving this way,
and that car suddenly stopped.
-Wake up, sir.
-Get him out.
Did he mention any other cases
besides the Segok Station case?
-Just the Segok Station case.
-Do you know why your late husband
was in Namyangju the day he passed away?
I guess it could have been a VIP.
What makes you think that?
You know why I called for you, right?
It's highly likely that he already knew
there weren't any security cameras
from the entrance of the alley
to the scene of the crime.
Could Prosecutor Seo's disappearance
have anything to do
with this case from a year ago
where a man died of a heart attack?
Chief Choi used to be the chief there.
If he was targeting Chief Choi,
he would've brought it
to the Supreme office for sure.
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi