ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
LOCATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
There are 3,400 intelligence police
officers in this small country.
And intel they gather every day
all goes to Choi Bit.
This February,
Gyeonggi Nambu Provincial Police Agency
apprehended a drug dealer.
Could Assemblyman Nam's son
have been one of them?
So you probably weren't aware of
how the Police HQ would deal
with an assemblyman
suspected of bribery for illegal hiring.
You said you didn't look inside.
You knew I'd look.
Why did you drag me into this?
You said it's an investment.
Then it has to be profitable.
I want you to treat me as an entrepreneur.
What about Seo Dong-jae?
He's looking for a former officer
from Segok Police Station.
He believes he could be the prime suspect,
and not the Captain.
There's nothing else.
This is all we could find.
Captain. You know,
Prosecutor Seo Dong-jae.
SEO DONG-JAE
SUPREME PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
EPISODE 7
It's over, so just let it go.
Nam Jae-ik has been bashed,
and his son quit his job at the bank.
Why do you have to dig it up again?
-Why does there have to be a reason?
-Hey.
"The goal line has to be fair
so that those who work hard can catch up
even if the starting line isn't the same."
That's what Assemblyman Nam said
when he made a pledge
to secure enough jobs for young people.
But he used his influence
to get his son a job at the bank.
And that year alone,
2,800 people applied for a job there.
The bank was hiring for 15 positions,
and 2,800 people applied.
That still wouldn't have changed anything
for those who didn't get hired.
Will you say the same thing
if someone who failed the bar exam
becomes a prosecutor
because his father is an assemblyman?
It's not "over."
Everyone is just keeping quiet about it.
This will also affect your boss,
Chief Woo.
My boss? I don't operate like that.
I guess you're not expecting
anything from me either.
Even a politician who abused his power
to get his brother hired
as a non-executive director
was never prosecuted.
Instead, he sued the prosecutor in charge
for defamation,
violation of the Protection of
Communications Secrets Act,
and divulgence of official secrets.
But do you know what was brought up
at the prosecution's council meeting?
That they should perhaps reprimand
the prosecutor who was sued.
It won't be different for you.
You can't handle this.
Don't reach out to me for help later on.
I gave up on that
when you asked me to come see you.
Hey!
You're old enough now.
And with all your experience,
you really should know better.
Why do you have to be so stubborn
and bother those around you?
Is this fun for you?
I guess I've been bothering you.
-Did you feel the same way in the past?
-Back then…
We're in a different position now.
Both of us.
I'll probably never
understand the things
that I should know by a certain age.
You see, I don't enjoy this either.
Then don't do it. Just don't go that way.
You should get going.
I'll probably never understand the things
that I should know by a certain age.
Thanks.
You asked me to treat you
as an entrepreneur.
You told me to choose
what would benefit me more.
That's all this is about.
It's not about you.
GENERAL SHAREHOLDERS' MEETING
FOR CHAIRMAN AND CEO SEPARATION
FOR: 41.9%, AGAINST: 43.8%, FORFEIT: 14.3%
PERSONAL INFORMATION RECORD
NAME: CHOI BIT
Good morning, sir.
Hey. What's with that guy?
Is Seo Dong-jae always like that?
He pestered me for a meeting
so I made time for him,
but he stood me up.
He didn't show up?
No. And I couldn't get a hold of him.
He didn't even answer my calls.
Unbelievable.
Who's calling so early?
Hello?
Detective Jang Geon?
It's me, Woo Tae-ha.
You didn't know this was my number?
Seo Dong-jae?
Yes, I spoke to him on the phone
yesterday. Why are you asking me?
What do you mean?
How could…
Are you sure he's missing?
-Hi.
-Are you busy?
The next meeting has been scheduled.
Hold on. I'm on the other line.
I'll call you back.
Sorry, I caught you at a bad time.
No, Prosecutor Seo has gone missing.
I'll call you back.
What?
Maybe it's not the Prosecutor Seo I know.
I have a meeting,
so don't call me before 3 p.m.
-Yes, ma'am!
-Have a good meeting.
INVESTIGATIVE PROCEDURE
REFORMATION UNIT
What the hell has he been up to?
Sir, you know everything that I know.
I've told you everything.
Then where is he? It's not like
he'd get lost. He's not a kid.
I never thought you'd actually
put in a word for me.
Yes, I spoke to him on
the phone yesterday.
You said you were supposed to see him.
What was it about?
I probably drink more coffee
than anyone else in Korea.
-Hello, sir
-Good morning, sir.
Hey, what's going on?
Didn't you notice anything unusual?
No, nothing.
Did he ever mention anything
about receiving threats
or having specific concerns?
-No, sir.
-Could it be because of one of his cases?
He's in the criminal division,
so I'm sure he has to deal with
all sorts of con men and hoodlums.
Why were you trying
to meet Prosecutor Seo?
I told you already.
He begged me to see him.
No, sir. This time,
you reached out to him first.
-What was it about?
-Hey.
Are you interrogating me?
If that were the case,
I'd first try to verify your claim
that you never saw him last night.
What was it about, sir?
-You know something, don't you?
-Me?
Your colleague that you've been
investigating with until yesterday
has disappeared,
leaving behind a single bloodstain.
But you don't seem worried.
You'd be more worried for some dog.
You can't react like this
unless you already knew about it.
Did you two plan this together?
What time and where
were you two supposed to meet?
Seriously?
At ten o'clock, near Yeouido.
I have you two keep me
in the loop on different stuff.
Did you think I'd only listen to you?
I'm sure you called him multiple times
around 10 p.m. when he didn't show up.
Did he not answer? Or was his phone off?
His phone was off
from when I first called him.
As you've mentioned,
the Uijeongbu office could be
where it all began.
It may have nothing to do with him
investigating the Segok case.
Go to the Uijeongbu office immediately.
But I do not have the authority
to pry into their cases, sir.
You said the Supreme Prosecutors' Office
doesn't investigate any cases.
Jeez, seriously. Can you just do as I say?
Yes, sir.
Is the deputy prosecutor general in?
Let him know
that something's happened
to a district prosecutor
and it looks like we should oversee it.
Find someone better suited for the job.
Why have Prosecutor Hwang handle it?
What?
Sir, may I come up to see you now?
PROSECUTOR SEO DONG-JAE
Captain Baek accepted the bribes too.
I checked with the business owners myself.
Officer Kim's uncle is the former chief
of Dongducheon Police Station.
We must get him first.
Just wait and see
who finds him first, okay?
This is Hwang Si-mok.
We met the other day.
I'm on my way to…
Yes, I heard. I'm on my way there now.
I'll need a list of all the cases
Prosecutor Seo has worked on this year
as well as all the files
on Segok Police Station.
Make sure I can get into
his computer right away.
DETECTIVE JANG GEON
Hello, Detective Jang.
It's me, Hwang Si-mok.
Please send all information
regarding Prosecutor Seo's disappearance
to the Criminal Legislation Division.
Yes, we'll be taking the case.
Everything you've found out so far.
Okay.
When a married couple who owns a pub
in the area came home after midnight,
the car was parked there.
Who parked their car like this
in front of our house?
Isn't there a phone number up front?
I don't see it at the back either.
Honey.
What is it?
We have to check
if it's your husband's blood.
We don't have any other samples
to check against.
I brought my husband's stuff.
You could've used those instead.
My son must be scared.
Maybe she's hardened
because she's a prosecutor's wife.
Her husband had gone missing,
but she seemed more worried about her son.
-Anything out of the ordinary?
-No.
Nothing out of the ordinary happened.
But he usually kept to himself
according to his colleagues.
Geon, we got his call logs.
Okay.
CALL HISTORY
Hello, I'm calling
from Yongsan Police Station.
I wanted to ask you a few questions.
You know Mr. Seo Dong-jae, right?
-Yesterday--
-Detective Jang Geon?
Yes, that's me.
-Who is this?
-It's me, Woo Tae-ha.
Chief Woo?
The number on the top of the call history
belonged to Chief Woo.
Right, Woo Tae-ha from the council.
Yes, the one who acts all serious.
-Prosecutor Seo stood him up last night.
-Yes, Seo Dong-jae.
-Didn't you speak with him yesterday?
-At 10 p.m.
Hold on a second.
This is Yongsan Police Station.
Yes, speaking.
You got the results?
Is it Seo Dong-jae's blood?
Senior Inspector Han, the analysis shows
that it is Prosecutor Seo's blood.
You have photos of the scene, right?
Can I see them?
The thing is, you're technically
not on the team anymore, but…
I'll have them photocopied for you.
Thank you. I'll head over there now.
I said I don't know anything.
I didn't see anything.
Stop ringing the doorbell.
I just managed to put my kid to sleep.
MOMO MARKET
His blood was found at the scene,
which means it started here.
Maybe it happened elsewhere,
and this is just like a cover-up spot?
Would he still be in this area?
But there were no drag marks.
Did they use something to carry him?
Maybe they carried him with an accomplice.
Considering his physique,
it wouldn't have been easy
to carry him alone.
Would the culprit still be in the area
or did he already run away?
Jeez, we couldn't even find
a single strand of hair.
In a way, that's a good thing.
If it was murder,
we would have found his body somewhere.
But nothing's turned up yet.
Right, but the fact
that his phone was turned off…
-What time did that happen?
-At 8:50 p.m.
He left the office just before seven,
so it took an hour and 50 minutes until
the phone was turned off in Bogwang-dong.
He was supposed to meet a prosecutor from
the Supreme Prosecutors' Office at ten.
What was he doing in this area?
Gosh,
talk about taking a shot in the dark.
It's not like we can get warrants
to all the houses in the area.
Hey, let's head out.
We have nothing else to rely on
but the scene.
Sun-chang, track his car and find out
his exact route from Uijeongbu.
Yes, sir.
Damn it.
CALL HISTORY
This is the overpass. And Uijeongbu…
-Hey, Sun-chang.
-Oh, hello.
Which one is Prosecutor Seo's car?
This one?
This is…
Wait. Does this mean you're back?
If you see here…
I've tracked his car from Uijeongbu
District Prosecutors' Office to here.
After this, I have no idea.
What about the area
where the vehicle was found?
I'm going to look into it now.
From the main road, there are
three alleyways that lead to the scene.
But there are no CCTV cameras.
Damn it.
CHIEF CHOI BIT
What? It's already three o'clock?
Yes, Chief.
Right. Now?
Give me five minutes…
No, I'll be there in ten.
Bye.
-Could we check the area near the scene?
-Sure.
Where Bogwang-dong begins.
UIJEONGBU DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
Prosecutor Hwang Si-mok, right?
Hello, I'm Jung Min-ha
from Criminal Division 1.
I got a call from the Supreme Office.
Our chief prosecutor is deeply concerned.
-First, you should meet--
-No, later.
What was the last thing Prosecutor Seo did
before leaving the office yesterday?
"You're so freaking annoying.
Are you proud
that your family is on welfare?
You're making it so obvious
that your family is dirt-poor."
That was just a joke.
Then what about locking him
in the girls' restroom naked?
Would he also think of it as a joke?
But all the other kids did it too.
If all the others did it too,
why are you the only one who's here now?
Do you really think it's okay
to do these things to another human being?
You told everyone
that his family is on welfare
and that they live
in a community housing building.
But he does live
Anyway, I'm too young to be prosecuted.
When can I leave?
What?
Do you want to go home?
No, I have to go to the academy.
Who told you that you're too young
to be prosecuted? Your parents?
I learned it at the law camp.
They said anyone under the age of 14
cannot be prosecuted.
Look at this.
This boy is half your size,
yet you beat him up for 50 minutes.
Let me ask you one thing.
Did you enjoy beating him up?
Do you really enjoy feeling someone else's
flesh against your fist and shoes
and watching that person in pain?
He's a total idiot, though.
What?
What about you?
-Pardon?
-What?
Fine.
Leave. Go to your academy.
But let me teach you one thing
before you leave.
The court can order protective detention
for kids like you.
You may be put on probation or be ordered
to attend lectures, do community service,
or go to the juvie.
If the judge thinks
you should be sent to the juvie,
you'll end up there.
Can I attend the lecture then?
That's only up to 100 hours, isn't it?
I guess I'm right.
I keep seeing more kids like him
these days.
Jeez. Now I'm afraid to
send my boy to school.
Oh, right.
Did you find out where he lives?
Well, I did find an address
registered under the name Kim Su-hang--
I have the address. I told you
that he doesn't seem to live there.
Right, that's why I'm still looking.
Forget it. I'll ask myself.
I have to leave. I have an appointment.
-Okay.
-Have a good evening.
What a rude little punk.
That's what he did
right before leaving the office.
Who was he going to ask
about Kim Su-hang's address?
He didn't tell us.
What time did he leave the office?
Just before 7 p.m.
Oh, I contacted our IT department
right after you called.
But it's taking a while
because we don't know his password.
All these reports on Segok were written
by Prosecutor Seo's predecessor.
Are there any new ones
written after he took on the case?
Technically, we can't really say
he took on the case
because it's not like
we officially reopened the case.
When our chief prosecutor heard about him
looking into the suicide case again,
he said we shouldn't tell the police
anything until we find concrete evidence.
That's why we didn't say anything
about the Segok case
to the officer from Yongsan Police Station
who was here earlier.
Do you think Prosecutor Seo went missing
because of that case?
If you have any other suspicions,
please tell me.
No, that's not what I meant.
-Oh, it worked? You got in?
-Yes.
-You got in?
-Yes, you can use it now.
-Thank you very much.
-No problem.
KOREA INFORMATION SYSTEM
OF CRIMINAL-JUSTICE SERVICES
Most of these are pages on KICS.
They're all for the cases he's working on.
Other than these…
What's this?
Did he watch a video or something?
Yes, this was yesterday afternoon.
YONGSAN STATION UNIT 3 CAPTAIN
-Hello?
-This is Choi Yun-soo from Yongsan.
-Do you have a moment to talk?
-Yes.
I just got a call
from one of the detectives on my team.
He said one of the numbers
on Prosecutor Seo's call history
-seems to be yours.
-I don't know who that is.
Do you happen to remember
what you two spoke about?
Hello?
I asked you to send all the case files
to the Supreme Prosecutors' Office.
Have you sent them over yet?
Well, no one on the team is
in the office at the moment.
I'll send them over as soon as I'm back.
No need. I'll just go
to Yongsan Police Station myself.
What? You're going to stop by?
Yes, I'll see you there.
Please check every web page he accessed
until the moment he left the office.
Look through the cookies as well.
I'll go over those when I come back.
Also, I want information
on the six officers from Segok
who were charged with bribery.
And find out if anyone
around Prosecutor Seo
has any relation to the scene.
It's Bogwang-dong in Yongsan. A relative
who used to live there for example.
I heard Sergeant Baek
has been on vacation the past few days.
Summon him.
Are you going to request a warrant?
-What kind of warrant?
-A search warrant.
They think Prosecutor Seo was moved
from the scene in a car.
We should conduct
a search and seizure to see
if a Segok officer is connected to it.
Go through all the dashcam footage
or see if we can find his DNA
in Sergeant Baek's car.
But we haven't pinned down a suspect yet.
Right. I mean, to do that.
We can request one, but I doubt
the court will issue the warrant.
They'll say they do not see
why a search and seizure is necessary.
But a prosecutor has gone missing.
Won't the court take that
into consideration?
Let's say a cop went missing
while investigating a prosecutor.
And the police are asking us to get them
a search and seizure warrant
for that prosecutor.
Do you think you'll request a warrant
when there's insufficient evidence?
I'll ask for additional evidence.
Is the Supreme Prosecutors' Office
only taking the Segok case?
Or does it also include
looking for Prosecutor Seo?
I'd say both.
I'm relieved
that we don't have to investigate this.
Are you swamped?
No, that's not what I meant.
If we were to take it on,
Dongducheon Police Station would end up
investigating the case.
As you know,
Segok Police Station is their substation.
That would be like having the fox
guard the hen house.
Even if we transfer the case
to a different precinct,
it won't be any different because
they're the same organization after all.
We'll figure out
which precinct should handle it.
Prosecutor Seo trained me.
I spent my probation period in his office.
Me too.
Hey, what's up?
Captain, I think we've found the weapon.
What is it? Where did you find it?
I clearly remember seeing four of them
when I was heading out yesterday morning.
I didn't notice it last night,
but I've realized
that there are only three now.
The actual weapon hasn't turned up,
but it may be one of the bricks
from the scene.
Any chance you're just confused?
I move these everyday
after my husband drives off.
How could I be confused?
There were always four of them,
but one is missing now.
I suppose he was struck with a brick.
INVESTIGATIVE PROCEDURE
REFORMATION UNIT
You look as if you were caught
while slacking off.
-Did you go somewhere far again?
-May I have a word with you?
-Chief.
-Is it a kidnapping?
It seems like it.
-And he was attacked?
-Yes.
The blood found at the scene
belongs to the owner of the vehicle.
CALL HISTORY
It's a crazy world, you know.
Some lunatic can randomly chase you
for no reason.
Right.
And people get mugged.
It doesn't matter if he's a prosecutor.
But it's unlikely, right?
You never know.
What if the prosecution orchestrated it
to trap us?
It's far-fetched, right?
-Ms. Han.
-Yes, ma'am.
I want you to prove
that the police have nothing to do
with Sergeant Song's death
and this disappearance case.
I hope it's unrelated,
but what if that isn't the case?
-If we catch them--
-I'm not asking you to catch anyone.
I don't expect you to find the
missing man.
That's the detectives' job. You'll--
Hold on.
Hello?
Yes, sir.
Why postpone the council meeting?
It's already been scheduled.
What does a missing prosecutor
have to do with the council meeting?
Is that what Chief Woo said?
I'll tell them we should stick
to the schedule and can't postpone it.
Yes, sir.
What a lame excuse.
He's trying to wiggle out of it.
We can't do what we did last time even if
things don't turn out in our favor.
What "last time"?
Even if Segok had something to do
with Prosecutor Seo's disappearance,
we can't wait until the meeting is over
to catch the culprit
or put off the investigation until after
we gain investigative authority.
Ms. Han.
If I ever talk such bullshit,
just go ahead and report me.
People who mess with things
that could cost lives
don't deserve to be treated with respect.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Find out the truth.
Yes, ma'am.
Chief Woo, it's me.
I heard you wanted to postpone the meeting
because of a missing prosecutor. That's…
When?
Prosecutor Hwang!
Hello. It's been a while
since we last met.
-Right.
-I heard you were back in Seoul.
It's too bad we're meeting like this.
I hope nothing will happen this time.
Could it…
It won't happen again, right?
Right.
I sent Prosecutor Seo's computer records
to your email address.
My goodness.
Oh, right. Coffee.
It's fine.
You haven't come here in a while, though.
Anyway…
This is all the info we gathered so far.
We're interviewing the residents there
individually right now
to see if anyone's connected to
Prosecutor Seo.
The culprit would have had his car keys.
If they lived in the neighborhood,
they would've gotten rid of the car first.
If the car hadn't been found,
the neighborhood wouldn't have
been involved.
I guess so.
But this neighborhood
has the least security cameras
within our jurisdiction.
They haven't been installed since
there were rumors of redevelopment.
There's been reports of thefts in the area
a few months ago,
but it was tough
since there were no cameras.
If they chose that place intentionally,
they must know the neighborhood.
But more importantly…
"More importantly"?
Is there something else?
No, it's just that
we can't find any clues.
We need to find the missing person,
but all we can do is search the scene.
So…
I called you
because your number
was on his call history.
PROSECUTOR WOO TAE-HA
What time and where
were you two supposed to meet?
At ten o'clock, near Yeouido.
The phone you have called
is currently turned off.
-You will be directed to voicemail…
-Jeez.
PROSECUTOR SEO DONG-JAE
Prosecutor Seo and I discussed matters
regarding the Uijeongbu District
Prosecutors' Office.
What kind of things?
Things related to adjusting
investigative rights.
I see.
Did he bring up anything unusual?
Or perhaps he acted strangely?
He said it was tough
being transferred too often
and that he doesn't get to spend time
with his kids.
Things like that.
What's this?
Tongyeong?
Oh, that? Well, two university students
drowned in Tongyeong
at the beginning of March.
I know. I was stationed there.
Oh, right.
He's the student that survived.
One of the three students
who were at the beach.
And Prosecutor Seo called him?
According to him,
it wasn't the first time
that Prosecutor Seo called him.
He said that at first, he thought,
"I feel so bad that my friends drowned.
I'll never drink again."
Then he heard that some people had
gotten rid of the restriction line
and that they were released because of
special treatment in the prosecution.
So he realized it wasn't just an accident
and that his friends were victims.
A prosecutor from the Uijeongbu District
Prosecutors' Office suddenly called me
and talked about the incident,
so I first thought he was
just trying to offer me help.
When did he first call you?
It was around the time there was news
about the prosecution not doing
their work properly.
But he just kept talking nonsense
as our conversation carried on.
What nonsense?
He made excuses, saying that
it wasn't the prosecution's fault
that his friends died,
and then asked if an officer
named Choi Bit visited him.
So you're saying Prosecutor Seo
called him just to say that?
Wasn't there anything else?
Well…
Why would a prosecutor say that to a kid?
He wasn't trying to sue
the prosecution or anything.
The kid wasn't the only one he called.
He even called one of the victims' fathers
and asked if Choi Bit said anything bad
about the prosecution during her visit.
He even asked if she pressured him
into doing an interview,
and stuff like that.
I checked his call history
and he did call the victim's house.
Jeez. He was probably trying
to dig up dirt on Chief Choi.
He called the house of one of the victims
and said the same thing.
-He called the victim's family too?
-Yes.
Hang on.
I'm sure it's on his call history too.
Anyway, the survivor from the Tongyeong
incident said he remembered
deciding never to answer
Prosecutor Seo's calls again.
He hesitated a bit
before answering his call yesterday,
and Prosecutor Seo
said the same thing again.
So he just hung up after a while.
CALL TIME
2 MINUTES 21 SECONDS
POLICE VISITS FAMILY OF TONGYEONG
DROWNING VICTIM
Chief Choi is representing the police
in our fight for investigative rights.
If he reveals that she secretly
talked the victims' families
into criticizing the prosecution,
she'd be disgraced for sure.
Why would he dig into
such a petty thing like that?
That cheap bastard.
-But…
-You can curse him after we find him.
Sir…
What?
If Prosecutor Seo went missing
while digging up dirt on Chief Choi,
would she really be unrelated
to this case?
Are you serious?
Would a superintendent general
really hit and kidnap someone
just for trying to dig up dirt on them?
If that was the case, there would be
no prosecutors left alive by now.
They arrested former commissioner generals
every time we talked
about investigative rights.
If what you said was true,
why would they have gotten arrested?
Right. If that were true,
those people would've all killed
the prosecutors investigating them.
Hey, I'm going to tell
Chief Choi about you.
I was just thinking out loud.
Never mind.
By the way…
Are you in contact with Hanjo Group
by any chance?
Besides this one,
he made multiple calls to Hanjo Group
a week ago.
Sometimes he called them,
and sometimes Hanjo Group called him.
But we can't check anything.
Hanjo Group is rejecting our calls.
-I'll look into it.
-That's good.
If you get anything, please tell us.
Sure.
Oh, right. One more thing.
Here.
We got a list of Prosecutor Seo's recent
destinations from the GPS in his car.
But there aren't any from yesterday.
We can't tell if he didn't use it
or if the culprit deleted the history.
Wait. I'll give you a copy of that.
We didn't have time to make a copy yet.
This is the original file.
SUN-CHANG
I'M WATCHING YOU
Dongducheon Police Station would end up
investigating the case.
That would be like having the fox
guard the hen house.
It won't be any different because
they're the same organization after all.
Oh, right. We didn't get it filed yet,
but I think we found the weapon.
What was the weapon?
Does Prosecutor Seo
always park this terribly?
No, he cared a lot about his car,
his belongings,
and the things he wore.
If he had enough time, he would've
parked his car properly.
Then he must've stopped in a hurry
before getting out.
And his blood was found in a small alley…
Maybe he wasn't visiting
one of the houses here.
Maybe he saw someone in this alley.
The weapon…
Was he facing the culprit?
You asshole! Have you lost your mind?
Unless the culprit was really big…
Prosecutor Seo is well-built himself.
But we only found his blood on the scene.
He showed his back to the culprit,
and the culprit hadn't prepared
the weapon in advance…
The blood was spilled behind the car,
and the car came from over there to here.
If he saw the culprit standing here…
If he met the culprit here by coincidence,
that would mean
that the culprit lives nearby.
Then they would have
gotten rid of his car first.
They wouldn't have just left it there.
If they weren't a resident here,
they would have lured him here.
If the culprit wanted to lure
someone in a car,
they would have used their car too…
No.
What if Prosecutor Seo gave the culprit
a ride and dropped them off here?
If that was the case,
he would've parked his car properly.
What if he was arguing with the culprit
and suddenly stopped because he got angry?
Did they find signs of anyone
sitting in the passenger seat?
It seemed like they were working on it.
But it'll take some time.
There are so many things
to analyze in a car.
Then…
if Prosecutor Seo and the culprit
shared a ride here together,
what would the culprit have done
after attacking him?
They would have moved his body first
before anyone saw it.
They would have moved him
using Prosecutor Seo's car,
unless they were going to carry him
to a house nearby.
What if they did? If they moved him
to one of the houses here,
then they would've come out right after
and moved his car somewhere else.
But…
if there was an accomplice,
then any one of those scenarios
would be possible.
We have to find him soon.
It's almost been a whole day.
Do you know where the former chief
of Dongducheon Station is?
Prosecutor Seo could have met him
just before he went missing.
CALL HISTORY
NAMYANGJU POLICE STATION
UIJEONGBU POLICE ADMINISTRATION DIVISION
MS. HAN
Why would Prosecutor Seo meet
the former chief of Dongducheon Station?
An employee in Seo's office said
that he mentioned asking
Officer Kim's whereabouts himself.
So of course, he'd ask the Chief.
He found out that they're connected.
Let's go.
I'm not going to come back here though.
-I'll take a cab on my way back then.
-What?
It'll cost a lot to catch a cab
from Dongducheon to here.
I didn't know we were going
to Dongducheon.
Oh, really?
Well, Chief Choi
mentioned that he moved
to somewhere nearby.
Where?
That's what I'm about to ask.
The number you have dialed…
Oh, I guess she must be busy.
Was it Chief Choi who told you
that Officer Kim was related
to the former chief
of Dongducheon Station?
Yes.
I guess she really does get info quickly.
Of course.
She's one of the highest ranked
intelligence officers.
A while ago, she even…
MOBILE PHONE CALL HISTORY
This is Officer Kim's address.
You found him already?
That must be it.
If he was going to meet the former chief,
he would've called him beforehand.
-Those are the case files, right?
-Yes.
Look at the calls from his office phone,
not his mobile.
Do you see Uijeongbu Station?
Yes, it's here.
I think it's there.
The station where the former chief
was transferred.
"Administration Division."
UIJEONGBU POLICE STATION
When I called a while ago,
you definitely said the chairwoman
would be back soon.
No, you told me she'd be back
after the meeting.
You told me so yourself.
All right.
It must be impossible to meet
the chairwoman of Hanjo Group.
I should just visit her office tomorrow.
Will they even let you in?
They'll just stop you at the lobby.
Is it you two?
Did you ask to see me?
Are you Mr. Jeon Seung-pyo?
I'm Han Yeo-jin.
The Reformation Unit?
I'm Hwang Si-mok from the prosecution.
We have a few questions
regarding your nephew, Kim Su-hang.
Come with me.
-With that build…
-Right.
What?
I told you it wasn't me.
I'm not the one who sent him.
Why are you bringing up Song Gi-hyeon now?
That was years ago.
I'm not the one who sent him
to Segok Station.
Did you say that to Prosecutor Seo too?
-Who?
-There was someone else who brought up
what happened years ago, right?
Prosecutor Seo Dong-jae
from the Uijeongbu Office.
You talked to him on the phone
two days ago. What did you talk about?
What are you talking about?
I have about 100 phone calls a day.
I don't remember.
What did you two talk about?
Aren't you listening to me?
I don't remember!
Do you know how busy we are?
We make calls regarding budgets and…
You know, planning!
We do all kinds of work. We're busy.
We get dozens of calls a day too.
But I don't think your division
would receive that many direct calls
from prosecutors.
And I've heard you were demoted.
-Even within the Administration Division.
-Damn it!
Fine. You're right about the demotion.
But hey.
I'm still a higher rank than you,
got that?
You shouldn't be doing this…
to a fellow police officer.
I…
Why don't we go to Headquarters
if you have any problems?
Headquarters? Are you showing off?
I get it. You learned this from her.
Hey!
You work for Choi Bit, right?
Damn it. Let's not address her by name
and step out of line.
What?
We both used to be Chiefs
and I can't even call her name?
Chief my ass.
You're not even a Senior Superintendent
because you assaulted someone.
And Chief Choi
is a Superintendent General now.
If you don't mind your manners,
I'll just call you by your full name too.
You saw the news, right?
Prosecutor Seo is missing,
and we think he may have been kidnapped.
Jeez. This is unbelievable.
So you're saying…
I'm at a loss for words right now.
So are you implying that I did something
to that prosecutor?
You came here to accuse me of kidnapping
just because of the call?
You said you didn't talk to him.
Why would I do that to someone I've never
met before? Do you think I'm crazy?
Why would I kidnap him?
I'm still a part of the police force.
You sent Officer Song
to Segok Station, didn't you?
And you knew he was being bullied
and suffering from depression, right?
We were talking about some prosecutor,
and now Segok Station?
I had my doubts
about you being the culprit.
What doubts?
He did get disciplined
because of Sergeant Song,
but could it really be a motive
for murder?
Would he really have ordered
his nephew to kill Sergeant Song
when he was chief of police?
It's not enough of a motive
for him to commit murder.
I did think that the possibility
of him being the culprit
was lower than Sergeant Song's
team members.
But what if something unexpected happened?
Even as his uncle,
he didn't know his nephew was
taking bribes from local bars and clubs.
But Sergeant Song,
whom he sent there to be bullied,
found out about his nephew
and then was killed by his nephew
while investigating the bribes.
And what's worse,
a prosecutor comes to him two years later,
wanting to dig up dirt about the case.
If he knew
that his nephew was the culprit,
he would've been startled.
Because he was worried
either about his nephew
or about being caught
for being the one who ordered it.
Where were you last night?
I'll bring it, so just wait here.
And get ready to apologize to me!
He's bringing his alibi?
He's well-prepared.
-So you think he's alive?
-He'd better be.
I heard about the golden hour principle.
Why do you think the kidnapper
isn't demanding a ransom?
He might still be bleeding
somewhere even as we speak.
Let's find him.
Your brain's trying to squeeze out lies,
so it's taking blood
from the tips of your fingers.
If he locked him up somewhere,
he'd check up on him at least once.
-Are you investigating it?
-What were they about?
They'd do anything to cover it up even if
they had to be up against a prosecutor.
Is Detective Jang meeting Officer Kim?
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi