=The Quirky and The Charming=
=Episode 14=
Where's Yi Ran?
Does she really not want
to see me one last time?
She asked me to give it to you.
Please open it after you get in the car.
Thank you
for watching over her for me.
Thank you.
Take care.
(For Yi Ran)
=The Quirky and The Charming=
(Ran,)
(forgive me.)
(I have never been a good mother.)
(My weakness and selfishness)
(made me incapable
of devoting my life to you.)
(It's not that I didn't try.)
(But in this world,)
(Name: Zhang Xinmei)
(not everything)
(can be fixed through effort,)
(especially relationships.)
(People get married for happiness.)
(Name: Zhang Xinmei)
(It's the same for divorce.)
(You know)
(your father and I)
(were always fighting back then.)
(I couldn't convince myself)
(to be trapped)
(in a failed marriage)
(and let it drain both of us.)
(After the divorce, I had no home.)
(At that time,)
(Name: Zhang Xinmei)
(I had no ability)
(or the courage to take you with me.)
(I won't make excuses)
(for my failures.)
(I won't ask for your forgiveness.)
(But please never doubt
my love for you.)
(The memories of your childhood)
(have always been engraved in my heart.)
(Your first cries as a baby)
(and your first words
calling me "Mom"...)
(They're my most precious memories.)
(In my hardest times,)
(you helped me overcome)
(one hardship after another.)
(Ran.)
(I've been through it myself.)
(So I know how hard it is for a woman)
(to make her way in this world.)
(Please take this card.)
(Use the money however you want.)
(For living, for learning,
or whatever you need.)
(I will always support your decision.)
(Please give me a chance)
(to make it up for you.)
It looks like you've met your challenge.
Why are you here?
Just getting some air.
You're doing the same, right?
With so much space outside,
did you have
to come here to do that?
From the way you look,
I'd say something's bothering you.
Life, work, and relationships,
all come with struggles.
Sometimes,
they can make you feel powerless.
But as long as you take a step forward,
you'll realize
that only you can heal yourself.
Ran,
you haven't looked happy
these past few days.
Is work not going well?
No.
No?
Then what's wrong?
I saw my mom.
She's doing well.
She has a new family
and a daughter now.
Ran...
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
I always felt like
a heavy weight was pressing on my heart.
But now I finally feel lighter.
It was 2:30 AM,
and she scared people half to death.
Good thing the guest was a young
and healthy person.
If it was an older one,
they might not have survived!
What are you guys talking about?
Ran,
last night Bei Lala put
a funeral wreath in the hallway.
At 2:30 AM,
the complaint hotline
was ringing off the hook.
Bei Lala?
How did she even manage
to get something that big in here?
She's actually quite pitiful.
What happened to her?
Her dream guy is gone,
and as a goddess in people's eyes,
she is abandoned.
She won't do something drastic,
will she?
I saw her on the rooftop yesterday.
She said she just wanted some fresh air.
Do you think she wants to...
No way...
She won't do something foolish, right?
Bei Lala!
Miss Bei.
Come down. Let's talk.
Oh, it's you.
You're not just here for fresh air,
are you?
Yesterday, you told me
to take a step forward,
and I'd find a solution.
So?
So don't do anything foolish
because of a man.
Do you think I'm going to jump?
(Three years ago.)
Let's take a set of photos
of the bride and groom right here.
Hello, everyone.
Hi there.
Hello.
You're taking photos already.
You're here.
You look dashing today.
He does, doesn't he?
Three years ago today,
this was where I met him.
Come and catch me!
If you catch me, you'll get a reward!
Stop right there!
Jiawei.
Jiawei?
You always trick me.
And then?
He disappeared.
We never met again after that.
For years, I kept thinking about him.
I even did tarot readings,
imagining he was somewhere close,
breathing the same air
and watching the same sunset as me.
But now, I've decided to let go,
right here where we met.
Come in.
I thought you didn't want to see me.
You didn't answer my calls or texts.
I need your help finding someone.
A wedding planner
who stayed here three years ago.
Why? Did he owe you money?
Mr. Xiao,
this is not the time
for silly jokes.
I wasn't joking.
That's what your face says.
So, will you help me or not?
That goes against hotel policy.
I know.
With my position,
I shouldn't be asking
about a guest's private matters.
But I really want to help Bei Lala.
That's not something
you should be worrying about right now.
What you should focus on
is preparing for next month's
onboarding assessment.
Hotel service standards say
that when a guest needs help,
we should do everything
we can to help.
Hotel service standards also say
that when helping a guest,
we must first consider
if it affects the hotel or ourselves.
Do what is within your ability.
So I can't help you.
Do you know why I want to help her?
I want to help her find an answer.
Feelings shouldn't be left so vague
and unresolved.
Even if the answer
is only a ridiculous excuse,
falling out of love
or never loved at all,
it should still be clear.
A person who loves sincerely
without holding back
shouldn't be the one
who gets hurt the most.
Why is she leaving?
Boss,
did you fight?
Let's focus on work.
Beisiman just sent their feedback.
They're willing
to add 10% more investment
on top of the original amount.
But only if the terms remain unchanged.
What do you think?
I think
it's obviously a good thing.
With your capability,
meeting their requirements
within three years
should be no problem.
Since you think it's a good thing,
that must mean there's a catch.
What's the issue here?
First, think about what we have to give
to get something in return.
For a company like theirs,
do you really think they'd agree
if it weren't an equal exchange
or something even more valuable?
Do you think
Spring Sea is worth it right now?
Boss,
aren't you being a little too cautious?
With the Chairman still around,
whether our hotel survives or not
is entirely up to you.
Either way,
I don't believe in free lunches.
I'll think about it.
Then I'll head out first.
Wait.
Look into someone for me.
Who?
A wedding planner from three years ago.
We can start now.
Excuse me.
This dress is way too tight.
Can I change back into my clothes?
No, it's perfect.
Only in this outfit
can you really show off your figure.
You can start now.
It can be a flower...
It can be a tree...
This is nothing like my style.
I'm not like those streamers
who rely on makeup and padded bras
to boost their looks.
I am a singer.
Go on.
Do you take
a singer as a joke?
Girl, take my advice.
Make some money
and gain some followers first.
Once you have both,
you can do whatever you want
and say whatever you like.
These days,
only carnival gifts
are real business.
Everything else is just nonsense.
Come on, let's keep going.
Forget it.
I'd rather have no one listen
to my songs
than sing for people like you
because
you don't deserve it.
Wow, I was being nice,
and you're acting all high
and mighty now?
If you don't like it, then get lost!
Take off our clothes before you go.
I still have a few songs.
They're not finished yet.
But I put my heart into writing them.
Please listen to them.
I get hundreds of songs
like yours every month.
If it's a no, it's a no.
Music takes talent.
Don't waste your time, okay?
Hello?
Mom?
Are you busy?
No.
Did you catch a cold?
Did you take your medicine?
Yes.
I know you don't want to hear me nag.
But I also know
it's not easy being out there alone.
But look at the girls you age
around here.
They are all married.
You're not making money...
Mom,
can you not talk about this?
You're not making much money,
and you don't have someone
to take care of you.
Dreams are just a hobby for rich people,
not something ordinary folks
like us can afford to chase.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Hurry.
What's going on?
Miss.
- Are you okay?
- Miss?
Call an ambulance now.
Okay.
- Miss.
- Miss, are you okay?
Hello.
Is this Aijia Wedding Planner?
I'm calling
from Spring Sea Resort Hotel.
I'd like to ask
if you have
a wedding planner named Huang Jiawei?
Huang Jiawei?
Never heard of him before.
What about three years ago?
I don't know him.
Are you sure you call the right place?
Sorry for the trouble.
Hello.
Do you know Pan Yiyi?
Yes, I do.
She passed out outside.
Please come to the hospital.
Which hospital?
Central Hospital.
Okay, I'll be right there.
You're up. How are you feeling?
Lie down and don't move.
Where...
Where am I?
You're getting an IV at the hospital.
You passed out by the beach.
The doctor said
you have low blood sugar and anemia.
Have you not been eating proper meals?
I have been taking my meals.
I've just been busy lately
and didn't have time.
You sing all day at the music restaurant
and stream at night.
You're skipping meals and not sleeping.
Are you trying to ruin yourself?
Yi Ran.
I want...
What?
I want to eat.
I'm hungry.
Now you realize you're hungry?
Just rest.
I'll go get you some food.
Boss, we found the person
you were looking for.
Boss. Boss?
Take me to him.
Thanks for everything
these past few days.
You're welcome.
Welcome to visit us again next time.
I will come back.
I've burned my obsession away.
But the memories remain.
Wait!
I never thought I'd see you here again.
You shouldn't have left
without saying goodbye.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to hurt you.
I didn't want
to drag you down.
Not a single day has gone by
during these years
without me thinking about you.
Do you know how hard
these past years have been for me?
You can see that.
I want to hold you.
But I can't.
Do you know what love should look like?
It's when you can't do something.
But I can.
It'll be okay.
Everything will be okay.
I'll be here with you.
How did you find them?
I searched every wedding company
that worked with the hotel
three years ago.
But I couldn't find anything.
After a lot of effort,
I finally got in touch with one.
Only to discover
he was never a wedding planner.
He's Qiao Yu's friend.
They've been in touch all these years.
(Three years ago,)
(Jiawei was diagnosed with ALS)
(and cut off contact
with the outside world.)
(He's been relying on medication)
(to slow the progression.)
(But the results haven't been great.)
(A caregiver has been looking after
him all this time.)
Hello,
I am Xiao Mucheng, the Head
of the Housekeeping Department
at Spring Sea Resort Hotel.
Bei Lala has been waiting for you.
I believe you've been waiting too.
She's leaving today.
Are you willing to see her?
There's nothing to talk about.
We broke up
a long time ago.
I completely understand.
I have someone I care about too.
Sometimes,
we make decisions thinking
they're for the other person's good.
But I recently realized
that it's not always what they want.
When two people truly love each other,
they should hold nothing back.
It has been three years.
Bei Lala has been waiting
for your answer.
Why the sudden change of heart?
To the hotel,
securing valuable clients
is what benefits the hotel the most.
Is that really what you think?
If I don't say this,
how would I live up
to the cold-hearted image
you have of me?
By the way,
there's a resort project.
You should check it out.
You want me to lay low for a while?
It's a work assignment.
Besides, a lot has happened lately.
You need a break.
I'll handle everything else.
Thank you, Boss.
I never expected things
to turn out this way.
That's exactly why
this proves one thing.
Love is like a ray of light
in the darkness.
When will that light shine on me?
I was hoping Bei Lala would say
a few more words to me.
She did.
She said
your energy is as powerful
as nuclear energy.
You're bound to explode with happiness.
When did she say that?
You're being naughty,
you little mischief.
- Stop...
- You were lying to me, huh?
Stop messing around.
Let's just focus on the meal.
Here you go.
Who is it?
What are you up to now?
You passed by this shop the other day
and said their cheesecake was amazing.
So I got one for you.
- Pretty thoughtful, huh?
- I...
I'm busy and don't have much
of an appetite.
Why are you packing?
Did you finally see the true colors
of God of Plague
and decide to leave this place
of heartbreak?
I'll have your back.
Actually, our hotel and the resort
are collaborating on a project.
God of Plague asked me to check it out.
It's not that simple.
A man knows a man.
It could be a trap.
I'll go with you.
Sounds like you're the one
with ulterior motives.
You're at a risky stage right now.
I don't trust letting you go alone.
How about this?
I'll go pack right now.
I'll see you tomorrow morning. Bye!
I didn't say you could come.
Boss, something happened.
Mr. Lin Jr. came to pick Yi Ran up.
He said they were going to the resort.
What?
Bring her back right away.
No, that won't work.
Maybe I should go myself?
Yes, I'll do that.
Let's go.
Chairman Xiao.
Are you heading out?
I'm going to the resort
to check on the project.
You don't have to go
for something like that.
Just send someone.
Mr. Xiao, just let him go.
Yishu,
your team is also involved
in the resort project, right?
Then you should go together.
Okay.
We'll be back soon.
Chairman Xiao...
Go.
What are you doing here?
The company sent me
to inspect the project.
What is he doing here?
And why is she here?
Oh, hey. We meet again.
This is your solution?
Stalling me
while keeping others on the side?
I'm not! I'm here for work.
Stop making excuses.
Player.
Me? A player?
I haven't asked you yet.
Why did Lin Youjia follow you here?
Do you even see me
as your boyfriend?
Oh, so I'm your girlfriend?
If you were coming here
with God of Plague,
why didn't you tell me?
I should be asking you that.
Didn't we agree
to update each other on any moves?
What now?
We play it by ear.
Also, don't drag me down.
Same to you.
Hello, Ms. Ling and Mr. Xiao.
I'm Liu Jing, the resort manager.
I wasn't informed
that there would be this many guests.
It was a last-minute change.
Can you prepare another villa?
I'm really sorry but we're fully booked.
This villa was specially reserved
for you.
Then we'll just make do.
I won't disturb your rest.
Let me know if you need anything.
You all heard that.
That's that.
Mr. Xu, all four of them have arrived.
All right. I understand.
All four of them?
Yes.
Some things didn't go exactly
as planned.
But overall,
everything is unfolding
according to your plan.
People have to go through certain things
to understand other things.
Vincent is growing fast at the hotel.
He's already capable
of handling things on his own.
I trust he'll make wise decisions.
I'm not insisting
that he must be with Yishu.
I only want to see
whether he can stand by his choices
when faced with difficulties
and obstacles.
Small matters reveal big truths.
Are you worried
that his mind isn't fully set
and he might make a choice he'll regret?
Parents who love their children
always think ahead for them.
Do you have an extra toothbrush?
Isn't there one in your room?
I already used the disposable one once.
I brought my toothbrush.
You can use the one from this room.
Disposable toothbrushes
can be used two to four times.
(Lin Youjia)
(This God of Plague)
(is definitely up to no good.)
(Remember to lock your door.)
(I'll be downstairs.)
(Call me if you need anything.)
What now?
Do you have an extra towel?
Boss,
this isn't Spring Sea.
If you need a towel, slippers,
or a toothbrush,
you should ask customer service,
not Yi Ran.
Let me remind you again.
It's already 11 PM.
You may not need sleep, but I do.
Stop knocking on my door.
Good night.
I didn't get a chance
to say good night earlier.
Good night.
Did you
just knock on my door?
I didn't.
But I can knock now if you want.
No need.
You're still up?
Well, so are you.
I am thirsty.
I'm getting some water too.
Get some rest early.
Get in.
When opening the car door,
your face will be blocked.
Action.
Then you realize he doesn't
care about you at all.
Is that really what you think?
If I don't say this, how would I...
What did the Director say?
Just stand still.
Okay.
=The Quirky and The Charming=