Grandpa, isn't this cool?
Hey.
THE BELIEVERS 2
All right.
This is our fundraising project
for Wat Nong Khan Hospital,
a simulator game
where players help build the hospital.
You've played sim games before, right?
Oh, you guys are monks.
You probably can't play. Sorry.
Building stuff…
As all of you may know,
one pain point with donations is
once people have donated,
they often don't know
how their money is used.
But with this model,
we're creating a donation simulation
so donors can see real-time updates.
And this is the "Phoken."
This is too much.
It's like a game token.
The Phoken comes in
a few colors and styles.
Ninety-nine baht.
This one is 999 baht.
And this one is 9,999 baht.
People who buy our Phokens
can scan the QR code on the back.
It links to the website we made.
The donations can then be turned
into virtual items for the hospital.
We're making merit-making more tangible.
But for those uncomfortable
with the online process,
there is also an on-site option.
We'll build a giant Pho tree
where donors can place the Phokens.
In other words,
we'll make merit-making tangible
with both the website and the tree.
This allows us to reach all target groups,
regardless of gender or age.
The Pho tree will be the centerpiece
of the fundraising campaign.
We'll install it
at the center of the hospital.
As donations grow, this giant Pho tree
will become the largest
gold and silver Pho tree in the world.
This is the fundraising,
merit-raising plan for this megaproject
of the greatest meritorious deed.
PRESIDENT
WAT NONG KHAN HOSPITAL FOUNDATION
Personally,
I don't see the need
for something so extravagant.
The website, the giant tree, the game.
We just need people to make merit with us.
Isn't this too much?
But I think
in today's content-saturated world,
if we do things the old way,
it won't work.
You're building a huge structure
at the temple.
What about safety?
Have you considered that at all?
You know my team is professional.
We don't do lousy work.
Personally, I disagree.
Abbot, how about you?
Can we put up a screen near the Pho tree?
So the visitors can see
the images on the website.
Also, right now,
we're only targeting B2C.
If we want to reach B2B as well,
what do we do?
We'll look into it.
This is clearly a pipe dream.
Do you really trust these kids?
And the politicians are only after
their own interests. Can't you see?
Deputy Abbot.
I saw you.
You snuck out on your motorcycle,
delivering water.
Really? What's going on?
-What will happen now?
-This isn't right.
Could you bring the monk's assistant here?
This is Korn.
He's the monk's assistant.
And older brother of Deputy Abbot Kit.
I guess they don't look that similar.
Shit.
How was I supposed to know
he had a brother?
Fucking two peas in a pod.
Next time, you can ask me first.
Your project plan does sound over the top.
But in a good way. I like it.
What about cash flow?
They won't let us near temple accounts.
How about this? My company will cover
the construction costs upfront.
Here's the new total.
Are you serious?
Let's get to work.
BOON TO
CONSTRUCTION CONTRACTOR
Fuck.
We have to take a loan from her company?
It's her fucking project.
Where's our profit from Phummaram?
Seized by the cops.
Whatever.
As if I can trust you anyway.
Can I help you?
Step away from the computer.
The audit team's here to check it.
Password?
Whatever you got away with elsewhere,
don't think you can try it here.
Hey. Where are you going?
Are you running away?
I'm going to pee. Check whatever you want.
So far,
we've found nothing suspicious.
Are you done? So I can get back to work.
I can always come
to check again and again.
So don't slip up.
This way, Venerable Master.
Please come this way, Venerable Brother.
Please come this way.
-Hello. How are you?
-I'm well.
Hello.
WAT NONG KHAN FOUNDATION
Council Member?
An auspicious event should have
an odd number of monks. We invited eight.
It's okay. I know.
Another monk is on his way.
I see.
Please come this way.
After you. Please, go ahead.
Let's go inside.
Can you guide us a little?
Not even a little?
Okay, never mind. We'll figure it out.
Please join us…
HELP US BUILD
THE WORLD'S LARGEST TREE OF DHARMA
…by donating money
to help construct the gold and silver tree
to be enshrined
at our sacred Wat Nong Khan Foundation.
Building the gold and silver tree
is a great auspicious act.
It symbolizes bringing abundance…
…wealth, fortune, good luck,
and prosperity throughout life.
It doesn't matter
whether the merit you make is big or small
if your faith is pure.
All donations will contribute…
Well?
What should we do?
We've promoted it via all channels.
The tree isn't finished,
so people don't know what it'll look like.
-Will it be ready before we break ground?
-If all goes as planned, yes.
We didn't account for people
getting in our way and causing delays.
I don't need excuses. I need answers.
Figure it out.
Shit.
-Oh, hello.
-Hello.
Today is an auspicious day
with a chance to make merit.
We invite you all to grow a tree of merit
by donating money
to support the construction
of the gold and silver tree
to be enshrined
at our sacred Wat Nong Khan Foundation.
Building the gold and silver tree
is a great auspicious act.
It symbolizes bringing abundance…
Hey, kid. Want the jackpot?
If that's the winning ticket,
why don't you just keep it?
Give me the winning two digits.
Sure thing.
Right here, kid. Here you go.
-How much?
-One hundred.
May you get rich.
What do you think merit makers want?
To go to heaven.
That's half right.
But today's heaven means money.
Merit makers all hope to be rich.
To get people to donate to our tree,
we should offer more than merit and peace.
We should give back to customers.
With what?
The lottery.
DHARMA PATTANA PARTY
SETTAWUT KLAIDUANG
Quick, Aun! Get in here!
Where's Dad?
With Venerable Father upstairs.
Hey, Ae. Are you going with the family?
Where to?
They're taking Venerable Father
to a Thai temple in Switzerland in March.
Dad is so damn devoted.
He booked first class.
SETTAWUT FIGHTING COCKS
Goodbye, Venerable Brother.
Shouldn't you be at the factory?
Nope. Personal leave.
Personal leave?
To play games at home?
You're on payroll.
-The mic's picking up your voice.
-Damn it! You suck!
Yeah, yeah.
Tell the maid to serve you food.
I'm good. You go ahead.
Then why are you here?
The hospital project's a hit.
We got a lot of donors,
probably voters too.
I eat vegetarian today. No meat!
About the road construction,
have you talked to the department?
-Aun!
-Yo, whose voice was that?
Yes, Dad.
Shoot! Get in there, Aun!
-Yo, I gotta go.
-Dude!
Why are you skipping dinner?
You look like a twig.
Whatever, Dad.
-About the road, you have to talk--
-Later. We'll talk later.
Hey, Dad.
Ae gets to build a hospital.
Can I run a car tuning shop?
How many times have you failed?
The bar you just opened went bust,
and you haven't learned?
I'm buying experience.
Gotta learn some way.
-How many millions already?
-See?
You're so discouraging.
When I do nothing, I'm lazy.
When I do stuff, you never support me.
Get your factory going first.
I am. Don't talk when you don't know shit.
You're all talk, Aun.
You haven't accomplished shit.
I've seen nothing but failures.
If you're so great, you do it.
If I take over, what'll you be left with?
That car tuning shop?
Or what? Just stay home
playing games and leeching off Dad?
If my company wasn't funding your factory,
you'd be out.
-My life isn't your business.
-It's my burden.
It's 4,000 baht per month.
Two months' deposit in advance.
Electricity is eight baht per unit.
Water is a flat fee of 150 baht.
What are you studying, son?
Law.
Oh, that's great!
My son graduated from law school.
He's waiting to take the prosecutor exam.
But it's so hard.
Unpack and go down to sign the documents.
Okay.
LOTTERY DRAW DAY, NOVEMBER 16
The second, third, fourth,
and fifth prizes have been announced.
Next, we will draw
the three-digit prefix twice,
the three-digit suffix twice,
the two-digit suffix once,
and the first prize,
using another type of equipment.
And now…
PHILIP MAGIC SCHOOL
WELCOME
We will now place them inside the wheel
and invite committee members…
Hey!
You called earlier, right?
Hi there, Philip.
All right. Come on.
Come on up.
Okay.
The aforementioned equipment
will be used with ten balls,
numbered zero through nine.
They will be placed
inside a spherical container,
where they will then be mixed.
After the chairman has reviewed…
All right.
Are you ready to enter the world of magic?
Yes, I am.
Do you have a trick to switch out balls?
Balls? What fucking balls?
These ten balls
will be placed
inside an opaque spherical container.
After we've closed the container,
we'll place it
in a piece of special equipment.
Following that,
I'd like to invite the committee members
to spin the equipment so the ten numbers…
Can you draw the balls
at the Lottery Division?
Come and take this container
and open it to reveal the number inside.
LINDA YOOAMNUAY
PUBLIC RELATIONS OFFICER
What?
The lottery balls.
Rig them.
Damn it. I thought
you wanted to be my student.
Turns out you're a criminal.
Two million.
Are you crazy?
Do you really think they'd let a magician
draw the lottery balls?
-Hey!
-What?
But I can teach you.
Excuse me. Are you Kao Hom's mother?
That's me.
I'm Saint's father.
Saint talks about Kao Hom all the time.
I see.
So which elementary school do you want
Kao Hom to go to for first grade?
We hope for the Demonstration School,
but it's hard to get in.
Same with us.
But I'm lucky to have a quota spot.
I might be able to help Kao Hom get in.
But I'd like to ask you
for a small favor in return.
If you get a chance
to make merit with monks,
it's also worth finding time
to listen to Dharma.
Do you need this one? This side?
Yes. Just a moment.
Can you drive?
-No, I can't.
-Go check aisle 14.
Any computer skills?
I can use Word a bit.
Besides teaching Dharma,
what skills do you have
that would make me hire you?
Nothing else? Too ordinary.
Okay. I'll make a new one.
What now?
People filed a complaint with a lawyer,
saying the construction noises
are disturbing them.
How? My team talked to everyone.
The municipality gave us permission.
I don't know.
My job is to bring you
the lawyer's documents.
As for you,
your job is to clear things up
with those people.
One more thing.
About the construction materials,
put them all away
and move them out of the temple grounds.
Take it.
PHILIP MAGIC SCHOOL
Oh, hi there.
Philip.
-Yes?
-This is Linda.
-Hi.
-And this is Philip.
Hi.
What's your name again? I forgot.
It's Jack.
Oh, got it.
This is Wichai. He'll learn
the ball-switching trick today.
-He'll be the one who draws.
-I see.
And these are the actual balls.
LOTTERY DIVISION
Wow.
Shall we begin?
Yes, let's do it.
-I'll start with the basics.
-Okay.
-How to hold the ball naturally.
-Right.
-The hand positioning.
-Okay.
Use your thumb
and index finger to hold it.
-Like this?
-Exactly.
-Hold it like this.
-Okay.
To switch numbers,
you need practice.
I see.
Yeah, hello. What's up?
Construction's suspended.
-What?
-People filed a complaint.
Did you sort it out, you dick?
-I'm not following.
-Come back and fix this.
Fix what?
I sorted it out with the village head.
Gave him loads of money.
Then why are we getting hit?
Beats me.
Win,
I'll leave that to you for now.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Which one?
-In the black shirt.
-Hi.
-Scared the life out of me.
Son of a bitch.
Let's go.
Get on the truck.
Get on.
Yes. And sit tight.
Shit.
-Hello there.
-Hi.
-Hello.
-I'm Dear.
-I'm here for the interview.
-Oh, okay.
Please follow me this way.
Sure.
You can leave your luggage here.
Okay.
This is our retreat area.
I see.
Let's discuss the details inside.
Sure.
Any experience working in retreats?
Well… yes, I have some experience.
I see. That's good.
IMNOTDEAR:
GAME, HOW ARE THINGS WITH YOU AND WIN?
Hey.
I saw it. The world's largest Pho tree.
It's pretty badass.
Want me to donate too?
I checked it out.
The list of board members
of the savings and credit co-op.
Your dad's one of them.
The other is the lady who disappeared
with your dad from the phone shop.
The last person
got sick and died
about the same time your dad disappeared.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but two people disappeared.
And one died.
If your dad didn't run off
with a mistress,
what do you think happened?
And the chairman?
I couldn't find him.
Sombat is a common-ass name.
No last name either.
Next time,
can you give me more to work with?
You think I like meeting you here?
I don't. It's a waste of time and gas.
Okay.
You're here.
What are you doing?
I give freedom, and you do this?
What did you tell the cop?
He asked why I was there.
What did you tell him?
-About the hospital.
-Why would you talk to the cop?
-Why put us all at risk?
-What else could I do? He's a cop.
I brought you guys here to work,
not to waste time on nonsense.
Donations are still low.
The tree project is frozen.
Do you think I was joking
when I asked you to do something?
Hey! Wait!
Hey! What are you doing?
Hey!
Hey! Calm down!
Wait! Please calm down!
Let me try the lottery again.
Do you really think you can rig it?
I know a way, all right? Just calm down.
Don't make me get violent, all right?
It's a waste of time.
As for this,
I'll handle it.
Focus on what you should be doing.
Why are you putting us at risk?
You'll get us all killed!
My job's to find a way out.
What's yours, asshat?
The lotto draw's coming up. Got a plan?
I know a way.
Don't screw up.
Still talking shit
after putting us in danger?
IMNOTDEAR:
GAME, HOW ARE THINGS WITH YOU AND WIN?
Thank you so much.
-You're kidding.
-Let's grab a bite.
-Shall we?
-Ask him.
Hey, Dol!
What?
Come down.
He's been working so long.
He's so fucking calm.
-Doesn't he look familiar?
-Who does he look like?
-Like a bottle of soy sauce.
-So stiff.
-What?
-Hands together.
Dol, did you get your paycheck?
Let's go grab a bite.
You can eat dinner now.
-He can.
-Let's go.
-Go easy on him.
-Why?
Let's eat offal.
A bad man like me
Who'd be so blind to want me?
I'm only fit to be a servant
Can't even pay my bar tab
We should be singers.
Aren't you singing?
I'd rather not. I can't sing.
-Dol, one song.
-Let's hear it.
-You're too stiff.
-Or you can chant.
-Namo…
-Mo…
-You're laughing?
-With girls… What?
Looking for trouble?
-You laughed at our friend.
-You started it.
-Wanna fight? Let's go!
-Come on!
-Coughing up blood.
-In the lungs!
-Wanna try?
-Just a little.
Party pooper.
Put the beer away and order kids' cereal.
I'm done. I gotta pee. Can't hold it.
-Let's go.
-Wanna come? Let's go.
-Careful.
-Carry my junk for me.
-You okay?
-Where's the restroom?
Hey, are you a human or a giraffe?
So tall. I'm gonna shoot you down.
So? No money,
yet you still came to a place like this.
Sorry. The number you've dialed
isn't available…
Please wait.
Pay up.
Or we go to the police.
Please let me call them again.
Make it quick.
GAME_OLO:
FUCK YOU! YOU DITCHED US
WE HAVE TO GET HER A BILLION BAHT
WHERE ARE YOU?
Hello.
Dear?
Sorry to call you so late at night.
Is everything okay, Venerable Brother?
I've left the monkhood.
Something urgent came up.
I need 30,000 baht right now.
Thirty thousand baht, you say?
If it wasn't really urgent,
I wouldn't bother you.
I'll pay you back
as soon as I get the money.
What's the deal?
Do you have the money or not?
DEAR:
PLS SEND ME YOUR ACCOUNT NUMBER
"Put it on hold"?
It's not a small amount of product.
Yai, you know I'm working
on a big project right now.
I have to be careful with everything I do.
For how long?
I have to give Mr. Roj an answer.
Until the hospital's finished.
That's a year.
Does your dad know? Is he okay with it?
I want to finish it sooner.
But someone keeps getting in my way.
-Who?
-Your beloved junior.
I'll talk to him.
Don't talk. Just fix it.
I can handle my own people.
I want to get it done.
So I can import medical equipment,
medicines, and other supplies.
Actually, I need your help
facilitating this part.
I can't do it alone.
Back up! Okay, that's enough!
Stop!
Okay, you can come down.
Please go upstairs.
Careful, mind the step.
Why not just buy lotto tickets online?
That's the next step.
Hey! Get in the front!
Dad!
Here's your sticky rice with grilled pork.
2GR CHACHOENGSAO 91
LOTTERY DRAW DAY, DECEMBER 1
…into the catch tray in front.
The officials will open the opaque case
to show the next number.
Hey.
No smoking.
Okay.
…three-digit prefix prize.
The first draw…
For the first draw
of the three-digit prefix prize,
the number is…
Be a good student.
Toey. Let's go.
Mr. Wichai Thairath.
We are ready to draw the last two digits.
The two-digit suffix prize
for December 1, 2023.
The number is…
nine, one.
I want 91! Come on, hurry up!
Now! I'm counting the bills.
Here.
The number is nine, one.
Shoot! I didn't win the lottery!
SOY MILK, YOUTIAO
LOTTO FOR SALE
-How many 91 tickets do you have?
-I got five.
-What about you?
-I have three.
-Five.
-And you?
-Wait, okay?
I have five.
-Five tickets.
-Here.
Five, right?
-I have 20 tickets.
-Here.
Thank you.
-How many?
-Only one set. Hurry.
Five tickets.
Venerable Brother,
can I have toilet paper?
Need to take a dump?
Here.
Win!
Hurry!
-Go!
-He's here.
-Take it!
-Okay, guys!
-It's here!
-Quick, stand up.
Raise your hand
if you didn't get one! Okay.
Here, take it.
Keep your hands up.
Who didn't get one?
Who else? Almost gone.
-They all got one.
-If you got one, come here.
This way! Get in line!
Walk out now. Go on!
What's all that noise?
I'm gonna head out.
Come on!
Follow me!
Rich! We're gonna be rich!
Okay, walk up here!
Watch your step!
Go up there, everyone!
Come on.
Let's go.
Okay.
Get up there.
Hey, excuse me. Take it here.
Make sure everyone and the tree
are in the frame.
All right, hold it up. Okay.
Smile a little. Good. Keep smiling.
Hold it up like this. Okay.
I want three things in the photos.
First, the lotto.
Second, the Phokens.
Third, the Pho tree in the background.
I'll count for you. Ready?
Hold it up and smile!
-Okay. Ready?
-Great!
One, two, three!
2GR CHACHOENGSAO 91
Subtitle translation by: Piangpat Namtip