Take care of it.
THE BELIEVERS 2
LOCAL NEWS REPORT
This is the bustling atmosphere
at Wat Nong Khan Foundation,
where 91 villagers
from Si Racha have gathered.
They've all won
the two-digit prize with the number 91
by purchasing silver and gold
Pho leaves for merit-making.
Over there is a Likay troupe
that the villagers have paid for
to perform for three nights
as an offering of gratitude
after their lotto win.
We chartered a bus from Chonburi.
-There were 93 of us.
-Right.
But two people went to the restroom,
so they weren't counted.
-We ended up with 91 people.
-Right.
So we bought that number and won.
Wow!
But unbelievably, amid the joy,
tragedy also struck
at the Wat Nong Khan Foundation.
At around 3:00 p.m. today,
Mr. Korn Silpsomwang,
a monk's assistant at the temple,
was killed in a collision involving
his motorcycle and a pickup truck.
The police are now looking
for the truck driver who fled the scene.
And most importantly,
here's the shocking part,
Mr. Korn's motorcycle license plate
also ends with 91.
Our condolences go
to the family of the deceased.
Namaskar.
Have they found the driver?
Not yet.
The truck used fake license plates.
MR. KORN SILPSOMWANG
For your school fees.
Thank you.
-I'm sorry for your loss.
-Thank you.
The police caught the suspect
but concluded it was joint negligence.
So the driver was released
on a suspended sentence.
That's impossible.
A witness saw the truck
driving in the wrong lane.
We have to let the police
handle the investigation.
So,
what about Korn's daughter, Toey?
Who will look after her?
My mother will probably
take her back to Nong Khai.
An elderly woman and a little girl.
Can they manage alone?
I have no idea what to do.
Everything happened so suddenly.
I think you should leave
to look after your mother and niece.
Being a good layperson
and supporting your parents and family
is also considered a good deed.
What do you think?
Life is so uncertain, isn't it?
But what can we do?
Life must go on.
I believe in karma.
Good deeds will be rewarded.
Just like how evil deeds will be punished.
We lost a monk's assistant.
Win should take over for the time being,
since Game has a record.
Move all your things tomorrow, guys.
THE 91 COINCIDENCE
MONK'S ASSISTANT DIES IN HIT-AND-RUN,
LICENSE PLATE MATCHES WINNING LOTTO
Here's some water.
You read it.
-My eyesight is bad. How much?
-37,000.
-Well? Was it worth all those rounds?
-You did it too.
Pay up.
Here, Dol.
I can only give you this much now.
My mom's in the hospital, so…
When can you pay me back?
The thing is,
I have to pay back
the person I borrowed from.
Okay, next time we'll…
Yes, ma'am? Oh, okay!
-Let's go! She's calling us.
-See you!
What?
-You gotta do it under a big tree outside.
-I know!
Enough with the lecturing.
Fuck.
Nice view. How many people
can this pavilion hold?
About 20 to 30 people,
depending on how you plan to use it.
It's for a retreat.
That should work. People use it
for retreats from time to time.
What kind of retreat is it?
Well… a mix of a few things.
I see.
Our rules are no illegal drugs,
no gathering for malicious purposes,
no noise after 10:00 p.m.
We'll provide housekeepers.
If you need anything else, let us know.
I'd like to disrobe.
Everyone,
please consider me a layperson.
Are you sure, Father?
Is this how you want things to be?
Things that are too black or too white
don't mix well.
As long as someone still benefits,
I believe I must remain here.
PHRA KHRU NARES WORAKAWINTO
ABBOT OF WAT NONG KHAN FOUNDATION
That's it for today.
MUEANG PHANOM POLICE STATION
JURISDICTION MAP
Yod.
Stay.
Should I stay too?
What is it?
They're transferring you to Mae Hong Son.
I knew it.
What do you want me to do? It's an order.
Yai.
When will you stop serving those dicks?
Watch your damn mouth.
I'm trying to save your life.
Yeah?
You think you'll get away?
You'll end up like me one day.
Or even more fucked than I am.
Fuck.
Cool it, bro.
You got me transferred?
They found out.
You bastard. I gave you a chance.
You're fucking done.
You better pray I don't come back.
Our temple is still
in great need of financial support.
We humbly ask for your generosity.
Please help us in our time of need.
Our temple is still under construction…
-Hey, Game.
-What?
I know why
Ae wants to build a hospital here.
She donated drug money, then used
her company to build stuff for the temple.
Huge profit in just the first step.
Chamaiporn Klaiduang
from the Dharma Pattana Party.
Remember to vote for her
in the upcoming by-election.
Hello, Grandpa.
I'm building Wat Nong Khan Hospital.
She set up the foundation, and now
all the temple donations go through it.
The money's then sent to schools
and other organizations.
They can fake the donation numbers,
and nobody would know.
That's a shitload of money.
Enough to make her filthy rich.
-A new hospital. Please take a look.
-Sure.
May you be prosperous. Where's your dad?
Busy with work.
I'm building a new hospital,
Wat Nong Khan Hospital.
Next time you're sick,
you'll have a hospital nearby.
No need to go downtown. Nice, right?
Yes.
Goodbye.
-Delete the part about my dad.
-Got it.
People used to pay so little
to rent land around here.
OCCUPIED PLOTS OF LAND
Ae is chairperson of the foundation.
So she can rent the land out to businesses
and collect more rent.
That's probably billions yearly.
So the abbot must be in on it.
TENANT PAID AN ADDITIONAL 50,000 BAHT…
WATTHANA, NATTASIT, CHAMAIPORN, KORN
Even we know.
VERIFIED BY:
ABBOT PHRA KHRU NARES WORAKAWINTO
How could he not?
Get the abbot to sign the disbursement
papers for the new Pho leaves.
Why me?
It's my day off.
What?
DHARMA PATTANA PARTY
Can you hold your hand up?
One, two, three.
-This one's nice.
-Got any of me smiling more?
Should we make small-sized prints
of this one to hand out?
Do as you see fit.
Anything else on my schedule?
Today, you have to go to…
a boxing stadium.
-What time?
-At 8:00 p.m.
Okay. There's still time.
-This one too.
-Okay.
Ms. Ae, someone's calling.
Excuse me.
Hello?
What do we do?
All of you were here.
Did none of you try to stop him?
Should I call an ambulance?
Are you fucking stupid?
I'm sorry, boss.
Call Dr. Chamrat.
Yes.
Hi, Ae.
Hello.
Venerable Brother, this is Pond.
He'll help oversee your brand image
as your manager.
Namaskar.
Blessings to you.
Ae gave me homework.
To start, I drafted a strategy.
I think for a monk to become
nationally famous overnight,
we need to create a brand that's clear,
strong, and focused on one point.
The wait is over
for the Lightweight World Championship!
In the blue corner,
Emerald Bullet C. Wattana Gym.
The fastest way to become a phenomenon
is to use an idol
that everyone in the country knows.
Sadhu.
To leave a lasting impression,
you need to create your signature.
Fight!
And let everyone see
what your remarkable virtues
are capable of.
And then,
you just wait
and see.
The idol everyone has faith in
will do the job.
Then comes the "wow" moment
when your spiritual powers are proven.
And finally,
the idol's victory
will also be your victory.
The winner is Emerald Bullet!
May I interview you, Venerable Brother?
Venerable Brother, may I interview you?
Venerable Brother!
Do you think the win by knockout was
because of your virtues or his skills?
I'd like you to think of a sailboat
in the middle of the sea.
For a boat to sail in any direction,
it partly depends on the wind.
But the other part,
we can control
by setting the sail ourselves.
Luck is like the wind.
But a person's life
cannot rely on luck alone.
We must also put in effort.
We have the power to steer the boat,
to turn it left or right.
You could say
life is a combination of both.
Some might think
it's all about encouragement and morale.
Others may believe
it's the monk's sacred power.
WAT NONG KHAN TEMPLE FOUNDATION
You know, don't you?
Father Kiw died because of Ekachai.
Well…
When I went to see Father Kiw
to talk about Tang,
Father Kiw pointed
to a picture of a child.
And I think
that child is probably Ekachai.
What about Tang? Was that Ekachai too?
DHARMA GUIDES LIFE, FREES THE MIND
FROM SUFFERING, AND LEADS TO NIRVANA
MONK EKACHAI ABHIJAVO
DPT
DHARMA PATTANA PARTY
-Use this photo.
-Okay.
Blur out the background.
Sorry, the number you have dialed
is not available at this time.
Is this your daughter?
Yes, it's her.
She studied business in the US.
She's working there now.
Come by my quarters tomorrow
to pick it up.
Father, can't you just sign it now?
I need to go through it first.
Sure.
-Excuse me.
-Yeah?
Can I have a cigarette?
How do you know I have one?
That's my last one.
And the lighter too?
Sure. Here you go.
I've been fucking dying for one.
Haven't smoked in three days.
So are you dressed like that
to practice Dharma?
Yeah.
I dreamed of a huge tree
three nights in a row.
When I saw the tree on the news,
it was just like my dream.
I drove from Chonburi right away.
And got here.
Can you believe it?
I hadn't even made it home
when someone paid me back
ten million right away.
My business was in a slump,
and it fucking got back on track.
What business do you do?
Here.
For the cigarette.
I already used some.
I don't know if you mind.
Actually,
I came here to fulfill a vow.
I didn't know practicing Dharma
would be this hard.
I should've vowed to run naked instead.
Hello.
Yes.
I got them. Beauty Beauty Cosmetics.
This new lip balm's a total hit
and super hot right now.
I got three
because I was afraid they'd sell out.
I missed out on it last time.
But this new peach scent, it's like…
Let's see just how soft
and fragrant it is.
The packaging is nice,
easy to open, and cute.
This new peach scent is perfect.
It's super cute.
Everyone, look at this, the juiciness,
the glow, the shine. It's just…
Isn't it great?
Here, I'll swatch it on my lips.
It's easy to use
and doesn't smudge on your hand.
Hi.
This way, please.
Thank you for coming.
We're just meditating, right?
Yes. You can get changed first,
and we'll go over the details.
Meditation
is not peace.
But meditation is stability.
We practice the mind
by noticing where it wanders.
When the mind wanders, notice it.
When the mind wanders to the bottle,
notice it.
When you notice it,
the movement stops.
The mind will become stable again.
Use your breath as an anchor.
Breathe in.
Be aware.
Breathe out.
When the mind wanders,
and we notice it immediately,
awareness will arise.
Thank you.
And tomorrow,
what do you want me to do?
Another sitting session?
Is there anything else?
Like, a different style of meditation?
I'm not sure.
But
maybe we could try walking meditation.
Okay, let's do that.
I'll prepare the area and…
Outdoors is probably better, isn't it?
Dol.
When did you disrobe?
A while ago.
What about you, Dear?
Did you move here?
Well, something like that.
I want to try running my own business.
What time am I leaving on Wednesday?
I have work in the morning.
Oh, I booked you the earliest flight.
Here's your key.
See you in the morning.
You have a scheduled service
this Friday at 10:00 a.m.
Look,
we only need the top-tier people
in the country, the VVIPs.
This is a waste of time.
All right.
Well, I'll look more into it.
But it'll take a while.
Getting access to A-listers
is not that easy.
Remember this.
We don't need a million people
donating 100 baht each.
We only need ten people
to donate ten million.
ABBOT NARES'S RESIDENCE
-Hello.
I really appreciate you coming to help.
Thanks.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
There you are.
Come on, give me an update.
How are things going?
You can talk. They're all our people.
Here, see for yourself.
Looks okay.
But the growth is still a bit slow.
-Right.
-I'm not blaming you.
I'm here to help.
I have a plan to get us
to one billion baht faster.
I asked Pond to contact
ten boys' love series actors
to ordain here during the New Year break.
Monk Ekachai will be the ordaining monk.
It'll make good content.
Game, you don't look well.
Is something on your mind?
If you're stressed or unhappy,
you can ordain with those kids.
It can remove bad luck.
Advertise this on his page.
His followers might be interested
in joining the New Year event.
It can help boost donations.
Sure, Ae.
I have to thank you guys.
I got this idea from you two
when you put it all together
with Monk Dol.
Oh, Ple.
What should we eat for lunch?
You've had nam prik and boiled vegetables
for the past few days.
Anything you want?
-Want to go to the market?
-Yeah.
Good idea.
We can buy something to cook for dinner.
I'll drive.
Oh, Win?
How did you get here?
I'm hungry. Got any food?
You just got here,
and you're hungry already?
I didn't cook.
Let's go out, then.
I'll drive you guys.
Let me pack up.
It's fine. Let's just eat at home.
-Yeah.
-Oh.
I'll see what's in the fridge.
Ple, can you hang the rest of the laundry?
Sure, Auntie.
Hey, what about minced pork omelette?
Mom.
What?
Is she with you all the time?
Yeah.
Never out of sight.
I usually go to the market alone,
but she insists on driving me.
Like I'm an old lady
who can't take care of herself.
Where does she sleep?
I let her sleep in your room.
But if you're staying tonight,
sleep in my room.
I'm not staying.
What meal is this?
Breakfast.
See?
You're going to get a stomach ulcer.
Oh, are you done?
I'm out of clothespins.
-Could you find some more for me?
-Oh, sure.
Let me show you something.
In here,
I have everything.
I can take care of her.
Or kill her.
It's your choice,
Win.
Ple.
-Here you go.
-Yes, Auntie.
TRAI BURIN TEMPLE ORDINATION HALL
ORDINATION HALL DONORS
1. MP SETTAWUT KLAIDUANG: 50,000,000 BAHT
KANNIKAR PARANSAKUL
AUGUST 26, 1966 - NOVEMBER 11, 2005
What are you doing?
DHARMA PATTANA PARTY
This area's full.
If you want a spot, go over there.
Where's the undertaker?
I'm the undertaker.
I thought undertakers were old.
Oh, my grandfather died last year,
so I had to take over.
You keep staring.
Want some?
You're here on your own?
Yeah.
It's lonely being an undertaker.
Not many people want to talk to me.
Yeah. Try this.
This temple is fucking strange.
It's huge, but not many people come.
The abbot doesn't care
about these petty things.
He has powerful, high-ranking sponsors.
Some of their Kathin
and Pha Pa donations are huge.
Are you a vote-broker?
What vote-broker?
People like me are only in it
for free T-shirts.
So he owns the whole district?
Yeah.
But his son's a complete screwup.
He's done so many drugs,
his brain's fried.
Karma for rich people.
Their kids are fuckups.
But he's a good man.
A devoted Buddhist.
He's done a lot to develop this place.
Pulled strings
to get the temple road built.
That crematorium's his.
That wall too.
The people inside the wall,
are they his too?
I wouldn't know.
Bathroom's inside.
Outside is fine.
DONATED TO TRAI BURIN TEMPLE
BY MR. SOMBAT KLAIDUANG AND FAMILY
DEDICATED TO THEIR KARMIC CREDITORS
Thank you.
This is for your time.
You take some of it
as payment for my debt.
I already did.
There's 50,000 left over.
That much?
Please take it.
If it weren't for you, Monk…
If it weren't for you, I'd be in trouble.
It's okay.
I don't usually charge
for teachings anyway.
Hello?
Oh.
Yes. Sure.
Subtitle translation by: Piangpat Namtip