Ha..
Bastard..
That bastard..
Chew... up..
You piece of trash
Sigh..
Huh?
It's pretty Jaehee
Another glass, please
What are you saying..
If I drink too, who's going to take you home?
Come on, drink alone?
That's no fun..
I'm disappointed
It's not even a fun atmosphere today
What's up today?
Minjae..
Cheated on me
What?
He said he was busy with exams
Why did he cheat with another girl at the academy?
Ah..
So?
What do you mean so?
Of course..
I begged him
Ah, really..
Why beg?
I really begged him pathetically
That I would do better
Not to leave me
Holding onto his pants
I begged so pathetically
But Minjae wanted to break up
Hey, why are you taking my drink?
You really... never listen to me, do you?
What?
Since he started changing academies
Didn't I say something was off?
He said he was studying
But instead of studying
He was hanging out at PC rooms
Didn't I say something was up?
You did..
I said he looked like a weasel, didn't I?
Hey, don't criticize his looks
He's quite cute and delicate looking
You still say that after what happened?
Ah, seriously..
Why are you so bad at judging guys?
What?
You're not a trash collector
Hey
Don't talk like that
Minjae was nice at first too
I'm not an idiot
Why would I collect trash?
What do you know about love?
I'm leaving
Don't follow me
Ah!
Are you okay?
Can't you get up?
I think I sprained it
It's swollen here
I'm fine
I hate you. Go away
Ah
Okay
I'm sorry
Huh?
Calm down
I was too harsh
Do this quickly
Why?
You..
What perfume do you wear?
I don't wear perfume
I see
Can you get up?
Ah, it's cold
Cold packs help right after a sprain
Bear with it a little
Why have you been staring at me?
Huh?
Nothing
But..
Yeah?
Why did you like him so much?
Well..
Just..
Because he was nice to me?
I'm nice to you too
Huh?
Even at school
I showed you all my homework
Bought you bread
Wasn't I the nicest to you?
Yeah, you were
Can I take a shower?
Yeah, go ahead
Want to shower together?
Gross, what are you saying
Stop crying in front of me
Huh?
When you cry..
I want to hug you
Are you going to avoid me?
You..
Do you like me?
Are you asking because you don't know?
Jaehee, wait
Huh?
I also..
I think I like you
Are you awake?
Sorry
Hey
I haven't brushed my teeth yet
It's okay
I haven't brushed mine either
Do you know?
What?
You have really long eyelashes
And a really high nose
Why didn't I notice?
You always say I'm pretty
Were you just saying that?
No
I just never looked at you so closely
Do you know?
What?
Your lips are really soft
Your tongue is really soft too
You're saying weird things in the morning
I want to sleep for 5 more minutes
Okay
Aren't you answering?
Who is it that you're not answering?
What?
You haven't blocked him yet?
When would I have had the time?
Want me to do it?
No
If I don't answer, he'll hang up
Why?
Yeah
It's Jae-hee
I heard you broke up with Hye-soo
Why are you calling in the morning?
Hey, stop it
If you cheated, just quietly disappear
Before I really grab you and beat you up
What are you doing!
What are you doing?
Why are you still hesitating?
It's not hesitating
It's obvious
It's clear that you're still shaken by one call from him
It shows that you're still shaken by his call
Hey, Yoo Jae-hee
Who are you to tell me what to do?
What?
Even though you're my friend
I've been with Min-jae for over a year
Do you think it's easy to end it like that?
What made it so easy for him to cheat on you?
What?
Don't be mistaken
He's not sincere with you
Are you stupid?
You said you liked me
Isn't that enough?
Why are you wavering?
Yeah
I like you
As a friend
What, a friend?
Don't exaggerate
I only think of you as a friend
I'm sick, buy me some medicine
I can't go now, I have a test tomorrow..
I can't walk
Hye-soo
Yeah
I bought some medicine
Take the medicine
You'll feel better soon
Get some more sleep
How did you come?
How else
I was worried about you so I came home
With such a high fever
You should have called an ambulance
Or called me
How could I call you
I have no face to show you
At least you know you have no face to show
I'm glad
That I found you
I'm sorry
For what?
Just
For everything today
It's okay, just lie down again
Stop talking
Lie down next to me
I'm cold
Hold me
Jae-hee
Yeah?
Why do you like me?
Um..
Kind and
Innocent and
Something..
Feels like I need to protect you?
Is that really liking you?
Not just feeling sorry?
What?
Why are you pitiful?
Always meeting weird guys
Getting dumped and crying
Right?
So you thought I liked you?
Actually
I like you because you're pretty
You're so pretty
I'm weird
Hm?
I feel tingly from head to toe
My heart is beating too fast
Is it because of a fever?
How about now?
It's gotten worse
Take a picture of me.
Okay.
Pretend you're looking somewhere else.
Naturally.
Like this?
Yes, that's right.
As if you're lost in thought.
Good.
Think of a funny story I told and laugh.
It's so funny.
Did it turn out well?
Yes.
Awesome.
They all turned out well.
I took it without a filter.
You look prettier without the filter.
Oh, Yoo Jae-hee.
Come here.
Let's take a picture together.
Hey, someone is watching.
So what?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Congratulations on your acceptance -UBC Admissions-
What is it?
Ah.
Actually, I've been preparing to be an exchange student.
So?
I got a text saying I was accepted.
Isn't that a good thing?
Then why do you look like that?
I'm not going anyway.
I've decided not to go.
Why?
Just because.
Aren't you hungry?
Should I buy you a cake?
It's really hard to get accepted, right?
You worked hard and got accepted, so why not go?
Just because.
It costs a lot of money to go.
Don't worry because I'm not going.
Why is mom making a fuss when I'm not going?
Plans can change.
Why feel sorry for what you prepared?
Even if you go, it won't be much of a credential.
I'll look for something else to do here.
Stop worrying.
Jae-hee.
Yes?
Exchange student.
I think you should just go.
I said I'm not going.
The school you got accepted to is really good.
I'm sure it will be good for you if you go.
Why are you doing this?
I already decided not to go.
So why? When?
Ah, that...
Don't tell me...
Are you not going because of me?
No, it's not that.
I knew it.
You're not going because of me, right?
What if it's because of you?
Is it wrong?
Yes, it is.
Why waste such a good opportunity because of me?
I'm wasting it because of you.
Because it's you.
Why are you doing this?
What?
If I don't go, it would be good for you too, right?
We can go on more dates.
You don't trust me, do you?
What?
You're worried that I'll meet someone else if you leave.
That's why you're not going, right?
Because there's still no trust between us.
I know you're doing this.
But this is not right.
Don't postpone your plans because of me.
I feel pressured.
Pressure?
You and I are on different paths.
I'm not even attending school.
You're smart and have a lot to do.
I don't want to be a bad influence on you.
Does this make you feel pressured?
That's not what I meant.
You really don't know how I feel.
So it is burdensome.
Honestly, I think you're right.
I'm worried about leaving you here alone.
I worry you might contact your ex because you're lonely.
Or that you might drink and cry again,
and end up with another guy.
Are you done talking?
Why?
Are you confident?
Even after showing me that side of you?
I'll go.
Oh.. the smell of alcohol.
I hate you.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I spoke too harshly.
I don't know..
Don't try to brush it off.
You caught me?
I said I'm sorry.
What?
So what are you going to do?
I'm not going this semester.
I'll spend this semester with you.
I'll go next semester.
Really?
Yes.
I already talked to the school.
Don't worry.
Even if you cry and tell me not to go then, I'll go.
I won't cry.
I'm sorry too.
For what?
For saying it was a burden.
I felt bad for having a negative impact on you.
But you...
Why do you look pretty even when you're angry?
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
You look like a goldfish.
Ah...
I have to go to work.
Is it that time already?
Looks like it.
When are you going home?
Me?
Should I not go?
Want to stay at home?
Yeah.
I have to take the bus for an hour.
I'm really tired.
Then do your homework at home
and sleep if you're sleepy.
I'll be back.
Take care.
I'm back.
You're back?
Yeah.
Wow.
What's this? Is this our house?
An elf must have come by.
What? When did you clean everything?
I did it quickly.
Are you tired?
Yeah.
Night shifts are so exhausting.
So many difficult customers.
Good job. Did you eat?
I did.
Wasn't cleaning hard?
Not at all.
Should we
live together?
What?
The school isn't too far.
Hmm...
It's hard to match our schedules.
If we live together, we can see each other more often.
I think it would be nice.
Oh.
And you,
How about going back to school?
School?
Yeah, it's too wasteful to spend your time like this.
I shortlisted some schools.
Your grades aren't bad,
So there are many places you can go.
How about this one?
It's close.
The tuition isn't expensive.
Jaehee, I'm not going to school.
Why not?
These days, cyber universities are good.
No, Jaehee.
I'm not going to school.
I'll be fine without going.
What's fine about it?
You might think it's okay now because you're young,
And you have some money saved up from part-time jobs.
But we won't be in our twenties forever.
Will you still be working part-time jobs in your thirties?
What's wrong with that?
What?
What's wrong with working part-time jobs forever?
I may be like this now,
But if I find something I want to do later,
I can do something else then.
To do what you want later,
You at least need to graduate from college.
That way, it'll be easier for you to choose later.
No, I said I'm not going.
Just because you want to work for a big company,
Does that mean I have to do the same?
That's not what I meant.
Do you want to live with me?
So I have to match your level?
There you go again.
You know that's not what I meant.
Sigh...
Alright, let's stop.
I'm tired too.
Do you have a lot of homework left?
Huh?
A little.
Why?
Then can I
Go meet a friend nearby?
A friend?
Who?
Someone you don't know.
I have a friend you don't know?
Yes, of course.
The ones I worked with at the buffet before.
Okay.
I'll be back.
What's this?
Why hasn't there been any contact?
Hello?
Yeah.
Where are you?
Why aren't you coming?
I'm here at the bar with my friends~!
Did you drink?
Yeah! Just a little!
Did you finish your homework?
Yeah.
I finished it.
You should at least tell me if you're going somewhere.
Sorry. Do you want to join?
No.
I'll go to your place first then.
Okay, I'll be back soon!
You weren't sleeping?
Don't you have work in the morning?
Yeah.
Right.
But how can you drink so much?
Oh my...
Are you my mom?
Why do you keep nagging?
It's fine.
You don't like me, do you?
What?
Always working part-time, hanging out, drinking,
Living like a loafer, it frustrates you, right?
I know everything.
It's all written on your face.
I've never said that.
What's written?
You want to live with me.
Right?
That's because...
I like you.
Do you think we can live like this together forever?
What do you mean?
If we like each other?
Oh, you're so smart...
You
Later, when you get older,
You'll be pressured to get married.
Can you endure that?
What will you say?
I'll just say I'm a non-marriage advocate.
So let's say you live with me.
Working part-time jobs all the time,
Eventually, you won't even be able to do part-time jobs.
Can you handle that?
That's why I keep telling you to go to school.
The point is different.
You're trying to change me
To keep me by your side.
I'm not going to change.
As you know,
My world is narrower than yours.
That's who I am.
What will you do?
Will you quit now?
What?
Are you serious?
Yes.
You know the saying "truth comes out when you're drunk," right?
I'm telling you with courage.
Won't you regret it?
No.
You're amazing, really.
Why are you always so confident and proud?
Do you think I'm easy because I like you more?
You have so many ways to hurt me.
Thanks to you, I've had a good experience.
Thank you.
If you cry...
I want to hug you.
I'm glad
That I found you.