(panting)
(groans)
(heartbeats rapidly)
(foreboding music)
(finger snaps)
("You Make Me" playing)
(foreboding music)
MINHU: Hong Yesool!
Damn it.
(Minhu panting)
You didn't pick up your phone!
What are you doing here by yourself?
Why are you worried about me?
I thought we decided to break up.
You're going to keep this up?
(breathes heavily)
Let's go. Let's go and talk.
What are you doing?
(theme music)
EPISODE 09
YESOOL: Mr. Cha, that hurts.
Please slow down.
Let go! I said, let go of me!
(panting)
How did you even know I was there?
Do you have a GPS on me or something?
Are you really going to break up with me?
You wouldn't listen to me,
and you wouldn't even let me explain.
Did you see something about me, by chance?
I didn't see anything.
You're the one who kissed another woman.
(foreboding music)
What's wrong?
YESOOL: Are you sick?
You've got cold sweat...
Are you all right? Should I call for help?
No. I need to take my medicine.
(panting)
Medicine?
(breathes heavily)
(light music)
Do you have a serious illness?
You had a lot of pill bottles
in your room, too.
Do you have an illness
you can't tell me about?
Where does it hurt?
I just...
collapse easily.
YESOOL: What?
Is it like anemia? Feeling dizzy?
No.
I just collapse when I kiss someone.
(stammers)
What?
What's that supposed to mean?
You collapse when you kiss someone?
You see the future when you kiss someone.
I'm like that. Just like you.
And...
I'm about to tell you one more thing...
you'll find hard to believe.
YESOOL: I'm a little stunned right now.
Yes, I understand.
But that's how I am.
So, you really feel better
when we're like this?
MINHU: Yes.
If I hear your heartbeat
or hear your chatter,
then I feel even better.
No way.
If you want to hold my hand,
just say that.
Why is he saying such a weird thing
when he's sick?
You can choose not to believe me,
but it's true.
Should I call Oh Seungtaek
and have him confirm?
Dr. Oh knows about it, too?
Well...
is there such an illness
where you get sick if you kiss someone?
I mean, we've kissed
so many times thus far.
Then were you sick every time we kissed?
(whimsical music)
(gasps)
(rain pattering)
No way.
(Yesool breathes deeply)
Wait.
-Hey...
-Don't...
Don't scream.
That's right.
Mr. Cha did seem a little off then.
(light music)
But he was fine then.
I said I'm okay if you're with me.
We were together that day.
I do find this a bit ridiculous, but...
So is this what you meant
when you said you'll explain everything?
And Ms. Oh Jiyoung knew all of this too?
Jiyoung is the daughter of the doctor
who's treating me.
I've been like this
ever since I was young.
Jiyoung also knows
that my pain is relieved...
when you're with me.
YESOOL: That's why Oh Jiyoung
said that to me then.
(sighs)
Then you should've just said so.
Why didn't you tell me
and cause me to misunderstand?
I was going to tell you,
but you wouldn't hear me out.
I can't believe Jiyoung kissed you
just to find that out.
Was it...
true?
You said you were swayed
by Director Lee earlier.
Is that true?
Well...
it's not that I was swaying.
I just missed my timing to respond to him.
(sighs)
But seriously, what is this?
How come you feel better
when you're with me?
Why do you feel better
when you hold my hand?
Why is it that when we both kiss...
(gentle music)
(sighs)
(gentle music fades)
(Yesool screams)
MINHU: Hong Yesool!
Damn it.
(light music)
Please look for a black NFC vehicle.
It's a rental from JJ.
The suspect covered up the license plate,
so it's likely that he turned off
the vehicle black box too.
But you never know. Please check and see
if there remains any recordings.
Gosh, the Privacy Act
is difficult to get around...
Besides, you're not even the victim.
I think this case is related
to case number 2022-000832,
that the Seoul Jungdaemun Police Station
is investigating.
Please check and get back to me.
Sure.
(sighs, mutters)
(phone beeps)
Mr. Cha.
You really do seem better.
Does it make sense
that you recovered overnight?
You're not messing with me,
are you, Mr. Cha?
MINHU: I'm fine.
Are you all right? You seemed to be having
a nightmare early this morning.
Oh, really?
I had no idea.
That keeps happening lately.
Including what happened last night,
has anything strange
happened to you lately?
Like someone following you
around or something?
Yes, there is.
Really? Who is it? How tall is he?
What does he look like?
You, Mr. Cha.
What?
You keep following me around
like you did last night.
You keep following me.
(playful music)
I'm sorry about...
yesterday.
Saying let's break up...
and not picking up your calls.
It's okay if we argue.
Just don't say we're breaking up.
Also, don't dodge my calls like that.
But...
I didn't like...
that you kissed Ms. Oh last night.
I could say the same thing.
I don't like how you
and Director Lee Pilyo
keep getting involved over everything.
Should we make up?
(soft music)
Don't ever say you want to break up.
I'll really get mad.
Well, you usually get angry easily anyway.
Come on.
-You really want to see me get angry?
-No.
(both chuckle softly)
My goodness.
(quirky music)
No one's here, right?
So what if there is?
YESOOL: Are you crazy?
(quirky music)
(gasps)
(light music)
PILYO: We're here to go over
everything for our shoot today.
I didn't know you'd be here too, Ms. Oh.
Mr. Cha, I'm sorry,
but could I join you guys later?
Since I bumped into Ms. Oh,
I can explain why scene 2B was omitted.
Yes, please come this way...
We have a lot to shoot today,
so I have to explain...
-(grunts)
-YESOOL: Gosh! Seriously!
What are we going to do now?
What do you mean? Is there a problem?
Do I know you?
What happened to the guy
who wanted to keep his personal life
separate from his work?
What's the problem?
Those two already know we're dating,
and they're outsiders.
Besides, we're not on the clock right now.
What's the issue here?
I mean...
(sighs)
Whatever. I'm leaving.
-(Jiyoung sobbing)
-(somber music)
(sighs deeply)
I think you'll make it to Cannes.
Who said Oh Jiyoung couldn't act?
Who said you're a terrible actor?
You'll do a great job
with your crying scenes today.
(sobbing)
Please don't cry.
Your eyes will get puffy.
We're almost ready to shoot.
Director Lee, your ex is with another man.
Doesn't it bother you?
They were together
because of the meeting this morning.
And I was on my way there.
Don't make me laugh.
A meeting?
You had only two sandwiches and drinks.
But didn't Minhu
look perfectly fine back there?
Didn't he look cool?
Excuse me?
He looked healthy, too.
So it's true.
It must be true.
Oh, no...
(sobbing)
Gosh, stop crying.
Your makeup won't go on well.
I have to get ready for the shoot.
Be sure to come out on time, okay?
And make sure to eat that, too.
Please.
(sobbing)
(wailing)
(sighs deeply)
(sobbing in distance)
She's driving me crazy.
Let's do a bit more.
-Mr. Cha, put it in the right place.
-Could you look at the placement?
(light music)
(gasps)
(exhales deeply)
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR: How's the sound?
Director.
We have some background noises
like waves since we're outdoors.
We'll edit it out later.
We'll take that into account.
EOMJI: What a spectacular lovers' quarrel.
Fighting into the night
and sleeping in your boyfriend's room.
Coming back to the room this morning.
It's not like that.
You always say that.
Mr. Cha texted me,
saying you're sleeping in his room.
EOMJI: And you say not to worry?
Be quiet.
Look, you're being shy. You're being shy.
You're really being shy about it.
(light music)
Director Lee, how much longer
do we have to wait for Ms. Oh?
If she takes any longer...
We'll have to get
other actors' scenes first.
-Give me the storyboard.
-Okay.
(sighs)
(car approaching)
MANAGER : Hello.
Hello.
(soft music)
-EOMJI: Hi, Ms. Oh.
-HAIRSTYLIST: Hello.
-MANAGER: Hi there.
-STYLIST: Hello.
Over here.
Get a nice close-up shot of me
at this angle.
My left side is especially prettier.
(chuckles)
Thanks for the sandwich.
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR: Let's get ready.
Let's get ready, everyone!
Ms. Oh, you'll see it on the schedule.
We're going to shoot
all the way to scene 13 in the AM.
Were you with Minhu all through the night?
He told you everything, didn't he?
And now he's feeling fine
because of you, right?
Yes.
It's hard to believe,
but apparently, it's true.
(sighs)
Gosh, you two.
What's with you guys?
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR:
All right, please standby.
We'll get the cameras rolling soon.
(bright music)
(in English)
Cut! Cut!
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR: Cut!
They're way out of the frame.
Why didn't you mark the direction
for the actors here?
My apologies.
Mark it up here.
PILYO (in English): Ready.
-ASSISTANT DIRECTOR: Ready!
-PILYO: Action.
Cut, let's do it again.
We're going again!
Let's do it more dynamically.
(finger snapping)
(finger snapping echoing)
(foreboding music)
Okay. Let's set up for the next scene.
Okay. Let's set up
for the next scene, everyone!
Let's take five and start setting up!
Yes, sir!
PILYO: You got all the inserts
for the car interior, right?
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR:
Let's set up for the next scene!
Yesool.
Did anything happen
after you went back to your room?
No, why?
Nothing. After the shoot,
let's go and ship everything together.
Be sure to pick up my calls.
(mellow music)
(sighs deeply)
(in English)
Ready. Action.
(all grunt)
-STYLIST: Jiyoung!
-HAIRSTYLIST: What happened?
My goodness.
-Jiyoung!
-Are you okay?
-Let me see.
-HAIRSTYLIST: Are you okay?
-EOMJI: Are you all right?
(indistinct chatter)
-MANAGER: Does it hurt there?
-HAIRSTYLIST: My goodness.
It's swollen.
MANAGER: Get a first-aid kit.
What do we do?
I'll spray it. It'll be cold.
JIYOUNG: Hey, not too much.
What do we do about the shoot?
Hey, that's not the problem. She's hurt!
Are you okay, Jiyoung?
MANAGER: I think we need to spray it
down here, too.
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR:
The previous take isn't too bad.
What should we do, Director Lee?
Everything else is fine,
but we need a couple more
of the knee shots.
I don't think that's going to happen.
Ms. Oh can't even walk right now.
I think we should change the storyboard,
so we only film her upper body.
Then what if we
use someone else for the knee shots?
Director Lee...
while I was in college,
I've worked as a body double part-time.
I also look pretty good from the back.
I'm sorry.
There's a difference in length a bit...
-What length...
-The length of your hair. Your hair.
Right, the hair.
-Here's the dress.
-Okay.
(sighs deeply)
My goodness.
Oh.
Director Lee.
PILYO (in English): Ready.
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR: Ready!
PILYO: Action.
(cheerful music)
Okay, let's get a shot from another angle.
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR:
We're doing another angle!
PILYO (in English): Cut.
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR: It's a cut!
PILYO: Let's do it again.
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR: We're doing it again!
(waves crashing)
We had a bit of a delay,
but I think the flights for the staff
and the boat for the vehicle
and the equipment
will go as planned without any changes.
How much longer
are you going to keep that on?
Well, it's not like I want to keep it on.
They said we might need
to shoot some additional shots.
Change out of it
as soon as you're done standing by.
Pardon?
Everyone's staring at you
because you're too gorgeous!
(ominous music)
What's gotten into him now?
PILYO: Follow them with the camera,
then when we pan out, the father...
Wait. Let's take a three-minute
break and resume.
-Sorry?
-Please put away the equipment
for a bit, too.
And move the barricade as well.
All of a sudden? It's the last scene.
Uh...
I think we'll have an emergency situation.
What are you talking about?
I need to fix my makeup.
I'll be back.
HAIRSTYLIST: Hold onto me, Jiyoung.
-Excuse me, please let us pass.
-Passing through.
-Please go inside.
-Oh, okay.
Everything's set up...
Let's take a break.
What the heck?
Wait. Wait a second.
Jeez.
(siren blaring in distance)
What, what is this?
(suspicious music)
(siren blaring continues)
(whooshing)
How did you know about that?
Did you hear that?
Uh, well...
(chuckles awkwardly)
Is Mr. Cha bionic or something?
How did he hear something we'd hear
after three minutes?
I just checked the mic,
and that didn't even catch it.
-I know!
-Those mics catch a fruit fly buzzing.
(Sanggoo laughs)
We're not even shocked anymore.
It's not the first time.
This is how good we are. Right, sir?
Gosh.
(gasps)
What if he's listening to us right now?
Jeez, what are you saying?
(quirky music)
We'll get ready for the last scene. Yes.
-Here.
-(applause)
Let's start shooting.
Jiyoung, it's the last scene.
We're doing the last one.
Okay.
Let's go.
(light music)
Congratulations.
(in English)
Cut. Okay!
Good job, everyone.
Good job, everyone!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Shoes, shoes.
HAIRSTYLIST: It hurts, huh?
MANAGER: Your left foot first, slowly.
-MINHEE: Thank you.
-SANGGOO: Good work.
(waves crashing in distance)
Great work.
Thank you, Director Lee.
You looked so beautiful today.
I can't believe I left the ring
back in my room.
It would have been perfect
with that dress.
Stop rambling. So you wanted to say?
This morning...
I was totally craving
some seafood noodles this morning.
You know the place we went to
whenever we came to Jeju?
The owners loved us. Remember?
-Do you want to go there later...
-It's not there anymore.
The owner lady went to Seoul
and opened up another noodle house.
When was the last time you were there?
(chuckles awkwardly)
Then do you want to go
to that place in Hamduk...
That cafe became an auto repair shop
a long time ago.
Sorry. I can't meet with you today.
I have to return the car,
and I have plans afterward.
And...
I have to look into something as well.
See you in Seoul.
Okay, then.
(dramatic music)
ROMA: Are Mr. Cha and Ms. Hong
going back on a night flight?
SANGKOO: They stayed behind
to return the vehicle.
Mopix is really sensitive about that.
Those two are dating, aren't they?
That's why they stayed behind.
Are you crazy?
That jerk, Cha? Yesool?
She's a workaholic! What dating?
I saw Ms. Hong and Mr. Cha together
while I took a walk early this morning.
And at the shoot earlier,
they had a special look in their eyes.
(sighs deeply)
Ms. Hong really has everything,
doesn't she?
SANGKOO: Wait a second.
Now that I look around,
Director Lee Pilyo's not here, either.
He said he's stopping by somewhere...
Let's go. Whatever. My gosh.
ONE-WAY
(dramatic music)
(sighs)
Everything's changed here.
When did that place
become a sashimi restaurant?
(scoffs)
(airplane engine rumbles)
(somber music)
MINHU: The covers are slightly loose,
so there's a possibility
of the car being exposed.
Please pay special attention to it.
Please maintain tight security.
-MAN: Yes, sir.
-When will it arrive?
MAN: If the waves are not too turbulent...
(snaps)
(light music)
(tires screech)
(gasps)
(Yesool screams)
MINHU: Hong Yesool!
Damn it.
Yesool, are you okay?
YESOOL: Mr. Cha.
What? What are you...
Hush, it's Ms. Jo.
(Sunhee sighs deeply)
Planning Team 1 upsets me so much.
You didn't pick up your phone.
What are you doing here by yourself?
(light music)
All right.
Please take care. Thank you.
MAN: Yes, sir.
YESOOL: I'm leaving first.
DOMESTIC DEPARTURES
(indistinct announcement)
(light music)
(Minhu sighs)
You knew exactly where to find me.
I didn't even tell you where.
This is the opposite direction
from our gate.
This has happened so many times.
How am I supposed to understand this?
Excellent instincts? Great eyesight?
A good sense of direction?
Or...
you're hiding something from me.
You believed me when I told you that
I can see the future.
I'll believe you, too.
So tell me everything.
So you're saying...
you're usually hyper-sensitive?
So when you kiss,
your senses go into overdrive
and causes you so much pain
that it makes you collapse?
I know it's hard to believe.
(indistinct announcement)
(sighs)
I believe you.
Now I can believe everything...
that's happened so far.
You heard my conversation
with Director Lee last night, too, right?
I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
But I could just hear it from my room.
So why didn't you say anything, then?
You had many opportunities to do so.
When I told you my secret
and even last night...
I'm sure you wouldn't like it if you knew.
Someone I like would feel uncomfortable
around me and will try to avoid me.
I know how you feel.
Is that why I was drawn to you?
Because we're both weirdos.
(soft chuckle)
I know, right?
So, how much can you hear?
Well, when you asked me out,
you said you didn't know
exactly how you felt.
But I heard it.
The sound of your heart
beating faster for me.
I don't know. It's just that...
-(heartbeats rapidly)
-...you're always on my mind,
and I want to confirm my feelings as well.
(heartbeats rapidly)
You could hear that?
That's not fair to me.
You caught me.
But you get to see
the future that I can't see.
You're not hiding anything else
from me, are you?
No more surprises, right?
Let's go. It's almost time
for us to board.
ANNOUNCER: To all passengers,
if you are on flight 713
and have completed
your boarding procedures,
please head to the departure waiting room
to go through the departure procedures.
(sighs)
She's here again.
Oh Jiyoung.
She doesn't even have
to make an appointment. She goes right in.
Hey, it's because they know each other.
Are those two dating?
No, no, no.
Ms. Oh Jiyoung's not exactly
on Dr. Oh's level.
True. They're on a different level.
Hey, can't you hear someone crying?
(Jiyoung sobbing)
Hey, stop crying.
You should have been more careful.
Do you want to get an x-ray?
No.
Do you want to see
an orthopedic surgeon, then?
SEUNGTAEK: Okay.
(sighs deeply)
Hey, so he's not in pain
if he's with Ms. Hong?
That's so...
And?
So you kissed him
to find out if it's true?
Whoa, crazy Oh Jiyoung. In my opinion,
you're nuts. Crazy, Oh Jiyoung.
That's right!
I'm a crazy bitch.
But I had to see it with my own eyes
to believe it, okay?
(sobbing)
Hey, Oh Jiyoung, stop crying.
My head hurts, and it's killing me.
Hey!
That asshole's not the only man
in the world!
Jeez, you've got to give it a rest.
Seriously.
There's only one Cha Minhu.
Minhu is the only one who has been
by my side since my childhood.
After my mom died when I was little,
he was like my mom, and my older brother.
He just has to become my husband now!
What the heck is this?
My plan is ruined.
(sobbing)
So why did you come up with
such an unrealistic plan to begin with?
Shit.
All right. Sorry.
Okay.
(somber music)
I'll go ahead and pack.
I'm off to enjoy my first break in a week.
Aren't you going? Let's go.
Then we'll go too...
I can't even get between them now.
There's nothing I can do.
It's driving me crazy.
What the heck does that mean now?
He's not in pain when he's with her.
So what can I do?
I hate to see him in pain
even more than if I were to be in pain.
I don't know. This is tough for me too.
This is tough. It's so tough.
I'm dying here. Oh Jiyoung.
What is love?
What's love, huh? What is it?
I want to cry too. I really want to cry...
I'm going crazy. I feel like crying too.
(somber music)
You know, you're not
looking too good yourself.
What's wrong?
-Seungtaek.
-Yes.
(quirky music)
Do you want to go eat pasta?
-SEUNGTAEK: Well...
-JIYOUNG: I'll feed you.
You're always dropping your food
like a baby.
Seungtaek. She's looking at you...
-like you're just a piece of stick.
-What?
-She has zero interest in you.
-Really?
Just give up.
(exhales deeply)
(grunts)
SEUNGTAEK: Stop it!
Make sure to lock your door,
and call me if anything happens.
They caught the burglar,
so don't worry too much.
Make sure to pick up my calls.
-Okay.
-Go in.
Bye.
(lock rattles)
Did you check the footsteps,
stride and shoe size
left on the road and the window?
(sighs)
Look, he confessed.
Can you check if he got on a plane
or drove anywhere yesterday and today?
I interrogated him yesterday and today.
How on earth could he have
gotten on a plane?
Besides, he doesn't have his license.
He got caught drunk driving.
All right.
Please contact me if anything new happens.
You know, you told me last time
not to contact the victim
and call you directly.
Is there a reason for that?
Can I also check
the other suspects' records?
Check...
Just come over here. You should just...
-Just sit here, and...
-No.
Okay, then.
(quirky music)
I came home in a week. What's going on?
It hasn't even been an hour
since I came from the airport.
How am I supposed to choose?
I want to take all of my babies.
This one.
Yesool.
Do you remember this? You drew this.
I did?
You don't remember?
I think I have some pictures
from back then.
I wanted you
to become an artist back then.
I never thought you'd be making
commercials like your father.
Should I hang up one of your pieces
at my exhibition?
My goodness.
Let's see.
You weren't kidding about this drawing.
Dad took this picture for me, right?
But then, this hand...
Wait.
All of Dad's pictures are gone.
That picture from the frame was gone too.
(gasps)
Could it be that burglar
who broke into our house last time?
A burglar?
What are you talking about?
Oh, I mean...
Well...
(suspenseful music)
Auntie, the drinks are all set up.
You guys can start. I'll be right there.
Why?
Is it because of the photo album?
They caught the burglar,
so don't you worry. Okay?
But that burglar is so weird. Right?
Why would he take someone else's pictures?
Is he some kind of a pervert?
Anyway, come on, Auntie.
(door closes)
(dramatic music)
-YESOOL: Cheers!
-HOWOO: Cheers!
(gulping)
This used to be an everyday thing.
How precious is this? Don't you think?
Yes.
I'm not up to date with things
since I've been at the hospital lately.
So are you all lovey-dovey with Cha Minhu?
Hey.
You said you're not going to date anyone.
Yet one-night stand with Dr. Seungtaek?
It wasn't just one night.
We slept together for one straight week.
What?
Forget it. That's not helping
my case at all.
Tell me about you.
(Yesool sighs deeply)
I just...
wanted to know why I told him
about my secret.
It turns out there was a reason for it.
I don't know if it's right
to get involved with him
just because of that future I saw.
What are you talking about?
It's just that...
we're both kind of weird.
So it's so weird that...
you like him that much, huh?
How about Pilyo?
I saw the video,
and he knows all about your secret.
Did you talk to him about that?
When I was dating Pilyo,
I never told him about
what was going on with me.
It felt like he'd leave me
if I told him about myself.
He'd be scared of me and avoid me.
I tortured myself, thinking that
we'd end up breaking up like that.
But I guess Mr. Cha felt like that too.
Just like me.
(Yesool sighs)
YESOOL: I don't know.
Let's just drink.
Gosh.
-Cheers.
YESOOL: But why isn't Mom coming?
NEMO THE BLOOD MOON MURDER
THE BLOOD MOON MURDER
A BLOOD MOON PHENOMENON
THE SUSPECT OF THE BLOOD MOON
MURDER FOUND DEAD AFTER SIX MONTHS
THE POLICE HAVE CONDUCTED
AN INQUIRY INVESTIGATION
AND PRESUME THAT MR. KIM ATTEMPTED SUICIDE
(suspenseful music)
(lock rattles)
What brings you here so early...
Get in.
What's the occasion? Out of the blue?
Does it have to be a special occasion
for me to drive my girlfriend to work?
Get in if you don't want to be late.
Okay.
(gentle music)
Over there.
Can you drop me off over there?
I mean, it's not like our agency
forbids employees from dating in-house.
What's all the fuss about?
I said I don't care.
I care.
After all that uproar
with Director Lee Pilyo,
what if there's a rumor about you and me?
It won't be a rumor. It's true.
I am your boyfriend.
I mean, people are already saying that
I got to where I am with your backing.
I don't want people gossiping about me.
(gasps)
(quirky music)
Jeez.
(whooshing)
They didn't see me, right?
How could you miss them
when you have such sharp senses?
What? Should I have told you
to hide, then?
Do you want to hide the fact
that we're dating that badly?
Well, right now, it's...
Anyway, don't make it obvious
that we're dating when we're at work.
Act like your usual self.
Just be totally rude.
Act like a psychopath,
just like now. Okay?
Don't you make it obvious!
PLANS FOR IMPLEMENTING SCHEDULES
You must've planted
a lot of trees on Arbor Day.
Just how many trees were
cut down to produce this garbage?
How many pages is this?
What a waste of paper.
(yells)
Ms. Hong.
Is your vision okay these days?
Excuse me?
Is this the post-production budget sheet?
I think you put an extra zero in here.
Get your head back in the game.
Take the extra zero out and bring it back.
I almost said to take out two zeroes.
All right, understood.
(paper rustles)
Undecided on the follow-up process.
Undecided on sharing the rough cut.
Undecided, undecided, undecided.
Should we say our paydays
are undecided too?
I guess I've been smiling
too much lately, huh?
Let's all work late tonight. Dismissed.
SANGGOO:
He seems a little scary, but not really.
What's with him? What's gotten into him?
Stop web surfing and turn that off.
And do something about
clicking your mouse so regularly
while playing the card game.
Stop messaging each other
and let's work, okay?
Why don't we resolve
the follow-up process first?
-Okay.
So what are you trying to play at today?
You two are at it...
Don't say anything.
Just text me.
(grunts)
You poked my nose.
HOWOO: Pilyo did another interview.
I think it's about you again.
He's really in love.
I feel so bad for him,
going on like that by himself.
Meet with him and talk it out, Yesool.
If the woman had told him
everything she had been hiding,
do you think the movie
would've had a happy ending?
I think the movie
had a happy ending, actually.
And I think the woman is in the process
of going after her happiness.
Do you mean that...
the man and the woman
reunite after the ending?
PILYO: I really don't know about that.
But one thing for sure is...
that the two will make
the best choice for themselves.
The choice that would make them happy.
(light music)
What are you thinking so deeply about?
Aren't you going home?
Let's go.
Mr. Cha.
Let's take a walk.
Sure.
(light music)
We've been walking for an hour.
Say what you want to say.
Or should I say it first?
I have no intention
of getting dragged around...
by the future you saw and you will see.
Even if our future is not a happy one,
I have no intention
of breaking up with you.
Why are you bringing that up
all of a sudden?
I don't know.
I just felt like I should say it
seeing how you are right now.
Do whatever you want in this relationship.
I'm going to do the same.
The first thing I want to do is...
dropping you off at home.
(light music)
I'm home.
SARA: Yesool, you got a package.
I put it in your room.
Okay.
HONG YESOOL
HAROO
(light music)
PILYO: I thought it was about time
you watch it.
This is our story...
that I've been wanting to tell you.
POST-EVENT AGREEMENT (EDITED)
The brain CT scan looks good...
and MRI and MRA scans are both fine, too.
The frontal, temporal, and parietal lobes
and both occipital lobes are fine too.
Your senses are functioning as usual.
By "usual," I mean by your standards.
I know, Doctor.
Looks like you're doing well.
Is it the power of being in love?
(laughs)
So, how did Ms. Hong react?
She wasn't shocked
when she found out about you?
I shouldn't have been so worried.
She was so understanding.
That's great.
But I'm worried, Doctor.
Now that she knows
about my heightened senses,
and the potential risks that follow,
would it be okay to tell her more?
What if I bring back bad memories for her?
Are you afraid that she'll remember
that she knew you as a child
and ultimately remember that incident?
Yes.
As you mentioned before,
if she chose to forget the incident
for some reason,
then maybe it's wrong
to keep revealing myself
and provoking her.
Just face it head-on.
So that you can move on to the next.
Aside from all that,
I wish you'd become freer.
HAROO
DIRECTOR LEE PILYO
I CAN'T HELP BUT CRY WHEN I KISS YOU
HAROO
(soft music)
I want to join this club.
Yes.
Are you Korean?
Yes, I am.
A handshake. Don't you know?
PILYO: Let's do a good job.
As a director and staff.
(birds chirping)
WOMAN: What's special about today?
MAN: The day we get to kiss.
(light music)
YESOOL: From the moment I saw that future,
I've never been in control
of my relationship with Pilyo.
Because I was afraid of the future,
because I was anxious,
and terrified,
I've never been myself.
So I ran away.
I couldn't handle the future.
All I remember is running away...
while ignoring what I had seen.
HAROO
(light music)
Thanks for watching it to the end.
There's a question I haven't been able
to answer after we broke up.
The future I saw...
Was it bound to happen?
Or did I make it happen?
I still don't know the answer to that.
What would've happened had I confronted it
and told you everything back then?
I was afraid of breaking up with you,
and that you might leave me.
So, rather than enjoying
the present moment,
I was always so anxious.
But even if we were
to go back to that time,
I don't think I could've told you.
I'm sorry...
for not facing the situation...
and always running away.
But I realized something
after watching this movie.
I don't want to go back to the way I was.
I'm not going to make...
the same mistake again.
I guess I see the future, too.
I thought you'd say something like that.
The way you look at Cha Minhu...
is the same way you used to look at me.
So, now I know.
I should be cool and say, "Fine.
I'll let you go for your happiness."
I want to say that, but...
(scoffs)
...you know me, right?
I'm not that cool.
So what if...
you see another unhappy future?
If you see a future that you can't handle,
what will you do then?
I'll still go for it.
I won't avoid the situation and run away.
I'll face it head-on.
(light music)
You sure took your time. I know
you've been back in Korea for a while.
(soft chuckle)
Wow, nothing's changed here.
Still no customers.
How do you pay your rent?
Are you able to keep up?
Yesool is a regular here.
She has nowhere else to go
if you go out of business.
So, you can't take her away
from Cha Minhu?
You know about that?
(scoffs)
You know everything, don't you?
Well, I don't think Cha Minhu is all that.
Try to win her over, okay?
I came back to do everything I can,
but I don't think there is much I can do.
You've done everything you can? Really?
Do more. All the way.
There's nothing you can't do.
But I think that will make
Yesool struggle even more, though...
and I really don't want to do that.
Gosh, I really came back determined.
But am I too late?
It's never too late.
Life is all about the right timing.
You have to wait until the end.
While doing what you can do.
Until she knows how you feel.
Should I call up Yesool?
Where is she?
(cell phone vibrates)
YESOOL: Mr. Cha, where are you?
Is something the matter again?
Yes, something is the matter.
What's going on?
I'll tell you when I see you.
What?
Let's meet right now.
-Where are you? I'll be right over.
-No.
I'll go to you this time.
To your house.
What?
Wait for me.
(upbeat music)
What's wrong?
You know...
I don't need this contract anymore.
I cancel everything that's written here.
I want to know everything.
I'm not going to miss the moment
and tell you everything.
I'll do everything I want to do.
With you, Mr. Cha.
And regardless of the future,
I want to sleep with you.
Even if we end up breaking up,
I'm going to really
pursue this relationship.
Let's be real lovers.
Passionately.
It's okay if you collapse.
I'll be spending the night here.
(romantic music)
POST-EVENT AGREEMENT (EDITED)
(romantic music continues)
(closing theme music)