=Bossy Husband Who Loved Me=
=Episode 22=
Miss Liu, stop playing the fool.
I came here only for one thing.
Who is
"Yuan Ju Qing"?
You're making no sense.
My original plan
is to use Mu Xiaoxi as a pawn
and tarnish your name,
so that you won't be able
to lead the troops.
But since you've already found out
who I am,
don't blame me for showing you no mercy.
Come in.
Come in now!
I'm afraid Your Highness won't see
the person you're waiting for.
However,
the tea does taste quite different.
You're not as good
as someone I know
at spiking drinks.
Zhao Tie.
Yes.
Your Highness.
I've completed the task
I was assigned with.
According to the original storyline,
I would catch them
at Shuixie Pavilion.
I didn't see this coming.
After so many twists and turns,
we still end up following
the original storyline.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to catch my cheating spouse.
I need to look menacing.
How dare the two of you do this
under broad daylight?
Come out now, adulterers!
Why
are you
on your knees?
My goodness.
I'm done for.
I thought I could set him up
in a badger game.
How did it end up
with her being tortured?
The princess of Beiqing
has been arrested now.
We still need her
for the remaining story.
The plot has changed completely.
What should I do now?
I can't let this happen.
There must be something wrong with this.
I shall find it out myself.
Can you say it now?
I admit my defeat
and I surrender to Your Highness.
Your Highness is a dignified man.
Do you really want to do this
to a helpless lady like me?
Our countries are at war.
Our genders don't matter now,
but our nationalities do.
If I take pity on you,
even only for a little,
I will be betraying the troops of Sheng.
What do you think
I should do?
I...
I am the princess of Beiqing.
According to diplomatic etiquette,
I shouldn't be treated this way.
The embassy of Beiqing
will be meeting the Emperor soon.
Let's see how you shall explain this.
I didn't find your name, Shangguan Ruyu,
on the list of envoys
who're going to visit the Capital.
Since your name is not on the list,
I simply arrested a suspect.
There's no need to explain the arrest
to our guests.
You...
You've caught all the spies
I planted in the Capital.
You also saw through my scheme.
What else do you want from me?
Why are you asking the question
when you already know the answer?
I really have no idea
who "Yuan Ju Qing" is.
I have completely no idea!
Your Highness.
Let me try.
Look.
You're the princess.
You don't have to suffer like this.
Just tell us now.
What do I do when I really don't know
who the person is?
Who are you?
You're in no place to talk to me.
Get on your knees now!
Then...
You have to tell me the truth
if I get on my knees.
Just tell me the truth.
Go away!
Stop staring at me.
Or I'll dig out your eyeballs
and feed the dogs with them.
Go away now!
What a shrew.
Close the door.
Your Highness.
I didn't expect
the princess of Beiqing
to be such an aggressive woman.
She would rather die
than tell me information
regarding "Yuan Ju Qing".
The more she resists it,
the more it shows
how important the person is.
Even the princess is trying
to help him hide his identity.
It's a pity that my ability
doesn't work on others.
I can't read her mind.
Then...
Why don't we
try it on Her Highness again?
That's the only thing we can do now.
"Yuan Ju Qing"?
He doesn't sound like a good man.
Wait.
Why does it
sound so familiar?
"Yuan Ju Qing"?
"Yuan Ju Qing".
Wait.
The original storyline!