=Bossy Husband Who Loved Me=
=Episode 14=
No way...
When I was writing
this part of the story,
I wrote three poems for Qin Chuan.
They're all famous poems
I copied from the internet.
These are not the three poems.
Did the plot change again?
Previously,
the ledger turned out to be fake.
Qin Yu, the villain, was supposed
to play a big part in the story.
But he got cut off right away.
This time,
the poems have turned out
to be fake as well.
Then, the Second Prince won't be able
to frame Qin Chuan.
He's supposed to be the protagonist
of the angst fiction,
but now he's having
the time of his life.
Luckily, I have memorized a few poems.
Let me write three new poems for you.
Qin Chuan.
I created you.
There's no way you can run away from me.
To govern a country,
we need someone who's both
a good scholar and a good fighter.
Today,
we're going to judge your poetry.
I will entrust
the winner
with important tasks.
Now,
it's spring.
The theme of the first poem
shall be spring.
Yue.
You'll go first.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The spring breeze is
working tirelessly
along the flower beds and willow trees.
Whilst bees make honey
and swallows peck clay,
the rain falls and blows it away.
What's going on?
You didn't expect this, right?
You think you've tricked me,
but I'm a better trickster.
If it wasn't for me,
Prince Tai would've fallen
into your trap.
(Stay calm.)
There's no way Qin Chuan will find out
that I was the one who gave his poems
to Prince Tai.
I will lose my life
if I fail this mission.
I'm sorry you had to deal with this.
What a good poem, Your Majesty.
Prince Tai's poetry compared spring
to a man.
It's a very fresh idea
and describes all the details perfectly.
It's a masterpiece.
It's very decent.
Fourth Brother.
What do you think
about my poem?
Your Majesty.
It's an amazing poem
from Second Brother.
I knew there was no way
I could beat him in this.
Fourth Brother has always been
outstanding in poetry.
Why not
let Fourth Brother
recite his poem first?
Chuan.
You'll go first, then.
(It's a pity)
(that I can't take part
in the Poetry Contest.)
(Otherwise, I will make your jaws drop)
(by reciting a random poem.)
The adored moss perhaps.
Clogs leave behind footprints.
Knocks on the wooden gate,
and gets no response.
A garden of spring flowers
can't be contained.
Over the hedge,
an apricot blossom tempts.
The adored moss perhaps.
Clogs leave behind footprints.
Knocks on the wooden gate,
and gets no response.
A garden of spring flowers
can't be contained.
Over the hedge,
an apricot blossom tempts.
What's going on?
Did he actually write
"At the Garden Gate"?
Prince Rui's poem
uses beautiful phrases.
It describes the scenario perfectly.
At the first glance, it is a poem
speaking of a trip to the garden.
But if you listen carefully,
there's a lot of meaning to it.
It is way more artistic
than Prince Tai's poem.
It is brilliant, Your Highness.
I didn't expect
Chuan to be so outstanding
in poetry.
Do I look good?
No one said you looked good.
(This is strange.)
(The Sheng Dynasty is fictitious.)
There aren't Tang, Song, Yuan,
Ming, and Qing Dynasties.
Is Qin Chuan
really that good?
(How could he write a poem exactly
the same as "At The Garden Gate"?)
It's a must
to view the moon in spring.
The theme of the second poem
will be the moon.
Your Majesty,
let me go first.
The moonlight of autumn
is prettier than the one of spring.
The world is vast and silent.
The frost has been heavy
over the past few nights.
And the leaves are slowly withering.
There are ups and downs,
and twists and turns in the poem.
It's a very decent poem.
Yue.
You've made impressive progress.
Thanks for the compliment, Your Majesty.
I saw the moonlight before my couch,
and wondered if it were not the frost
on the ground.
(I raised my head and looked out
on the mountain moon,)
(I bowed my head
and thought of my far-off home.)
There hasn't been a poem
that can surpass this one.
(I'm curious to see)
(what you can come up with this time.)
Chuan.
You shall do it too
this time.
I saw the moonlight before my couch,
and wondered if it were not the frost
on the ground.
I raised my head and looked out
on the mountain moon,
I bowed my head
and thought of my far-off home.
How could he come up with this?
The moonlight reminds the author
of his hometown.
The choice of words is simple
and refreshing,
but at the same time,
also meaningful and sentimental.
Prince Rui is a genius.
This poem
is definitely an extraordinary one.
Write it down
and distribute it across the country.
Share it with the scholars.
I do look good.
This makes no sense.
It's not making sense at all.
How could he know this?
This...
The theme of the third poem
will be farewell.
Speaking of farewell poetry,
my favorite is “Farewell to Dongda”.
Yellow clouds covering a thousand miles
and the sun setting dim,
(in whirling snow the north wind
drives south the wild geese.)
On the road ahead surely
will be friends dear and true.
Throughout the land
is there anyone who knows not you?
If you're able
to write the exact same poem again,
you can have my head.
Yellow clouds covering a thousand miles
and the sun setting dim,
in whirling snow the north wind
drives south the wild geese.
On the road ahead surely
will be friends dear and true.
Throughout the land is there anyone
who knows not you?
Your Majesty.
It's a very emotional poem
that carries great meaning.
It's a poem that will shock the world.
The three poems by Prince Rui
are the best out of the best.
They must be distributed
across the world.
It's a blessing for Your Majesty
and the Sheng.
(Oh, no.)
(He'll definitely win the contest.)
If I fail my mission,
I'll lose my life too.