Don't! Don't! Don't!
I said no!
I don't want it.
Tang Jiajia.
Just date me.
I promise this time,
there is no package or trick.
No.
Why?
Give me a reason.
You don't look honest.
It's not suitable to stay at home.
Is it my fault that I'm handsome?
You're not humble at all.
Admit your strength bravely.
Don't you like my strength?
It's fun.
Just have fun.
Are you done?
I'm leaving.
You're going home early to sleep?
Who told you I'm going home to sleep?
No, you can't leave.
Just give me a chance
to prove myself.
If it doesn't work,
I'll stay in your gallery.
What do you mean?
I can do it.
One month.
I'll give you one month.
Follow me.
Okay.
Not today.
I'm really
I'm so sleepy that I'm going home to sleep.
I'm leaving.
Not today.
One more day.
so nice to me.
Wait for me.
When a man works hard,
is really handsome.
How about I set up a stall in front of their gallery
and do some street writing?
Looks like you're serious this time.
No wonder Elsa said you've evolved.
Have you ever fallen in love at first sight?
Just once.
Her face
in my mind.
That's so cheesy.
You'd better tell Sister Jia Jia.
Screw you.
By the way, I've been wanting to ask you a question.
Go ahead.
Is it worth giving up
Is it worth it to go back to China for her?
Yes.
Because it's her.
Because it's me.
Why don't you go to her now?
I've been suppressing myself
over 30 times every day.
But I said I won't disturb her.
I'll look for her again.
Isn't that a slap in my face?
And if she misses me,
she will come to me.
Are you sure?
The netizens
are arguing whether you are a puppy
or a puppy.
I think you are a big tail wolf.
No matter what type I am,
she won't think about me at all.
Look.
You're so popular outside.
But why are you always afraid of her?
When you like someone enough,
you will feel
not good enough.
Chief Editor Zhang Ran has been fired.
This incident can stop the loss in time
and restore the reputation of the group.
Xia Anran deserves the credit.
This incident
we need our colleagues to work together.
The new chief editor
will be officially notified soon.
Safe.
Congratulations in advance.
Thank you for your support, Mr. Zhou.
I will keep working hard.
From now on,
if anyone dares to abuse power for personal gains,
I won't show mercy.
Okay.
Dismissed.
It's a done deal.
Congratulations, Chief Editor Xia.
All right.
Get back to work.
Okay.
ABC.
Hello?
[Hello?]
I want to ask you out.
I know you're still angry.
I'm not...
No.
But I'm afraid if I don't say it today,
I won't have the courage tomorrow.
Are you drunk?
No, I'm sober.
I'm actually quite timid.
I'm afraid of everything that will expire.
I'm afraid it'll expire if I wait.
So I want to ask you out.
I don't have time.
I'm always here.
It won't expire.
You miss me?
Let's meet and talk.
I told you.
I only show up
when you miss me the most.
I'll wait for you at the aquarium.
Come if you want.
I'll send you the location.
Good night.
Hello?
Mom, look, that's huge.
Slow down.
Isn't it pretty? Look at that.
Look at that.
Look at this.
It's pretty.
Hey.
What?
An Ran.
This is the last letter your father left you.
And this cake.
He told me
to meet him
for you
I'll give you the cake for him.
You're still like this.
You're irresponsible.
Will you make up for me
Can you make it up to me?
Don't eat if you don't want to.
Just say no.
Why do you
push yourself?
When I was young,
every time my dad sent me to your house,
I was afraid that he would pick me up.
Every time I'm at your house,
I'm afraid that my parents won't like me
your parents won't like me.
Now,
I'm afraid
I can't eat the cake anymore.
Are you really going to ignore me?
An'an,
I really don't know
what you've been through.
I blamed you for not eating desserts.
I was angry and ignored you.
Sorry, An.
I'm really sorry.
An'an,
If you don't see it now,
What if you regret it later?
That's not important.
When my dad bought me a cake,
I thought it was the sweetest reward.
Later I found out
cake was just a tool for him to dissuade me.
Every time my dad bought me a cake,
and sent me to your home,
to get me far enough
he could bring another woman home.
Then I stopped eating cake.
When I see the cake,
I feel disgusted
because of that feeling.
I'm going to say this today.
I can let it go in the future.
But this time,
my home
It's really gone.
Why don't you have a home?
You still have me.
An, I'll always be with you.
An.
Let's go home.
Can you promise me
promise me
Be happy or not,
tell me.
Now I'm sure
love is sweet.
I like this taste.
I thought I left the abyss of misfortune
I finally met a perfect love.
step by step to my happiness.
Love is like a cream cake in summer.
The first second I took it out of the window
started to melt.
It's like love bumps into each other in the real world.
in the real world.
Let's break up.
Xia Anran, are you crazy?
You have to give me a reason.
That's the reason.
No matter how thick the sugar coat is,
When the knife pierced into the heart,
the pain will not fade.
The beginning of every beautiful story
The tragedy is counting down.
I'd rather
never start.