Come on. Come on.
Don't always say you're in a rush to work.
How many times have you shaken me with this?
I was in a hurry today.
According to reliable sources,
the suspect, Mr. Xia, has escaped breakfast many times.
[has been escorted by a special person.]
You can be bailed after breakfast.
If you don't eat breakfast,
You might get indigestion.
I'm reading work information.
Work is more important than health.
You can support me if you don't work.
I'll support you.
An'an,
I'm serious.
Everything I have is yours.
Even if it's mine,
you have to be responsible for your life.
Thank you for the food.
Bye.
You're shaking me again.
Pay for the meal.
Keep the change.
According to the informant,
the photographer of the "Queen" magazine
is suspected of sexual harassment.
We will further follow up.
Hello, this is the "Queen" magazine.
Hello?
Give me a pen.
There are so many complaints this morning.
Okay, let me sort it out.
Why are the photographers
Why are there so many controversies?
What's wrong with you?
Anran didn't participate in the cover.
It's our fault.
How far has it gone?
Last night, a netizens reported
that this photographer
to sexually harass female models.
I'm still
the real identity of this matter.
On the other hand,
the statement we released last night
was too stiff
causing the virus.
It's not good for us.
The statement yesterday was Chief Editor Zhang.
What I want now is the solution.
My suggestion is to cut it directly.
to cut the loss in time.
It's just that this matter involves a lot of people.
I'm afraid I don't have the right to handle it.
From now on,
report to me directly.
Okay.
I'll deal with it.
How's the platform?
We've almost contacted the relevant platforms.
Once the statement is stamped, it will be released at the same time.
As soon as the time is up, we'll send it together.
OK.
Keep an eye on the feedback of the platform.
Okay.
And the photographer...
contact the legal department to terminate the contract.
Remember to check the compensation plan
of intellectual property.
Don't let him take advantage of us.
The photographer is Editor-in-Chief Zhang.
He strongly recommended it.
It's business.
Okay.
Also,
help me contact
the model in the case.
But remember to protect the client's privacy.
This...
Okay.
I'd like to remind you
It's time for lunch.
I'm working as you say.
I've asked someone
to your desk.
Eat it while it's hot.
I don't usually touch things that don't indicate the price.
I'm afraid of being extorted.
I'll take interest.
A lot.
Have a seat.
Louis.
Let me put it simply.
the situation is not good for you.
Although you are actually a manager of A&H,
the person who applied was Xiao Jin.
Amanda.
So she can get the logo back anytime.
Can I solve this problem
through legal procedures?
If we enter the judicial committee,
it will be suspended.
You have to think about
you have to think it over.
The best way
the best way is negotiation.
and trademark transfer.
What if you pay for it?
Buy?
One million.
Ten million
This is ten times the original price.
Okay.
I'll think of another way.
Thank you, Mr. Zhou.
OK.
Who is monitoring the situation now?
Show me the report.
Anran,
You are really risky.
After this conversation
and the harassment models,
the news online has started to spread.
The public opinion has started to change.
Keep an eye on the rest.
Good work, everyone.
What's wrong?
Why did you drink?
An'an,
You have your life.
I have my life.
Okay.
Would you like a glass of lemon water?
I'll read the report.
Thank you for your hard work.
After this is over,
after this is over.
Okay.
No problem.
Go back to work.
Okay.
Look at the person you're looking for.
He's good in the industry.
to make a statement
could cause such a big trouble to the company.
Did you do a backtone before finding someone?
Is this person suitable or not?
Looks like someone thinks
after cleaning up the mess.
As you know,
what you've done is a mess.
But whoever is useful
will be pushed to the front.
Don't get too worked up.
Black can't be white.
The white won't be black either.
As long as you have a clear conscience.
Looks like Louis
from you.
What do you mean?
Didn't Louis tell you?
I guess there's a secret between you two.
People like us
can't trust others.
Right?
I'm sorry.
I fell asleep.
I happened to be downstairs.
It's restricted today.
Luckily I met you.
Otherwise, it wouldn't be easy to get a taxi at that time.
It's not a coincidence.
It's been too long.
I want to see you.
Are you busy recently?
Yes.
Thank you.
Safe.
You can come to me if you feel pressured.
Physiotherapy, basketball,
Anything.
Just like before.
Actually, I'm...
We're friends.
Right?
Of course.
We've always been friends.
It's just that everyone has to face the pressure.
Right?
I'm leaving.
Is your seat belt stuck?
Thank you.
Are you still angry?
Why did you ask Ding Zhiwei to pick you up?
He was just passing by.
Who would believe that?
He's waiting for you.
All right.
I won't do it again.
Why did you drink so much again?
You said you'd work hard.
Of course I have to
for my work.
I met Amanda today.
What happened between you and her?
What did she tell you?
She said you're going to die with her.
What do you mean?
Is there something you didn't tell me?
We have to be responsible for our lives.
Isn't that what you said?
There's another half of this sentence.
When you can't handle it alone,
you have to be honest with each other, not silence.
Then did you tell me the truth?
I told you.
I didn't know he was waiting for me.
Did you know later?
Why didn't you explain to me?
Lin Hao.
Why should I explain to you?
Because I got in a car
a car that likes my man,
Or I didn't tell you
tell you everything in the past.
Before I was with you,
my life wasn't empty.
But now that you're back,
I chose to be with you.
to respect each other's life.
This is how adults get along.
Just like your recent secret.
I didn't ask much.
Right?
I want to terminate the contract with Amanda.
Why didn't you
Why didn't you discuss it with me?
With her personality,
she won't agree so easily.
You shouldn't have broken up with her.
She did make a condition.
to take A&H away.
She has the logo.
So it's hard.
But don’t worry.
I will buy A&H back.
Why did you terminate the contract with her?
Is it because of me?
Yes.
But not exactly.
I don't like people who hurt you.
But she's not
a good partner.
Since we're going to terminate the contract,
why don't you
How much did she ask you?
Ten times the original price.
I made a new product.
Are you hungry?
Do you want to try it?
Let's go.
That’s just a shell.
If you can make the first brand well,
you can make the second one.
Different.
Do you know what A&H means?
Our names.
So it's everything to me.
Lin Hao.
I can accept your love.
But it's not worth it.
It's worth it.
When you eat my dessert,
your face is overflowing with smiles.
I think everything is worth it.
Can you face problems
like an adult?
I don't need to be like an adult.
I'm an adult.
Trust me.
I'll take care of everything.
I'm not eating.
Try it.
I made this especially for you.
I'm really not eating.
Have a bite.
I stopped eating desserts ten years ago.
Try it.
Lin Hao, be serious.
I didn't mean it.
What did you just say?
Can you be serious?
You always said the cake
you said it was delicious.
I lied to you.
You lied to me.
Why did you lie to me?
Because you never listen to me.
You're like a child.
like a child.
You never care about what others want.
Your self-righteous things are too childish.
I'm childish?
Yes.
I'm childish.
But I did it for you.
For me?
For me again.
My mom left me to my dad for me.
My dad sent me to your home for me.
You just leave.
You just come back.
You just chased me.
Who asked about my feelings?
I really can't afford
I really can't afford it.
When I was young,
we had a deal.
Every time you come,
you eat this kind of cream cake.
Every bite you eat is carefully.
You told me it was the taste of happiness.
I went back to the old house
But this shop was long gone.
After you came back,
since you came back.
I thought
as long as I find
the taste of this cream cake,
If I make it,
you'll become like before.
the happy you.
Do you know why
I don't like you mentioning the past?
Because when I was little,
when I was little.
Everything you think is fake.
I don't want to go back to my old self.
So please
stop forcing me to recall the past.
An'an.
I'm sorry.
For all this time,
I was wrong.
I won't bother you anymore.
An'an,
You can only eat a small piece a day.
In that case,
I'll pick you up after you finish eating.
An'an,
Didn't Uncle Xia pick you up today?
The cake is so big this time.
Does Uncle Xia need a long trip this time?
Dad said he'll be back in a few days.
If you only eat a small piece a day,
for about a week.
Really?
Great.
You can stay with me for another week.
I'll put it in the fridge.
So she can stay longer.