I don't want to get married.
Xia Anran.
What are you talking about?
It's safe.
Are you satisfied with
the venue we watched recently?
You can tell us if you have any ideas.
I mean
I'm not ready to get married yet.
But I'm serious about this relationship.
Nail.
Here.
Why is it so cold?
How time flies.
Yeah.
In the blink of an eye, I've been working
for more than half a month.
What?
Are you happy working here?
This is the first time in our gallery.
to be displayed by the artist.
You saved me a lot of money.
At this point,
our friendship is still measured with money.
I should work harder.
How about
I do something else?
I'm going to shoot with Anran in two days.
Finish this as soon as possible.
Do you know when you're the most charming?
When I reject you,
let me remind you.
There are only a few days left.
Why are you squatting here?
An'an.
Are you too busy with work?
Shall we sleep in the room?
No.
I have work to do.
The coffee is overdosed today.
Do you want to eat something?
Okay.
This is a new product developed by my company.
I need a picky customer
to evaluate for me.
Not sweet.
A high evaluation.
What are you busy with?
I'm busy with the proposal.
You're so considerate.
Why don't you have any shortcomings?
Actually, I have shortcomings.
But I dare not tell you.
I'm afraid if I tell you,
if I tell you.
Every dessert I made
is not perfect.
No way.
But
it's good to have flaws.
That's everyone's personality.
An'an.
Have you seen a movie?
What movie?
In movies, it's hard work,
When are you free?
You can joke about everything.
Proposal is not a joke.
You don't even have a ring.
That way, girls will talk about you forever.
What do you want to do?
Let's go to a movie sometime.
Sure.
When I have time.
The ring is not measured. Mission failed.
You can take a close-up.
Yes.
OK.
Anran,
We’re almost ready.
Arrange guests to make bazaar cakes.
That's a great idea.
We can interact in their stage.
They have both feelings and space to dig deep.
What's more,
Mr. Louis agreed to attend the class himself.
Ms. Zhao finished the last scene.
He didn't even have time to change his costume.
Okay.
I'm here.
Starlet Chan, long time no see.
Let me introduce.
This is the supervisor of A&H,
dessert chef, Louis.
Hello, Mr. Zhao.
I watched your show.
You look even better in person than on TV.
You can call me Astronom.
Okay.
Later,
if you have any questions later.
Miss Star-Chan.
Let's start now.
Wait.
Put this on for me.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let's start.
Okay.
Wipe it for me.
My hands are occupied too.
Look.
It's okay.
Let's continue.
Is Louis shy?
So cute.
Put the protein into warm bubbles.
What is warm bubbles?
What are you doing?
Like this.
It won't fall.
Just warm bubbles.
Don't mix
mix the protein with the yolk.
Because the milk is very hot.
If you mix it too fast,
it will destroy the bubbles in protein.
So Shelley won't get up.
That means...
Don't mix relationships with marriage.
[Or Romantic cell will be killed.]
Love is gone.
Handsome and pretty girls in the same frame are so eye-catching.
Here.
Let me teach you.
Amy.
Anran.
Where's Louis?
I just saw him.
He said he went to see Mr. Zhao.
Over there.
I've never seen Louis
look so bright.
No one
can refuse the attraction of a beauty.
I still don't have Louis's WeChat.
Let's call it a day.
OK.
An'an.
Didn't we agree to come back together?
Are you angry?
What did you say to Starlet?
Wait.
Mr. Zhao.
I have a question.
what’s your ring size?
Okay.
Yes.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
We just added each other on WeChat
and talked about work.
Nothing else.
Are you jealous?
Who's jealous?
Kids are jealous.
No no
Women usually say no
she must be
must be very sad and jealous.
You know a lot now, right?
No, no, no.
Leo taught me that.
It has nothing to do with me.
You don't learn well from him every day.
You are jealous.
I'm not jealous.
Jealous. Jealous.
Jealous?
I'm not jealous.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I put the ring in the dessert.
Okay.
After her shoot,
we'll find an excuse to lure her to the rooftop
and prepare a big surprise.
I'm counting on you.
Brother.
What are you two doing?
Are you having an affair?
Who said that?
Okay.
So what you like is to play unnormally.
Most importantly,
I want to be a charming villain.
We have gathered
some questions from netizens.
I want to ask you some questions.
Some netizens said
he dated his boyfriend for a year.
My family urged me to get married.
I don't know how to say no.
What do you think about this question?
I don't think
is not
that I'm willing to.
When I started dating,
it's like a high-speed slide is locked.
Falling rapidly.
When will you get married after you fall in love?
When will you have a baby after you get married?
I have one.
Do we need another one?
When you realize it,
you'll find the brake is out of order.
If you want to get off, you'll get scratched.
or smashed into pieces.
What kind of relationship do you want?
Like a train.
We will meet different people
in different cars.
We may meet at any time.
and the freedom to leave.
If your destination is the same,
can you join us?
That's boring.
If the answer is confirmed,
then all we have to do is endure it.
I wish the destination was a secret.
The most important thing is the present.
We care about each other
but we don't.
We have the right to regret.
We want to keep and don't want to take responsibility.
Isn't that too selfish?
I admit that I'm a little selfish in this aspect.
But I'm definitely not perfect.
You can't accept my bad side.
you won't be able to enjoy my good side.
Tang Jiajia.
I finally found you.
Stop.
This is my workplace.
You crossed the line.
Why did you disappear in the last two months?
We were happy before.
We just ate and drank.
We didn't sign a contract.
We're all free, aren't we?
Jia Jia.
I...
I'm serious about you.
No matter what you do,
I advise you not to...
Jia Jia.
I officially propose to you today.
Will you marry me?
Can I officially reject you?
If you don't, I won't stand up.
Keep kneeling if you like.
How about I draw a safety line
to surround you.
as a performance art.
Since it's not convenient here,
let's go upstairs and record.
Yes, let's go upstairs.
Is it because of him?
Is he your new boyfriend?
Why are you guys so close?
Wait.
First of all, you're not my boyfriend.
Second, he's not my boyfriend.
I don't believe it.
You're working together to lie to me.
I know.
You went missing to cheat on me, right?
Think whatever you want.
Aren't you afraid I'll expose you?
You evil woman.
What?
You want to post a slide
and expose my crime online?
Please pick a good one
when you pick the photos.
If you don't have enough materials,
go to my Moments.
Look more.
You're shameless, aren't you?
I gave you my face.
First of all, you need this face
to be humiliated.
I thought your face
look handsome.
But you came here without saying goodbye.
That means
is the last five minutes you see me.
Go out and turn left.
Four minutes.
The security will be here in one minute.
Okay.
How dare you!
bully me.
I have to say
Miss Tang Jiajia
is the best.
I was so awkward that I was sweating.
What else?
I'll show you how touched I am.
But I think he dares to do this in public.
Actually, this boy is brave.
He's not brave.
That's called hatred.
What would you do
what would you do?
I'll kill him first
and then kill myself.
In the end, our graves
from each other.
So serious?
Luckily, I didn't listen to you.
Fortunately, we have a backup plan.
Death is not scary.
The scariest thing is social death.
I was shocked. Come and eat.
I made it for her.
It's not sweet at all.
She doesn't like sweet food.
Doesn't that girl like the sense of ritual?
It's better not to have an inappropriate sense of ritual.
It's tacky and killing.
There's a kind of thing
in everything
waiting for girls to find it.
Like cake.
Okay, stop it.
My sweat is up again.
I can't make it.
An'an, it doesn't taste good.
I'll get a new one.
Yes.
This is not good.
Lin Hao.
What are you doing?
Nothing. Nothing.
Come and get something for me.
Okay, right away.