I read a sentence in a book
If I can avoid the strong joy,
there won't be any sadness coming.
But
Even though I avoided the strong joy
Sometimes sadness comes uninvited
I can't even drive her away
I can't even avoid it.
Safe
until you show up.
you show up
A boy
wants to grow up
who can protect you.
You have a long way to go.
Fortunately, at the end of every nightmare,
at the end of every nightmare.
Lin Hao.
An'an, I saw you sleep soundly. I didn't wake you up.
Remember to finish the milk when you wake up.
See you later.
Are you okay?
Aren't you shooting?
What are you doing?
We're done.
Playing pillow battle.
What are you doing here?
I miss you. I want to take you somewhere.
Stop showing affection.
An.
Do you want to play together?
Do you dare?
Why did you come here?
What are you looking for?
Look.
I checked it before.
It's called Manta.
I've lived in the sea since the Jurassic era.
It's been over 100 million years, but his body shape hasn't changed.
It's amazing.
Although it looks fierce,
but actually,
it's one of
in the world.
No wonder you said it was cute.
There's another reason why I like it.
What is it?
Because they are always in pairs.
And they love each other all their lives.
Mom, look at these two fish kissing.
Where are you going?
What did you want to tell me last time?
When we were interviewing at the jellyfish restaurant,
you covered my ears.
What did you say?
I asked you first.
Our interview was six months ago.
I'm the one who asked first.
You're cheating.
You're lying.
After you came back,
I always think of the past.
An'an.
I didn't come back to bring you back.
That doesn't matter.
I don't want to recall the past,
but when I was young,
you were naughty.
but you always make me happy.
I never asked.
Have you been happy these years?
An'an.
The most important moment
right now.
Although I've walked a long way,
Anan,
I finally become
who can protect you.
An, wait.
A promotion gift.
You drew it?
I didn't draw it,
but to get it,
to get it.
How much is this painting?
I didn't spend money.
Trust me.
Why don't you go home?
Forget it. I have something to do tomorrow.
Besides,
I'm afraid I can't leave if I go home.
Fine.
Let's go. Let's go.
Painting.
Should I send it to you?
No.
Don't you have something to do tomorrow?
I'm afraid you won't be able to leave if you go upstairs.
Good night.
Thanks.
I've signed
I've signed it.
Take a look.
Why do you agree?
Things have changed.
You can confirm
No problem.
Let's go through the payment procedure.
I'm in a hurry.
Armanda, no matter what,
thank you for your recognition.
You're very talented. I'm sure.
But it doesn't matter to me.
I'm not professional in dessert.
Do you know why I chose you?
Why?
I like your determination.
You won't change once you're certain.
Of course, you even terminated the contract with me.
Do you like Xia Anran?
I'm sure.
In an uncertain world,
I'm most certain about loving her.
This city
I don't know since when
become so romantic.
It doesn't suit me.
I'm really leaving.
Good luck.
I heard you made up.
It's just a small gift.
Delivery.
You're welcome.
Jiajia, what is this?
How do I wear this?
An'an.
Just come in.
I didn't change the password.
The password.
I should change it.
What if the bad guy comes in?
What should I do?
Of course you're not a bad person.
I am.
Someone is knocking.
No one.
Are you hallucinating?
Why is nobody here?
This child is safe.
Anran.
My mom.
Haohao is not picking up.
Here.
Be careful.
Why is the tie still here?
It's safe.
What are you doing?
He was looking for something.
Go.
Mom.
Why didn't you tell me you were back?
I'll tell you what else is fun.
I want surprise.
Yeah.
By the way, Anran,
Aunt Tan is back.
Let her stay here for now, okay?
Mom,
Don't bother her.
I'll book a hotel for you.
What hotel?
I’ll stay here.
Okay, auntie.
Well, Lin Hao and Shen Yu are staying there.
His room is available.
You can stay here.
Okay.
Let me show you the room.
Let's go. Okay.
Let's go.
This way.
What do you think?
Great.
I won't beat around the bush.
Give A&H back to Louis.
He'll compensate you for the compensation within a reasonable range.
In exchange,
I won't expose
to the president.
Why do you think you can defeat me
you can defeat me?
Zhang Ran doesn't want to cut the table with the photographer.
out of friendship or interests.
we both know it.
Didn't you
because
Is that why you're under his control now?
You can eat whatever you want.
Don't talk nonsense.
Do you have evidence?
This is a photographer.
When I was filming the cover for V magazine,
the side photographer took a photo
that he reached out to molest me.
The editor-in-chief of V magazine was Zhang Ran.
Someone reported him for personal gains.
There are some words in my phone
in my phone.
Some of them included you.