I must make it hard for you.
I want you to be happy, Ko Sang Sik.
If you consider me for a tiny bit,
you could let go of the past.
I thought it was behind me, but...
Okay, then.
We can bury our past for each other.
I can't look at you...
as if nothing happened.
I came here to be happy.
And there were such moments.
But for his sake,
I realize that I can't stay here.
(Second to Last Love)
(Episode 14)
What? What's happened?
She packed her stuff and left.
Didn't she reach out to you?
To me? Why would she?
It was you who signed the lease.
You're right. Hold on.
My word.
I'm sorry for not saying goodbye.
I'll contact you later.
I didn't know she had texted.
Where were you when she left?
We were at the stable because
Honey has been unwell.
Did you give him the bracelets?
Right, here.
Why do you have them?
I was cleaning out your desk...
and found out that she left it there.
Why didn't you give it back sooner?
So you packed your things and left?
Yes.
What about your other stuff?
There is a storage place you can rent.
Unbelievable.
I don't mind having you crash here,
but why would you run like a fugitive?
I don't know.
Do you know what this looks like?
It's like you're a newlywed...
who came running from your first fight.
- What?
- You left Jun Woo...
and poured out your feelings.
So why are you running away
instead of being happy?
I didn't run away, he did.
I feel sorry for the guy.
Life isn't that long.
So why live miserably because of his past?
Solve the next question on your own.
It's already autumn.
We broke up.
Ye Ji, I know a great study cafe.
Would you like to go with me?
Don't text during class.
- Are you finished?
- Yes.
You guys, it's not speed that counts.
You should be on point.
The same goes for life.
It's not about going faster,
but knowing where you're headed.
Have that sense of direction.
Mr. Park, I need the bathroom.
Mr. Park, I need the snack bar.
I'm hungry.
Goodness.
Whose turn is it for parent speaker day?
- Ye Ji.
Ask someone to come in next time.
Okay.
Don't you think this is a better spot?
You're right.
The place has great facilities,
but isn't widely known yet.
It could be a dating spot in the drama.
- Right.
- Then it's settled.
Let's hope it brings in more tourists.
- Chief Ko.
- Yes?
(Chief Ko, hang in there)
Are you feeling unwell?
It's nothing.
So which spot should we go with?
Something is really up with you.
Chief Ko.
Is this how you handle your work?
You must have some connection
with Producer Gang...
to take her there and mess it up.
What connection?
Why show her a non-operating ferry...
to create such a mess?
The city promised active support
to the production teams...
that were competing for the drama.
Active support?
You should have kicked out
the troublemakers...
and even canceled their win.
As for the ferry,
I assigned you to make it float.
Exactly.
Despite using the taxpayers' money
with a reckless budget,
there were shoddy repairs, a collusion,
and more to investigate.
What did you say?
Are you saying it was because
of botched repairs?
A contractor is working on it,
so look forward to how my team
promotes and handles it.
What if you waste this investment?
Then there won't be a drama to produce,
and you won't keep your job.
Keep that in mind.
Boss.
- Boss.
- There you are.
What happened? Why did you move out?
Well, it just happened.
We were so worried.
Who?
My brother and the entire family.
I'm grateful.
I mean, where are you staying?
Let's go in.
- Producer Gang, congratulations.
- Thank you.
Hello.
We got the Woori City Drama.
I'm sorry.
You don't seem to know this industry.
Productions could get put on hold...
or not get aired despite all the work.
Okay. I'll work hard.
I hope you enjoy our drama.
Does she get what I said?
The girl should leave at this point.
- Leave?
- Why?
How could she not in this case?
But that wouldn't be true love.
Exactly. Why would the girl leave
if she wants to stay?
But it doesn't add up for them.
They could be feeling awkward and uneasy,
but it's all in the past now.
Why would that be a problem?
Shouldn't their bond grow deeper?
The guy can't bear looking at her.
So what choice does she have?
I wouldn't leave.
They should face it together.
That's real love, and it's what he needs.
Why can't you see my point?
Are all young people like this?
Am I being lame?
Jun.
Do you work here now?
Yes.
Right, I see.
I heard about Min Ju.
Yes.
It must have been hard.
No, I'm okay.
- What about you?
- I've recovered.
And my feelings are getting better.
Yes, that's good.
I've been working hard as a model,
and I take acting lessons.
Really? That's great.
Gang Min Ju set me up with it.
It's a first for me to love something
other than you.
I see.
Min Ju is better for you than me.
You're still a good person to me.
I know.
Okay. Good.
All right.
The press conference is in two days.
How can the male lead quit?
That's ridiculous.
We'll have to convince him.
There is even this poster shoot.
- It won't work.
- What?
He's in a legal battle against
his former agency.
And being a rookie actor,
he seems to lack confidence
against Na Joo Yeon.
Wait a minute.
Look at the time.
Why isn't he here yet?
What now? There isn't time.
How about Mr. Wook?
He's preparing for another drama.
I know the drama's director.
He called to vent about Mr. Wook,
saying it would do well to replace him.
Seriously?
Figures. Only you can handle him.
But how do we convince the actor?
We need what he wants.
There might be something like that.
PR ambassador of Woori City.
Right.
Woori City's PR ambassador?
With a city drama underway,
shouldn't we have a new face
that represents the city?
I see.
How about Mr. Wook?
Do you mean from the grape festival?
He helped us manage the grape crisis.
Yes, all the farmers are grateful.
Mr. Wook can be our lead in the drama,
and serve as our PR ambassador.
But is that feasible?
Whose idea was this?
Producer Gang suggested it, of course.
You two make a great team.
Why don't you make a move on it?
Now excuse me, I have a date planned.
Ta-da.
I'm here.
You should come on time.
I was here ten minutes before.
What? Then why are you late?
I watched you from over there.
My word, really?
I can't believe you did that.
Why does that matter?
I found you very lovely.
I came early to capture the moment...
when you are waiting here for me.
Goodness, you're making me blush.
Isn't it nice? The Wind Hill.
Like those pinwheels there,
people might appear glamorous.
But we all come like the wind...
and disappear like morning dew.
We don't have much time left,
so don't go home tonight.
What?
Spend the night with me.
My goodness.
What are you saying?
Goodness me.
People are staring. Stop that.
They must be jealous.
My word.
With all of you here today,
we're honored to have Mr. Wook
deliver his special lecture.
Let's hear about his journey
in life as an actor...
and give him a warm welcome.
I have everything I need.
There is air that I can breathe...
and passion that fuels my dream.
But most importantly,
every day is unpredictable...
Since each day is unpredictable...
In this unpredictable life...
You don't know who you'll meet
or where you'll end up?
Yes, bingo.
Life is a gift, so don't waste it.
You don't know what hand
you'll get dealt next,
so take life as it comes at you...
to make each day count.
Make it count.
Titanic.
Bingo.
It's a quote from "Titanic."
Give him applause.
What's he doing here?
There is Mr. Wook!
You must have wheels on your feet.
Are you on board with it?
I'll think about it.
There isn't time. You have to decide.
The grape festival improved your image.
You could even be the PR ambassador.
Okay, I'll think about it.
Why did he come here?
Did he already leave?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
- You're the Titanic guy.
- Yes.
Here.
What's this?
Take a look at it on your way.
You'll like it.
And if you do, please contact me.
Okay.
Look, Director Kim.
I'm not saying I won't do it.
But you keep brushing off my opinion.
Do you take me for a mindless drone?
I'm a person with a mind and emotions!
Forget it.
This is so annoying.
The grape festival...
would've been a total disaster
without Mr. Wook.
I sent grapes abroad for the first time.
That made me so proud.
Since he's a world star,
I thought he was nothing like
us common people.
But thanks to him,
I could pay my granddaughter's tuition.
I was too busy to watch dramas,
but after shipping grapes to China,
I bawled my eyes out.
That made me so happy.
I shed tears of joy.
Really? Mr. Wook said "Yes?"
Okay. Thank you.
That's great! Boss.
Mr. Wook decided on our drama.
He's going to appear in our drama.
Really?
How did he decide so fast?
You see, Chief Ko from Woori City...
had it out with him in person.
What? Really?
Saying he trusts your skills and insight,
he called the City Hall...
and assured them it would surely succeed.
Really? That's great.
Boss.
Shouldn't you at least
thank Chief Ko for it?
Goodness, is this a study cafe?
- Isn't it nice?
- Yes.
People study here these days.
I see.
I'm glad you're here.
First, let's check Ye Ji's learning style.
She scored the highest in visual learning.
Studying in a visually soothing space...
might be the most effective.
Then we'd like such a spot for her.
Okay.
Hello.
You're Hyun Seok, right?
Yes.
Ye Ji, did you enroll here?
I'm not here because of you.
- Dad, let's go.
- Okay.
Hyun Seok, just try to get along.
I don't know what caused the rift,
but kids your age are all buddies.
Ye Ji is more than just a friend.
Okay, then.
Are you good with Hyun Seok?
No.
Then what?
I can't get my heart
to soften up toward him.
But all I need is one real apology.
You said you wouldn't see anyone.
Did you intentionally go there
to run into Hyun Seok?
No, I'm just going to study.
What? What's this?
What?
- Wait a minute.
- You look good together.
Did you have a date with her?
No. Goodness.
Dad, are you dating her?
I said no.
Why did she move out suddenly?
You see...
Did you fight?
So you did.
Then you're dating her.
You're so sneaky.
What? Sneaky?
What's the big deal?
It didn't work out with Uncle Jun Woo.
Patch it up. Why make her move?
You're a man without manners.
What did you say?
Adult relationships seem harder.
She even had to move out.
- Let's eat.
- It looks delicious.
Sang Sik isn't eating again.
I know why he's not eating right.
What do you know?
It's because of our neighbor lady.
What are you talking about?
Uncle Jun Woo, are you okay?
Are you guys bothered that
I know all this stuff?
Why would I be bothered?
You're just smart.
I don't really care.
They're adults who can sort it out.
What's that about adults?
Not having breakfast again?
No, I'm not feeling well.
You go ahead.
Just tell her sorry.
If you're into her, just apologize...
and bring her back here, holding hands.
What are you talking about?
It's nothing.
You, Hyun Seok, and all men are the same.
Turning into adults,
we say "Not yet" and "That won't do"
as we become more cautious.
But as we live in adulthood,
perhaps the words "not yet..."
is nothing but fear and cowardice.
Turning into adults,
we say "I should or shouldn't have,"
and repeatedly regret the choices we make.
But even if they feel wrong,
let's remember that was our best.
Hello?
Yes, I'm nearby there.
What brings you two here?
It's just for something.
I'll leave you to talk.
Thanks.
I don't know what happened
with my brother,
but how can you leave like this?
There's still time left on the lease,
so if you're overwhelmed,
just spend a few days outside
and then come back.
It's not that simple.
Let's just end the lease.
Well, there is this situation.
Why? What's the matter?
It's because of Hun.
Preparing for his study abroad,
I already submitted the lease papers
as evidence of sponsorship.
Really?
How did my brother upset you?
What did he do wrong?
Me and my family will do better, okay?
Some say food is a feast for the eyes.
That's why plating is important.
The Nordic colors and simplicity...
elevate the taste of the food.
What?
I need to take a picture.
Did you upload everything?
Yes, take a look. Do you like it?
Goodness, you're a great photographer.
This comes with good sense.
You're superb.
What, why is this only shots of my face?
What?
I was just taking random shots.
Did you unintentionally fall...
for my handsome face?
Sang Sik should learn social media.
He wouldn't be interested.
The city blog is even a hassle for him.
But he should keep learning.
That way, he can keep contact
even from a distance.
With whom?
That's a good idea.
Should I handle her?
Okay?
Okay.
- Boss.
- Yes?
Do you post on social media?
No, I used to post, but not anymore.
Why not?
It's just a hassle.
Sharing what belongs in a diary...
with the public is a bit too much.
Now it's flooded with ads, anyway.
As a star director, she used to get
comments like a celebrity.
That's what I'm saying.
Posting updates to promote
about our drama...
would be a good thing.
My account doesn't get many views.
Should I reactivate yours?
That's a good idea.
To promote the drama?
Perhaps we should.
Social media?
Yes.
You've become a star since
the Woori City song,
so it's a chance to promote the city.
I couldn't manage after making
something like that.
Just post about tourist spots,
safety guidelines for facilities,
wildfire, heatwave, earthquake warnings,
and all that kind of stuff.
That sounds pretty good.
Once you have an account,
you'll get used to managing it well.
I'll activate one for you.
Sure, let's do that.
Name, Ko Sang Sik.
So she can't return your money?
Not for quite some time.
Why don't you just talk to him?
I already tried before leaving.
You decided to keep away...
for the sake of the other person.
But I don't buy that.
You claim you left for him,
but perhaps you left because
he didn't ask you to stay.
Give it some thought.
Hang on.
Hello. I'm with a friend now.
Goodness, was that today?
I can't believe that I forgot.
Okay, I got it.
What's it about?
It was the student I mentioned.
I promised to accompany him
to the city education fair.
Today is the last day.
I'm okay, so you should go.
Then I'll see you at home.
You should head home first.
All right.
- Sorry.
- No problem.
How did you like it?
It was very helpful. Thanks.
Where are you going? One more drink.
For crying out loud.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
What's with this guy?
Just move along.
You're looking good.
How much older are you?
She looks at least ten years older.
He might be her son.
- What did you say?
- Let's just go.
You can't leave yet.
There is trash on the ground.
Just move along if you're drunk, okay?
Lady, don't bother with kids
when you have men like us.
Please don't...
What are you doing?
What's this kid's problem?
Look, let's just go.
Let go. I'm going because of you.
I can't with those geezers.
I'm embarrassed they're my age.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
You're not hurt?
I'm okay.
My word.
(People who you might know)
(Ko Sang Sik)
Goodness, this is unexpected.
These are recent updates.
Shouldn't you thank Chief Ko for it?
I wanted to drop a thank you
about Mr. Wook.
As the SBC's producer,
let me express my gratitude.
This Wednesday after work,
I'll wait in front of Cheonglim Station.
Sorry.
You should have stayed out longer.
Why would I be out all night?
You could if you like him.
He's my student.
Right. You hate younger guys.
But he was quite manly today.
What?
Drunk guys were coming at me.
Just move along, okay?
What are you doing?
That must have been nice.
Dating must be as fun as this.
Has he contacted you?
Why would he?
But are you waiting for him?
Since he helped with work,
I messaged him online to meet me.
But who knows?
Heartbreak is also a part of love.
It's not over yet.
Are you here with your friends
for a live broadcast?
Yes.
I recently looked up your dramas...
- and watched them.
- Really?
Every single one of your works...
strangely touched my heart.
And they weren't just light entertainment,
so there was a lingering feeling.
That made me like you even more.
But you were cool before that
and quite modern.
So what did you want to tell me?
Just get to know my dad.
What?
I've seen you two bickering a lot,
but friendship would work for now.
For now?
Best friends don't break up.
But it happens to people in love
and married couples.
You know everything.
Of course. I've been there with Hyun Seok.
Aren't you hungry? Let's grab some food.
No, I know you're busy.
I should get back anyway since
my friends are waiting.
Really?
Then I won't stop you.
Could you do something for my class...
- What?
- Never mind.
I'll get going.
Okay.
(Min Ji Seon)
What's the happy news you
want to tell me first?
I got picked as a sub-model
for Woori City.
Really? Do you mean with Mr. Wook?
Yes.
That's great news. Congratulations.
It's all thanks to you.
No, it was an open audition.
I'm a model with good skills,
unlike my acting.
Your wish came true.
You said this is your second home.
Do you have a date here?
Jun.
Is there good news?
Ji Seon was picked as our city model.
I'm only a sub-model.
That's just as great.
Really? That's great. Congratulations.
There is something I want to ask you.
Me, too.
Among the characters in our drama,
there is an excellent chef like you.
I thought you could help with
preparing the food.
Mi Rye told me about it.
So you're in need of a food stylist,
right?
Exactly.
That sounds good.
Thanks a lot.
No worries.
I should be there for you as a neighbor.
Your neighbor?
That's what I want to ask you.
Get some rest.
Rest?
You should return to rest at home.
I truly have the best neighbors.
All your family members asked me
to come back.
Well, except for one person.
I see.
All right.
One more time.
Great.
(Ko Sang Sik)
(I wanted to drop a thank you note
to Mr. Wook.)
(Unread)
The PR ambassadors are here.
Chief Ko, the drama posters are out!
Got it.
Can you email me pictures of that?
Sure.
Actually, never mind.
Let's see here.
Ms. Han, out of the way.
Chief Ko, do you post on social media?
- Yes.
- Really? Let me see.
- No.
- We can follow each other.
I'll find your username.
(Read)
He read the message.
Hello, Ye Ji.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but I have a quick favor to ask.
What is it?
We had many parents come to class...
and explain their various professions.
Today, Ye Ji has invited a special guest.
So let's look forward to it.
Please come in.
Hello.
- Hello.
I'm SBC's Producer Gang Min Ju,
and I make dramas at the network.
- You're pretty.
- That's amazing.
All the repairs have been finished,
including the damaged and botched spots.
All right, good work.
I've discovered during the repairs...
that repair materials were swapped
and rebates were taken,
which yielded quite a profit
for Director Shin.
Are you going to let that go?
No.
But first, we must save the ferry
to cut back on costs.
Do you have any plans?
You wanted to hold the drama's
press conference here.
Yes, it was a suggestion
made by our team.
That's not a bad idea.
Afterwards, it can be a marine museum...
or perhaps a bird museum.
Then should we hold
the press conference here?
Let's do that.
(Moms with daughters to meet on
October 5th at 4 p.m.)
I didn't expect such a huge response.
Thanks for coming on short notice.
No, I enjoyed it more.
Today was such a great time.
It gave me a chance to reflect on my work.
I'll tell Dad about this when I get home.
That you came today.
No, just leave it.
This was a favor I did for you.
Then you two should make up
and get along now.
Okay, get back to class.
All right. Take care.
Bye.
Your new car runs like a dream.
Of course, you helped pick it out.
This is really nice.
It's been a while...
since I went on a drive with a woman.
That's why you shouldn't
get too lost in work.
Come out and enjoy things.
You should feel the seasons change.
Tell me about it.
I'm stuck in my office all the time.
Why is that?
Don't you travel a lot for global trade?
What?
Well, my employees handle that.
All I do is exercise and sign papers off.
For school.
There is Ye Ji's dad.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
You can sit here.
- Is Hae Dam doing well?
- Of course.
You're such a sweet dad to come like this.
I know.
I wish my husband were more like you.
You're too kind.
Ye Ji might have been happier
if her mom were around.
What makes you say that?
Though her grades are impressive,
she has been hanging out
with problematic friends lately.
Problematic friends?
After spending more time with them
instead of Hae Dam,
she ditched her English contest
and goes to idol concerts.
I see.
It's okay, kids her age are like that.
Even Hyun Seok tired of Ye Ji...
and asked her to break up.
Well, about that.
The thing about Hyun Seok is,
Hae Dam keeps showing interest in him.
My little Hae Dam?
That doesn't seem right.
Maybe you should have a talk with her.
I guess I should.
Ye Ji is so fortunate.
She has a dad who communicates with her.
I'm so envious.
(Cheonglim Station)
On this upcoming Wednesday after work,
I'll be waiting in front
of Cheonglim Station.
It's raining.
The forecast was right about it.
- Thanks, I forgot to bring an umbrella.
- No problem.
I'm told Ye Ji brought someone special...
to career lecture day at school.
She did? Who?
It was a producer lady for a network.
The kids were fascinated,
and she was a hit.
Is that right?
Thanks for waiting with an umbrella.
Wasn't it great spicy seafood noodle soup?
Yes, on rainy days...
- Spicy seafood noodle soup is the best.
Hurry along.
Ms. Koo.
Do you know you were my first love?
What?
I'm just saying. You should go.
And take this umbrella.
Hurry.
- Okay. Bye.
- See you.
Min Ju!
Thank you.
I forgot to leave you my key.
Why didn't you buy an umbrella?
I wasn't in the mood.
Why? Did something happen?
He didn't show up like I expected.
I saw him share an umbrella
with another woman.
Seriously? Chief Ko?
Yes.
You might have seen it wrong.
No, I saw it clear as day.
Maybe she's an acquaintance.
He was laughing and acting
too sweet for that.
They even clicked so well.
Is that jealousy I hear?
Don't be absurd.
Then what is it?
I just never thought...
he would be so cool about it
like nothing happened.
Then should he be moping
like at a funeral?
That's not what I mean.
But still, that was wrong of him.
Why don't you just call him?
Why should I?
You're obviously waiting for his call.
- No, I'm not.
- You are.
I said I'm not!
Ye Ji.
Yes?
For your career lecture day,
did you invite someone?
How did you know?
You see, I wasn't prepared for that day,
so I asked our neighbor for a quick favor.
And she came right away.
Really?
- But I wasn't supposed to tell.
- What?
Since it's just something between us,
she said you don't need to know.
Is that what she said?
You should call and thank her.
All right.
(Gang Min Ju)
(Ko Sang Sik)
Your call cannot be connected...
I married him without question
since he was a lawyer,
thinking it would be a secure life.
But who knew he'd cheat on me so quickly?
Hearing your life story tells me...
you've had it really tough.
At our age,
everyone has faced some hardship.
I wanted to become a teacher
respected by students.
But now, I want to live as I please.
A teacher?
What?
I mean, that was my dream before.
I see.
- Here.
- No, this is enough.
What? Let's talk some more.
I'm tired. Let's sleep now.
Sleep?
Aren't you going to?
I must take a shower.
Right, then you should wash up first.
All right.
Are you going somewhere?
I was just putting it down here.
I see.
You should get washed.
I should.
How could he not come home
and have his phone turned off?
Mom, didn't Dad come home?
Don't worry about it. Hurry to school.
I know where he works out.
Do you want to know?
You know where?
It's Aegyeong Sports Center.
That's not it.
Really? But I found a towel.
- A towel?
- It was with his sweatsuit.
So I put it in the hamper.
I'm off to school.
Okay, have a good one.
(Aegyeong Sports Center)
My goodness.
Aren't you friends with my neighbor?
Yes, that's right.
Have you seen my husband here?
Who is your husband?
Park Cheon Su.
There isn't anyone like that.
What? There isn't anyone like him?
Can I ask for your name?
Who are you to ask that?
Come on, Ae Gyeong. Get in the car.
I'm sure he said Ae Gyeong.
Ae Gyeong.
What? Ae Gyeong?
So "Angel without Wings" is...
our neighbor's friend?
Are you sleeping, Richard?
No, not yet.
Sleep if you're tired.
No.
We should do it.
Do what?
What?
Never mind.
Wait a minute.
(Homebody)
The ringtone is "Angel without Wings."
Ae Gyeong.
Just go.
What?
I'm tired, so I should sleep.
I see.
Okay, then.
Have a good night.
What an idiot.
How could I be such a fool?
Hurry up, you'll be late.
What a naive man.
He seems innocent and nice.
No way.
I'm not looking for a first love here.
I was someone's first love.
Who?
My student from the blind date.
He said you're his first love?
Kids often crush on their teachers.
I guess you're both dating now.
- Dating?
- No.
I doubt it. Your faces look thrilled.
- You mean us?
Jinx, you read my mind.
So what are you going to do?
Do what? It's over after moving out.
To be honest, he's not exactly a catch.
The guy is widowed with a daughter,
and he has a bustling family.
Right. You're neither friends nor lovers.
You work together but separately,
so you're not his office wife
or business partner.
He's nothing but my contact for
the drama, so what?
Goodness.
I'm home.
Didn't you hear me?
You're such a lazy sloth.
What? Lazy sloth?
Look, Park Cheon Su!
Where were you last night?
Where did you sleep?
I slept at the sauna, so what?
The sauna?
Which sauna are you talking about?
Good grief.
So now you start talking.
Do I have to not come home
to get you to talk?
How about we don't speak at all?
That's best for us.
Where are you going? Where's my food?
Goodness.
My word.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to exercise.
Really?
- Yes.
- Why all of a sudden?
Not so much for anti-aging,
but to build more strength.
- Strength?
- Yes.
To fight and pull at someone's hair,
I need courage, strength, and guts.
Is that right?
You got the right idea. This way.
(Gang Min Ju)
This Wednesday after work,
I'll wait in front of Cheonglim Station.
Wednesday? It's Thursday.
I should go see her.
Nobody leaves until the 3rd round, okay?
- Let's go.
- Okay, you got it.
All right.
What are you doing? Leave it alone.
Just do your own work.
Why? We always did this together.
I told you to leave it.
Get in here.
You were too busy dating,
so why bother now?
What?
I even cleaned the windows by myself...
when I couldn't even reach them.
Did you really?
You little brat.
That's why I told you to wait.
Look.
Look, Ko Mi Rye. You...
What?
You're too tall, like a giant.
Why are you still so short?
You even eat more than me.
Just step on it.
- Good heavens.
- For crying out loud.
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not okay.
Are these all the filming locations?
Why? Don't you like them?
Well, they're okay.
But we could use someplace special.
Then how about this place?
(Woori City's Suspension Bridge)
Well, I'm not sure.
I'll have to see it myself.
Are you going alone there?
Everyone else is busy with the conference.
Work hard.
Stay safe, Boss.
These are what you asked for.
- Here.
- Thank you.
I got you one each.
This is the Regional Tourism Team.
What? Lost her footing?
Is she badly hurt?
Okay, that's a relief.
Tell me her name and contact details.
Yes, all right.
What happened?
A tourist slipped and fell
on Gamak Mountain.
The emergency team is on its way.
They asked if there was an issue
with the facility.
Chief Ko.
Sir, what's happened?
You need to fence off this place.
She was in there picking acorns.
That's not good. Is anyone else hurt?
No, they're all okay.
You can't go in there.
Collecting acorns like this is illegal.
Illegal?
Why is this such a big deal?
It might not seem like much,
but these acorns feed animals like
squirrels, deer, and raccoons.
If you sweep them from the mountain,
the critters starve in the winter.
Taking acorns like this could even...
get you fined. Did you know that?
- Yes, I did.
- Please don't do it again.
Okay.
Those who are destined will meet.
Even if you try to run.
Even if you circle Earth ten times.
Those who are destined will meet.
Even if you try to run.
Even if you circle Earth ten times.
(Second to Last Love)
A press conference on the ferry?
Problems are sure to arise.
Chief Ko, we're the Audit Team.
Richard Park? I got you now.
You should come with me.
Are you heading home?
Where is Chief Ko?
He went looking for you.
Ko Sang Sik.
Come back.
What should I give up for that?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)