[This drama is fictional, and any similarity
with reality is purely coincidental.]
Ma'am.
Now I understand.
This is my reality.
And this is my future
that will not change.
I was wrong.
I don't want to live like this.
Is being poor a crime?
No.
I'll make having money a crime too.
I will escort you home.
Okay.
[Baek Jenna is pretty, so she's unaffected.
What does being pretty have to do with it?]
[If you're pretty, do you get
to inherit the company?]
[It might be different if she were a son,
but she's a daughter, right?]
[Would they abandon her
just because she's a girl?]
Have you seen this?
Black Dog?
Black what?
Hello, this is Black Dog.
Today
I brought some very interesting news
and the complete summary about
romantic Chairman Baek Joo Won's
love affair.
[His mistress, whom he's been seeing
since the beginning of this year,]
[is the contract teacher, Ha Min Hee!]
Baek Jenna's father's lover is Ms. Ha Min Hee?
Ha Min Hee?
That contract English teacher Ha Min Hee?
Yes!
That's crazy! But how did he find out?
If the kid she's carrying is a boy,
is Baek Jenna done for now?
What to do? It hurts my heart.
[Currently, she is 5 months pregnant,
and it's said to be a boy.]
[Seo Jae Kyung is an alcohol and drug addict.]
[Will the succession plan for the heir,
Baek Jenna, become unclear?]
If you're going to hide something,
you should hide it well…
Oh, no!
Jenna is watching too?
Is this your work too?
What? That Black Dog?
Are you crazy? We're not thugs.
Why would we do such a thing?
Does Baek Jenna also know
she should be embarrassed?
Exactly.
Who is this Black Dog guy?
Find him quickly!
Yes, I will look into it immediately.
I warned you, didn't I?
I won't tolerate any nonsense during my tenure!
You can't even handle one thing like this,
Mr. Kim Jin Seop…
Oh! Do Un, come in.
Hello, Mr. Chairman.
I told you to come say hello sooner.
When it's just the two of us, call me Uncle.
You're having a hard time because of your dad?
Don't worry,
nothing has changed.
I will protect you till the end.
If you're going through a tough time,
you have to tell me.
Stay strong and square your shoulders,
understood?
Yes, Uncle.
That's it.
A sigh is interpreted differently
by the one sighing and the person watching.
Someone else's sigh is seen as sadness,
while one's own sigh is seen as
despair, or something like that.
Anyway,
Baek Jenna and "despair"
don't go well together.
Apologize. I'll accept it.
Apologize?
Why should I?
All you do is bully kids.
That's because you were being played
like an idiot, not knowing a thing!
- What did you say?
- Let's say Kim Hae In's poverty isn't a crime.
But what about her trying to extort money
from me, using her poverty as an excuse?
Do you think I was the only one?
He was being blackmailed too.
Kim Hae In slept with Park Woo Jin.
- Hey!
- Hey, come out.
Hey!
Yeah, I didn't expect you'd apologize.
And Hae In
will wake up.
When that happens, I'll ask everything myself.
Do as you like.
Are you okay?
What if I'm not?
Deep down, you're happy
that I've ended up like this, aren't you?
No.
I'm worried about you.
Cute, isn't it?
Why are you here?
I moved in.
I was going to tell you beforehand,
but you wouldn't answer my calls.
You're hurting my feelings, Jenna.
You know that students are the busiest people.
But is there a reason you'd leave Hannam-dong
to come all the way here?
I'm not really into houses.
I like looking down from above.
Then enjoy the view, from above.
Jenna.
I decorated your brother's room.
Do you want to see it?
I think you once said
that used to be your mom's room.
How many empty rooms do you think there are here?
It's south-facing, so it gets great sunlight.
Parents should be in the room
right next to each other.
It's a problem if they're too far away.
No matter how much you hate it,
you have to accept it now.
You're going to have a younger brother.
You should act like a big sister,
be willing to compromise,
and share.
You are smart, Jenna.
You understand what I'm saying, right?
A younger brother?
Even if he's born, he'll just
be a half-rate life, won't he?
I'm truly begging you like this.
If you could just give her another chance…
Please…
My daughter, I made some
delicious curry in the morning.
Make sure to have dinner at home.
Here.
Sun Joo,
have you ever been sued?
Sued?
That jerk Hwang Bo Seok won't agree to settle?
Yeah.
That jerk said he'd sue me for school violence.
I am even investigated
because of the Oh Si Eun incident.
If the school violence case opens,
it'll be recorded on my school register,
and I'll be expelled.
What?
What about employment in the future?
My life will be over.
But
all of this
is because I didn't know my place
and entered Cheongdam International High School.
Is there any way out?
I've come this far.
I don't want to give up just like this.
And I don't want anything taken from me.
Right. You can't let them take anything.
You definitely can't give up.
There's only one way.
You have to get into the Diamond 6.
The Diamond 6 is above the law, you know.
Even if they commit a crime,
no one can touch them.
How am I supposed to get in there?
The way I see it,
you don't have any other options right now.
You can only get into the Diamond 6
and receive immunity.
Diamond 6?
Hello?
Baek Jenna, it's me.
I have a favor to ask--
No.
I want to make a deal.
My life is on the line. Let's meet now.
But I can't now.
I could
really end up dying.
I can't go out right now.
You either come to my house or…
To your house?
Are you crazy?
You want me to get you into the Diamond 6?
I'm not asking for a favor.
I'm proposing a deal.
A deal?
Do you have anything to propose a deal to me?
I'll give you
Min Yul Hee's necklace.
What can you do with that necklace?
Hey, Equal Opportunity Leech,
don't be mistaken.
Diamond 6?
You can never give me something
that matches that class.
I'll do anything.
Just help me this one time, please.
At this rate, my life is completely over.
Yeah, that…
Equal Opportunity Leech.
You probably won't understand.
Because you live looking down
at the world from a place like this.
But as for me,
if I slip up even once, it's really over.
So,
just this one time.
Just once, please.
Just once.
Help me.
Do you know why I called you to my house?
So you could see
why we are different.
What?
If you're done talking, then leave.
You should say something that makes sense.
You crazy punk!
Are you threatening me right now?
Why are you so curious about
whether the baby in my womb is a boy or a girl?
I'll just make him Chairman Baek's son!
The heir of Hanmyeong Group.
Do you still not get it?
Wow! He's really handsome!
Hey, Baek Jenna!
If I bring something suitable,
we can make a deal, right?
Are you still talking about that?
Baek Jenna?
I was curious,
but now that I've seen your face,
you pass.
Pass?
Who are you?
And while you're good enough now,
come a little prettier tomorrow.
Don't be late.
The elders don't like tardiness.
Ah.
Please continue your conversation.
What is that?
Hey!
Who is that guy?
Stay there.
Jenna, they're hilarious.
They don't even greet you now?
You look terrible.
How is your mother doing?
She's really shocked, right?
But still, congratulations.
Even though it will be born out of infidelity,
a sibling is still a sibling.
Come to think of it,
isn't Ms. Min Hee really amazing?
For a contract teacher?
Didn't you understand what I said?
I believe I told you
I know who killed Kim Hae In.
Who died?
Kim Hae In didn't die, did she?
Don't you...
ever wake up.
The next time, I might really kill you.
She's lying there like a corpse,
but she's not dead.
Keep that in mind.
You're the one who started it, right?
One of us will end it.
Of course.
But it won't be me.
Dad, Dad.
Go inside and sleep.
Oh! My daughter is back?
- Go inside.
- Okay.
Alright, I'll sleep.
[Kim Hye In]
Die!
Are you threatening me right now?
Why are you so curious about whether
the baby in my womb is a boy or a girl?
I'll just make him Chairman Baek's son!
The heir of Hanmyeong Group.
Do you still not get it?
Hey, Kim Hye In?
Where are you?
What is it? Why did you suggest
meeting in such a creepy place?
You said you wanted to make a deal.
And no one should know about it.
You're dumber than I thought.
I told you, the necklace doesn't matter.
At least there should be some CCTV footage.
What will you do with this?
Really?
Then,
how about this?
You crazy punk! Are you threatening me right now?
Why are you so curious about whether
the baby in my womb is a boy or a girl?
I'll just make him Chairman Baek's son!
The heir of Hanmyeong Group.
Do you still not get it?
How about it?
Isn't this enough for a deal?
I don't have time.
Will you take it or not?
The more I look at Jin Wook,
the more handsome he looks.
Thank you.
He came from a good bloodline, right?
You take after your mom.
Why are you so late? We have an important guest.
Nice to meet you. We meet again.
Seeing the two of you like this,
I think we could set a wedding date right away.
Whose daughter is this?
You've raised her well.
Oh, you flatter me.
What do you think you're doing?
If I had known it was this kind of
meeting, I wouldn't have come.
- Jenna…
- How can you
go this far and be so selfish?
Sit down and talk.
Baek Jenna!
I'll go see what's wrong.
Sure.
I'm disappointed, Baek Jenna.
Get lost.
It's not like I'm thrilled about this situation,
getting married as soon as I come to Korea.
Marry?
But
it's not so bad that I'd scream about it.
Don't you think?
It seems like you and I
are both just pieces on a chessboard
laid out by those old folks.
I think we need to do some thinking
about...
whether we'll be pawns...
or if we'll move the pieces ourselves.
Don't we?
Could you please just get lost?
I also have my thoughts.
Oh, really?
I'm looking forward to it.
Chairman Baek?
He's so lost in his love affair
that he's raised his child like absolute trash.
You should be the one to tame her properly.
Yes, Father.
Do you know why I called you back?
You are different from your elder brothers.
You know that, right?
- Yes.
- You will have to
prove your abilities yourself.
Chairman Baek…
Yes.
Today, I had dinner with my father
and Chairman Baek of Hanmyeong Group.
Baek Jenna was there too.
Don't worry, Mom.
You know that
I don't play games I'll lose, right?
And I think...
it's going to be quite fun.
Mr. Director,
didn't you make a promise to me?
As you requested, Jenna's
disciplinary action is being discussed.
But why is Baek Jenna still walking
around the school so confidently?
As her friend, you know it as well,
that Hanmyeong Group's sponsorship is the largest.
And Jenna is also
the only daughter of Hanmyeong Group.
The mistress of Chairman Baek
was a teacher at our school.
Furthermore, she got pregnant.
And his daughter, Baek Jenna, attends that school.
Don't you think this is enough
to convene an ethics committee?
Just issue the disciplinary action.
Then, I will proceed with the next steps myself.
I'll get Baek Jenna
kicked out
of Diamond 6.
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
Yul Hee just came by
and asked about your disciplinary action.
This isn't a request from some commoner,
so I can't keep pretending
I don't know about it, can I?
Let's talk more at school tomorrow.
I also have something urgent to discuss with you.
The moment the media finds out
Kim Hae In's incident was an attempted murder
and not a suicide, they'll go into a frenzy.
Wouldn't your position as
chairman be in jeopardy too?
So,
if I accept this?
Then my friends and I will graduate
quietly as if nothing happened,
and Hanmyeong will continue
to be your biggest sponsor.
Of course,
your position as chairman will remain unchanged.
Then I'll take that as your
acceptance and be on my way.
I'll leave this as a sign of trust.
When did you say
the Oh Si Eun case would be closed?
The investigation will be
concluded within this week.
What's the scenario?
Hospital records show that student Oh Si Eun
had been suffering from depression
and showed signs of suicide,
such as overdosing on tranquilizers.
In particular, the bereaved family
does not want things to get noisy
and has requested the case be closed quietly.
Wrap it up that way.
And erase all of Kim Hye In's
investigation records.
Yes, I will handle it as soon as possible.
Hello.
It's been a while, brothers and sisters.
Lee Sa Rang?
The youngest of Diamond 6!
It's Sa Rang.
So, you're the new member from the first years.
If everyone's here, let's just say what
we have to say and get this over with.
You must all be uncomfortable
being in the same space.
You're here early.
You've never seen me before, right?
My name is Cha Jin Wook,
a transfer student.
And
the new member of this club.
It's a pleasure.
Hey, Baek Jenna,
isn't it proper manners to tell us first
when you're recommending a new member?
There is a spot left by Lee Deok Min.
And I'm telling you just in case,
but I meet the basic requirements to join,
so you don't need to worry.
And
there will be one more new member coming.
What are you talking about?
There are no vacancies.
What are you doing, Baek Jenna?
One of the conditions for joining the Diamond 6
is a top-tier donation.
But isn't there someone among us
who hasn't paid the donation?
Seo Do Un.
I'm sorry,
but you'll have to leave.
What are you doing?
The new member of Diamond 6...
is Kim Hye In.