I've always wondered...
why you hated me as a child.
Why did you hate me so much?
Day after day, it's always saddening...
If I were you...
I would have done the same.
I am a daughter who killed her mom.
Kae In,
what are you saying?
Kae In.
Who are you?
I should have introduced myself sooner. I am Jeon Jin Ho.
Leave.
Kae In!
Are you okay?
I...
remember everything.
It was...
a bright and sunny day...
When I looked at the sky and my mom...
My mom's face...
for a second, I couldn't see it.
Mom.
I was just...
My mom...
I was just trying to call her.
I...
just wanted to ask her to play with me.
Just to take care of me...
But...
mom didn't answer...
Then, I...
I...
No.
It's not like that.
Kae In, you just had a bad dream.
I remember.
Back then...
Mom...
looked at me.
And she was smiling.
This picture...
Where did you find it?
The basement,
you opened it?!
Yes.
Who are you to do so?
WHO ARE YOU TO DO SO?
Get out.
Get out of my house this instant!
I said get out!!!
Episode 15
Trying to forget you
Mom.
Because of me...
Mom...
While trying to save me,
Kae In...
My dad...
I've always wondered why he hated me.
Now, I know.
I would have done the same thing.
If I had a daughter like me...
I'd rather not see her either.
- Tae Hoon.
- Yeah.
I got the new blueprints.
Look over it carefully.
How old is this paper?
While he was at Sang Go Jae,
Jin Ho was rushing through work.
And there wasn't any other draft paper.
What's that?
It's just what it is, you punk.
To save our skins,
it's the Ace of Spades "hidden card".
Ace of Spade... so what is this?
Your job is to print.
Not finding out what it is. Got it?
Just tell me, I'm part of this company too.
You don't tell me anything always.
It's because you can't know.
You know what I mean?
I can't figure it out. Just tell me.
- You can't know.
- Just tell me!
JUST DON'T TALK ABOUT IT!
Are you standing up to me? Huh?
No.
Just do as I told you to.
Hello, I am M Construction's Noh Sang Jun.
Yes, hello, Director.
Excuse me? $200 million?!
He said we had to raise 200 million by the end of the month.
If it's not solved by the end of this month,
then he plans to take legal actions.
I am sorry, Jin Ho.
This is the only choice we have.
This is our company's finished draft of the Dam Arts Center.
I wanted to see what you would say if I brought it to you.
I know this is a little underhanded...
If you could just point out some good or bad points,
then following that, we could make some improvements.
Did Director Jeon request  this?
Of course.
Jin Ho...  I mean Director Jeon...
If it was Director Choi,
he will seriously help by taking a look.
Well, then I'll leave it to you.
You are Noh Sang Jun, correct?
Yes.
If it's the Director Jeon I know, then I know he wouldn't do something like this.
This is a characteristic I see in him.
Or is it that I've misinterpreted him all this time?
No, sir.
That...  I...
Take it back.
Truth is...
our company is having a really hard time.
This isn't something Director Jeon would ask,
but in a state of panic, I came here.
Please, sir.
Go.
I...
I don't know what to say at this moment,
but can you think of this one thing?
I...
am always beside you.
Right now, it may not be much.
No.
Since you're here by my side...
right now, for me,
is everything.
I...
although I am not old-fashioned enough not to misunderstand youths these days,
my daughter is living with a man before marrying...
Jin Ho was living here while paying rent.
You gave him a room to rent?
Let's talk about this later.
Go inside and rest for today.
That Jeon Jin Ho did something he wasn't supposed to.
I've blocked the basement,
so forget what happened.
You can't erase something that has already happened.
Kae In!
Good night.
Thank you very much.
You can be part of the judgment panel this time,
I don't know how to thank you.
The Dam Arts Center Project is fated with me.
I am participating as a judge now.
Ah, right!
I don't know if I'll be of much help.
- Please, have a seat.
- Yes.
You are headed to the Dam Art Gallery?
Yeah...
Ji-Jin Ho... wait...
Your sketch... I just went ahead and gave it to Director Choi.
Sketch?
The Dam Arts Center Project sketch.
That isn't completed yet.
Yeah, that's right, but...
I think he can give us some pointers.
So I went ahead and gave the plans to him.
What do you mean by that?
The sketch that was in the black case.
I showed it to him.
The thing in there... You showed it to Director Choi?!
I know that you hate things like that,
but if we show it to him first,
he will be more considerate of us.
Aigoo, I didn't draw that.
Then who did?
Professor Park Chul Han.
Kae In's father.
Th-then ho-how do you ha-have Professor Park's sketches?
Hey! Where are you going?
What do you mean? I have to go get them back.
Why did you do something I didn't even ask you to?!
Jin Ho...
Where do I find Director Choi?
Before the judgment is set,
this set of blueprints I have...
Will you take a look at it?
Yes.
Please sit.
Kae In, how...?  Here...?
Come in.
Yes.
She's designing the Children's Room.
Have a seat.
Yes.
Ah... I see.
Now that your father came, we might as well have a meal together.
You must be shocked to see that your daughter is working at the Dam Art Gallery.
She is still lacking in many ways,
I don't know if she has caused more trouble here.
No.
Miss Park Kae In is very talented.
I think I have good foresight.
I am proud of scouting her and discovering her talent.
Thank you for saying so.
Excuse me... That...
Who is it?
The person who did this?
M Construction's director Jeon Jin Ho.
I don't know if you've heard yet, but Kae In and Jin Ho...
they are dating each other.
Jeon Jin Ho is a person with many talents.
Jeon Jin Ho is here.
This sketch... is it yours?!
I...  That...
IS IT YOURS?!
I'm sorry.
This is my design of the Dam Arts Center from 30 years ago.
Is this the reason you came into our house?
I wasn't trying to steal it,
but I understand your present feelings.
What... are you saying?
What sketch are you saying you stole?
I think there's some misunderstanding.
Jin Ho, go ahead and say it.
Eh?
You're really amazing...
You moved into my house solely because of these plans!
When you got the chance, you searched everywhere in my house.
In the end, you found this sketch.
And you played with my daughter's feelings.
WAS IT FUN?!
That's not it.
My love for Park Kae In has no deception.
How can I trust the words of someone who stole my plans now?
Underhanded bastard!
Father!
Who are you calling "father"?!
Can you please... listen to my explanation?
Please listen to Jin Ho's explanation.
There must be some type of misunderstanding.
Are you still that way?
Not knowing if he has a knife to your neck,
trusting anyone you meet.
To win the Dam Arts Center Project,
he used you!
No...
It wasn't like that.
Right, Jin Ho?
The Dam Arts Center was something that belonged to me.
And he knew that,
so from the start to steal my sketch he came into Sang Go Jae!
If there is some misunderstanding, then say it.
Yes.
What you said was right.
When I first moved into Sang Go Jae,
I had some of those thoughts.
When I heard that the Dam Arts Center's concept would be Sang Go Jae, I wanted to see if I could get some insight.
What did you say just now?
However...
once I started liking Kae In,
I changed my mind.
Because you thought...
that being my son-in-law will benefit you in many ways.
You are okay with that kind of love?
So, is it really because of the Dam Arts Center project...
that you came to Sang Go Jae?
I'm sorry.
I was going to tell you, but...
When?
After you won the Dam Arts Center Project?
With the sketch you stole from my father?
Kae In...
that's not it.
How?
How could you do this to me?
Then...
from the start...
you came close to me just to use me?
Jin Ho!
Did you get the sketch?
I couldn't just sit around and wait because I was so worried.
It's all over.
It's all over?
Professor Park stopped by.
By using Kae In,
and revealing he took the plans, Professor Park was very angry.
Tha- That's not the truth.
That sketch,
I thought Jin Ho made it and took it to Director Choi.
Jin Ho.
I'll go to Professor Park and Director Choi, and figure it all out.
I'll tell them that our company was in bad condition, and this is how it turned out.
And I'll say that we're aiming for a new concept, okay?
Leave it alone.
How can I just leave it alone?
If we call it like this,
that's the end of the company and you.
Wait a second.
It's better to have a talk with Director Choi first.
I said stop it.
I did wrong.
Because I had the wrong intentions when I entered Sang Go Jae.
That's why it happened.
Why did you want to meet again?
Congratulations.
What are you talking about?
Events have changed,
it became favorable to you.
What?
The person who worked with Jin Ho
revealed Professor Park's Dam Arts Center sketch,
as if it were Jin Ho's.
and showed it to Director Choi.
So in the end,
Professor Park's sketch,
Jin Ho stole it.
Now, Jin Ho...
He'll probably lose the director's trust.
Looking at Professor Park's attitude,
it may all be buried away.
Jeon Jin Ho, that crazy bastard...
Call up that person and tell him to pack his stuff.
If you can't do it, then I will.
I'll... do it.
Me as a person..
If I weren't your daughter...
I wouldn't have gotten love
from anybody.
Aren't you going to answer your phone?
What would I have to say?
Why wouldn't you have something to say?
It was my fault you got into Sang Go Jae.
And it was also my fault for continuously saying that you were gay.
And the sketch-
No matter what you did...
they were still my mistakes.
Explaining everything now won't help.
The truth doesn't disappear.
Then are you going to keep ignoring Kae In's phone calls?
Are you going to keep taking the blame for things that you didn't do?
Look how far you and Kae In went.
If you two are breaking up, I will feel so sorry.
How can I look at your face?
Jin Ho,
let's just find them and beg.
You don't have to say anything, okay?
Let me do the talking.
You and Kae In can't end things like this.
Even if you end it,
let's clear up the misunderstanding.
If you break up with Kae In now...
how will Kae In face her father?
Anybody there?
Oh gosh, Professor Park!
It's a pleasure to see you face to face after only seeing pictures of you.
I'm sorry, but, who are you?
Oh, yes.
I greeted you on the phone once.
I'm Han Yoon Sub from Mirae Construction.
Oh, yes.
But, then,
what brings you here?
What are you doing, brat?
Introduce yourself to your father-in-law, quick.
Pleased to meet you.
I am Han Chang Ryul.
He's my son.
I heard Jeon Jin Ho stole Professor Park's plans.
Underhanded bastard!
I warned you so much not to get close to him...
By chance... did you know about this?
About why Jin Ho came into Sang Go Jae?
In the end, you found out too.
To prevent you from getting more scars...
It would have been better if you wouldn't have known...
Even after experiencing this,
you won't still have feelings for him, right?
Lying about being gay to get in here,
it was all to get Professor Park's sketch.
Isn't that what you and your father are doing as well?
Everything you said about getting back together,
was all because of the Dam Arts Center.
Your father finding himself here...
They're all the same reasons.
Kae In!
I'm not like that!
Everything...
it's all the same.
You must have been very shocked.
Having been caught head-on with so many problems.
But that Jin Ho...
did something unimaginable.
Jin Ho, he has always harbored some bad blood with my family.
So then,
he knew that my son was dating your daughter,
but he still managed to get close to her.
Please don't talk like that.
That's not it.
This man...
What is your relationship with him?
We were dating before.
We broke up because it was my fault.
Young people breaking up and getting together, isn't that what they do these days?
Well anyways,
you know my son had good intentions
when using Do-Il Furniture.
He bought all of your daughter's furniture designs.
Having your own name as a brand
is every designer's dream.
Do-Il Furniture...
You did that?
The launching...
We aren't fully responsible for it.
So don't mind it too much.
If you end it,
let's still clear up all the misunderstanding.
If you bear the misunderstanding and break with her...
what will Kae In be to her father?
Aigo, it is an honor that you can come to be a judge.
Thank you very much.
Coming here without prior notice,
it seems very impolite of us. We are very sorry.
I'm sorry.
Chang Ryul...
Yes, father-in-law.
Are your feelings for my daughter sincere?
Yes.
Of course.
Back then,
I gave her so much hardship.
And although Kae In's heart isn't opened up to me yet,
I am prepared to wait,
and give effort.
When my daughter opens her heart to you,
then, I guess we will be meeting again.
I will do my best.
Let's talk.
If it's about Jin Ho,
then I don't want to talk.
So...
are you saying you'll keep meeting up with the man who stole my blueprints?
Although I'm not sure...
there has to be a reason.
Jin Ho would not cause something that he would get caught so quickly for.
He is not that foolish of a person.
Because he is so sly,
he obviously did it after he captured your heart.
Anyways, about the Chang Ryul lad...
he seems okay.
You don't know him.
What kind of pain Chang Ryul gave me.
That pain...
How Jin Ho cleared all that away...
How could you still want to protect Jeon Jin Ho?
If he, to whom you feel so grateful,
really is that innocent,
Then he should have come down by now and explained everything.
But yet, he didn't.
You said you wanted to talk.
But yet, you're not listening to what I have to say.
You don't even believe me.
Is this why you came into my house?
I mean,
you should at least come and explain something.
Yes, Young Sun.
I heard everything from Sang Jun.
Don't tell me you met with Jin Ho?
No.
Really?
What I heard from Sang Jun, he said that Jin Ho left to go see you.
He didn't come.
I heard that there was a big problem because of the sketch.
- I'm hanging up.
-  Hold on, don't hang up.  I'm asking you to listen.
Jin Ho didn't do it.
It wasn't Jin Ho's intention to steal them.
What do you mean by that?
Sang Jun, this moron,
took it by mistake to let Director Choi see it.
But when Jin Ho went to go find them, he encountered your father.
But, the fact that he came into my house with a motive...
Yeah...
That's right.
Anyways, with knowing that situation, it wasn't Jin Ho's fault.
Alright, hanging up.
Hey!
Can you be eating at a time like this?
Father...
you think I am a bad person...
and want to punish me, don't you?
When I did wrong,
I can't even beg for forgiveness.
I'm pathetic, right?
But father...
I...
There is nothing I can do for that woman.
Being recognized by her father...
is the only wish in her heart.
But I shamed her in front of her father.
I'm pretty useless, aren't I?
Where are you?
I'm at the tourist rest-stop that we've been before.
Whether you get this message or not, I'll wait.
What did you wish for?
That us two,
that there will never be a time where we have anything to hide from each other.
I was very angry before,
so I said we should never meet again...
I, as a person... can't do it.
I would like to give you one last chance to explain things.
Until you tell me what happened yourself,
I won't believe any of that.
I don't care if I see it with my own eyes,
I don't care what other people say.
Say it... Say that it's a misunderstanding.
Say that it wasn't on purpose.
That the truth is, it's not because of you,
but because of Sang Jun, it became like that.
It was all me.
Don't lie to me.
Look at my eyes, and tell me.
Going into Sang Go Jae, pretending to be gay,
and the sketch.
It was all me.
I don't know what Sang Jun said,
but after hearing the Dam Arts Center's concept was Sang Go Jae, I entered the house.
And to not get caught, I pretended to be gay.
And then I found Professor Park's sketch.
I imagined that I hit the jackpot.
You were my woman already,
even if I got discovered, what can you do?
This is what I thought.
Now do you understand?
What's wrong with you, Jin Ho?
Why are you being like this to me?
I made use of you all this time,
yet you still believe me like a fool.
That's why you got thrown away by Chang Ryul.
Do you think I would like a girl like you?
You love me.
That's why you looked at me with those eyes.
Because my heart was in pain,
and you hugged me.
I pretended to love you
to do whatever I could to succeed.
Because tricking a girl like you isn't difficult.
Then...
why didn't you lie to the end?
Why are you telling me now?
If you have just told me it wasn't you, I would have believed you.
Only you will trust me.
Professor Park wouldn't have.
Lying to you isn't difficult,
but Professor Park is not that stupid.
Don't be like this.
You're trying to give me scars on purpose.
Don't talk like that.
You're not someone like this.
No.
The person you knew from the start was like this.
I'm telling you this now,
only because I am feeling a little pity for you.
Because you're sorry,
That's why you're being like this.
Please tell me that.
I'm not sorry to you for anything.
I'm just frustrated things didn't go as I planned.
So...
don't ever appear in front of me again.
I'm not going to love Park Kae In.
I don't love Park Kae In.
I've never loved Park Kae In.
Where have you been, coming home at this time of night?
Where have you been?!
Like you told me to do,
I broke up with Jin Ho.
Have you decided to come back home?
Yes.
You broke up with that young lady, right?
Thank you.
You seem to look alright.
I'm worried because there seems to be more work to be done than I expected.
As stated in the contract, I need to finish by next week.
Because of that, I think I will have to work through nights too.
Miss Kae In...
with so many things going on, it must be hard.
Don't overdo it.
Director, I think you are caring too much about me.
If the other staff members hear of this, they will protest!
You remember what you promised me, right?
Huh?
I want to fulfill that promise with you today.
Follow me.
Oh, did you see Kae In?
Then, you did well.
Although the motive wasn't good,
you didn't do anything wrong after you moved in.
To be honest, after you met Kae In, she completely changed into a different person!
Then even that's good enough.
I ended it with Kae In.
That's right, Kae in...
You broke up?
I'm going to continue the Dam Arts Center project.
Don't be concerned.
It's yummy.
This is good, and that's good too.
Your expression...
It seems like you don't know if food is entering
through your mouth or your nose.
You know you have no acting skills, right?
We, as friends, in times of difficulty or pain,
should always confide with each other.
Tell me.
Tell me what happened with Jeon Jin Ho.
Everything...
It's true that he used me.
From the start...
he didn't...
love me as a woman.
I see.
But Kae In,
do you believe his words?
If it was for success,
then why didn't he go all the way with his "gay lie"?
And...
when he told me he wasn't gay...
do you know what Jin Ho told me?
"I'm sorry.
I am in love with Park Kae In."
That person...
No matter what comes out of his mouth, if you look at his eyes you will know the truth.
Jeon Jin Ho's gaze...
is proof of what he said is true.
I couldn't sleep for a few days, and now I can't get my head straight.
I better go get some sleep.
Aren't you going?
What?
Are you going to meet Kae In?
Jin Ho...
The director wants to see you.
Hey...
It seems that Director Choi hasn't thrown you away just yet.
I thought you would give up.
But you still withheld your feelings.
Pretty brave.
The participant will only be allowed one competition entry.
Are you confident?
Fact is...
I don't know right now.
Even so...
everything I can do,
I plan to do the best I can.
To enter Sang Go Jae,
did you lie about being gay?
Then,
what are your feelings about Kae In?
That...
wasn't a lie, was it?
Whatever my feelings may be...
what use are they now?
When I first met you, I thought that you were a very capable and dependable person.
I discovered feelings that I previously have never felt from you.
However...
no matter how much I tried to understand it,
without knowing everything, I will be defeated.
I...
I've decided that I want to...
trust you one last time.
Because I...
still have a bit of feelings.
Professor Park will be together with me.
So please do your best.
I'm thankful for that...
but it's okay.
From the start, I have never walked the first step properly.
In the end I will. I have confidence in the end result.
The messed up buttons, why don't you try to re-button it correctly this time.
I'm sorry.
Hey, don't you think you can forgive Jin Ho now?
Everything's over...
What's there to forgive?
Do you think it's that easy to just forget about your feelings?
Although the going wasn't smooth,
you know that Jin Ho loves you,
and I know, as well as everybody else.
If you're going to keep talking about that, then let's go.
Okay, okay.  Stay seated.
Just have another drink.
Well...
I heard that their office will need to move again...
And they will have to forfeit their deposit...
Seems like Jin Ho will be tired out...
Hey, Lee Young Sun!
Fine!
Geez... I can't even say anything...
In front of me...
don't talk about that person.
Please, I'm asking you.
I feel more pained whenever I listen to those stories.
So please stop.
Please.
You're still so loyal, really loyal.
Never mind. Just go.
I don't know what the hell you do everyday.
Get up!
Now!
Kae In.
Park Kae In!
What am I doing here?
Oh please, just come and take a look.
I'm sorry.
Please drop Kae In off at home.
Are you joking with me?
Are you really going to be like this?
I have no reason to meet with Kae In anymore.
Fine! I have to go home, so I'll just leave Kae In here.
I don't care about whether someone else takes her somewhere or not.
Kae In, let's wake up, okay?
Oh, Jin Ho!
Why were you so stubborn before?
From now on, this is none of my business.
I will leave it all to you. I'm leaving.
Jin Ho...
Just how much did you drink?
Let me give you a piggyback.
Let go.
You can't even walk properly because you're drunk.
Why did you come?
I'm asking why you came!
I don't know either.
I answered Young Sun's call...
And I came without even knowing what I was doing.
Why should you?
Why would you come?
Didn't we break up?
Therefore, everything's over!
Before you fall over, just get a piggyback.
Why should I?
Do you see me as an easy woman?
When you call me, I'll come.
If you say go, then I'll go?
From now on,
don't ever look for me.
Even if you hear that I died,
pretend that you didn't hear about it.
Why would you die?
I'm so pathetic!
I shouldn't have ever met you.
When I broke up with Han Chang Ryul,
I just...
If I just suffered by myself...
now...
I would've been able to laugh like nothing has ever happened...
by myself.
Please, just get on my back.
Because I met you...
everything has been messed up.
Let go!
Park Kae In's weather forecast for tomorrow...
A moment of clear weather,
after breaking up,
feels like it's overcast from a thunderstorm.
A heart that seems like a tornado...
Everything is a big mess.
And yet...
when I'm on this man's back...
it makes me feel warm.
In the future...
there won't be any chances for me to get on his back...
ever again.
Kae In.
Fa-Father...
Both of you have been drinking til now?
No... This...
You, really...
Even if you are thoughtless...
I said so many times, no matter how young a child is,
the child will know what to do.
You are really beyond help!
I am sorry.
It's late, so just go in.
It wasn't Kae In's fault.
The fault lies with me, so why are you apologizing?
I might be wasting my breath,
that I have no right to be saying anything right now,
however...
all Kae In has done is trust me and love me.
What?
Since now,
do you know what hardships Kae In has gone through because of you?
Wanting to get her father's praise,
she gave so much effort.
What gives you the right to interfere in our relationship?
I don't have a reason to interfere.
However, I can't hold it in because I'm angry.
Are you crazy, Jin Ho?
Kae In was so much in pain,
you have no idea how hurt she was.
Because she was blamed for her mother's death,
that's why she saw her father hating her as a given.
Just like a sinner.
Is she not your daughter?
Why must you let her lead her life as a sinner?
Stop it!!!
What do you know?
From what I see, all your guilt and sorrow,
you have transferred them to your daughter.
Insolent fool...
What do you know? To lecture me like this!
Go!
Rejecting to oversee the Dam Arts Center,
it was because you failed in the design of Sang Go Jae, isn't it?
Is that not the truth?