Episode 2
Ka... Ka... Kae In?
Why... why are... you here?
Seriously?!  Hey! Kim In Hee!
Secretary Kim! Secretary Kim!
Let go!
You evil jerks, let go!
Get out.
Isn't it that woman again?
Let go.
There must have been a misunderstanding.
The ceremony will continue.
Hyung, Director Choi is leaving.
In Hee!
In Hee, hold on.
Are you happy now?
I'm sorry that I messed up your wedding.
That's okay...
I won't be sorry from now on, either.
Why you little...
You have to be sorry for the rest of your life, bitch!
Let's go!
Hey!
In Hee, are you okay?
Oh, hyung.
I'm sorry.
I was in a hurry to leave and I accidentally...
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
I see you've left your contact information.
Please just go.
The Dream Art Center presentation.
I enjoyed your speech.
My schedule is busy today...
why don't you contact me around Tuesday?
I have something to say too!
I'm in the same situation as you...
Listen to me... I, too...
In Hee...
Hey! Wait a minute!
Hey!
I really told Kae In!
I even gave her a wedding invitation!
Forget it.
Whenever you open your mouth, you lie.
Just look at all the embarrassment you've caused me.
Give me the ticket.
Ticket?
Right! The ticket.
We can do the wedding again later.
Let's go on a honeymoon first.
You think I'm crazy enough to go on a honeymoon with you?
Hey! Wait a minute!
What do you mean? We're going together!
I must have been crazy!
Forget it...
In Hee!
In Hee, wait!
Well sir,
at least you didn't get your face slapped.
What kind of a man can't keep his girl under control and creates such a fiasco?
Father...
Ok, ok.
Ohhh okay, thank you.
The project was originally going
to a firm of foreign architects,
but Mr Choi intervened to stop that.
He insisted that foreign firms had to
compete on the same terms in an open contest.
Really?
If it's a fair play, it's good for us.
Oh boy, we were just going to butt in
without knowing anything...
You ARE really something.
This is only the beginning.
You're already back from the wedding?
Hey kid, what are you doing here? Get out!
You're not really going to fire me
just for losing a drinking bet?
Hyung, get rid of Tae Hoon's desk.
Okay, let's get rid of it.
Where are all the office staff?
No way! It can't be like this!
If you throw me out, you'll regret it
Then do whatever you want.
But there will be no salary. Forever.
Salary? No way!
Hyung, hyung!
But I have a piece of information.
A top-class tip-off!
Don't need it, bye-bye!
But it is a secret plan to win the Dam Art Gallery contest!
Have you ever heard of a house called Sang Go Jae?
- What?
- Sang Go Jae.
Sang Go Jae. Sang-Go-Jae.
Isn't that what it says?
Doesn't that character say  'Ko'?
It's not "Ko", hyungnim.
It's Hyang Oh Jae, hyungnim.
Kae In, answer my call.
Kae In...
Please leave a message.
I'm sorry, Kae In.
Without you knowing,
I borrowed an extra ￦ 10,000,000 ($ 10,000).
Some famous star did their commercial,
so I thought it was a bank or something.
But hey,
they just had the facade of a bank.
I... will definitely pay you back.
Sorry.
Evil jerks... I trusted them and used the money...
Evil jerk! I trusted you and gave the money.
Hyungnim! Here is the rat!
Get him!
GET HIM!
Han Chang Ryul...
Was that your best effort?
Put the house on auction? No way...
Hey, Lee Won Ho! Answer the call!
Hey!
So, Tae Hoon... You're saying that Director Choi who heads the MS Group, which is the parent company of the Dam Art Gallery,
is your dad's friend.
Okay, from here a new person comes into the picture.
Director Choi was completely smitten by a traditional Korean house called Sang Go Jae built by Professor Park Chul Han.
So he invited Professor Park to head up the Dam Art Gallery,
but Professor Park turned him down.
That's right.
So you're saying... Director Choi still has a special interest  in that house called Sang Go Jae?
That is exactly it.
Hey Jin Ho,
if what he says is true, this is a sure thing for us.
Ah, I said it was true.
First, let's find out more about Sang Go Jae.
But...
who's your father that he's friends with a corporation chairman?
Really?
Really, you're seriously the son of that family?
Oppa!
Hi, Hye Mi.
Aigoo...
Hye Mi!
Wow, is today a special day?
Yup! The day I go on a date with Jin Ho oppa.
- What is she saying?
- Stop fooling around. Go home if you're done shopping.
No, you'll have to go on a date with me today.
Just wait and see.
Hey, Lee Won Ho!
Father?
Why are you ringing at this hour?
Isn't it around dawn over there?
Ye...Yes, how have you been?
Am I having problems?
N-No, none at all.
Y-Yes...well... It's been a while since we've talked...
May...?
Weren't you originally coming back in August?
Ahh, I see.
I'll see you then... Yes...
What do I do?
If father comes home...
I'm dead meat.
Hey...hey come to your senses.
There's got to be a way.
What should I do? What should I do?
Regular Savings Plan...
...that's $2,250...
...if I add this... And this...
In Hee!
Kim In Hee!
Young Sun...
What do I do?
Happy birthday.
Please blow the candles. Don't forget to make a wish.
We could've done this at home since you're so busy. Why bother coming out?
There are too many candles.
That's too much.
I don't look like I'm in my thirties.
Who says?
You have no idea. If I walk around with you locking arms, people whisper, "Are they lovers?"
They whisper like crazy.
Their eyes are messed up. My gosh!
Mother, did you make a wish?
There's not much to it.
You two getting engaged soon.
Mother, your birthday gift.
My gosh! Thank you.
Your presence is a gift enough.
Why bother with this, too?
The sensible son, do you have a gift for her?
Hi, Sang Jun hyung.
Really?
Okay, we'll talk when I get back. Did you make a reservation to that spa?
I see. All right. Thanks.
Mother, you wanted to go to a spa, right?
Go with Hye Mi.
- It's your birthday gift.
- Gosh...
I can't say anything with you around.
I just mentioned it. I can't believe you remember it.
I'll see you at home later. Something urgent came up.
Really?
Hye Mi, please take care.
Oppa...
Hi, Sang Joon hyung.
Make a reservation at that spa.
Kae In.
Park Kae In.
What are you doing there without any of the lights on?
Cheer up!
You came.
Seeing you're stuffing yourself,
I guess you have a tenacious hold on life.
Eat up.
I have no one but you, Young Sun.
You little rascal... We're bosom buddies, aren't we?
That's why I want to ask...
Umm...
Do you have any money you could lend me?
Wow, this looks delicious.
Did you use those herbs I brought you before?
I thought we weren't strangers.
Well, strictly speaking... there's nothing between us.
We're not a couple or something.
Just go then, you wench!
Just tell your father what happened.
Don't you know what my relationship with my father is like?
Why oh why did your father have to love
your mother the way he did?
Lee Young Sun.
Look, I didn't mean it that way... It's just...
...you and your father are all that's left of your family,
so why do you give each other such a hard time?
Sorry.
Just at the time Sang Go Jae was finished,
Park Chul Han lost his wife.
Since then, almost 30 years ago now,
not a single outsider has ever been allowed in.
But don't you think the exterior is very simple,
considering that Professor Park designed it?
What on earth sparked Director Choi's interest?
It seems Professor Park is in the UK
right now on a faculty exchange program.
So, who's actually living there?
His only daughter is living there now.
Hold on.
A daughter means a woman.
And seeing how she's a woman...
That's your opening, Jin Ho.
Why let that handsome face and fine body go unused?
Let's exploit your good looks.
Stop speaking nonsense and focus.
Why is this nonsense? It's exactly the answer we're looking for.
Also,
they say Professor Park's wife was a stunning beauty.
What if the daughter takes after the mother?
Drop that idea. I'll be making my way
over to the Dam Art Gallery tomorrow.
You're the one who's keen on beautiful women,
so go to Sang Go Jae and spy out the land.
I really wanted...
...to get recognition from Father,
so I tried really hard.
But in the end, here I am like this again...
But...
today, I can cry for once, can't I?
Let me just
...abandon myself to the pain for this one day only.
Then I'll shake it all off and stand tall again, Mom.
I'm your brave daughter, Kae In.
No, no, I'm 29 years old.
Yes. No.
No, it's not that.
Fortune teller, what will happen to me now?
Wait!
I see it. I see it.
See what?
An important visitor is approaching you from the East.
They're here. Yes, they're here.
Where?  Where?
The person coming from the East today
is the one who will open the gate to your fortune.
No matter what, hold on to him tightly.
The person from the East.
East...
This...
It's the important visitor!
Important visitor, sir!
You!
Y-You're...f-from the wedding yesterday...
No. I'm not.
What's this?
What's that woman doing here?
Could it be that... she's Professor Park's stunningly beautiful daughter?
Don't tell me...
Did you come from the East?
Our office is south of the river.
Aiiishhh...
You should separate from that pervert.
Your scheming is showing.
She's crazy. Totally gone.
Hello?
Is this Creative Director Park Kae In, of Kae In Design's?
Yes.
I'm Park Kae In. Who is this?
This is Nice Department Store.
Do you think you can come in right now?
Yes.
I'll leave right now, yes!
We're sorry.
I really think it's an extraordinary piece of art, but...
the higher ups say it's not marketable.
I've been ordered to cancel the order.
Listen, I'll fix it.
Whatever you want, it's all possible.
N-no. It's not a matter of modifying it.
I'm sorry.
Wa-wait!
Yes.
What would you like to eat?
Ah, yes.
Jin Ho!
Do you know this person?
"Know him" isn't the word!
His father and I were the very best of friends back in the old days.
You rascal! Didn't I tell you to think of our house
as yours and come and visit us often?
It's been a long time since we've met.
Yes, that's true. But what brings you here?
I just had some business to do.
Ah, is that so? Well, we're about to go to lunch right now.
Is it alright if he comes along?
He's like a son to me.
No, thank you.
I'll come back again another time.
Yes, I think that would be best.
You're going to enter the contest
for the Dam Arts Center project, I believe?
Yes.
I'll look forward to seeing your entry.
Let's go.
Ahh, yeah.
A young man full of passion is a good thing, but...
you should be able to tell the difference
between passion and foolhardiness.
I'm not saying it in particular to you.
Wow Daddy! Is this our new house?
That's right.
Hey, Director Choi is leaving with Mr. Han.
Are they trying to fix this like the Dream Art Center?
What's going on with Sang Go Jae?
Oh hey... don't even talk about it.
We've got a magnitude 12 earthquake situation here.
What do you mean by that?
That girl is the daughter.
The girl who messed up Chang Ryul's wedding,
the one who makes strange furniture,
the egotist, she's the professor's daughter.
What?
Sang Go Jae has never been opened
to anyone at all for thirty years.
You think a woman as crazy as that would let us look round?
Let's not try it,
let's just give up for once.
Hyung.
I'm determined to do this.
I really wanted to invite you!
Mom, did Dad really leave things like that?
He's too much.
That's just too much.
Huh?
That...it's because the house hasn't been cleaned yet.
When I clean it, you may come over.
Yes.
By the way, are you regularly checking your blood sugar?
Yes, the brown rice is very good for you.
You have to eat continuously.
It's Yun Hee Dong's mother.
Mom, I got a call from Yun Hee Dong's mom right now.
I'll call you later, Mom.
Yes.
Yes, Mom.
Of course, the wedding was fantastic!
Honeymo...
Since I was so busy...
we'll go on a honeymoon later.
What? Because of my wedding,
you decided to get botox?!
You're pretty enough without that.
Where?
Mom, it's a call from Dad. Yes, I'll call you back.
Yes.
Yes, Father.
Where have you been cooped up?
You said you hated the very sight of me!
What?
Arrrgh...
Jin Ho, that rascal.
He seems to be interested in the Dam Arts Center.
Ehh?!
The kid's going to have another go?
This time, the method we used with
the Dream Art Center isn't going to work.
As the man who inherited the MS Group,
there's nothing Mr Choi really wants
that he hasn't got already.
Father, I will never lose to Jin Ho,
so you don't need to worry.
And...about the situation with In Hee... I'll-
Don't even mention it, you punk!
Do some research on Jeon Jin Ho
and the people around him.
Background check?
You know the sort of thing...
his regular drinking places, relationships with women,
character flaws, stuff like that.
Jeon Jin Ho.
Don't fall apart just yet.
This time, let's fight properly.
Ew, fundamental measures are necessary.
What to do?
I'm going to catch Lee Won Ho, that jerk.
How can you catch him when
he's determined to stay hidden?
So what do I do?
Why not just rent out In Hee's room?
Are you crazy?
I got a loan off that house! How can I let an outsider in Sang Go Jae?!
If I let a stranger in, my father will kill me!
But taking in a stranger would solve the loan problem.
Any other ideas?
I don't.
Let's put it on the market before we go back.
Huh?
Who's that?
We're there. Wake up!
- Won Ho! It's Won Ho!
- Won Ho!
- Ahjussi! Let us out here!
HEY!  LEE WON HO!
HEY! YOU!
YOU!
Kae In!  Fighting!
HEY! Stop there! I won't hit you!
HEY!  LEE WON HO!
Hey!  Stop! You hear me?
HEY! YOU!
You sure have complicated relationships with men.
Oh!  What are you doing here?
Hey!!! You!!
Are you okay?
I'm okay, but that man there! Catch him!
HEYYY!!!
Hey, you!
If you ran away...
You...
Hey you!
￦10,000,000 ($10,000 in US)
What happened to it?
How much do you have left?
You didn't use it all, right?
You have to have something left over.
Hurry up and hand it over. Quickly!
Hurry!
I used it all.
Hey!  Hey!  Lee Won Ho!
What am I going to do, Lee Won Ho?
What am I going to do?
Haven't you even been eating?
Eat slowly.
Or you'll have vomiting and diarrhea like crazy.
You're the one who gave me vomiting and diarrhea.
Shut up and just eat.
Before I hit you.
So... do you really have no money?
My father is coming back 3 months earlier.
What am I going to do?
I even put the room In Hee used to have up for rent.
Rent a room at Sang Go Jae?
I'm going to go to the washroom for a second.
Oh...hey... Make sure you come right back.
Are you stupid?
Can't you see he's running away?
Don't worry,
he wouldn't lie to me....
Hey!  Hey!  Lee Won Ho!
Yahhh!
Are you always like this?
What?
You just trust everyone like that?
It's kind of my chronic disease.
I think you have to go to the hospital.
It's fine. It'll be just a waste of money
if I go to the hospital now...
Let's go to the hospital.
This is so strange.
Thank you.
Let's go. I'll drive you home.
So what's your motive, then?
Ehh?
Well, you caught Won Ho for me...
and you paid the hospital bill...
and you're even dropping me off at my house.
You seem to have changed from how
you were a while back and become kind to me.
In a situation like this, you're just supposed to say
'Thank you.'
I'll definitely pay you back for the hospital bill.
You don't have to pay me back with money.
If you're so grateful,
how about showing me round Sang Go Jae?
How do you know the name of my house?
My father hasn't sent you here, has he?
I just read what it says on the signboard.
And how should I know who your father is?
Then...why do you want to look round my house?
Aren't you renting out a room?
Well...thank you for today.
I'll repay you for today some time in the future.
Come on, don't be like that.
Just let me take a look at your house.
Our house is always closed to outsiders.
So goodbye now...
Then why did you put a room out for a rent?
Well, I don't plan to rent out a room to you.
Aishh...  He doesn't understand me at all.
Don't be so obstinate, at least consider it.
What is this?
Did you use your house as collateral for a loan?
This isn't any of your business.
It's obvious.
You're going to lose a house like this to a loan shark just for the sake of a little cash.
You are really...
Please mind your own business.
Why are you making this matter more difficult?
Can't you just put out a room for rent to me.
You have to take care of the immediate problem first.
(D.T - You need to extinguish the immediate fire first)
But...
how can a girl who's living by herself let some random guy into her house?
What girl are you talking about?
Is it you?
You're back?
Yeah.
What about Won Ho?
I knew that was going to happen.
I've put that returned furniture at the back.
Thank you.
That person from before...
From the wedding ceremony...
Right?
But why are you two...?
Then... you may leave now.
Can you think about it again?
Hey.
Although I may not know what's going on right now,
I'll make things work out, so just wait here for a second.
What's wrong with your foot?
I fell chasing after Won Ho and sprained my ankle.
But,
did that man want to rent a room in this house?
That's right.
Then what's the problem?
That's good. Everything's worked out.
Huh?
You have a room. He has money.
Hey! Even so, how can I live in the same house with a man?
It's not like you don't know him, so why make such a big fuss?
And bear in mind that...
Bear in mind what?
Well, that whatever happens, that guy certainly won't try anything on you.
You won't be more than a rock or a tree in his eyes.
You think so?
Of course.
And what good would it do if you rent out to a female?
She might just betray you like In Hee.
For now, let him in.
And if you don't like him, just return his deposit and kick him out.
Kae In,
gay friends are really fantastic.
- Oh, this. I totally love it.
- What's that?
Kae In's complexion needs some attention.
Right here.
Hey!
Come in and see the room.
Quick, quick!
Come in.
Please, look around.
Oh, you're back?
Yeah.
You're back?
How was it?
You didn't even get as far as the doormat, I'll bet.
I just got a room.
A room?
What room?
Are you planning to move out because of Hye Mi?
Well, that too.
Several reasons.
So where?
Where else?
Sang Go Jae, of course.
What? Sang Go Jae?
Really?
Hyung,
I'm going to move into Sang Go Jae.
How did you pull that off?
You've got to keep this a secret from Hye Mi and Tae Hoon. Understood?
I mean it!
Oh, of course!
You're really the best.
So, are you allowed to move in right away?
Of course.
Nice!
­
What is it?
What?
You can leave early.
- Goodbye!
- Goodbye.
It's nothing.
You, look after the office.
What is it now?
Bravo!
Hey,
I'm not sure if you can applaud this.
I'm now going to live in a house with another man.
Anyway, it still doesn't feel right.
Ever since I met him, all of these bad things kept happening to me.
Hey, just forgive him.
He's good-looking.
What?
Kae In...
When someone looks like that, you gotta forgive him whatever he does to you.
Aw, if only I could grab those pert buttocks.
They sure were pert, like chock-full in my palms...
What did you do?
If there's something good, we have to share.
We're good friends, aren't we?
Come on, you're a middle-aged woman with a kid!
You'd better pull yourself together.
I'm only just letting him in because of the situation.
Finally you enter Sang Go Jae.
Our company's life depends on you.
That's why I came to live with that Miss Clumsy.
Whether she is Miss Clumsy or Miss Wild,
I think that lady is interested in you.
If she wasn't, do you think she'd let a man move into a house where she lives alone?
Yup. She would.
Ah, I've got to tell you...
Be careful.
Always leave your door ajar.
Watch your personal hygiene for when the inevitable happens.
And when it happens, you have to sacrifice your body for the sake of our company.
Stop saying horrible things!
I'm not saying horrible things.
You're a guy...
who's already had that woman's hands on your butt.
If you think of it that way, it'll be easier.
Hyung,
let me get in.
Alright. Because you're important.
Oh yeah.
Why did you come to our house?
Oh yes, yes...  Well... That...
Well, it just happens that...
You two...
must have known each other a long time.
Sure, that's right. A real long time.
He's a bit picky, so it's not that easy to be around him.
But...
how did you know about us two?
Ah...well... I was a little curious...
But... you can't take interest in our Jin Ho...
Hyung, stop talking about weird nonsense.
You two are too obvious.
Well, there aren't that many rules you have to follow,
but you definitely can't take pictures of the house. My father hates that.
And we'll share the use of the fridge and the washing machine.
That's about it.
Hold on a second.
There are a number of things I need you to pay attention to.
What?
The house is too messy right now.
While I'm living here, I expect you to always keep it clean.
You've got pots of instant noodles lying around all over the house.
Please keep your hands off any food I leave in the refrigerator.
And I hope you won't make the mistake of washing my clothes when you wash yours.
I believe you're civilized people here, right?
Ah, right then...
Let me make some things really clear then.
Mr. Jeon Jin Ho, please keep away from me, except your own room and the shared areas... If you break that rule...
What are you going to do?
I'll cut it off.
Ehh?
Cut what off?
Any part of your anatomy that crosses the line.
Oh, she's a real joker!
Well...
She has a great sense of humor!
Yes, yes.
Then...
- why don't we close the contract like this?
- Oh, sure.
- I hope we will have a good relationship.
- Yes, yes, let's do our best in that direction.
You punk.
Why are you pushing her buttons?
Don't you see this place is a mess?
She has no respect for the spirit of this house.
Ouch!
- Ow!
- What?
What? What's wrong?
What? Let me see.
Oh boy, you got a scratch on your million-dollar thigh!
Hold on a second, where's the first-aid kit...
Forget it.
Hey, take off your pants. I'll put on the medicine.
I said it's fine.
In a relationship in which we saw everything off each other, are you embarrassed?
I said I don't want to.
It'll get infected.
What? You think I'm going to hurt you?
I'll do it carefully.
Oh boy, don't be such a crybaby.
Ow! Do it carefully!
I'm rubbing it carefully, so stop whining!
I'm doing it for you.
I'll go in more gently, okay?
Ahh, you punk!
Just be patient.
Eavesdropping like that, you dreadful woman!
Oh, you've really been blessed!
It must be true that you saved the nation in a previous existence.
I wanna move into Sang Go Jae too!
Just cause they're alone, they think they can do anything in there!
And with a man too, what are they doing anyway, really?
Whatever they're up to, you ought to be thankful for it.
In any case,
I feel so sorry for his partner.
Why? They really like each other.
Do you know how promiscuous he is?
The other night at the motel,
he was kicking up a tremendous racket with a huge beast of a man, it doesn't bear thinking about.
Oh, really?
But why were you at a motel?
Ah...Things just happened that way.
When will that beast of a man come calling?
I want to see him.
Anyways, I'm going to have to put my foot down firmly.
I'm not going to let him bring home men from here, there and everywhere.
Where does he think he is.
You mean girl!
Is love a sin?
Is it?!?!
I thought you were a respectable woman!
Oh!
Well, I'll be going now.
I'll be trusting you to take care of this guy.
Yes, well...of course.
You don't have to worry about it at all.
Bye.  I won't see you out.
Umm... But...
Where's... the other man?
Huh?
Umm...
Hey, Jeon Jin Ho.
There is one thing you have to keep in mind.
Hey!
Don't worry about her and keep going on.
- Huh?
- Love is always on the move~
In Hee?
Why are you here?
This is our house.
Honey...
You came back.
Are you crazy, what makes you think this is your house?
Will you leave, please?
I've been kicked out, so I can't go back to my house.
And...this is a house that my dad bought for us.
How cheap you are!
Hey, get up!
What?
This bed, it was a present that Kae In gave me.
So, get up.
Gosh, you've a nerve!
If she'd known you were the one who'd stolen  her guy,
do you think she'd have given you this present?
But the same goes for you, seeing you were that guy!
Hey! This blanket is mine too!
So are the pajamas! Take them off!
Alright.
You think I won't take off the clothes if you tell me to?
Hey...well you're one dirty and selfish person...
-Hey! Hey!
-Take them off!
Take them all!
Here! Here!
You think I'm happy to see this?
Aigoo...even your underwear is ugly.
What's wrong with this?
Then what about you?
What are you wearing underneath? You're probably wearing the lingerie I bought for you from France!
If you are, I want that back too.
Quickly, take it off.
I'll take it all off, you jerk!
Wait a minute...
That lipstick you're wearing right now looks like one I bought you, too. Am I right? The pink one-
Hey!
Here you go.  Satisfied?
You really...!  Hey!
Then, this is my house.
Don't even step on the floor.
I bought the air filter. Don't you breathe.
Your call was unsuccessful, you will be connected to  voicemail after the tone...
Don't worry, Hye Mi.   I'll call him.
Jin Ho will certainly answer a call from me.
Jin Ho, where are you right now?
I can't answer the phone right now.
I'll call you back later.
What are you doing right now?
Just hang up for now,
and I'll talk to you later.
But you can tell me right now, can't you?
OH MY!
What are you doing in here?
Do you think you can tell me right now?
It was dark so I got into the wrong room...
The agreement we made earlier...
you do remember it, don't you?
What agreement?
Did I come on too strong?
I'm tired. I'm going to bed.
Hey...
Kim In Hee...
How come you're showing your face here?
I'm coming back to where I live.  Do I need your permission for that?
What?
I ended things with Chang Ryul,
so that should satisfy you.
Then you're saying... Good for you then.
Let's not fall out over one guy.
Hey!
Do you even know what you did?
Did you forget?
What about you?
Wasn't it because of you the party ended?
I have no place to go and I'm treated like an outcast at work.
How are you going to make that up to me?
Anyone listening to you might think I was the one who'd stolen your lover.
Lover?
You're really funny.
What?
Do you really think there was a moment that you were ever his lover?
What did you say?
Park Kae In. You don't know what love is like.
You need someone to love you first before you can know.
So you've been given so much love,
and yet you steal my lover and lie to me?
Is that how hard-hearted you are?
But I don't beg for love like you do.
You don't even know the difference between love and pity.
Men pity you so they give you some attention,
and you think that amounts to love?
Hey!
- You! You!
- AAHHH!
Hey! Let go of me!
- Hey!
- Ahh!
- Are you not going to let go?!
- You!
- Ah!
- Hey!
- You better let go right now!
- You!
Kae In! Geez!!!
Did you come out to watch?
Please be quiet.
You think you're the only one in the house?
Hey... What's with that guy?
What will you do if you know?
Park Kae In.
You shouldn't live so recklessly.
How can you take in a man like this, especially one as young as him?
Why?
Do you envy me him, too?
Do you want to take him too?
I've never taken others. They just come to me.
But, you definitely can't take that guy.
Why not?
Give me any man at all for 10 minutes, and I'm in business.
You can bust a gut trying,
but you're not his type!
Is that so?
Then I guess we'll have to find out.
You can put all you've got into seducing him.
That man...
is gay!