I love you.
Did you hear me? I said I love you.
You fool.
You give it all in for this love, huh?
Acting is my career.
Bee is the person that I love.
Can't it just happen at the same time?
You can be...
anyone else's happiness.
But I will be...
happiness for you myself.
Can I?
You've been having fun, huh?
Do I seem like a fool to you?
It's not like that P'.
Get out.
I already prepared to give you this,
but I didn't get a chance to do it.
I'll really give it to you this time.
Are you ready?
I am ready, Hia.
Whose vehicle should we take?
Mine.
No Hia.
Riding your bike to Chonburi?
My butt would be numb.
I didn't complain a thing when I rode it to see you last time.
Hia...
Just take my car.
Full tank.
Plus, I will feed you snacks along the way too.
I was just kidding.
Here.
I'm taking my car.
Woww.
And it's a Mercedes too.
I also have a Porsche.
If you wanna take that one,
I will go back and switch the car for you.
That's okay, Hia.
Mecedes Benz is more than enough.
I'm afraid that I might not know
how to open Porsche's door.
Mmmm.
You don't have to be afraid of anything when you're with me.
I only talked about car's door.
You don't have to be romantic just because of that.
But I love youuu~
Hia!
Why?
Cause I love you.
I know that you love me.
Why do you keep saying that?
If you don't want me to say...
Then...
Hmm.
What are you doing?
I'll bring this doll with me.
To protect myself from you.
Let's go.
Go.
Let's hit the road.
How is it dating an actor? Fun?
Oww. My back hurts.
You're probably tired.
I'll prepare a hot bath for you today.
Thank you.
Hey!
I'm still standing here.
Ohhh.
You should close your eyes, P'Tum.
I'm about to kiss him.
You're so annoying!
Guess I'm leaving!
So sick of love birds.
Driver will come pick you up same time in the morning
Sure.
The coast is clear.
Shall we?
What? No!
Let's put this upstairs.
So you can go bath.
Let me kiss first.
I missed that!
Go!
Come on!
So you can go take a warm bath upstairs.
Are you sure you can?
I'm sure.
Heavy huh.
It's okay. I'll carry it myself.
That's fine, Team.
It's his job. Let him do it.
Thank  you.
Hia Win.
Can I sleep with you tonight?
No, you cannot!
What!?
Why?
And where is Team going to sleep?
With us. The three of us.
We can just take the big room. There're 3 beds.
Please please please.
Sure / No!
He is his boyfriend. They have to sleep together.
Just leave them alone. มันขวาง***
Hia!
You told everyone!?
Why do I have to keep it a secret?
You are my boyfriend.
Hia!
There're lots of people here.
I'm so sick of these two.
Hia.
Here here here.
Let's go.
You're sick of them? Let me kiss you then.
Why are you bringing the medal?
Do you remember...
that I have something I wanna tell you?
I'm ready to talk about it now.
This is for you P'.
When we were young,
I promised you...
that when we grow up
we both will become athletes.
The silver medal is for me.
And the gold medal belongs to you.
Hia.
This is P'Ton.
He's my cousin.
P'Ton! Let's swim.
Is this a good idea? The pool is about to close.
That's even better, so no one will be here.
If my mom found out, she'll punish me.
Let's swim and compete with me.
Please P'Ton.
Fine.
But we have to do a warm up first.
P'Ton...
we've taken classes already. What are you afraid of?
Please P'Ton.
Um.
Yayy.
Team.
Just one hour, okay?
Okay.
1 2 3 go!
I am ahead of you...keep up!
I will do my cheating move.
I have to win.
Help!
Yeah I won!
Hey Team!
I was stubborn.
I wanted to swim
even he tried to stop me.
But I didn't listen.
And I drowned.
But why was he the one who died?
And not me?
You can't think like that, Team.
Don't think that way.
I'm so damn guilty, Hia.
We promised each other
that we'll become swimming athletes when we grow up.
And why there's only me left?
Everytime before any competition...
I would always dream about that incident.
I always see him drowning to the bottom of the pool.
I always see people gather around trying to save him.
I see him lying there not breathing.
Calm down, Team.
It's been a long time a ago.
Not at all, Hia.
Everything...
feels like it happened yesterday.
All the memories are still in my head.
I can still see aunty Ta...
P'Ton's mother
bringing the food to his grave and talk to him like he's still there.
She's still in grief.
She still cries.
She's still in that conditions.
Everything is like this because of me.
Team.
Before you ask anyone to forgive you...
you need to forgive yourself first.
Do you understand?
Why am I not the one who died?
If I died...
everything would have been better.
No, it would not.
You can't die. Do you hear me?
Team...
Why do you still think that way?
I'm not angry or hate you at all, son.
Aunty Ta.
But I am the reason why he's dead.
You said I killed him.
Oh boy...
I'm sorry.
I said that...
becasue I was miserable.
I said things without actually thinking it through.
Why did you kill him? Why did kill Ton?
Ton.
I didn't know...
that..
it's still haunting you.
Aunt Ta.
I'm sorry, aunt Ta.
I'm sorry I'm the cause of all these.
Can you please tell me?
What can I do to repay for what I did?
Nothing.
You've...
repaid more than enough.
But I--
From now on,
you need to become a great athlete
and be happy.
for him please.
Aunt Ta.
I love you, Team.
I love you like I love P'Ton.
Thank you.
Get some rest.
We'll have dinner downstairs in the evening.
I have my staffs prepare lots of seafood for you.
Thank you, Hia.
Do you realize?
That you've thanked me a lot,
since I've known you.
But I really do want to thank you.
Go get some rest.
I'll bring a cold cloth to compress your eyes.
So it won't get puffy.
Sure.
***
Go to sleep.
Yes.
You have very little happiness...
but still pushed him away from your life.
Win!
F*ck you.
You love him,
but you keep your lip tight.
You know me.
What I hate the most
is liars.
But he didn't mean to lie to you.
Are you actually on your friend's side rather than mine?
I'm not.
I'm just speaking the truth.
He told me everything.
He didn't know
who you are
at first, did he?
But when he found out,
he chose not to tell me.
He treats me like a fool.
Doing poker face when we meet.
He's really good at lying.
You said it yourself
that you don't wanna meet up with him.
I said that
because I didn't know
that he's your friend.
The reason he lied...
is because he didn't wanna lose you.
Think about it.
If you knew who he is,
were you gonna be able to see him more than your brother's friend?
How is it different with right now?
Even now
I feel for him more than I should have
but at the end
we can't be together anyway.
So you're accepting that
your feeling for him is more than a friend.
I don't know!
I'm just comfortable to talk to him
And...
would you talk to him again if you got a chance?
Even if I want to, but I already pushed him away, didn't I?
If I go back to him now, I would lose my cool.
One more thing,
I don't even know who he really is.
If you don't know,
then you need to get to know him.
Let's do this.
If he came to talk to you,
would you talk to him nicely?
I don't know.
What the hell, bro?
He has to try first, right?
Hey!
P'Waan.
I'm here to ask for your forgiveness!
P'Waan!
I'm sorry.
Please stay calm.
Why are you arresting me? I came to apologize the hotel owner?
Please come this way.
P'Waan. Help me!
P'Waan.
You betrayer!
After I'm done with this, you'll be doomed.
How are you going to do it?
I'll come back and deal with you later.
Wow.
Is this really your hotel?
You know all of it.
About my life.
Why do you ask?
P'Waan...
I did not dare to tell you
who I am.
I was afraid that if you knew the truth,
you wouldn't talk to me the same way.
How long were you thinking to fool me?
If I did not fall,
were you gonna lie to me until I die?
Maybe.
Tul!
I was trying to find the time to tell you.
But you found out already.
Then...
Let's not talk about the past.
You're here but...
not gonna talk about the past,
then why are you here?
I'm here to talk about the future.
The future of you and me.
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
Kissing you.
You're crossing the line.
P'Waan.
Can you be my future?
I wanna have you in my future.
But I have to move and work here.
You study in Bangkok.
Two different cities.
Bangkok and Chonburi.
It's not that far.
I can drive to see you.
I can drive to see you morning and night everyday.
I'm almost 4 years older than you.
That's fine.
I like old people.
P'Waan!
Can we just don't talk about things that haven't happened yet?
I really wanna be your safe zone.
I want you to be comfortable to say...
...comfortable to talk to me.
Just like when you trusted T-Rex.
I can try.
Try what?
I can try dating you.
I'm also old already.
Don't wanna be picky. It's a waste of time.
Tul.
I've always wanted to do this.
Too much.
Eat up, so you can grow more.
Hia.
I'm a grown up already.
It is already perfect then.
Easy to carry.
Hia.
Carry?
Where are you going to carry him?
Can't P'Team just walk by himself?
Hia.
Stop talking and eat.
Poor boy.
Why don't you pass some food for Tul, Hia?
Your hand.
I can get it myself.
Hia.
You scared me.
I came to ask you to go eat.
If you're hungry, you can eat first.
Let me breath fresh air in for
a few more seconds.
I can't eat without you.
Blahh.
You brought this for me?
You forgot our little tradition already?
What do you have to do before you drink?
Since when did it become our tradition?
I just made it our thing.
Kiss me. Come on.
I'm already bored of your cheek.
Team.
You don't know what you're getting yourself into.
Why?
Don't you like it, hmm?
Not that I don't like it.
But if you do that,
you might not get to eat.
What are you trying to say?
Let's go eat.
Hia.
Let's go.
Come on!
Wait up.
I'm hungry already.
You know what...
today is the day that I have the clearest mind.
It's like...
someone took the rocks out of my head.
That good?
Yeah.
That good.
When things first happened,
I had insomnia.
I had to take medicines.
It was torturing, Hia.
No matter how tired you are,
you cannot sleep.
Cause you're afraid to have nightmares.
But now...
you can sleep, right?
I have to try, Hia.
Since I've been sharing my bed with you,
it keeps getting better everyday.
Is there any reasons behind?
I don't know either.
When I'm with you,
I feel safe.
I'm super comfortable
being with you.
Me too.
When I'm with you,
I never wanted go anywhere.
I can't believe it.
We started off from a random situationship.
I don't care.
I just know...
that I love you so damn much.
This is so good, Pharm!
Pharm.
You want some?
Hmm..
I have chicken breast salad.
Pharm's cooking
is always yummy!
Really?
Aren't you only like P'Win's cooking?
Manow.
Yeah.
I have a swim meet to record my stat today.
Do you wanna go watch me?
But...
even if I didn't invite you guys,
you two would probably go anyway.
Right?
Was there any time that we didn't go see you?
Yeah.
There're other people in the club too. Not just me.
There's also P'Dean.
P'Phruek.
Don't you dare be mad, Team.
Lately, you've been with P'Win all the time also.
Me? Being with him all the time?
It's him who is attached to me.
Can't help it.
Since I'm too hot.
Handsome? Got it?
I don't wanna waste Pharm's sandwich.
If I was not, I would throw up.
Stop talking and just eat, Manow.
Thank you Pharm.
Eat up.
I wanna have that too.
Manow.
There're lots of people here.
Yeah so many people.
Where should we sit, Pharm?
Over there?
I'll lead you there.
Team!
Go Team!
You can do it Team!
Take your mark.
Team!
Go Team!
Come on, Team!
Team.
Swim swim.
Swim.
Swim swim swim.
He's ahead now.
Team!
Go Team! / Come on swim!
Well done, Team!
You're so good.
Wait a bit more, Bee.
Soon, our relstionship won't have to be a secret anymore.
Let's just wait until everything is settled.
And I'll stop working in this industry.
You don't have to do that, Prince.
Working as an actor,
is something thast you love, right?
And why...
do we have to give up on your career?
I don't want you to wait anymore.
But...
leaving the industry
is not a way out.
But...
both of us...
and many other people
have to wait...
until society changes.
When that day comes,
it's gonna be the day
that the problem will be truly solved.
Do you understand?
Thank you.
Then...
can we do it one more round?
P'Phruek.
Hmm?
Read this for me.
Is it real? Am I reading correctly?
"Passed the casting"
Huh?
Are you really getting the role?
The name...the name is correct right?
Yes, it is.
I am really getting to play a real role!
I am you first official fan.
You can't forget that!
I won't.
You're both my fanclub...
and also...
my boyfriend too.
You're crazy!
Yayy.
Very well!
Nice!
My boyfriend.
Thank you for dropping me off.
Sure.
See you after class.
Yes.
Hia.
You sneaked here alone again.
I did not.
I just...
came to think about stuff.
What are you thinking?
Tell me.
Well...
I'm thinking about the future.
Thinking about tomorrow
and the next days.
Wonder how is it gonna turn out?
And what does it look like...
the future that you have in mind?
I don't know either, Hia.
But...
no matter what it is...
you'll always be there.
Then our thoughts are the same.
Ready?
Ready for what?
Hia.
What are you doing?
Hey!
I can walk by myself.
I really like the beach.
I love listening to the waves.
I love soft sand.
I love it too.
You mean the beach?
I love the person who loves the beach.
Oh.
After...
you graduate,
we might have different schechdules.
I would have to work.
You'd also have to do your thing.
When that time comes...
I'm afraid that... / It's fine.
I totally understand you and everything.
Then...
this coming up break,
let's go see your mom
in America together.
P'Dean.
We'll get married there.
Like I promise you.
P'Dean.
Please Pharm.
I know
that
we will never stop loving each other.
But I wanna have a solid thing
to show you
that I will love
and take care of you for the rest of my life.
I love you P'Dean.
You love me as much as I love you?
Maybe even more.
Really?
You have to prove it.
P'Dean.
Let's see...
Try kissing me please.
P'Dean!
I'm gonna go.
I'm gonna go see Team.
You're not gonna fight me back?
I will catch you later!
Pharm.
Hia.
Let me go!
No.
What are you doin'? Let me down.
Hia.
What?
Thank you...
for trusting me to take care of you from now on.
I'll be here for you to take care forever.
I love you, Hia.
I love you too.
But...
I have something I wanna ask you.
What?
Let's compete swimming with me.
Woww.
What Pharm?
You're blushing.
How's it going, Mr.Vice?
Not blushing.
What's up with you?
Always mocking me.
Team: You're also blushing.
Look at your boy.
The pic you took was bad.
You better stay fit.
I took a lot already.
Swim!
Look at that!
There's only you.
Oh.
Stop arguing.
I look shitty / Stop arguing.
Where's Bee?
Oh.
Oh hey! / You guys!
Wow.
What was that? What was that?
As you can see.
Temple dog is leveled up.
Temple doggo.
Not me. You are!
Don't be a bully!
But you were slow too.
- Not true.
- You were slow.
Not true.
What's up P'Phruek?
Manow.
This is my girlfriend, you guys.
Hia Win.
What about me?
Guys.
So...
I have something to tell you.
Hey! Don't tell me that you guys are getting married?
No no.
Well...
I challenge Hia Win to compete with me.
That's no fun.
Are you sure you'd win?
Why wouldn't I?
- What's up with you?
- I don't know.
We'll see.
They are all couples.
Let them enjoy the moment.
Ready?
What about you? Are you ready?
I've been ready for so long.