What am I gonna do
if something happened to you?
What am I gonna do, Team?
Whatever you're feeling right now,
Whether you just worry about him,
Or you really love him.
I feel like...
I started to have a feeling for someone,
I'm afraid that, if I loved him,
I might lose him someday.
If you don't wanna lose,
then keep him.
Not trying to avoid like this.
Where is he gone to?
Mom, what's wrong with P'Ton?
Why is he not awake?
Did I just kill him?
No, you did not.
It's not like that. It was an accident.
No.
No, Ton.
Ton.
Team.
Did you kill my son?
Why did you kill him?
Why?
Ton
Why did you kill Ton, Team?
Why did you have to kill him!?
Why did you kill my son?
It was an accident.
It was an accident. They were just playing.
Why did you kill him?
Why did you kill my son?
Why did you kill my son, Team?
Did you kill my son?
Why did you kill Ton?
Watch me.
When I grow up,
I'll become a national athlete.
You can be whatever,
but we have to stick together.
Ok, I promise.
Promise?
I promise.
When I grow up, I'll become a national athlete.
I'll bring mom the silver medal!
Why only the silver one?
Cause the gold medal belongs to you!
Team!
What's happening?
Why are you here?
Team!
Hia.
Where have you been?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Team.
I'm not gonna disappear from you again.
I'm sorry I couldn't keep my promise.
What promise?
That I'll always be there for you.
Hia.
I'm fine.
I'm just waiting for you. That's all.
I'm kinda tired today.
So I fell asleep.
Really.
I'm sorry.
I'm totally fine.
What about you? Are you okay?
Let's go inside.
Go to bed.
Oh Hia.
You didn't come watch me
at the swim meet today.
I beat my time record.
First one that finished too.
I got caught with an urgency.
So...
I couldn't be there.
Umm.
Okay.
You should go take a shower.
You should go to sleep too.
Ok.
Were you having a bad dream just now?
Yeah.
Thought it only happens
before the competition.
Why is it still happening after?
I don't know why either.
But it's been happening a lot lately.
Sometimes,
It happens
when I nap during the day too.
But...
It never happened...
when I'm with you.
Sweet dream.
Okay.
Look at me!
If I didn't walk pass and saw the lights,
If I didn't walk in to check...
what do you think was gonna happen?
Tell me.
What would happen?
Why did you do that?
I just wanted to practice.
What?
Why do you have to be so pissed?
F*ck the practice!
You almost drowned. Damn it!
You almost died right in front of me.
Did you realize that?
But if you're serious about this,
please make it clear.
If not,
don't give anyone's hope.
I didn't meant it to turn out this way.
I know that you didn't intend to.
But your actions...
make it seems like you mean it.
I already slept with him.
We started off our relationship that way.
You started like that?
And how is it going to end?
I don't know.
But what we have right now is already perfect.
And...
what exactly do you mean by what we have?
I don't know what exactly is my feeling.
I'm not fond of him
just because we slept together for sure.
It's just a nice feeling.
I wanna get to know him better.
Wanna support him to do what he loves.
And I also...
worry...
about his sleep.
Have he eaten?
What's he doing?
Love...
is the feeling that you're having right now.
It's called love.
Yeah.
I don't wanna start loving anyone.
Because I don't wanna lose anyone.
But you can't run away from it like this.
If you don't wanna lose it,
then keep it.
Not avoiding like this.
I'm not gonna disappear anymore.
There's a reimbursement.
I'll sign on their behalf.
Bring it down.
I did. See!
Just bring it down.
There's the queue left.
Who should do this?
You're not helping us.
I'll be here supporting you guys.
Hey! ABC gang.
Come here.
P'
You called us like kindergarten kids.
My nickname is Bumblebee, FYI.
It's too long.
Mine is also Sea that means the beach and such.
Not C as a letter.
Yeah whatever.
When I call you three it's A,B,C anyway.
Or you want me to call...
Kasidis, Theep, and Panuphat
He remembers all of our first names?
I heard that he has good memory.
Probably remembers everyone in the club.
He's really good.
- Yeah.
-He is.
Real good.
Are you gossiping in front of me?
Here.
Bring this to the 1st year,
they need to draw the queue to be on the tank.
This way.
And write down the names for me.
Move, Hia.
Hey you guys.
Go hand these out to the 1st year.
I'll go hand out this to the rest.
Why don't you let they come get it themselves?
Stop complaining.
Help me out. Come on.
I think we've got our first boy.
What?
The queue to be on the tank.
You're the first one to draw.
Come on.
Here.
Congratulations!
You're the last one to be on the tank.
Shit!
The last one will probably get picked on a lot.
I'll be the last one who dunk you.
Yeah especially you! Such a jerk.
I'll help.
After you're done with this,
I'll buy you a meal.
You said it!
I'll eat until you're broke.
Go.
Go that way.
In front of us again?
Yeah...
They're pretty close.
Right.
I mean you and Prince!
Right!
Hey Sea!
You don't like being a human right?
Wanna become a dog?
Who's gonna become a dog?
You!
He is so out of your league.
And you are just a temple dog.
(Thai idiom)
You don't think we notice, huh?
You've been putting on sunscreen lately.
Don't you think we know?
Oh but...
you need to be careful as well.
He's a superstar.
He's also a human just like us.
Why do people nowadays love to
snoop on others' business so much?
Actors can be in love too.
Why do you have to be so negative?
Aren't you a little overreacting?
Speaking of the devil...
Yeah...speaking of the devil.
If I was a dog, then you guys would be bats.
What do you mean bats?
Bat friends!
(Bad friends)
Wow.
When he shows up, he suddenly lightens up.
Wow look at him.
Temple dog!
Look at him, looking all flirty.
Such a poet. Playing with words.
Try to reach for him.
Doggo!
I'm full.
Continue with snacks?
You might be too stuffed.
Please.
Just a tiny bit to satisfy.
I'm gonna go buy. Will be back.
How much is this?
40 Baht.
Here.
Thank you.
Hia.
Here check this out.
So smiley when he's with his boy.
But he's so cold with his friends.
Don't know where they're now.
That's the business faculty.
There's a Buddy event there.
Do you wanna go?
No.
I'm so glad
seeing Pharm so happy.
Always care for him,
got me thinking that you guys're secretly dating?
Are you crazy?
How could you think that way?
Pharm is my friend.
Why?
I care for the person I have nice feeling for.
Doesn't mean we're dating.
Yeah.
What about me?
Do you care for me?
Are you messing with me?
Hmm?
I'm not messing with you.
I'm being frank.
Do you care for me?
Well...
I guess.
So you care for me and...
also feel protective of me?
Both.
You ask too many questions.
I'm leaving.
Hia, come on!
Yeah.
Why so hurry?
You're too slow.
Hey P'Team. Hi!
Oh.
Hi there.
Thought you're not coming anymore.
You wanted him to come, didn't you?
He ringed me since early morning.
Wouldn't let me stay to finish my work first.
So I have to bring him here.
Oh.
Team.
This is Hia Waan, my brother.
Hia.
This is Team.
Hello P'.
Hi.
P'Team.
Take me around the uni please.
It's super big here.
Sure.
I'll take you to have some good food.
Ok let's go.
Hia, I'll see you at the the club.
I'll show your brother around.
Bye P'.
So it's this one?
Yeah.
Are you still confusing?
What are you gonna do now?
It's up to him.
Are you interested in Cooking club?
- Feel free to try.
- You can try this.
Here's the brochure.
Do you wanna try?
We're from Cooking club.
Thank you.
If you're interested, please join!
Team!
Pharm.
Wow P'
What kind of snack is that?
It's called Bulan Dan Mek.
Can I have one?
Thank you.
How is it?
Is it good?
So good!
Pharm.
This is Wiew.
Hia Win's brother.
Wiew.
This is Pharm.
Hello P'Pharm.
Hi.
This is so yummy.
I told you.
Seeing only Pharm and it's already worth the drive.
You're exaggerating.
Hey.
There's more in the club,
do you wanna go check them out?
- Sure.
- Let's go.
Can I leave it here with you guys?
- I'll be back in a bit.
- Sure.
Let's go.
Where are you going next?
Waiting for Wiew or leaving?
Probably wait for him here.
I'd love to take him back for you.
But I'll probably finish my work late.
That's fine.
I'll just hang around here.
Ok.
Hey! Tul.
Oh P'Waan.
Hello.
Which faculty are you interested today?
Smart mouth.
Oh Tul.
I'll leave Hia Waan with you.
What?
See you.
Hey!
I can be by myself.
Why?
What's wrong with staying with me?
My tummy is crying.
I'm hungry P'.
Do you wanna go eat?
Let's go.
I'll take you.
Fine.
Here.
This shop
is the best one in the uni.
Try, if you don't believe me.
If it's not good, I'll let you kick.
Really?
Yeah.
Kick...
Kick the shop owner.
Try it.
How is it?
Do you have to kick the owner?
It's good.
See?
I knew that you're gonna like it.
What?
Why are you looking at me?
Is something on my face?
Nothing.
I just feel like I've known you before.
Your voice sounds so familiar.
You're crazy.
Maybe my face just looks like other people.
For the voice,
it could similar to other people too.
Eat eat eat eat.
Eat.
Probably.
Do you have to go back to the club?
Yeah.
You too, Team?
Yes.
Hey!
I'm the last one on the tank today.
People from the club will mess with me
more for sure.
You'll be fine.
I'll go see you in the evening.
Okay.
Well...
Here's for you.
Thank you.
If you wanna try anything else,
just let Team know.
I'll make it for you.
Sure.
Would you excuse me?
Okay.
Bye P'.
See you this evening.
- See you this evening.
- Bye bye.
Let's go.
P'Waan is waiting for you.
Go.
Fine.
Brrr It's freezing.
Here's the towel.
Take it.
Can I play too?
Ughh.
Enough.
After this round, my shift is over.
Oh and today...
you don't need to hurry back to work?
No.
I cleared all my schedules
just to come see you as a dunk boy.
You like it huh?
When all of this is over,
I'll force you to be up here.
So you'll know
that it's not fun.
Look at you.
Prince!
P'Tum!
Excuse me.
Thought you're tired.
So I gave you a slot to rest.
But this is how you spend it?
P'Tum.
It's not like that.
Then what is it then?
Prince just wanted to join uni activities.
And...
come to see my friend.
Friend?
The friend that you rode behind his bike?
The friend that you went to his dorm?
Is he really a friend?
P'Tum...
The show is almost on aired.
So what?
I cannot have any friends?
It he is really just a friend then it's fine.
P'Tum.
I created you.
We've been through together since day 1.
I know what are you thinking
in just a blink of an eye.
What if I really like him?
What are you gonna do then?
- Prince.
- What are you gonna do?
Prince.
This is not something you can joke about.
You know what...
I've worked since I was very young.
I never got to live a normal life like other kids.
But when I met Bee,
he let me do things I've never done.
Like just eating on the side of the road.
But did you know that it was really good for me?
It's like...
I just learned how to be happy for the first time.
But you are not a normal person, Prince.
I am!
a normal person.
Who just happens to work as an actor.
Prince.
What if the company finds out?
Or the fans find out?
This is a very serious matter.
It could be worse than you can ever imagined.
Why?
Why can't an actor be in love?
Prince.
It's not that actors can't be in love.
But not every guys in this world can accept who you are.
Maybe,
if he finds out that you like him this much,
not only disappointing
but the friendship with him
might no longer exist even.
You need to learn a lot more, Prince.
Still here?
Yeah.
Just now...
you heard all of it, right?
Do you want me to hear it?
If I said no...
is that possible?
I'm afraid that...
after hearing those things,
you might turn into whatever P'Tum said.
That guy is Tum?
Yeah.
He's my manager.
Why do you ask?
So I can remember
that he's not nice to you.
Don't let me see him next time.
I'll take my revenge on him.
Can I have his car license number?
Should I flatten his tires?
Just kidding!
Let's put it this way,
I am...
not going to be what he said.
Feeling better?
So relieved!
Tum...
I'll keep an eye on him.
I can't rely on you
like at all.
I wanted Wiew to check out faculties.
But for 2 hours,
you guys spent in the Cooking club?
Cause the dessert was good, Hia.
I wanted to have some.
Why?
- Again?
- Shit I disappointed in them.
The president of swimming club is gay?
He is so cool.
His face looks pretty too.
Why is he has to be gay?
Yeah.
I'm so disappointed.
Yeah thinking about it already makes me cringe.
Hey!
Calm down.
Hia.
Listen to them talk.
Calm down. Come here.
They're talking about P'Dean.
come here!
Hia.
I'm gonna go punch them.
What's the matter with you?
I'm not okay with that.
Why do they have to say those things?
You can't control people's thoughts.
If you went to punch them,
do you think you can change their minds?
or stop talking?
How many people out there?
That are homophobic?
You can't expect everyone to understands us.
But they don't have to be that rude.
Cringe or disgusted?
What did Pharm and P'Dean do to deserve that?
Why did they have to say those things?
If you're not like what they said,
then you shouldn't care about their words.
Also,
they posted pictures like that.
People will talk about it anyway.
All walks of life out there.
I just freaking hate that.
Those smart mouths,
when they're done gossiping.They're done.
But those on the internet,
the more rude, the better for them.
But people who got bullied,
is there anyone who actually care about them?
What if P'Dean and Pharm heard that...
Even I heard that...
it still makes me feel shitty.
Dean knows.
and he has always known.
And..
He's not gonna do anything about it?
He doesn't care.
Do you wanna know what he said?
Don't value
those who don't value us.
But Pharm is easily concerned.
Why?
Love is just about two people.
Why do people have to be discriminated?
Pointing out that they are...
like this and that.
It's not fair, Hia.
Come here.
You don't have to worry.
Pharm has Dean.
And also us.
If people talk bad about him,
both you
and Manow
will always be by his side, right?
What about you?
What?
About you and me...
Does it worry you?
What if I say no,
are you gonna believe me?
Are you afraid?
No.
Not at all.
I'm never afraid of anything when I'm with you.
Like you said,
we can't control anyone.
but we can choose
not to care.
Then...
let's fight this together.
You're so adorable.
But I'm going to wait...Hia
wait for the day the P'Dean and Pharm's love
will become a norm for everyone.
That's good.
Let's go.
Are you ready, dunk tank boy?
Ahhh.
No, I don't like it.
- Let's go, kiddo! Go.
- No, I don't want to.
- I don't like it, Hia.
- Go go.
- Why do you have to force me? Stop Hia.
- Go!
- No!
- Come on.
Oh.
P'Phruek.
Err...
it's been super busy at my club today.
so I couldn't make it to see you on the stage.
I was just...
walking around a bit on the stage.
But I was...
super nervous too.
My heart was beating so fast.
Err...
can I take some pictures with the actress?
I shouldn't have changed.
That's fine.
I just wanna take pictures with you.
Not with the outfit.
P'Phruek!
Why are you still there?
Come take pictures with me!
Okay.
Smile.
One more?
Sure.
Today...
you look so pretty.
Thank you.
Bottoms up at the same time?
P'Phruek and P'Dean are not coming?
No.
They said they have some stuff to do.
Do stuff with my friend probably.
Here guys. Cheers!
- Cheers!
- Wooo!
Bee.
Come on!
Take it easy.
I don't wanna carry you home.
Hey Bee.
When did Prince leave?
I didn't see him leave.
Yeah right.
In the evening.
Bee.
What's the matter?
You seem depressed like a sad dog.
You.
Not just an ordinary dog too,
he's a temple dog that wants things out of his league.
Am I missing something here?
Try and ask him.
Bee.
Or you and Prince...
that actor...
Hey don't be too loud, Team!
He might be affected.
Ooh be affected?
So you really like him, huh?
I'm not sure.
But can we just don't talk about this now?
Let's drink!
Cheers! Cheers!
Here.
Cheers then.
Keep drinking.
We're really good.
Cheers to the shyness.
But hey...
when you said you're not sure
that phrase has destroyed many couples too.
It's not easy.
To be sure that you really love someone.
If you made the wrong decision,
there's only regret.
If you're not sure, then prove it.
Yeah.
Huh?
If you like him, then tell him.
Yeah.
If you love him, then tell him.
How?
You're hogging him to yourself.
He could feel bad about that.
Right.
Don't play hard to get.
That's right.
Yeah.
Sitting here being depressed.
- You two.
- Hey guys..
I'm gonna go to the restroom.
Okay.
Hia.
Need to use the toilet?
I came to see you.
To see me?
Why?
Hia.
What are you doing?
Can I?
Dad. Mom.
This is Team. He is a junior from my club.
Team, what’s the matter?
I’m just a junior.
I’m not sure
whether Hia’s feeling is reciprocated with me.
I’m afraid that Hia Win probably can’t take this.
If you don’t wanna lose him,
then try first.
Hia.