[Previously]
I don't reckon it is a typical migraine.
There's a high chance it's brain meningioma.
I don't think Gun should know this yet.
Please, I beg you.
- How long have you known?
- More than a week.
And when were you planning on telling me?
Or would it be at her funeral?
Don't be mad at Tinn.
He didn't do anything for me, but he did for my son.
Thanks for always being by my side.
After today, whatever shitty rules there are, they can't stop us.
I have the results in my hand now.
Chinzhilla!
Hot Wave Music Awards 2022's Best High School Band goes to…
The band...
Chinzhilla!
Yay!
Good morning, Students.
Good morning.
Has any of you got some good news for me?
Come and confess which university you got into.
I'm going to get acknowledgment from the director.
None of those strange places, all right. Like the faculty of comedy.
Oh, man. Good job!
Write down the name of your faculty.
The faculty of comedy is unacceptable.
Do you want to be a comedian?
Doesn't he feel better yet?
Hot Wave Music Awards 2022's Best High School Band goes to…
Tuaifoo!
What are you going to do now?
Have you talked to him?
I think…
this is not a good time.
So you two have to break up
to abide by his club rule, right?
That's a shame.
[Music Club]
[Fourth | Gemini]
♫ Having you with me, I want you to know ♫
♫ No matter how long, no matter how far ♫
♫ You are the only one ♫
♫ And I don’t mind being a rock ♫
♫ I’m shouting from the rooftops ♫
♫ I love you lots and lots ♫
♫ I am a rock on the star ♫
[My School President]
Hey, guys! How about we have a party this evening?
We haven't been in the club for a while.
The Holy Chinzhilla must have missed us so much.
I'm not available.
I have to visit my mom.
I get you.
What about the rest of you?
You? How about you?
I have a workshop this evening.
My series is about to start shooting.
I'm going to dinner with my dad.
I have make-up classes for those I've missed.
What the hell? Are you guys giving up just from a little defeat?
You're running away just because of this much?
Just freaking disband then.
Wait. How can you speak to your friends like that?
You just joined.
You won't get us.
Are you going to visit your mom?
Yes.
Then... I'll be going to the council.
[Music Club]
Hey, Ai Pat.
"Irasshaimase."
(T/N: "Welcome to enter" in Japanese)
Sit, sit, sit. I just got started.
I'm here just to grab some notes.
That's okay.
Get to class.
Don't be late.
Ai Por, just go home.
No one is coming back.
Our band is way over.
[Boon Yavej Hospital]
So yummy!
The hospital meals are tasteless.
I could barely swallow them.
How are you doing, Ma?
I'm still a bit dizzy,
but everything else is fine.
Oh, the doctor said I could go home next week.
Hey, don't rush it.
I can stay alone at home.
I want to make sure you're really okay.
I'm okay.
But when will you get better?
Ever since I woke up,
I haven't seen you singing.
I usually had to tell you to quit singing.
Do you think Dad would be disappointed in me?
What about you,
were you disappointed in him
for not being able to release his music?
As people,
if we've tried our best,
there's nothing to regret.
I think your dad would think the same.
Do you want to eat with me?
No.
Did I make it?
Visiting time is over.
Go get some rest first before I have to visit you instead.
Go, go, go.
Let's rest over here.
Tired?
How is your mom?
The doctor said she could be discharged next week.
I'm happy to hear that.
And… what about your club?
How is it going?
I see you guys don't go there anymore.
Right?
I'm still tired.
I think I'm going to take a break for a little longer.
You can take a break, but don't take too long.
If your skills get rusty, your audience will be disappointed.
What audience?
I asked people to vote for the band they wanted to see at prom night.
Guess which band they voted for?
My band?
[The Top Band "Chinzhilla" Is Performing at Niyomsil Suksa Prom Night]
Damn!
This is so cool.
You can ask your friends first.
Of course, they're performing. This is prom night.
P'Yak once said,
"Don't count yourself as a music club member if you haven't performed at the prom."
- He said that.
- He did?
Yes.
[Chinzhilla Baby]
Can't sleep, Honey?
Yes.
So I came downstairs to go through our son's photos.
Someone here doesn't want her son to grow up.
- Honey.
- Yes?
Do you think we raised him well enough?
Why would you ask that?
Do you think we've made any mistakes along the way?
There weren't any.
I believe if there was a Best Mother contest,
you would surely to be the champion.
Speaking of mistakes,
it's probably this one time.
You had a seminar to attend, and Tinn had to go through his singing test alone.
He was so nervous that he forgot the lyrics.
Then he came home and felt gloomy for a week.
- Do you recall?
- Yes.
Gosh.
Do you think if something like that happens again,
I'll be able to help him?
And if I can't help,
will he forgive me?
It's okay, Honey.
Hello. Welcome to Student Council channel.
This is the first comeback practice of Chinzhilla band!
Chinzhilla comeback!
Yo!!!
Please send them love by hitting the heart icon and share button.
Say hi to the camera, Guys.
- Hello!
Gun, are you okay?
I'm okay!
Do your best.
Are you guys ready?
We are.
- The band...
- Chinzhilla! Chinzhilla!
Chinzhilla! Chinzhilla! Chinzhilla! Chinzhilla!
Chinzhilla! Chinzhilla!
My apologies.
Can we continue tomorrow?
Ai Gun!
What just happened?
He hasn't sung for a while.
He might be getting stage fright.
He will be back in no time.
He won't.
Don't waste your time waiting.
Just cancel this freaking band.
I'm out.
Ai Win, where are you going?
Come back and apologize to your friends.
Ai Win! Ai Win!
Ai Win!
What the hell...
Does your band...
have some sort of issues?
Ai Win!
Ai Win.
Stop right there.
How can you say that shit?
Apologize to your friends right now!
It's not just Ai Gun who can't play on.
I can't either.
Every time I pick up the bass,
I think if I hadn't made mistakes, our band wouldn't have lost.
What do you want me to do?
Ai Gun doesn't get me! Ai Yo doesn't get me! Ai Por doesn't get me and Ai Pat doesn't get me!
No one understands. I'm so disappointed in myself. Don't you get it?
What do you expect me to do?
What do you want me to do? No one gets me!
What do you want me to do?
No one understands me.
- They don't understand me! I'm disappointed in myself!
- Enough!
That's enough!
You have no idea how much I tried.
I tried my best.
I made mistakes. What can I do now?
I made a mistake!
It's okay.
- You don't under—
- Enough!
I really tried...
I really did.
Next time,
let me know whatever you're going through.
Okay?
We're a couple.
Stop blaming yourself.
I... am sorry.
I shouldn't have rushed you.
I thought this event could motivate you again.
It's not your fault.
I was the one who ruined everything.
You've always been there for me.
I've lost so many times.
But this time…
Damn, it hurt the most.
You're feeling this because you did your best.
There's nothing to regret.
My best?
You remind me of when P'Yak lost Hot Wave.
He couldn't play on like I can't now.
Sit over there.
Please have a seat, Phi.
P'Yak, sit down.
Have a seat.
Why did you bring us here?
You know we quit playing.
I'm not asking you to play.
I'm playing for you.
Our song will comfort you guys.
Comfort us? You guys?
How about you learn to play the chords right first?
So what if you lost? Start over.
At least
you all did your best.
Our best?
Don't you say that to us again.
You guys will never get how we feel.
Today,
I think I get it now
when people say,
"It's okay. You did your best."
I keep asking myself today.
If I had sung better that day,
or if I had written a better song,
if I had arrived at the Hot Wave venue sooner,
would everything change?
Ai Gun.
Lift up your face.
What are you doing?
I saw it in a movie.
It said if we do this, we won't cry.
It's okay.
Whether you win or lose,
I will always be right by your side.
I'm not going anywhere.
[Music Club]
Let's go.
I don't think anyone will come back.
Come on. Wait a bit longer.
I think they'll come back this time. Trust me.
Sorry, Buddy.
I have to go.
I must catch the last ride home.
I think you should go, too.
Damn.
It's over.
I prepared barbecue pork as a surprise to celebrate Chinzhilla's comeback.
Look now.
I am the one surprised now.
Are you and Ai Tinn free?
Interested?
Ai Tinn just messaged me saying he's taking Ai Gun home.
I don't think he's coming.
Fine.
I apologize on their behalf.
You guys even came to help us.
But we wasted your time.
Then... How about you pay me with your barbecue pork?
I've heard about chef Por for so long.
I'd like to try his food.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Let me tell you,
you'll love it from the first bite.
By the second bite, you'll love it so much you'll choke!
Just kidding.
Whatever you want to eat, let me know.
I can make everything for you.
I want to eat you.
That was a joke.
All right.
I'll go prepare it.
Sure.
[Music Club]
Is that cooked?
Of course.
Let me try it.
- Should I dip it in the sauce?
- No.
The pork is marinated.
It's so tender.
- It's delicious!
- Isn't it?
Watch the temperature, Chef.
That was scary.
Just eat. Here.
Let me try.
When you said "big meal,"
I didn't think it would be this big.
Were you trying to feed the whole school?
Come on. I haven't made it in a while,
so I miscalculated the portions a bit.
Shit!
Hey! Watch it.
Didn't you see? You almost fell.
Watch where you're going or you'll—
Ai Por!
Ouch.
Where are you hurt?
[Niyomsil Suksa High School]
Wow!
How are you?
As you can see,
I'm lucky it's just a little bone fracture.
I thought they would have to cut off my leg.
That doesn't look like it's little.
Why didn't you two help him carry?
You let him carry it all himself and look what happened.
Who was the first one to leave?
I didn't know he brought barbecue pork.
What? It was you!
- You were the first!
- What?
Hey!
Don't argue!
It's my own fault.
I'm being punished because...
This happened because I forgot to make an offering for my wish.
What?
I didn't see that coming.
Do you remember when we were at the beach
and paying respect to the buddha image up on the hill, wishing to win Hot Wave?
Satu!
I wished for my zero-mistake performance.
It's unbelievable.
I didn't make any mistakes on stage at all.
I'm still getting chills.
Since then, I haven't had time to give offerings to repay for my wish.
I think that's why I'm facing such bad luck.
This is the worst so far.
This is serious. Why didn't you say anything?
You guys have been down lately.
I don't want to add insult to injury.
But it's okay, Guys.
I'll go make the offerings tomorrow.
You're going in this condition? I'll go with you.
Don't act like a hero. I'll go.
- I'll go.
- I'll be the one to go.
- I will.
- I will go.
- I'm going.
- I'll go.
- I'm going to go!
I'm going! I said I was the one who was going first!
Don't even say anything! You were the first to leave!
- Don't! I'll go!
- Hey!
Why do you have to fight?
We all wished for something, right?
Then let's all go make an offering!
Done!
Fine. Do as you said.
[Chinzhilla Baby]
Hello.
Hey. I have to go make offerings to pay for my wish next week.
Are you confused?
We rockstars
suddenly become so spiritual.
You're right.
Speaking of the wish, I kind of miss that trip.
We didn't get to relax to our heart's content. P'Yak ruined it first.
Do you want to come, too?
Can I?
Of course.
Why not?
I'll ask my mom then.
Okay, that's all for now. A customer is walking in.
Hi. How can I help?
Hello, Director.
What would you like, Ma'am?
May I have Ginkgo Nuts in Fresh Milk to have here
and Steamed Bread with Thai Custard to go?
Of course.
Do milk bars these days provide live music too?
My mom knows I love singing,
so she set it up for me.
If you're interested, you're welcome to play.
I'm sorry.
I have a habit of asking people if they want to play.
It's okay.
Thanks for asking,
but I can't sing at all.
And no one in my family can.
But Tinn has got a really nice voice, Director.
Tinn?
Have you heard him sing before?
More than just sing.
He helped me sing at a senior's bar.
If it wasn't for Tinn, I would have been doomed.
Gun, may I ask you something?
It's about Tinn.
Excuse me. One Iced Thai Milk Tea, please?
One moment, please. Just a moment.
Please go serve your customer.
What would you like?
Sorry, Mom. The meeting ended a little late.
Have you eaten?
It's okay.
I ate something already.
[School Milk]
I...
visited Gun's Mother's milk bar.
You went there?
Yes.
They serve the good stuff.
Why?
Ah, no. Nothing.
Mom,
a friend invited me on a beach trip tomorrow.
Which friend is it this time?
A friend from the Music Club.
Gun was the one who invited you, right?
Yes.
Can I go?
You can. Take care of yourself.
Of course.
Let me help.
You can store your belongings at the back.
Not there, over here.
Oh, I got it.
Are you sure your mom just wanted to
buy desserts at my Mom's bar yesterday?
And not that she's suspecting anything?
You're right.
But she didn't say anything though.
I think it was just a coincidence.
It's nothing.
Let's go get into the van.
Guys, if you're ready, get in the van.
Okay, get in.
Let me carry it.
Hey, it's okay, man.
- Please.
- Ai Sound.
Get in the van quickly.
I reserved you a spot.
So... do you like it?
You always read my mind. Let's go.
Come on. That's everyone.
- Let's go.
- All set, right?
- Yes, all done.
- Whoa, let me help you!
Slowly, slowly...
- His leg!
- Ouch!
Does it hurt?
All right. Let's get in on the other side.
Let's go.
Are we all set? We're all here.
As soon as we get there, we will make our offerings.
Once we finish, we will go straight to the beach to relax!
Let's go!
[Construction Ahead. No Passing!]
Watch out for our friend.
Dang!
I guess we must walk up there.
But look at Ai Por's condition.
It's hard enough for him to get in the van.
We also have the offerings.
Why is there so much as if we're going to open up a store?
Calm down first.
I'm sorry, all right.
I will come again by myself tomorrow.
Ai Por, this is not your fault.
Though I can't lift your burden, I can lift you.
Damn! How cool.
Call me, "Ai Pat the Carry."
Ouch!
Ow! Ow! Ouch!
Ouch! Ow! Ow! My back!
Argh! My back! Lift me up!
Ouch! My back!
- I'm carrying the stuff for you here.
- Can you walk faster?
♫ Wherever I look, you’re never far ♫
♫ Thanks for loving me and staying where you are ♫
♫ When I’m down, you’re right here ♫
♫ (You’ve got ma back back) ♫
So exhausted.
Come on, let's go.
Ai Yo, help me carry!
Why is all his weight on me?
Let's go.
Damn it. Ai Por alone is tough enough for us.
Someone just had to show off. Hurry up.
Hey, do it gently.
I'm exhausted.
We're all tired.
Does anyone have water? I'm thirsty.
Let's take a break here.
No, we don't have any.
I didn't think we would have to go through this much trouble.
We only have this red soda for the offerings.
Guys, it's okay. I'll walk down and buy you some.
You shut it.
Look at you. How can you even walk?
Should we rest?
Yes. Let's take a break.
[Ohishi Tea]
Take it. I only have one bottle.
I'll let you drink it first, and then you can share with the rest.
You want me to hide it from my friends?
I can't.
- Do you want me to throw it away?
- Hey.
I'll share it with them later.
Ai Gun, do you want to take my place?
Hey, Ai Gun, what's wrong?
Why are you two hugging?
It's nothing.
If nothing, then why are you guys hugging?
He's a little dizzy, but he's fine. You guys can go ahead.
Ai Gun, you're dizzy? What's wrong?
- He's fine.
- Do you have a fever?
You're tired, aren't you?
It's nothing.
You're being a cheat!
I just said I was thirsty.
Can I have some? I'm thirsty. Give me that.
I want some, too.
- I want some, too!
- Let's get some!
Are you guys forgetting me?
Right. Sorry.
Here.
There's nothing left!
- I'm sorry!
- I'm thirsty! I'm thirsty! It's sweltering!
Go and lift him up.
It's so hot.
- Ouch!
- What's wrong?
My back hurts.
I'll buy you some later.
- I can't go on.
- You're okay.
Hey. Let's take a break.
When will we get there?
According to the GPS, we're close.
Close to halfway.
Damn it.
We've walked forever and haven't reached halfway yet.
Are we going to make offerings or going on a "journey to the west"?
Don't complain.
We're slow because I have to carry you.
I know, but I can't go on anymore.
Let me drink something. Please, I'm begging.
- No, Ai Pat.
- These are for the offering.
Please. I can't carry on.
No, Ai Pat. You can't drink that. It's for the offerings.
Otherwise, there won't be enough for the offerings.
Why would we walk all the way here just to let you drink it?
Screw it! I'm thirsty!
- Ai Pat, are you out of your mind?
- Hey, Ai Pat!
- Pat.
- I'm thirsty!
What the hell are you doing? Stop!
Hey! Ai Pat, you asshole!
Why the fuck would we walk so far up here then?!
Well, I'm thirsty.
And you think we're not?
- I'm thirsty, too, you asshole!
- Hey! Hey!
Let's do this.
You guys stay here. I'll go get the drinks.
You can't go like this.
You don't need to go. He should go so he can stop being so fucking selfish!
Who's selfish? Isn't it you!
When was I being like that?
Since we competed.
You always wanted to rearrange this and that. You messed up our band.
And you didn't make mistakes at all, right? Was I the only one wrong?
Can you even play the drums?!
If you're going to blame me, blame that asshole Yo!
That jerk! It was all over the place and he made so many mistakes!
What mistakes? I was trying to cover up Ai Sound!
You jackass. Why are you saying that?
Because you all sucked. That's why I had to carry you all.
Why can't you become a world-class musician if you're so great?
Asshole! Don't get smart with me!
Why don't you play as great as having a smart mouth, Jerk?
So what? You bastard!
- Hey!
- You're friends!
Stop it!
Calm down.
- Asshole.
- That's enough.
Both of you.
Will anything get better if you fight?
You don't get to talk.
What do you do every day aside from stopping fights?
We lost because of you.
Right.
It's my fault.
I was the one who made our band lose!
It was me! Only me!
Are we done here?
You just realized that, Asshole?
We lost because of you, Ai Gun.
We lost because of you.
We lost because of you, asshole Gun!
Because of you, Bastard!
How could you say that?
- Gun! Don't!
- Hey!
Gun, stop.
You've always been like this, you dipshit
Ai Gun, that's enough!
Enough! I've had it!
It's nobody's fault.
If there's anyone to blame, blame it on me
for dragging you all up here.
Please stop fighting.
You want me to beg? Should I?
Should I beg for that? Please, Guys. Please. Please.
How long have we been friends?
Shit.
I'm sorry, Guys.
I started this.
Ai Por, I'm sorry.
Ai Yo, I'm sorry.
Ai Sound, I'm sorry.
Ai Gun, I'm sorry.
Ai Win, I'm sorry.
Ai Por, I'm sorry.
Ai Sound,
I'm sorry.
Ai Gun,
Crying like a baby.
We can't even manage to make offerings.
This is so us.
It's not just Ai Por who wanted to make offerings.
On that day, I didn't wish for us to win.
I only wished not to have anxiety on stage.
I wished for myself to wake up in time for the competition.
But I didn't get any sleep at all.
Honestly,
I wished that my wrist tendonitis didn't act up.
As for me,
I wished not to be hot-headed like P'Yak and make us lose.
Our wishes came true,
yet we still lost.
Damn us.
Are you going to let it end like this?
Aren't you tired of hearing people say we suck?
We never succeed in anything we do.
All we do is eat barbecue pork.
Your high school lives
are almost over.
Don't you want to succeed in anything for once?
I...
will continue going upward to make the offering.
Who's coming with me?
I will.
Me, too.
- Me as well.
- I'm going.
Me, too.
That's it.
Love each other a lot.
You guys are in the same band.
I love you guys.
Don't cry. Why are you crying?
That's all we need.
That's all it took.
No more of that.
Guys, your drink is here.
- I want one.
- Please give me one.
Water please!
So refreshing.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's go. All set.
All done.
Do you have to make any offerings?
I must be the one to ask you.
I wished for whatever
you wished for to come true.
Right.
You haven't told us what you wished for.
That's right.
You know what?
I was so scared
to be the club head.
We joined it together.
We played music together.
We were punished together.
And one day, I had to lead you guys.
I was afraid I would lead our band to failure.
I was afraid our club would get terminated because of me.
But my biggest fear
was that I would make you disappointed.
On that day, I didn't wish for us to win Hot Wave.
I wished for you guys
to not regret being in this club.
Gosh!
Then go ahead and make your offering for your wish.
We've come this far
because of you.
Come on.
Good job, Ai Gun.
♪ Among millions of people in this city ♪
♪ Without having to search for ♪
♪ When you took hold of me ♪
- Honey.
- Yes?
What are you doing?
Are you sneaking peaks at Korean celebrities?
Are you out of your mind?
Have you seen this?
Tinn went to help his friend sing at his upperclassman's bar.
The video is on the bar's page. Lots of people shared it.
Are you sure?
Tinn is singing?
Can you believe it?
After that day,
Tinn had always refused to go up on stage.
Whenever he felt hesitant,
he let me decide for him.
Hold on.
Is he the singer you told me Tinn has been close to?
Yes.
You've been having a hard time sleeping
because of this, right?
Yes.
Our son used to cry on stage whenever he got on stage.
But look at him now.
He's happy.
Shouldn't we be happy, too?
What if this world is so cruel to our son?
If this world is cruel to our son,
we should be his peace of mind
when he comes home, shouldn't we?
Five, four, three, two, one.
Surprise!
We're paying back for the last time we let you eat alone.
Thank you, Guys.
When did you prepare this?
I was with you guys the whole time.
We're superhuman.
Seriously, when did you guys find time to do this?
I prepared this.
How did you get here?
I saw you were quite upset.
I want to do whatever makes you feel better.
Did I miss something? What is happening?
What did you miss? It's nothing.
Just hurry up and shove it in your mouth!
Let's save our energy for prom night tomorrow.
What did you two talk about? I want to know, too.
Think about prom night.
Save your energy for prom night.
- Eat, eat, eat.
- What are we waiting for?
Let's eat!
Save your energy for prom night.
Put that in too.
I noticed you're sitting far from the grill.
I was afraid you couldn't reach it.
Thank you.
It's so good.
- Do you want more?
- Just eat. I'm good.
- I want some water.
- Wait!
Your leg hurts. Let me do it.
Here.
Did you forget something?
My leg hurts, not my arm.
Let's eat.
Anything else you want? Let me get it for you.
Sure, here.
Ai Gun.
Eat a bit.
Are you worried about singing at prom night?
Leave that for later.
Eat for now.
Eat the pork too. It is so good.
Okay?
I want to eat veggies.
[Incoming Call - Yak]
Hey.
P'Yak is calling.
What?
- Seriously?
- Is he maybe hiding around here?
What?
No, he's not.
Hello, P'Yak.
How are you guys?
Are you guys feeling better?
I'm worried.
Thank you.
I didn't know you could be cute and kind.
Of course, not.
I just called to brag to you losers about something.
Listen carefully.
My band just won the freshmen music contest.
More importantly, we beat our Hot Wave rival.
How satisfying!
Okay. Okay.
If you're done bragging,
I'm going to hang up.
Hey, hold on.
Listen first. I'm not done yet.
I just want you to know that we got back to playing music
because we heard this one song.
I'll send it to you.
It might help you too, like it did to me.
Okay?
What?
- What?
- Huh, what song?
Let's go take a look.
What song?
So what if you lost?
Start over.
At least you all did your best.
Our best?
Don't you say that to us again.
You guys will never get how we feel.
Right.
We don't get you.
You guys are way better.
We can't even compare to bands in school.
That's why we want you to fight.
This song,
we're playing for us losers.
[Music is brief. Friendship is long.]
♪ I know how disappointed you are ♪
♪ The ordeals that life put you through ♪
♪ And you, how many tears you cry ♪
♪ On days things go awry ♪
♪ Disappointment is your only company ♪
♪ I want you to know, you’ll always find me ♪
♪ Whenever you’re in pain ♪
♪ Every teardrop that falls on your face ♪
♪ You have me to heal your pain ♪
♪ When you lose, rest and start over ♪
♪ When you fall, get up and run for cover ♪
♪ Know that it’s true ♪
♪ I’ll be the one to heal you ♪
♪ Aim for the stars, but the sky seems so far ♪
♪ It may leave you with scars, hang on tight  ♪
♪ I want you to know, you’ll always find me ♪
♪ Whenever you’re in pain ♪
♪ Every teardrop that falls on your face ♪
♪ You have me to heal your pain ♪
♪ When you lose, rest and start over ♪
♪ When you fall, get up and run for cover ♪
♪ Know that it’s true ♪
♪ I’ll be the one to heal you ♪
♪ I want you to know, you’ll always find me ♪
♪ Whenever you’re in pain ♪
♪ Every teardrop that falls on your face ♪
♪ You have me to heal your pain ♪
♪ When you lose, rest and start over ♪
♪ When you fall, get up and run for cover ♪
♪ Know that it’s true ♪
♪ I’ll be the one to heal you ♪
I'm sorry, Guys,
for not being able to take you to your dreams.
Hey, we...
Can you forgive me?
Come on. Get up and we will tell you.
Hurry.
At the final round, your band was the coolest for me.
Can I witness the Chinzhilla tribute again right here?
Do it. Come on. Hurry.
Three, four.
Chin-Zhil-La!
[School Milk]
Thanks a lot.
Get back home now,
or your mom will get worried.
Actually, it's not just P'Yak who has a song for you.
I had it custom-made.
I was going to give it to you as a post Hot Wave gift.
It's cute.
You mean me or the box?
Both.
After what happened, I just couldn't find a chance to give it to you.
Open it and listen.
How is it?
It's so romantic.
About us, don't you worry at all.
Although your club doesn't allow lovers,
I can wait until you're a college student.
If your faculty doesn't allow that either,
I can wait until you graduate and get a job.
No matter how long, I'll always wait for you right here.
Who told you we can't have lovers?
It's your club rule.
Doesn't it say you can't have lovers unless you win Hot Wave?
Where did you learn that?
Listen carefully.
My club rule says,
no dating until
the Hot Wave competition is over.
It doesn't say anything about winning.
Ai Yo is still dating his girlfriend.
Nook?
So that means,
you and I...
Why not?
You said it yourself, you would wait until I have a job.
Because I didn't know about your club rule.
Don't you want to be my lover?
If you date me right now, you will also get the hashtag, #MySchoolPresident.
All right. Go home now.
- What is that?
- Go home already.
I need to pack my clothes.
- It's my mom's last day at the hospital.
- Yeah?
Yes.
Go.
Wait.
Can't I talk to you a little longer? Please. Can I?
Before we talk, how about you let me talk to my mom first
about that hashtag you mentioned?
Really?
You'll talk to your mom?
Are you happy? Go home already.
Why do you keep shooing me away?
- Go.
- What am I, a mosquito?
Go home already.
♫ My heart flies high, it needs something to lean on ♫
♫ Where could I move on to, this unmovable heart is set on you ♫
♫ Love, love I need somebody to love ♫
♫ But that person must be you ♫
♫ I pray for us to be true ♫
♫ This is the love I’ll never hit undo ♫
I'm making my unofficial mark first.
Once you get your mom's approval,
I'll give you the official one.
I'm leaving now.
- Hey, Mom.
- Tinn.
Can I talk to you?
About Gun.
[Directed by Kornprom Niyomsil]
[Next Episode]
Ai Gun! Have you seen this?
My friends asked if it was you.
Yes. I'm dating Ai Gun.
I'm part of the council. I'm not here to help you pursue someone.
Think about your parents with whatever you guys do.
Especially you, Tinnapob.
Your mother is this school's director.
Let me take you.
No. You know why.
Forget whatever they want to think.
I will always be by your side.
Don't worry. We will walk on together.
♫ Only once in a lifetime ♫
♫ When destiny brought to me ♫
♫ A wonderful thing that is you ♫
♫ Any moment in time ♫
♫ None I would regret ♫
♫ It will be a memory ♫
♫ That I’ll never forget (I’ll remember us this way) ♫
♫ Once in a lifetime ♫
♫ I have no regrets ♫
♫ (I’ll remember us this way) ♫
♫ Once in a lifetime ♫
♫ I have no regrets ♫
♫ (I’ll remember us this way) ♫
♫ Once in a lifetime ♫
♫ I have no regrets ♫
[GMM-TV]