Do you want me to make you feel better?
What do you think you're doing?
Are you crazy?
You're crazy.
It definitely gave you energy.
I knew my kiss of support
would give you strength.
Go home now.
Manager, didn't you do it too?
Before, when you were going on blind dates.
You did it too.
And to think I could talk to you...
Then why did you close your eyes?
You're the one who puckered up.
When did I do that?
Eighth Cup
Are you going to give me strength again?
You do it, and you're dead.
How Han Kyul-ian.
Do you know what that means?
It means…
To look cool when you're
having a hard time.
You can't admit you like
something when you do.
You're good at making things up.
You have to visit your grandmother.
I should.
I don't know how I should act.
What should I say?
My dad died after he was
sick for a very long time.
But I showed him my report card.
And when my mom scolded me,
I tattled to my dad.
If I got sleepy,
I slept next to the IV stand.
The day he passed away,
when I said good bye to him
before I went to school,
I just knew right away.
There might be a chance that
when I came back from school,
Dad won't be there.
Little punk.
What if I was a girl?
If I was a girl,
do you think we could date?
It's a good thing you're not a girl.
Why?
If a girl as hectic as
you followed me around...
saying she likes me and
that she wants to date me,
It'll be too hectic.
Huh… you sure are infatuated with yourself.
Who said I wanted it?
I think it's time for me
to stop fooling around.
Getting pushed and pulled,
even dating is annoying.
I'll get married to some girl who
my grandmother and mother both approve.
It'll be some rich business
man's third daughter, right?
It doesn't sound too bad.
Because my grandmother grew up
in a good environment,
that kind of a girl is
her ideal granddaughter-in-law.
And my mom's that kind
of daughter-in-law too.
Jong Gook oppa, just wait a little.
I'll come out with an album within the year.
Then I'm going to sing a duet with you.
Should I just reveal that I'm a girl?
Calm down.
If you tell him,
do you think he'll be like
Oh My Darling right away?
What if he doesn't like you as a girl?
Do you have the courage
to still face him after that?
I went to the café last time,
and I suddenly had this thought.
I think I would just like to be by his side.
Then, I would have nothing else to want.
There are two solutions.
You can tell him expecting
to never see him again.
Or you throw away your greed
and live like this with him in front of you.
Just to tell you,
Oscar from The Rose of Versailles.
Pretended that she was a
boy to save the country.
But I don't have a duty like that.
Unni,
you have love!
Go Eun Chan to protect the man she loves,
pretends to be a boy.
We have to go to the Soo Suh neighborhood.
After we deliver ten kilograms to Toto,
I think we're done with today's
coffee bean deliveries.
I'll drop you off in Soo Suh,
so you can go home afterwards.
What about you, Manager?
I have to drop by the hospital.
Then you'll come back to work, right?
Then, let's go together.
I don't think it's respectful to not pay
a visit to an elder in the hospital.
Hm, my knees keep hurting these days.
It's been a long time
since I've hugged my mother.
You were really worried. right?
You know your grandmother is not
going to like it if you know, right?
Don't act like you're worried
and just act as you normally would.
My mother's face aged a lot...
Hello!
Who?
My employee. He came to visit.
I asked someone and they said
100% fruit juice is okay.
You gave a lot of attention.
Thank you.
Come on in.
Your stomach's acting up because you keep
eating spicy, salty and sweet stuff too much.
What's going to happen to my grandmother?
I guess you can't have any shaved ice
with red beans now.
Look at this punk!
He's totally excited.
Are you having a good time
making fun of me?
I'm not enjoying it at all.
My heart hurts so much.
I might go to the bathroom and cry a lot.
Look, look!
This is why I can't even allow myself to be sick.
I'm sick because I did a bit of work.
Why don't you just tell me to go die,
you rascal!
And why have you been just
standing over there?
You should introduce yourself to me.
I introduced myself to you before.
Hello! I'm Go Eun Chan
and working at Coffee Prince.
Grandma! Have some strength!
This punk thinks I'm deaf.
What are you going to do with someone
who has no control over himself?
Replace him immediately.
What's this?
You folded a lot.
It looks like a thousand!
Did you make a wish
while folding them?
I prayed that she would pass away
slowly without pain.
But folding paper cranes is a little lame.
But that's why it's pretty,
Choi Han Seong.
I have nothing…
What's this!
I have nothing to eat.
Yeah... look at this one! Look!
You're sweeping the board!
You guys are cheating!
What? Who's cheating?
Do you have proof?
I do! I do!
When manager touched his nose,
you put down that card.
And when you touch your ear,
he puts down that card!
You guys work perfectly together.
Do you still deny cheating?
I'm not playing anymore...
I touched my nose because it itched!
You stay still, you cheater.
I'm not going to play!
How dare you accuse me of cheating?
Where did you come from?
Did you come to visit a sick person
or raise their blood pressure?
I didn't want to play Go Stop,
and you're the one who pressured me to play.
And then you accused me of cheating?
I hate people who do that
playing Go Stop. Go.
Do you think it's over
if you clear the board?
Let's play one more round!
Or... just give me back my money.
Why should I give you my money?
I won't!
You're here?
Welcome!
Grandmother looks good.
Grandmother, I'm here.
Eun Chan, you came too.
Hello.
Are we all in mourning?
Why is everyone coming?
What, Grandmother?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Do I need your permission for that too?
I'll go with you! I'll help!
You rascal!
Even though I'm old, I'm still a girl!
You keep treating me like
a brainless old lady.
Grandmother, go with me.
It's all right!
The bathroom's right there.
Let's go, let's go.
Why are you here?
I was playing.
Sit, sit!
Did you get anything?
Get what?
The two planned it out...
I only have 1000 won left.
Where's Han Seong?
Grandmother wanted vegetable soup,
so he went to buy some.
And Go Eun Chan?
He went with.
I told them I wanted to be here with you.
But...
Eun Chan is very unique.
When I'm with elders,
I get stiff and feel really nervous.
But how come Eun Chan is
so perfectly comfortable?
He's good to everyone.
He doesn't shy away from strangers
and he becomes friends easily.
I think he can do everything if he wants...
he just doesn't have the opportunity.
Either way, he's a really unique person.
A star's shining here too.
Grandmother is healthier
than I thought she was.
I'm relieved. I worried a lot
after Han Seong called me.
I pay attention only when something happens...
Last night, I realized it's been a lot time
since I went night fishing with Grandmother.
Do you know how good she is at fishing?
Do you want to borrow it?
This side is exclusive for Choi Han Kyul.
You're having a hard time, huh?
I know Grandmother likes spending time
with me more than fishing.
So when she said to go fishing with her,
I feel bad for thinking she was annoying.
Are you happy that you're
working at the café again?
How did you know?
Then how would the two
of you come here?
He said that he really needed me…
Because I wasn't there,
sales weren't going up.
So he kept begging me to come back
and I was getting annoyed.
Who? Han Kyul?
Well, yeah.
Mister, I saw your name!
Music Director, Choi Han Seong.
In a movie! It was really cool!
What movie?
I forgot.
Let's eat before we go back.
I don't want to.
What's wrong with you?
Don't pay attention and just drive.
You're tired because you're hungry, huh?
See, who told you to come?
Eat two bowls of rib stew.
That's good, right?
I don't want to eat.
Let's just go.
Are you sick?
I'm not sick or hungry.
Let's just go back!
Stop annoying me.
You punk,
why are you giving me an attitude?
I kept saying you were cute
and now you do what you want.
How can you be like that?
How can you lie on your
cousin's girlfriend's lap?
How can you do it especially
when he's not there?
So disgusting and annoying.
What? Annoying?
Do you have any brains or not?
How do you think Han Seong felt?
How can you be so forward with your actions?
You're lucky Han Seong is
just a really nice guy.
Stop it.
If you like her that much,
why don't you just steal her?
Do you only see me as that much?
How can I...
with my cousin's girl...
Stop pretending like you have a conscience.
You already do lots of weird things.
With an already taken girl, disgusting.
Not just a couple of days,
but a couple of years.
How annoying!
Wow, I'm hearing all kinds of things in my life.
Seriously... wow...
How is it?
The title is Lame Paper Cranes.
Why do you keep getting more handsome?
It makes me nervous.
Wow, I've been nervous for nine years
since we've been going out.
You're just getting nervous now?
How was I in my twenties?
Your twenties?
Busy, hectic, urgent...
It felt like you were chasing after something.
You kept running after something,
but I'm not sure what that something was.
These days I look at Eun Chan,
and I think about my past.
Why wasn't I so fresh
like that in my twenties?
You're still fresh.
Only a little more of liking her,
and that's it.
She's just cute and pretty. That's all.
I'm not going to let anymore happen!
Huh? Huh?
And what if you won't?
You punk! Really!
Hyung nim!
- Move!
- Eun Sae...
Manager, what's wrong with them?
They're burning, mixing and making
all the flavor come alive.
Why isn't she answering her phone?
I was wondering if you
can give me counseling on life.
My Eun Sae keeps ignoring my phone calls
and I don't know what to do about it.
You've been waiting for one
girl for three years.
Can you tell me the secrets?
Stop talking nonsense.
Don't worry about it!
I'm taking your amazing secret of love
with me to my grave.
Do you want to know another secret?
I'm Japanese.
Nihonjin desu.
Wow!
So that's what... no wonder!
You're so good at Japanese.
I'm sorry I've been annoying about telling you
to speak your country's language.
I'll keep your secrets, don't worry.
You're telling me all your secrets.
Wow, so this is a man's worry.
I really wasn't going tell anyone this...
But I feel like it's unfair if
I know all your secrets.
Go Eun Chan... is a girl.
What?
Girl.
I'm serious. She's our older sister.
I gave him a kiss.
I went to the hospital with him.
I made him laugh.
And still it's her?
And when will the results come out?
Hello!
Good morning!
I think it'll be good for her to stay at the hospital
until the results come out?
Okay then, I'll see you at home.
Left, left.
No, it's crooked.
Can't you even see it?
Right, right.
A little more.
No, you can't even see that?
Are you a fish?
The picture's upside down!
How can you not even see that?
Hey! I don't know why I have
to say this to you but...
You think I'm a jerk who looks
at my cousin's girlfriend.
I mean, Han Yoo Ju and I.
We used to be but now we are...
Hey, the picture's upside down.
Introducing super star, Jang Dong Geun!
I'm totally cute, right?
Hello! I'm Go Eun Sae.
It starts now, little by little
Next.
I'm usually really good.
It's okay.
Do you want to see me dance?
It's okay. You can go now.
- Next.
- One more!
Next!
Hey! I watched a movie with
customer number three yesterday!
Isn't that breaking the rules?
What rules?
How dare you call the relationship
between a man and a woman rules?
But this is a secret to Han Kyul, okay?
Look! She's dying of happiness.
You're the one dying of happiness.
Look at the picture, she's dying.
Do you want to meet her friends?
I'm so hungry.
Are we going to the farm
to get the apples?
The farmer's going to deliver to us.
Did you organize all the orders and stuff?
I put the list and stuff in your car.
After we eat, let's go deliver.
You can go with Ha Rim.
I have stuff to do.
Where are you going?
You only ate one row.
I'm done. I'm going to go.
He's not even looking at me now.
Hey! Hey!
What's wrong with you?
If you have a problem,
let's talk about it.
What did I do?
Besides you,
I'm already in a crazy situation.
Hurry and tell me without the attitude.
What's the problem?
I like you.
What?
But I shouldn't...
because it's man to man.
You punk, playing again.
So I'm trying to set aside my feelings.
Just leave me alone.
Tiny punk keeps sucking out my soul.
Psychiatry, psychiatry.
Do you want some coffee?
No, I'm good.
Have you kissed?
An impulse to want to become a woman.
An impulse to want to put on make up.
Or feeling nervous when seeing men...
Since when have you had these symptoms?
I don't have symptoms like that.
Then, you just simply like men...
Excuse me, I'll come next time.
You just need medicine.
I'll give you three days worth.
I try not to, but I keep getting mad.
When I see his face,
my insides get hot.
Because you like him?
I'm not sure myself.
I like him, I hate him.
I get mad.
It keeps changing.
Do you think a pretty face will come
out if you do it like that?
What is that?
She's drawing an angel.
Angel.
Why are you here?
I told you not to come here.
You weren't answering the phone.
I wanted to watch a movie with you.
Have you seen this movie?
I heard it was fun.
Who said I was going to
watch movies with you?
Angel.
Let's go together.
Listen carefully because
I'm not going to repeat it again.
I like smart guys.
I hate guys who are stupid like you.
I'm going to study!
I even applied to a prep
school for exit exams.
Either way.
Don't call or visit me.
And don't send me text messages
with wrong spellings, okay?
I did that on purpose to make you laugh.
Wait.
But first, just take this.
Even if I try everything,
I don't think it'll work with that person.
I know it won't work but I still like him.
Do you think it's love?
Just end it. Stop hanging on pitifully.
Yeah, I'm going to.
Hey! Hey!
Do you want ice cream?
Hey!
What's wrong?
I got cut from the audition.
Are you crying?
Yeah.
Ju!
You're coming now?
Do you remember the first time
I opened an art exhibition?
I'll never forget that shabby basement.
The smell was terrifying too.
You bit your lip to prevent
yourself from crying.
That's why I fell for you.
I thought you said you fell
for my artistic inspiration and talents?
That comes later...
How's the musician?
How's the underwear model?
We're good.
He's warm and comfortable.
It's good.
I came here to get you.
I'm going to make a restaurant.
And I want to fill it with your artwork.
The door handles, the lighting,
even the spoons,
I want you to design it and
participate in its making.
I'll give you rights to the restaurant.
I like this one. Give it to me.
The pancake you made last time,
can you make it smaller?
Just enough for one person?
The price would be about 3000 won or so.
It would not be profitable that way.
Is that so?
You're good looking,
with a good personality.
You're really mysterious, huh?
I thought you're Japanese initially.
You're right, I am Japanese.
It's true?
Then how come you can
speak fluent Korean?
My mother's a Korean.
I'm just asking out of curiosity.
How did you hide your chest?
You don't have any?
Hwang Min Yeop!
What good do you see in that girl?
There's a limit to avoiding somebody.
It's total disrespect now.
She's really tortured Min Yeop half-dead.
Is she the only girl in the world?
She's my first crush.
The first girl I have ever kissed.
I only love Go Eun Sae.
Min Yeop,
the first is not everything in your life.
There will be a second after the first,
then the third...
even 100th, 1000th, 10,000th.
Hey, how are you planning
to repay my kindness?
Go away! I have no mood to joke now.
I'll do you a good deed for once.
I will handle Go Eun Sae.
You just do as I say.
You come over here.
Come over here.
What are you doing?
What have you told Sun Ki?
That...
That is...
Come let's have a drink together.
- That...
- Shut up!
What's up with you guys?
There are still guests around.
What are you guys doing?
Aren't you going in?
Your voice is louder.
What did you just say?
I said I'm going deaf because
of your loud voice.
Look at the guests' reactions,
they're more bothered by you.
What?
Ah...
why did you park your car here again?
How many times have I told you?
Not to park your car here.
Everyone would want to touch your car
and they'll leave fingerprints.
Drive it away quick.
Who are you to tell me to move my car?
Go back to work!
Well done for today.
Le's go eat something.
Aren't you going?
See you.
Come over if you feel like eating.
Have you managed to settle your feelings?
That day you told me that you had
some feelings for me,
I'm asking you about that now.
Have you settled your feelings?
Basically.
When I've settled my feelings totally,
I'll tell you about it.
See you.
I played well, right?
How do I play this?
Now I know why Kenny G's
face is puckered up.
Want to learn to play that?
No, I have no music talent.
Mom used to bring me to music school
to learn the piano when I was young,
and all I did was mess up the keys.
I was quite famous for that incident.
Trying playing it.
No way. I might break it.
It's alright. Just try playing it.
You play well.
So you knew how to play?
Looks like you're in good form today, huh?
Exactly contradictory to my feelings now.
Rather than fighting my way
against the opposite direction,
it's better to follow my own feelings
no matter how bad it is.
Mister, you're just like a Santa.
Am I that kind?
And your body's also a bit...
Large?
Yeah.
When I'm with you,
it feels like I've received a Christmas present.
You really know how to sweet talk, huh?
Let's start.
You will keep your promise right?
If you spill it out...
Come to my house to do cleaning.
What?
Once a week.
Then I'll keep the promise.
A promise is a promise,
what's this about?
If you're not happy, then forget it.
Alright, I'll do the cleaning.
I'll just have to do the cleaning, right?
You must not say anything else.
What is it about saying something else?
Did you damage your brain?
Could you have managed studies
with that brain of yours?
Why are you rubbing on me?
After all, I have an IQ of three digits.
Have you read the books
I bought for you last time?
I was tired,
so I just flipped over some pages.
The milk temperature used to
make Ratia should be?
65 degrees.
So, you did read a bit?
I didn't get that from reading
and memorizing from books.
I got that from practical experience.
Do you like eating ice?
Alright, I got it.
I will talk to her about it.
Oh.
Who was that?
Han Kyul.
He wants to go for a joy ride tonight.
What is there to drive around
in the middle of the night?
What's wrong? We can enjoy looking
at the night scenery of the Han River,
it should feel really good.
You will be blessed.
If we had sent Han Kyul to the orphanage.
Thanks to you, Mother. I have a good son.
If you hadn't said those words,
I couldn't have acted so cool about it.
I'm in a good mood now.
Here you go.
Mother.
Isn't this your most precious...?
Is this for real?
You cannot go back on your words.
Hey, let me hold it for a while,
and I'll give it to you later.
Give it to me.
Grandmother.
How can you eat ice?
What's with this child?
You're eating shaved ice.
You should protect your stomach.
Why are you being so troublesome?
Grandmother, you came here just
because of your grandson, right?
It's so cold.
Soup, eel, chicken stew, pig's feet.
There are lots of healthy foods.
Why shaved ice? Ice.
Hey! you.
Weren't you the one who
felt like eating this?
Grandmother,
my manager wasn't good in his studies
when he's young, right?
Look at his face before
you ask me this question.
You must have spent a lot
employing home tutors, huh?
You went to New York also because you couldn't get
into the universities in Korea, right?
Am I right?
With my handsome face,
if I excelled in studies as well.
Don't you think it'd be really unfair?
Right, Grandmother?
Well, that's right.
Both of you aren't Nam Chul
and Nam Sang Nam,
why do you both always stick together
and bicker all day?
Oh, you're talking about the
group which dances,
swaying their bodies here and there, right?
I know that dance.
You even know that?
It's delicious.
It feels so nice.
Grandmother, wait for me.
Wait for a while.
How can a guy look so pretty?
He's quite friendly.
At least he'll not die of hunger.
Why don't I take him in as a brother,
grandmother?
How's the shop doing?
It hasn't collapsed yet,
you're managing it properly?
I've even got an apple business done.
Now I'm planning for our
shop's second promotion.
It'll be a very special one.
I will succeed and prove myself to you.
That's good.
Grandmother.
A hot one, and a cold one...
consume them in turns.
Or else you'll fall sick.
I was taking a cold one in the beginning,
what nonsense are you talking about falling sick.
I'm eating ice now. What for do you want me
to drink something hot?
You just ate some ice just now.
Quickly have a hot drink now.
You child.
Wait a minute.
Eat this and later, drink this...
Ah... it's hot.
Feels nice.
Drink this quick. Quick... quick...
What are you rushing for? It's so hot.
Grandmother, grandmother, grandmother.
Look over here. Look over here.
I'll come over too.
1... 2... 3...
Our darling here is frightened?
We have something to discuss with you.
Relax, relax...
No doubt she's my angel.
Are you playing with me?
I don't know where you guys came from.
But my boyfriend's a
gang boss in this area.
If he finds out that you guys are bullying me,
he'll dig your eyes out and kick
them like a football.
She said he'll kick our eyes like football,
this angel.
Min Yeop has a weird liking.
I'll hand this over to the cops.
You guys are dead.
- Yes, it's the police, right?
- Catch her, catch her.
Hey, grab her phone first.
This is what you called righteousness?
Did you come because of that?
Didn't you come because of the 50,000 won?
Let me do it.
Get off me!
I will kill you guys.
Angel! Angel!
Eun Sae, are you alright?
What should I do now?
You guys are dead.
Min Yeop Oppa.
You jerks!
What's wrong with him today?
Thank you.
His face's messed up.
Enjoy your drink.
I couldn't think of anything
else seeing Eun Sae cry.
You fella, how dare you
abandon your comrades?
I should be the one wearing this.
Why should it be you?
No, you can't wear that.
Eun Sae gave that to me.
Hey, come with me.
What are you doing?
What is it?
Hey!
I've been thinking and I still can't forgive
you for what you've done.
What are you doing?
I want you to write a blood promise.
You jerk.
You really.
You!
If you dare say it out...
be careful I'll sew up your mouth!
My lifespan has decreased
by 100 years just because of you.
I'm sorry, Hyung nim.
I won't betray you from now onwards.
Can you swear on Eun Sae's name?
I swear.
You like Eun Sae that much, huh?
Hey!
I'm just asking because I'm curious.
What do you think of me as a girl?
Eh?
I am a girl.
But others think I'm a guy.
Just that, if I was a girl...
Ah! I'm crazy. I'm crazy.
To have said such things to you.
For me,
if you're a girl, it'll be revolting.
Eh?
Frankly, I can't even differentiate
whether you're a guy or a girl.
And you're not as pretty as Eun Sae.
I don't like girls who are stronger me.
What more can I say to you?
I'm sorry.
My standard's higher.
Each of you choose an instrument of your own.
We're not even a band.
Why do we have to perform?
You always do things your way.
You can handle the stage designs, right?
I can handle those.
But Hyung,
we can't present a stage performance.
What is a stage performance?
Is it a band?
Sun Ki,
you know how to play the guitar, right?
Not on professional basis.
Stop doing unnecessary things already.
You think we can promote the shop
by displaying a performance?
All we have are regular
customers all the time.
Always wasting your time
on meaningless stuff.
Except for Manager Hong,
everyone's in for this.
I will allocate you guys your instruments.
Go back and practice.
Let's promote our shop while it's doing well.
We have to take this opportunity.
The end.
The end, the end...
I don't feel like doing this.
Is it that we can't afford to hire a band?
Let's just use a karaoke set.
Bingo!
[Little Girl]
Not bad.
It's not that easy to play this either.
Well, nothing's easy in this world.
I have to perform my best during the gig,
and make Manager Hong's glasses fall.
You guys still bickering nowadays?
I tolerate him more.
I wonder who he takes after,
such a bad temper.
His mother looks like a nice person.
Of course Auntie's a nice person.
I used to envy Han Kyul's family
when I was young.
They always had home made Kimchee
and pickles prepared for dinner.
The curtains were changed every season.
All of those were interesting,
it made me envious.
Didn't your mother do that too?
My parents were always busy with studies.
So basically I'd spent most of
the time with my nanny.
You felt lonely?
I didn't like being alone.
So I always switched on
the lights night and day.
The music turned on as well.
In the end, I fell in love with music.
But what does a music producer do actually?
Rather than hearing what people say,
follow me.
Listen here.
When will the music play?
Here it comes.
It's amusing.
You really composed this?
It's really amusing.
It's so nice.
Mister, you're really good.
What is it, Mister?
Hello.
I'll call you again tomorrow.
Brother, have you kissed before?
With Customer Number three?
You guys have already kissed?
It's not even something difficult,
why waste time?
We did it last night.
Hyung, how can you simply kiss just like that?
Kissing as if it's a joke,
kissing anybody just like that.
They're more difficult things than kissing...
we can't waste our time on that, right?
You, did you?
You fella, you have a girl already?
Is it somebody I know?
You fella,
save that I was worried that you couldn't...
find one because of your pretty face.
Hyung.
It seems like he has a girl already.
Should we give him some advice?
He doesn't know a thing.
When did I say I have a girl?
Bring her over one day.
We'll have a look.
Right, bring her over.
We'll have a look over this girl.
You really scare me lot nowadays, huh?
I will appear like this more often before I die.
Do you want to be frightened
like this every time?
I'll be a good boy for today.
Besides grandfather, no man has ever let you
pillow his arm, right?
Choi Han Kyul.
Come and have a drink if you're not busy.
Come to the office, starting next week.
You're not young anymore.
Don't waste your time on useless stuff.
The world's not that easy,
that you can do whatever you like.
You don't know what I really want.
Do you know that?
Let's have a drink.
It's the first time you've said this to me.
I was curious to what you'll say to me.
In the end you still chose to tell me off.
I'm leaving.
I vacated a position for you
in the Marketing Team.
I can't drink such strong liquor.
I get drunk with a glass.
Just like what I promised Grandmother,
I will go to New York in three months.
Is playing with toys your dream?
Useless fella.
You were the one who
fathered this useless fella.
You never used to yell at me.
That's something new.
Even if I'd run away from home for 1 month,
or if I'd thrown a temper
refusing to go to university,
or even do something worst than that.
Don't act like a kid asking for attention now.
I had even once wished that
you could slap me on the face!
If you had intended not to care,
then you shouldn't have taken
me in from the beginning.
Why suddenly apply facial mask today?
Something's bothering me.
So what?
Human feelings are so complicated,
like a spider's web.
What's a scissor for?
Just cut it with a scissor.
That's brutal.
Hey!
I work so hard to bring you up.
You don't even buy me
chewing gum to repay me.
And yet you bought Min Yeop
a pair of sunglasses.
I was just letting a bothersome guy
have a taste of sweetness.
Here you go.
Hello?
The whistle woke me up from my dream.
The whistle blowing from my window.
Don't go. Don't dare you go.
It's like a wave of sand...
A person who's lived with a woman before
is indeed different from others.
You can even memorise the poem just like that.
It's my creation.
He's very talented.
Why don't you sing a song?
What should I sing?
Why don't we drink some beer?
Beer?
You're buying?
Aren't you going home?
Don't you plan to sleep?
Why don't you sleep?
Really...
I'll help her fan.
Really.
Why are you so quiet?
What's wrong?
Want me to switch on the TV?
I asked you to come over because
I wanted to hear you ramble.
Why aren't you helping me out?
I'll rant about myself then.
My past might be a bit boring,
but just listen.
You also know how to talk about your past?
It happened during my
2nd year of senior high.
I escaped from class and rushed home secretly.
My Aunt from America making a fuss
grabbing grandmother and my father's hands.
Not only did my mother raise a kid out of
my father's affair with another woman,
she also honored and cleaned
the woman's grave for ten years.
My aunt cried asking,
how can such a thing happen.
You know what I was thinking then?
I had to creep off quietly,
without being discovered.
I kept quiet until this very moment.
But I spilled everything out today.
So...
The mother now is not your biological mother?
She's more like a real mother to me
than my biological mother.
I was afraid I might not be able to cope
if I'd spilled it out, so I just kept quiet.
I regret not keeping it a secret until the end.
Ah...
you are pretending to be drunk again, right?
You always need people
to carry you when you're drunk.
Oh... really!
My life's really difficult.
You're gay, right?
But I'm not.
So stop seducing me.
Who asked you?
To ask me to come over so late at night?
Let's be sworn brothers.
It's not like we're writing
some kind of historical legend.
Have you read that book before?
Do you know the story of Do Won Gyul?
You think you're clever.
Comic books have it as well.
Yoo Bi, Gwan Woo and Jang Bi.
Isn't it all about them?
You're right.
Sworn brothers who are
even closer than real brothers.
So even before they die,
they have no reason to separate.
Call me brother from now on.
Try calling me.
Let' see... we as sworn brothers,
we need an item to prove it.
You have an ear hole?
Why do we need proof?
You're so old-fashioned.
Try calling me brother for once.
Why should I call you brother?
Come here.
Call me brother.
I'm not calling.
Come here.
Let go off me.
Call me brother.
Say that you're happy that
we're sworn brothers now.
Brother!
Just like that,
even if it means being a younger brother,
I still want to stay by his side.
Just like that,
even if it means being an older brother,
I still want to stay by his side.
So we're brothers from now on?
So you'll give me lots of love?
What are you talking about
love between men?
It doesn't matter as long as you're giving it
to somebody you like.
You're telling me it's not a mistake?
Instead, you really like her now?
My wish has finally come true.
What else do you know?
Don't tell mom that I already know about this.
Don't tell her.
I like that fella.
Out of all the people in the world,
why Eun Chan?