THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION,
WHICH IS NOT BASED ON REAL
CHARACTERS OR EVENTS.
He's a hardworking student.
He's well-behaved and has a high level
of academic achievement.
His quiet and calm attitude sets
a good example for others.
He is a model student
who rarely causes any trouble.
Rank one, one, one, and one.
One, one, you're the only one.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You have no demerits or any warnings.
It's almost as if you're invisible.
I have no clue to figure out
what you're like.
Anyway, model students like you are
the most difficult.
Thank you.
It's not a compliment.
You need to make a little trouble
now and then.
Or you'll get into huge trouble later
all at once.
HOMEROOM TEACHER'S ADVICE
1. GET INTO A LITTLE TROUBLE
Are you able to manage your daily life?
I believe I am doing fine.
So, which universities will you apply to?
Just the top three.
Which one, exactly?
Wherever I get in. The best among them.
-And what about your major?
-Anything I get into.
What do you want to do later on?
Anything that makes money.
Wow, your attitude is fucking annoying.
What do you mean?
Forget it.
What do you want to be
when you grow up?
What kind of an adult do you want to be?
Is there anything you want to do?
Don't you have dreams, hopes,
or anything like that?
FIND AND CORRECT THE GRAMMAR MISTAKES
Shit, it's fucking annoying!
Hey, are you kidding me?
-Hey.
-What's wrong?
Take a look, bitch.
-What?
-Are you kidding me?
What's disappeared?
-Give it back.
-What the hell are you talking about?
The gift box that was over there!
You are the one who lost it.
Don't bitch at me.
It's a gift to celebrate 100 days
with Kitae.
-Don't mess with me and give it back.
-I didn't take it!
What the hell is your problem?
Hey!
Maybe it was that bitch.
-What bitch?
-The angel bitch.
That's right. It must've been Netty!
You got Nettied.
You idiot.
-Fuck! Fuck!
-You should've waited until the day.
How could you use such foul language?
-Kitae!
-There, there.
What?
She has lost something.
A gift for you or something.
-Be quiet.
-A gift?
What's the occasion?
-For me?
-"What's the occasion?"
Is it for me?
Hey, did you just ask
what the occasion was?
"What's the occasion," you said?
-"What's the occasion?"
Huh? "What's the occasion?"
Dreams.
Dreams are expensive.
GUARDIAN
They get even more expensive
for a kid without parents.
JUNGJIN OH
You will never be able to buy them,
no matter how hard you try.
Doggo, check messages.
Checking messages.
You have one unread message.
First message.
Help.
Text Mr. Lee.
Not now.
Eat up.
ARE YOU NEARBY? WE HAVE A DIRTBAG.
PLEASE CHECK ON IT.
Take one.
Once again, I'm enlightening someone
who sold humanity to capitalism.
This is the record.
I will give you one last chance
to defend yourself.
How did you end up falling
into this rut of "compensated dating"?
Fuck off, asshole.
Fuck.
Oh, my god!
What the hell?
Don't come closer. What are you?
I'll stab you, huh?
-That wuss.
-I mean it.
I'll do it.
I'll...
-Scissors.
-Sorry?
The blades will get dull.
No...
My scissors!
I said the blades will get dull.
"It was the wind
that raised 80 percent of me
for the last 23 years."
Look, what does that mean?
The wind raised me?
SELF-PORTRAIT BY YUN DONGJU
Does that make sense?
All right, then who's here
with academic tuition the wind paid for?
Hands.
Anyone?
That's right, no one.
Who raises kids, then?
-Parents.
-That's right!
Parents do.
They pay for things and support you.
That's how they raise you, right?
But what does this narrator mean here?
He's saying that the wind raised him.
What could that mean?
Yeah, 15 for her time.
With the bruises, the busted lip,
and emotional distress and all that,
it'll take about two weeks to heal.
How much should we charge
for the hair that was cut off?
Now, look.
The warmth of parents.
How much did he cut?
About two finger-widths?
We request two million won
including compensation.
Two million won?
That's how much I should pay?
He has 23,000 won in cash in his wallet.
He's 1,977,000 won short.
Fuck.
Look.
The family love and the warmth
and tenderness of parents.
The complete lack of these things...
Please search him.
Top, belt.
Bottom, socks.
"Some read a sinner in my eyes.
Some read a fool on my lips.
But I Regret nothing."
BUT I REGRET NOTHING.
"On the morning
that begins to rise brightly,
the dew of poetry
sitting on my forehead..."
In total,
it's 323,000 won.
Thank you.
He's 1,677,000 won short.
-Client.
-Yes?
Not you.
There is a default
in payment of 1,677,000 won
for the injury suffered
during the course of business.
-A or B.
-B
If you choose option B,
you may incur a loss--
B! You motherfucker!
-Babe.
-Yes?
-Open your mouth.
-What?
Open it!
Open. There you go.
Okay.
Option B shall be executed.
Mr. Lee, keep it up. Thank you.
What does that mean?
It means you'll get beaten up.
Just enough to pay for 1,677,000 won.
A MESSAGE FROM MUSCLEMAN
MUSCLEMAN: HI
MUSCLEMAN: COMPENSATED DATING POSSIBLE?
BLUE FLAVOR: YES
MUSCLEMAN: SEND ME YOUR PICTURE
MINJU HAS REQUESTED HELP FROM DOGGO
MUSCLEMAN: HOW MUCH?
BLUE FLAVOR: 300,000 WON
Mr. Lee.
Here.
My dream is to graduate.
Go to college, get a job.
Have kids, raise kids.
Live a normal life and...
die in a normal way.
BROKERAGE FEE 350,000 WON COLLECTED
NO INCIDENT. TODAY'S WORK COMPLETE.
GOOD JOB, THANK YOU
The money I need for that...
is 90 million won.
That's the price
of my dream.
A rabbit came down from heaven and said...
Kang Bbang!
Hey.
You punk, shit.
Dominus is here,
but you're having a siesta?
Are you nuts?
Sorry, I didn't know you were here.
You little shit.
Kang Bbang, did you miss me?
Y-Yes, Dominus.
Kang Bbang, whom do you like best,
your mom, your dad,
or Kitae?
Kitae.
Let's play ball.
Let's play.
Dunk!
Pass!
Hey!
Gyuri never passes! Seriously!
Oh, shit. I missed.
Dunk!
Hey, get back up. Let's continue.
Hey, Gyoungsik. Let's go.
-Pass.
-Three!
Are you okay? Shit. I'm so sorry.
Hey, Kitae hit his noggin.
-Hey, what's your name?
-No, I'm fine.
-I'm really sorry.
-I said I'm fine.
Hey, Jisoo.
Mr. Cho wants to see you.
COUNSELING OFFICE
Do you think... there would be a wacko
who forges his parent's signature
on a report card with top grades?
Well, I have no idea.
You punk.
What a weirdo.
Hey. Do you want to join my club?
What club?
Social Issues Research Club
BEST CLUB IN KYEWANG HIGH:
SOCIAL ISSUES RESEARCH
HEY! JOIN THE CLUB!
Doesn't it look super fun?
What do you do in the club?
We study old-minded people like you.
Say it sounds fun.
It sounds boring.
You are being salty.
You are definitely
a subject worth studying.
-I won't join.
-Why not?
I'm not that interested
in social issues or anything.
You are just 18 years old
and uninterested in everything?
Then, what are you interested in?
Hey.
Are you an amphibian or what?
Why are you always drenched?
-Here's what you asked for.
-Give it to me.
Where did you get this?
Here and there.
Can I go?
You're citing foreign sources.
Did you translate it all?
You must be busy.
Baeggyul. Stop right there.
You'll come later
to revise the questionnaire, right?
Am I really supposed to do that too?
Of course, you are.
You're the only one in this club.
Why did you join then?
I did it to beef up
my extracurricular activities.
I thought it was a fake club.
You lazy punk.
The smart ones are worse, I tell you.
Hey, Baeggyul.
It must be hard doing this alone.
Sorry?
Here.
Your assistant.
What?
Come right away after school, okay?
Yeah...
The more I think about it,
the more pissed off I get.
-Minju.
-Yes?
Look at this.
It's what I told you about.
What is it?
This is it. Isn't it pretty?
This cost 320,000 won?
Someone stole this?
You're both insane.
The bastard who receives
such an expensive gift,
and the high school bitch
who spends that much money on a guy.
Hey, don't be so mean.
So? When is your 100-day anniversary?
Next week.
What's this?
Wait, what happened now?
The quantity went down by one.
What am I going to do?
What do I tell Kitae?
Cheer up.
Hey, your hair.
I've had a fucking stressful day.
Aren't you guys hot?
Hey, your hair...
You said you'd rather die
than get your hair cut. Oh, my...
Is it fucking ugly?
It's fucking pretty.
-I love you.
-Me too.
Jiye.
Add a number to the blacklist.
Say it.
I shared it in the group chat room.
ANOTHER DIRTBAG.
That asshole. Why did he have to cut
my bangs? That son of a bitch.
Shit, he cut your hair?
It must be a fetish or something.
What? Is he a psycho?
What was Mr. Lee doing?
That old man was fucking late.
It's so fucking annoying.
Whatever.
I feel like crap. Let's call it a day.
-Let's go out. It's on me!
-Really?
-What's that?
-Where did you get this money?
Did you get settlement money?
I did. I got fucking lots.
Hey, it was fucking hilarious.
I took option B, and asked Mr. Lee
to beat the crap out of that asshole.
He got his ass whooped begging me
to let him go then rushed out.
He withdrew a shitload of cash.
Talk about profit.
Shit, awesome. Uncle's really useful.
-I give him credit.
-Me too.
By the way,
I wonder what Uncle looks like.
How old do you think he is?
Well...
-He may be a fucking fat and ugly geek.
-I hate those types.
Hey. Why is she so down in the dumps?
She has no fucking energy at all.
She needs to eat meat.
Meat sounds good.
Let's go.
-Yes!
-What are you gonna wear?
-Should I wear this?
-Excited!
-What are you gonna wear?
-Hurry up!
Hang on. Let me change first!
Seriously...
I can't go out dressed like this.
Come on!
SOCIAL ISSUES RESEARCH CLUB
Okay, next old fogy question.
Question 14.
"What should the school do regarding
homosexual students at the school?"
How's it relevant?
It's totally related.
Why should the school do anything
about students' sexuality?
Homosexuality isn't a crime.
I give you props.
-Let's take that one off the list.
-Mr. Cho.
Stop using slang.
It sounds awkward when you say it.
No. I'll keep using it.
-Next.
-Hold on.
Jisoo...
Jeez, he must have never had
seasoned fries.
You dumb hick.
I'm feeding you only fast food
until you learn
how to eat seasoned fries properly.
Question 18.
"I've seen or heard about prostitution
occurring around me."
What about it?
Likewise, It's none
of the school's business.
What? This is definitely something
the school should care about.
Sex workers' rights is
a controversial issue that never ends.
"It's a legitimate labor
of providing a service."
"No, it isn't. It is unethical."
Blah Blah Blah.
Isn't this going too far
by ignoring the dispute?
You're taking it too far. The dispute
and the law are different things.
Regardless, prostitution is a crime
according to the current laws.
Plus, this is about minors.
It's the police that should handle
a legal matter, not the school.
Sure, if the school is only
supposed to teach kids academics.
That's actually how it is now, isn't it?
Wow, look how this kid talks
in front of her teacher.
Jisoo, don't you have any input on this?
You must have thoughts and ideas too.
I really want to know.
I think the person will be ostracized.
If someone says
they saw the prostitution scene,
and her name is revealed,
she won't be able to keep going to school.
It's not about right or wrong,
but about consideration
for the person involved?
You're surprisingly thoughtful, Jisoo.
Actually, what Jisoo said is
exactly what I want from you guys.
Are these questions really based
on proper respect for the students
at this school?
If not, fix it
from the student's perspective.
We'll work on it this weekend.
-What do you say?
-What?
Do you have time this weekend?
Me?
Leave the house and do other stuff.
At least on the weekends.
GYURI BAE
HALF-ASSED LIFE
I can do the questionnaire myself.
Don't bother if you're busy.
JOB REQUEST, MINHEE
ACCEPT, DECLINE
I can help...
If you need my help...
No, it's fine.
Let me help.
What should I do?
SECOND-HAND MARKETPLACE
Tomorrow at one o'clock?
One o'clock at Famous Lamb.
Hello?
Urgent notice.
We will be closed tomorrow.
We will not accept
coordination or protection requests.
Confirmed.
In the meantime, repair your phone.
Okay, will do.
Mr. Lee.
Yes?
Thank you always.
What?
Enjoy your day off.
Ha, ha, ha.
Shit, it doesn't open!
Fix this shit!
Damn it.
When are we supposed to work,
if not on weekends?
He does whatever he wants.
What the fuck! I can't stand this shit.
What is it?
What?
A discount for the day off.
Ha! What the fuck?
Old Man.
Can't you work with just me
over the weekend?
I won't tell the girls.
I'll pay you more.
-Your foot.
-Shit.
Please? I'm begging you.
I'm going to die.
I'm going to meet some psycho
and get slashed to death.
You'll regret it then, Old Man. I mean it!
Where are you going? Old Man!
Old Man! I'm really going to die!
Old Man!
Hey!
Hi.
DATING EXPENSES FOR HIGH SCHOOL COUPLES
HOW MUCH DO HIGH SCHOOL COUPLES
SPEND ON A DATE?
DATING EXPERIENCE OF A HIGHSCHOOLER
FAMOUS LAMB RECOMMENDED MENU
DOUBLE SHOT ESPRESSO
Three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten.
Hundred thousand won.
Eleven, twelve...
Hey!
Why are you here so early?
Hi.
Can we go inside?
-Thank you.
Let me know when you're ready to order.
I'll have a double shot espresso, please.
Espressos have just the shot
without any water. Is that okay?
A double shot espresso and...
Iced royal milk tea
in regular size, please.
-So, that's two in total, correct?
-Yes.
I'll pay.
Sure.
A strawberry and whipped cream cake too.
That will be 20,500 won.
Hey, look. Gyuri.
It's my mom.
I'll be right back.
-It's your first time at a cafe, right?
-Yes. I mean, no.
-Yes.
-Are you saying it is or isn't?
Let's finish this quickly.
-Where were we?
-What about your mom?
What?
Is she well?
-Yes, she is. Is your mom well?
-I don't know. She left me.
Why is this so funny to me?
You're fucking random.
What the heck?
Wasn't it meant to be a joke?
Did I just put my foot in my mouth?
No, it's okay. Just don't tell anyone.
What about your dad?
Are they both gone?
Do you live alone, then?
Since when?
Since the end of ninth grade.
Wait, that was when we were
in the same class.
But no one knows you live alone?
Even Mr. Cho?
Will it get annoying if people find out?
Unbelievable.
-How are you alive?
-What?
It takes money to stay alive.
How do you pay rent?
How'd you pay
for your uniform and stuff?
Well...
I work part-time.
What do you do?
Just this and that.
"This and that"?
-A male escort or something?
-What?
I was just kidding.
With that face? No way.
Actually...
With a little work...
You might not be so bad.
Anyway, you are so fucking commendable.
Commendable?
You've been through hell
for a year and half
without your parents.
But are you okay telling me these things?
Hey, what's wrong?
Why are you crying out of the blue?
Are you bipolar?
It's just that no one's ever told me
those things before.
You can sit there and relax.
-Babe.
-Yes?
How old are you?
How old do I look?
What do you think?
You look good in glasses.
I hear that often.
You're hurt.
Yes, a little.
Take off your bag.
Oh, I like having it on.
I'll go wash up first.
Yeah, shall we wash together?
-No, rest here.
-Okay.
-Wash up.
Call the old man.
Go on.
That fucking old man.
Um, I need to use the restroom.
Doggo, check messages.
I could not understand. Bad Doggo.
REQUEST FOR HELP
MINHEE'S CURRENT LOCATION
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message after the tone.
You will be charged after the connection.
MINHEE
The old man isn't showing up.
Goodness. There, there.
The person you have called is
not available.
All right.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Uncle isn't answering either.
Why isn't he answering?
You sons of bitches.
You scumbags.
Hey!
Oh, so scared!
No, I won't hurt you.
Okay, isn't there anyone else
you can call?
No. Okay, all right.
Anyone?
Damn it!
This isn't what I expected.
Uncle.
Uncle, I know you're off today,
and I know
you have nothing to do with this,
but...
you'll come get me, right?
You won't abandon me, right?
You have no more unread messages.
Why aren't they coming? Why!
-Why aren't they?
-Stop it, for fuck's sake!
-Thank you.
-I need one of these. Hurry up.
Those are all the batteries that we have.
-It's not there?
-Shit!
Listen carefully.
I have to find that old man from before.
That bastard.
That bastard who beats people up!
He needs to get beat up just as much.
That's only fair, right?
Right?
Shit!
-You asshole!
-Your nose!
Stay still.
Why are you bitching about that to me?
Are you okay?
What do you want me to do?
Fuck!
Mister, what are you doing there?
You can't make a mess here. Please leave.
Mister!
Jeez, am I talking to myself here?
Hey! Oh, my god!
Mister, here's your change.
I'm calling the cops.
Stay still, okay?
You bitch.
-It's him!
-Shit, come on.
It's him!
Client.
Are you all right?
This is it! That robotic voice!
Let me confirm your current location.
Are you at W2 Motel, Room 805?
I will now give you instructions
regarding how to exit the premises,
bypassing the elevator.
One, exit the room through the door.
Two, turn right.
Three, make a left at the end of the hall.
Four, descend the emergency staircase.
Five, take the back door
to the parking lot.
And six, exit. That's all.
-What is he talking about?
-Beats me.
The police will enter shortly
using the elevator. Please be careful.
Police? You said they can't call the cops.
What do we do?
Hey! This is all bullshit, okay?
Think about it.
If the cops come, she'll be arrested too.
Then, they're all screwed.
Am I right?
You can't call the cops.
Look out the window in 15 seconds.
Shit.
Hey, police... We're screwed.
Come on, let's get out. Hurry!
-Where are you going?
-Hurry!
-Come on!
What is it...
Shit!
How may I help you?
Excuse me.
Fuck!
Fuck...
You know what happens if you talk, right?
Shit!
Excuse me.
Sir? Please open the door.
-What is it?
-Hello.
May we check your room briefly?
Well... Why?
Well... we received a tip
about prostitution of a minor.
What? What are you talking about...
It won't take long.
No, that's not...
-Well, I...
-Excuse us, sir.
That's not what...
Jeez.
-We'd appreciate your cooperation.
-That's not it, seriously.
Excuse us.
Gosh...
You see? I told you that's not it.
-Gosh.
-I told you we shouldn't do this.
What are you talking about?
You said you'll do it.
Let me see your ID, sir.
Why would I have my ID right now?
Excuse me.
Are you looking for this?
"It was the wind
that raised 80 percent of me.
The more I see the world,
the more shameful it is."
When you read
Seo Jungju's Self Portrait,
you can see his sense of linguistics.
His poetic language shows
how the Korean language maximizes
the potential of linguistic expression.
GYURI
I'M REALLY SORRY
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED EARLIER TODAY
SOMETHING REALLY URGENT CAME...
KYEWANG HIGH SCHOOL COMMUNITY
WOULD YOU LIKE TO POST THIS?
Well, what brings you here...
Have fun.
Shit.
Damn it.
OJI
SORRY
HELLO, I SAW YOUR POSTING ONLINE.
IS IT SOLD ALREADY?
WHICH ONE?
400,000 WON
INCLUDING SHIPPING FEE
IF YOU NEED HELP, REACH OUT TO A PARENT,
A FRIEND, A SCHOOL COUNSELOR
OR AN ADULT YOU TRUST,
OR CALL A LOCAL HELPLINE.