(Tomoyuki)《Harumi, you are with me
Were you happy? 》
(chee)< here
An elementary school that closed several years ago
built and renovated
A certain hotel>
< オープンを間近に控えた現在は
Former elementary school graduates
Invite those involved
As a pre-opening period
I am struggling >
Ah, that...
The invitation is
It was for my wife...
(chee)
Ah, Mr. Kitamura. I understand.
By booking a single room for 2 nights
yes
Well then
Please fill in here
yes
Ah, before
I work at a police box near here.
When this was an elementary school
I also had a little involvement.
Ah, that's right
Yeah
Is it crime prevention training?
…Yeah
As expected, the teacher held it
to apprehend suspicious persons
They do it with a lot of force.
It was also my elementary school.
Actually, what is my wife?
That's how we met...
``Actually, I'll do it myself.''
it's okay"
(Harumi)《Okay.
Please sit down.》
《No, sorry》
《I'm kind of excited》
《I think it’s good to be enthusiastic about work》
"…thank you"
《Go! 》
《Hehe, it hurts, isn't it?》
"yes"
《Let's do our best together》
"picture? 》
《In the sense of protecting children
I am the same》
《Ah ah!
That's right, let's do our best》
《Although it is difficult for both of us》
"yes"
《Yes, that's fine》
"thank you"
《Ah, that's right
Um... If you like, this is it.
From the policeman's pocket
chocolate"
《When you're tired
This is the best》
"thank you"
《Yes, sweet》
♬〜
"yeah! 》
《Ah… no?》
"picture? 》
《In this season
A white-eye comes to that tree over there.
From here
I can see it flying.
《Hey, white-eye...》
(Sound of lights being turned on)
(Taiki) Where did you go?
Yay!
Good job
Oh, you can't be serious.
Um... is this it?
No, that's it!
thank you!
This is my favorite
It would have been terrible if it disappeared.
thank you!
(Taiki) No, I was saved.
(Sound of bag falling)
Wow!
Wow, what a terrible thing to do...
Ah, it's okay
kind
Ah, no...
No, I'm sorry
Now, Mr. Yome, go somewhere.
I'll be waiting here.
Where have you been...
Oh, are you sure? that~
Do you want to invite people from the same elementary school?
…Yeah well
Ah, then you're Yome's senior?
Great senior!
Ah, no, I'm not...
picture? Oh, is it your favorite?
…I agree
Ah, then you're the same as me, aren't you?
No, it's like this
I'm glad I can't stay the night.
Is there a difference in tension?
Hmm, what do you think...
(baby crying)
oh thank you
Well, in the first place
Ever since we had a child
I feel like my tension has been constantly slipping away.
It's already dangerous though
After all, I can have a child.
It's going to change, right?
We don't have any children.
Ah, that's right.
But that's better
I feel like the couple has always been good friends.
I understand too
Isn't it deep?
...Just because we're a couple
It doesn't necessarily mean that we will understand each other.
Ah ah...
Sorry, I said something strange.
Ah, no, nothing special...
There's something wrong with this one...
(baby crying)
Oh sorry sorry sorry
So...
(Taiki) Is it hot?
Goodbye, teacher!
Goodbye!
Yes, be careful and goodbye
《I want children after all》
《What about Tomo-kun? 》
《I want it》
《How many people do you want? 》
《Eh~ One person or 10 people》
《10… 10 people is a bit~》
"picture~"
《10 people》
"Yeah"
《Harumi
You live alone with me
I wonder if he was happy...》
《Your last words over and over again
I remember it》
《Let's meet in the next life...》
"Because I was an only child..."
《What you seek is
Only in the next life》
``I've always had those feelings for you''
I think he was letting it happen...》
《It's now too late
That's all I'm thinking about...》
《The site of Asahi Elementary School
It is said that it will become a hotel》
《Hotel? 》
"Yeah"
《Completion is said to be two years away.》
《Let's go together if possible》
《Is there anything you need? 》
♬〜
《There is
There are lots of memories》
"Yeah? 》
《This is the first school I worked at》
"Yeah"
《I was present at the closing of the school》
"Yeah? 》
"Yeah? Yeah? 》
《Ah hehehe...》
《My life has changed too》
"Yeah! Haha…》
《It also taught me how to be strict.》
《The student's parents yelled at me.
"For you who don't have children
What do I know?''
《That was frustrating》
``But you said it back, right? 》
“Every day, we see the faces of hundreds of children.
Only I can see
There are things I don't understand.''
《A little commotion
But it happened》
♬〜
"sandwich~"
《Yay, it’s a sandwich》
"happy"
《I also made some side dishes》
《I went anyway.
picnic! 》
《Tomo-kun is busy.
Because I couldn't go anywhere else.
《No, sorry...》
《Hehehehe》
《Ugh
I really like Picnic》
《But there will be many more from now on.
Go to various places》
``I was also assigned to the police department.
I can make more time than before.
《Harumi? 》
《…That was fun~》
"what? 》
《Crime prevention training
After we became a couple》
《Ah... why? 》
《The two of us will meet at school.
Prepare in advance》
"It's like two people in a secret"
I was so excited》
《Is it okay to go on a date like that? 》
《Dating...》
《No, it's a date》
《Because I don't have any children》
《What we do together is
It's all a date》
《…Yeah》
"yeah? 》
《It's nothing...》
♬〜
《Way Mama, I'm falling!
《Wow, could you please stop?
(baby crying)
(Taiki) Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
(Miya) I'm sorry.
Look, I cried!
Ah that person
(Taiki) Look, we talked at night.
(Miya) Ah
(Taiki) Huh?
(baby crying)
I went
sorry
(baby crying)
Sorry!
《Harumi…
Were you happy with me? 》
"I will be with you until the end"
I couldn't do anything for you.
《I want to talk more with you...》
《Something like that
I can't believe I can't...》
(Miya) I'm sorry.
Ah… not now!
Oh no... um...
Sorry, what is it?
that…
It's Kitamura-san, right?
Harumi Sensei's husband
…picture?
Crime prevention training
ah…
on second thoughts?
Is Harumi-sensei coming too?
My wife... can't come...
Are you in danger of divorce?
Please excuse me
To Mr. Harumi
Please don't make me feel bad
It's this way
Ah, it's forbidden to enter here...
Ah, it's okay
(sound of window opening)
About now, it's that tree over there.
A white-eye is coming
When I was in elementary school here
It was a health room.
yesterday
The first thing I looked for when I came to stay was
I was a regular at the nurse's office.
At first, when it came time for math
I feel sick
I couldn't enter the classroom
Then it got worse and worse...
What I am now is
It's because Harumi-sensei was there.
《I feel dizzy...》
"Are you okay? 》
(Miya) Really
Just came to school
I mean, just thinking about it
I just feel bad
Something disappeared and I
all day long
It's like I'm holding back my tears
《I see~ That’s painful.》
"Yeah"
《Hmm, other than school? 》
《Favorite time etc.
Is there anything fun? 》
《Teacher, please go home.
I took a breath and said, “Phew!”
While eating dinner》
(Miya)《When I wake up in the morning
When the sky was bright blue with no clouds...
《Yeah yeah》
《My cat Chacha
When it got on my stomach...》
《Ah, wonderful! 》
《Try to remember more
My favorite time》
《For me...
I'll time it for your return
walking together
Even the picnic I never got tired of
About you...》
《That's good!
There are so many! 》
《That kind of thing
Keep it full in your chest
You can feel happy》
《What’s even more wonderful?
To Miya-chan
Someday I'll share that happiness with you
What the other person can do》
《To each other
You can increase it rapidly》
《Now the teacher is Miya-chan.
I'll share it with you》
《Hey》
"Yeah? 》
《Teacher too
Are you sharing your happiness? 》
"of course! 》
《Like this》
♬〜
《I'm going to make a proposal to the school next time.
I think so》
"Yeah"
《To the children
How many accidents happen around us...》
《And then like this》
"yeah? 》
《It's nothing...》
《Be with this person
I feel so happy》
Stay with Tomo-kun
I was happy
I feel it
(Miya) Um...
Maybe Mr. Harumi...
(Taiki) Ah, I knew it was here!
Ah, once upon a time, Miya
It seems like you were taking care of me...
Yeah…
About my wife...
I was asked...
(sobs)
(baby crying)
Hmm...
thank you…
《Tomo-kun...》
"you know what…"
"Yeah? 》
"lie…"
《In the next life...
Let's meet...》
♬〜
(big tree)
Hoi hoi hoi hoi
yeah? ah
I always carry this with me
ah…
please
Are you okay now?
Yeah it's okay
Ah yes
How about we have a barbecue together tonight?
It's lonely being alone
Just a word...
I'm sure you'll get lonely by yourself
If you don't mind
of course! Please come and see us!
See you at the barbecue area at 6 o'clock!
I'll bother you
I'm looking forward to it later.
Also
♬〜
♬〜Yeah
(White-eye cry)
(Sasaki) 2 years
i'm going to london
Leaving Miku behind after making me wait for so many years
(Nino) This is what love tastes like
I learned this for the first time
(Miku) Congratulations to London
(Nagisa) My feelings are
It hasn't changed since before
(Nino)
I don't like not being able to do anything