[English subtitles are available]
[Fall in Love with a Scientist]
[Episode 20]
Just go.
Go back to the lab.
What was it?
It's about you.
Impossible.
The headmaster asked you
to stay just because of me?
Yes.
We just
talked about your topic.
He said the Chinese Academy of Sciences
has a focus set
for central ion beams.
They usually don't lend it.
But he can try to apply for it
for us.
Really?
Really.
Why would I lie to you?
Oh,
you scared me at the
meeting just now.
I've never seen anyone
talk to Headmaster Li like that.
Even you?
Of course I dare not.
I'm awesome.
No.
The point is
he can't find anything wrong with my topic.
But why did he
discuss with you
about my topic
instead of Mr. Jiang?
Because I'm a genius.
A genius needs me
to save his life?
So you are the life savior
of a genius.
[Huaihai Biology Laboratory]
Tomorrow is a day off for everyone.
So come to my house and have dinner tonight.
Let's celebrate.
Celebrate what?
The success of the
clinical trial of course.
No.
It's early for that.
So what else is worth celebrating?
I guess it's a celebration of
two colleagues in our lab
being together.
You know me.
OK.
We should go now.
Restrain yourself.
Well.
Yang Lanhang intended to
make Zhai Qingyi and other guys
buy these things.
But I'm worried.
I guess that kid
can't even tell shallots
from garlics.
I don't trust him.
Is Lanhang not worried
about your driving skills?
Whoa.
What about my driving skills?
He said I'm a good driver.
Good. Good.
But he didn't know
that I'd drive today.
I stole his car key.
It's addictive.
What happened?
My impression on you two
still stopped at
when she called you an eggplant.
Aren't you always
incompatible as fire and water?
It started to get better
just in recent months.
Why are you together
all of a sudden?
Yes.
I still remember that
they didn't even friend each other on WeChat
before the clinical trial.
Right.
Is this the sequela
of the clinical trial?
Impossible.
He replaced the heart valves,
not the brain.
Guru,
whatever decision you make,
you have my support.
Yes.
I know you two
have so many questions,
so let's finish this once and for all.
OK?
Go on, ask me.
Come on.
Were you
with Li Feifei?
Did she dump you
or did you dump her?
That female star.
We had a meal together.
Bai was there too.
That's quite a scene.
Really? So Cruel?
What scene?
There was nothing
between me and Li Feifei.
Guru,
this is wrong.
How can you
have a vague attitude
when we talk about the female star?
You have to make it clear.
No.
I... I never
had anything to do with her
We're back.
Don't say anything stupid
to Lingling's face.
Do you hear me?
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Why are you sitting there?
Is the TV show so interesting?
Come here and help us.
Help. Help. Help.
Help. Help.
Help.
I've read the contract.
There is no problem.
I have signed it and sent it.
[Transfer from Guan Xiaoyu]
You don't need to
give me so much money.
Don't think too much.
This is for redeeming
my Mini Watermelon and Starlet bags.
Fine.
I'll deliver them to you soon.
So this means I can see her
every time she
redeems a bag.
This must be my reward as I'm such a good man.
Did you miss me?
Miss me? Miss me?
Relax.
They look exactly the same
as the way they were when you gave them to me.
My dear Mini Watermelon,
why are you deflated?
Don't try to blackmail me.
I didn't even touch it.
It must be you.
You put them in the trunk
and they couldn't get fresh air.
It's alright.
Mom is back.
Come on. Get in.
Poor thing.
Considering you helped me
cope with an emergency,
I will let it slide.
Just go.
I'm not leaving.
I'm warning you.
Don't try to stay.
You think I want to
stay here?
I can't go back.
Hang said their lab
has an after-class academic
seminar at home.
If I go back now,
I will not only interrupt them,
but also hinder the progress
of the society and mankind.
I can't do that.
Let's watch a movie.
Do you like horror movies?
Take it easy.
Careful.
Here.
Careful. Careful.
I know Lanhang is good at cooking.
I didn't expect Lingling
to be a good cook.
Here.
I think they say you'd better
find someone who is complementary to yourself.
You are outdated.
Who said they have to be complementary?
Kid, you first.
Why?
It seems Bai really considers
herself as the hostess.
What are you talking about?
Do you believe I and Yang Lanhang
will double kill you?
Choose your words carefully.
Here, Jing.
Come on. Sorry.
Let's celebrate and
hope you can double kill.
And let's hope everyone
can find the loved one.
Every Jack has his Jill.
-Cheers. Cheers.
-Great.
Cheers.
Cheers. Cheers.
Don't drink too much.
Come on.
Have some dishes.
They taste better when they are warm.
Come on.
I think this fish is nice.
I'll have some.
Go ahead.
Here, shrimp paste.
I specially made it for you.
Thanks.
You have some.
You too.
Bai,
the fish you made
tastes like take-out.
Put down your chopsticks. Stop eating.
Here.
Just put there.
Come here.
Help me with my sleeve.
Thank you.
I invited you guys,
but you bought the food ingredients
and you cooked the meal.
And now you are washing dishes.
You are my girlfriend,
not here to do things for me.
What are you thinking about?
I just think
you don't feel well recently,
and I want you to get more rest.
Just wait.
When you recover,
I'll let you know
who is the real boss.
Really?
OK. Then...
I'll keep you company.
I'm really happy today.
There have never been
so many people in the house.
Every dish you made
is also delicious.
And I like them.
Although I always said I'm a genius,
I just
said it casually.
I don't make as much money as my mom.
I'm not as good as my father
in scientific research achievements.
I'm not the best
among the peers.
But fortunately,
my eyes are sharp,
finding you to be my girlfriend.
One and only, and the best.
I'm flattered.
I'm not as good as you said.
Alright. Alright.
Don't wash it.
You are almost breaking the cup.
Come.
I think I can't
let my girlfriend
do housework anymore.
Because it will waste too much water.
Wait.
You tell me honestly.
Did you Google
romantic words?
You just reminded me
that you confessed
your feelings to me.
That's the shame of my life.
Don't mention it again, OK?
No.
At least I want to
do what I wanted
to do.
Will you let me wash dishes or not?
There are so many to be washed.
You just go out first, out.
Don't wash them.
It's getting late. You...
You should stay.
Wait. Stay?
Am I
sleeping here today?
Ouyang and Guan Xiaoyu
are in your house now.
So I'm thinking,
should we give them
a chance?
Don't wash them.
I will
wash them later.
[So that's what it is, Qianchuan.]
Oh man.
I've watched
this movie for three times.
I'm immune, OK?
I...
Am I not allowed to be scared?
Why did you want to watch
a horror movie if you are scared?
Am I not qualified to
watch a horror movie for being scared?
Don't you know that
the more one is scared,
the more he wants to watch a horror movie?
Why don't you just go back to watch it
by yourself if you are scared?
I can't go back,
because Bai Lingling hasn't come back yet.
Does it matter
if she comes back
or not?
If she doesn't come back,
that means she is at my home.
Why should I go back?
They are in love,
and I just stand there applauding?
Fine.
Watch the movie by yourself.
I need to go to my room and sleep.
I can't help falling asleep.
Don't. Don't. Don't
I... I...
I'm scared.
I'm the first party in our contract.
Don't leave me alone.
I let you stay here
to watch the horror movie
just because you are the first party.
Let me go.
Keep quiet.
Open... Open the door.
Hurry. Open it.
I'm so scared. Oh God.
Open... Open the door.
Hurry.
He asked me to stay overnight. What should I do?
What should I do
when I go out?
Be a man.
Got it.
[Hang]
Hang,
you slept on the sofa, too?
How about my coming back at once?
Let's jump into the bed
to get some more sleep?
Which do you think
is better?
Dating on a yacht?
Anyway I have
a yacht license.
Or seaside resort?
I think this is also good.
But...
I let you sleep on the bed,
so can you answer
my questions seriously?
You didn't sleep all night.
Aren't you sleepy?
I didn't sleep
last night,
because I was thinking
about this thing.
We've been together
for almost six months.
It's not right to stay in the lab
every day, right?
So I'm thinking
how we can date
like other
normal lovebirds.
Normal lovebirds
often eat, go shopping,
and watch movies during their date.
Isn't it exaggerated that you
get her on a yacht in the beginning?
Eating, shopping,
and watching movies
are too normal, right?
Then make
them innovative.
Take your time.
You can do it.
How?
What am I supposed to do?
Li Feifei finally
became the endorser
of Qingyu Manor.
Look.
[Li Feifei announced as the endorser of Qingyu Manor at a press conference.]
Even though she has so many fans,
she is also
attracted by guru.
I have to admit
that guru is really good.
A popular
and beautiful girl likes him,
and he has managed to
resist the temptations.
Right, Zhang?
There is a press conference today,
and we sort of know each other.
I must show my support.
Right. You should.
I'm not familiar with her.
You know that.
I... I just met her once.
Don't be nervous.
I'm not a mean person.
Go ahead. Look.
Look. Look.
Go ahead.
Let's go on with our chat.
Free on the weekend?
Do you want to go to the Happy Valley?
Sure.
You must be occupied.
ou need to show your support.
Bai,
Li Feifei has bad intentions.
She won't give up on guru.
You should be careful.
Don't worry.
He can't escape.
Is she too confident?
I can hear you.
Eat. Eat. Eat.
Li Feifei.
[Endorser of Qingyu Manor Li Feifei
Many tasks with big prizes are waiting for you.]
Li Feifei, I love you.
Li Feifei.
She is so beautiful.
Miss Li.
Wait. Wait.
What's the problem?
Well,
I... I am an assistant engineer
[Qingyu Manor Employee's Card]
of Qingyu Manor.
I'm also a fan of Miss Li.
Can we take a picture together?
It's inconvenient.
It's OK.
Let's take a picture here.
Me, too. Me, too.
Me, too.
Me, too. Li Feifei.
Do you know Yang Lanhang?
This is the destination?
Yes.
How do you think?
Do you like this place?
How did you find
this place?
It's beautiful.
Right?
♫ Monday ♫
♫ With a T-shirt in white ♫
♫ Tuesday ♫
♫ Keeping spin ♫
♫ In my mind ♫
♫ You made me feel like ♫
♫ Dancing in highway ♫
♫ Unhappiness goes away ♫
♫ The red, yellow, green and purple ♫
♫ All colors in my dreamland ♫
♫ Tennis, baseball and swimming pool ♫
♫ We'll ♫
♫ Play them together ♫
♫ I'm here ♫
♫ And I will stay ♫
♫ Can you hear ♫
♫ My heartbeat loud? ♫
♫ Like a rainbow ♫
♫ Follow the rain and storm ♫
♫ Sunny day never go ♫
♫ Who can be your Van Gogh? ♫
♫ Who can play ♫
♫ The music you favor? ♫
♫ So right ♫
♫ The smile I like ♫
♫ Sleepless through the night ♫
♫ I'm here ♫
♫ And I will stay ♫
♫ Can you hear ♫
♫ My heartbeat loud? ♫
♫ Like a rabbit ♫
♫ Passing by your window ♫
♫ Is another way ♫
♫ To hello ♫
♫ I'm here, and I will pray ♫
♫ Can you feel it in my way? ♫
♫ Like a rainbow ♫
♫ Follow the rain and storm ♫
♫ Sunny day never go ♫
Look at the photo.
What's this?
Which one?
What?
Let me see.
Look at your face.
It's not in the right shape.
Don't look at it.
Alright. I will stop.
The battery is dying. I will stop.
I will
develop the photos,
make an album
and give it to you as a gift.
Well, thank you.
You are welcome.
Don't you think the maze just now
is hard?
The maze just now
is quite simple.
I just walk out of it without any effort.
Could it be called a maze?
I'm just chatting with you.
Do you really think I think
the maze is hard?
I'm quite smart, OK?
Well,
don't be that serious.
We scientists
are just serious and accurate,
right?
The situation is like this.
What about your side?
How's the clinical trial going?
Combining the visiting record
of our center
and other four centers
of the recent months,
everything goes well.
However, we still need to be alert.
The entire degradation of the valve
in the following months
is essentail.
When the observation period
of one year is over,
we can hand in
the clinical trial report.
OK.
I will prepare
manufacturing lines
according to your current process,
and will adjust it
with your experimental results anytime.
You didn't sleep for the whole night again?
You are transferring from one side to another.
It's so tiring.
Would you like to tell the truth to your father?
I don't have
any credit from my dad.
If he knows that
I have a company outside
and is producing
some promising
yet not-knowing-when-to-come-to-the-market
material for hospital.
Do you think it persuasive?
Not really.
Right.
So, I won't say it.
It's what I deserve
for being too comfortable in the past two years.
Right,
today is Yang Lanhang's birthday.
Do you know it?
Yes.
Our Hang
is one year older now.
He didn't have formal birthdays
as he was abroad in the past years.
Now that he is back,
I think we should
show some warmth to him.
I will book a restaurant tonight.
Let's have dinner together.
No.
He doesn't need your warmth.
Alright.
Other processes should catch up.
Mine is almost done.
The rest will leave
to the girlfriend of my brother.
Your brother has a girlfriend, too?
He has one for a long time.
It's Cui Jing in his lab.
Did he tell you that?
He doesn't
talk much.
How could he tell me that?
Of course I
knew it thanks to
telepathy of twins.
Am I great?
See you later.
Connections.
[The Climax of Science]
Why don't you
get the cake out and eat it?
What if it becomes bad in the car?
Do you know guru's birthday is coming?
No.
What?
Anyway, it's coming.
What
should we prepare for him?
Hello, Xiaoxiao.
Can you help me
ask if Yang Lanhang's
birthday is coming?
That's your boyfriend.
How could I know?
No.
Hello.
Hello?
What's wrong?
Angry?
I'm sorry.
The number you have dialed
is not answered.
Please re-dial later.
No way. Really become angry?
I'm sorry.
The number you have dialed
is not answered.
[Swipe up to cancel or transfer it to text.]
Hello.
Do you know which date is
Yang Lanhang's birthday?
Bai Lingling,
why are you back for so long?
I just found it,
okay?
Okay. Okay.
There is power.
Let's go.
What's wrong? Just ignore me.
Why are you here?
I was afraid that you wouldn't reply my message,
so I came here specially to look at you into your eyes
and talk to you face to face.
Who didn't reply whose message?
Why do you
ask Hang's birthday?
What do you think of him?
Do you have a crush on him?
What are you thinking of?
It's not me.
Lingling asked me to ask it.
Please
tell me a better lie.
How could Bai Lingling
not know when
her boyfriend's birthday is?
What's more,
they are
a couple now.
And they planned
to spend the day together.
Don't you know it?
So, you mean
it is Yang Lanhang's birthday today.
Correct.
Although Hang was annoying for asking me too many times
and I'm not willing to teach him step by step,
I still
prepared a cake for him.
And put it
in the back of the car with some ice.
It's all I can do.
I...
This...this is mine.
Hello, Lingling.
I'm not coming back tonight.
I'll be here for Yang Lanhang's birthday.
They are spending the night there?
I have guessed it.
Great.
It's good to spend the night together.
♫ Happy birthday to you ♫
Hold, hold on.
Today is my birthday.
You don't know it?
No, well.
Does Yifan prepare
this cake?
I should thank him for the reminder.
But luckily,
I have made it.
Hurry up.
Hurry up and make a wish.
Thank you.
OK.
Hurry.
I will make a wish.
I hope
our material
can go to the market as soon as possible.
So, Lingling's grandma
and other patients
who need it
can perform the operation
and become better.
The second wish.
I hope
people I love
can be safe
and healthy.
The third wish.
It's okay. You should stop now.
I know the third one.
It must be
being with me forever,
right?
Well,
you don't need to make a wish to candles.
You just need to make a wish to me.
Maybe I can help you realize it.
OK.
Don't waste your chance.
Hurry up and make another one.
I...
I really don't know what to make.
It's okay.
You just say it in your mind.
Bai Lingling be young forever.
Young forever.
Right.
Young forever. Did you finish it?
Yes.
OK.
Happy birthday!
Thank you.
Actually, I haven't spent
a formal birthday for many years.
Your birthday
is important.
I will spend it with you
in the future, every of it.
OK.
We will spend
all the important
days together.
Like your birthday,
my birthday,
Christmas, Valentine
and New Year.
And Women's Day,
Labor Day
and Children's Day.
What is this?
I was so rushed today,
so I just fold
this for you,
Great.
Together with the cake,
it means you will start your voyage with blessings.
It even has a meaning.
If we meet any problems
in the future
that you feel difficult,
you can tear this up.
There is an answer in it.
There won't be such a day.
That's even better.
I hope you
never tear it up.
Because I spent much time folding it.
I won't.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Thank you for accepting me,
and forgiving me.
It's like a miracle
meeting you.
I'm so happy every day.
I should also thank you.
I'm so happy
every day with you, too.
I also think
you are my miracle
and my hope.
Right.
When
did you fall in love with me?
Honestly,
I don't know.
When I realized I did,
it had been a long time.
I need to confess a thing.
My favorite movie
is not Before Sunrise.
Well,
I tried to
find a topic to chat with you,
so I copied the note of Guan Xiaoyu.
Is there any chance that you like
After Dusk?
I never watched this.
Actually,
no matter it is dawn or dusk,
it is too short for me.
What I want is
every moment.
So, Yang Lanhang
doesn't know
it is his birthday today.
Lingling doesn't know, either.
And you tell me
they are spending the birthday together on the sea.
They are both smart.
I'm sure they can find the clue soon.
Why don't you just tell them?
It would be less interesting.
It's a big misfortune
that Yang Lanhang
has a cousin
like you.
Ouyang,
my work is almost done.
I can go home after that.
Are you free tomorrow, Ouyang?
Yes.
Lingling said a
good fiction movie is newly on.
She intended to watch it with me.
And I have bought the tickets.
But she has something to do suddenly,
so I'm wondering if you would like...
OK.
I work for two companies at daytime.
Taking care of my dad's side
and managing the company for Yang.
He is dating his girlfriend
at night at home,
and I cannot go back
and almost sleep on the street.
Where can you find a better cousin?
What?
What misfortune?
It's a fortune,
OK?
When did you sleep on the street?
Didn't I save you?
Where are you now?
Saving me?
I just sleep on your couch.
You didn't even give me a blanket.
I almost got a cold.
Didn't I get you a blanket?
I...
OK.
Even if I didn't give you a blanket,
so what?
Don't you come from a wealthy family?
You can live at a hotel.
Why do you sleep at my place?
You don't have money, right? I invite you...
Strange...
to come to my house and you have so many complaints.
You even blame me for not giving you a blanket.
It's good enough to give you the couch,
OK?
Interesting.
You don't have money, right?
Take away all these money.
And give my bags back
starting from tomorrow.
Where does so much money come from?
I have lots of money.
I have saved it for long.
For long.
Why do you return 10 thousand yuan to me
at a time?
Ri, right.
Why?
I just don't want to
spend it at a time.
What?
No.
You just want to see me more.
No. You think too much.
Guan Xiaoyu,
it's not direct at all. It's not like you.
Who is indirect?
I need to tell you.
Don't pretend
to know me.
I...I...
Just go back
to your five-star hotel.
You liked me for a long time, right?
No. Who likes you?
You just like me.
Get away.
Why don't you admit it?
What should I admit?
I...
♫ Honey ♫
♫ I don't intend to be silent ♫
♫ Don't break the wall ♫
♫ I'm afraid ♫
♫ I will overthink after your glance ♫
♫ Actually ♫
♫ I have much more to say ♫
♫ Like the great weather ♫
♫ Or can we ♫
♫ Sit by the seaside? ♫
No way.
I...I will
change the password tomorrow.
Then,
what about now?
Call the
unblanking company now.
What time is it now?
They should be sleeping.
What about coming with me?
OK. Let's go.
Drag.
Don't touch me.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
Are we going to Yang Lanhang's house?
I'm just
living there temporarily.
It's not good to bring someone else.
Let's go to a hotel.
Hotel?
Right.
I will open a room for you
and you can spend the night there.
I will pick you up tomorrow morning
and find someone to open the door.
OK.
Go inside.
Right.
You should
take some responsibility for this.
It has nothing to do with me.
Call me with the phone
in the hotel after
you are awake tomorrow morning.
I will pick you up.
Dial one for my home.
Rest early. Goodnight.
Hello.
I just realize that
you should have
no clothes for change.
I have bought you some
from the store casually,
and have asked the waiter to put it at your door.
I got it.
Thank you.
Why didn't you
push me away just now?
Hello.