"Today...
only comes once."
- Dante -
What is that?
What's wrong?
There is a drone flying
in front of my window.
Professor!
I will be right there!  Don't hang up and stay on campus until I get there.
Hello?  Professor?
Lieutenant.
Lieutenant!
Hey, there's been an accident here!
My gosh. What happened?
What?
What happened?
- Oh, what happened?
- 911, hurry!
There is no one here!
Someone, please report it!
- I will do it.
- There is no one in the back, either!
- Maybe they fell?
- Check the trunk!
The moment the child becomes a time traveler,
the prophecy will begin.
But the moment of fate...
has not yet arrived.
Excuse me, where is the professor?
The professor just went to teach.
Where is the lecture hall, please?
Lecture Hall 7 at room 318 in the second building.
Can I help you?
I am sorry.  I think I am in the wrong lecture hall.
Excuse me,  would you happen to know where Professor Yoon Tae Yi is?
- Who?
- I am looking for Physics Professor Yoon Tae Yi.
There is no professor by that name in the Physics Department.
Perhaps, are you looking for student Yoon Tae Yi?
Are you all right?  What happened to the drone?
What?
But why are you sitting here?
What are you, Mister?  Do you know me?
Excuse me, how about taking your lovers' quarrel outside, please.
Professor, let them be.
That's right.  Hey, keep going!
- It looks good!
-  Wooo!
Student Yoon Tae Yi?
If someone who looks exactly like me comes through that door,
who can clearly explain the situation?
I can!
The theory of Parallel Universe based on Erwin Schrödinger wave mechanics?
- B!
- Me!
The endless repetition and replication of the universe due to the Big Bang Theory.  In other words, the possibility that doppelgängers exist.
- B+!
- Me! Ant-Man and the Wasp?
Get out.
As earlier said, the Big Bang Theory states that the universe is too big so...
it's not one but several.  According to quantum mechanics,
more than one of the same object can exist in the same space.
However, Quantum Physics, the Big Bang Theory, and the Theory of Parallel Universe...
None of them are the answer to my question.
Unfortunately, we cannot explain it yet.  This is the correct answer.
This is the reason why we need to learn Heisenberg's Uncertainty Principle.
Do we really need to learn such an uncertain study?
- I agree!
- Right!
Of course, we must!  We must prove it is uncertain.
As a trivia, Heisenberg presented his Uncertainty Principle when he was 26 years old.
So, you guys go out right now and discover a new principle.  That's it for today's lecture.
- Yes!
- All right!
Thank you.
Why can't I get in touch with you?  It is worrying me...
Did you travel through time or something?
Call me.
- Professor!
- Why are you doing this?
- Don't you know me?
- Are you famous?
- No, I am not.
- Then, how would I know you?
May I ask how old you are?
I am 22 years old.  Why?
You are not 32 years old?
Are you saying I look old? Are you blind?
Yes.  Why?
Of course, I know that there will be a super blood moon today.
I was going to drink while watching the lunar eclipse.
"Lunar eclipse?"  Why do you watch that kind of stuff?
This lunar eclipse is the super blood moon and it only happens once every decade.
It is very special.
If I miss this one this year, in 2010, I'll probably never see another one before I die.
No, that's okay.  I will just see it alone.
- What are you doing?!
- What year is this?
It's 2010.
What was that?  He looks perfectly fine.
Hello?
Who is this?
Is it you, Mom?
Son?
Aren't you in class?
Is it really you, Mom?
Jin Gyeom, what's wrong?
Is anything wrong?
Where are you?
I am home, of course.
Jin Gyeom!
Mom, listen to me carefully.
I will go there now.
I will go home, so
lock all the doors and windows.
Don't go outside, no matter what.
You must stay at home.  Do you understand?
Mom?
Mom!
You really didn't call me?
How would I call you when I am in the middle of a class?   It was probably a prank call.
Don't worry.
I am going back in.
Jin Gyeom.
Recently, did anyone come to visit you?
Who?
Just... anyone.
No.
If any stranger comes to visit you, let me know right away.
Okay.
The phone is turned off. Please leave a message after the tone.
What is with this guy?
Why are you like this?
Do you happen to know where Lieutenant Park Jin Gyeom is?
It's all your fault.
Jin Gyeom became strange after meeting you!
He drank although he never drinks, and he's ignoring my calls!
- What are you talking about?
- Where is Jin Gyeom?
I asked, where is Jin Gyeom?
That's what I mean.  What are you talking about?
Jin Gyeom disappeared.
He was in an accident, but he disappeared into thin air!
Ah! This is nice.
Why do you drink when it's not good for your body?
If you are curious, would you like some?
No.
If anyone, your parent should be the one to teach you how to drink.
I need to study later.
It's your mom's birthday.  Is studying so important?
You finished it anyway.
You are right.  I was going to drink while watching the lunar eclipse.
"Lunar eclipse?"
It's a super blood moon that hasn't happened in 10 years.
If I miss this one, I probably will not be able to see another one before I die.
I better hurry and go buy some more.
You'll drink with me, right?
It was you.  I knew it.
You don't have time for this.  Your mom's in danger.
- What?
- I said your mom's in danger.
Tonight is the night of the blood moon.
Mom!
If you want to save your mom, hurry up and go.  Hurry, go!
Mom.
My son.
You grew up to be handsome.
I am sorry, Mom.
I wanted to protect you.
It's okay.
My son.
Everything's okay.
Jin Gyeom.
Time card, where is it?
Can you give it to me?
Yes.
You...
shouldn't be here.
Mom, what do we do?
I can't leave like this.
Who is it?  Who did this to you?
You can't get involved in this fight.
To see you all grown up like this,
Mom is so happy.
Don't ever come back and
you have to live happily.
Mom.
Mom!
Mom, what happened?  Who did this to you?
Mom, hang on just for a little while.  I will call 911.
♫  Even as time goes by  ♫
♫  And if you're going through this messy life  ♫
♫  When there is no end in sight  ♫
♫  I'll trust every moment of you  ♫
♫  From the beginning, I'll follow my chosen fate  ♫
♫  And tomorrow will be yesterday  ♫
The Alcubierre drive proves...
that faster than light space travel can be made possible by distorting spacetime.
♫  With you  ♫
♫  One day and somewhere  ♫
One moment.
♫  I'll be with you  ♫
♫  Whenever, wherever, whatever  ♫
Is it because you're a lieutenant or is it just your personality?
How can you not call even once when people are so worried about you?
Why don't you call even once when you are alive and well like this?
I normally don't worry at all about anyone, but
do you even know how worried and nervous I was thinking that you got into an accident while talking to me on the phone?
Why aren't you saying anything, after making me feel guilty?
Lieutenant Park!
♫  Remember, forever don't forget  ♫
♫  It's a meaningless moment without you  ♫
♫  Whenever, wherever, whatever stay with you   ♫
♫  Today and tomorrow, I'll be with you  ♫
I'll be back soon.
Drink up.
I'm sorry.
I've been discourteous again.
I didn't have any weird intentions. Please don't misunderstand.
Your mother and I must look very similar.
How did you know?
How could I not?
Anyone could tell from the way you've been treating me.
Asking if I'm over 50 with a son, then crying while hugging me.
How could I not know?
I apologize if I've offended you.
Do we really look that similar?
Enough for you to be reminded of her when you see me.
Yes, but just the appearance.
Your personalities are very different.
My mother was mild and tender.
She's a very good person.
How's my personality?
Of course, you also...
You...
So I mean, you also...
I'm sorry. I'm not good at telling lies.
Do you have any pictures of your mother?
I want to see.
I don't.
Why not?
Please excuse my recent actions.
If you see another drone, please let me know.
Where have you been since the accident for all this time?
You don't need to concern yourself with that.
I'm curious.
Where have you been for a week?
A week?
What do you mean?
Excuse me?
Was the accident... a week ago?
Yes.
Lieutenant.
Lieutenant!
Come to your senses, Lieutenant!
The reports from a week ago apparently weren't an error.
The wormhole opened again an hour ago.
- Who it is?
- Park Jin Gyeom.
Are you certain?
Who was driving the truck during the accident?
I can't figure it out.
It was a stolen truck, and the driver intentionally avoided all CCTVs while driving,
so there isn't a way to find out.
I think the police are also investigating,
but have no idea either.
How could Park Jin Gyeom travel through time?
We don't know that, either.
Hurry up and find out. Erase all records in the CCTV and dash cam footage.
Okay.
Where is Park Jin Gyeom right now?
In the hospital.
He must've been hurt since he didn't go through the departure gate.
Are you feeling okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Do you know how surprised I was?
I'm sorry I shocked you.
Were you in a power plant for a week?
What do you mean?
You're curious about what the hospital exam results show, aren't you?
You're a patient who suffered a car accident, but there are no signs of a fracture, rupture, nor sprain.
There's something even more strange.
Because of this, there was an error in the CT.
I thought that was so interesting, I looked into the radioactivity of this card.
And it is 6.3 microsieverts.
Do you have any idea how high that is?
The natural radiation level in this country is 0.3 microsieverts at most.
But... this card has more than 20 times the amount of  radiation.
Where were you for a week?
I'm asking where you were.
Where is Seok Oh Won now?
Excuse me. Hey!
You can't enter!
Excuse me. You may not enter!
Please leave.
It's all right. Take your leave.
Please have a seat.
Ten years ago, you came to my house.
Talking about that again?
How did you know my mom?
I've already told you I don't know your mother.
No.
You knew my mom would die on the night of the blood moon.
Why do you act like you know nothing when you're not even the killer?
Lieutenant Park Jin Gyeom, I looked into it and found that you have a history of mental illness.
You sound like you're in the early stage of reticulosis.
Shall I introduce you to a psychiatrist I know?
What do you know?
What I know is the frustration of a son who could not catch his mother's killer.
If you really want to find the suspect, why not try looking for your father?
Wouldn't your father know something you don't?
For example, what she was like before she got married.
Did you look into my family?
I've just did a little bit of research because you keep suspecting me.
Park Jin Gyeom time traveled?  How?
He had an unregistered time card.
It's also weird that someone tried to kill Park Jin Gyeom.
There must be something we don't know about.
We can't fully control it, anyway.
First, track down the time card.
It's not that simple.
He traveled time illegally, without our knowing.
He'll continue to suspect and investigate our existence.
We can't just brush this incident aside.
What do you plan on doing?
We've to kidnap Park Jin Gyeom and bring him to Alice.
Don't worry too much.
He called because he's safe.
He may have jumped off the car prior to the accident,
and the witnesses might've missed that.
How long is the jail time when you're arrested for murder?
Why are you asking that?
When Jin Gyeom comes back, I might kill him.
Let's just compromise with a broken leg.
Could it be that someone tried to kill Jin Gyeom?
We're looking into it, so wait just a little bit.
You still haven't caught them?
Can't you trust me?
I know I'm at the corner of the office now, but I used to be quite the detective in the old days.
Jin Gyeom was unjustly arrested under a false charge because of you in high school.
That's because you, with your eyes wide open...
claimed with certainty that Jin Gyeom was the suspect.
That's true.
I just got a call from Lieutenant Park.
Where is he?
You were in the ER?
What did they say?
They say I'm fine.
Really? You're not hurt at all?
No.
That's good. I guess I can hit you all I want.
How could you not call even once for a week?!
Do you know how worried I was thinking that you might be dead?
I am sorry for worrying you.
Why didn't you call?
I couldn't get any cellphone reception.
Where were you?
Somewhere far away.
Far away where?
I will tell you when everything becomes certain.
Why did you go to the emergency room with that professor?
You still think that she is your mom?
Not anymore.
I saw it for myself that she is not related at all.
What does that mean?
I got it.
You look tired so we can talk about the rest tomorrow.  Get some sleep.
I am going to sleep here tonight, too.
Let's go to the hospital as soon as you get up tomorrow.  I need to see it for myself for certain that you are okay.
They said I don't have any injuries.
But you were in an accident.
Big or small, it's an accident, regardless.
Getting shot with a gun softly doesn't mean that it won't hurt, so go with me to the hospital tomorrow.
There is someone I need to find.
Mister will catch the suspect.
Not the suspect.
Then who?
My father.
Why your father, all of a sudden?
Wasn't there anything you learned about my father during the course of investigating my mom's case?
There is something I need to confirm when I find him.
Something's up with you, right?
Don't you think it's strange that you were gone for a week and suddenly you show up and want to find your father?
Explain what's going on first.
There is nothing to explain.
I just want to find my father, that's all.
So, why?
You've never once looked for your father before.  You said you hated your father because he abandoned your mom.
So, why find him?
I am not looking for him because I am curious about what kind of person he is.
I am looking for him because he is the only person who knows about my mom's past that I don't know about.
At that time, we also looked into your father, but
you know it, too...
how many single mothers are out there.
I understand.
How is your health?
You sure do ask early.
When you didn't even come once for a hospital visit.
I was going to visit you after I caught the punk who did that to you.
If you are going to make an excuse, at least be imaginative.  Why do all the ones who didn't visit have the same repertoire?
Hello.
I am Jin Gyeom.
Who?
I am Park Jin Gyeom.
The green gated house.  That kid?
Oh, that's right.
After your mom died, the police asked me so that's what I told them.
How did you know?  Did you hear it directly from my mom?
It's not like your mom is the type to talk about herself.
I happened to see her talking on the phone over there.
That day your mom came to get some meat.
Are you sure that the person my mother was talking to was my father?
It's not for certain.  It just felt that way, that's all.
Even to the police, I told them that it felt like it was the husband, not that it was for certain.
Anyway, your mom's behavior was not normal.
She was trembling the whole time she was on the phone.
Okay.  Keep monitoring him.  We need to catch him alive tonight.
Yes, Team Leader!
Do you think Park Jin Gyeom will get caught?
We will have to catch him.
Wait.
Did you personally collect the information on Park Jin Gyeom?
Yeah.  Why?
I think we need to re-investigate Park Jin Gyeom.
It's not like you can time travel just because you have the time card.
Okay.  I will look into it again.
Please take care of it.
Unnie, did the result come out?
Yeah, but this is really strange.
How did you know?  Did they conduct an experiment there?
Don't beat around the bush.  Hurry up and tell me.
On the 7th and the 14th,
on both days, the radiation readings on the roads spiked by more than 40 times.
Okay, got it.  Thanks, Senior.
What are you investigating?
You don't need to know.
Am I even your partner?
Look at this.
Ah, look at this.  My clothes are loose because of muscle loss.
This is all because I was looking for you, Lieutenant.
I couldn't even work out properly for a week.
You were locked up somewhere for a week, weren't you?
Don't be embarrassed and just tell me honestly.
What kind of punks were they?  I will take care of them.
You wouldn't believe me even if I told you.
I know you don't say empty words so just tell me.
Would you believe me if I told you that I was in Seoul in the Year 2010?
Sorry?
Is that so hard to believe?
I lived in Seoul in 2010, too.
I lived in Seoul at that time, too.
Me, too.
See? Everyone lived in Seoul.
You suddenly disappeared from a car that was involved in an accident, then reappear after a week...
You don't have any noticeable injury.  Instead,
the radiation readings went up.
This is my theory.  You had become an invisible man or...
you time traveled.
But nearby CCTVs didn't capture any floating clothes.  So,
that rules out invisible man.
That leaves just one, right?
It will be best if you don't get yourself involved in this matter.
This is not something that you want to approach simply with a scientist's curiosity.
Do you know why I became a physicist?
In truth, my mom really is a good mom but she is not my biological mom.
I was told that my biological mom left me at the orphanage and disappeared.
Lieutenant,
do you remember when you were 5 years old?
I... remember my mom's smell.
Even though it was only for a day,
and so, I don't even remember my mom's face, but
her warm embrace and her smell,
I clearly remember them.
When my mom left me at the orphanage and didn't come back,
do you know what I thought about?
Time travel.
If I travel through time and go back to the day I got separated from Mom,
I will not let her go, no matter what.
That's why I decided to become a scientist.
I also wanted to go see my mom.
Lieutenant, you always asked me.
Is time travel possible?
This time, I will ask you.
I know it doesn't make sense...
Yes.
You controlled time using that card.
Can you go again?
I'm not sure how it works yet.
Where's the card? I'll find out.
If we succeed,
you can meet your mother.
Even though it doesn't make any sense, we could
save your mother.
Give me the card.
Where is it?
Goodness.
Does a person really live here?
Even a model house is messier than this.
Do you live with a girl?
It's Do Yeon's.
Please have a seat.
Would you like some coffee?
Yes, black coffee, please.
How do you know the reporter?
We're just friends. Please don't misunderstand.
I think you're a bit too understanding.
Reporter Kim is really pretty.
What's the issue?
There isn't an issue.
That's the issue, huh.
Do you have someone else that you like?
No, I don't.
I don't like women.
Oh, I think I get it now.
It's all right. I understand.
Then... do you have a man that you like?
No. I also don't like men.
Then, who do you like?
Do I have to like someone?
We don't like someone because we want to.
We just... are overtaken by emotions of liking someone, even without our knowing.
When we think of them, we're happy and want to be with them.
- Have you never had anyone like that?
- Nope.
Not even once?
- Yes.
- Is that possible?
It may be because I've alexithymia.
You have aspermia? (mujeongjajeung)
(T/N: she mishears and confuses the medical condition which means infertility)
No. Alexithymia. (mugamjeongjeung)
Okay.
Isn't that like a psychopath?
My ability to experience emotions is a bit lacking,
but that doesn't mean I break the laws of society or act out in violence.
Please have this.
You didn't drug this, did you?
I didn't.
Why is it so bitter?
It's black coffee.
Oh, I see.
But are you allowed
to just be talking about stuff like this?
I've never thought of hiding it.
I don't care what others think.
You're really interesting.
I'm always so shocked every time I meet you,
I think I keep losing weight.
Why?
Are you sure you've weighed yourself?
I think if anything, your cheeks have gotten a bit puffier.
I apologize.
I was only being honest...
Stop being so honest!
Even a psychopath is less cruel than you.
But what kind of person with alexithymia cries so often?
Maybe that's not what you have.
Thanks to my mom, it's gotten a bit better.
Your mother must have struggled a lot.
If your mother really was a time traveler–
Let's stop talking about that.
I'll bring you the card.
Is it a blackout?
I guess things like this can still happen...
Do you have a flashlight or candles?
What are you doing?
Lieutenant!
What's wrong?
Stay behind me.
Please stay inside.
What was that?
Hye Soo.
Jeong Hye Soo.
Hye Soo!
Hye Soo, what happened?
Min Hyeok...
Who did this?
Why did you turn the lights on?
We didn't do that.
Get out of there immediately.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
I've never seen him before. Is he another broker?
I'm not sure.
He's the man that called the police.
Then he must not be a broker.
Since he would want to keep things low key.
Who could he be?
Why did he save Park Jin Gyeom?
Maybe a couple of kids in the area got into a fight.
What did the caller say?
That's what was a bit weird.
He said there was a break-in in apartment 305,
but 305 is your unit.
Is something wrong?
No.
Let's go. I'll escort you home.
- Good work.
- They will keep targeting Park Jin Gyeom.
Park Jin Gyeom... Until he realizes his own fate,
we must keep protecting him.
Yes, Sir.
You may go. Keep a close watch on him until I instruct you otherwise.
That day is approaching.
Be more careful in the future.
Yes, Sir.
Earlier... why did you draw your gun?
You don't need to worry about that.
Just in case, if anything happens while you're analyzing the contents of the card,
please call me right away.
Please make sure Seok Oh Won
does not know anything about the card.
Are you still suspecting him?
I just want to warn you to be careful.
Unnie!
Yeah.
What the heck? Why are you with the pervert?
Why are you calling him a pervert?
You said he was one.
When did I say that?
Sorry, my sister is kind but is a bit slow.
What the...
Get home safely.
- Unnie.
- Huh?
What's your relationship with the Lieutenant?
Just an acquaintance.
- Is that all?
- Then what else?
Well... I'm amazed to see you talk to a guy for more than a minute.
Of all the things to be amazed by...
There are so many things that are fascinating in the world, but that's what you find amazing?
That's why you don't make progress.
Do you think I gained weight?
I can't really tell.
Right?
Alexithymia...
What?
Chief! Chief!
What is it? What?
Is something the matter?
Did you write this article?
I wonder... Did I?
It says you're the author.
Oh, I did write this!
This is my article.
Did you investigate this yourself?
Of course. Hey, back in my day,
we never asked others to investigate for us.
Do you still have the investigative files from this case?
Of course. That's the life of a reporter. I have all of it.
Can you please show that to me.
Why?
The victim is someone I know, so I want to know if there's any information on the husband.
Okay.
I'm serious! Our chief was behind that investigation,
and he said someone came to your house in the afternoon the day your mother died,
while you were at school.
- Are you certain?
- Yes.
Why?
I didn't hear about that from the Team Leader.
I didn't see that in the files for that case either.
Really?
Our chief said that he told him...
Maybe he just forgot.
Who was the person who came?
I don't know who it was, but it wasn't your father.
A man in their late 20s to early 30s.
Oh right! There's another thing I found out, too.
About a month before she was murdered, your mom visited someone in a prison.
My mom? Who?
Wait a minute.
Have you heard of the name?
No.
I'm not sure what his relationship was with your mother,
but this person is still in prison.
Which prison?
I'll meet him alone.
No, I want to go with you.
It's a personal investigation. I'll be uncomfortable with you there.
Why are you hiding so many things from me lately?
I don't want to worry you.
You're allowed to worry for me, but I'm not allowed to worry for you?
Just give me a bit of time. Once I figure things out, I'll–
Do you know why people go missing in the mountains?
It's because they mistakenly think they'll find the way if they just go down the mountain.
When you're lost, you have to ask for help.
Instead of trying to resolve it on your own, you need to shout for help!
This is something I need to solve alone.
I'll drop you off here.
Don't misunderstand what I'm about to say.
The person who's in prison right now is around your mother's age,
and began his sentence in the year you were born.
He could be your father.
That may be why your mother didn't say anything about him.
So if you get to meet him, don't be rude.
I don't care what kind of person my father is.
The only father I have is Mr. Ko.
Some bastard tried to kill a fellow cop, but you guys haven't found anything about him in the last week? Answer me!
I feel like your body got bigger. All you did was work out, huh?
It's really not true. I want to find something, but I can't.
To be honest, Lieutenant Park isn't really cooperating either.
Where's Jin Gyeom?
He went to visit a prison with Reporter Kim.
What is he up to now?
A prison?
- Park Jin Gyeom?
- Yes.
He's meeting Lee Se Hoon in prison.
Let the people of this world punish you for your crimes here.
Argh!
Who are you?
Why are you here?
Do you know this woman?
Give me the book.
What the hell is in this book that everyone wants this?
Who are you?
I'm this person's son.
Why did you come looking for me?
How did you know my mother?
Go ask her yourself.
She passed away 10 years ago.
Why are you laughing?
It's interesting.
Whoever comes by "The Book of Prophecy" either dies...
or ends up like me.
What's "The Book of Prophecy?"
You're her son,
but you don't even know that?
Did my mother
die because of that?
What's written in the book?
Are you curious?
It's the end.
The end?
The end of time travel.
♫  My love will bring us back  ♫
♫  Ain't nobody holding me back  ♫
♫  We be like Bonnie and Clyde  ♫
♫  We ride or die  ♫
♫  We tight  ♫
♫  My love will bring us back  ♫
♫  Ain't nobody holding me back  ♫
♫  We be like Bonnie and Clyde  ♫
♫  We ride or die  ♫
♫  Like Bonnie and Clyde  ♫
- I saw him.
- Who?
The man from the picture in 1992.
He's going to kill four more people.
Did you know there was a super blood moon 10 years ago?
What does that have to do with my mom's death?
If you were in my situation, you would've done the same.
Let her go!
A program similar to the one I'm researching is in this card.
The card that Park Jin Gyeom was carrying emitted a signal.
Have you lost someone you've loved before?
You... What's your identity?