[Previous Episode]
A vespa?
Was it expensive? I want one too.
I think you don't need to have one.
Because from now on, I will be
picking you up and drop you off.
Do you like my friend?
Why do you think that?
Based on what you're doing...
from bought him the shirt
to the coincidental meetings.
I think it's surely suspicious.
Are you sure you want
me to punch you back?
But, you've seen...
my junior already.
So, are you gonna
let me see yours too?
[Warning liquor can cause brawling and crime]
How's P'Paew doing?
I don't know, I didn't talk to
him when I was heading out.
Does he has any bad
reaction that he can't drink?
I don't know.
P'Wee.
He followed you earlier
to talk about him, right?
Yes.
How do you know?
I got it from lakorns.
Korean?
It's from Thai lakorn,
if it's Korean it's called series.
Just relax, let me handle this.
Evil things like this...
has to be me.
P'Tonmai.
Yes?
Wanna have a drink duel?
Pew.
Don't.
Just relax, I'll handle this.
What do you say? Wanna do it?
I think...
we should just drink in a chill way.
No!
[Serve Love to Greet the Heart]
♫ Every passing day ♫
♫ Everyone's heart melody is different ♫
♫ Every starless night ♫
♫ There is another person who
guides me in the direction to go on ♫
♫ When my heart feels hopeless ♫
♫ And when I take the wrong steps ♫
♫ You make me able to think ♫
♫ No more ♫
♫ I just gave up the dream
in my heart that day ♫
♫ No way of moving forward ♫
♫ From now on, every
breath is with you close to me ♫
♫ Thank you for making me having today ♫
[Serve Love to Greet the Heart]
The weather is nice.
You called me out here...
is there anything?
I noticed that you're
not good at drinking.
You might get
persuaded to drink by them.
How do you know that
I'm not good at drinking?
Well...
I can tell by your face.
Why?
What's wrong with my face?
It's because you
have such a soft face.
You're looking down on me.
A guy like me never wrong.
Is that a joke?
Yes, are you not gonna laugh?
No.
Please laugh for me a little.
Please, help me laugh a little.
No!
Wait for me here for a moment.
I'll be back.
Yeah, Ai'Mike?
Well, I went for a little errand.
Settle the bill,
I won't be back anymore.
I'll clear things tomorrow.
OK, see you.
What is this, Kawee.
It's beer.
You and I will have a duel.
I don't see this to be necessary,
I was just joking.
I will let you know that I'm...
I will let you know that I'm... not...
not... at all...
I will let you know that I'm...
not... at all... soft!
Come on.
You...
Cheers a little.
P'.
P', the bar is closing.
Don't disturb me.
I want to sleep.
Just do what you hae to do, go.
Sleep as you please.
Have a nice sleep.
Cheers.
Cheers!
That's enough.
I believe now that you're not soft.
No way, we have to cheers!
- Cheers, cheers, cheers!
- OK, OK, cheers.
Kawee.
Are you alright?
Kawee?
Kawee.
Kawee, Kawee.
Ka... wee.
P'Phupha?
Am I dreaming?
It's real.
What are you shocked about?
How am I sleeping with you?
And...
did you do something to me?!
Wait, wait, calm down.
I didn't do anything to you.
This is not my shirt and pants.
Don't tell me you...
Yes.
I changed it for you last night.
That means...
you saw...
Kawee.
Talk to me, Kawee.
Actually, I didn't see anything.
I tried to look but
yours are too small.
Close...
so close.
Lips look so kissable.
So wonderful.
How am I having this thoughts?
Kawee...
your face is red.
Are you having
some thoughts on me?
I'm not.
You're being ridiculous.
Really?
I'm not. Let me go,
I want to go home.
I'm not letting you go.
Until you tell me what
you're thinking just now.
If you don't say it...
then don't go home.
I will count to 3.
1...
2...
Fuck it!
Just gie it a go.
Sawasdee, please excuse me.
What's all this, Ai'Phu?
What?
Well...
with that kid...
It's nothing.
Are you sure it's nothing?
If there's nothing...
then why is he running in a hurry?
I don't know,
he's rushing home probably.
Rushing home?
This is your house.
How can you let
someone else sleeps here?
Well...
he was wasted last night.
So I brought him here to sleep.
Why are you asking too much?
I'm gonna go shower.
What's wrong with you, Phupha?
How can I kissed his cheeks?
What he did...
he did it just to escape, right?
Yes.
I only did it to escape.
He should understand.
He'll not be mad at me, right?
Please don't be mad at me.
Please?
Where is he?
Is he not here yet?
Who are you looking for?
No one.
I'm not looking.
What are you doing
standing all frantic here?
I saw you and thought you
were looking for someone.
No, I'm not looking for anyone.
Really?
Then you're
stretching out your head...
what's the matter?
My back hurts so bad.
I'm in pain often lately. Constantly.
My back is in bad shape.
Back is in bad shape.
I think should be the one in pain.
Both right and left side.
I don't know what
happened last night.
The pain is so heavy.
You said you didn't do anything to me.
Then what's with the back pain?
What's so heavy?
Did...
you do something to me?
Calm down.
When I said I'm having back pain...
Because I carried you
home to a taxi last night.
What kind a guy that's short...
but so heavy.
It's concealed by your looks.
I carried you and now I'm sore all over.
What were you thinking?
Nothing.
Where are you going?
Wanna have some coffee with me?
Sorry for kissing your cheek.
What were you making merit of ?
Why can't you enter a bar?
What merit?
I was making a merit
for my shop of course.
Really?
I want my shop to sell well.
Your shop already did great.
Tell me what did you made merit of.
Forget about the merit.
By the way, last night...
how did you went home?
Me?
I went home by taxi.
E'Pew told me...
that you...
went with P'Phupha.
Then you're gone!
No!
I went home to Pew's room.
How can you
went back to Pew's room?
Pew drank until morning.
I was the one who picked
her up and get him home.
You left with P'Phupha, didn't you?
No!
I...
didn't went to his house!
You went to his house, didn't you?
Didn't you?
You went to his house, didn't you?!
Come back here!
You think you can escape from me?
Tell me!
Tell you what, Sis?
I told you not to call me "Sis".
Because you're older than me.
So what?
We're friends. Just call me "kae"(you) is enough.
[ "Kae" is often used by female friends when addressing
each other, you heard them quite often in Thai series ]
But...
Don't force me to use strong words!
You were sleeping with
P'Phupha last night, didn't you?!
Yes.
I slept at P'Phupha's house.
But we didn't do anything.
I was drunk, when I woke up
I was already in his house.
You really are stupid.
You got to his house.
You should've "settled" with him.
Are you crazy?
Why would I do that?
Did you forget?
That you're doing this for this cafe?
If you can build a relationship
with him, anything will be easier.
Opportunity like this...
you shouldn't have let it go.
Come in.
Kok?
Jeed?
You're working here?
Yes.
I came around here many
times but haven't been here once.
If I knew you're working here,
I'll be here a long time ago.
Have a sit.
Where have you been?
You haven't been to class for 2 days.
I was busy so I didn't go to class.
But that's alright,
I've taken the lecture notes for you.
What do you want, just order.
It'll be my treat.
I made this for you.
Who's that?
My friend.
It's nothing, what do you like to have?
Then I'll have a hot mocha.
Hot mocha.
Sure thing.
That's it?
OK, I'll have it ready for you.
Why are you pulling me here?
Let me go.
Come with me, don't worry about it.
Fine.
You're not coming nicely, right?
What are you doing? Let me go!
Where are you going?
Work.
Have a sit first, you can go later.
Hey.
I'm working in an office.
Now the lunch break is over.
I have to work.
I'm not as free as you.
Can't you sit with me first?
I don't know what you're stressing about.
What you're facing and
what problem you're having.
If you're only siting here and sigh...
it's not gonna help
you with your problem.
We all have our problem.
It's up to you...
on whether you want to solve the
problem or avoid the problem.
What you're doing now...
is avoiding from your problem.
And it's not a good way to do it.
Fight for it.
Why are you
sitting here and sighing?
You made this yourself?
What did you cook for me?
If you want to know, then open it.
There's banana too.
You made rice with omelette for me?
Why?
Before I could accomplish that,
I lost a whole tray of eggs you know.
Just an omelette and you
used a whole tray of eggs?
Yes!
I never done this before.
I can't cook either.
And they all burned with
only this remains. The best one.
Is it edible?
Why are you saying that?
Give it here.
I'm eating it.
I'm just kidding,
why do you have to get upset?
It's quite good.
I want some too.
No, you made this for me, didn't you.
I'm not giving it to you.
I want some too.
Alright, fine.
Here, eat on your own.
Are you not gonna feed me?
Fine, I'll feed you.
How's it?
Is it good?
Of course, I made it myself.
You're boasting.
You almost eat the whole box.
Fine, fine, I admit.
Kok, can you give
this to P'Phupha for me?
Sure thing.
Why don't you give it yourself?
Kok, back to work.
OK.
Why do you have to
ask Kok to give it to me?
Well...
Or you're shy...
about secretly kissed
my cheek this morning?
Turn your face here and talk to me.
Kissed my cheek and
thinking of running from me?
In that case, shall I kiss you back?
Is no one gonna help me?
Let me help.
Thank you.
Slowly.
I'm Noom.
I'm Paew.
I'm single, rich and will love sincerely.
- Are you hurt?
- Yes.
Hurts.
Slowly.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Are you hurt?
Don't ask.
Not a single one of
you help me when I fell.
What were you doing?
I saw it.
You two were going to
kiss each others' cheeks.
No, P'Paew.
No one is kissing anyone's cheek.
That's right, no one's kissing. No one.
But I saw you were about
to kiss each others' cheeks
No, we were just
standing and talking.
That's right,
we're standing far apart too.
Out of sudden...
who's gonna kiss each others' cheeks.
Really?
Or was I dreaming?
But I saw it.
Yes, they were gonna kiss.
I saw it.
I saw you two were gonna
kiss each others' cheeks!
Where did they go?
Why are they avoiding me?
I'm not crazy.
Or am I crazy?
I think we've escaped him.
Where are you going?
Nowhere.
Why did you kissed
my cheek this morning?
I was just trying to escape, P'.
You were not gonna let me go.
So I'm not wrong.
Smells good?
My cheek.
Was it smells good?
Kawee.
I'm asking if my cheek...
smells good?
I should ask you.
Earlier...
were you really gonna kiss my cheek?
You're good at changing the subject.
I didn't.
But if you answer, I'll answer.
What's in your mind then?
What's in your mind...
I think the same too.
He did?
He's gone?
You don't want the shirt back?
Thank you for the ride.
I'm hungry.
Hungry?
Then go find something to eat.
Why are you telling me?
I'm hungry.
Then go find something to eat.
What's your problem?
You're not gonna invite
me for dinner in your house?
Why should I?
Aren't that too mean?
I gave you a ride home.
Don't you think about repaying me?
You're the one who voluntarily
wants to send me home.
I told you not to.
That's true, I volunteered.
But you can be nice to me, right?
In my house...
there's nothing to eat.
My hand is also hurt.
I can't cook for you.
Go eat at a restaurant.
No. I want to eat in your house.
You brat.
This uncle.
You're calling me uncle now?
Just "P" will do I think.
No, I will call you "uncle".
Uncle, uncle, uncle.
Why are you following me?
I'm hungry.
Here.
Eat.
What the heck?
I was wondering what I'll get to eat...
but it's only an instant noodles.
You're not gonna eat, right?
Yes, yes, I want.
So, you're not gonna eat?
You can't even invite me
to your house for dinner.
I have to eat
instant noodles at the park.
What are you
complaining so much?
Hurry eat and go home.
You're chasing me away.
Think whatever you want.
I'll eat slowly then.
P'.
Yes?
The cafe is closed.
What close?
It's not the closing time yet.
P'Phupha called and said
I can close the cafe already.
He has work to do.
Where's Wee gone to?
I saw P'Kawee
drove home already.
Drove home?
He left me again.
How am I gonna go home now?
Please excuse me then.
He always left me behind.
Do you want me to drive you home?
Is that OK?
Yes.
OK.
Come.
Kawee?
P'Phupha?
Don't tell me...
it's another
coincident that we met here?
Yes.
The coincidence is too often that I
think you're secretly following me.
I'm not.
Besisdes I like coming to this park.
I was joking.
Again?
You always tease me.
So...
what are you doing here today?
Just taking a walk.
What about you?
I came here to recall past memories.
What memory?
It's nothing.
Wanna take a walk?
Why are you grabbing my hand?
I've walked but you didn't follow.
Or you legs are too short
that you can't follow my steps?
You're calling me short?!
Or is it not true?
I have the standard
height of a Thai male.
It's you who are too tall.
Let's go.
Kok.
Jeed?
Are you here for a coffee?
The cafe is closed.
No, I'm here to see you.
Me?
Yes.
I've brought the lecture
note during the class for you.
I'm afraid you won't be able to keep
up with our friend's progress.
Thank you so much,
it's troubling you.
What troubling? It's just notes.
Have you had dinner?
Not yet.
Then, wanna have dinner together?
Kok can't go on a dinner with you.
Today...
he's having dinner with me.
Ai'Tai is joking.
What joking?
What do you want to eat, Jeed?
It'll be my treat.
Consider that I'm
paying for the lecture note.
For real?
Then, I won't hold my appetite.
Then, I'm heading home.
You're not gonna join us?
No, I cooked back in the room.
But it's a pity that no one will eat.
I think your friend is probably angry.
Then why don't we go some other time?
It's fine.
Besisdes, I need to
ask for your help too.
What subject do you want me
to take notes for you now?
No wonder you said you
want to invite me to dinner.
That hurts.
Uncle.
Can I have the water?
Do I look that old that
you're calling me "uncle"?
No.
But you told me yourself that
you're older than me, right?
That's why I called you "uncle".
That's true.
But you can call me "P", right?
Because I want to call you "uncle".
Why? Can't I?
Fine, call me whatever you want.
Uncle.
Give me the water.
I'm thirsty.
Uncle.
Can I ask you something?
Have you ever...
had a crush on someone?
Why do you ask?
Just answer my question.
Because you're having a
crush on someone, aren't you?
The reason you were
siting and sad all day...
it's because of this, right?
You know too well.
Whoever you're secretly love or like...
just tell them.
Will they know if you don't tell them?
I don't dare to.
I'm afraid of the answer.
You're having a crush on a friend then?
You know it again.
Don't tell me you can read my mind?
Nonsense.
Let me tell you.
If you secretly love
or like someone, go for it.
Whether it'll be
a happy ending or not...
forget about that first.
The more you keep it inside...
the one who'll be
siting uncomfortably and sad...
is you.
It's better for you to let them know.
At least if you get sad, it'll be only once.
It's better than you siting and feel sorry
for yourself over and over again.
when you see them
doing things with someone else.
Fighting.
Love...
there's nothing certain about it.
You have to understand and accept it.
Thank you, Uncle.
Hurry and eat.
What did you cooked?
Why do you ask?
Because I'm hungry.
You've eaten, didn't you?
What are you doing?
Throw it away.
Wait, wait,
why do you want to throw it?
No one's gonna eat it, why keep it?
I'm going to eat it here.
You think I'm being unfaithful?
You've eaten, didn't you?
Not yet.
I came home to eat
your cooks, of course.
But...
I don't know if it's edible or not.
Whether it's edible or not, give it a try.
Why talk too much?
If you wanna smile, then just smile.
Don't put on a facade.
What? Who's gonna smile?
You of course.
You talk too much.
So are you gonna eat or not?
Yes, yes, eat, eat.
What?
Eat it.
Is it good?
It's edible.
Then don't eat, give it here.
Calm down.
So fierce.
Is there something you want?
I do.
I'm here to talk about Phupha.
Why?
From now on...
you and I...
eye for an eye...
and tooth for a tooth.
May the best man wins.
[Next Episode]
You're teasing me?
What teasing?
I'm just shake the
clothes to dry it off.
You wanna play, right?
What?
P'Gawin, your brother left me alone again.
Serve you right.
P'.
Can you get out of my head?
You have to enter it.
I'm talking to you and you're not talking to me.
You wait.
I'll make you love me to death.
♫ And I will take you away ♫
♫ From this soil ♫
♫ Take you, you and me ♫
♫ We will have our time ♫
♫ Just the two of us ♫
♫ I'm only asking for you
to trust and confident with me ♫
♫ We will go together ♫
♫ We will hold hands
and walk away till the end ♫
♫ Till we lose our breath ♫
♫ Thank you so much for everything
that you made go through ♫
♫ You made me realize that I have value ♫
♫ Like the days when you are by my side ♫
♫ It's good when in times I have you ♫
♫ Whether it's happiness or sadness,
it doesn't matter ♫
♫ Just having you standing here ♫
♫ Stay here and we'll go together ♫
♫ And I will take you away ♫