[Previous Episode]
Any idea what you wanna make?
There's cabbage.
I'll make a fish
stir-fry with cabbage.
What are you doing?
Helping you cook, of course.
Stir the eggs like this.
He already has an
appointment with me.
What are you doing?
Follow me.
Fine.
What the heck?
Ponfah?
Phupha.
- Manfah?
- Phupha.
Manfah...
Are you not gonna invite me in?
Come on in.
[Serve Love to Greet the Heart]
♫ Every passing day ♫
♫ Everyone's heart melody is different ♫
♫ Every starless night ♫
♫ There is another person who
guides me in the direction to go on ♫
♫ When my heart feels hopeless ♫
♫ And when I take the wrong steps ♫
♫ You make me able to think ♫
♫ ♫ No more ♫
♫ I just gave up the
dream in my heart that day ♫
♫ No way of moving forward ♫
♫ From now on, every breath
is with you close to me ♫
♫ Thank you for making me having today ♫
[Serve Love to Greet the Heart]
Manfah...
when did you arrived in Thailand?
I arrived here today.
When I got here, I have to find you.
Why do you look
unhappy that I came here to you?
So...
what about your boyfriend?
Don't talk about him.
We...
parted ways.
So...
you came back,
do you have a place to stay yet?
Well, I actually came here to ask to
stay with you for the time being.
When I get a place to stay,
I'll move out.
You don't mind, right?
Why?
Do you have a girlfriend now?
No, Manfah.
I don't have a girlfriend yet.
Well...
If you want to stay here...
you can.
You're still single, so that means...
you still keep your promise
that you'll wait for me, right?
You must be tired.
Wanna get a shower and rest?
I'll prepare a room for you.
Phu.
Fah...
is there anything you need?
Well...
I think I want to sleep in
the same room with you.
But...
I've prepared a room for you.
Phu...
you're acting like we
haven't sleep together before.
But it was a long time ago.
I think...
you better sleep I the
room I've prepared for you.
You've changed a lot.
I really can't forget about you.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing, Ai'Kok?
Let me go.
I thought you'd ever
come to see me again.
I called you many times
but you didn't pick up.
I went to alley of house
but you didn't come out.
I wasn't free.
I had to submit an assignment
to the professor yesterday.
But now...
let me go.
Are you sure that
you were doing assignment?
You're not mad at me, right?
No, what mad? No.
Then why are you avoiding my face?
You're definitely mad at me.
I said I'm not.
You can look away now.
No.
Until you admit...
that you're really mad at me.
So...
you...
want me to get mad at you, right?
No, my friend.
Go and take a shower.
OK.
Hello, Kawee. I'm at your front door.
- Sawasdee krub.
Same direction...
so we go together, right?
Are you mking fun of me?
No, I was just...
saying what you said.
Go together...
the world will get a lot cooler.
Kawee...
you're not gonna stop
making fun of me, aren't you?
Let's get going, P.
I won't say anymore.
You're naughty.
I keep this in mind,
I'll get back at you later.
That's Ai'Phu's car.
Who is he picking up?
Or...
he's picking up Kawee?
What are you daydreaming about?
What were you daydreaming about?
What daydreaming? I wasn't.
I'm just missing someone.
Don't you wanna
ask who that person is?
No, I don't want to know.
You don't wanna know...
but I want to tell.
Right now...
I'm missing someone
who's much older than me.
This one old man.
You mean me?
You think I miss you?
No, I miss my father.
This brat.
Drive.
Closer.
Awesome.
Can you do a combine heart?
Is there any other pose, Kawee?
How about the
one that Paew suggested?
Is that a good idea?
We're out of pose now.
There's nothing to lose.
We'll try.
What is this, Tonmai?
I have no idea too.
Shocked?
What is this, P'Paew?
Are you sad?
No.
I'm very chilled.
So...
Why are those two doing that?
Because koo-jin is
very trendy right now.
[ Koo-jin = imaginary couple ]
This.
The coolest barista
and the cool waiter.
What is this craziness?
What crazy, bitch?
We're very open in this day of age.
Phu!
Can I talk to you?
Sure.
She's Ai'Phu's ex-girlfriend.
This is the person...
that he promised to
wait for her to come back.
Wait.
P'Phupha's ex is...
not a guy?
No.
What makes you think that?
Ponfah...
is the first girlfriend...
and the only girlfriend of Phupha.
Phupha loves her so much.
He made a promise...
that he'll wait for her to come back.
And he won't accept anyone.
Now that you know,
don't you feel jealous?
I think this question...
I should ask you.
Then I confess to you here...
that I...
already stop liking Phupha.
I have been persistent
for so many years...
before I realized it.
I find out that it's the kid
of liking that lovers have.
But now...
I have someone I really like.
You can call it love too.
Do you wanna know...
who that person is?
Even if you don't wanna know...
it's alright.
But I want to tell.
The person that I really like...
is...
your brother.
Don't think about stopping me.
Because I really want this person.
What is this, Phu?
What were you doing?
Taking photos.
What taking photos?
Why do you have to
hug a guy like that?
It doesn't mean anything.
Is this what you
mean waiting for me?
That's too much.
I took photos earlier...
because the customers ask for it.
So I give them that service.
They like it.
This will also increase sale.
How can I not do it?
You really don't have
any feelings to that kid, right?
Don't forget about
your promise to wait for me.
Fah!
But it was years of torture.
If I want to forget...
I don't think it's a problem.
Phu...
But I'm back now.
If you forgot it then it's fine.
But from now on,
you can remember it.
Then...
you should get back to work.
All done.
Too many customers today, P.
There wasn't eve enough cake to sell.
Never thought that the koo-jin
trend got our cafe to sell this good.
Of course.
This is on a koo-jin.
If it's...
Paew!
I'm kidding, friend.
But I'm gonna be honest.
You two look matched together.
I even got blushed seeing
you guys taking pictures.
If it's a real couple...
I guarantee...
our cafe...
The sale will surely doubled.
There, your real one is here.
The cafe is closed?
Anyway today...
I have to thank...
N'Paew so much for helping.
More like it's forced.
Then I'll transfer you
the fee for your work.
N'Paew can send your account number
to Kawee and he can send it to me.
It's alright.
The coffee I drank
and the cake I ate today...
it's more than the
amount of work I did.
Are you gonna
chat for a long time?
I'm tired so if it's gonna
take log, I'll sit and wait.
It won't be long,
I'll be home soon.
But...
I'm gonna give
Kawee a ride home first.
It's alright.
I can go home with Paew.
No way.
I picked you up this morning.
So I have to send you back.
Phu.
He said he can go back o his own.
Besides, today...
you're going for a dinner
with me, did you forget?
Let's hurry. come on.
Hurry up, Phu.
Let's go.
Please excuse me.
I don't like Phupha's ex.
What about you, Kok?
Do you like her?
No.
She seems...
if she wants to be my girlfriend,
I won't want it.
She has this somewhat a scary face.
Besides...
she seems jealous of
P'Phupha and P'Kawee.
Absolutely.
Look at her
expression and her eyes.
Paew, Kok!
Let's get a drink.
What's it gonna be?
Are you coming or not?
Then I'll go by myself.
I...
can't enter a bar for a year.
I'll send Pew in my place.
Don't sulk at me and...
look, Kok is coming with you.
Right?
Yes.
I'm coming.
This night will be heavy for sure.
You seem to care
so much about that kid.
I was the one who
picked him up today.
If I don't send him home,
it's a little disgusting act.
Nothing more than that, right?
You said you're hungry, right?
Shall I cook
something delicious for you?
You're still as adorable as before.
Then...
you can wait here.
- Just a minute, OK?
- OK.
N'Pew.
Long time no see.
There must be something
good that got you here.
It might be something
bad on the contrary.
Introduction is in order.
This is P'Gawin,
P'Kawee's older brother.
And this is N'Kok,
a waiter at P'Phupha's cafe.
And N'Tai is...
a friend, I guess. Or...
a boyfriend, I wonder.
A friend!
Answer at the same time,
no suspicious at all.
Something's bothering you, P'Tonmai?
What's with that face?
Nothing.
What am I not satisfied about?
Good then.
Because if you're
not satisfied, I think I might...
N'Kawee.
I'm very happy.
Good that more
people here. More fun.
Nong.
I'll have four cups please.
What are you smiling at?
Nothing.
I just feel that you look weird.
Or you wanna
sit just the two of you?
Why does it have
to be just the two of  us?
Well...
Come, come.
Drinks are here.
Let's drink.
Let me take care of it.
I'll help.
OK.
What's the matter?
Nothing, P.
Just a little stress.
It looks more than that.
When you're ready to tell me,
then you can tell me.
Brothers hugging each others,
They're brothers.
I saw that.
I didn't say anything.
Here you go.
This is Kawee's.
Come.
I'll drink with you tonight.
He must be very stressed.
I understand.
How can you?
Well...
the feeling of
having a crush on someone...
One person seems to want
to give another person hope.
In the end, though...
they can only be brothers.
I think he...
has someone he likes.
What? What are you looking at?
You're like him?
What?
I just understand the feeling
of someone having a crush.
How torturous it is.
You talk too much, just drink.
P'Tonmai.
Are you not gonna stop P'Gawin?
What about you? Don't you
think about stopping N'Kawee?
Your cooking...
looks appetizing as usual.
By the way,
how about your feelings?
Is it still the same?
I think...
we should just eat, shall we?
I can tell by watching you cook.
I know that your feeling is the
same and haven't changed.
Right?
So...
How did it goes
on finding a condo today?
You talk like...
you don't want me to stay.
I didn't mean it like that.
Well...
you're a woman.
Staying in a man's house...
it doesn't look nice.
Excuses.
We're in this age now.
No one cares about this kind of stuff.
You don't want me here, just say it.
If you want to stay, I don't mid.
I'm just afraid that
people will look badly at you.
The I'll stay.
I don't want to find a condo.
Please let me stay with you.
Up to you.
I don't want to eat anymore,
I'm gonna take a shower.
OK.
Uncle, you're drunk.
You have to go
to work tomorrow.
I can ask for a leave.
Give that to me.
I'm drinking with my brother.
Don't drink too
much or you'll get drunk.
You have to go to work.
I know, I only had a few cups.
I won't get drunk.
Why?
Why is there no one
worries about me like this?
This is so sad.
What are you doing?
Well...
To sleep with you.
I don't want to sleep alone.
Fah.
I think...
you should go back to your room.
Do you hate me that much that
you don't want to sleep with me?
I don't hate.
Don't hate, then why you
won't let me sleep with you?
Yes, Mai?
What's up?
Wasted?
OK, OK, OK.
What's wrong with Tonmai?
Tonmai told me
that Kawee is wasted.
I have to take him home.
I won't let you.
Why?
Why do you give so
much importance to this kid?
Fah.
I give priority to all my employees.
But this is too much,
let Tonmai do it. Why it must be you?
Fah.
Tonmai has someone
else he has to take home.
Phu...
Fah!
I think we should
stop arguing about this.
If it is as you said, then good.
Whatever you wanna do,
don't forget your promise to me.
I went out of
my way to come home.
Tonmai...
Stay calm.
Don't look.
Fuck it, we're already here.
I'll clear it up tomorrow.
Be mine, Uncle.
Kawee.
Wake up, Kawee.
It's morning.
P'Phupha!
How are you here?!
Why are you so shocked?
Who was it last night...
drink too much and got wasted?
I had to pick you
up and bring you home.
Is this your room?
Look carefully.
What time is it?!
I need to go shower now
or I'll be late for work.
What's the rush?
Are you fully conscious now?
Do you remember
what you did to me?
Don't tell me that...
I...
you?
Why did you uncover it?
It's alright?
I know when you did it...
you were very drunk.
So...
I'm not mad.
I don't the blame
on someone who's drunk.
I'm sorry.
Don't stress about it, Kawee.
Get out of my room!
Uncle.
Hear me out.
I'm not listening to you.
I said put on your
clothes and leave my room.
Don't make me lose my patience.
Kawee.
Yes?
Lift your face and look at me.
Look into my eyes.
I told you.
I'm not mad at you.
I know you did
because you were drunk.
I don't mind either
So...
we get to the way we're before, OK?
OK?
Behave normally.
Phu.
Are you creating the imaginary scene?
N'Kawee, if you finished
creating the imaginary scene
the you should get back to work.
Let me handle things at the counter.
Phu.
Where did you sleep last night?
I slept alone last night, you know.
When did you got back?
You didn't even wake me up.
Ponfah,  I think I
should get back to work.
Customers are full.
I'll help.
Let's eat outside,
I don't want to eat boxed food.
Fah.
This is my working time.
After lunch I need to go back in.
I don't want to eat boxed food,
please eat outside with me.
Fah.
I told you that
today is my working time.
How can you expect me to go out?
But this is your cafe,
you go whenever you want
and do whatever you want.
It is because this is my cafe...
that I have to go back
in and brew coffee for my
customers after my lunch.
There are so many customers waiting.
There's a customer, right, Kawee?
Alright, I'll go in
and brew coffee for them.
Thank you for letting me know.
N'Kawee.
Yes?
Let me warn you about something.
About that imaginary thing,
just let it be imaginary.
Don't think more than that.
I fear you might get sad.
Phu will never like someone like you.
Like me how?
Unusual unlike me.
You should know what is real...
and what is false.
Do you wanna have lunch?
Please.
The other box is mine.
Don't steal it.
It's not nice.
I won't.
Because I...
doesn't like to eat old stuff.
I should just throw it away.
Because no matter what, old stuff...
is not delicious anymore.
P'Phupha, he...
might not want to eat old stuff too.
Because new stuff...
is a lot more delicious.
Thank you.
How will you go back today, Kok?
Will Tai come pick you up like usual?
Yes.
Then go home safely,
see you tomorrow.
Thank you.
Kawee.
Let's go home then.
P'Phupha.
From now on...
I probably won't be
working at your cafe anymore.
From now on...
[Next Episode]
I probably won't be working
at your cafe anymore.
Good that he's gone.
So you won't have to feel
courteous to get back to me.
What do you
mean by feel  courteous?
The reason you're afraid to
show your true feelings for me...
is out of courteous to him.
You know he likes you.
I'v decided to sell our cafe.
Is this true?
Why?
I didn't succeeded.
P'Ponfah?
You already have a cafe...
but still went to work
at Phupha's cafe.
You must really like him.
How did you seduce him
that got him to pick you?
♫ And I will take you away ♫
♫ From this soil ♫
♫ Take you, you and me ♫
♫ We will have our time ♫
♫ Just the two of us ♫
♫ I'm only asking for you to
trust and confident with me ♫
♫ We will go together ♫
♫ We will hold hands
and walk away till the end ♫
♫ Till we lose our breath ♫
♫ Thank you so much for everything
that you made go through ♫
♫ You made me realize that I have value ♫
♫ Like the days when you are by my side ♫
♫ It's good when in times I have you ♫
♫ Whether it's happiness or sadness,
it doesn't matter ♫
♫ Just having you standing here ♫
♫ Stay here and we'll go together ♫
♫ And I will take you away ♫