=Good Luck=
=Episode 10=
Lu Jingzhao, what are you doing?
You've completely ruined
the Gu family's reputation,
especially on such a significant day.
(Never mind,
I'll just get through this first.)
Consider this my free help for Mr. Shi.
The information is in this scroll.
Do you think you're a strategist?
I don't need it.
Of course, if you have any concerns,
you don't have to open it.
My good intentions
are already given.
(Shout "I'm a fool" three times,
and I'll solve everything for you.)
Shi Lai, what's going on?
What do you think?
He's utterly embarrassed.
Security,
throw him out!
I'm a fool! I'm a fool! I'm a fool!
He has a mental illness?
Are you out of your mind?
Come over here!
This guy
has gone mad!
Get out of the Gu family!
(Are you crazy?)
(You might be good at stone gambling,)
(but I'm an expert)
(in understanding human nature.)
Isn't this Mr. Lu Jingzhao?
Yeah, that's him.
Remember,
make sure you film everything.
I want him discredited
in all of Yongjing.
I can't believe
the Lu family would stoop
to using such tactics!
They're so manipulative!
Lu Jingzhao,
anything else to say?
No.
No!
This is all slander!
Your video must be fake!
Is your video real then?
Just get out already!
You're embarrassing yourself!
Yeah, this is ridiculous!
This is pure slander!
The second son of the Lu family
would do something like this!
So shameless!
Slandering others!
Kneel!
Brother!
He deserves it!
Exactly! He should've been kicked out
long ago!
Master Nine,
Mr. Shi,
it's my fault for not disciplining
my younger brother,
which led to this disgraceful behavior.
It's truly a shame for the Lu family.
Brother!
You're a disgrace!
Get out of here right now!
Shi Lai,
this isn't over.
Mr. Shi,
I'm so sorry.
(A smart move to save face.)
Don't say that, Mr. Lu.
It's not your fault,
so no need to apologize.
You really are generous.
The scene got a bit out of hand,
but I'll definitely visit you
to apologize later.
I'm sorry, Master Nine,
I've spoiled your mood.
You have some ability, kid.
I wasn't wrong about you.
You flatter me.
You want the official
stone appraiser certification, right?
As long as you pass the written test…
Master Zhou Tong?
Isn't he the most famous
stone appraiser in Yongjing?
I've heard he comes from
a family of appraisers
and has been in the business
for almost 40 years without losing a case.
But he's known to be eccentric
and doesn't interact much with people.
- Didn't expect him to be here today.
- You don't say.
Master Zhou is well-known
and also the chief appraiser
of the Jade Society.
Perhaps,
he's here because of
Master Lin Jiang's grandson.
So that's Master Zhou Tong.
The Jade Society Stone Appraiser Exam
results are out!
- The new rising star in the jade world...
- 33 points.
(Appraiser Exam)
...came last.
Lin Jiang's grandson only scored
33 points!
What a joke!
Yeah, so embarrassing!
What a disgrace to Master Lin's name!
He's trash.
The biggest joke
in the stone appraising world!
He really is trash.
Master Nine,
please give me another chance.
Alright,
since
Master Zhou Tong,
the chief appraiser of Yongjing,
is here,
let's have a
raw stone appraisal competition.
If you win,
the certification
is yours.
Otherwise,
the Jade Society will never certify you.
Do you dare to compete?
Alright, how do we compete?
Shi Lai.
Trust me.
Master Zhou Tong, what do you say?
I was here just for fun,
but now you want me to work?
I've heard of your fame,
and seeing you today,
you truly live up to it.
This is too far from me.
If I could have the honor
of competing with you
and learning from you,
it would truly be
a life-changing experience for me.
Cut the formalities, don't be so poetic.
You're
a rising genius;
no need to be so humble.
I prefer to see your
wild side.
You flatter me.
What I mean is,
dealing with someone like you
won't be free.
You're Lin Jiang's grandson, right?
Yes.
Even your grandfather
might not have been able to beat me.
How much can you have learned from him?
You're right.
I'll learn from you today.
On behalf of Master Nine,
I'll host today's competition.
It will be five rounds,
best of three.
The rounds will test different aspects:
identification, cutting, feeling, faking,
and guessing.
These are the skills the Jade Society uses
to assess an appraiser's overall abilities.
To ensure fairness,
Master Nine
will act as the judge.
The first round is identification.
These are all Hetian jade rough stones.
Each of you
will choose one,
and whoever picks the higher value
wins.
(Shi Lai has always appraised jadeite,)
(but I wonder
if he understands Hetian jade?)
Master Zhou is an expert
in Hetian jade identification.
Shi Lai will definitely
lose the first round.
You have five minutes
to pick your stones.
The competition begins now!
Gentlemen, please.
(Round 1 - Identification)
Time's up.
Now, cut the two stones.
Shi Lai clearly picked his stone
based on Master Zhou's,
since the size and color
are almost identical.
He's just copying Master Zhou.
There's no way he can beat him.
He can't beat him at all.
Master Zhou's stone has
light-colored autumn pear skin,
golden
and elegant,
with a delicate texture—
truly
a top-tier stone.
Impressive!
Master Nine, you flatter me!
There's no suspense here!
As expected from Master Zhou,
he won the first round easily.
Shi Lai's sure to lose!
Shi Lai's stone is darker
with more spots,
and it has
rare watergrass inclusions
that resemble autumn pear skin blemishes.
From a collector's perspective,
Shi Lai's stone is much more unique,
with higher ornamental value.
First round,
Shi Lai wins.
Didn't expect this kid to actually win!
He didn't just guess, did he?
(Round 2 - Cutting)
One cut makes you rich,
one cut bankrupts you.
The second round
is cutting.
You'll each choose a place
to cut your rough stone,
and the result will be determined
by the cut.
(This is a fish scale window,)
(which could be a trap window.)
(It looks clear,)
(but it might have been tampered with.)
(I'd better)
(be cautious.)
Cut.
Full green.
Is he still pretending?
He's no match for Master Zhou!
(This looks like a typical flower window,)
(but it's actually a trap window)
(with a small opening)
(and tricky placement.)
(It's quite misleading.)
(What should I do?)
How long has it been?
I think he's just stalling.
Yeah!
He has no skills, yet he's boasting.
He's embarrassing the Lin family!
What's wrong?
Are you scared?
Shi Lai, do you want to take a break?
Miss Gu, if you're worried
about your boyfriend,
you should just let him admit defeat,
then I can go back
and rest.
But this money
is too easy for me to earn.
Master Nine has been too generous.
Just admit defeat!
(From the surface green,)
(this is most likely from the Huika site…)
(a skin green.)
Skin green is a type of green
that grows on the surface of jade,
and it's one of the riskiest forms.
The "immortal-cutting green"
is another form of skin green.
The owner of the rough stone
often cuts it through the green streaks
to show the green in the middle,
creating two full green faces.
People praise this
for its precision and skill,
calling it immortal-cutting green.
(At Huika,)
(skin)
(and floating colors)
(are common.)
(Many people mistakenly think
green skin is full color,)
(but when cut,)
(it often just reveals
a thin transitional layer)
(or white-bottomed green.)
(Since it's just one cut,)
(I'll bet it all on this one.)
♪The stage of competition♪
♪I'm the king who can't be defined♪
♪Every step of my growth♪
♪Is the declaration of my victory♪
♪The fire of a comeback♪
♪Is burning in my blood♪
♪The pain of growth♪
♪Forges my pride♪
♪The pride of competition♪
♪The field of competition♪
♪I'm writing my own legend♪
♪The dream of jade♪
♪I'm carving glorious chapters♪
♪They say stones can't speak♪
♪But I've heard their secrets♪
♪Beneath the rough exterior♪
♪There are brilliant treasures hidden♪
♪Every bet♪
♪Is a promise for the future♪
♪On the journey of growth♪
♪It's a promise for the future♪
♪The heartbeat of jade♪
♪Follows the rhythm of the cutting machine♪
♪The hot blood of a comeback♪
♪Is as precious as jade♪
♪The moment it begins♪
♪Is where dreams and reality meet♪
♪The journey of a comeback♪
♪I speak with my strength
and prove with my achievements♪
♪The passion for cutting stones♪
♪Ignites the flame in my heart♪
♪The challenges of growth♪
♪I never shrink back
but march forward bravely♪
♪The glory of competition♪
♪Should be fought for with my own hands♪
♪The chapter of a comeback♪
♪I'm the most passionate author♪
♪When fortune smiles♪
♪What I'm gambling on is not just luck♪
♪It's my promising future within sight♪
♪Every decision♪
♪Is the mark of my growth♪
♪In the waves of competition♪
♪I'm the brave warrior riding the waves♪
♪In the sky of a comeback♪
♪I'm the brightest star♪
♪When fortune smiles♪
♪At this moment♪
♪I'm the master of my own destiny♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)