[English subtitles are available]
[Her Fantastic Adventures]
Why are you still standing here?
Call the doctor.
Young Master Duan said he's fine.
But it doesn't mean he's actually fine.
Go get the doctor.
Okay.
That's right.
Tighten the core. Adjust your breathing.
Faster.
Keep it up. Faster.
3 minutes and 39 seconds.
When I was about your age,
I ran much faster.
Alright.
I think it's good enough.
At least you did better than yesterday.
Chunjiao.
Going above and beyond is the biggest
breakthrough.
Come on.
Again.
[Episode 5]
Okay, hold on.
Hang in there, Chunjiao.
Hurry!
-Mom.
-Hold on.
-It's too heavy.
Don't talk.
You'll be deflated if you talk.
Don't lose the strength in your back.
Focus.
Or else you'll get hurt!
Dad. Help!
My mom is killing me.
Chunjiao.
Believe in yourself.
You can do it!
Come on! Try a bit harder!
Faster. Lift your feet.
Don't lose your strength.
Tighten the core.
Hang in there!
Dad.
I want to quit.
Can I just be your daughter?
Ok. Ok. Ok.
That's it for today.
Here, baby girl.
You did much better than your dad.
If your mom sat in the back,
I couldn't even pull her.
Let's leave aside your results for now.
Did you notice
that nothing in this world
can happen overnight?
Just like the bond between me and you
was cultivated over many lifetimes.
That's why
if you don't work hard, you won't succeed.
Do you understand?
I'll just simply change the time.
Right?
How dare you two come back at this time?
What time is it?
It's just past eight.
What did you say?
Can't you see there's no one on the street?
Well...
Maybe my watch is broken.
It says it's past eight o'clock.
You've got to be kidding me.
Stop pretending.
Don't you smell it?
It's fine that you went to have hot pot
until the place closed.
You didn't go to training this afternoon.
You even took her to ride a roller coaster.
How did you find out?
How many times have I told you?
She's an athlete.
Even a small injury
could impact her whole life.
Are you out of your mind?
Can't you behave?
Stop indulging her in food and games.
Stop spoiling her, okay?
It's like I'm the only bad one in the
family.
The kid needs to take a break sometimes.
What's the big deal?
How about this?
From now on, I'll be the bad guy with you.
Alright?
You are the bad guy.
Stay out of this.
-OK. I'm a bad guy.
-Let's go.
-I'm the only bad guy in the family.
-Hurry up.
Dad.
If I win this qualifying round,
I can bring glory to our ancestors.
What are you talking about?
You've always been our family's greatest
pride.
Dad,
don't be late this afternoon.
If I win,
can you reward me with a grand prize?
No problem.
I'll come home early today.
If you win,
I'll buy you a skirt, okay?
Dad.
I don't want a skirt.
Can you please not go?
Stay at home with me.
It's getting late.
I got to get going.
Remember what I told you.
Come on. Come on.
I'm rooting for you.
Dad.
Don't leave.
I will never see you again if you leave.
Dad, please don't leave.
What are you talking about?
Don't forget what I said.
Great power produces miracles.
-I'm leaving.
-Dad.
Don't go.
My Lady, you're awake.
Where am I?
Why am I not home yet?
If I'm not at home,
who's going to help Mom change the gas
bottle.
My Lady.
You're at home. You're at home.
I'll tell Master that you're awake.
It's all my fault.
The thief who attacked Miss Gu escaped.
How is Miss Gu feeling?
I just received the news.
She's awake. She's alright.
She was just frightened.
But
it was dangerous for you
to tackle the Right Guardian alone last
night.
Looks like the Right Guardian was the one
who attacked me at the food festival.
Did the Right Guardian
stay in Changqing just to kill you?
He was injured by my Qilin Bow.
I think he must be holding a grudge.
But this person was able to
come and go in Qingfeng Restaurant freely,
and not be discovered.
He ought to be a pro.
Since he didn't get his way,
I'm sure he'll take revenge later.
We just have to be on our guard.
But this incident is related to Miss Gu.
Don't you think it's strange?
I need you to do something for me.
Guard Xing.
What's going on?
Chairman Gu,
Young Master has been worried about Miss Gu.
He was afraid that Mantra Sect would
come back,
so he sent these Wuyi Guards here
to protect the Gu Residence.
I see.
He is so considerate.
Thank you.
Dad.
I thought it's easy to come
so it would be easy to go back.
I guess I oversimplified it.
I'll have to pull myself together from
now on.
You should visit Mom more often when you
have the time.
After what I've been through, I believe
everything now.
You might be watching me somewhere now.
Take good care of Mom.
I might have gone too far this time.
I have to take the responsibility.
I'll ask Duan Yu to marry Gu Qingqiao,
and set up a successful business in Qingfeng
Restaurant before I go back.
My Lady,
what are you talking about?
Nothing. Nothing.
I'm planning for the future.
Why are you here
in such a hurry?
Young Master Duan sent a lot of Wuyi Guards here.
A lot?
I'll have to check it out.
They are everywhere.
Si.
Miss Gu.
Young Master didn't show up.
He's still investigating the Mantra Sect.
He told us
that you made a great contribution
in catching the Mantra Sect.
In order to prevent any more attack from
the remnants of the Mantra Sect,
he sent dozens of Wuyi Guards to come here
to protect you.
Dozens of Guards are here to protect me.
This is too much.
I just wanted to say
I really appreciate it.
If Miss Gu need anything,
they are at your disposal day and night.
Tu Jia, step forward!
Yes.
Hello, Miss Gu.
This is a female Wuyi Guard.
She masters martial arts and medicine.
It'll be easier for you to go anywhere
with her around.
OK.
Just call me Qiao.
It's just perfect
that I need a friend who's good at fighting.
At Qingfeng Restaurant last time, we were all
on our duties.
I wasn't able to take good care of you.
Thank you for your Chairman's kindness.
And thank you for protecting me.
From now on, we are a family.
If you need any food or clothes,
just ask the housekeeper.
It's me. Me.
Si.
I want to ask you something.
What's the matter?
Do you know Magistrate Du's
daughter, Du Ruoyun?
No, I don't.
Then your Young Master and her?
You are the only one
in his heart.
Are you sure?
Definitely sure.
Dongxi.
Get Xing Si a silver VIP card
of Qingfeng Restaurant.
Yes, My Lady.
Thank you, Miss Gu.
Shaoyi,
weren't you sent back to Jizhou Academy?
Yes.
Then why are you back?
I heard
you were kidnapped by Mantra cultists.
That's why I came back to see you.
Thanks to Miss Gu's help that day.
Or else you might never see me again.
My Lady.
Everything is ready.
Where are you going?
The Gu Residence to show our gratitude.
I'll go with you.
Why are you being so nice?
You even want to go with me.
I heard that Miss Gu
really wants to marry Uncle.
I want to see
who exactly she is.
They don't need to be dramatic.
Hello, Miss Gu.
Young Master Shaoyi.
Hello, Miss Du.
What a grand scene.
There are so many Wuyi Guards here to
protect you.
You are like a well-respected god.
Shaoyi.
That Shaoyi became this Shaoyi.
Miss Gu, what's the matter?
You are the Shaoyi who can't do
anything but cause trouble.
What did you say?
Your uncle said that.
No way.
My uncle wouldn't say something like that.
Who is your uncle?
Tu...Tu Jia.
Tell her who I am.
Yes, Young Master Shaoyi.
Miss Gu.
This is the Young Master of the Duan family.
Young Master Shaoyi's father
is Young Master Duan's brother.
How could you be Duan Yu's nephew?
What do you mean by that?
Are you crazy?
I'm really crazy.
I think both of you are crazy.
Xing Si.
I didn't expect you to be so knowledgeable.
Thank you for your compliment.
You're being too kind.
I meant you are flirtatious.
Young Master, it's getting late.
Let's go to Nanny Xu.
You're feeling guilty?
What are you talking about?
I just write dialogue novels to make a
living.
You mean I didn't give you enough money?
Of course not.
Alright.
Hit me or punish me.
I can take the blame.
I wrote that you and Miss Du
A perfect couple.
A hero and a beauty.
Xing Si.
You mentioned about a genius, an immortal,
and a hero.
Which one is referring to me?
The Duan and Du family of Changqing have
been family friends for generations.
Du Ruoyun is my sister.
What were you thinking?
Well...
What are you talking about?
I think the dialogue novel
was about yourself.
No. No. No.
Of course not.
Young Master, it's all imaginary.
Imaginary?
Why are you panicking?
I'm not panicking.
All right.
I'll stop teasing you.
I don't blame you.
Keep writing.
I...
But I have two conditions.
Don't worry about two.
Even if there's ten, I'll say yes.
Okay.
One.
Show me the dialogue novel first after
you finish.
Two.
I'll only take 90% of the money
from selling the dialogue novels.
Young Master,
I can show you the dialogue novel.
But the money...
50%.
Young Master Shaoyi,
I'm so sorry.
You looked like
an old friend of mine.
I was surprised at first.
I was so baffled.
What's baffled?
It means I was confused.
Yes.
It means a blackout happened in my brain.
It means suddenly you don't know what's
going on.
Miss Du is really smart.
You're rich, beautiful and smart.
Although your wordings confuse me,
it's really interesting.
So what brings you here?
I heard from Miss Ruoyun that you saved
her life.
We're here to thank you.
I came along with her.
Miss Gu faced the danger calmly at Qingfeng
Restaurant yesterday.
You saved my life.
I'm very grateful.
It was a natural reaction that day.
Don't worry about it, Miss Du.
It was a matter of life and death.
Anyone would help in that scenario.
I didn't expect
that although Miss Gu is not smart,
she's quite brave.
But there must be a reason
why so many people are protecting you.
Even if I'm not that smart,
I can tell the difference
between protection and surveillance.
Miss Gu,
I really like your personality.
If you don't mind,
we can keep in touch more often.
When I saw you at Qingfeng Restaurant
that day,
I liked you too.
But it was not appropriate to kiss up to
the daughter of a Magistrate.
Kiss up to?
It means it's not appropriate to flatter
you.
Miss Gu, you're treating me like a stranger.
You saved my life.
I'm willing to kiss up to you.
Let's kiss up to each other in the future.
OK.
I like straightforward gals.
We are about the same age.
Don't call me My Lady.
Just call me Qiao from now on.
I'll call you Ruoyun.
Okay.
Qiao.
You used to call me by my name.
Then you call me Gu Qingqiao.
I'll call you Duan Shaoyi.
OK.
I like straightforward gals.
Do you think I'm a unique
Qingliu here?
Then I'll call you Qingliu.
There's Qing in it anyway.
Qingliu,
I heard you were desperate to marry
my uncle.
Why is that the case?
I wasn't desperate.
You were the desperate one, weren't you?
I...
Shaoyi and I...
and Duan Yu and Xing Si grew up together.
When I was little,
I already decided to marry Duan Yu.
As I've gotten older in the past two years,
he showed less interest in me.
Duan Yu is so ungrateful.
How could he not be interested in a good
girl?
Who else could he be interested in?
Get out and study abroad.
A jerk.
Study abroad?
Jerk?
That...
That means he doesn't deserve Ruoyun.
That's right.
Jerk!
Ruoyun.
Do you think Duan Yu will change his mind?
No.
He will always treat me as his sister.
Love between a man and woman is destined.
We can't fight for it.
I know.
Why are you still clinging to him?
I'm doing it to piss him off,
and to deprive him of freedom.
Qingliu,
aren't you going to marry my uncle?
Why are you asking so many questions?
At first,
marrying Duan Yu was just a wish.
But things got more complicated.
I owe Gu Qingqiao an explanation.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I'll explain it to you later.
But Duan Yu never said
he wanted to marry me.
My Dad arranged it.
Jerk!
[Arrest Warrant]
The government is making arrests again.
Look.
That's quite a lot of money as the reward.
What's that smell?
Why does it smell so good?
It's a naan.
Look, they're queuing up to buy naans.
My Lady
do you want to buy some naans?
In this way,
Da wouldn't need to
cook for the Wuyi Guards.
OK.
Let's buy some more.
Give some to Young Master Duan.
He stole money! Catch the thief!
Run!
Where do you think you are going?
The naan is too light.
Please forgive me. Spare me your life.
I didn't steal your money.
It's a really hard hit.
Cut the crap.
Changqing, Changqing. Changqing Forever.
When dealing with guys like you
who destroy the comfort and harmony
of Changqing people,
no one should be merciful.
Where is the money bag?
Give it to me.
Send him to a yamen.
Take him away.
Can you stop them from following me?
It's like hunting wolves.
Xing Si.
Yes, Young Master.
Everyone, follow me.
Yes.
Let's go.
My Lady.
Miss Gu.
Please.
Coming.
Auntie Xu, what's going on?
I'm coming.
Stay away from me.
Long story short.
I'm not good enough to check
the Four Pillars of Destiny between you two.
I can't tie or untie it.
How about
giving them back to you?
We'll each go our own way.
Auntie Xu, don't go.
What do you mean?
How could you return them?
Miss,
I returned them because you look like
a nice person.
But look at this pair of
strong legs I've had for years,
they are crippled because of you.
Why don't you do me a favor?
Please...just let me go.
-Be careful.
Did you encounter any difficulties?
Just say it.
Alright.
Since we've come to this point,
I'll make it clear to you today.
But
give me back my cane first.
Since I got your Four Pillars of Destiny,
I've fallen flat on my face.
I got kicked by a horse.
Water got stuck in my teeth. I got choked by
the wind while talking.
Look how miserable I am.
Your Four Pillars of Destiny
are all from out of this world.
The combination
indicates a curse.
You can't untie it.
If you take different roads,
it will be a bigger curse.
You can't solve it.
So,
you two should find someone else.
I'm just not good enough for this.
You need to find a master.
Maybe there's a solution.
That's quite a profound statement.
But it may be just bad luck.
It's not as dramatic as you said.
Why don't you try again?
Miss,
you look like a nice person,
but your Four Pillars of Destiny show
that you would die young.
I heard you came back to life before.
I can't handle the case.
As for Young Master Duan,
your Four Pillars of Destiny are even more
powerful.
There's no Official Star in the year, month
and date pillar.
That means he has no marriage fortune.
The hour pillar brings the peach blossom
and wood. Seven kills end the life.
The God of Slaughter couldn't
be stopped by any God and Buddha.
The sign of early death is haunted by gods
and ghosts.
The God of Slaughter who orders seven kills
is still alive.
It sounds like a curse.
But I think
we are a good match.
You can't say that.
If you were to get married,
the marriage shall be unfortunate with both
of you suffering.
Bringing bad luck to the husband and wife
might also impact the people around you.
Look at me.
I am a living example.
I've never believed in gods or ghosts.
The Four Pillars of Destiny are just
a formality.
Don't you worry about it.
Auntie Xu,
do you have a way to solve it?
Miss,
I'd advise you to give up.
Auntie Xu, it's our fate to meet you.
If you don't give me a solution,
I'll come by to have tea with you every day.
Never mind.
In that case,
there is a solution.
I mean there is a possibility.
It may be possible or not possible.
Don't beat around the bush.
Just tell me.
The Acacia Tree on the east side of
the city.
It's spiritual.
But you have to pray by yourselves.
As for how it goes,
it really depends on fate.
Let's go.
The Acacia Tree.
The Avatar.
This tree must be thousands of years old.
It's over 1,300 years old.
The tree had originally died
but somehow,
when everybody made a wish,
it's silently growing again.
A withered tree comes to life again.
Amazing.
What does it say?
One heart, one person.
Not to part for ever.
What about this one?
Grey hair meets grey hair.
Let's meet again in the next life.
They were written for those who passed away.
Miss Gu.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I was just thinking that
an elderly couple with grey hair
came to this tree to make a wish.
It must have been so romantic.
My Lady.
Let's put our Four Pillars of Destiny
under this tree,
and pray for God's blessing.
Okay.
My Lady.
I finally got it.
What a coincidence.
Dongxi.
You came just in time.
Everything is ready.
I just need to get down on my knees.
Don't look.
It won't work if you look.
Okay.
I won't look.
♫In the noise♫
Okay.
♫I glanced back briefly.♫
Why?
♫You looked up♫
♫The fireworks shine across the night sky♫
It absorbs the spirit of heaven and earth.
Didn't you see it?
The cloth hanging on the trees are exposed
to the wind and sun every day.
♫The night breeze blew gently♫
The words on the edges are fading.
♫Even the birds stopped flying♫
It's safer to bury them in the soil.
♫I remember how gentle you were♫
Bury it deep.
♫I'm afraid I won't see it in my dreams♫
What are you waiting for?
Give me our Four Pillars of Destiny.
♫Your smile♫
Okay.
♫Until the end♫
♫Love doesn't need to be pieced together♫
♫Feel it with my heart♫
♫Missing you from autumn to winter♫
♫Even if I turned grey♫
♫Meeting you is all my reason♫
Done.
♫I'm obsessed with finding you in the crowd♫
♫No matter how far it is♫
Don't get on your knees.
♫I'll stay by your side♫
You're wearing white.
I'll kneel for you this time.
Next time, you'll do it for me.
♫Love doesn't need to be pieced together♫
♫Feel it with my heart♫
I just immersed myself in the essence
of the Holy Tree.
I feel so much more energized.
♫Missing you from autumn to winter♫
♫Even if I turned grey♫
I'm in such a good mood
after clearing up this problem.
I want to fly freely.
♫Meeting you is all my reason♫
♫I'm obsessed with finding you in the crowd♫
♫No matter how far it is♫
♫I'll stay by your side♫
I want to fly a kite.
A kite?
Yes.
The paper kite.
OK.
I'll do whatever you want.
You bought this with a lot of money.
Do you like this dialogue novel?
Of course.
I cried and laughed every day reading it.
I want to tell you a secret.
Go ahead.
What do you want this time?
Nothing.
I'm thinking about the business of this
dialogue novel.
Tell me.
Do you know who wrote this?
Who?
Xing Si.
Which Xing Si?
Who else could there be?
Our brother Xing Si.
That nerd knew how to write dialogue novels.
And it's so good.
Are you surprised?
Are you amazed?
Oh my god.
By the way,
What was it Gu Qingqiao said?
It's Qingliu.
Duan Yu.
Let's compete.
Let's see whose kite flies higher.
The loser has to treat the winner
to some beer and skewers.
Some beer and skewers?
That's right.
It's about drinking and barbecuing.
I see.
Sword Roast Whole Lamb, right?
That's one of
my mom's specialty.
Miss Gu.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Mom.
Hang on.
I'll be back soon.
Duan Yu.
Come on.
Sure.
I won't have mercy.
That's cheating.
I forgot the ancient people knew how to
climb walls and fly.
See?
I told you.
A man with skills won't easily admit defeat.
My kite!
What happened to everything going well?
A broken kite will bring bad luck.
If you can't save it, just buy another one.
No.
Duan Yu, pull your kite.
Pull it.
Yes, that's it.
No.
It's too windy.
I can't hold it much longer.
Come and help me.
I can't hold it anymore.
Dongxi.
You are really good at embroidery.
You're very crafty.
Don't My Lady know how to embroider as well?
Why are you asking me to do it?
There's a lot to be said for giving a pouch.
What's the meaning behind it?
If a girl meets her soul mate,
she must embroider a pouch for him
to keep his heart.
This means Dongxi has a crush on someone?
My Lady, don't say that.
But I'm planning to make this pouch
for my mom.
Well,
I want to give one to my friend's Mom,
but my embroidery is too ugly.
It's not that presentable.
Could you do me a favor?
I'm happy to do anything
for My Lady.
It's secretly satisfying.
You even know this.
Dongxi, you're so cute.
I'll miss you.
You don't need to miss me.
I'll go with you when you get married.
You're so nice.
It's great to have you here.
The new My Lady is really nice.
The new Lady?
Was the old Lady not good?
Her health used to be quite fragile.
She didn't go out every day.
She coughed all night in winter.
I was heartbroken.
Madam Zhang was looking for medicine
everywhere.
We were worried about her every day.
Now,
My Lady who came back to life
is so energetic like a deer.
Even if your brain isn't working properly,
we are happy.
My...
Is my brain not functioning that well?
You don't remember anything from the past.
And you keep saying things we don't
understand.
So,
Master thought Young Master Duan was
interested in you.
He wanted to marry you off.
So you wanted to marry me off
because my brain wasn't working properly.
What else?
My goodness.
How could you say that?
One takes on the color of his company.
This idiom does make sense.
Why did Madam Zhang
go look for medicine everywhere?
Madam Zhang is Madam's dowry maid.
Madam had obstructed labour when giving
birth to My Lady.
Madam Zhang was entrusted with taking
care of
Master and My Lady before Madam passed away.
She said she could only leave
when Master marries again or My Lady marries.
But it turned out that Master didn't want
to marry again.
He said he was afraid that you could be
bullied by the stepmother.
Later,
Madam Zhang has been taking care of the Gus.
When Master was doing business during the
day,
Madam Zhang supported the family at home.
Everyone in the mansion respects her.
Even Master respects her a little.
Everyone in the Gu family is good,
so you're also a good person.
So,
I must make the Gu family happy.
Of course.
Oh, Dongxi.
What are you going to do?
My goodness.
Who's swearing again?
Or crossing the tribulation?
Eunuch Thunder and Grandma Rain.
Duan Yu asked me to come.
He is the one you should punish.
Please forgive me. Please forgive me.
Xing Si.
Young Master.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Young Master, is there any taboo on this?
A taboo?
What taboo?
Then why did the lightning strike me,
and why was the rain pouring on me?
You've done too many bad things during
the day.
Young Master.
Why did you want to dig this wish card?
What do you think?
Is it because Miss Gu is the Star of
Rebellion?
She wants to use the spiritual power of the
Acacia tree
to destroy the Duan family.
I'm just curious about
what wish she made.
[Life can be bitter, but we can be sweet]
[Have a baby soon]
Is there anything wrong?
No.
Miss Gu fell off the cliff.
I discovered that
she didn't know martial arts.
Young Master risked your life to save
Miss Gu.
Is it because
you like her?
What are you talking about?
I'm not as flirtatious as you.
Oh my.
See.
You're learning to talk like her.
What did you learn?
Flirtatious.
Cut the nonsense.
Give me the dialogue novel and the money
from it.
Young Master,
I'll go take a bath.
I'll get going.
I...
I need to take my conical hat.
Life can be bitter,
but we can be sweet.
Young Master asked me to bring you the kite.
It's exactly the same.
You found it?
It's a new one.
Is that for me?
Or is he asking me to fly kites again?
It is for you.
He didn't say he wanted to ask me out.
No.
Fine.
I'll bring a kite,
and invite Ruoyun and Shaoyi to go wild.
Invite Miss Du.
Go wild.
Why can't I?
You mean flying a kite, right?
What else?
Let's go wild.
Let's do it.
Can you stop making a fuss?
By the way Si,
could you go to the kitchen
to get some pastries from Da
to bring home for your Young Master?
It smells so good.
Chef Da,
Miss Gu asked me to pick up some pastries
for Young Master.
I... I'll get it ready.
Thank you.