[English subtitles are available]
[Her Fantastic Adventures]
According to the tip-off,
someone like Miss Gu went north.
Can we believe it?
Even if there's a slim hope,
I have to give it a try.
Duan Yu.
Miss Du.
Why are you here?
I came to see Shaoyi.
I didn't expect you were here.
We're leaving.
Please take care of Shaoyi.
These are three amulets.
I got them from Shangqing Temple.
Take them with you.
Three?
If you see Gu Qingqiao,
please give it to her for me.
I owe her one.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you, Miss Du.
By the way,
I wrote
the third and fourth seasons of
"Young Master falls in love with me".
You can read them when you are bored.
Thank you.
Also,
during our absence,
Miss Du, please take care.
It's getting late.
We're leaving.
[Episode 13]
My Lady.
Where are we going?
To see Shaoyi.
Miss Du.
Have you seen Young Master Shaoyi?
No.
I was about to visit him.
He was here just now.
He disappeared
after I came back with the thing he wanted.
Where could an injured man go?
Yeah.
Where could he go?
Young Master Shaoyi.
[Miao's Tavern]
Where are we going?
To Xiling.
To find the Black Wood Human-shaped Sword.
Okay.
Come out.
You are talented.
Young Master.
What should we do now?
Young Master Shaoyi can't leave the city with us.
Why can't I?
When my uncle was my age,
he went around the whole country.
He established Changqing Chamber of Commerce
and made a name in the Martial Arts World.
I can do it too.
Shaoyi.
This trip is unusual.
We might run into the Sacred Blood Sect.
If anything happened to you,
I would be ashamed in front of your father.
I hid under the carriage for three days
in case you sent me back.
I can't even straighten my back.
Think about it.
You need a team to send me back.
If something happens,
who will be responsible?
You are a genius.
A genius.
The Moon Wolf Tribe will make deals
in less than five days.
We are running out of time.
Mr. Qi.
I'll leave Shaoyi to you.
Okay.
Uncle.
Thank you.
For what?
You can hang under the carriage for three days.
You are impressive.
Fine.
I'll send a message to His Lordship.
Please say something good for me.
Uncle.
I'm actually on your side.
I'll stall Mr. Qi for you.
Do whatever you want.
What's wrong?
Are you still thinking about Duan Yu?
No.
I'm not.
Don't talk nonsense.
You still won't admit it?
I've come this far with you.
You should tell me
what's going on
with you and Duan Yu?
I...
I'm the Star of Rebellion.
Star of Rebellion?
What is the Star of Rebellion?
Duan Yu said I would bring destruction to the Duan Residence.
This is outrageous.
He wanted to kill someone because of this rumor.
Alright, stop talking about him.
I don't want to talk about him now.
For me,
the most important thing is to find the Four Treasures.
Why?
Look at the petals on my leg.
Two of them turned black.
I will die if they keep turning black.
Is the Black Wood Human-shaped Sword one of the Four Treasures?
Master said
it was.
Okay.
I will find it for you.
Why are you so serious all of a sudden?
I'm still not used to it.
Because you saved my life.
So your life is
of great importance to me.
That's too much.
Behave yourself.
Qingshui Town is over there.
We'll see the Xiling Sect when we go up to the mountain.
I don't know whether the Black Wood Human-shaped Sword that master mentioned
is real or not.
This sword is very influential.
The Black Wood Human-shaped Sword is the treasure of the Xiling Sect.
It is said that the founder of the Xiling Sect
was invincible thanks to this sword.
But no one has ever known how this sword looks.
Fifteen years ago,
the Sacred Blood Sect massacred Xiling because of this sword.
That's why the sword disappeared.
Rumor has it that
this sword has been destroyed in the war.
Someone also said that the sword fell into the hands of the Sacred Blood Sect.
The Sacred Blood Sect again?
The Sacred Blood Sect is really a disaster.
Some said this sword was still in Xiling
and was guarded secretly.
It could be possible that the sword is still in Xiling.
At this time,
we can only trust Master.
Thank you.
Thank you, Master.
I was rude just now.
Please forgive me.
Amitabha.
When we go up to the mountain tomorrow,
we need to change our outfits.
We are so popular that we need to disguise ourselves?
Popular?
We are on the order for arrest written by cinnabar.
Do you think we are not popular enough?
What should we wear?
Hurry up.
Don't move!
Behave yourselves!
Stop crying. You're so annoying.
Where are you from?
We're introduced by Miao Sitong, the wine dealer.
I
did business with Mr. Miao a few years ago.
He's an honest person.
Tell me.
Do you want slaves or horses?
Slaves.
No right to choose.
Ten in a team.
Take them if you have enough money.
Mr. Qi.
May I choose now?
Of course.
Take them here and show them to our God of Wealth.
Go over there.
-Hurry up. -Don't slouch.
Hurry!
Go.
Hurry up.
Get another batch.
-Stand up. -Hurry up.
Go.
Over there.
Do you hear me?
Young Master.
Run for your life!
Run!
They're here to make trouble.
Chase them!
Gu Qingqiao.
Qiao.
I got you.
You are a bad guy!
Let me go if you dare!
Stop talking.
Let me help you up.
Slow down.
My butt.
My leg.
Let's go back.
No.
If I can't find Duan Yu, I'd rather die outside.
Watch out!
Watch him.
Waiter.
Be our guards ourside.
Sir.
Let me ask you.
Are women and children nearby often caught and sold?
Yes.
The tribes nearby are often attacked by the Moon Wolf Tribe.
Young Master Shaoyi.
Do you remember
the characteristic of the girl who ran away that day?
This is the totem of the Fire Crane Tribe.
Fire Crane Tribe?
Where is the Fire Crane Tribe?
Go north.
Close to the stream and rocky beach.
Okay.
Let's go.
Maybe Duan Yu is waiting there.
Young Master Shaoyi.
Your butt.
Not a big deal.
I'm fine.
Stick out your belly.
Don't forget your identity.
My identity?
What is my identity?
Are you out of your mind?
You're a widow in Zhang Village.
You are pregnant because you had an affair with a man.
I'm a kind fortune teller who passed by.
You wanted to commit suicide.
I saved your life.
Can't you think of something good for me?
It's so complicated.
I can't memorize it.
How much
is the fortune-telling?
I do not tell fortune.
How stupid you are to drive away a potential client!
Wait a moment.
Sir.
You'll have a bloody disaster.
Your family will be unsettled. You will have arguments with your wife. Nothing will be in your favor.
You won't have any chance to get rich.
Since your life is so miserable,
I won't charge you any.
Qing.
Let's go.
You are a born actor.
Bravo.
I can be your mentor.
Don't you think it's strange?
What's strange?
Along our way here,
many people wear white clothes
with the same sword.
[Wanted]
Take a look.
A clearance sale.
Only 998.
You can have the same outfit as Ruan Siqiong, the greatest martial artist in the world.
Ruan Siqiong?
Only 998.
Could this be a coincidence?
You can have the same outfit as Ruan Siqiong, the greatest martial artist in the world.
Who is Ruan Siqiong?
Why is everyone imitating him?
He's obviously not important.
Take a look.
-The same outfit as Ruan Siqiong. -Let's go.
Since last month when
Uncle Ruan defeated Nangong Wuhen,
the best martial artist of Shenlong Pavilion,
this town has been bustling with large crowds.
What are you looking at? Can you hurry up?
Do you know how hard it is to pretend pregnant?
Peole come here to see how charming Uncle Ruan is.
I'm tired.
I want to take a rest.
Why are they still not used to it?
Why are you so troublesome?
Senior.
I want to buy the same outfit as Uncle Ruan.
What do you think?
Can you aim high?
You are a disciple of Xiling.
How can you wear counterfeits like them?
Please join the line.
Everyone will get one.
Okay, thank you.
Today, Yuelai Inn opens to welcome guests.
It's an honour
to have Master Ruan who returned from his journey in our inn.
Welcome in
and take a look at the greatest martial artist in the world.
I didn't expect ancient people
also like to join in the fun.
Do you want to see Master Ruan?
Let's go.
We need to find the sword in Xiling.
Let's go and see the greatest martial artist in the world.
Let's go.
Come on.
Stop pushing.
For the sake of my baby,
please let me have a look at
the greatest martial artist in the world.
No problem.
Senior.
It's Uncle Ruan.
Please come in.
Doesn't Uncle Ran hate the crowd the most?
Let's go, Senior.
Are you stupid?
You don't have to elbow your way out
if you want to see Uncle Ruan.
Do you know the shortcut?
Let's go.
Let's take a look at the master of martial arts.
Please line up.
Don't push.
Isn't it this way?
[Wanted]
Junior Man.
We didn't learn martial arts for nothing.
This is the best time to use it.
I'm busy.
Senior, look.
Are pregnant women so tough now?
Shh.
What did you say to them?
I said we were all martial artists
and there was no need to expose each other.
Can they understand it?
No problem.
Senior.
What did you say?
I told her that she displayed the gestures so fast
that I didn't get it.
Hmm.
Hurry up.
Master Ruan.
It's really him.
So handsome.
So good-looking.
He's so handsome. I finally meet him in person.
What's so good about me
except my handsome face?
Why did you escape marriage for me?
When I was young,
I sweared that I would only marry the greatest martial artist.
Is it really so important
to marry the best one in the world?
Of course.
People only remember the best.
It's so noisy outside.
Senior.
Is that Uncle Ruan?
Hold on.
This is not an ideal position.
I can only see the back side of his head.
I don't think it's Dr. Ruan.
It doesn't look like him from this angle.
Take down another piece.
What if they notice us?
I'll help you.
I'm not afraid.
Did you leave a letter to your family,
saying you would elope with Ruan Siqiong?
Of course.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I'll take you with me.
Madam.
Are you alright?
Uncle Ruan.
Uncle Ruan, are you alright?
Who are you? You are so ugly.
So rude of you!
Who are you?
How dare you pretend to be Uncle Ruan?
You are so shameless.
I will definitely give you a lesson today.
Where is Lu Zizheng?
Why isn't he here at such a critical moment?
I hate people ruining my hairstyle.
Who is that?
Uncle Ruan?
Nangong Wuqing.
I didn't spare your life
for you to bully the weak.
Dr. Ruan.
Ruan Siqiong.
I'll say it again.
I'm not Nangong Wuqing,
but Nangong Wuhen.
Watch out.
I'll let you remember my name today.
I don't remember the name of a dying person.
Dr. Ruan.
My chest hurts so much like it's on fire.
Am I dying?
Be quiet.
Dr. Ruan.
I'm Chunjiao.
I'm Chunjiao who broke her arm.
Are you showing up on your own or do you want me to force you?
Greetings, Predecessor Ruan.
What's your relationship
with her?
She's my sister.
She was hit by the Flame Palm of Shenlong Pavilion.
I need to take her back to Xiling to detoxify her.
[The Xiling Sect]
If someone is easy to panic,
suffers from insomnia
and is forgetful.
In addition, he has cankers in his mouth
and has constipation.
His pulse...
Senior Lu. Senior Lu.
Who's attacking me?
Who?
Lu Huahua, tell me.
What medicine do you need to cure the illness I said just now?
If you can't answer it,
I can't give you the antidote
to your toxin.
Master.
You...
It hurts.
What happened?
I can't take it anymore.
I didn't expect that after all these years,
the one who accompanied me through the last moment of my life
was Dr. Ruan.
Life is unpredictable.
I am not sure how my mom feels
if she knows this.
Don't worry.
The Flame Palm you got
can be cured by Uncle Ruan
with his Prajna Palm.
But
you have to endure
the pain and bleeding from your wound.
When did Dr. Ruan leave?
Dr. Ruan.
Ruan?
You mean Uncle Ruan?
Yes.
Dr. Ruan.
is your Uncle Ruan.
Don't worry.
With Uncle Ruan's treatment,
you won't die.
If he doesn't want to save me,
I will still die.
You're fine now.
Then...
Do you mean I can leave now?
Uncle Ruan said three days.
You can leave in three days after you fully recover.
Three days?
Yes.
You will surely recover in three days.
Thank you for your help. I'm Furong.
Furong?
Your name is so nice.
I haven't asked your name yet.
I...
I am Qing.
My brother is Bai.
Where is my brother?
Your brother has settled down.
You just need to recuperate.
Qing.
Where did you come from?
We came from the east.
We are on our way to Xiling to seek our family.
In order to avoid bandits,
I disguised myself as a pregnant woman.
You're so smart.
Have you heard
that Uncle Ruan brought back a girl?
Senior.
-Senior. -What's wrong?
I heard that Uncle Ruan brought a girl back.
Is she pretty?
What are you thinking about?
Qing saved us today.
Uncle Ruan took her back to cure her wounds.
What are you doing here?
Why aren't you studying?
Go back.
Senior.
What are you looking at?
Go back
to study.
Let's go.
-Senior was beaten again. -What are you laughing at?
Stop laughing.
Uncle Ruan.
This is the account book of Xiling this year.
[Account Book]
You can check the account anytime.
You are in charge.
Uncle Ruan.
The Great Master was in seclusion,
while Master focused only on cultivation.
You traveled around the world.
So I have to take care of the account book all the time.
Now that you're back,
it's better to give it to you.
You've done a good job.
Keep it up.
Got it.
[Rhinoceros horn, earthworm, Chinese ginseng and shark gall]
Go to the pharmacy and buy these medicinal materials.
Rhinoceros horn, earthworm,
Chinese ginseng and shark gall.
Uncle Ruan.
These medicinal materials are very precious.
Yes.
I'll get the medicine right away.
How could the Black Wood Human-shaped Sword be here?
So stupid.
You are indeed stupid.
Lu Zizheng?
Shh.
I thought you left me behind.
I was going to leave you behind,
but I'm free now,
so I drop by.
Drop by?
It's heavily guarded here.
No outsider is allowed to enter.
You dropped by so easily?
Of course.
I can go anywhere I want.
Good for you.
Why are you so complacent?
You were hit by Nangong Wuhen,
so we have a reason to stay here now.
Do you have any conscience?
I almost died from that palm.
So annoying.
What should we do now?
What should we do?
You have to ask yourself.
Let's split up
to find the Black Wood Human-shaped Sword.
No problem.
What does the sword look like?
Well...
You don't know, do you?
I...
It looks like a sword.
Greetings, Dr. Ruan.
Master Ruan.
Are you Chunjiao?
I'm Qing.
Actually,
my full name is Dongfang Chunjiaoqing.
It's a mouthful name.
So just call me Qing.
Master Ruan.
Have you seen me before?
I've never met you before,
but you seem familiar.
Think about it.
You might be able to recall it.
I think you mistake me for someone else.
Do you want to see me throw discus?
Discus?
Discus? Discus?
This...
That's it.
I used to know nothing
but throwing discus before.
Then my arm was injured.
A doctor encouraged me,
saying that life was not only about scores,
and it was not just about discus either.
Where is the doctor now?
It's hard to see him again.
Even if we meet again,
I don't think he still remembers me.
Fate cannot be made.
This is too shallow.
Isn't it a little perfunctory?
Thank you for keeping off the Flame Palm for me.
The toxin of Flame Palm needs to be deactivated at noon every day.
It's already afternoon.
Come here tomorrow.
Why has Dr. Ruan turned into the goblin mode？
She seems to have no martial arts skills.
How can she pull out the Black Wood Human-shaped Sword?
Qiao.
Who is Qiao?
I'm Wu.
Miss.
Where am I?
This is the territory of the Fire Crane Tribe.
I will thank you for your help.
Please contact my subordinates.
No way.
I have the right to punish
the sinners I brought back.
You can't go back to the Central Plain.
I must go back.
I have something to do.
The most important thing for you now is to take the medicine.
Miss.
Where is my ring?
It remains unknown if you can survive.
What's the use of that ring?
It's very important to me.
Please give it back to me.
Take the medicine first.
Miss.
Qiao.
Let's change sides.
Let me step on it.
Do you want to change?
No?
All right.
There's enough sadness for today.
All right, I've made the bed for you.
You can sleep next to me.
Thank you.
Man Tianxing.
Come and help me.
Are you drying your hair again?
Do you even have a hair dryer here?
Summon the wind.
Speed up.
Raise the wind speed!
You are really talented.
I've never seen someone drying their hair with martial arts.
It's not a big deal.
There are people who cook with internal force.
Our master said
there wouldn't be so many bad guys to punish.
Practicing martial arts can make your life easier
except for building your body.
Take the Flame Palm you got for example.
If you don't vomit blood or feel any pain,
it can serve as a heater in winter.
It will be perfect.
It's thought-provoking.
I feel like I've entered
a new world.
We Xiling disciples study medicine and practise martial arts as well.
That's why we can understand the world better than ordinary people.
Of course.
It's nine fifteen now.
Time to put off the candles.
Hurry up.
Senior is here.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Hurry up. Close the door.
Get up.
Senior has left.
I want to gossip about something.
Although I'm not a martial artist,
I've also heard of the Black Wood Human-shaped Sword,
the greatest treasure of Xiling.
I don't know if I'm lucky enough to...
Shh.
In Xiling,
no one is allowed to mention that sword.
And it disappeared 15 years ago.
Why can't no one mention it?
Because
it brought bloody disaster to Xiling.
Don't mention it again.
Got it?
What's wrong with you?
Why are your nostrils stuffed?
I don't want to be poisoned by your drug.
You think too much.
Let's go.
The more powerful a weapon is,
the simpler it is.
How is it?
Do you feel it?
This is just an ordinary wooden sword.
Try this one.
When I saw it,
I felt something special.
It's obviously a pile of scrap metal.
I searched all night in vain.
What about you?
Anywhere you haven't searched?
In the residential area,
I haven't gone to Tianshan Residence of Tianwang Mountain
and Ruan Siqiong's dome.
Touch the dome
when Ruan Siqiong
treats you tomorrow.
Okay.
Be careful.
Where is it?
It's strange.
How could it disappear?
Junior.
Have you seen my Trident of the Sea God?
How many times have I told you
not to eat in bed?
No idea.
Did you leave it in the martial hall?
No.
I've searched everywhere.
I suspect
there's a thief.
Master Ruan.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
I'm just curious
what the residence of the greatest martial artist looks like.
I'm just looking around.
Do you need me to show you around?
No.
It's noon. Let's start the treatment.
I knew it.
Her body can absorb my internal force.
It seems that she is the one who can pull out the sword.
Does the wound still hurt?
Master Ruan.
You're amazing.
It doesn't hurt at all.
The treatment for today is over.
You can go back now.
Come here tomorrow.
Did you find any clues?
He entered
when I was looking for the clue.
It's not good.
You have to go down the mountain when you recover the day after tomorrow.
We don't have enough time.
I'll visit Tianshan Residence tonight.
Be careful.
How's your wound?
You know what?
Ruan Siqiong is indeed the best martial artist in the world.
When he treated me,
I felt like I was reborn.
-Why is he so... -You're obsessive with him.
Don't go.
I'm not sleepy.
I must catch the thief tonight.
Master's Tianshan Residence?
I finally have a chance
to perform in front of Master.
[Medicine]
Brat!
Stop!
It's you!
Brat!
I caught you.
Bao.
I'm here to see Master Wang.
I have something important to discuss with him.
How dare you still find excuses?
Trying to escape?
It's not that easy.
Who are you?
Why are you fighting in my residence at midnight?
Master Wang.
My brother and I grew up together
after our parents died.
We've never been apart for a second.
He entered Tianshan Residence by accident
because he worried about me.
Please forgive him
for the sake of his love for his sister.
Master.
He is not a good brother at all.
He broke into Xiling
and looked around at night.
He is clearly a thief.
Also, when I was checking the armory today,
I found many weapons were lost.
It must be him.
Is it true?
I've never stolen anything from Xiling.
I've never stepped on any plant.
You framed me
without
any evidence.
Aren't you too hasty?
If you really lost something,
how can you prove that I stole it?
If I really wanted to steal,
why didn't I steal some valuable items?