I'll count the birds
Create a daylight
Go to the free
Let's cross the wind
Dancing ring at the stars in the room
And night away
This is a fierce happiness
Stay here all but hope for Johnny
The Story of Johnny
Episode 1
If you're angry again, I'll let you find it.
Try it again.
I'll go to bed early.
Go.
Honey.
Do you want to be together?
I can make breakfast for you.
I'll go to bed early.
The Story of Johnny
Episode 1
Sister is back.
Mom, mom is back.
You can sleep on your own.
I'll go to bed early.
Mom.
Okay, okay, you can do it.
Sister, did you live in my house?
Yes, I lived in the house I was a kid.
I still remember.
Why don't you remember?
Because you're stupid.
Sister, is dad's house fun?
It's fun when I was a kid.
It's not fun now.
I won't go there anymore.
Why?
Because my house is not in my room.
I can only sleep on the sofa.
Why can't you sleep on the sofa?
Is it because you didn't buy the money?
No, I have a lot of money.
But dad doesn't love us.
Dad doesn't love us?
I don't love dad anyway.
I only love mom.
No.
I love sister.
I love auntie.
I love aunt Xiaoxia.
I think you're right.
I don't love dad anymore.
Forget it.
I just love dad a little bit.
It's getting cold.
I think it's the two little pigs who haven't woken up yet.
They're coming to eat.
They're not woken up yet.
We're so handsome.
Let me see.
You're so handsome.
You said today is a sunny day.
It's all happy every day.
You said you were happy.
You said you wanted to be more happy.
The rainbow must appear.
I said I would be more happy with you.
The sun will warm up a little bit.
I think tomorrow is a wish.
Open your heart.
Even if life is wind and rain.
I'm afraid of the weather.
A little more courage can pass.
Give the future can pass.
Give the future new self.
Don't forget to be happy.
The passionate eyes.
Don't need to laugh.
Don't laugh.
Give the future new self.
Happy is around you.
Don't forget to be happy.
The passionate eyes.
Don't need to laugh.
The youth is around you.
Can't run away.
Is the celebration done?
Yuanyu Le is so happy.
Give the princess a thumbs up.
Yuanyu Le, come and eat.
Eat quickly.
Don't be late.
If you are not late,
I will take you to eat fried chicken.
It's a feast.
Great.
Eat quickly.
Yuanyu Le, come and see.
Choose your clothes.
I want to wear a white dress.
I want to wear a square skirt.
Choose a white dress.
Yellow looks good.
This one.
OK.
Dad, this one.
Hurry up.
Go.
Yuanyu Le, wait.
Let's go!
Wait for a while!
Let's take a photo together!
Come on!
Three, two, one, yeah!
Okay, family wedding is the first one!
Four, five, six, seven, eight!
Let's go!
The first day of the wedding
Look, this is the design of our main house
You should give it a try
The first one
The second one
Come here
Wait for a while
What's wrong?
I've changed the seven-day schedule
to the wedding date
That's my first date
You can't move
I'll help you think it over
Look, is the bedroom space big?
The chair is from the head office
I've put a big chair on it
to ensure that you can put everything down
No, I don't agree
You let them stop
to make me wear a hat
What do you mean?
My son came
and didn't have a second-hand room
to stay with us
Then what?
Yeah, that's not good
What about you?
You have a study room?
I have
All my work in the future
will be completed by the company
and I'll move it to a few places
and come back after that
No way
Mom, give me a way
Then I can only make a living
I think my life is
a little bit lost
Now we have a problem
It's easy to solve the problem
All the unnecessary things
and the necessary things
are all recorded
You're so smart
You must understand
Good boy
So I'm the one who has to do the work
Forget it
Isn't it just a hat?
I'm sorry for you
You should be sorry for me
It's a deal
Mom, I like this
I have a problem
It's like a dream, car
Happy
I still think that
the price is the lowest
and the performance is the highest
My sister said
that we can still do it
without a break
Then the more the salary is,
the more suitable it is
to buy it
But I think this car is good
The car shape is linear
and the color is suitable
Dami, which one do you think is good?
Mom, I like this
Mom, look
There is no such big sky window
You can look at the stars here at night
You can see the rain from the sky
from the top
This is the position of mom
You sit here
We sit here
I also want to put my favorite little bear here
You can also put Mr. Kong Long here
I want this
This is very expensive
It's over 20,000 yuan
This is for me
Mom, I'm the best
Let's go to the middle of the road
Okay
Take the car certificate and ID card
and pay half the temporary number plate
The car plate needs three days
We will give you a discount
Do you need a discount?
It's okay
We can buy a car without a car certificate
We will drive the car back for you
After you finish the test, we will drive
Okay
Since the atmosphere is so red
We must buy it today
Let's go
I'm happy to see you
Okay, sister
Let's go
Okay
One, two, three
Two, three
Okay
One, two, three
Two, three
Okay, let's go
One, two, three
Okay
Wait, I need to wash my hands
Wash your hands
Is it delicious?
Yes
It's delicious
Okay
I like this one
This one
Yes, this one
Let's see
Do you like this one?
Yes
Both are pretty
This one
I don't like it
No, I don't like it
Okay
Is it delicious?
Yes
Okay, you can eat more
I'm not good at it
Do you like it?
Yes
I love it
Oh, thank you
They like that one
Hello, Kitty
You see
You've liked this since you were a kid
You are the one who likes this
I like it
I'll buy it for you
Do you remember it?
Of course
I like it
How much?
What do you want to eat, Kitty?
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat Hanbao
What else?
This one
Here
I want this one
This one
What do you want, Sister?
I want this one
Dad, you can eat it
You can eat more
I want to eat it
Okay
I'll eat it for you
Dad, you can eat it
I want to eat it too
It's sour
Where is it sour?
Why isn't it sour?
So sour
I like it
Okay
You feed me both
I like it
You can eat it
You can be happy in the future
Yes
I like it
I love them
I promise
I hope
You can eat it
The vivo is gone
Okay
BothINGS
BothDO
I'm going to sleep.
These two guys are really too excited today.
They only sleep for an hour.
Let's see how they can get up tomorrow and go to school and kindergarten.
You...
If you don't get up, there's no way to get up.
How can you let a kid decide on such a big thing?
Do you know what Big Brother told his brother this morning?
He said he slept in the front yard.
Because my dad's not in my room anymore.
He only sleeps in the back yard.
But do you know how he told me?
I just lived in the house where my dad lived.
He told me that my dad's house is big and spacious.
But the three rooms are the same.
Why is there no bed in the girl's room?
The money is really not human.
I know that you feel disappointed.
But I can't stop him from falling and bumping into his dad.
But if he really falls, I feel more hurt than anyone else.
So today, I'm going to make you happy.
No matter how much money you spend, you have to be happy.
Yes, as long as you are happy, you have to be happy.
No matter how much money you spend, you have to be worth it.
Hello, Miss Xu.
Well...
Well, I'm really sorry that day.
Miss Xu, I'm really sorry.
I was really too much that day.
I said some nice words.
Please don't put them in my heart.
Besides, I'm sorry.
Besides, there's something else I want to ask you to do.
If you have time tomorrow night, we can meet again.
It's better to make it clear.
And you can also meet at the new restaurant.
I'm coming.
I'll hit him.
I'll go to the police station.
Dad, why haven't you slept yet?
If you don't want to sleep,
at least drink this every day to relieve your hunger.
Don't think about anything else.
Mei Yi.
Mei Yi, I'm here.
You said that Zhai Lan suddenly called your friend.
I want to see you.
Can we not call her like that?
What do you mean by that?
I suddenly saw her today.
Do you think she suddenly came to our party?
I think I'm quite nice.
I want to see how I can get along with her.
Xu Kai Jin, do you know what I'm most excited about?
I think you're not a good idol.
Do you remember where you got the title of a college mentor?
A person who is rich and knows how to eat rice.
Come on.
Okay, Xu Kai Jin, you're good at finding skills, right?
You're so good at playing the fool.
You're so small.
What are you doing, Mei Yi?
Mei Yi, let's eat something together.
Okay, you guys go ahead.
Jia Fang has another request.
I'm done with the plan.
Then we'll go first.
They're leaving.
I'll stay with you.
Two bottles.
Okay, okay.
Mei Yi, you want two bottles?
No, I don't.
I'll add some more.
Okay, it's still the last time.
Okay, I'll see you tonight.
Hello, Mr. Qian.
Let me introduce you to the owner of the shop.
The shop is in a state of emergency.
Hello.
Come on, sit down.
I'll just say it without delay.
There's a gold-gray father behind my company.
He really likes this street.
He wants to rent a shop on this street.
He's just looking at your shop.
If I can't find a good one,
I'll just go to the shop.
He really likes to look at your shop.
If you're willing,
Mrs. Jin and I are really in a good mood.
How do you feel about having a 1.5 times price?
That's good.
The contract of my house
hasn't arrived.
If you take them away,
you can buy them a gold-gray father.
Yes.
Maybe my father doesn't say it clearly.
I'll repeat it again.
Mrs. Jin and I are in a good mood.
If you're willing,
he can offer you a gold-gray father
as a deposit.
And he can pay the whole amount at once.
What do you think?
If that's what you said,
then this matter can be settled.
Then it's settled.
It's settled.
Okay, okay.
That's a good idea.
I have to tell them.
Tell them to eat.
Don't worry.
We're back.
Come back to your mom's house.
Let's go to school.
Sister Ning.
Let's go to school later.
Send Xiao Mi back.
I have to go out.
When it's late,
take Xiao Mi back.
Okay.
And,
tomorrow morning is my first day in school.
I might have to get up earlier than usual.
I'll bring the cake over first.
You got up early enough.
You still have to get up early.
Don't be so lucky.
I have a pet.
By the way,
Xiaoxiao called me.
Why did you drag her?
What's going on?
I'll bring her back later.
I forgot.
Sister Ning, did you get your phone?
Okay.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Let's go in.
Wait a minute.
I can't hear you in our school.
Did she ask you?
She did?
That's great.
I had a conversation with you.
No, I'm fine.
I...
I went out for a drink.
She knows that she's fighting with me.
Thank you.
Don't talk to me in the morning.
I love you.
Good friend.
Mom, you scared me.
Why are you here?
What's wrong?
You said something so loud just now.
You said something.
What's wrong?
The sound outside is so noisy.
You must have heard it wrong.
I called my friend.
She said she bought a bottle of
expensive tea.
I said you use such expensive tea.
Be careful.
It's hot.
Mom,
the decoration is so noisy outside.
You're not feeling well.
Come and rest.
I have to watch it.
I have to watch the decoration
of my grandson's house.
Some people are too cheap.
If they use bad materials,
my grandson's health
will be a problem.
I'll watch it.
Watch it.
Mom.
Please sit down.
Thank you.
This man is really
handsome once.
Hello, Mr. Mei.
Hello, Miss Xu.
What's the matter?
Just tell me directly.
Well,
I want to
treat you as my girlfriend.
I didn't hear it wrong.
There's still such a good thing.
Don't misunderstand.
I haven't finished talking about it yet.
It's temporary.
Or it's for my girlfriend.
I can pay you
according to the time.
I won't waste your time.
You're so considerate.
You can still be handsome.
Can you do this?
Now that there are so many chips,
it's not a game.
Miss Xu.
Well,
I'll make it clear.
Maybe I can
remove your new pants.
My wife has a sister.
She was always outside.
After she came back from abroad,
she couldn't find a job.
My father-in-law
made up the idea of being together.
Of course, for them,
after finding such a mother,
my two daughters
would not be angry.
I would not agree.
So I lied to them.
I said I have a girlfriend now.
But when we met in the day,
my father-in-law's friend
took a picture of us.
Take a picture?
The key is here.
She wants to check my girlfriend now.
So I stopped her from
asking about our relationship.
I want to ask you to play a play.
I said that
you understand?
Yes.
Then you play a play for me.
I'll give you 500 yuan.
Is that okay?
But I have a question.
In the process of
being a girlfriend,
do we need to be close?
Of course.
If we are far away,
my father-in-law
will not believe us.
But how close?
Like this.
Can we be closer?
Like this?
You need to be closer.
We are actors.
We are going to be close to each other.
I'm sorry.
I'm not going to.
Don't worry.
I won't take advantage of you.
If you hold hands or need to hold your shoulder,
you need to be close.
Let me tell you this.
I'm the most professional.
If I agree to be your girlfriend,
I will be in the drama.
When we need to be close,
we can't be soft.
Our goal is
to make your father-in-law fall in love.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Okay.
That's good.
Help me cut the food.
Xiaojiao.
Is Qianhao being honest lately?
Not only his mom,
we are both very good.
When we get close to his mom,
it must be my fault.
This is the typical mother-in-law.
Didn't I tell you that
Qianhao has a flower price.
His name is written on his head.
With your heart,
he won't even leave you alone.
Listen to me.
Get divorced quickly.
You will be in a hurry.
Otherwise, you won't have a good wife.
Aunt, did you hear that?
My uncle is here for three times again.
He wants me to get divorced with him.
You don't listen to your uncle.
How can you do that?
Since ancient times,
he has been persuading me to divorce him.
I think Qianhao is a good boy.
He is good to him.
He is good to Qianhao.
If Xiaojiao doesn't have me,
he can make money for him.
He can make profit for him.
What do you think of him?
I have seen a lot of people like him.
Qianhao is a man with a skin.
He is happy to meet women.
Uncle.
You don't want me to say it.
I want to tell you the same.
How about this?
My uncle will give you a idea.
Let's talk about it.
What do you mean?
You can tell Qianhao that
I have made a mistake in my work.
I have to be punished.
I even got fired.
I can't help him
with his company.
You have to be serious.
If he keeps on making you suffer,
then uncle will lose.
I will beat him.
Why?
If I lose,
your relationship with me
will be bad.
Look at you.
You are still a young man.
You are married.
What's so good about a man like you?
I can't get rid of him.
You can't get rid of him?
You are right.
You can't change your job.
You are pretending.
You are so happy to see me.
I am happy.
Miss Xu.
Let's find a time
to practice it.
I will do it.
Now,
we need to know each other better
and know each other better.
My father-in-law is an old painter.
I didn't mean to lie to him.
He is a cute old painter.
He is not a good man.
He always asks
some strange questions.
We will write a letter in advance.
Is that okay?
Yes, no problem.
The first question is
do you introduce your parents?
I don't know.
I didn't tell you.
I grew up with my aunt.
I didn't see my own parents.
I am sorry.
I don't know.
You know,
I told my father-in-law
not to ask him to leave.
It's not a big deal.
My aunt and I grew up
and we were very happy.
You haven't seen him, right?
He is a cute old woman.
Really?
He is single now.
I will make you see him.
Why?
It's good.
You are so open-minded.
He is so open-minded.
He must be a cute old woman.
Next question.
Do you have a house or a car?
No, sorry.
You can lie to this kind of private matter.
We just write a letter in advance.
You can answer it.
You don't need to be so familiar.
Lie?
I can't.
If you lie to someone,
you can lie to others.
But you can't lie to others.
I can't do that.
I am going to tell you the truth.
When we got divorced,
the house was cheated by the ex-husband.
Recently,
I bought a car
and it's on the test.
Good question.
What is it?
There is one more important question.
I will definitely ask you.
Yes.
Which one do you like?
Handsome.
Good question.
Smells good.
You are back, son.
Mom is here.
Mom is ready.
Let's eat.
Luo Xiao, come back and help mom.
Mom left after coming here.
She went out.
Why is she so unintelligent?
It's okay.
I don't want to see her.
We are so close.
Is that okay?
Is this a matter of the rule?
Mom,
what is the rule?
It's a matter of the rule.
It's okay.
That's not okay.
Don't say anything.
I will make the bottom line if it's not good for my mom.
Luo Xiao,
the phone is ringing.
Help me pick it up.
Hello, Luo Xiao.
Where are you going?
My mom left after coming here.
What do you mean?
Mom is a secret.
It's okay.
Mom can't stand people's support.
Luo Xiao,
tell you what.
Come back to me.
My mom is tired from the hospital.
She has a cold.
Don't be like this.
Your uncle
always scolds me here.
is about to die.
I have been thinking about it for years.
Think about it.
We will live together.
I have told you many times.
If it's not good for my mom,
you should go.
Keep your word.
Don't pretend to be dead.
I said I ate too much.
You and your uncle
always play with me.
It's not over yet.
Hello,
honey.
What's up?
You miss me?
It's fine.
I'll go to the toilet.
Go to the toilet.
Don't want to be a pet.
I'm a pet.
You are a pet.
I can't say you are a pet.
I'm a pet.
You are a pet.
Where are you?
I'm at my uncle's house.
I told you I ate too much.
I just went to the toilet.
She...
You...
Did you take the phone?
Hello?
Honey. Honey.
Uncle.
What's wrong?
The money is very good.
It's very good. Tell her that next week,
I'm going to give her a big gift.
Hey, honey, did you hear that?
This is praising you.
I'm going to give you a big gift.
Why did you hang up?
What's wrong?
I just went out.
Why did you leave again?
Xiao Zhao gave you a dream medicine.
A dream medicine?
This is not a good thing.
I have to take a bath.
You...
What's going on?
It's raining.
Miss Xu, look at the phone.
I'll send you the document.
It's simple and clear.
We don't have time.
It's basically covered.
I have no details in the information.
And my father-in-law
might ask you about it.
Do you have a password?
You can go back and memorize it.
No.
Why do you have to know
where your son-in-law is?
I was asked that year.
Fortunately, I had a prediction.
It's said that the other half of the examination
is deeply related to Cantonese.
You know my father-in-law?
He was the director of the human management
before he retired.
He was very slow in his time.
You know, the problems with the pictures of HR
and the sculptures.
After he retired,
he was angry at me every year.
He was still studying at night.
When I first went to the door,
he asked me about the problems.
He said that I would send you
the document to the human management.
Of course, I'm not his son.
He asked you,
he wouldn't be so anxious.
He just wanted you to go to the hospital.
He just wanted to make it more serious.
Look at these problems.
The two daughters' business,
their previous days,
the two daughters' favorite color,
animal, cartoon characters,
and the favorite food and snacks.
Let me tell you,
you have to keep your hands on the standard
for the rest of your life.
What did you say?
Well,
I think
you should stop looking for your wife.
Find a machine to get it.
No.
I thought these were okay.
Since you care about them,
you should be the first one
to take care of your daughter.
Of course, I will follow the standard
and take care of the other half of the child.