If you didn't have to go to the Flower Moon Night,
how could I have been able to catch you?
You're a scoundrel!
The day before yesterday, I gave Lord He a bottle of wine.
He didn't wake up for three days.
Yesterday, I gave Lord Zhang a massage.
Yesterday, I gave him a fracture.
Today, I let you praise Lord Li.
You said that his head is the biggest and most powerful of the six realms.
I think you're the one who made my head big.
Say it. Can you do it well?
I... I...
If you can't do it well, then get lost!
Lord, he's not in the room.
Wait for me here.
You're back, Lord. Are you hungry?
The scallion oil cake I made is very delicious.
The owner of the Flower Moon Night, Fu Yue, told me that
if you want to keep a man's heart,
you have to be diligent and virtuous.
So I thought I'd go to the man's kitchen
and make you breakfast.
Scallion oil cake?
You were making this before?
Yes.
Scallion oil cake is my favorite food in this world.
I don't know if you like it or not.
I'm not sure if you like it.
Do you like it?
Then why don't you come to me?
Lord, he has my safety.
He doesn't want me to go out.
Then I have to think about what to do for you.
Lord,
could it be...
that you miss me?
Of course I miss you.
Lord, what are you doing?
This is just the piano.
Perfect.
I'm playing the drum.
I'm playing the piano.
Yes.
Lord,
do you want to be here?
This is not appropriate.
You seem...
You bit me?
This...
This is not a good day.
You are going to affect your spiritual cultivation.
You have a bad habit. You have to take care of yourself.
You are so sincere to me.
But you are so careless.
If that's the case,
you can go back.
I won't leave you here.
You are so annoying.
Madam.
Lord.
Send her back to the night.
Lord, I know I was wrong.
Please don't send me back to the night.
If I go back, the housekeeper will think I'm useless.
She will torture me to death.
My lord.
I have been poor since I was a child.
My parents died.
I spent days and nights in the garden.
I only ask you to give me a place to stay.
I beg you.
Finished?
The story is so ordinary.
It's more boring.
My lord.
You can leave me here.
I will do whatever you want.
Please believe me.
My lord.
I will do whatever you want.
Please leave me here.
Lord.
It's not fair.
My lord.
He really misunderstood what happened.
I...
I didn't mean it.
I just...
My lord, I will send you back to the night.
Can he think so highly of me?
My lord, send me back to the night.
I'm so useless.
Please don't make a big deal out of it.
Could you be quiet?
Even if noise,
All this time?
songs
Come on, drink
Here, drink
.
You don't know, right?
Last night,
the little fairy who was brought back from the Flower Moon Night
by the Count Ji and the Immortal Ji,
do you remember?
Yes, I remember.
Tell me.
He didn't know what to do
and offended our new star?
He was thrown back this morning.
He was thrown back?
Or the Immortal Ji
is so fresh
that he couldn't even stay up all night.
He was taken home for a day
and sent back.
It's too limited.
Is it true?
The Count Ji was sent back?
Yes.
The housekeeper of Fuyue
is still being swept away by the enemy.
Poor thing.
He was swept from the south to the north,
from the east to the west,
from the back to the back,
but he didn't stop.
Why is the housekeeper of Fuyue
so cruel?
There's such a thing?
Yes.
Since the fairy has been sent back from the Flower Moon Night,
this is a good chance
for us to send someone back.
After the Qingyun Conference,
I've been telling Count Ji many times
that he hasn't got a reply.
I'd like to see
why he refused me this time.
As long as I can send someone back to the Wu Gui Sea,
then in the eyes of outsiders,
the alliance between the Count Ji and my niece
is not too stable.
I understand.
Your Majesty,
the shadow has been sent back to the Flower Moon Night.
Now he's being punished by the housekeeper of Fuyue.
What about the barrier of magic being broken?
As long as he's back.
There are salt fairy everywhere in the Wu Gui Sea.
He's not the only one who's suspicious.
We can find a reason to send him away.
The most important thing now
is to get the Night Grass.
The Qingyun Conference was won by Zhu Shui and Ling Zhou.
The blind talisman is about to be lost.
I'll find it and take it.
I'll remember it in the tribute.
You can go there tomorrow.
Yes.
Bu Xiu,
Zhu Shui and Ling Zhou are evil.
You must protect yourself.
Wu Ai,
I'll kill one of them.
Your Majesty,
a woman has come.
It's from Lord Yan Xiao.
I'll do it.
Don't kill him yet.
You can transfer the favour on Jiang Essentially in your next life
to Lady Xiao encont.
Lord Ye next.
that fairy has been sent back to the Flower Moon Night by Lord Ji.
Since the fairy served you badly last night,
it's also right for you to go back.
But these two fairies
were specially chosen by Lord Han Feng for you.
You are the chief warrior.
You should...
I really heard that
you went back to the Flower Moon Night.
Yes.
I'll be honest with you.
You left home with me this morning.
I was going to pretend to be fine,
but I was so confused
that I was like a little kid.
I didn't expect that I would make such a misunderstanding.
It's really funny.
But in the end,
I was really anxious
to make a mess.
Excuse me.
Xin Er.
This is the chestnut cake
that I made for you.
Try it.
Is it good?
It's good.
Since Ming Xian lost the competition
and escaped from Yaoguang Mountain,
His Majesty won't give His Majesty
any more affection.
Xin Er.
As a mother,
I finally have a chance to help you.
I've sent someone to get the hunting mirror
and searched the six realms.
Once Ming Xian's trace is found,
I'll take it down.
As long as I can get Ming Xian to die outside,
and the dragon is not in my hand,
before the next Qingyun Conference,
I will definitely
find a new Crown Prince.
You're acting.
Hurry up.
Your spirit energy is so weak.
You've been doing this for a long time
after someone else's ice.
How dare you offend the late Emperor Ji?
My sign of the Flower Moon Night
is almost ruined by you.
I really don't know
how I was soft-hearted
and brought you in.
I...
Because you're soft-hearted.
You're the best.
Mr. He,
are you leaving?
He said
he'd stop wiping the floor.
He's a tall and a short person.
He's been skating several times today.
He's very unhappy.
I've put on several more pairs of shoes for him.
Why don't you care about me at all?
Why don't I care about you?
Then why do you let him wipe the floor here?
Enough.
Stop wiping.
That's it.
Erqi,
did you
fall into the trap?
Listen,
Mingxian
was defeated by Ji Xingyuan just now.
He can't come here.
I think Lord Chengxun
is very confused
and sent you and me
to find him here.
No matter if we can find him or not,
we must come here
because the late Emperor is so lucky.
But
we still have to
find a way to deal with him.
Ji Xingyuan's night
is indeed a good one.
Come on.
Let's have a drink here.
The one who's chasing Ji Jing
is the one who's with him.
If Mingxian shows up nearby,
he'll definitely warn us.
After the door is opened,
there will only be a compass in the mirror.
Why isn't there any reaction?
Is Mingxian really hiding here?
Chase him.
Don't run.
Stop.
Move.
The compass is spinning.
Why can't we see him?
I'm sorry.
This...
Let me pass.
Where is he?
He's here.
It's him.
Don't run.
He found me again.
Still trying to run?
Turn around.
Why isn't Chief Qi here yet?
If we can't do anything,
we can only do it ourselves.
This...
He's my man.
Why are you chasing him?
The Ji County Army has taken a move.
Why are you interfering?
The Fairy is suspicious.
She's trying to get the mirror.
Move.
Yao Guangshan.
You lost the Qingyun Conference.
Now you're the next.
Now you're trying to get the compass.
You're trying to get the mirror
and get me on the ground.
Get lost.
Chief Qi.
We're following orders.
The Fairy is suspicious.
She ran away when she saw us.
We...
Can't you understand me?
I said,
get lost.
She's a fairy from the Garden.
She can't be a fairy.
It must be the magic of Lord Chengyun.
Let's go.
Don't make a fuss.
Okay.
They left.
Yes.
Why are you running around?
Hurry.
Change your clothes.
Come back to Wugui Sea with me.
Yes.
You're not affectionate.
You keep recommending Lord Han Feng.
But if you really offend Lord Han Feng,
what's the point?
I'll do it.
Hello.
You're the MTall burned monster,
transfer girl and h plugging the set.
Let's play a match to decide a winner at the truth.
If sheNow
he won't do anything.
Go.
Your Majesty.
It's been so long.
You want to replace me so soon?
Don't be angry.
Brother Yan.
Explain it to me.
I'm sorry.
Miss Ming Yi.
These two immortals
were carefully selected by Lord Han Feng.
They will never compete with you.
My Lord.
When you brought me back from the Flower Moon Night,
did you promise me
to treat each other sincerely
and let me stay in the Wu Gui Sea
peacefully?
Kind of.
Since it's like this,
why am I not
the female master of the Wu Gui Sea?
I think so.
I think so?
Yes.
Okay.
You said it.
If you two
insist on staying in the Wu Gui Sea,
I'd rather ruin myself.
Never.
Then let them go.
By the way, tell everyone
that I'm the female master of the Wu Gui Sea.
Let them die.
Don't let anyone in.
Or I'll die for you.
Brother Yan.
Look.
What should I do?
My family has become
restless because of your kindness.
You can't just
see me as a official, right?
Right?
What a good official.
Since Brother Ji has said so,
what else can I do?
Please, Your Majesty.
You two continue.
I'll go.
What are you looking at me for?
I didn't take it back.
I'm the female master of the Wu Gui Sea.
You're welcome.
I'll go.
Sir.
Who are you?
You've been back to Huayue for only
half an hour.
So Yan Xiao brought people here.
It has nothing to do with me.
Sir, do you suspect
that I spread the news?
Yao Guang Mountain's broken mirror
has reacted to you.
Who are you?
Sir, let go of me.
It hurts.
Sir, you're just testing me.
Let's see if I used the transformation skill.
Who?
You.
You're determined to wrong me, right?
How do I know
what the broken mirror has to do with me?
The tribute from Yao Guang Mountain
is all yours.
Maybe the tracking agent
has been affected.
What a coincidence.
Then you tested me.
Did you find anything?
No.
I searched for the body and asked for the question.
I spent a lot of money.
But I got nothing.
I feel sorry for you.
I don't think so.
When I asked you the question,
you were in a mess.
You're the one who's in a mess.
If you don't believe me,
I'll leave.
Let's see where these things come from.
Please spare my life, sir.
Why did you come to the Wu Gui Sea?
I'm afraid I can't find the body.
Because I'm too poor.
My family has been in the water of drought for generations.
I can only use herbs to survive.
The only friends I know
are all in trouble.
So I...
You shouldn't do that.
You can't do that.
I'm sorry.
I've paid for the house of Xu Kuofu.
If you need anything, I'll...
Just say it.
I told Yan Xiao
that you're the owner of the Wu Gui Sea.
If you need anything,
just tell me.
And
this room will be yours from now on.
This room...
This...
Thank you, sir.
I...
Ji Bu is very suspicious.
We must be prepared.
What else do you need?
Hmm.
If I pretend to be greedy,
I can solve his doubts.
As long as I can solve it,
I can make you look good.
Master.
How many times have I told you?
I don't need your luggage.
Yes.
Go to the bamboo water bell tower
and go to the water of the cold rat first.
Why?
Ming Yi was born in the water of the cold rat.
You check his background carefully.
Master, you want to keep him?
I want to keep him temporarily.
He took my identity
in front of Yan Xiao.
It's not good to send him away again.
People outside
are also trying to
put their own people in.
If he really has no problem,
he can stay and be a pretext.
It's good to block those people.
Master is too cautious outside.
In fact,
it's easier to kill him.
If he really is a child
who wants the fairy's child in the water of the cold rat,
then his plan for me
will be useful.
Han Feng Jun is looking for you.
No.
I'm just here to play.
Please.
Thanks.
It's delicious.
I'm incompetent.
That Ji Bo Zai
took back the fairy of the Flower Moon Night again
and used her as a shield
to block the enemy.
Since you don't eat soft food,
then eat hard food.
It's not hard enough.
It's too hard.
Han Feng Jun means
he's trying to frame us.
But there's no evidence.
It's hard to get evidence.
Let me
feel it myself.
What is
the Wugui Sea like?
Han Feng Jun is right.
I can't see it outside now.
You can't hear us.
You're really good.
You managed to
calm Ji Bo Zai down
and let him keep you.
The current situation of Ji Xing Yuan
is that the God Lord is sick and fallen.
He usually falls asleep.
There's only one side of him.
He can't inherit the military position.
His brother Han Feng Jun is innocent.
He's likely to be the God Lord in the future.
But no one expected
that Princess Tian Ji
had found Ji Bo Zai who was in the dark.
He made Ji Xing Yuan who was constantly falling
to the top.
I was right.
After the Qiyun Conference,
Princess Tian Ji
also wanted to marry Ji Bo Zai.
Han Feng Jun
won't be happy.
So,
he's trying to frame Ji Bo Zai.
He's actually
trying to form an alliance with Princess Tian Ji.
So, Ji Bo Zai needs to block the arrows.
Just like I need to catch the target.
So, it's hard for Ji Bo Zai
to hide the dream of the emperor
in the turtle sea.
Have you checked his body?
Me?
What?
Think about it.
Maybe he has the most precious thing
with him.
How could it be so obvious?
The Lord is
in a mess.
The Lord is in a mess.
Could it be
he's really in a mess?
But can you search his body?
Searching his body might not work.
But
it can help us find his body.
Zai'er.
Where are you?
Do you want to die?
Masters won't kill me.
Hands up!
Hand up!
Who's your master?
Don't you know I'm still a kid?
Date him.
You'll be sure to get a certificate.
It's still here?
I've
some things
we have to go to bed on
Guards
later
It sounds
I had to find it.
Your master and I
learn things too fast.
This thing...
This...
What is this?
My eyes!
My eyes.
The Flower Moon Night
is almost half of my life.
This place...
I made many promises.
I also left many memories.
Thanks to your kindness,
I can forget about the past.
I'm very happy.
To give you a gift,
I hope you can
have a good life.
The thing I promised you
will be yours soon.
You won't regret
what you said before, right?
Don't worry, Xing.
You saved my life.
I will repay you.
I won't regret it.
I can't talk about kindness.
I will kill
anyone who doesn't have you.
He is my father,
but he treated my mother
so harshly.
I will never let him down.
I will do as you planned.
I will also
make him pay for it.
Darling.
Why should
you feel bad
about the person who's guilty?
For the piace,
I'm humans now.
I won't be like yesterday.
Tonight, again,
I'll get back
the Antrag network
Help me get a dress.
What dress?
You're so dirty!
Hurry up!
You're using my weakness to deal with me?
Don't you think you're going too far?
I'm not going too far.
Which cat is the most obedient?
I'm the most obedient.
This room is so airy.
It's so cold.
I can't even stand the cold.
You little brat.
You're trying to make me suffer?
This is too ordinary.
It's ordinary.
Okay.
You're back.
Is this really possible?
Okay.
Your Majesty.
Lord Han Feng is waiting for you inside.
Yu Jin.
Yu...
If it weren't for you,
I would have died in Ji Bo's hands.
It was that time,
I fell into his spiritual energy.
He's just treating Yu Jin
as a battle gift.
He keeps burning it here every day.
My brother.
There are very few outsiders in this Wu Gui Sea.
Did I offend you by coming here today?
No.
You're the one who brought me here.
I'm here to save you.
It's nothing.
I'm just a visitor.
I'm sorry to have offended you.
This is where you live.
Okay.
Lord Han Feng, please come in.
Brother.
You really live in a very good place.
Yes.
The past Chen Yuan
is full of dark and dark.
There are many places
that are too remote.
Right now,
I just like this cold and empty place.
You really are different from the rest.
But,
you only have that old house in Wu Gui Sea.
It's still very quiet.
Why don't I arrange two people for you
so that you can have more fun here?
Lord Han Feng, you must not.
I'm afraid that the little fairy
will be confused again.
How can you find such a vulgar jar?
Mrs. Xun, bring me the wine.
This wine
was made by Meng Yang Qiu.
It's from the Jiuxian family.
Try it.
It's good wine.
To be honest,
I don't know
what it tastes like.
But,
to be honest,
I've always wanted to be friends with you.
My little niece, Tian Ji,
knew you first.
She was so good at acting
that she made you a fight.
You've made such a great contribution
to Ji Xing Yuan.
Although I'm a descendant,
I admire your respect and respect for me.
You're really overbearing.
It's my honor
to have your love.
Since you're willing
to be my friend,
I'm curious
if I can help you.
I'll do my best.
Ji Xing Palace has been saying
that your spirit energy
is derived from Li Hen Tian.
You can survive
with Li Hen Tian.
Could it be
that you have the dream of the emperor?
It's enough to lie to myself
even if I've never been true to myself.
From the stars to the stars,
how long will it take for me to be with you?
Your tenderness to me
is all because of the love.
I'll drink up my pain
and give you freedom.
Once I have the love,
I'll be willing to give up.
Behind the abyss,
I struggle for a long time.
I want to ask the sky
what's wrong with me
being a puppet for you?
Fate has never been wrong.
The sun will eventually fall.
I'll try my best
to avoid all the absurdity.
From the stars to the stars,
how long will it take for me to be with you?
Your tenderness to me
is all because of the love.
I'll drink up my pain
and give you freedom.
Once I have the love,
I'll be willing to give up.
The End