Yo, what’s up?
First of all, welcome, everyone,
to the new semester.
As you can see…
(They say high school)
(is the most fun part of life,)
(especially in an era when
everything’s changing for the better.)
PRINCIPAL CHANCHANA GIVES EVERYONE FREEDOM.
NO UNIFORM. LESS HOMEWORK. MORE FREE PERIODS.
(Everyone is free...)
PRINCIPAL CHANCHANA GIVES EVERYONE FREEDOM.
NO UNIFORM. LESS HOMEWORK. MORE FREE PERIODS.
(to chase whatever makes them happy.)
(I mean... everyone else.)
(Not me.)
(Nothing about my high school life is exciting.)
(As far as I’m concerned, my duty is to study.)
(So I must perform my duty well.)
(That’s all.)
You’re a kid with a mind of your own.
You don’t follow the mainstream.
I’m so proud of you.
I’m just too lazy to pick out clothes.
This no-uniform policy is total nonsense.
I don’t get why people can be so shallow.
(This is Mr. Tan, my math teacher from Grade 10.)
(We’re close)
(since he’s the one who always
chaperones me to academic competitions.)
(To be honest, he’s taught me a lot.)
(But one thing I’ll never forget is that…)
(I’m never going to grow up to be as fussy as he is.)
In the end,
no matter how much freedom
you have with your clothes,
you’ll all still grow up to be useless cogs
in a country that’s not developing anytime soon.
So, what did you want to talk to me about?
Right. I’ve got a tutoring gig for you.
It’s for a student here at school.
The job only runs until the midterms.
The goal is to help him pass the exams.
They’re offering 30,000 baht, Shane.
30,000?
Mm-hmm. 30,000.
KORAWIT JIRAWARAPONG
SECONDARY 6 / LOSERS
Just one more round.
One more.
The green light.
Green light.
Excuse me, do you know where Kit is?
Kit, you asshole!
Someone’s looking for you!
Kit?
Kit.
Kit, you asshole!
Where the hell are you?
Kit’s not here.
You are Kit.
Mr. Tan sent me. I’m your tutor.
Ah.
He said we’re starting today.
See you after school.
Give me your phone.
Text me when your class ends.
SECONDARY 6 / WINNERS
- I haven’t done it.
- Me either.
Why didn’t you do it?
Because I thought I’d copy yours.
I thought I’d copy yours too.
Shane!
Come on. Take your seat.
Here.
Where have you been?
Can I copy your homework?
The homework is to write an essay
about what you learned during the school break.
Oh, come on. I’ll reword it.
Per hasn’t done it either.
I was planning to copy yours.
Same here, dude!
Just start writing already.
(These two are Per and Tar,)
(members of my friend group.)
(I’m not sure I’d call them good friends.)
(They can be pretty annoying sometimes.)
(But like they say,)
(we don’t always get to choose our friends.)
You do it.
I don’t know how to do it.
- I don’t either.
- All right, stop fighting.
Just copy mine.
Thank you, buddy.
Don’t.
Let me see.
What about you?
Aren’t you copying my homework too?
(This is Kim, the fourth in my friend group.)
(One look at his sad puppy face)
(and I already know. He confessed
to someone and got rejected.)
My 12th grade life is over.
Don’t tell me you’re…
I’m heartbroken, man.
(Here we go. Just as I thought.)
Holy crap, are you heartbroken?
Your first heartbreak, huh?
For this semester.
If we’re counting all the semesters…
It’s heartbreak number 100.
Fine!
I’m not falling for anyone ever again!
Hey.
Who’s that?
A new student, I think.
Heard there’s a transfer this year.
Now I know why
I’ve been heartbroken all this time.
Don’t tell me…
Because true love is right in front of me.
Jeez.
(So, this is what my high school life looks like.)
(And this semester)
(marks the beginning of my final year.)
Where are you going?
- Stop!
- Oops.
Oh, boy!
Do you know where the literature section is?
I’m looking for Wuthering Heights.
Been looking for a while but haven’t found it.
Uh…
What did you say?
Ah! I think it’s right here.
Let me help you look.
What’s your name?
I’m Mon, just transferred here.
I’m in class 4.
I’m Kim.
Class 1.
What are we looking for again?
Wuthering Heights.
Right!
I think it’s down here somewhere.
Are you sure it’s here?
Absolutely.
If the librarian didn’t move it, it must be here.
Seriously, right here.
It’s true.
I’m sure.
Hey, watch out!
I think they’re all gone.
Yeah, right.
I’m sorry.
Let’s keep looking.
I have cram school soon.
We can continue the search again later.
Mm.
Goodbye then.
Oh, man!
How cute.
PHADUNGPATSUKSA SCHOOL
FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL WITH NO UNIFORM POLICY
Hello.
I’m Nut.
It’s my first-day teaching.
Okay, I guess everyone’s here.
How’s everyone doing?
It’s the first day of school.
If you have anything to say, feel free to speak up.
Please.
May I, Mr. Principal?
I think the no-uniform policy
is going to be a problem, sir.
The school is in chaos,
and the students are becoming unruly.
I think we should go back to wearing the uniform.
I agree, sir.
I agree with that.
But I think…
we should push forward with this policy.
It’s just clothes.
Why do we need to make a big deal out of it?
I don’t think it’s just about clothes.
This is a chance for the children
to discover themselves.
It’s true that we can teach them
knowledge, skills, and social values.
But pride and happiness?
We can’t teach those.
They have to find that on their own.
I believe this policy is useful.
It opens doors for students to learn,
experiment,
and figure out who they really are.
We’ve already come this far,
so shouldn’t we tackle the problems step by step
instead of canceling the policy?
Woo-hoo!
Bravo.
Great.
Well said.
I almost cried hearing that.
Can I use your words for an interview?
I think people will resonate with it.
Maybe we should post it on the school page?
But, of course, I’ll take the credit.
It’s just perfect.
How did you come up with that?
What’s your name again?
I’m Nut, sir.
Welcome to my school.
Yo!
Excellent!
Shane, isn’t it?
Yes, ma’am.
Hello.
Please come in.
Thank you.
You can leave your shoes here.
Yes, ma’am.
So, you’re the one
Mr. Tan sent to be Kit’s tutor?
Yes, sir.
My name is Shane.
Hello.
Hi.
Kit, your friend’s here, dear.
We’re heading out to run some errands.
- Sure.
- Don’t be stubborn, okay?
Make yourself at home.
Yes, ma’am.
You’ve got this, son.
He’s in your hands now.
Hey. Have a seat.
Make yourself comfortable.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Okay, based on my calculations,
if you want your GPA to reach 2.0,
you’ll need more than half of
the total accumulated points.
But if you’re aiming for 60% on the exams,
you’ll need to collect all the accumulated points.
If you can manage that in the midterms,
the finals shouldn’t be a problem.
Mm.
Let’s start with a pretest
so I can gauge your level.
We’ll begin with Sets.
Turn to page—
You want the Pizza Lover or the Pizza Deluxe?
What?
Sets.
As in pizza sets.
Thin crust or pan pizza?
Do you like pineapples on pizza?
I’m ordering Hawaiian.
So, what set do you want?
Anything.
They don’t have “anything” on the menu.
Pepperoni.
Excellent.
Alright, I’m ready.
Okay.
There are 10 problems,
and you have 10 minutes to solve them.
When you do it, you must—
Hey!
Are you thirsty?
I’m gonna get you something to drink.
Hold on.
What do you want?
I’ve got regular and no-sugar soft drinks,
root beer, and some juices.
Orange, apple, and tomato.
Tomato juice.
Seriously? That stuff tastes awful.
I don’t get why
people make juice out of tomatoes.
Anyway, let’s get started.
Let’s solve the problems together.
Good.
Oh, wait.
Just one sec.
Wait here.
Hold on. I’ll be right back.
Just wait.
It’s the model figure I ordered yesterday.
Can you film me while I unbox it?
Here.
You have long eyelashes.
What’s my eyelashes got to do with this?
They're cute.
Don’t talk nonsense.
Back to the lesson.
Hey, the pizza’s here.
Want some more oregano?
I’ve got some in the kitchen.
It’s fine.
Let’s hurry up and eat,
then get back to the session.
Come on, I’m ready.
No other random things to do?
No.
But can I use the bathroom first,
so we can study for a longer stretch?
Be right back.
I MIGHT NOT BE SLENDER,
BUT WHEN YOU KISS ME,
YOUR HEAVY DAY WILL BE LIGHTER.
Hey.
I was heading to the bathroom,
but my friend sent me a cat video.
Look.
Want to see?
Okay, okay.
Let’s get back to the lesson.
If you don’t want to study, then don’t.
I don’t want to waste my time on you either.
Hey!
Are you mad at me?
No, I guess not.
This is your office, Mr. Tan?
Only temporarily.
Every table in the math department is occupied,
so I’m here for now until a spot opens up.
I’ve been waiting for two years though.
I see.
This is how it works at this school.
The students can ask for anything.
Don’t want to wear the uniform?
Fine, wear whatever you want.
Don’t want to cut your hair?
Fine, grow it as long as you like.
But when a teacher needs a table,
he has to wait two years,
and even then, he still doesn’t have one.
But that doesn’t mean
I want to sit with other teachers.
I’m actually comfortable here.
It feels like I have a private room,
which is the only good thing about this place.
The foreign language department is just as full,
so they’ve suggested I use this room as my office.
Nothing good left now.
Do you even know how to uncuff?
Why don’t you do it yourself if you’re so smart?
Just hurry up.
Can’t you see I’m working on it?
Turn it anticlockwise.
Do you even have eyes? I’m doing it.
No, you’re not.
Why don’t you do it yourself, genius?
Fine, fine.
- Just help me first.
- Damn it.
What’s going on now?
Old drama.
Name stole her snack, so she handcuffed him.
And where’d she even get handcuffs?
They’re his.
Could’ve hidden your couple’s plaything better
Don’t say that out loud.
Just hurry.
All right, they’re off.
Yes.
Gosh, that hurt.
Hey, don’t!
Name!
And whose cat is this?
It’s a stray!
I already named it. It's called Kaiju now.
Whoa, it already has a name?
Liar, liar, house on fire.
This fat cat can’t be a stray.
Your house and my house are the same house.
Our parents bought this place before they split
and dumped us here to fend for ourselves.
Why is she so dramatic?
It’s the neighbor’s cat.
Come here.
They were moving abroad,
so they asked Cheese if she wanted to adopt it.
- Right?
- No.
No pet adoption.
Give it back.
To who?
The owner already flew out.
You’re staying here, aren’t you?
I’ll post online and find it a new home.
I got handcuffed again.
Ugh! What a pain.
Taking care of a cat is easier than
taking care of a brother like you.
Hey!
Jin, come back and uncuff me!
You cuffed yourself, genius. Uncuff yourself.
I can’t! Look at me!
NETSAT TEST PREP – MATHEMATICS
Yes, Mr. Tan?
How’s it going, Shane?
How did the tutoring session go?
Kit didn’t give a rat’s ass, sir.
I can’t do it.
Take it easy, Shane.
His parents literally begged me for help.
They’re not asking for much—
just that he passes his exams this semester.
They’re worried he won’t get into any university.
Please, help them out.
It’s not my responsibility.
Do it for the paycheck, if nothing else.
You’re saving up to study abroad, right?
30,000’s nothing to sneeze at.
Besides, you’re a fighter, Shane.
You’re not one to give up that easily, are you?
GO STUDY ABROAD!!
Hey, Shane.
Why are you so early?
Where are your parents?
Mom has an appointment with a patient.
Dad’s got a show to shoot.
We’ve got the house to ourselves.
No prying eyes.
Want to play a video game?
Which hand do you use?
Lefty or righty?
Righty.
Okay.
Sit down.
Hey!
What?
What the heck are you doing?
This is to teach you discipline.
If you even think about breaking my command…
Jeez!
Do you really have to do this?
Yes, I do. For someone like you.
Let’s get started.
Come on.
Grab your pen.
Wrong page.
Turn to the next one.
Gosh! I can’t do this anymore.
I’m tired.
I don’t have the energy.
Can we take a break?
You’re tired already?
Try to push yourself.
If you don’t, you’ll never improve.
Keep going!
It’s just studying.
Do you have to be so damn serious?
If you can’t take studying seriously,
what the hell are you going to do in life?
Don’t you think you’re being too serious?
What kind of person are you, really?
No wonder…
They canceled the uniform,
but you’re still wearing it.
What I wear doesn’t concern this.
You even know how to spell the word ‘fun’?
I do.
Then spell it out.
Will you quit goofing off?
How old do you think you are, eight?
Junior high students can solve these problems.
But you’re still getting them wrong.
You’re not just dumb,
you’re a complete slacker too, asshole.
Can I step out for some fresh air?
I’m stressed out.
Ever since I started high school,
I haven’t been able to do math problems.
The more I do, the more I get wrong.
You’re smart. It’s easy for you.
But for someone dumb like me—
You’re not dumb.
If you really think it through,
you’ll see you do understand the equations.
You just slip up on the steps.
Take this one.
You moved the constant
but forgot to change the sign.
And here, you forgot the brackets.
When you’re solving equations, don’t rush.
Take it slow.
Keep practicing,
and you’ll eventually get the hang of it.
Thanks a lot.
Hey!
What the hell is this?
Payback for handcuffing me.
Enjoy the view from my room for now.
I’ll send the maid to unlock you in ten minutes.
I’m heading out.
Bye.
Kit!
You asshole!
Come back and unlock the door!
Kit!
Damn.
Why exactly do we have to help you find a book?
Aren’t you my friend?
Since you got here,
I haven’t even seen you touch a single book.
Are you sure it’s here?
I’m sure.
I asked the librarian.
She said it should be in this section.
But all the books here are super old.
The spines are done for.
You do realize that
even if you find him the book,
it doesn’t mean he’ll like you, right?
It’s better than doing nothing.
Is it this one?
Let me see.
That’s it!
Holy shit, we actually found it.
My chances are looking good this time!
Enjoy the view from my room for now.
Kit!
You asshole!
Come back and unlock the door!
I’M EIGHT YEARS OLD.
A CERTIFIED DUMBASS.
SUBJECT: HOW TO ENJOY LIFE 101
GOT A PROBLEM? COME SEE ME.
You even know how to spell the word ‘fun’?
Your card has been topped up.
Yeah!
We won!
Here. Let me try.
Hey!
Yes!
I got it.
It’s not that hard.
Hey.
How is it?
Cute, huh?
Come on. Are you still mad at me?
No.
Fine.
Let’s go grab something sweet.
My treat.
So, what’s wrong exactly?
It’s like you said.
I don’t know how to spell the word ‘fun’.
What’s gotten into you?
I didn’t win a single round of any game.
Don’t rush it.
Take it easy.
Keep practicing,
and you will win eventually.
That sounds familiar.
What you just said.
It’s what you told me.
What?
You’ve got something on your lips.
Let me wipe it off.
You’re such a messy eater.
I’m a messy eater—so what?
Nothing.
Come on, Kim.
Are you sure his cram school is here?
Yes.
I did some digging on his Instagram.
But I want both.
You can only pick one.
So, let’s go eat—
Mon!
Hey, Kim.
What brings you here?
I happened to find the book you were looking for.
Happened to?
Ouch!
You guys go ahead.
I’ll be right behind you.
See you there.
Thank you, Kim.
How about…
I treat you to a meal as thanks?
Sound good?
Yes.
What should we eat? Should we do it today?
I already have plans with my friends today.
Let’s do it some other time…
when it’s just the two of us.
My friends are waiting.
I’ve got to go now.
Yes.
What the heck, Kim?
I was the one who found that book.
Why’s he treating only you?
Say that again
Who found the book?
Oops, my stomach’s growling.
I’m hungry.
Let’s grab something to eat.
Kim.
Hey! Wait for me.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
Why are you smiling?
Huh?
What are you smiling at?
Why are you so happy?
Hm?
Why are you happy?
You’re grinning from ear to ear.
You’re very happy, yeah?
Order whatever you want.
It’s on me.
I’ll freaking order everything.
Go ahead.
Watch me.
Can I have this, please?
(Looks like this new semester
has more in store than before.)
Mon.
Checking out the clubs?
(Kim's new love is blooming,)
(but who knows if it’ll end
the same way as the others.)
(On my end,)
(Kit is pushing me into brand new experiences.)
Can you show me this dance?
No way!
What did you drag me here for?
To have fun.
(And now, I’m starting to…)
(feel something for him.)
(See you again next week.)