(Episode 2)
Bye. Come this way.
- Thank you. - Excuse me.
Did you see a woman in her mid-50s with a blue scarf?
They were all that there were.
Are you sure you saw her?
We called the police. They'll find something.
Did you see a woman in her mid-50s with a blue scarf?
Hey!
Did you see a middle-aged woman?
She has short hair and wore a blue scarf.
I don't think so. I'm fixing a boat.
I'm alone too, as you see.
(Yungcheon Seobu Patrol Division)
Look at this.
Your mother last made a call on the road to Seoul.
That was 20 minutes ago.
Call her again.
(Gwanak, Anyang)
In those four beats
There is love, breakup
And tears
The receiver cannot be reached.
I'm sure she'll come home.
Yes, Hyun Ji. You must've been mistaken.
What if she's on a stakeout and can't answer her phone?
I saw it clearly.
A man in black swung a stick.
What's the intelligence bureau chief doing here?
You must be busy with work.
Mom.
Come inside.
Come this way.
We have her on camera at the pier,
but not boarding a boat.
I have to look into something.
I'm alone too, as you see.
If you want a missing person's team...
or a detective on the case,
what we have now just isn't enough.
- Let's wait... - The man that just came in.
Does he work here?
(Seobu Patrol Division)
What got into you now? You've been really weird today.
- We can't find her here. - What?
We'll send you all the cases from the other patrol divisions too.
All the missing person's cases that come in after today,
- send them directly to me. - I got one just now.
Who's missing?
A female in her 50s, a lieutenant from Seonneung Patrol Division.
Her daughter was just here.
Yungcheon Prosecutors' Office.
Like you said, Oh Tae Seok's cleaning up.
Director Wi Ye Nam took Mayor Do on a yacht.
I think something happened on board.
We must find out what.
Mayor Do wouldn't have turned against us over money.
- Hi. - The cop's daughter...
went to a prosecutor.
Stop her. You must stop her.
Why did things get so messed up?
You couldn't even clean up the death of a girl?
A prosecutor's involved.
Don't you see it's beyond my reach now?
There's no time.
Make the call.
What shall I say?
Okay, I understand. Sure.
File a document at the Public Service Center,
and they'll check the case.
No, I must see someone now.
I must talk to a prosecutor, not a police officer.
Sorry, but could you call someone else?
What's the matter?
(Prosecutor)
Here.
Thank you.
Your mother who is an officer disappeared and somehow...
you think the police is involved?
- Yes. - You saw what happened...
on a boat out at sea? That's a long way off.
No, I saw it clearly.
I wish I were wrong but...
- Here you go. - Thanks.
(Personnel File)
The person you mentioned is an officer.
Can I have a look?
The police said there's no CCTV footage.
If we're to gather evidence, we need time as well.
Sorry but right now,
all I can say is that you wait.
I hope your mother calls you in the meantime.
What a rare sight.
You are waiting for me instead of sleeping.
I'm surprised.
I thought you'd come running, asking me what it was about.
You seem like the anxious one, not me.
So Oh Tae Seok has killed someone.
On top of that, it's a cop.
But why?
Something probably went down before that.
You should've discussed it with me first, since I'm your husband.
Laugh at me all you want.
And don't say anything.
Don't try to find out more either.
You can decide the price, and add it to the alimony.
Why would I receive money from you?
Don't you think, Ye Nam?
I thought we reached an agreement.
No, I can't go away like this.
Everything I'm enjoying right now...
will become useless once we get divorced.
The son-in-law of Deo Group.
That's the last title I can rely on.
Don't try to meddle with it.
Cha Seung Jae!
Besides, I still love you.
Let's sleep in the same bed tonight, Ye Nam.
You jerk!
The receiver cannot be reached. You will be directed to voicemail.
I'll call you a taxi, so take it.
Call her a taxi, she's headed to Hyeonam-dong.
(Lee Hyun Ji, Seonneung-dong)
It says on my ID that my address is Seonneung-dong.
How did he know?
- Mi Jin, you have to get up now. - What is it?
Did your mom call?
Wake Ye Jun up and get him dressed. We have to leave.
Hyun Ji, what's the matter this time?
Hurry up and get dressed! We have to get out of here.
Mom, where are we going?
Ye Jun.
Don't say anything, and just run with me, okay?
Do you understand?
Are the people who hurt your mom after us too?
Oh, no.
I'm so out of breath.
Come here. Hurry.
What do you want us to do in here?
I'll lose him and come back. Don't go anywhere and wait, okay?
Don't come out.
Get in.
Thank you.
But how did you know?
Are you okay?
Wait, hold on. We have to go back.
Hurry, please.
Where are they?
Let me see that.
Where's the girl?
Did Jenny Jang take her?
I'm afraid so.
She'll use that cop's daughter as a hostage and threaten me.
That brat Jenny Jang will try to take away everything from me.
I've gotten rid of everything that can be used as evidence.
Even if this case comes up to the surface,
it won't be connected to Mayor Do...
or you in any way.
You will...
take the blame for everything?
If it becomes a problem,
I will.
To me, you are...
someone I cannot live without.
20 years ago, and now as well.
I must meet Mayor Do.
I have to make a move...
before Jenny Jang does something.
I've confirmed a woman in her 30s and a little boy...
have not been taken by Oh Tae Seok's men.
Thank you.
Don't be mistaken.
We're not trying to save you.
We're just people trying to use you.
Still, you're on the other side.
The people who hurt my mom...
And the people who want to hurt me.
At least you're not on the same side as them.
That's good enough.
That's enough for me, so thank you.
Chairwoman Kim, I found this while cleaning the house.
(Letter of Resignation)
(Letter of Resignation, Wi Jung Hyuk)
His belongings are still in here.
There's no need to clean. Throw away everything!
What do you mean, write up a written agreement?
It hasn't been passed by the Urban Planning Committee yet,
and it's too early for this.
Then I guess this will have to do instead.
What is this?
Write up a will for me.
(Looking for a Kitchen Helper)
Gosh, no. I can't do it.
Mom, where are we going to sleep tonight?
Where is Hyun Ji?
I don't know either!
My gosh! Oh, no.
- Goodness, it's all wet. - Mom.
Put it back in. Not now.
My gosh, it's soaked.
Here you go.
Sorry? Why are you giving me this?
Well, so that you can wipe yourself.
My gosh! What are you looking at? And you're standing way too close!
Sorry?
- Well, I was just... - See? You're doing it again!
Mister, you were staring at my chest just now.
How could you sexually harass me like this in broad daylight?
Help! This molester is trying to run away!
- My gosh! - Goodness, look!
Mom.
Mom!
Mom...
Give me some settlement money and get lost.
Here.
Thank you.
Good job, my sweet pumpkin!
(Last Will and Testament)
Promise me that you will never...
desert me and Deo Cosmetics no matter what happens.
That is what I need.
(I, Do Jun Sub...)
(Did you have a good time on the yacht?)
I'll trade the original file with you for 20 big bills.
I'll give you three days.
- Hello? - This is so messed up.
I can't believe you threatened me after ruining everything.
- What happened? - The video clip...
There is a video clip.
Someone's threatening me using a video that shows the dead girl!
Find out who's doing this at once.
If you can't stop this, I won't go down alone.
Both you and I will be doomed.
Who could it be?
Who recorded a video of it?
I'll track down everyone who was at the party.
It's only a matter of time. We'll be able to find who did it.
Darn it!
Why won't you share any information with me?
Because I'm a member of the Deo family?
I just think it'll be better for your sake as well.
I guess you don't know me well.
I've known Jenny Jang since I was nine.
I grew up confiding in her a lot more...
than in my own sister, who is greedy and spoiled.
I'm on Jenny's side.
Why?
Because she'll fight the war against Director Wi on your behalf?
What matters is that we're comrades at the moment.
I mean, who knows...
when you'll turn your coat?
I know you're keeping a girl with you.
Why aren't you reporting it to your boss?
Do you not like the idea of Jenny winning against Ye Nam...
and marrying my brother?
For now, I'll pretend not to know about it.
Because we're on the same side.
You're evil. How could you stab your teacher?
They say you should never take in someone else's child.
Even brutes won't do such a thing.
She didn't do it. I stabbed him.
- Sun Woo. - That teacher started it.
She clearly told him not to do it,
but he came by every night and bothered her.
How dare you glare at me like that, you brat!
Do Young.
The police have confirmed that Sun Woo was the one who stabbed him.
He's very young, so he'll be on probation.
Thankfully, his stab wound isn't too deep.
He called and said he'll return to work next week.
But one of you has to leave because of what happened.
We're offering a bit of money to help you stand on your own feet.
If you decide to leave,
I'll find a place for you to stay until you turn 18.
Do Young!
Let go! Let go of me.
Let go!
Do Young!
We found the girl Oh Tae Seok was after.
Her mom is a cop.
I think she has something to do with the incident on the yacht.
(President Wi Jung Hyuk)
We need something more concrete.
Even if the cop and Oh Tae Seok are exposed,
Ye Nam and Mayor Do won't be affected.
Why are you calling nonstop when you can't even keep your woman safe?
- Let me talk to Do Young. - I'm her lawyer.
You can talk to me if you got something to say.
Tell her I've submitted my letter of resignation.
Mr. Wi...
has resigned.
Running away for love?
Nice excuse.
Hello, Ms. Jang.
Tell everyone to leave the room so that we can talk in private.
Sun Woo.
Ms. Jang.
Some jerks are threatening me using this video clip.
You know how those jerks are.
Offering money won't silence them.
This will eventually bog me down.
I'll call back later.
I took care of the girl.
Now, nothing...
can hinder your bright future.
But I want...
my company, Deo Cosmetics,
to be your partner in the international city project...
instead of Deo Hotel.
Ms. Jang, it must've been very stressful for you.
I was distracted for a short while...
because Director Wi kept pestering me,
but she obviously can't outshine you.
Let's find the person who recorded the video and take care of it.
After that, we can build the international city together.
What's with that reaction?
I'm giving you another chance.
Why must I build the international city with you?
What are you talking about?
We've worked together toward the same goal for the past seven years.
I know you want to build the international city...
so that you can run for President after that.
I gave you...
that dream.
You were...
a politician wannabe from the country.
I clothed you, fed you,
and taught you how to talk and walk.
From your candidate nomination to the election,
I paved the way with my money.
After all that,
you stabbed me in the back.
Why do you think I didn't say a word so far?
Because I considered changing horses...
to work with a new mayor instead.
Why?
Now you are worried?
You didn't think much of me.
Leave.
Whether I release the video, make you a killer, and ruin you,
or block the video's release and give you another chance,
I need to think about it.
Oh, one more thing.
Show some remorse.
Why don't you value me and mess things up yourself?
Sun Woo, let's track a video.
A son of a witch...
killed a girl with drugs.
You still play go.
Is it because you like it or just out of spite?
I like it.
I'm happy when I win,
and when I lose...
I'm happy to find out why I lost.
Is that humanly possible?
Are you okay with not being a pro?
Yes.
My goodness.
I'd love it if I could be a crime-busting officer,
but if I had to be on patrol forever, I'd hate it.
There are still matches to win.
Whether I'm a pro or an amateur.
Hey, kid.
Stop it.
My goodness, you.
There's no stopping you, is there?
How did it get into such a mess?
Ms. Wi did her best.
Mayor Do got into trouble...
Either way.
You couldn't clean it up.
That sly mayor fool...
changed sides again and went back to Jenny.
It's not over yet, Mom.
There's still a way to clean it up.
Mayor Do can't ignore the cards up my sleeve.
Hello, Chairwoman Kim.
Mom.
You called her?
Sit.
Mom, I haven't lost yet.
I can head the international city project.
I see you heard the story.
I came here to ask you for an urgent favor.
Okay.
As you know, Deo's future depends on...
the international city project.
It will decide...
whether in the next 10 years Deo will become...
one of the top 10 groups.
You can't just be the developer,
but for the next decade or century after the project's completed,
Deo must be in management.
What about that?
All that depends on my wedding...
that will happen at noon tomorrow.
Wedding?
Noon tomorrow?
It's the time you were going to marry my Jung Hyuk.
I will get married as planned.
Then Deo Group will be named developer.
How are you so sure?
Don't fall for it, Mom.
She's bluffing and even blackmailing you.
I'll deal with Mayor Do.
I'll sort it out...
and get him to sign the contract as if nothing happened.
Okay?
Mom.
You won't give in, will you?
It's a marriage.
Will you really make her part of the family?
What if I don't permit that?
What'll you do then?
Will you elope with Jung Hyuk...
and marry like immature kids?
I'll find another company.
Jogwang Group would work.
It's their opportunity to beat Deo, their 30-year rival.
They'd take the plunge.
No businessman...
hands over the goods before checking if they have money to pay.
If you win the developer deal,
then you can marry and join the family.
A smart businessman makes an investment...
based on the chances.
If you only make safe investments,
you waste your time counting chump change.
That's what you taught me.
I wonder if you still have the wise eye of investment.
I'd like to...
have a simple wedding...
in the front garden of this mansion.
If you'll excuse me.
I'm getting married tomorrow.
I should put on a mask pack.
Mom.