[English subtitles are available]
Thank you, honey.
Ms. Ning Mochen.
On the day they fall into the lake,
the world is drenched with torrential rain.
At this critical moment...
They both manage to survive.
The main female character is reincarnated.
She then triumphs over her enemies and finally changes her life, right?
Yeah.
I can always predict how this kind of story ends
when I read the beginning of it.
Didn't you tell me to write an exciting and dramatic story
where the main female character takes revenge?
You also said the first few scenes had to be eye-catching,
and appealing to the readers
so as to captivate their attention, right?
Then where is the creative element I asked for?
Where's the dramatic part?
There has to be slumps before a rousing climax.
Rising from the lowest point brings the most joy.
Ms. Ai, I'm not being harsh here,
but I just hope the beginning of the story
contains all the elements I've asked for.
I hope the readers can grasp the gist
of this story at first sight.
If I add every element you want into the story,
it'll only end up a huge mess
that repulses the readers.
But the project will be canceled if what you draw falls below expectations.
Fine. I'll add a big twist to it right away.
[Perfect Her]
[Episode 2]
[Ruikang Hospital]
Isn't she Ning Mochen, who was brought here yesterday after drowning?
I heard that a female patient named Bai Li
fell into water at the same time as her.
Isn't it weird?
[Ruikang Hospital]
There must be a feud between them.
Was my body switched with Ning Mochen's
because we fell into water at the same time?
Chen?
You have awoken?
Look what you've done to me...
Do you even have a conscience?
What have I done?
Everything you told me before
was a lie, wasn't it?
Chen,
I know what you're thinking.
The fact that I'm in Bai Li's ward instead of yours
has made you mad, right?
This is a public place.
Look, Bai Li is lying in bed now.
Even God is trying to fix us up, right?
Ye Yunkai!
Ning Mochen!
You human scum!
How could you do this to me?
-Mochen, what are you doing?
-Let go of me!
Ning Mochen, are you out of your mind?
Let go of me!
Is Su Yu the reason
that you're treating me like this?
I'm sorry, Chen.
You were yelling at me, so I flew into a rage.
Don't be mad at me, alright?
Chen?
Chen!
Look, Bai Li is lying in bed now.
Even God is trying to fix us up, right?
Cha!
Hey! What are you doing?
I'm so happy to see you here!
What's wrong with you? Let go of me!
Hear me out!
-Let go!
-When I suddenly
woke up in the hospital,
I realized that I wasn't Ning Mochen...
How dare you show up in front of me?
You homewrecker!
You seduced Bai Li's husband.
Don't ever show your face again.
I'll beat you up if I see you again!
Crazy woman!
Cha,
I'm not Ning Mochen.
I'm Bai...
Bai...
Su Yu.
Ning Mochen,
is this what you want?
Bai Li is still in a coma now.
Do you take pleasure in breaking families apart,
and bringing misfortune upon others?
You're mistaken.
I'm not Ning Mochen.
I'm Bai...
What stunt are you pulling now?
The doctor has checked on you.
You're all fine.
You can be discharged this afternoon.
Su Yu,
please hear me out.
Every sentence you say
disgusts me.
If Bai Li can't wake up,
I'll make you pay for that.
I'm not Ning Mochen.
Cha,
I’m Bai…
I'm not Ning Mochen.
I'm Bai...
Why?
Whenever I try to say who I really am,
I would feel dizzy as if my soul is being pulled away.
Is there something unusual
that keeps me from revealing my real identity?
Is it related to Bai Li who is unconscious in bed now?
Ning Mochen,
are you occupying my body now?
Hang in there.
I must find a way to switch our bodies back.
I swear I'll find a way to switch our bodies back.
Ms. Ning, are you going home?
Home?
What home?
Your own home, of course.
Mr. Ning asked me to pick you up.
Be careful.
Now, what I know is,
Ning Mochen and I fell into the same pool of water
at the same time.
What kind of bizarre thing
happened to us in the water
and caused this trouble?
So this is Ning Mochen's home?
Su Yu?
What are you doing here?
I've been waiting for you.
You were just discharged from the hospital.
I'm worried about you.
Are we living together?
Su Yu, I’m a little tired today.
I want to be alone.
You should go and take a rest.
What nonsense are you talking about?
How can I leave you alone at home?
Ning Mochen,
do you even know what you're saying?
Are you trying to mess up everything?
Su Yu, I...
Let’s go upstairs.
What?
Watch out. There are stairs.
Have you forgotten that we might be heard?
What?
Are you pretending to have lost your memories?
What devious plan are you hatching now?
Are you doing this to me
because of my relationship with Ye Yunkai?
Ning Mochen, I'm gonna say this again.
We simply faked our engagement.
I don't care if you're involved with another man.
But you really shouldn't have hurt Bai Li.
A fake engagement?
Let me ask you something.
Did you investigate me,
and destroy Bai Li's family on purpose?
I don't know.
I really don't know anything.
Are you leaving?
Yes, I am!
I can't bear to be in the same room as you for another second!
But I promised your parents
to stay here and take care of you tonight.
I'll sleep in the next room.
What is going on with Su Yu?
Why would he become
completely different all of a sudden?
My soul is in Ning Mochen's body now.
Is Su Yu somehow forced to stick with Ning Mochen?
You have a fiance.
Why do you have to do this?
Are you seeking thrills?
Thrills?
It is thrilling.
Ye Yunkai keeps saying
how beautiful and tender his wife is.
I would love to see what happens
when a woman like you is driven mad.
It must be fun, right?
How do you like my face?
Your husband loves it very much.
Why?
Why must my soul be in Ning Mochen's body?
I have to figure out what made this happen.
Mochen, good morning.
Come have breakfast.
Come on.
Dig in.
What's the matter with Su Yu?
Why is his attitude all different again?
There must be a secret
between him and Ning Mochen.
It seems like Su Yu is not just attracted to Ning Mochen's pretty looks.
About Bai Li...
How is she doing?
Has she woken up yet?
Wipe those crocodile tears of yours.
Then I guess she is still in a coma.
I'd like to pay her a visit.
You have just gotten well.
You should stay home and rest.
I'm fine.
I'm more worried about her.
I already said no.
Her husband is with her now.
We shouldn't disturb her.
That's exactly why I need to visit her.
Look, there's food all over your mouth.
Ning Mochen,
I'm warning you,
stay away from Bai Li.
Eat up.
I know you hate it when I approach Bai Li.
However,
I insist on visiting her.
Okay.
I’ll go with you then.
Su Yu,
well...
How much do you know about
my relationship with Ye Yunkai?
How long have I been with him?
You told me about it, remember?
I know nothing about you,
and I'm not interested at all.
So it's news to you too.
How long have we been engaged?
Ning Mochen, what are you trying to say?
My head got a bit fuzzy after I woke up.
There are many things I can't recall now.
We got engaged a month ago.
Ning Mochen,
I don't care how you dally with men outside.
We're just cooperating with each other.
We aren't supposed to interfere with each other's personal life.
After we reach our respective goals,
we'll stop doing what we're doing now.
But don't you forget
that if anything happens to Bai Li,
I'll hold you accountable.
She will wake up.
She will.
You'd better pray for that.
Su Yu,
isn't Bai Li a schoolmate of yours?
Why didn't you contact her in the past few years?
Why didn't you tell her about your return and engagement?
I didn't see a reason to contact her.
The woman lying in bed
is my wife who I've been with for years.
Let's wait and see what happens.
My wife is the love of my life.
This accident
got her into a vegetative state.
I have no idea when she will come to.
All the products of Chenyun Jewelry
were designed by me and her together.
A lot of people have told me to give up,
saying
that it is meaningless
to stay with someone who might never wake up.
But,
however hard my life gets,
or even if I have to spend every penny I own,
I will never give up on my wife.
Honey,
many people like our designs.
Our rings have contributed to
some successful marriage proposals.
We are also the reason
for some people to believe in true love.
Honey,
can you please wake up?
Lots of people are waiting for us
to design jewelry for them.
What are you doing?
You wanna help Ye Yunkai rub salt in Bai Li's wound?
Su Yu,
believe it or not,
I'm as angry as you are.
Knock it off, hypocrite.
Why are you angry?
Is this eating at your conscience? Are you feeling remorse?
Do you even have those things?
[Regulations on Ward Management]
Mr. Su,
when did you arrive?
Thank you for visiting Bai Li.
I don't know when she will wake up.
I've heard a lot about you from Bai Li.
It's a shame that I couldn't have a longer talk with you in the ceremony.
Actually, I've always liked your works.
I hope there will be an opportunity to work with you.
I believe if Bai Li were awake,
she would love to see us designing jewelry together.
I'm here to visit Bai Li today.
I don't want to talk about other things.
Okay.
Well, I'll leave you to it.
Ms. Ning,
can I have a word with you?
Stop it.
Drop the act.
Su Yu can’t see us now.
What act?
If it weren't for the purpose of impressing Su Yu,
why would you ever come to visit Bai Li?
You keep surprising me, Chen.
You can be innocent and seductive,
aloof and sweet.
What is wrong?
Are you jealous?
Don't think too much.
I invited that reporter over.
I said those things only to sell more jewelry.
Ye Yunkai,
you're milking Bai Li's misfortune.
You're inhuman.
So I'm inhuman?
What's the purpose of your visit then?
You can put up a show but I can't?
At least I've admitted it was an act.
What about you?
Have you gotten so used to acting that you can't get back to real life?
Chen, I know what is going on.
Recently, because of Su Yu,
you've started to feel differently about me.
But soon I will prove to you
that I’m better than Su Yu.
It won't take long
before you receive a surprise prepared by me.
Aren't you gonna ask what the surprise is?
I'm not interested.
Bai Li,
in the past ten years,
I refrained from contacting you,
because I knew you were having a good life,
and I didn't want to disturb you.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Sorry.
Hi, everyone, my name is Bai Li.
Welcome to our studio.
From now on, if you have any questions,
feel free to come and ask me.
Thank you.
I wish I had come back earlier.
[Regulations on Ward Management]
We rarely have a gathering like this.
Shall we have dinner together?
I'd rather not.
[Regulations on Ward Management]
I hope you'll take good care of Bai Li.
If anything happens to her,
I'll hold you responsible.
[Regulations on Ward Management]
Sure.
She is my wife.
Why wouldn't I take good care of her?
I'm going to my company.
Suit yourself.
Ning Moxi?
She is Ning Mochen's younger sister.
Hello?
[S&YU Jewelry Design Corporation]
Hello, Mr. Su.
Boss,
why would you come back to work today?
Anything wrong?
Hello, Mr. Su.
I heard Ms. Ning had an accident.
Is she okay?
All alive and kicking.
Great. I'm glad she's fine.
When I heard the news,
I was shocked.
Ms. Ning is so lucky.
Boss, when will we start
cooperating with Ningmei Jewelry?
It is not the right time yet.
Ningmei Jewelry is a time-honored brand in the country,
but they're already lagging behind in designs and silver jewelry production.
In contrast, we're running a thriving, fashionable
and popular brand of silver jewelry.
We're just seeking a larger platform that can help us further develop.
If we partner with Ningmei Jewelry,
we'll both benefit.
But, Boss,
it is true love that has brought you and Ms. Ning together.
It has nothing to do with business.
You are a perfect match.
By the way, when is your wedding?
It'll be a sensation, right?
Boss, I'll get back to work.
[Peng Yu]
Hello.
Ms. Ning,
you finally answered my call.
You made an appointment for today. Are you still coming?
What is it about?
I'm Peng Yu,
your therapist.
Oh.
Today is not good for me.
Let's postpone it.
I gave a call to Ning Mochen,
and she was so polite on the phone.
When I asked her to come home for dinner,
she even said "thank you."
Everything is odd.
First, she suddenly hooked up with Su Yu.
Then, she had a serious accident,
but she managed to stay unscathed.
I guess she was just lucky.
Anyway,
the cooperation with Su Yu means a lot to your father now.
Mochen has become Su Yu's fiancee.
For the time being, we'd better be kind to her.
The woman on the left
must be Ning Zhaoxiong's third wife, Chen Ling.
The girl on the right
must be Ning Moxi, the daughter
of Ning Zhaoxiong and his second wife.
What a complicated family!
Chen, you're back!
Chen,
welcome home.
Hi, Sis.
Mom.
What did you call me?
This has never happened before.
What's wrong?
I'm not used to hearing you say "Sis" and "Mom."
Maybe you should get back to calling us by our names.
It sounds creepy when you call us in that chummy way.
Xi,
how could you talk to your sister like that?
Mochen is your older sister.
You two are related by blood.
I'm so happy that she calls me "Mom."
Come on, Chen.
Let’s sit on the couch.
Did Su Yu drive you home?
No, I came here myself.
He's your fiance,
and you just had an accident.
Why didn’t he drive you home?
Chen, you and Su Yu are engaged now.
You might as well marry him soon.
Have you two decided when to tie the knot?
We're not sure yet.
Let's go downstairs.
Your dad is there waiting for us.
Let's go.
Come on.
Zhaoxiong, Chen is here.
Sit.
You've recovered?
Huh?
Oh.
I'm fine now.
Why didn't you
call us when you were discharged from the hospital?
Hey, Zhaoxiong,
you know Chen loves to have fun.
At least she is back now, right?
She has a fiance now.
It's time to settle down.
Listen,
you're perfectly aware of Ningmei Jewelry's current situation.
It's being threatened by many new brands.
We're in urgent need of a creative
and famous designer like Su Yu.
I hope you can make good use of your relationship with him.
Don't mess it up. Got it?
Chen, your dad is talking to you.
Dad, I think Chen has tried her best.
You'd hate for your daughter
to lose her dignity, right?
Mr. Ning, Ye Yunkai is here for a visit.
Can I go with you?
Mr. Ning.
There you are, Ye.
Ms. Ning.
Come on. Have a seat.
Ye,
it's late at night. What are you here for?
When Ms. Ning attended my wife and my
10th wedding anniversary celebration,
she got into an accident.
I feel terribly sorry for that.
This is why I'm here for a visit.
Is that all?
Mr. Ning, during this visit,
I'd also like to discuss
future cooperation with you.
Go on.
You see, since I received media interviews,
more attention has been drawn to me and my wife.
As a result, the sales and popularity of Chenyun Jewelry
have reached a new level.
I think
we can be a great partner for Ningmei Jewelry now that we're in a better position.
Look,
Ye,
your products are fast moving consumer goods.
I think Ningmei Jewelry deserves a better qualified partner.
It's true that you've received media interviews
where you talk about love stories.
It seems like a great publicity campaign,
but I'm not sure
how much good it will do to your brand.
Listen,
Mr. Ning,
today I came here also to tell you
that an inheritor of intangible cultural heritage,
namely the master of jade carving Mr. Feng,
is going to be our strategic partner.
By then, Chenyun Jewelry's brand image will be totally different.
Mr. Feng has just won an award.
He has now been thrust into the limelight.
Besides, he is a very eccentric man.
He has refused many big companies' invitations.
Ye, are you sure you can persuade him?
Although it is difficult,
I'll still try my best to make it come true.
Well, when you make that happen,
we'll talk again.
Okay.
I should get going.
Let me show you out, Mr. Ye.
What do you think, Chen?
This is the surprise I told you about.
How did you get to know Mr. Feng?
Mr. Feng and Bai Li are close friends.
Bai Li is sick in bed now,
and I'm taking good care of her.
Mr. Feng has been deeply moved,
saying that I can ask him for help if I'm in need.
As I told you before,
I'll be more successful than Su Yu.
You and I can help each other too.
You're not only using Bai Li,
but also taking advantage of her friend
in her name.
How many more shameful things are you capable of?
Shameful?
There is no limit to what I can do for you.
What?
Are you still not satisfied?
You are really going to leave me for Su Yu.
Am I just a piece of worthless trash to you?
Why would Su Yu get together with you?
All he wants is profit too.
He might ditch you at any time.
Taking my side
is the best choice for you.
You're a smart girl.
I believe you'll make a wise decision.
I'm not smart.
In this world,
I'm the biggest fool.
Chen,
why am I feeling
that the accident
has turned you into a different person?