[English subtitles are available]
Come out!
Call me Dad.
How can you accomplish big things without being ruthless?
Your dear senior is still my wife.
Why are you doing this?
People die for money. Birds die for food.
This is Mr. Su’s design.
It seems to have more of a feminine touch.
The meal and the hospital took up half of this chapter.
It's not necessary to use all the space
to explain the main male character's difficulties.
I'll say it again.
The main male character's revenge target is the female's father.
Just wait.
It's the darkness before dawn.
It's the rising action.
You mean the main characters won't open their mouths
and can't say anything?
Boss, look.
For example, we don't have a very good relationship.
So tell me,
even if your impression of me changes after a long time,
will you believe everything I say?
Of course...
I won't.
But I can test you.
If you don't believe me, what's the use of testing?
Does the main female character believe in the male character?
Why won't she ask him directly for help
and work together?
Isn't that better?
That's right.
That's the next chapter.
Next, next, next.
It's like a drama.
You always tell me it'll be better after episode 4,
it'll be better after episode 8.
Do I have to wait until you finish it all before it's good?
Boss,
the main female character was hurt before.
Even in front of her former junior,
she still has to keep things back.
Plus, she can't reveal her identity now.
Keeping a distance is a type of self-protection.
It's like her defense mechanism.
I guess you're the only one who's right.
Of course.
You can go now.
I have work to do.
[Perfect Her]
[Episode 9]
[Beidao Cocktail & Whisky Bar]
Mr. Su?
What brings you here?
Cha,
I came to ask you a question.
Aren't you busy preparing the wedding with that home-wrecker?
I have nothing to tell you.
You're not welcome here. Please leave.
Let me ask my question first.
Su Yu, let me ask you.
Do you not think you've let Bai Li down?
She is still hospitalized and in a coma because of that home-wrecker,
while you went to work with that scumbag Ye Yunkai.
Let me ask you.
Does nothing matter when you're faced with interests?
Bai Li used to tell me
that she had a junior named Su Yu,
who was a genius and a good man.
She was very proud of him.
I didn't expect you to not be able to tell right from wrong.
You really let Bai Li down.
Yes,
I did let her down.
You and that bitch Ning Mochen really love acting,
but I'm sorry.
I won't fall for this.
Please leave.
Let me ask my question first.
I'll leave as soon as I finish.
Spit it out.
I heard you went to Ye Yunkai's place
after Senior fell into a coma
and took all her things, right?
Bai Li's things
shouldn't stay in such a filthy place anymore.
Did you see a notebook of hand-drawn designs?
No.
Even if I did,
I wouldn't give it to you.
Leave.
I don't want to see you.
[Beidao Cocktail & Whisky Bar]
Hello, Ms. Ning.
I’m at the door of the bar.
I was about to talk to you about this.
The owner is here too.
Okay, Ms. Ning.
We'll agree with your terms
and you'll continue to pay half of the rent,
but I have to remind you.
This bar's performance isn't too great.
Okay.
Okay, bye.
Hello.
I have a question.
Is the Ms. Ning that you mentioned in the call
Ning Mochen of Ningmei Jewelry?
You know her?
She's my fiancée.
You are so lucky.
Ms. Ning is a great person.
What do you mean?
I am the business manager of this district.
Ms. Ning has been paying half of the rent for this bar
and won't let me tell the boss.
How long has she been doing this?
It's been a while,
but I don't remember exactly how long it's been.
Thank you.
Mr. Xu,
what brings you here?
I was just passing by,
so I came to let you know
that your rent for this quarter is the same.
I'll give you a 50% discount,
but you have to improve
your bar's performance.
Okay, I will.
Thank you so much.
Why are you still here?
You knew Ning Mochen before.
How would I know her?
However, she does
like to come to get insulted by me for no reason,
just like you.
You two are a perfect match.
Chen,
I've been waiting for you.
What are you doing here?
I heard you were discharged from the hospital.
I came to celebrate with you.
Look.
I even prepared the wine.
I walked around your house just now.
I found you and Su Yu are still sleeping in separate rooms.
Stop beating around the bush.
What are you doing here?
You should have received the news.
The anticipation of the preorder for my collaboration with Su Yu's company
is at an all time high.
We'll soon become a top brand.
How did you
manage to make Su Yu agree to cooperate with you?
I have something Su Yu can’t get.
I have his Achilles' heel in my hands.
What is it?
Let me put it this way.
I, Ye Yunkai,
am no longer a nobody that you can look down on.
You don’t need to marry Su Yu anymore.
You are free now.
Soon,
we can be together legitimately.
As for Bai Li,
her condition is getting worse.
I think she will die soon.
For you,
I can speed things up for her.
What are you going to do?
I can create some accidents on her.
Ye Yunkai,
you're a monster.
What can I do?
Because...
Chen, you're the one I love.
I feel disgusted when I see you.
Get lost.
I did all this for you.
What else do you want me to do?
In your eyes,
you've always thought lowly of me,
right?
You know your place well.
Yes.
I know
that I'm a jerk to you.
That's right.
I'm a jerk.
I abandoned my wife
to pursue you, who is more perfect and powerful.
Was I wrong?
Isn't this how men should be?
To pursue higher goals and higher status.
This is how the world is.
Everyone is realistic.
Plus, I didn't let you down.
I've always fulfilled all of your requests.
No matter the time and place,
I've always been there for you.
And for you,
I even abandoned my wife.
For me?
Ye Yunkai,
stop making excuses for yourself.
What excuse?
Look at your father, Ning Zhaoxiong.
He's had so many wives.
Has anyone said anything about him?
No,
because he's powerful.
I, Ye Yunkai,
can only become stronger,
and stronger,
in order for you to think I'm qualified to be with you, right?
Chen,
I really love you.
You love me too,
right?
Admit it.
You love me too.
I've done so much for you.
You can't say you don't love me.
I loved you,
but now,
I just feel sorry for you.
You're like a maggot.
You believe the world is rotten,
because only in this way
can you accept your ugly nature.
Ye Yunkai.
Now,
you won't have the chance to hurt me anymore.
Ning Mochen, listen.
Countless women will love me in the future.
Don't come crying to me then.
Ye Yunkai didn't keep his promise.
After signing the contract with me,
he refused to hand over your custody.
You'll be in danger
every day that he doesn't do so.
I suspect he never wanted to hand it over.
Instead, he's already decided
to kill you
at the right time.
But don't worry, Senior.
I knew he would cheat me,
so I have another plan.
Senior.
Can you hear me, Senior?
Nurse!
Excuse me.
Please wait. You can't go in.
Who are you to her?
I'm her junior.
Inform her family to come.
Something happened to her. Come to the hospital.
Ye Yunkai.
I'll destroy you if you don't come to the hospital.
[Ruikang Rehabilitation Hospital]
[Ruikang Hospitall]
Why isn't the patient's family here yet?
How is the patient?
I'm her husband.
Here's the thing.
The patient has been in a coma for too long.
All her bodily functions are deteriorating.
Problems have occurred in her brain.
We need surgery now.
What will happen if we don't do surgery?
She might never wake up.
Doctor,
what are the risks for this surgery?
Let me put it this way.
This surgery has
around a 20% failure rate,
but if the surgery succeeds,
the patient will maintain the current condition
and might even wake up.
Then,
what will happen if it fails?
Her life will be in danger.
This is the agreement.
Take a look and sign it.
Sign it.
No.
Are you afraid that she'll wake up after the surgery?
What are you talking about?
I'm doing this due to considerations about Bai Li's life.
The doctor just said
the surgery has a 20% chance of failure.
Bai Li can die.
Then should we give up and make her never wake up?
The 20% chance of failure
means there's an 80% chance of success.
I'm not scared of anything
except "if."
Ye Yunkai,
I don't think you're afraid of her dying.
You're just afraid that she'll wake up.
Only when she's in a coma
can you threaten me with her custody.
Are you even human?
How can you still think about interests right now?
Su Yu, get it straight.
That's my wife inside.
If you force me to do the surgery
and she dies on the operating table,
can you take the responsibility?
If Bai Li dies,
it'll all be your fault.
What are you doing here?
I already heard of the news.
Su Yu,
Bai Li needs surgery.
Why are you here?
Ye Yunkai, let me tell you.
You must sign this today.
This is my family matter.
It's none of your business.
I see.
You want Bai Li to die.
Both of you want Bai Li to die.
Do you refuse to sign it
because you want her stay in the hospital bed forever
like the living dead?
Su Yu,
Bai Li is not someone who gives up easily.
As long as there is a one percent chance,
I believe she will take the risk.
Is this the work you'll join the China-France Joint Exhibition with?
Yes.
Using steel to connect the porcelain
so it's both firm and soft...
Great idea.
These are all defective.
They can't be used.
Are you using red porcelain?
Red porcelain is extremely difficult to create.
The bold red glaze has low heat resistance,
but porcelain
needs to be fired at 1450 degrees to form.
That's right.
That's why they say it's hard for 1,000 kilns to produce one product.
But the exhibition is coming soon.
If you keep trying like this,
you won't have any finished products.
Change the material.
Actually, I'm also not confident
that I can make a qualified finished product,
but this red porcelain
is so mesmerizing.
So even if there is a one percent chance,
I have to take the risk.
Ye Yunkai,
if you don't sign it,
our cooperation ends here.
The Ning family will definitely terminate the contract with you too.
[Keep Quiet]
Don't you know that if you go back on your word after signing the contract,
you'll have to pay a huge fee for liquidated damages?
I don't care.
Sign it.
[Keep Quiet]
You really spare no expenses.
[Surgery in Progress]
She'll be fine.
[Surgery Room Environment Maintenance System]
I didn’t expect Mr. Su to be so devoted.
You're so worried about someone else's wife
that your hands are trembling.
Ye Yunkai,
if anything happens to my senior,
I won't forgive you.
Mr. Su,
can we be reasonable here?
You begged me
to do the surgery.
You forced me
to give my signature.
If anything happens to Bai Li,
it's your fault.
Besides,
I don't want anything to happen to my wife either.
If anything happens to her,
my custody will be useless.
What can I use to threaten you with,
right?
Custody?
Could it be that he's cooperating with Ye Yunkai
for me in the hospital bed?
You love my wife so much.
Even I am touched.
I believe
if such a loving man is waiting for her,
she won't want to die.
I didn't expect my wife to be so attractive.
She's in a coma,
yet she can still make a man give up everything for her.
What’s wrong?
Su Yu.
Su Yu, what are you doing?
Don’t come over!
Don't come over.
Don't come over!
[Surgery in Progress]
Doctor, how is Bai Li?
Don't worry. She's fine.
[Ruikang Hospital]
Did she wake up?
Not yet.
She's still in a coma,
but all her physical indicators
are back to normal.
[Ruikang Hospital]
It's not easy for her to get through this.
There's still hope for her to wake up.
Thank you, doctor.
You've worked hard.
How did you know something happened to her?
The attending doctor told me.
I told him
that if anything happens to Bai Li,
he must let me know immediately.
That's strange.
Why do you care so much about her suddenly?
Su Yu,
believe it or not,
Ye Yunkai is the only person I truly hate.
So,
is what Ye Yunkai said true?
What?
You
love Bai Li?
Yes,
but it's just my one-sided feelings.
Senior doesn't know anything.
She definitely never crossed the line.
So,
you just want to change Bai Li's custody
and not let Ye Yunkai have control over her life,
so you agreed to cooperate with him?
It seems to have nothing to do with you.
Why is the sample you gave to Ye Yunkai
the work that Bai Li made when she was in college?
How do you know?
I...
I saw her design drafts
at Ye Yunkai's home.
So the draft is still there?
Yes.
I know where it is.
Tell me.
Before that, tell me first
what exactly you're planning.
Su Yu,
trust me once.
I can help you.
If you
can get Bai Li's draft,
I'll trust you one more time.
So,
Su Yu has always been protecting me.
He did so much for me,
but I didn't realize
his feelings earlier.
Instead, I misunderstood and suspected him.
Unfortunately,
I'm in this body now.
I can't tell him
everything I'm thinking.
The surgery went well today.
The doctor said
there's a chance of waking up.
If you can wake up,
can I return to this body?
Whether Bai Li dies or wakes up,
I will lose the bargaining chip to threaten Su Yu with.
It seems I have to speed things up.
Mr. Ning,
I’m really sorry for not letting you know
before coming.
What is it?
Is there something urgent?
It's urgent,
but it's also not.
Chenyun has prepared
the manpower, product, and money,
but Designer Su
still hasn't given us the design draft.
He's an artist. I understand.
He needs some time,
but I'm afraid
that if our work progress is delayed,
I won't be able to report to you.
Maybe it's because Chen was hospitalized after the banquet
and that distracted Su Yu.
Mr. Ye,
have some tea.
Thank you.
Where is Ms. Ning?
She’s upstairs.
I'll go get her.
I know what you're talking about.
I’ll rush Su Yu again later.
That’ll be great.
You are a senior in the industry.
As long as you give the order,
Designer Su will definitely take your project seriously.
Mr. Ning, your villa
is really magnificent.
Every time I return home after visiting you,
I feel a little ashamed.
Mr. Ye's business is getting bigger.
Getting a new house is no big deal.
Ms. Ning.
Hello.
If you need my help in work in the future,
just let me know.
Yes, Mr. Ye.
Actually, you don't have to visit personally in the future.
Just give Xi a call.
Right.
I was too rude this time.
I'm really sorry.
I'll have to trouble Ms. Ning more in the future.
It's no trouble.
We are business partners.
We should contact each other
and help each other more.
Then I won't call you Ms. Ning anymore.
How about I call you Xi?
Sure.
I'll call you Kai then.
Mr. Ye,
the bank has approved the loan.
It's not enough.
Borrow more from the bank.
Borrow as much as you can.
You must raise the production scale.
Yes.
By the way,
ask some online writers to go to
the hospital in an hour.
Yes.
[Regulations on Ward Management]
What are you doing here?
That's my wife lying in the bed.
Why can't I come?
What are you doing here?
I just want to see
if Bai Li can wake up or not.
[Regulations on Ward Management]
She won't wake up.
Yesterday,
who told you to come to the hospital?
Su Yu is my fiancé.
Isn't it normal for me to know his whereabouts?
Why did you pretend in front of Su Yu yesterday?
You insisted on having Bai Li get surgery.
What,
you were beaten by Su Yu yesterday,
so you're taking it out on me today?
Say that again.
So what if I say it?
You are not as good as Su Yu.
You're inferior in every aspect.
You can say anything,
but you can’t say I’m not as good as Su Yu.
You aren't!
What are you doing?
I want to do something exciting,
something Su Yu can't give you.
Ye Yunkai,
there are so many people here.
Aren't you afraid of ruining your image as a loving husband?
The writers will only arrive after one hour.
I can play the role of a loving husband later.
So, you've always been acting.
You didn't come to visit Bai Li at all.
Bai Li? I can have her die anytime.
How?
Su Yu won’t agree to it.
It'll happen sooner or later after I finish using him.
I still have Bai Li's custody.
If I want her to die,
she'll die immediately.
What do you mean?
We can't do it here.
Tonight,
I'll go to your house.
Ning Mochen,
I knew it.
You and I are the same kind of people.
Ye Yunkai, you scum.
You've destroyed my last bit of feelings for you.
I must expose your ugly nature to the public.