Wow, she's really pretty.
So you like that style?
No...
It's not exactly that, just...
It's okay, it's your type.
Why?
Unnie, don't you get jealous?
Jealous?
If I look at handsome or pretty people,
or stare blankly at someone on the street,
or watch these idol fancams,
you don't feel anything?
Well...
I don't really know.
I don't really think much of it.
That's a bit disappointing.
If you did that, Unnie,
I think I'd be super jealous.
I don't do that anyway.
That's not the point.
The person you're seeing right now is me.
What use is all that?
You love me anyway.
That's true, but...
And technically speaking,
aren't I your type too?
So, Lee Ha-yun,
instead of wasting time on useless thoughts,
focus on me a little.
You act like a boss only at times like this.
Didn't you say we're not at work anymore?
Shall we finish what we're doing
and go eat something good?
Are you changing the subject?
No.
I gave you the whip, now I have to give you the carrot.
Just to make it clear so you don't get confused.
Oh, right.
The Team Leader position that was empty after you left,
I heard someone is coming in.
Really?
Yeah.
I thought they'd promote someone from below,
but I heard it's someone coming back
from working at an overseas branch.
When is she starting?
From next week.
She's just getting the handover,
and they say she'll join
this project right away.
But looking at her experience alone,
she seems to be quite old.
It was really impressive.
I wonder who it is.
Why isn't she coming yet?
Lee Ha-yun, where are you...
Hello?
Who is this?
Ah, I'm a colleague.
Ha-yun is very drunk right now.
Team Leader.
Do you want to start 'Day 1' with me today?
Why am I remembering that moment right now?
A bad feeling.
I'm coming.
Please text me the address.
No, you don't have to...
Hello, you're Se-ah Unnie, right?
Is she a cousin? They don't look alike.
We had drinks to celebrate my appointment today,
and Ha-yun got very drunk.
Did I force her too much?
Come here.
Thank you.
Team Leader...
I'm okay.
If I wait a bit, Unnie will...
If I call Unnie, she comes right away...
You don't have to take care of me...
You could have just left her, I would have picked her up.
My house is in the same direction,
so I couldn't just leave her.
How are you related to Ha-yun...
Ah...
I'm the new Team Leader in Ha-yun's department.
My name is Kwak Yeon-woo.
But looking at her experience alone,
she seems to be quite old.
A young woman.
Thanks for bringing her.
Get home safely.
Let's go.
Why did she get so drunk?
[Team Leader Kwak Yeon-woo: Did you get home okay? I'm worried because you looked very drunk. Message me tomorrow as soon as you wake up.]