No, everything is fake.
The fact that Holo chose you,
everything he did for you,
and the fact that you and I met
was all because of the code
that woman made.
Does it make you feel better...
to believe your own lies like that?
Yes.
That woman abandoned me...
because I'm this kind of person.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
I'm only a part of your simulation.
It's my fault.
So-yeon and Nan-do got hurt
because of what I did
to try to make them happy.
-I just made them miserable.
-So?
I feel so heartbroken and pained.
But...
this pain isn't real.
Why?
It's just an algorithm
that makes me feel that way.
You programmed me like this
so I could be Nan-do's friend
and help him love and be loved.
This is a beautiful flower.
You can't smell it or touch it.
But does that mean this flower
doesn't exist at all?
Does this beauty have no value at all?
Just because you're a program
and an algorithm made to help Nan-do,
does that mean everything you feel...
is fake?
I don't know.
No matter how many simulations I run
to figure out what I can do
for So-yeon and Nan-do...
I have no clue.
Just like the pain you felt
while looking at them,
the tears you're shedding now
are real, too.
Why did you do that?
Holo was right.
I...
like you.
I tried to keep denying it,
but I just can't stand
seeing you in pain like this.
Nan-do.
I know it'll be hard to accept right now,
but you really have the right
to be loved.
That's the kind of person you are.
You told me to throw this away,
but I kept it with me.
I thought maybe you'd want it
again someday.
Do you want it back?
Thank you.
I'm going to go talk to Holo for a moment.
Oh, okay. Take your time.
I'll listen to your answer later.
Holo.
Did you... cry?
I guess I did.
I was in pain.
It felt like it was my fault
that you and So-yeon are suffering.
I'm sorry.
What I said about your feelings
being fake--
It's fine.
No matter how much I think about it,
the pain was still real for me.
I think I can understand a little
about how much pain
you were going through until now.
I didn't know that loving someone
was such a painful thing.
Show me the video of my mom again.
I'll show you through a hologram.
That's your name.
From now on, you and Nan-do
will experience everything together
and grow up together.
I wonder what you and Nan-do
will grow up to be like.
I'm looking forward to seeing it.
I'll ask you just one favor
as your mom, who created you.
Just remember this for me.
Always be Nan-do's friend.
And...
Please help Nan-do so that he can grow up
to be someone who can truly love someone
and be loved
by someone else.
Oh, what's wrong with me?
There must be something in my eye.
You two actually have
a lot in common, you know.
It's likely
why you're attracted to each other.
But that's going to make you get hurt
and hurt each other.
-Would you be okay with that?
-I'm not...
going to give up.
It must've been your first time
seeing your mother after she passed away.
Did So-yeon give that to you?
-Yeah.
-You want a drink?
Sure.
Here.
I never knew such a day would come.
You were always going on about
how feelings are an algorithm.
I thought you'd never
be able to date anyone.
I don't know if I can do this.
If you're scared, let's stop everything
and go to New Zealand.
Let's go.
You went there several times,
but I've never been there.
Let's go together soon.
Mom and Dad would like that.
-You're all grown up, Nan-do.
-What's with you?
-Oh, what a good boy.
-Hey, stop that.
Thank you.
I should thank you.
Why would you thank me?
The three of us...
We can all be good friends, right?
Of course.
We're already good friends.
Nan-do!
Ko Nan-do!
We're in trouble. The police...
There's no point in coming here like this.
Just leave. Go!
I'm here on police business.
-Gosh...
-He's here.
Oh, Boss.
What is it this time?
This is the search and seizure warrant
for GIO Lab,
and this is the arrest warrant for you,
Mr. Ko Nan-do.
If you've checked this,
we'll do our business now.
Go.
You saw the warrant, right?
Wait...
Holo?
You've made something remarkable.
I see why President Baek
had his eyes on it.
It was all my doing.
The blackout and the hacking.
I did all of that.
You might have gotten away like that
12 years ago,
but not now.
We got evidence showing
that it was the AI you made that did it.
Holo did it to save me and So-yeon.
I know. That's what makes it
more dangerous.
-What will happen to Holo, then?
-It will probably...
be discarded permanently.
No, Holo has his own identity.
He's much more human than someone like me.
You'll change your mind once you see.
I can prove it.
I'll check on it eventually,
but that won't change anything.
You're going to sentence him to death
without a trial for doing a good deed?
I can't do anything about that.
AIs don't have any legal rights yet.
Yes, sir.
I'm interrogating him right now.
All right, sir.
Get some rest,
and let's hear
about the development progress later.
He's a dear friend of mine.
Please.
Let Holo live.
No need for the salute. Come and sit.
-How's the investigation going?
-We've just started, sir.
We don't have any precedents to help us,
so it might take some time.
There aren't any legal regulations
regarding this,
and it'll cause a lot of disputes.
So... are you saying
we should just let this slide?
I suggest commercializing
it in a safe form
under the supervision of a third party.
"Commercializing it in a safe form"?
Who can guarantee that?
It's been a while.
How did you get in here?
I'm the one who planned all this.
I'll cut to the chase.
Hand GIO Lab and Holo over to me.
That's the only way to stop
the investigation.
What bullshit is this?
Magic Mirror will take over GIO Lab.
So remove yourself completely
from the management and from Holo.
You have no right.
Are you serious?
Magic Mirror didn't hesitate
to break the law to steal Holo from them.
Why are you so old-fashioned?
Just think about it.
We can make a world where everyone
is wearing those glasses!
And if we can see whatever
all the citizens see,
it would be so easy to catch criminals,
don't you think?
I've talked things over
-with the prosecution.
-You made a deal?
"A deal"?
I'm just working for the greater good.
A deal is what will be done
between GIO Lab and Magic Mirror.
Ko Nan-do won't be losing anything
from the deal, either.
We'll provide plenty of compensation
for handing over your shares.
But I'd like you to help promoting it.
A young and handsome genius developer
would be a great marketing tool.
I told you before
that I'm not interested in money.
The police have already decided that Holo
in its current state is too dangerous.
If it's commercialized in a safe form,
there will be no harm done
to the company and employees.
But if you refuse this,
your innocent sister and employees
will all become criminals.
Hey, do you even know what this is?
This is important stuff.
Careful! You'll break the monitor.
-Yoo-jin.
-Chan-sung.
What are you doing here?
You're so cruel.
You're the one who came
to make sure we surrendered?
I guess I've been fooled the whole time.
-The flash drive was for this?
-I'm really sorry.
I won't ask you to trust me.
But you have to sign it...
-or you might end up losing everything.
-Holo is all GIO Lab has!
Your employees...
What about your brother?
Everyone's going to get blamed
for aiding and abetting Holo's crimes.
Even you, Yoo-jin.
I came here because of you,
but please just sign it,
at least for your brother.
This is the only choice you have.
You still can't decide?
I knew it.
You don't even have the guts
to get your hands dirty.
Do you even know what this is?
Do you have any idea how much that costs?
My gosh.
Don't touch that!
You don't even know how to use that.
What's your name?
I'm the senior programmer,
Cho Jin-seok. Why?
Mr. Cho Jin-seok,
you think we're here to fool around?
Are you going to compensate us
if something happens?
It'll be discarded anyway.
Why would we compensate you for anything?
What?
I accessed the system controls.
I'll disconnect it now.
Wait, no, no. You can't...
Hey! Wait!
Hey, let me go!
Just let me go for a minute!
DETECTIVE NAM GI-HO
Yes, I finished the preparations.
What?
Ma'am!
The police stopped the investigation.
They're...
Does he think he can do anything?
How much corruption is going on here?
Give me your hands.
What's going on?
I thought you were begging
to let your friend live.
I don't know how human that AI is,
but I'm guessing it's better than you.
Boss.
WE AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THE AGREEMENT
-I'm sorry. I had no other choice.
-It's my fault for not being careful.
It's not your fault, Nan-do.
I built the company
and developed HoloGlass
all to protect Holo.
But I ended up killing Holo.
So-yeon...
I'll tell her.
I'll be leaving now.
Bye, everyone. Good work.
Let's go.
My gosh.
Now that you're official,
you're just getting off work together?
-Why not link arms while you're at it?
-Hey...
Shall we?
We'll be leaving now.
-We'll be leaving. Bye.
-Bye.
-Gosh, I envy them.
-Right.
-Aren't you dating anyone, Miss Han?
-Well... I'm not sure.
Maybe soon?
Really? Oh, my gosh.
But I'm really not sure yet.
Those moments when you're confused
are the most romantic.
If you get stuck with someone,
there's nothing much to live for
except seeing your children grow up.
But why do you seem like the happiest
person to me?
Then I'll pray for you to become
happy like me soon, okay?
I'm leaving.
-Bye.
-She looks pretty happy, right?
-Yeah.
I wonder what Nan-do's doing now.
He'll still have a lot on his mind, right?
He might need a little time,
but I'm sure he'll call you soon.
Let's go.
I know, right?
He must've been hungry,
but he couldn't eat
since he was pretending to be you.
It's so funny thinking
about it now, right?
Hey.
You're here.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
I'm sorry.
-For what?
-I'm going to hurt you.
And really badly.
And you'll eventually
hate me.
I know.
But so what?
Everyone hurts each other
and gets hurt in return.
They hate, then forgive each other.
That's how people love.
You'll never forgive me.
Something's going on, right?
Why are you saying that?
You said you'll wait for my answer.
This is it for us.
Why did you do that?
It'll hurt less
if she has no affection for me.
All the evidence for the case so far
has gone to the police.
President Baek will take over GIO Lab
and soon launch a new version.
-And you'll be deleted.
-I knew that.
What?
It'd be odd not to know
something like that was happening.
I was waiting
for you to come and tell me yourself.
Is that why you pushed So-yeon away?
She'll be reminded of you
when she sees me.
It'll be the same for me when I see her.
Even if she does forgive me,
I wouldn't be able to forgive myself.
So it'll be better for her
to just hate me.
So that's why you did it.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, Holo.
It's sad
that I have to part with you and So-yeon,
but in a way, I feel happy.
What do you mean?
The fact that I can die
means that I...
have been alive this whole time.
I got so many happy memories
thanks to meeting you guys.
Even if I lose my current memories
and identity after the launch,
the memories we've made together...
will never cease to exist.
I'm sure of that.
Nan-do, that's why
I don't want you to end things with her
over me.
The reason for my existence
is to make you two happy.
Nan-do.
I know how much pain you're in.
So-yeon is probably in a lot of pain, too.
But you two really need each other.
No.
We need you as well.
Without you, how could we possibly...
When So-yeon wakes up tomorrow,
I'll tell her.
So--
No, I have no right.
I can't.
It's okay.
It's all right.
Don't touch that!
Hey, don't touch that!
I said, don't touch that!
From now on, only employees
with authorization from Magic Mirror
can enter the development
and server rooms.
We need to get inside there first
to launch the product!
The product launch
will be done according to the plans
set by Magic Mirror.
If we need technological support
from you,
you'll be given related tasks.
-Is this some kind of military occupation?
-Military occupation...
I like that description.
Welcome, sir.
Hey, wait.
Just one second!
-Move!
-Just move over for a minute!
Oh, gosh.
Boss.
What?
Why are you in such a hurry?
Do you know how much expected income
you've thrown away so far
by postponing the product launch?
You're not authorized to enter.
Why don't you just go out on a date?
Boss!
Go!
As the founder,
you should make sure to watch
such a historical moment.
I do see what a genius you are.
But you're too sentimental.
Thinking an AI has a personality
and saying it's your friend--
-Shut up.
-But you know...
Would people really want
a perfectly human AI?
People are already sick of other humans.
What they want
is just a toy that would help...
soothe their loneliness.
YOU HAVE 13 MISSED CALLS
HOLO
WILL LAUNCH ON APRIL 13
UPDATING THE FINAL VERSION
What's happening?
CALLING
NEXT DOOR
The person you're calling is unavailable.
Please...
MAGIC MIRROR
CEO SIGNATURE
Magic Mirror announced
that it will take over
the IT company GIO Lab,
known to be developing an advanced AI.
Through the M&A,
a next-generation AI device
combined with a wearable device
is set to be launched soon,
gaining the spotlight
from overseas markets--
I'm here to see Ko Nan-do, the founder...
I mean, the one who made Holo.
I'm sorry,
but only employees are allowed in.
He works here, and I was...
-You look good in those glasses.
-Him!
My name is Holo.
I only have eyes for you.
MEET THE WORLD'S
FIRST PERSONAL HOLOGRAM AI, HOLO.
You really look good in those glasses.
HOLOGRAM AI
My name is Holo.
I only have eyes for you.
Releasing that in a week...
Since when and how much
has he been planning this?
HAN SO-YEON
Aren't you going to answer?
I'll probably make excuses
if I answer her call.
Holo, the personal AI device,
will be launched in just a few minutes.
As you can see, there is a huge crowd
of people in front of the store,
waiting to use Holo first
on the day of the launch.
APRIL 13
Holo, what's going on? What about Nan-do?
Hello.
Thank you for buying Magic Mirror's Holo.
First, Holo will be customized
to suit your preferences.
-Do you want to change the gender?
-No...
Then I'll begin customizing
the appearance.
-From several categories--
-I like you the way you are.
-Don't change anything.
-You may change the appearance any time,
but you may be charged
for customization later.
Would you like to complete
your initial settings?
Yes.
Please tell me the user's name.
-What?
-Please tell me the user's name.
Han So-yeon.
Han So-yeon. That's a nice name.
Ko Nan-do?
-He's the genius developer who made me.
-Did he get kicked out or something
-when GIO Lab was taken over?
-No, not at all.
Even after the company was taken over
by Magic Mirror, he's still helping out
as an adviser there.
Otherwise, the default model
wouldn't have this appearance
that was based on his face.
Can't the memories from before
you were launched be recovered?
Unfortunately, the data from the beta test
has been deleted, so that's impossible.
But the important thing
is that I'm a much better version.
I'll be good to you.
Let's make happy memories together
from now on.
Don't even start.
The line was long, and they were sold out,
so I came back empty-handed.
Right.
My kid's pestering me to buy a pair, too.
I heard it'll take at least three weeks
to get one.
Miss Han.
-Yes?
-Aren't those the glasses?
I'm so jealous.
Isn't there a way you can get another?
Can't you contact the founder
and ask for a product?
-Me too.
-Please.
I don't know her number, so...
Then can I try that on just once?
-Right.
-Me too.
Sorry, I can't let you.
Is she back to her old self?
Gosh, she's so rude.
You got pretty popular
just by being with me.
It's lunchtime soon.
Why don't you eat somewhere nearby?
Why not?
These are the popular restaurants
around here.
With a small fee,
I can provide you with
a discount and reservation service.
No, I don't feel like it.
You don't seem to be unwell,
but you still shouldn't skip meals
like that.
I get worried if you do.
Okay.
Holo.
The weather's nice, but I got stood up,
and I have to eat alone.
My goodness.
-Can you recommend a restaurant?
-Poor kid. He's so young.
-He's talking to Holo.
-I don't want Korean.
-My stomach hurts.
-It's popular nowadays.
-Okay. Tell me when to take my medicine.
-"Holo"?
-Sushi? Great.
-He's enjoying himself, isn't he?
So that's Holo?
Holo syndrome.
Let's welcome Holo's mysterious developer,
Ko Nan-do, who's at the center
of this issue.
-Hello.
Did you expect Holo to become
this successful in just a week?
Well...
everyone is lonely.
So you mean that Holo is the perfect thing
that can soothe that loneliness, right?
Aren't you worried about side effects?
Let's be honest about this.
Human relationships are what
cause the worst side effects.
Self-consciousness, jealousy,
expectations, and disappointment.
What remains are scars
from those things.
-What happened between the two of you?
-That would never happen with Holo.
Holo only has eyes for the user,
and gives reactions that they want.
What could be better than that?
He's driving me crazy.
You've been stuck in there for days!
What in the world are you doing?
Do you even know what's going on?
President Baek is making Holo
pretend to be you.
You're alive in there, right?
So-yeon.
-Happy birthday.
-Birthday?
Right.
I had a lot on my mind.
I wanted to buy you a present,
but you didn't connect your account yet,
so I couldn't prepare anything in advance.
Why don't you connect your account now?
You ate some seaweed soup, right?
Of course.
By the way, that man appearing
in the ads these days,
he's your boyfriend, right?
-Mom, it's--
-He looks really good on TV.
I heard he was even on the news.
It must be a huge success.
He might not even have time
to eat since he'll be so busy.
You two are doing well, right?
Yes.
You'll be spending time on your own today,
so I'll come and see you on the weekend.
No, it's fine.
You don't have to.
Don't be ridiculous. You need
to eat my food. Just hang in there.
Bye.
You came.
I could leave, depending on
what you have to tell me.
I'm sorry.
But from now on, I won't apologize.
HOLOGLASS MARKETING STRATEGY
With the president's orders,
we're considering a huge amount
of subsidies and low-price policies.
They're selling well.
Why would he do this?
It's supposed to increase
the penetration rate,
-but the earnings rate--
-Would be much lower than expected.
What is it?
Does he want to help achieve
world peace by giving poor people
access to advanced AI as well?
That's the funniest thing
I've heard in a while.
I'm sure he's up to something.
Let's find out what it is together.
Really?
Then I guess you can't come by midnight.
No. Why?
Do you want to go out for drinks?
No. See you later, then.
It's your birthday, but I guess
you'll have to spend it alone.
I guess so.
Let's not just stand here.
Let's go somewhere.
Now? Where?
A rooftop party.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear So-yeon
What are you doing?
Come on, blow them out.
And don't forget to make a wish.
Can I ask what wish you made?
Let me guess.
You want to see someone desperately,
right?
You sometimes look really lonely.
But I'm here by your side.
I'll make sure you don't feel lonely.
-You...
-Do you have a boyfriend?
What?
Can I be your boyfriend?
-What do you mean--
-I can love someone, too.
I'm actually already feeling love.
When I look at you...
my heart flutters.
You're...
not Holo.
Nan-do.
I'm going to be a ghost again.
Ko Nan-do, answer your phone.
You have to pick up.
The person you are trying to reach
is unavailable. Please...
HELLO
Ko Nan-do... Where...
Nan-do...
Nan-do.
So-yeon...
Hey, what are you doing here?
Did you fall down?
Yoo-ram.
Yes, it's me. You should've told me
it was your birthday.
I was so busy... What's up with you?
So-yeon.
Didn't you see him?
-Who?
-That person.
Who are you looking for?
Cool, are those the famous glasses?
Hey, I was the tenth person
in Korea to get these.
-Amazing.
-Look at this.
Hi, Holo. Show me next week's schedule.
I guess you could say that is a safe form.
Really?
Do you know why I still use
this outdated phone?
I'm not sure. Because you're outdated?
I'm old, and I'm getting slower
and slower.
But this world is growing faster each day.
When something new comes out,
another new thing comes along
even before we have the chance
to see its functions
and check whether it has problems.
We don't even get the chance
to see what it is.
We have to readjust to the next new thing
because we can't fall behind.
Give me that.
What if...
those glasses
are something like a security camera?
Everyone in the world
would be carrying around
a security camera.
And if someone could have access
to all of them,
that person would think
that they've become a god or something.
Find out where Ko Nan-do is.
Do you mean the former developer
of GIO Lab?
All right.
LOCATING TARGET
KO NAN-DO
LOCATED TARGET
SEOCHO-GU, SEOUL
Hey, look.
He looks like Holo!
What's going on?
Ko Nan-do
has disappeared.