♪Who is coming?
The wind brings dust along♪
♪A mountain flower blooms alone♪
♪With half a pot of turbid wine,
I drink to my heart's content♪
♪Asking Li Bai:
Where is the carefree one today?♪
♪Seems like an old friend has arrived♪
♪Hand in hand beyond the horizon♪
♪The wind and moon
listen to my monologue♪
♪Alas, in this world♪
♪Though it's full of helplessness♪
♪Under moonlight, you step
through mountains to enter my dreams♪
=My Contractual Husband=
=Episode 23=
=Song Shirui Gets Beaten=
=Gu Ping'an Saves the Day=
Bring the people from Tongque Tavern!
Justice!
Kneel!
Shirui, are you okay?
Let me ask you.
Where is Gu Ping'an?
Alright.
Since you all refuse to speak,
bring in the punishment.
Start with twenty lashes.
Let them watch Miss Song
getting beaten.
Beat her!
(Order)
I made a vow to the Bodhisattva.
I'm willing to exchange my marriage
for Tongque Tavern's success.
You're making such a big bet.
I haven't fallen in love.
I just want to be a chef.
So,
I scoff at the Yue Lao Temple
but kneel and pray
in the Kitchen God Hall.
Alright, I promise you.
I won't let you down.
Tongque Tavern will surely become
the largest tavern
in all of Jiangnan,
and you'll be the top chef in Qiantang.
(Gu Ping'an,)
(the Bodhisattva really heard my vow.)
Shirui.
Cihua.
Miss Song, we must protect you,
or we won't be able
to explain it to Mr. Gu.
You don't have to do this.
Alright.
You like to protect her, right?
Stop.
Pull them away.
Put Song Shirui on the nail board.
Who dares to do that?
It's Gu Ping'an. Take him down!
Mr. Li,
the Patrol Inspector is here.
How dare you act recklessly!
Surround them!
Zhou.
Greetings, Patrol Inspector.
Shirui, Shirui...
Come on. Here.
You...
Why did you return?
I'm sorry.
I'm late.
You've suffered.
Get up.
Bring the body.
Miao, isn't that...?
Zhou, what are you...
Mr. Li, please be patient.
I have an important case
to report to you.
Mr. Gu.
Mr. Ximen, Ms. Miao,
I have a story
to tell you both.
Please listen carefully
and tell me if I'm wrong.
Ximen's family business
is one of the best in Qiantang,
but unexpectedly,
this ordinary restaurant business
couldn't satisfy your appetites.
So, you started selling private salt.
Is that right or not?
My mother passed away early,
and my father raised me on his own.
But I was born a good-for-nothing,
unable to be of much use.
To protect the family's prosperity,
my father intended to remarry.
Your family valued my father's position
as the Forwarding Magistrate
and married Ms. Miao to my father.
Is that right or not?
Unexpectedly, my father,
true to his name,
was an honest man with no greed.
He went to Jiangnan
to investigate the salt case
and discovered the Yin-Yang Sect,
the largest private salt
trafficking organization in Jiangnan.
And the leader behind this sect
was you two.
So, unable to stop,
you orchestrated the shipwreck plot
and killed my father.
Is that right or not?
After Gu Qingfeng's death,
Ximen Miao seized all the assets
of the Gu family
without knowing Gu Qingfeng
left behind a Tongque Tavern.
However, Ximen Bang in Qiantang
had long been prepared
to wipe out Gu Ping'an completely.
Once the plan succeeded,
Tongque Tavern would still belong
to the Ximen family,
and you would suffer no losses.
But who would have thought
Ximen Bang wasn't Gu Ping'an's match?
So, you planned to kill me first
and then Gu Ping'an.
Is that right?
Patrol Inspector, please be fair.
Someone must be plotting against us.
Please look into it, Mr. Zhou!
Yes, yes!
This doesn't prove that we did it!
- Mr. Zhou, please investigate!
- Please!
Please look into it, Mr. Zhou!
I found this severed finger
and a Yin-Yang Sect ring
among Gu Qingfeng's remains.
Mr. Ximen,
can you tell me
which finger you lost?
Why was your name engraved on this ring?
How could you lose everything?
You didn't even look
for your finger or your ring!
Miao,
I didn't know this would be discovered.
I thought it would be done quietly,
so I didn't dare tell you.
- You!
- Miao!
You're more trouble
- than you're worth.
- Three years ago,
Gu Qingfeng brought evidence
of the private salt case
to board a ship at the dock
outside Fengshan Gate,
planning to report back.
But after you two found out about it,
you immediately decided
to eliminate Gu Qingfeng.
But when the assassins
arrived at Tongque Tavern,
Gu Qingfeng had boarded the ship.
They had to destroy the tavern first
to prevent any future risks.
Then, Ximen Bang
managed to board the ship
and struck Gu Qingfeng's head
from behind with a blunt weapon.
After Gu Qingfeng passed out,
you tied him to a stone
and threw him into the river.
But,
during the struggle between Gu Qingfeng
and Ximen Bang,
Gu Qingfeng bit off
Ximen Bang's ring finger.
This ring and the finger bone
are the evidence.
Mr. Li,
can these two be thrown directly
into the dungeon?
Yes, yes.
Someone, take these two away!
- Yes.
Miao!
- Please spare us, Mr. Zhou!
- Mr. Zhou!
- Please spare us!
Mr. Zhou!
- Mr. Zhou!
- Miao!
Please spare us!
What about the staff at Tongque Tavern?
They're all innocent.
Zhou,
I'll confess everything.
Please ask the Emperor to show mercy
and spare my family.
Mr. Li,
as the Patrol Inspector,
it is my duty to handle
the case impartially.
As your son-in-law,
I am deeply sorry.
Forget about it.
Zhou Sheng, can I entrust Wanjun to you?
I am honored by your trust.
I will love Wanjun
for the rest of my life.
Shirui, Shirui.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's all my fault.
I made you suffer.
I'm glad I got here in time.
I was wrong.
Will you forgive me?
May I ask
if this lady
still needs a manager?
Well, my demands are very high.
I swear
that from now on,
I'll always follow Song Shirui,
never leaving her side.
Then,
eight taels a month.
You'll start tomorrow.
♪The ice melts into the waters rushing
into someone's mortal world♪
♪I fold a leaf into a boat;
it floats across the water♪
♪My heart is no longer cold; the flowers
are blooming to open the gate♪
♪A breeze passes by
like you brushing past me♪
♪Among the drumbeats,
praying for good weather♪
♪I hope we have a peaceful life forever♪
♪Through the four seasons,
a cycle of fate comes♪
♪And trapping me in this life♪
♪Asking the world:
Whom do we celebrate spring for♪
♪I shed tears, feeling sorry for you♪
♪Grateful for heaven's grace,
though it cannot yet grow into love♪
♪But it will flourish♪
♪I kiss the world,
celebrating spring for you♪
♪But you wait,
waiting for me in sorrow♪
♪I was just a withered tree,
but I won't sink♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)