♪Who is coming?
The wind brings dust along♪
♪A mountain flower blooms alone♪
♪With half a pot of turbid wine,
I drink to my heart's content♪
♪Asking Li Bai:
Where is the carefree one today?♪
♪Seems like an old friend has arrived♪
♪Hand in hand beyond the horizon♪
♪The wind and moon
listen to my monologue♪
♪Alas, in this world♪
♪Though it's full of helplessness♪
♪Under moonlight, you step
through mountains to enter my dreams♪
=My Contractual Husband=
=Episode 2=
=Song Saves Her Husband=
=Gu Fights His Romantic Rival
and Loses Money=
(For the land deed, I'll risk it all.)
Shirui!
The ceremony is complete.
Send the newlyweds
to the bridal chamber.
(Married)
Why do you look so gloomy
on your wedding day?
I got married
before the mourning period ended.
I even kissed you.
Come on.
You're a grown man.
Why are you acting like a woman?
You're taking advantage of me, alright?
I was forced into it.
I came to Qiantang
to open a tavern.
Who would've known...
Who would've known
I'd meet a female bandit like you?
Calm down.
It was my fault
for being attracted to you.
You just helped me act in a play.
Don't try to get close to me.
How about this?
Let's sign a gentleman's agreement.
No consummation.
Is that okay?
Well...
Once your tavern is up and running,
we can divorce.
Alright.
It's a deal.
We'll have to sign it.
(Song Shirui, Gu Ping'an)
Come on, drink with me.
We're only pretending to be married.
Why should we drink the wedding wine?
This isn't the wedding wine.
This is a drink to celebrate
our happy cooperation.
Come on.
Alright, I'll drink.
Hurry, another cup.
I really can't drink anymore.
What are you doing?
Don't take it off.
Stop taking it off.
We have a gentleman's agreement.
Don't blame me
for what's going to happen then.
It's so hot.
(Ximen Mansion)
How absurd.
Shirui.
My Shirui...
How strange.
Song Shirui
has had no luck in love for years.
Now out of nowhere, a husband appears.
This is suspicious.
Go check on him.
Find out everything about this brat.
What if this is true?
True?
Then we'll deal with her husband.
Understood?
Understood.
We agreed on a gentleman's agreement,
right?
Yeah, so what?
Then why did you take advantage of me
while I was drunk?
You're the one who got drunk
and acted wild.
Female bandit.
I was wrong, okay?
Female bandit! Female bandit!
(Song's Big Buns)
Fresh buns! Come and take a look!
Miss Bride.
Selling buns
right after getting married?
Get lost!
Don't waste my time with business.
How else can you support your boy toy?
What do you mean by that?
You go wait over there.
- My money sachet!
- Stop!
You two are lucky today.
- Just wait!
- Stop!
- Serves you right!
These thugs abusing their power
deserve a beating.
Miss, five big buns,
with plenty of meat.
(Cihua, a street thug)
Got it.
(Song's Big Buns)
Thanks for helping me earlier, Miss.
Yeah.
Here, consider these buns a gift.
No need to pay.
You're welcome.
To deal with thugs,
you have to use
even more ruthless methods.
By the way,
call me "Young man".
Don't call me "Young lady".
Young man?
You're clearly a girl.
Young man, thanks.
Keep the money.
If you ever need help, just call me.
Bye.
Take care.
Qiantang River.
Golden on the outside,
silver frost inside.
What are you looking at?
Come on.
Why do you walk so quietly?
It's really scary.
We've only been married for two days,
and you're already complaining about me.
By the way,
where exactly is the Tongque Tavern?
That building is on the same street
where you fainted.
It's just a bit further ahead.
How would I know where I fainted?
Why don't you take me there?
I'm not going.
Then I'll go by myself.
(Tongque Tavern)
Drink up.
How come it's you guys again?
What a small world.
Everyone,
what are you doing in my tavern?
Please leave.
Your tavern?
Do you understand the rule
of first come, first served?
This is the deed to my tavern.
If you don't leave now,
you're trespassing on private property.
Stop talking nonsense.
The whole of Qiantang
belongs to Mr. Ximen.
I don't care about your property rights.
Give it back to me.
Come and take it.
I'll fight you!
Pretty boy, watch carefully.
Today, I'm going to tear up this deed.
How dare you?
Have you asked for my permission
before you bully my husband?
Mr. Ximen told me
not to make it hard for you.
Don't be ungrateful.
Tell these words to Ximen.
You wait here. I'll go get my helpers.
Bluffing.
You're so weak.
How did you make it all the way
from Kaifeng to here?
It was very safe the whole way.
It was only after I met you
- that things started going wrong.
- Trinkets!
Candied hawthorns!
- I've saved you twice.
- Come and take a look!
- Don't be ungrateful.
- Little trinkets!
Yes, yes, yes.
(Does the last time even count?)
The bun shop...
My bun shop.
What happened?
Let's report it to the authorities.
Report it? To whom?
They're in cahoots with Ximen.
No way. I'm not done with them.
Wait.
You just said they're in cahoots.
We can't act impulsively.
Let's go home first.
Mr. Ximen, we've investigated that brat.
His name is Gu Ping'an.
He's from Kaifeng.
Gu what?
Gu Ping'an.
(I need to send a letter
to Kaifeng right away.)
This news is very important.
Send out more pigeons.
Make sure nothing goes wrong.
Yes.
Those thugs think they're invincible
with Ximen's protection,
so they're running rampant in Qiantang.
I'll make sure to vent my anger
after this.
I have an idea.
Since your bun shop is gone,
why don't we just open a tavern?
I'll need seven taels of monthly salary.
Five taels.
Eight taels.
Seven taels.
- Ten taels.
- Ten taels it is. It's a deal.
Let's go to the Tongque Tavern tomorrow.
(Tongque Tavern)
Chef Song, please.
Manager Gu, after you.
The furnishings aren't too old,
but they haven't been used
in a long time,
so they're dusty.
We'll need to hire someone
to clean it up.
What do you think?
Are you satisfied with your kitchen?
Yes.
These bowls and chopsticks
are pretty new.
I guess they opened not long ago
and then shut down.
If there's anything you need,
or if something's inconvenient to use,
just let me know,
and I'll take care of it.
Within one tael of silver.
Then let's get started.
Stop.
That was close.
Looks like all of these lanterns
need to be replaced.
When do you want to open?
No rush.
We need to go
to a place first.
(Caidie Resto)
Caidie Resto? What are we doing here?
Know yourself and your enemy,
and you'll win every battle.
Today, let's check it out.
Let's go.
You ordered all the signature dishes.
You really don't hold back with me, huh?
You didn't go through the proper rituals
before marrying me.
What's wrong with treating me to a meal?
Mr. Ximen.
I'm not dead yet.
- Mr. Ximen.
- What's going on?
Song Shirui's here at the Caidie Resto.
Really?
That's great.
I knew Shirui had feelings for me.
Let's go. Let's see Shirui.
Her husband is here too.
Mr. Ximen.
My dear guests,
here is your pastry.
Did you order pastry?
The manager knew Miss Song was here,
so he had someone make
our signature Six Treasures:
Empress's Red Date Cakes,
Icy Snow Dumplings,
Sweet Sugar Fruits,
Colorful Phoenix Five-Spice Cakes,
Immortal's Wealthy Pastry,
and Golden Chestnut Cakes.
Miss Song, please enjoy.
These are free, right?
Shirui.
Look.
Why didn't you let me know
you were coming here?
I would've welcomed you personally.
Stay away from me.
Don't be so aloof.
Mr. Ximen, how would you like to drink?
Fill it up.
Got it.
My husband drank too much yesterday,
so I will
drink it for him.
- Wait.
Mr. Ximen,
I'm not here to swear allegiance today.
These three bowls of wine
are for the future opening
of my Tongque Tavern.
Please show your support.
Take your time drinking.
Darling,
let's go.
Mr. Gu,
you've had the food and drunk the wine.
Do you want to leave without paying?
That's not proper, is it?
How much is it?
Eighty taels of silver.
That's so expensive.
Are you robbing us?
This is
one hundred taels.
You don't need to give the extra back.
Darling,
let's go.
My 100 taels.
It's just gone like that.
You didn't seem so heartbroken
when you tossed it to Ximen just now.
That was the startup capital
for my tavern.
My father only left me 200 taels.
- What?
- My money.
You gave away half of it, Gu Ping'an.
I just can't stand him eyeing you.
Why can't you stand it?
Why?
Because I'm your husband now.
What are you doing?
Darling.
Tonight,
can you not tie me up to sleep?
♪The ice melts into the waters rushing
into someone's mortal world♪
♪I fold a leaf into a boat;
it floats across the water♪
♪My heart is no longer cold; the flowers
are blooming to open the gate♪
♪A breeze passes by
like you brushing past me♪
♪Among the drumbeats,
praying for good weather♪
♪I hope we have a peaceful life forever♪
♪Through the four seasons,
a cycle of fate comes♪
♪And trapping me in this life♪
♪Asking the world:
Whom do we celebrate spring for♪
♪I shed tears, feeling sorry for you♪
♪Grateful for heaven's grace,
though it cannot yet grow into love♪
♪But it will flourish♪
♪I kiss the world,
celebrating spring for you♪
♪But you wait,
waiting for me in sorrow♪
♪I was just a withered tree,
but I won't sink♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)