♪Who is coming?
The wind brings dust along♪
♪A mountain flower blooms alone♪
♪With half a pot of turbid wine,
I drink to my heart's content♪
♪Asking Li Bai:
Where is the carefree one today?♪
♪Seems like an old friend has arrived♪
♪Hand in hand beyond the horizon♪
♪The wind and moon
listen to my monologue♪
♪Alas, in this world♪
♪Though it's full of helplessness♪
♪Under moonlight, you step
through mountains to enter my dreams♪
=My Contractual Husband=
=Episode 20=
=Gu Leaves Without Saying Goodbye=
=Song Ends up in Jail
for the Greater Good=
(But you also said)
(the reason Uncle Xia would help me)
(was that he wanted
you and me to marry.)
(I can't agree to this.)
(I won't betray Shirui.)
(Are you going
to watch her fall into danger?)
(The Ximen family
treats human life as nothing.)
(Zhou Sheng, as the top scholar,
couldn't protect himself,)
(let alone the two of you.)
Darling, are you asleep?
I wasn't very kind earlier.
I came to apologize.
Darling?
I'm glad you're asleep.
It's raining outside.
I'm afraid it's too noisy
for you to sleep.
(Divorce Letter)
♪The dream gradually ends;
the night air is cool♪
♪The one I love is far away♪
(Shirui,)
(as a couple,
we share a deep affection.)
(Today, I leave behind the land deed
and all my money,)
(to atone for the crime
of abandoning you.)
♪Playing with my hair, gazing deeply,
waiting for someone♪
(You and I have worked together)
(and managed the tavern)
(Tongque Tavern)
(to this scale.)
(This is truly rare.)
(Qiantang County Yamen)
(I deserve to die.)
(Material wealth
can't make up for my guilt.)
(Darling, do not forgive me.)
(I have no fixed home,)
(but fortunately, you took me in,
and we got married.)
Let's sign a gentleman's agreement.
No consummation.
It's a deal. Let's sign it.
(Gu Ping'an, Song Shirui)
(Though we have this agreement,)
(I've long fallen for you.)
(Now, you've become
the top chef in Qiantang,)
(and our contract expires today.)
(I will then step aside.)
(After our separation,)
(I hope you'll comb your hair,
beautify your brows,)
(and choose a powerful husband,)
(someone who matches your beauty.)
(I fear there will be no evidence left.)
(So, I willingly set this document
as a reminder.)
(I humbly wish you all the best.)
♪Yet again, memories emerge
despite the years♪
♪Flowing through my fingers,
each note brings sorrow♪
♪The flowers fall;
the music of the night grows cold♪
♪Playing with my hair, gazing deeply,
waiting for someone♪
♪Dreams and strings are easy to lose,
but worldly ties are hard to sever♪
♪I give you all the tenderness
of my life♪
(Tongque Tavern; Closed Today)
The authorities are on a case.
According to reports from the citizens,
Gu Ping'an,
Manager of Tongque Tavern,
is the son
of the guilty official Gu Qingfeng.
The authorities are questioning him now.
Mr. Gu has left.
He's gone?
So suddenly?
When did this happen?
This morning.
Since Gu Ping'an
has fled due to his crimes,
arrest everyone from the Tongque Tavern.
Hold on!
Mr. Zhao,
I don't know
what my husband has done,
but this has nothing
to do with the staff.
I'm married to Gu Ping'an.
If you want to arrest him,
you can take me.
Mrs. Gu.
Stop calling me that.
From now on, I'm your only manager.
Alright.
With you,
Gu Ping'an will surely show up.
Someone, take her away.
No need.
I'll go myself.
Miss Song,
we'll definitely get you out.
Let's go.
(Tongque Tavern)
Move aside.
What's going on?
What happened?
Miao,
aren't they supposed
to arrest Gu Ping'an?
Why are they arresting Song Shirui?
Oh no, Gu Ping'an has escaped.
Mr. Gu,
how do you feel
now that you're back in Kaifeng?
(Kaifeng)
It's mixed feelings.
Open the door! Miss Xia is back!
(Xia Mansion)
Miss Xia is back!
Ping'an,
the side courtyard
is the most secluded part.
You can stay here at ease.
No one will find you.
Thank you.
Dinner has been prepared.
Let's eat together.
Perfect.
I can't wait
to meet Uncle Xia.
My father will surely be happy
to see you.
Ping'an, it's been a long time.
How have you been in Qiantang?
Thank you for your concern.
Everything's good in Qiantang.
The tavern my father left me
has reopened.
I've been gathering many clues
about my father's case
while managing it.
Ping'an came this time because...
Ping'an,
I see you're at the age to get married.
You went to Qiantang earlier,
and now you've come back.
Why don't you let me
arrange your marriage
with Wanwan as soon as possible?
Uncle,
thank you for your kind consideration,
but my father's case
is still unresolved.
I am focused on clearing his name.
I understand how you feel,
but this is
a big matter,
and it requires careful planning.
Uncle, I've gathered some clues...
Alright.
Let's eat first.
You know how to take care of me.
You're worried
I'll be bored in the courtyard,
so you came to see me.
Yes.
That's not quite it.
Miss Xia is afraid you'll run away,
so she asked me to watch over you.
Canghai,
you're as straightforward as ever.
What are you thinking?
I'm worried.
This time I returned to Kaifeng,
Mr. Li and Ximen
won't easily let Shirui go.
I'm worried Ms. Miao will cause trouble,
so I need to get the search warrant
as soon as possible.
What do you plan to do?
Tomorrow, no matter what,
I'll ask Mr. Xia to write the memorial.
Qiantang is full of danger.
I can't waste a moment.
I went back alone
just to investigate the case
and make plans.
If anything happens to Shirui
because of me,
I'll never forgive myself.
So, I've made up my mind.
In three days, no matter what,
I'll return to her side,
even if I can't get the memorial.
Mr. Gu,
you're a faithful man.
I'll clear any obstacles for you.
I'll go back with you.
Come on.
I wonder what Shirui is doing now,
if she's eating well,
and if she's thinking about me.
You wrote that divorce letter
so decisively,
and now you want her to think about you?
I had no choice.
Wait, you peeked at my divorce letter?
Who would want to look?
You soaked so many sheets of paper
with your tears.
I was just cleaning up for you.
I happened to glance at it.
Do you think I'll believe you?
Are you going to hit me?
Alright, I won't stay any longer.
I'm going to sleep now.
♪The ice melts into the waters rushing
into someone's mortal world♪
♪I fold a leaf into a boat;
it floats across the water♪
♪My heart is no longer cold; the flowers
are blooming to open the gate♪
♪A breeze passes by
like you brushing past me♪
♪Among the drumbeats,
praying for good weather♪
♪I hope we have a peaceful life forever♪
♪Through the four seasons,
a cycle of fate comes♪
♪And trapping me in this life♪
♪Asking the world:
Whom do we celebrate spring for♪
♪I shed tears, feeling sorry for you♪
♪Grateful for heaven's grace,
though it cannot yet grow into love♪
♪But it will flourish♪
♪I kiss the world,
celebrating spring for you♪
♪But you wait,
waiting for me in sorrow♪
♪I was just a withered tree,
but I won't sink♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)