♪A light shines on me♪
♪A leaf falls to the ground♪
♪A person♪
♪Living in another world♪
♪A beating heart♪
♪A gentle wind♪
♪You bring me the light♪
♪Falling in love in an instant♪
♪A story unfolds page by page♪
♪A lonely heart is slowly warmed♪
♪A star is twinkling♪
♪Destined to meet you♪
♪You mean everything to me
in reality or in my dreams♪
=The Next Stop W=
(Adapted from the TV series W – Two Worlds)
=Episode 8=
Why have the contents gone?
I can't input anything.
Why can't I turn on the computer?
Oh no.
Something must have
happened in that world.
What shall I do?
It's all my fault for telling him
that his world is in a comic.
(When the protagonist
finds out it's all a fiction,)
(the comic world will stop.)
(And only Jiang Zhe)
(will live in a still world.)
(It's like)
a punishment for him.
♪Seems someone is manipulating my fate♪
♪Lost in the fog, I am like his toy♪
♪Who heard and touched my unspoken remarks♪
♪Inside the heart♪
♪A light shines on me♪
♪A leaf falls to the ground♪
♪A person♪
♪Living in another world♪
♪A beating heart♪
♪A gentle wind♪
♪You bring me the light♪
♪Falling in love in an instant♪
♪A story unfolds page by page♪
♪A lonely heart is slowly warmed♪
♪A star is twinkling♪
♪Destined to meet you♪
♪You mean everything to me
in reality or in my dreams♪
What makes you want to learn boxing?
You are so rich.
A couple of bodyguards
will do the job for you.
Sometimes money can't buy everything.
Also,
I'm surrounded by danger.
You can't be there to
protect me all the time.
That's true.
Let's do it.
Sir.
Are you okay?
We're going to
close the shop now.
Does this comic
sell well?
Of course.
It's been one of the
bestsellers for years.
Is it?
How interesting.
Do you want to buy it, sir?
No.
I already know what happened in it.
I might not keep my cool
if she says it again.
(Sis.)
How is it?
I took the drawing tablet
to the repair shop.
The system is okay.
Nothing is wrong with the machine.
They don't know where the problem is.
Where are you now, sis?
The hospital.
I'm wandering on the street.
I dare not stay in the studio by myself.
I'll wait until Mr. Wu comes back.
Okay.
Bye.
Yanzhu.
Did you get engaged without telling me?
Engaged?
How is that possible?
A guy came looking for you,
saying that he's your fiance.
Who is it?
He said you'd know who he is
when I tell you
he's your fiance.
Excuse me for a second.
Hey.
Yanzhu.
Where are you going?
We're having the operation soon.
♪Looking out at you
from a lighthouse far away♪
♪Cupping a few rays of sunshine♪
♪Can it♪
♪Warm your heart?♪
♪The ties between people♪
♪Are countless and complicated♪
♪As long as♪
♪We hear♪
♪Each other's heartbeats and breath♪
♪I'm waiting for you to turn around♪
♪The world is silent
and I miss the hustle and bustle♪
♪Put my heart into your palm lines♪
♪The balance of the scales
of love is tipped by you♪
♪Touch your inner world♪
♪Start a fantasy journey♪
♪A pair of lovers have lost their minds♪
♪And been sinking♪
♪In love♪
♪The ties between people♪
♪Are countless and complicated♪
♪As long as♪
♪We hear♪
♪Each other's heartbeats and breath♪
♪I'm waiting for you to turn around♪
♪The world is silent
and I miss the hustle and bustle♪
♪Put my heart into your palm lines♪
♪The balance of the scales
of love is tipped by you♪
♪Touch your inner world♪
♪Start a fantasy journey♪
♪A pair of lovers have lost their minds♪
♪And been sinking♪
♪In love♪