♪A light shines on me♪
♪A leaf falls to the ground♪
♪A person♪
♪Living in another world♪
♪A beating heart♪
♪A gentle wind♪
♪You bring me the light♪
♪Falling in love in an instant♪
♪A story unfolds page by page♪
♪A lonely heart is slowly warmed♪
♪A star is twinkling♪
♪Destined to meet you♪
♪You mean everything to me
in reality or in my dreams♪
=The Next Stop W=
(Adapted from the TV series W – Two Worlds)
=Episode 22=
(Who are you?)
How does it feel to be in a world
without people?
You love killing people,
but now there is no one for you to kill.
How are you feeling?
Oh,
I forgot to tell you
the exit has been destroyed by me.
You can't get out of there.
You can die now.
(Die?)
(Huh.)
(Why should I die?)
(I just need to wait,)
(and you will surrender.)
(You are not qualified)
(to be the protagonist.)
(You killer and fugitive.)
(If the protagonist is eliminated,)
(I will be a new one.)
(The world)
(will go on)
(for me.)
(Why should I die?)
(Why?)
You're awake.
Come on.
How do you feel?
Alright.
How is my dad now?
Your dad is still not awake.
But,
Liu Feng and I
took him to a nearby hut.
Thanks.
Let's go on a date.
What?
While you've been asleep,
I've learned everything.
Now I know
in the comic book,
I am your husband.
You know me well,
but I don't know you well enough,
so let's go on a date.
I heard that it can reinforce bonds.
I'm so hungry.
We'll have a meal
and then come back, okay?
Go change your clothes.
Or you want the sexy, X-rated style?
No.
This restaurant is not bad.
We can be dining here quite a bit.
What's wrong?
You are upset?
What happened to your hand?
Do you want to keep it from me?
I was going to tell you after dinner.
Since Shenshen's death,
it's been like this.
Why is it like this?
Yesterday,
I had a talk with the murderer,
and I learned a secret.
Your father met the murderer
years ago,
and he made a deal with him.
It's over now.
Who are you?
I will kill Jiang Zhe.
Why are you meddling?
Why are you still alive
after being stabbed?
Who are you?
Spare my life.
I will make you
the master of this world.
(Jiang Zhe.)
(As long as you are dead,)
(I will be the protagonist.)
(This is what he said.)
(But he betrayed me after he went back.)
(So,)
(I could only devour him.)
(Because your father agreed to that deal,)
the setting to make our meeting
a dream
is invalid.
Besides,
the murderer is getting
stronger and stronger,
but I
lost my memory.
So,
this is not a good time.
What do we do now?
Do you remember it?
It was your father's tablet
that connected the two worlds,
and you only returned to the real world
at the end of each chapter.
But then there was a twist.
We're going to use it.
How?
I need you to draw for me.
Another dream?
You will forget me
and live your own life,
leaving me alone with our memories.
If you've already made a decision,
why are you dating me?
You're still
making a joke right now?
I read online
that this can calm a girl down.
It does seem to work.
I know what you're worried about,
but I'm not going to do that.
I don't want to live the same life
over and over again.
I hope
there will be a happy ending
between you and me.
Your father can only be resurrected
after the murderer dies,
so you must help me.
How?
I have a hypothesis.
I'm in the real world now.
At the same time,
I am the protagonist in the comic.
Now that
I can take people from the real world
into the comic,
I think I can take advantage of it
and get into the comic anytime.
Let's use this.
(When the time comes,)
(draw a car for me)
(so that I can get out of there.)
Hello.
I'd like to report a crime.
Yes.
Yanzhu.
Mr. Wu...
What happened to my dad?
H-H-He looks
a bit strange.
Haha.
Dad.
Dad, you are finally back.
Come and sit down.
That's great.
Your face finally returned.
Dad?
Who is your dad?
You are not him.
It's been a long time.
Wu Yanzhu.
It's you
who created the chaos.
I could have gotten rid
of Jiang Zhe long ago,
but you hid him and revived him,
and you lured me out and woke me up.
Without you,
the comic
should have ended.
Why are you so nosy?
Liu Feng.
Jiang Zhe
is not the only one who knows
how to enter this world.
Too naive.
That's not difficult.
I can do it too.
Don't forget
there is another me
in this world.
You...
Haha.
Too weak.
It's time for me
to settle the score with you.
Go.
Go quickly.
♪Looking out at you
from a lighthouse far away♪
♪Cupping a few rays of sunshine♪
♪Can it♪
♪Warm your heart?♪
♪The ties between people♪
♪Are countless and complicated♪
♪As long as♪
♪We hear♪
♪Each other's heartbeats and breath♪
♪I'm waiting for you to turn around♪
♪The world is silent
and I miss the hustle and bustle♪
♪Put my heart into your palm lines♪
♪The balance of the scales
of love is tipped by you♪
♪Touch your inner world♪
♪Start a fantasy journey♪
♪A pair of lovers have lost their minds♪
♪And been sinking♪
♪In love♪
♪The ties between people♪
♪Are countless and complicated♪
♪As long as♪
♪We hear♪
♪Each other's heartbeats and breath♪
♪I'm waiting for you to turn around♪
♪The world is silent
and I miss the hustle and bustle♪
♪Put my heart into your palm lines♪
♪The balance of the scales
of love is tipped by you♪
♪Touch your inner world♪
♪Start a fantasy journey♪
♪A pair of lovers have lost their minds♪
♪And been sinking♪
♪In love♪