♪A light shines on me♪
♪A leaf falls to the ground♪
♪A person♪
♪Living in another world♪
♪A beating heart♪
♪A gentle wind♪
♪You bring me the light♪
♪Falling in love in an instant♪
♪A story unfolds page by page♪
♪A lonely heart is slowly warmed♪
♪A star is twinkling♪
♪Destined to meet you♪
♪You mean everything to me
in reality or in my dreams♪
=The Next Stop W=
(Adapted from the TV series W – Two Worlds)
=Episode 7=
Okay, I got it.
No truck information was found.
It's like it appeared out of nowhere
and disappeared the same way.
Don't bother looking for it.
Perhaps the perpetrator
never existed at all.
Never existed?
Think about how many strange
things have happened to me recently.
Stabbed.
Saved.
Hit by a truck.
Everything feels like already written.
Just like 10 years ago.
I was on my way to
the shooting competition.
But somehow I ended up home
and became a suspect
who killed his whole family.
For 10 years,
we kept looking.
But we couldn't find one single lead.
Not even a motive.
So?
So I think,
the person we've been looking for
probably came from another world.
You mean an alien?
Yeah.
But probably
not the kind of alien we would imagine.
But like Wu Yanzhu.
With an appearance just like us.
Wu Yanzhu?
She knows everything about me.
It's like she sees me from
an omniscient perspective.
(At that time,)
you stood on the roof.
I was so afraid that you would jump.
She even knows things
that I've never told anyone.
Thankfully she doesn't
have ill will towards me.
She just wants to save me.
But there must be someone who does.
This is
unbelievable.
So I think she's the key to my life.
The only way for me to
find the answer to the secret.
Stop there!
What?
Are you going to confess again?
No.
The police came looking for me.
What should I do?
What happened?
Lu Shenshen...
It doesn't matter.
What should I do now?
Calm down.
Where are you now?
On the road in front
of the main entrance.
I'll contact you later.
Okay.
Go to the road in front of the house.
Don't let the police take her away.
Okay.
We need you to come with us, miss.
Where are you now?
How is it?
Mr. Jiang.
The police took her.
Why do you have her phone?
I found it in the grass.
(Police)
Visitors please wait here.
Hello.
Lu Shenshen.
I told you I'll take care of her.
Why did you tell the police?
She came out of nowhere
and means possible danger to you.
Why shouldn't I tell the police?
I was evaluating what's best for you
and I made the right decision.
If she's not dangerous,
we can all rest assured
after the police finish
the investigation, right?
Why can't she just tell us who she is?
Maybe,
she's not a witness
but the real murderer.
You believed her lies.
When I look at Wu Yanzhu
and those strange things she did,
it's like I'm looking at my old self.
Do you know that
she threw away the phone I gave her
before the police got her?
She did it to not get me involved.
How can she be the suspect?
How can you be so impulsive
as my secretary?
Jiang Zhe.
Sorry I'm late. Are you okay?
How can I be?
These things only happen in movies.
I never thought
I would be here one day.
Things are very serious now.
You can't explain your identity.
It's possible that they'll see
you as the potential suspect.
The only way
for me to help you
is to tell me the truth.
I can't.
If I say it,
you'll be unfortunate.
Well,
I'm not that fortunate now either.
I have trouble sleeping every night
because I don't know when I will die.
Look where you are now.
So please tell me.
Why do you know me so well?
You'll regret this.
I won't.
I've been waiting for
the answer for ten years.
It's a comic.
Comic?
Do you mean
you came from a comic?
No.
This is.
What do you mean?
This world is from a comic.
A comic that I'm reading.
And you, Jiang Zhe,
are the protagonist.
Why must I have emotional turbulence
for it to work?
Because you are the protagonist.
(To be continued)
Did you really go to
the detention center?
But you've only
disappeared for 30 minutes.
How could you have stayed
three days in the villa
and two days in the detention center
in the comic world?
That doesn't make sense.
I remember every single day
I've spent in there.
This is my first time
in a detention center.
Do you know how that feels?
I couldn't stay there another second.
So you told Jiang Zhe everything
to get yourself out?
What did I do?
Secure the exit!
Attention, all departments.
Suspect breakout.
Go to the monitor room!
Attention, all departments.
Suspect breakout.
Hurry up!
(This world is from a comic.)
(A comic that I'm reading.)
And you, Jiang Zhe,
are the protagonist.
(You really gave me an answer
I never could have guessed.)
(So,)
(this whole world is fake.)
♪Looking out at you
from a lighthouse far away♪
♪Cupping a few rays of sunshine♪
♪Can it♪
♪Warm your heart?♪
♪The ties between people♪
♪Are countless and complicated♪
♪As long as♪
♪We hear♪
♪Each other's heartbeats and breath♪
♪I'm waiting for you to turn around♪
♪The world is silent
and I miss the hustle and bustle♪
♪Put my heart into your palm lines♪
♪The balance of the scales
of love is tipped by you♪
♪Touch your inner world♪
♪Start a fantasy journey♪
♪A pair of lovers have lost their minds♪
♪And been sinking♪
♪In love♪
♪The ties between people♪
♪Are countless and complicated♪
♪As long as♪
♪We hear♪
♪Each other's heartbeats and breath♪
♪I'm waiting for you to turn around♪
♪The world is silent
and I miss the hustle and bustle♪
♪Put my heart into your palm lines♪
♪The balance of the scales
of love is tipped by you♪
♪Touch your inner world♪
♪Start a fantasy journey♪
♪A pair of lovers have lost their minds♪
♪And been sinking♪
♪In love♪