Timing and Subtitles brought to you
by Cracks in the System @ Viki.com
Did you know that Attorney Ha was from a conglomerate family?
I had no idea.
I just found out from the article.
I was honestly so shocked.
How can someone be so two-faced? It's so scary.
You're not secretly an heir, either, right?
Let's stop... and get back to work.
- Yes, Ma'am.
- Okay.
Can I get an egg?
Sure.
Are they reporters?
Isn't that Hanguk Group's secretariat?
Read the room.
What?
- What?
- Nothing.
Work together?
I've never co-counseled a case before.
Okay then.
Since they only have one associate, Attorney Kang Hui Ji will take that side.
Since we have two associates,
I'll check with Attorney Bae on our side.
I'll just take it.
The Advisor gave us this case under the condition
that we co-counsel it with another floor.
There he comes.
I guess you decided to take it, Attorney An.
- Am I working with An Ju Hyeong?
- Yeah.
You two know each other, right?
Yes.
Now that I see you like this, you guys look great together.
Pardon?
Well then, please take good care of Attorney Kang.
Please keep it professional.
Well, which side do we need to represent?
The plaintiff, Kang Chang Jun.
Hey, say something, damn it!
Why don't you listen when I tell you something?
How many times did I tell you?
What? Are you offended?
Damn it, you won't even answer me.
I said answer me, asshole!
You asshole!
Get up, get up, you asshole.
(Police in Korea)
We got a report about a fight.
Thank you for your service.
Yes, hello.
But there's really no problem here.
It's okay. I think you can go now.
There's no issue here.
If you come down here like this...
Are those the two who were fighting?
No, no. There's no problem.
Have you ever seen him hit people before?
No, it was the first time.
If it happened before, I wouldn't have been shocked. But...
he was beating him like an animal.
So, I felt compelled to call the police. But now...
the guy who got beaten up says he wasn't hit.
And you were told not to come starting the next day?
Yes.
After he found out I called the police, he told me right away not to come.
Did he give you a reason?
I'm sure he didn't say it was because you reported it.
He didn't give any reasons. He just said. "Don't come."
What did I do wrong that I should leave?
Isn't this what you call a wrongful dismissal?
Right, Attorney?
Put everything else aside,
they didn't follow any of the proper procedures for dismissal.
So wouldn't it be easiest to focus on that aspect?
It's true they didn't follow the dismissal procedures under the Labor Standards Act.
Then, isn't it resolved?
But the issue is whether we can establish Kang Chang Jun as a worker.
He's a club DJ. Does he qualify as a worker under the law?
Oh, worker classification.
You're right.
We need to get that recognized first.
But from what we've heard so far, it's vague.
He has no employment contract, no national insurance,
no solid way to prove his working hours,
and he wasn't working every day, either.
What about pay? He must've been paid, right?
Yeah, he probably was.
But because his shifts weren't regular,
his pay probably varied month to month.
Then, it won't look like a fixed salary.
More like he was paid per performance.
Exactly. Even if we prove that he was a worker,
since it currently looks like Kang Chang Jun falsely reported Lee Dong Su,
they might argue that the dismissal wasn't wrongful.
Even if this dismissal is invalid due to not following the procedure,
they could follow the procedure next time and fire him again for the same reason.
That's right. That's the issue.
Then, should we meet that person first?
- Who?
- The guy who got hit. Jeong Min Gyu.
Where?
- You came dressed like this?
- I should ask you that.
Of course. I came to work. How else?
We should hide that we're here for work.
At least take off your tie.
- Geez, why should I take off my tie?
- Just listen to me.
And let's open the top two buttons.
Okay, okay. I'll do it.
Take off that jacket.
Take off my jacket, too? It's cold!
- Take it off.
- Okay.
Much better.
But did we really have to come here?
Kang Chang Jun doesn't know his number, either.
I'm sure we could've found out somehow.
We don't have time to wait for that. Let's go.
You said you came to work.
Excuse me, is Jeong Min Gyu here?
Who?
Jeong Min Gyu.
Try over there.
Excuse me.
Hi. Are you looking for the restroom?
This area is for staff only. You can't be here.
You're Jeong Min Gyu, right?
- Who are you?
- You know Kang Chang Jun, right?
- Yes.
- We're Kang Chang Jun's attorneys.
When you were assaulted, he called the police
and got fired.
- Fired?
- Yes.
So, we were hoping to hear from you about what happened.
He misunderstood and reported by mistake.
I'm sorry, but I'm kind of busy.
We can help you as well, Jeong Min Gyu.
I got hit because I deserved it.
It's not a big deal.
It's not serious enough to need your help, Attorneys.
Next time you come,
let me get you a table and enjoy yourselves.
That's how you can help me.
I don't know what took place,
but there's no such thing as deserving a beating.
No matter what you did,
Lee Dong Su had no right to hit you.
So, if you change your mind, please call me.
Who are you?
This area is only for staff. You can't be here.
Where did you come from?
Are you hiring DJs?
I heard there was an opening.
- A DJ?
- I wasn't sure who I needed to talk to.
Both of you?
You don't hire teams?
"Are you hiring DJs?"
"You don't hire teams?"
I had no choice because you started out with DJs.
You should've said we're the DJ and manager.
- Called you my manager?
- No, you'd be my manager.
Well, anyone can see that you'd be my manager, and I'd be the DJ.
You don't look like a DJ, either.
In any case, do you think he'll call?
It won't be easy to get his testimony.
We'll have to wait and see.
I still have my wristband on.
- Give me your arm.
- No, it's all right.
Come on.
I guess you've gone clubbing quite a bit.
Yes. You haven't?
No.
And you said you were a DJ?
I'm getting off here.
- Okay. See you tomorrow.
- Okay.
Hello, Attorney.
- Hello, sir.
- You're coming in now?
Yes. Are you going somewhere?
I ran out of coffee this morning,
so I'm heading to the store to restock.
Chief, would you like this?
It's perfect instead of coffee on an empty stomach.
Goodness, thank you.
Hello.
How long will it take?
Just a moment.
Security Chief, what's all this?
Oh, this?
They're installing a base station in our building.
Oh, really?
Apparently, the rent for this is quite high.
Then, will the Advisor give you a bonus?
Gosh, I can't expect such a thing.
Go on your way, Attorney.
Yes. Have a good day.
Thank you.
Is there anything else you need?
This should be enough to work with.
Also, if the dismissal is ruled wrongful,
you can claim back wages for the time you couldn't work.
We'll include that in the claim.
No.
All I need is a ruling that proves
that my dismissal was baseless and that I did nothing wrong.
I don't want to be paid for the time I didn't work.
This is your legal right as the one who was
wrongfully dismissed, Kang Chang Jun.
You don't have to think like that.
All I want is to work there again with my head held high.
But do you really want to go back there?
Yes.
After all I went through to come from the countryside
to make it to a club in Hongdae?
There's no reason I can't keep working there.
I've done nothing wrong.
Okay, then we'll proceed with only invalidating the dismissal.
Thank you.
Yes, this is Hyungmin Law Group.
Okay. May I ask who's calling?
Yes?
A school senior?
Okay, then connect me.
Yes, I'm on the line.
Is this Attorney Ha Sang Ki?
Yes. That's right.
I'm Director Lee Min Woo from HR Hunting.
I'm a headhunter.
You graduated from Gwangseong University Law School, right?
I'm an alum, too.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry, but what is this about?
A startup that just completed Series C funding
wants to bring you onboard as a director-level legal counsel.
What do you think?
The compensation will be at an executive-level at a major corporation.
Me?
Yes.
They specifically asked for you.
That's why I'm calling.
Well, I've never worked in-house before.
But why me, though?
Well, they're looking to build a relationship with Hanguk Group.
It appears they're hoping you could help with that.
I'm sorry. I'm going to hang up.
Can I say something about that?
Yes, what are you referring to?
The article...
Is it true?
It's not.
Okay.
That will be our stance, then.
- Let me know if anything uncomfortable comes up.
- It's all good.
Okay.
Gosh, it's freezing.
He's here, he's here.
Where's Sang Ki?
He said something urgent came up. He said we can start.
So...
no one is going to say anything about Sang Ki?
He asked us to overlook it.
- Is that what that meant?
- Of course.
I told you to read the room.
- Is yours bulgogi?
- Yeah.
Swap with me.
Okay.
But did you guys know?
No, we didn't know.
Did you know, Oppa?
No, I didn't know.
I was the most clueless.
Why are you getting all upset about?
He didn't want us to know.
Yeah, let's give Senior Sang Ki some time.
What's wrong with you now?
Damn it.
Going home now?
Yeah.
You should've told me at least.
- What do you mean?
- That my family
made money subcontracting for your family.
It must've been so funny to you every time I brought it up.
- It's not like that.
- Even if you didn't feel that way,
now that I've found out this way,
I can't help but think that.
It's not like that.
Then, what is it?
What are you trying to do?
You still have nothing to say to me?
Even if it's not about my family,
I thought we were closer than just work colleagues.
I thought we could talk openly about anything.
I don't talk about my family with just anyone.
I told you because it was you.
I guess I was the only one who thought we were friends.
I'm sorry.
In response to the plaintiff's claims,
the defendant has denied the plaintiff's worker status,
and the plaintiff has submitted evidence to prove it.
- Yes.
Plaintiff's counsel,
could you briefly explain your evidence?
Yes. First, please take a look at
Exhibit No. 3, the plaintiff's transit card records.
They show that he consistently arrived and left
at the same time each day at the defendant's club.
If you look at Exhibit No. 4, the plaintiff's cell tower data,
...it shows his location at Seogyo-dong in Mapo-gu during commuting hours,
and the defendant's club is located in Seogyo-dong.
The plaintiff had fixed working hours
even when he wasn't performing.
His pay may appear inconsistent month to month,
but it directly correlates with the days he worked,
and you can see that it has nothing to do with the number of performances.
This proves it was a salary for coming into work
rather than as payments for gigs.
Moreover, if you look at the text details between the plaintiff and defendant,
you can see the plaintiff worked under the direct supervision of the defendant.
You also do the 11:00 p.m. and 3:00 a.m. slots.
I'm telling you to do them because the other guy can't make it.
Why complain? There's not much to do. Just go home.
- Defendant's counsel?
- Yes?
Are those text messages actually from the defendant?
- Defendant's counsel?
- Were they sent by the defendant?
Attorney?
Who are you talking to?
The defendant, Mr. Lee Dong Su.
Are you the defendant himself?
- Yes.
- Please come up to the front.
- Defendant's counsel?
- Yes?
Did you know he was sitting in the back?
Well...
If the defendant is present, he should sit in the front.
Why were you in the back?
Does it mean you have something to hide?
No, it's not like that.
You didn't follow the proper dismissal procedure, right?
He's not a worker, so it wasn't a dismissal.
Did you follow the proper procedure?
How's a club DJ a worker?
I guess you weren't listening despite sitting back there.
That's what we've just been proving.
Kang Chang Jun is a worker.
All right, plaintiff's counsel.
Please refrain from addressing the defendant directly.
Yes. I'm sorry.
Great work today.
Hello, Advisor.
I stopped by out of curiosity.
- You were really prepared.
- Yes.
Hey, I've got records of your false police report.
I could just fire you again with those.
Jeong Min Gyu gave us his full testimony.
He admitted there was an assault
and that the report wasn't false.
I came because what you said the other day stuck with me,
but I don't think I can do this.
If I give you my statement,
do you think I can keep working there?
Kang Chang Jun reported it
in order to help you.
Did I ask for his help?
Others are trying to help you like this.
Why won't you take care of yourself?
There's no such thing as "deserving to be hit."
You don't have to testify for us.
But at least protect yourself.
I'll help you.
Min Gyu, that jerk...
A complaint from Jeong Min Gyu will also be filed soon.
Just leave me alone!
Why do you keep following me around! So annoying...
How does Lee Dong Su know the Advisor?
Who's the Advisor?
You don't know Advisor Kim Hyeong Min?
No, I don't.
Really?
Is the Advisor that rich?
She owns this building.
- This building?
- Yeah.
That's amazing.
- Did you know?
- Well, I figured that might be the case.
She's Kim Hyeong Min of the Hyungmin Building.
You're right.
Did you two know, too?
No, I didn't know.
What about you?
I didn't know, either.
I'm clueless about stuff like that these days.
But what's with your reaction?
This is such big news. This isn't like you.
It's not like I can freak out over everything.
What?
What's wrong with him?
You'll be back here in a few days anyway.
Don't assert your pride.
It'll only eat you up inside.
Hello.
It's you. You may enter.
Hello, Managing Partner.
When you said you'd work for the office above for better pay,
I respected that.
It was honest.
They offered more money. Of course, you should go.
Whether it's a floor above or the firm across from us.
However, it now appears that it was all a lie.
If you didn't like our firm, you should've just said so.
Why did you use your salary as an excuse?
Mr. Seong, it's really not like that.
If you think that because of the article, it's a big misunderstanding.
All right.
- It'll be a bit cold.
- Okay.
She's my daughter.
Oh, I see.
I don't know where to start.
Please take your time.
Or would you prefer that I ask you some questions?
No.
I'll talk.
When she was young,
we sent her to study abroad in the U.S.
In the 8th grade.
I think that's the appropriate place to begin.
Since that turned out to be an error in judgment.
Did Kim Yu Jin go alone?
Yes. We sent her alone.
Her father and I had too much going on here.
We thought sending her, albeit alone, was better for her future.
We trusted she would do well in the U.S.
even if she's alone since she's our daughter.
But that's where she was introduced to drugs.
Yes.
She said she first started in college.
We actually knew early on.
We tried taking her to therapy,
brought her back to Korea to live together,
and we even moved to the States
to stay with her.
But nothing worked.
Then, does Kim Yu Jin have a criminal record for drug use?
No.
This is the first time that she has been arrested.
She was put under immediate arrest.
Where was the location of the arrest?
Incheon Airport.
She was arrested as soon as she landed.
As soon as she landed?
Then, someone probably tipped them off.
Do you know who?
Yes.
It was me.
Though she is our daughter, our efforts alone weren't enough.
So...
we told her to come to Korea...
and we reported her.
And...
I want her to be released from detention.
That's why I came here.
Please help her, Attorney.
- Heading out now?
- Yeah.
What's with this awkward air?
This is so unfamiliar.
- Hello. Attorney Ha Sang Ki, right?
- Pardon?
We're from News Off.
We're following up on the elite family law school admissions article.
That's not me. You've got the wrong guy.
You have the best background of all the admitted students...
- Hey. Stop. He said no.
- Do you believe you deserved your spot?
- Stop it.
- All right, all right. We get it.
You got the wrong person.
We know it's you, Attorney. Please give us a statement.
I said it's not me.
- Please stop this.
- Why don't you talk with me?
- Mr. Ha Sang Ki.
- You go on.
I said go on.
- It doesn't cost anything to talk!
- Mr. Ha Sang Ki, wait!
I know many fun stories.
Crazy jerk.
At a time like this?
When I was in college, my nickname was the Spirit of Spring.
Because I would vanish in the fall
and return whenever spring came.
I had to work through the fall
to afford tuition for the spring semester.
That's why it took me eight years to graduate.
I was what they call a "dirt spoon."
During my difficult, impoverished childhood,
studying was all I could do.
Because it felt like the only way out.
After graduation,
I wasn't even planning to go to law school, nor did I have the means.
But after six months of working,
I felt like I had to go back and study.
Maybe I was a Spirit of Spring after all.
If not for the school and third-party scholarships,
I could've never become an attorney.
I'm always thankful for the kindness of strangers
and the support that came through the system.
And I hope to pass it on someday.
As for the modern-day nepotism,
I don't really know much about that.
All I know is that students study hard
to become good attorneys.
Even the classmate you mistook me for
due to our similar names, probably did the same.
So please, don't criticize him, either.
And I hope no one ever has to
go through what I did tonight,
having to prove their poverty.
One bowl of rice soup, please.
This isn't your dinner, right?
No, I had dinner way earlier.
Then, why don't you just rest?
Why come all the way here this late?
I'm fine.
But you should stop working so late, Mom.
I should keep working as long as the owner lets me work.
Sitting around would only make me sick.
Who gets sick from sitting around?
Working too much makes people ill.
Can I get some more radish kimchi here?
Okay.
Hold on a second.
Have a fried egg before you go.
I recently handled Crystal Park's divorce case.
- What?
I represented the husband against Crystal Park.
And it ended through mediation.
- Wow!
- Amazing!
I even met her privately afterward and talked to her.
Wow!
Honestly, I've been doing visitation attorney work recently.
- Visitation attorney work?
- You know,
going in like a butler to keep them company,
update them on the outside world and entertain them.
The stuff we're not supposed to do.
- You were doing that?
- Your boss makes you do that?
Exactly.
When I go there now, they don't even check my attorney ID anymore
because I go there so often.
To be honest, I'm pregnant.
- What?
So, just in case, I haven't taken rhinitis meds,
and stopped drinking coffee. And of course, not alcohol.
I get worried when I'm working late
and even when I'm running around.
Wait, does Ji Seok know?
Hey, since when? How long has it been?
They said six weeks.
I already knew all of this.
- What?
- What? How?
You kept checking your period tracking app
and spitting food out.
How about Ju Hyeong's case?
When I ran into him at the family court,
I looked up his case number and party names.
- What about Chang Won?
- He told me that himself.
Wow, seriously.
You're incredible.
But wasn't I the main character today?
- Why would you be?
- Why, Oppa?
Why would you be?
What for?
You probably didn't know, but when I was young, I was really—
We know. You wrote such a long post. Why bring it up again?
You knew about it?
You posted it publicly for everyone to see.
Didn't you ask us to play ignorant?
- Wait, Ha Sang Ki.
- What?
If it took you eight years to graduate
and you worked in between,
then you didn't do military service, did you?
You've been pretending like you did all this time!
I did do military service, man! Six months.
My dad is a National Merit recipient.
The food won't be good if it gets cold.
Okay, we'll eat it right away.
Let's eat.
Crazies...
Hey...
Well...
- Sorry about that.
- No need.
Thanks for what you did yesterday.
Gosh, I take it back.
This is so awkward. Geez...
I didn't mean it, either, you jerk.
I cringed first, you know!
- He's so weird.
- Hey, wait up!
Hey!
Wait up.
I thought you wanted me to ignore it,
but you really weren't?
That's right.
That person wasn't me. I told you so.
Why didn't you deny it more emphatically from the start?
Why did you wait until everyone dragged your name through the mud?
Pardon?
Did you read all the comments, too?
Well, they were visible everywhere.
Was it really that hard to say
that it wasn't you, and it was someone with a similar name?
I mean, I just hoped it would blow over.
Honestly,
I didn't want to think about how I grew up poor,
and if I denied it too emphatically,
I felt like I was telling them to criticize that classmate.
I didn't want that, either.
Attorney Ha, I didn't know you had this side.
I thought you were the ultimate individualist.
Yes, it turns out I did.
I see that now.
Yes?
What are you doing? Why are you here in my office?
We're still collaborating on Mr. Kang Chang Jun's case.
But the hearing is over. Our job is done.
There's still the ruling hearing left. It's not over yet.
- Ruling hearing?
- Let's go.
Why would we go to the ruling hearing?
Don't you want to see how it goes?
It's your first collaboration case in ten years.
Let's go. We'll be late.
Gosh, I told you it's nine years, not ten.
All right, fine. Nine years.
Hurry up, let's go.
Fine...
Case number...
2024-Gadan-25134.
Plaintiff Kang Chang Jun.
Defendant Lee Dong Su.
Neither party is present, right?
Here.
Kang Chang Jun's counsel is present?
- Yes.
- And the plaintiff himself is present?
Yes, that is correct.
Very well. I'll now declare the ruling.
The dismissal issued to the plaintiff on September 3, 2024, by the defendant
is hereby declared invalid.
The defendant shall bear the litigation costs.
I judge in favor of the plaintiff.
Thank you.
Case number 2024-GaDan-1987.
Plaintiff Botino Inc. Defendant Flik LLC.
Neither party is present, right?
The plaintiff's claim is dismissed.
The plaintiff shall bear the litigation costs.
How was it? Aren't you glad you came?
I didn't even do anything there.
We were going to win anyway.
Damn it.
You...
Why did you have to introduce Kim Ji Seok to me?
Now I'm married and pregnant.
Why are you so mad about something to be celebrated?
Who says this is to be celebrated?
Who do you think you are?
And I'm the one who decides how to feel about it.
But I haven't yet, so could you shut up?
Damn it!
Is it that hard?
Yeah, it's hard.
This is making me worry in so many ways.
And I'm not someone with maternal instincts.
I don't think I'd develop any in the future, either.
That's what you're worried about?
Why do you think you need to have maternal instincts?
Of course, I need maternal instincts.
I'll need to raise a child.
But you like people in general.
You just swear a lot. That's all.
I'm sure you'll love your child, too.
Why worry so much about that?
It doesn't have to be maternal instincts.
I...
like people in general?
Yeah. You didn't know?
You're oddly kind lately.
No, I'm not.
Attorney.
Mr. Jang Su Gil went to court today.
I hear it's his ruling hearing.
Ruling hearing?
Gosh, you're so funny.
Attorney Jo, you're here?
Wow.
You look way better out here.
- I told you I'd get out, didn't I?
- He got acquitted. Not guilty.
I see. Congratulations.
Thanks for the fruit.
Yeah, yeah. Enjoy yourself.
I wasn't joking back then.
Come work for me. I'll treat you well.
See you around.
Please bring this to my office.
What are the prosecutors even doing?
They can't even convict a guy like him.
There were pretty female attorneys here after all.
Why did they send me a guy?
Who the hell is this creep?
Do you know me?
Move!
I'm sorry.
What the hell?
Do I really like people?
Everyone, gather up. My treat.
It's a pregnancy party!
Hello?
Are you home?
I'm heading home on the subway.
Are you still at work?
Yeah, I'm still at work.
I might be a bit late.
I see. Okay.
Is that why you called?
- No.
- Then?
My phone's dying. Tell me quickly.
- What is it?
- I'm pregnant.
Hello?
- Yeah.
- I said I'm pregnant.
They say I'm six weeks in.
Yeah.
That's it.
No one's here yet?
No.
Mun Jeong!
What the...
Why did you come here?
Well...
earlier, I was just... so shocked...
s-so shocked...
It was just that I was so shocked.
Well...
But then, my p-phone ran out of battery and died...
I t-thought you might be freaking out...
You're nuts.
Why are you crying?
I'm sorry. I-I was just so shocked...
You must've been so scared...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry...
Then, you're happy that I'm pregnant?
You're happy, right?
What kind of question is that? Of course I am!
- You're cold, right?
- Yeah, I'm cold.
Let's hurry up and go home.
Watch your head.
Your seatbelt.
Gosh...
It's really cold out today, isn't it?
So, you went home and brought the car?
Yeah, I came out in such a rush.
Drive safely.
You might get into an accident.
Let's feast tonight!
Gosh, you scared me.
It's a bar, man. A bar, not a restaurant.
Hey, you think I can't feast at a bar?
What's wrong with you?
Hello, how are you guys?
Hello.
I guess you're going home.
Yes.
Attorney Ha, you must've had a rough time.
Oh, no, not at all.
­
Well then, I'll see you around.
- Okay.
- Okay, good night.
So... I'm sorry,
but I have to cancel today's party.
Everyone go home. Don't party without me.
Geez, what's the matter with her?
She says we should all go home.
I saw it, too.
Gosh, seriously...
Maybe we should just grab a drink by ourselves.
Where?
Hey, tell me where!
Are you buying?
Could you please tell me where we're going?
Could you please stop asking me?
What do you mean? I followed you all this way.
Just come.
All these places are closed.
I know a perfect spot, man.
What is this place?
Is this a hidden gem?
Why come all this way to have rice soup?
Gosh, I'm freezing.
What are you waiting for? Say hello to my mom.
- What?
- Mom, say hi. This is my friend.
- Mom? Y-Your mother?
- Yeah.
H-Hello, ma'am.
M-My name is Jo Chang Won. H-Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yes, it's nice to meet you, too.
I'm a good friend of Sang Ki.
We eat, get drinks, and do everything together all the time.
- Have a seat.
- Oh, yes, yes.
Come on, feed me already. I'm cold.
Thank you. Yes.
Why didn't you tell me? You should've told me sooner!
This place is really good.
It's not my mom's restaurant. She just works part-time here.
- I said, no! I don't want to!
- Come on, just once. Just once.
Let's just do it once.
Goodness, what's with you?
- I want to do it so badly.
- Were you this kind of girl?
It's dangerous. No.
How's it dangerous? Let's just do it before the baby gets bigger.
There's no "just once"! We're not doing it!
Okay, wait, wait.
You just stay below me. I'll go on top.
You're not considerate of me on the bottom.
- Come on!
- I said, no!
- Please!
- Come on!
All right, it's only for one meter. Okay?
- Okay, okay. Just once.
- Seriously, you...
It's like I'm raising a kid already.
- Hey, my neck's bent! Go down!
- Are you okay?
- Gosh, this is so high.
Hey, hold on tight. I'm going to try leaning back.
Hey, try moving forward.
- Stop it. Hey!
- Move forward.
Spiderman. Spiderman.
Hey, this is so much fun!
- What's so fun about this?
- Gosh, this is so fun.
Quiet, Bae Mun Jeong! The neighbors will complain!
- Hey, too high. You okay? Be careful!
- Let's go. Go, go.
The more I think about it, the more ridiculous this is.
A pregnancy party sounded strange to start with.
Then...
let's call it a first successful collaboration celebration.
First successful collaboration celebration?
That's a mouthful.
So, you've never worked on a case with someone else before?
No, I never needed to since I'm good at my job.
You probably won't need to do that again even into your ninth year.
You're so insistent on saying nine years.
You could've just rounded up to ten.
Because it's been nine years.
You performed this song, right?
You remember that?
Shouldn't we have left earlier?
But that dim sum place was a must.
Who knew traffic would be this bad?
But it was good, though. Right?
Yeah, it was pretty good.
But let's hurry.
People would think I'm the one going to work.
- Are you hurt?
- No, I'm okay. Let's go.
Get on my back.
I'm fine.
You said you were covering for a friend's shift.
Come on.
Hold on tight.
Oh, right.
Thank you. I'll head in first.
- Okay. Hurry on inside.
- Okay.
When did you start playing piano?
Since I was eight.
Was it always your dream to be a pianist?
Yeah, I think so.
My parents loved watching me play the piano.
I loved seeing my parents smile while watching me.
So, you played the piano because you liked seeing them smile?
That's right.
I think that's why I keep playing.
Honestly, I never dreamed of becoming a world-class pianist or anything.
What about you, Ju Hyeong?
Did you always want to be an attorney?
At first, I had a different dream.
But I changed my mind as I got older.
Why? What made you want to become an attorney?
Growing up, I was good at two things.
Arguing and studying.
So, becoming an attorney felt like the natural path.
And?
Do you think you'll become a good attorney?
Yes.
That's my dream.
Wait, is your ankle okay?
Yes, it's gotten much better.
Would you sit down for a minute?
Put your foot up here.
It's really fine...
Don't you use your right foot to press the pedal?
- That's right.
- You pushed through it.
I don't notice it while playing.
What a professional.
When did you buy this?
I ran out quickly as soon as you started playing.
You're good to go now.
By the way, this place is really pretty.
Yes, really pretty.
When we're back in Seoul,
would you like to go with me if there's another place like this?
Where?
Gangnam Station...
Gangnam Station.
Sounds good.
Sounds good...
So, how did you end up becoming an attorney?
I thought you'd stick with piano.
You don't have to tell me.
No, it's okay.
My dad had a business back then as well.
Thanks to that, I could study without worry.
But then he got scammed big time.
It was some crypto pyramid scheme.
After that, our family became a mess.
At some point, no one was smiling anymore.
But I couldn't do anything about it.
So, I made up my mind
that if anything bad were to happen to my parents again,
I will protect them myself.
It must have been very difficult, but it was overcome.
You're right.
My dad is a really strong person.
No, I'm talking about you, Kang Hui Ji.
Me?
Not everyone comes out of that thinking like you do.
You overcame it well.
You did well.
You're right.
I did pretty well.
Everything's okay now.
I just want my parents to stay happy.
That's my dream.
Your dream hasn't changed in 10 years.
Did I say this 10 years ago, too?
You really don't remember anything.
I mean, I remember your dream.
It was to become a good attorney.
You've accomplished your dream.
I can't say I became a good attorney.
Why not? You're a good attorney.
You listen to people in need
and help them fight back.
Honestly, I don't think of it as helping them.
Based on what I can see,
I just get paid to fight on their behalf.
If being a good attorney means going beyond that,
then I'm not.
Still,
you're a good attorney senior to me.
And a good person.
Thank you.
Don't you usually take the subway to work only
and take the bus home?
Yes, since the subway runs on time.
And the bus goes straight to my house.
This way leads to the subway. The bus is that way.
I know.
You're heading back tomorrow, right?
Yes.
Shall we head inside?
- Okay.
♫  In a sea of unfamiliar lights  ♫
♫  You stood out, shining so brightly  ♫
♫  What began as coincidence  ♫
♫  I hope we are meant to be wrapped in fate  ♫
♫  Can I love you even as you disappear?  ♫
♫  Even if we don't love  ♫
♫  I want to tell you from back then  ♫
♫  That it was nice to meet you, and I liked you  ♫
♫  You and I from back then, if we ever meet again  ♫
♫  I want to say to you  ♫
♫  Can I love you even as you disappear?  ♫
♫  Even if we don't love  ♫
♫  I want to tell you from back then  ♫
♫  That it was nice to meet you, and I liked you  ♫
♫  Can I love you even as you disappear?  ♫
♫  Though you may not want to hear this  ♫
♫  These are the words I've kept in my heart  ♫
Timing and Subtitles brought to you
by Cracks in the System @ Viki.com
♫  That's not why I cried  ♫|
♫  It's just that everything felt so unfamiliar  ♫
♫  At the end of time that arrived before we knew it  ♫
The girl you met on your trip while in law school—
What? You two were like that?
Ever since Hong Kong, Ju Hyeong and Attorney Kang—
Hey, Mun Jeong is looking for you.
If you're drunk, hurry up and go home.
A voice phishing case?
They said they'd make a special exception to get me a loan.
This would normally be an easy case to defend...
Where do you get this?
This must be really hard for you.
So, do your families all ask why you're not getting married?
Gosh, that scared me!
Is this your first time in Hong Kong?
- Yes.
- When was your favorite moment?
Right now?
♫  Let's greet each other with a smile  ♫
♫  Hi, today is a good day for me  ♫