Timing and Subtitles brought to you
by Cracks in the System @ Viki.com
You haven't eaten, right?
Hey! Bring some food here, too.
Okay.
Did he have an existing condition?
No.
He was so healthy.
I didn't think he'd suddenly pass like this.
Have some.
He had a big family.
No, they're all village residents.
He has a son, but he's in the US.
Until he arrives,
everyone is claiming to be the chief mourner now.
Did the village residents prepare all this?
Yes.
There's no one in our village who hasn't received his help.
Even though it didn't concern him,
he was so diligent and worked so hard to care for everyone.
If it weren't for him,
I would've never tried to get back the family land.
I don't know where it starts or ends.
The stolen land is a lot larger than you think.
Pardon?
I found the cadastral map from the Japanese colonial period.
Mr. Han In Su owned the land beyond the stream.
The land back there was ours, too?
Yes.
But what's the point?
Mr. Park is gone now.
No one would volunteer to help us.
Please enjoy your meal before you go.
Thank you so much for hearing Mr. Park out.
He must've been an amazing person.
I quit.
Find another associate attorney.
What are you doing right now, Attorney Jo?
It's exactly as I said just now.
Fine. Forget about Director Jang's case.
No.
It's not just about this case.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
I...
can't work here any longer.
What are you doing out of the blue?
Do you think work is child's play?
Well...
You can't suddenly do this.
There's a notice period when you quit.
We have to hire a replacement, do a handover,
and take legal steps—
Were there legal steps when I joined?
You didn't even give me an employment contract.
So, you were upset about that. Gosh.
Yes. Let's talk it out since we're attorneys.
Have a seat there.
Okay, then.
Work only until I hire someone new, then.
I don't want to.
I didn't know you were so firm, Attorney Jo.
If so...
Give me just 10 days.
- A week.
- Okay. A week. Thank you.
You must've been through a lot, Attorney Ha.
I'm sure Ms. Kim didn't give you that case
just so you can get him a lesser sentence through extenuation.
She must care since he's her foundation's scholarship student.
Are you attending today, too?
I want to take the class, too.
Is that okay?
Are you getting a doctoral degree?
Oh, this? No, I'm not.
I recommend it. Highly recommend it.
Attorney Ha, fighting.
­
Yes.
Oh, Attorney Ha.
Ms. Kim.
Have a seat here.
Okay.
What brings you here?
Well...
The foundation you run...
is called "Seed Foundation," right?
Yes, that's right.
How did you hear about it?
It looks like you didn't just hear about it.
Well...
Thanks to you, without taking a leave of absence,
I was able to graduate from law school.
I think that was my first time
I was able to focus on my studies only.
Thank you so much.
If it weren't for you,
I never would've dreamed of this.
It took me way too long to thank you since I didn't know.
Thank you so much.
Gosh, sit now. Sit.
I'm the one who is grateful to see you doing well.
Did you know?
Of course.
When I found out you were at a law firm in my building,
I was so thrilled.
You should've told me, then.
What would've been the point?
You don't have to know about me, anyway.
I thought I remembered everyone who helped me,
but it's embarrassing that I had no clue.
I have so many favors to return.
You don't have to return anything to me.
You'll be returning a favor by living well like you do now.
Right. And...
just like you helped me,
I'd like to help someone.
He grew up in an orphanage.
I want to give him money so he can go to college.
But I don't want him to know it's from me.
I want to support him through your foundation.
You knew someone like that?
Our foundation will help him directly, then.
No. I want to help him.
And well, now...
I do have some money, Ms. Kim.
Actually...
I didn't know why I've been saving so desperately.
I want to spend it well now.
Okay. Let's do that.
It's hot in here.
Let's forget about that case.
I saw the summary.
If we do all this,
I'd owe the court quite a lot in the civil lawsuit and delivery fees.
This is for the better.
Mr. Park is gone, but we still have our clients.
We can definitely proceed.
You said there would be a lot of plaintiffs and defendants.
It'd get too complicated, and it'd take too long.
It'd take several years to finish.
We shouldn't take it. Just forget about it.
All right.
I knew you'd say that.
Do you only do what benefits you?
Who else would do this but me?
I'm doing it because someone needs to.
Since the burden of proof is on the plaintiff,
they need to overcome reasonable doubt,
but they aren't able to do that.
Please dismiss the plaintiff's complaint.
You didn't use to feel uncomfortable with stuff like this.
I was never uncomfortable.
I was just used to feeling uncomfortable.
Attorney An, should I put away the cadastral map in the conference room?
Don't put it away. Bring it to my office.
Okay, got it.
And...
please bring me Ms. Shin's files from the Deus GA case, too.
Okay.
­
Let's go.
Let's start with the case with a ruling.
2025-Gohap-7430.
A murder case.
Defendant Jeong Sun Ja.
Mom...
Here's the ruling.
Ruling summary.
Defendant Jeong Sun Ja is sentenced to three years in jail.
However,
starting on the ruling date,
she will be on probation for five years.
Thank you...
for hearing me out, Attorney.
I decided to quit my job.
I applied to become a career prosecutor.
I'll prepare for the exam.
- Prosecutor?
- Yes.
You hate prosecutors. Why all of a sudden?
That's why I want to try.
I won't become a prosecutor like that.
How long have you been thinking about this?
It hasn't been that long.
But I couldn't do this job once I started thinking about it.
I think you'd be good. It suits you.
Thank you. You're the best.
Why aren't you guys saying anything? Huh?
Are you disappointed?
- Prosecutor Jo Chang Won doesn't sound great.
- I know.
It'd be annoying to meet him in a trial, right?
Didn't your partner say anything?
He yelled at me when I quit, too.
So what if he did? I'm quitting.
Until when will you be working there, then?
Until this week.
- So soon?
- Yeah.
Worked out that way.
I applied to the doctoral program, too.
- You ended up applying.
- Yes.
Did you want to become a professor?
Yes.
You worked hard on teaching the interns. It must've suited you well.
- What about your job, then?
- Well,
I won't be able to keep it.
You're quitting, too?
My professor said he won't hire me if I keep working
while in the program.
I have an interview tomorrow, too.
What interview?
An in-house attorney position opened up.
I'll switch jobs if I get it.
When I think about having the baby,
I don't think I can continue to work here.
You didn't get maternity leave, did you?
That's one reason.
And the company will provide better welfare after giving birth, too.
I'll be working late a lot less, too.
You struggle to work in organizations.
Isn't that why you came here?
It's better that I endure the stress.
But it's incredibly competitive.
I won't be able to work there if I don't make it.
I'll just quit, then.
This is no good.
Ma'am, we'll have a bottle of soju.
Okay.
Everyone must've had a lot of concerns.
To be honest, there's something I couldn't bring up earlier.
What is it?
I'm thinking of doing public defense cases full-time.
Full-time?
I had a thought while working on Ms. Jeong's case.
If she had no one to listen to her,
she could've gotten a heavier punishment.
If it weren't for a public defender,
she wouldn't have had a chance to tell anyone.
Not all public defense cases are like that.
A lot of them are awful, vicious criminals.
I know. There will be people like that, too.
But I want to work for people like Ms. Jeong.
But that's possible only through public defense.
It might be much harder than you think.
Because you're devoted to your clients,
you'll also treat the unforgivable people the same.
I'm worried it'd be too hard on you.
I actually have something to say, too.
Ms. Bae Mun Jeong?
Yes.
Please come this way.
Okay.
You worked for a public office,
a company in-house attorney for a few years...
- A litigation attorney for quite a bit, too.
- Yes, that's correct.
Why did you work as a litigation attorney?
I wanted to meet the clients in person
and experience many trials, too.
Why are you trying to become an in-house attorney, then?
Once I worked as a litigation attorney,
I realized that working for a company is what suits me best.
I want to get back to it and do well.
Law Group Hyungmin.
I guess it wasn't a big firm.
You must've suffered a lot, then.
You probably had to deal with people in person.
I'm sorry, I'm a little late.
I'm Attorney Bae Mun Jeong of Law Group Hyungmin.
Attorney, please take care of the rest of the trial.
Let's reclaim that joy.
Dealing with people is pretty tough.
Yes, it is.
There will be none of that here.
You won't work outside or take on a new job often.
You just need to follow the routine and get along with us.
Okay. That sounds great.
We want someone to work with us for a long time.
Yes. I'm looking for a long-term job, too.
Sounds good.
Is there something you'd like to say before we finish?
No.
I don't think you need to contact me.
- Pardon?
- To be honest,
I like being a litigation attorney.
I like meeting people,
and I like attending trials.
I love taking on new cases, too.
I think that's more important to me.
You made time for me. I'm so sorry.
What?
How did it go?
- How did what go?
- The interview.
I won't work there.
What?
I said I won't work there.
I thought so.
Great. I'm glad you're doing this.
Why are you happy? Did you want me to not go there?
Yeah. That's not the type of work you want to do.
You're right.
- Did I really do the right thing?
- Yes.
You really, really did.
I'm so proud of you.
Let's eat.
- Water.
- I'll get you water.
Here's water.
A-Are you crying?
Thank you.
What?
You're ugly, Bae Mun Jeong.
Thank you.
You wanted to eat. Why are you crying?
Let's eat. These are all your favorites, right?
Yeah.
- Hello.
Hello.
- You came.
Delivery checklist.
Drool rash cream?
Temp for maternity leave?
How many cases are you handling right now?
And it's not easy to hire a temporary attorney for just three or six months.
Not that I want to, either.
I'm a new attorney mom who's on
a break caring for a 6-month-old.
My husband will be on paternity leave for a year after six months.
So, I'm looking for a place to work for a year.
It's hard to find a job that works with my timing.
Are there any moms in this field?
I've worked as an attorney at a law firm,
but I'm taking a break after childbirth.
I'm working as a maternity leave temp right now.
The contract ends when the child joins a daycare.
I think my child can adjust smoothly.
How many days do kids usually take to adjust?
I already forgot about the difficulties with the first child.
I can't believe I'm planning for the second one.
Thankfully, the results are good.
Let's collect the eggs in two weeks.
I want to be back in just a year.
I worry if I can find a workplace
when my child is ready for school.
But it'll work out, right?
Is there an attorney who's looking for a temp during maternity leave?
Hello. I'm an associate attorney
who's looking for a maternity leave temp before childbirth.
Mr. Kwon Guk Jin, correct?
Yes, that's me.
Don't be so nervous. What brings you here?
Our new employee reported me for sexual assault.
Could you explain what happened?
Well, when a new employee joined,
we threw her a welcome party.
She ended up sitting next to me.
And...
she reported me for touching her thigh under the table.
Did your hand touch her thigh accidentally?
No, it wasn't an accident.
I just touched her.
Pardon?
It wasn't a mistake. I touched her.
Are you admitting to the charge, then?
Yes. It's true I did that.
You must be looking to lessen the sentence, then.
Is this your first offense?
First offense?
Are you asking if this is my first time touching someone
or if I've been caught and punished before?
I've never been caught and punished.
There's no CCTV, and since it was under the table,
no one could see it.
I'm looking to get acquitted this time, too.
You can help me, right?
I've never been caught. If I got caught this time,
it'd be kind of weird.
Hello?
Were you passing by my office by chance?
Yes, that's right.
How did you come just in time?
What do you mean?
It's nothing.
What is it? Tell me.
Are you worried about something?
There's a job called a public defender.
The court hires them.
They only do public defense cases
to help people who can't afford an attorney.
Hey, I know what a public defender is.
You want to do that?
Yes.
But I'm wondering if I'm being too idealistic.
I see.
Do you have to do it?
I hope you didn't do it.
Why?
I don't want you to only work with problematic people.
You've been framed once, too.
There might be people like that, too.
Of course, there can be.
I'm not sure if I'm being selfish,
but I don't want you to do work like that.
Do you think so, too?
Did someone else say that?
Yes.
Attorney Jo, I'll come in.
Okay. Come in.
Well, what's this?
Mr. Seong wants you to write defense summaries for these cases.
All of these?
Yes.
Okay, got it.
You received the case files, right?
You can do it, right? You have plenty of time.
Yes, I can do it.
Whoa, Attorney Jo is so determined. Seriously.
Gosh, there's so much to do.
And regarding the unjust profit return...
Yes.
Let's make a decision today.
Whether I'll leave or you'll follow the law.
What's this?
They're resumes for the temp position
that you didn't bother looking for.
I've done this a few times, but—
You never have. I'm sure they all just quit.
But I can't quit. I mean, I won't.
It's my right. Why should I?
But realistically—
Be realistic and pick among these.
They want to fill my position according to the labor law.
Good, right?
I'll leave, then.
Geez. What's wrong with her?
I'm looking to get acquitted this time, too.
I've never been caught. If I got caught this time,
it'd be kind of weird.
Thank you...
for hearing me out, Attorney.
Let's discuss the acknowledgment of the charge again.
Yes.
Yes, Attorney Ha.
Do you have plans this evening?
Well, no. Why?
Would you like to have dinner with me, then?
Okay.
I'll grab my stuff real quick, then.
- Okay.
- Try this, too.
- Eat, eat.
It's delicious.
By the way,
why did you suddenly suggest having dinner?
I didn't think we'd come to a place like this.
Well, I haven't eaten with you in a while.
I realized I never treated you.
Are you paying for this, then?
Of course.
Ms. Kim,
I decided to start the doctoral program.
Oh, really?
That's so great.
Will the school let you work while in the program?
No.
Huh? What will you do, then?
I think I'll have to quit my job.
Are you announcing your resignation, then?
Yes.
I feel like I'm being dumped. Was this...
a farewell meal?
Well,
not exactly.
It worked out that way. I'm sorry.
This isn't a proper sendoff.
You're free after this, right?
Let's go and get a drink.
Well, okay.
Wait...
I mean...
This is expensive stuff.
Wait, Ms. Kim...
Yes.
What brings you here, Chief?
Director, they're conducting a tax audit of the foundation.
Why all of a sudden?
They received a petition.
I think they'll be here soon, too.
Petition? From whom?
Should I give him all of this?
Give me everything from last year to today.
This is Seong Yu Deok.
I have a question.
- Take all of these.
- As for the rest...
It's in here.
Okay.
Put the rest of those in.
These are from before the merger.
Put them in for now.
Let him have them.
What are you investigating, exactly?
I'm checking if the Seed Foundation's money was
sent here as legal fees.
If we suspect other crimes like embezzlement
and breach of the Attorney-at-Law Act,
we'll report you.
They found it suspicious that our law firm keeps receiving money
as legal fees.
That's what the petition was about.
They're saying you control both companies.
What's going on right now?
Because we took legal fees from you,
we're in the hot seat right now.
Who's Lee Dong Su?
- Lee Dong Su?
- Yes.
Mr. Seong looked into it.
They're doing this because of the petition he submitted.
Are you confused because you have an office
at a law firm?
This is nothing. Please calm down first.
We did nothing wrong—
What's your purpose?
For what purpose did you merge?
Did you merge to pocket the money from the foundation?
At first, it seemed to help
but we ended up on the same case on opposing sides.
The associate attorneys formed a clique to hang out.
All the associate attorneys became weird after the merger.
There won't be any issues with the investigation.
You received the fees when the foundation brought a case,
it won't be an issue.
But right now,
the investigation isn't the only issue for you all. Right?
How long have you worked at our firm?
It's been about three and a half years.
You were here for a long time.
I've always been curious about something.
Okay.
Why did you come to our firm after working
for the firm downstairs?
Because you offered a bigger salary.
Is that really the only reason?
Yes.
You're such an interesting person.
Moving from downstairs to upstairs
will have you keep running into Mr. Seong.
It must be awkward.
Why did you hire someone from downstairs, then?
You felt uncomfortable, too.
Because I liked you.
I could tell you wouldn't do anything funny.
I thought we'd be on the same wavelength, too.
Since when did you think that?
Since the interview.
We never really talked to each other since then.
I see. The interview.
Yes.
The interview. What did you think?
I didn't think anything.
What did you think?
What is there to think about?
Of course, it was the interview.
To be honest,
I suggested sponsoring you
for the doctoral degree, to make you stay a long time.
I really had no idea, Ms. Kim.
But you're about to leave because of my suggestion.
What a shame.
Ms. Kim,
thank you for everything.
I learned a lot from you.
Gosh, that's enough.
Let's just drink. Learn what?
Are we drinking all this at once?
- Drink at your own pace.
- It's too strong.
This is how I drink.
Well...
Take your time.
You look very tired.
Do you have a lot of trials tomorrow?
I have no trials tomorrow.
I'm still going to pursue becoming a public defender.
I know it's not easy.
As you said, it's so hard dealing with awful people.
I met one like that.
But still, I stuck it out until the end.
So, don't worry so much.
I know you can do well.
It's a very difficult job.
But I think you'll be best at it out of anyone I know.
Thank you.
- Ms. Kim?
- No.
Did you sleep well?
Yes. Gosh, I passed out.
I slept well.
Yes. Tell me what this is about.
I'll have to quit because there's something I want to try.
I'll apply to become a public defender.
I came here to tell you that.
Thank you for the great opportunity, Ms. Kang.
I suspected this.
I didn't think you'd become a public defender,
but I thought you'd want to do something like that.
I'm sorry I couldn't be more understanding.
Not at all. You've been so good to me.
How much longer will you work here, then?
I'll stay until you hire someone if you need me to.
I'll stay as long as possible.
Didn't you say you don't like staying and
getting paid while your heart has already left?
- Pardon?
- During your interview,
I asked you why you quit before you found a new job.
That was your answer then.
I liked your answer then.
I'll do my best before I leave, so it won't be a waste of salary.
I hired you because I liked your answer.
I can't tell you to do the opposite.
You need to study a lot for the public defender exam.
Study hard and make sure to pass.
I'll take care of things here.
It's sad, but let's call it quits now.
All right.
Thank you for everything, Ms. Kang.
Me, too.
I finished the appeal request for Taegwon Pipes.
The current status and transfer docs
for the 48 cases I've been on are
organized and saved on my desktop.
When you hire a new attorney, tell them to look at those.
Do you know an attorney you can recommend?
I'm having a hard time hiring.
Don't worry if you don't. I'll manage it.
Good work.
Let's say hello if we run into each other in court.
Yes. Thank you.
- Huh?
- Huh? What?
Huh? What?
- It's nothing.
- Okay.
I'll stop by the fourth floor.
You're quitting today, anyway.
Why do you suddenly ask for permission?
- Go.
- You go first.
Okay, I'll go.
I'll go this way.
Yun Su will think he's getting a scholarship
from our foundation through the orphanage.
Okay. Thank you.
Protecting someone's dream feels amazing.
Yes.
That's why I want to protect mine, too.
I didn't exactly want to become an attorney.
I think I wanted to study more.
The situation didn't let me study back then.
And I thought I'd make a lot of money as an attorney, too.
I didn't think I'd have time to have a dream,
but I have one.
I decided to...
apply for the doctoral program.
Really?
That's great. Congratulations.
I really wanted to let you know.
Thank you so much for letting me know.
Gosh, you're about to get even busier.
You have to study and work late.
Well, I'm quitting my job.
Since I found what I like,
I'll only focus on that.
- You're quitting?
- Yes.
Today is my last day.
Today is my last day, too.
What do you mean?
I'll quit being a legal advisor here.
I thought being in the Seocho neighborhood meant
I achieved my dream or something.
That's why I kept lingering around here.
I bought a building here and...
I only wanted to rent to attorneys, too.
But that doesn't bring any satisfaction.
I finally admitted it.
I will...
try becoming an attorney again.
Fighting!
You, too. Fighting!
I'll try to help you.
Sure thing.
I'm sorry for making you worry yesterday.
We didn't think it'd be an issue. It's okay.
If it did, it'd be your problem. Not ours.
Anyway, I'm worried about hiring a new associate attorney.
Did yours quit, too?
I have to hire someone new, too.
Well, me, too.
I'm not sure if I could hire someone as good as Attorney Kang.
Did everyone quit?
They were together all the time.
They're quitting together, too.
By the way, did Attorney Ha quit, too?
Did he find someone who pays more again?
No. It's not like that.
He's leaving to study. I suggested it.
Okay.
Are any of yours quitting?
I heard one of yours is pregnant.
Why should she quit? She can go on maternity leave.
I already found someone to substitute for her.
Why is yours quitting?
She wants to pursue something.
I know that associate attorneys quit eventually,
but we always feel sad.
They must feel sad, saying goodbye to each other, too.
It was nice to see them having fun together.
They helped me a lot, too.
I wanted to see you today to say goodbye, too.
Thanks to you,
I was able to live my dream briefly.
I couldn't have made this decision if it weren't for this experience.
Feel free to stay merged or go back to normal.
I'll assist you no matter what decision you make.
Are you going somewhere?
No. There's something I want to focus on.
I hope to see you again somewhere else.
Go ahead and finish your food.
Thank you.
I'll get going.
♫  That's not why I cried  ♫|
♫  It's just that everything felt so unfamiliar  ♫
♫  At the end of time that arrived before we knew it  ♫
♫  I catch my breath and get through the day  ♫
♫  Small but precious scenes of the street grow a bit wistful  ♫
Hi.
♫  To everything that scatters and disappear  ♫
♫  I give the names that have been forgotten  ♫
Don't come out. We'll go on our own.
You're all free now.
Studying at my age is tiring.
Don't go and stay in Seocho, then.
I'll visit often.
No one who says that ever does.
I have no choice but to visit often.
Gosh, how annoying.
You don't have to tell me when you come.
I'm not interested.
Okay.
- Shall we go?
- We'll go. Keep in touch.
I'll go.
♫  Hi, today is a good day for me  ♫
It's my hormones, okay?
Attorney An, Deus GA wants you for their appeal trial.
I suppose Ms. Shin appealed.
Since you did such a good job last time,
they want you again. Thanks in advance.
I won't take the Deus GA case.
What do you mean?
And I'll keep working on the Mr. Park case.
Excuse me?
What are you doing?
I said we should drop that case.
Yes.
I'm not saying I'll work on it here.
Thank you for everything.
Are you saying you're quitting?
Yes.
I know you've been dissatisfied with me lately.
But I have a job
as the managing partner.
I know you understand that.
I don't think your approach is wrong.
Because I got used to it, I've worked for you for 10 years.
But now I feel uncomfortable because I'm used to it.
I'll try doing things my way.
- Do you mean you'll start your firm?
- Yes.
No matter how I tried to persuade you,
you won't change your mind.
Probably not.
Okay.
Fine.
Thank you for everything.
Why did you want to see me?
I wanted to tell you something.
What is it?
Did the company tell you to deliver something to me again?
- It's not that—
- Let me ask you first, then.
Were you on Deus's side from the beginning?
Did you keep that a secret and pretend to listen to me?
I...
I trusted you and told you everything.
How could you be like that?
I'm sorry. It wasn't like that.
What was it, then?
What are you trying to tell me now?
I heard you're pursuing an appeal.
- Will you prevent me from doing that, too?
- No.
All insurance contracts are required to be signed up on the company system.
If they let people go home only after signing a contract, as you said,
many contracts must've been signed up late at night.
Some of them must've been under the salesperson's name.
You can prove their abuse if you submit that record.
Why are you suddenly doing this?
Because I want to correct things.
I'm very sorry about everything.
♫  I still remember standing there  ♫
♫  At the end of clumsy days  ♫
♫  But, slowly now, it feels like it's all right  ♫
♫  With a tired heart, I gave up  ♫
♫  Sometimes, it's nice that way  ♫
♫  And I can breathe again with your love  ♫
♫  Yes, a little bit closer  ♫
♫  Beautiful rain is falling  ♫
♫  In the midst of your busy day  ♫
♫  Just smile and forget the pain  ♫
♫  Beautiful love again  ♫
♫  With your smile  ♫
Hold on, please.
Thank you.
­
Manager.
Gosh, Attorney Bae!
Long time no see.
Congratulations on your baby!
Thank you.
Attorney Bae.
- Hello.
Hello.
I haven't been outside for so long.
Hey, you came.
- Mr. Na.
- Is the baby doing well?
Have you been well?
Take care, then.
T-The baby's growing well...
He hasn't changed at all.
Yes.
Gosh. You came, Attorney Bae.
Long time no see. Have you been well?
Yes. You look amazing.
I don't. I'm about to die right now.
Wait for the miracle of the first birthday.
Things change after the first birthday.
Will the miracle really come?
Yes.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
I called you while you were on leave.
No. It's okay.
I live right nearby.
You're struggling with the Sumyeong ENC case?
Yes. You wrote a petition for the case.
But it's going differently than I expected.
Can I look at the record?
- It's this part.
- Oh, this part.
Where was it?
- This? This?
- Yes.
What time is the evening class rescheduled for?
I'm not a TA for that class, Professor.
- You weren't?
- No.
That thing. This thing.
Yes.
The law school class later... The contract law one.
Let them know I'll be five minutes late.
Okay, got it.
Hold on. Hold on...
- Kang Su Min.
- Yes.
- Kang Hyeok Chan.
- Go Eun Ho.
- Yes.
Dong Hyo.
Yes.
- Min Ju.
- Yes.
- Seon Yeong.
- Kim Se In.
- Yes.
Kim Hyeong Min.
Yes.
- Na Jun Yeong.
- Yes.
- No Yun Seong.
- Nam Se Hun.
- Yes.
Mun Bo Ram.
Seriously. I told you to go without me.
Why? It's nice to walk together from here.
Isn't it hard having lunch here every day?
My boyfriend is a student.
I should feed him, at least.
Follow me.
I think you'll buy me something expensive today.
Huh? I'm not.
We're having tteokbokki.
­
Prosecutor, please request the sentence.
The defendant embezzled billions of the company's money,
but he continuously denied it.
In order to blame his employee for it,
he forced perjury on other employees.
He's not showing remorse at all.
His behavior is that of a heinous criminal.
As a harsh punishment,
I request a 15-year sentence.
Hello.
Here you go.
Attorney Kang, how many will you take today?
I have 17 today.
Drink water and wait over here.
Okay.
Don't worry, everyone. It will go well.
It will go well, ma'am. Yes.
Attorney An.
You're ready, right?
Yes.
Let's go.
Case Number 2026-Gahap-3784.
Plaintiff Han Su Cheol and the other 42.
Defendant Kwak Jeong Hyeon and the other nine.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Okay. Proxies, please come forward.
The other plaintiffs and defendants will stay in the audience.
We're starting a difficult case.
Who's the plaintiff's attorney?
Plaintiff Han Su Cheol and the other 42,
and their attorney, An Ju Hyeong, are present.
Let's go eat.
Was today's visit difficult, too?
I have a crazy jerk this time.
He's a total psycho.
How could someone be like that?
- You have a crazy jerk?
- Yeah.
Resign.
I can't. It's my job.
I'm a public servant.
Or join our firm.
- I don't want to.
- Why not?
You don't want to?
Everything changes, but not this.
This won't change.
Hello.
Can't you be more punctual?
I'm not even that late.
Something funny happened today. Want to hear about it?
Later. Later.
- You only poured yours.
- Hello.
Seriously.
You'll never change. You're so—
What time is it? What time is it?
Haven't you ordered yet?
Not everyone's here.
Is the baby doing well?
Here they are.
Do you not have a perception of time or perceptions in general?
It took 30 minutes for the defendant to come.
I met with 17 people in prison.
Hey, I came from Suwon.
I came out while caring for the baby, okay?
Let's order.
- Five bean sprout soups, please.
- Okay.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you
by Cracks in the System @ Viki.com
Let's meet halfway next time.
That's what I want to say.
But we've never eaten anywhere else, have we?
We've never been anywhere else.
Just come to Seocho. It's comfortable here.
Let's eat something fancier next time.
- Yes.
- Who suggested eating this today?
We need to get tonkatsu.
- Sang Ki.
- Yes?
Let's order bossam*.
(*Boiled pork shoulder; thinly sliced)
They have bossam?
Thank you for the meal, Oppa.
They have octopus bossam.
♫  And I can breathe again with your love  ♫
♫  Yes, a little bit closer  ♫
♫  Beautiful rain is falling  ♫
♫  In the midst of your busy day  ♫
♫  Just smile and forget the pain  ♫
♫  I start a new day like this  ♫
Channel Manager:
pilar_velasquez
Chief Segmenter: queen_sung_kyung
Segmenters: pilar_velasquez, hana_860, miss_rochester, xialongne
Chief Editor: kakashiandme
General Editor: vicky_daebak
Page Designer: perilousal
💝Thanks a lot to all Cracks in the System for your hard work💝
Is the kimchi tasty?
Yes.
♫  According to the flow  ♫
♫  According to the wind  ♫
♫  Stay with me like that just for a day  ♫
♫  When I feel frustrated  ♫
♫  I want to cry for no reason  ♫
♫  Just for a day, I want to understand myself  ♫