(Tin Tem Jai)
(Episode 10)
Park!
Huh?
Why are you washing the dishes?
I'll wash it myself.
I can wash it.
Why do you need to wash it?
It's my duty.
Did I ever tell you?
I remember I never said it.
I live in your house for free.
I have to do something in return for you.
You don't have to do everything.
If you're lazy, just leave it.
I'll do it myself.
I'm willing to do everything for you.
Uh.
Huh?
Please help me clean the house today.
Because I've been with
the old stuff for too long.
I'll help you.
Park!
Huh?
What about this?
My mom really likes this vase.
Please keep it there.
Right here?
Yes.
Park.
Huh?
Are you thirsty?
I'll bring you some water.
I want orange juice.
No more orange juice.
Oh, really?
Umm.
I will buy it if I go to the market.
It's okay.
I'll call my father to bring it to us.
Hello, dad.
Can you send me an orange?
You can send parcels to me.
Or... you can drive here.
Please bring lots of them.
We can eat it in time.
Yeah.
Done.
Uh.
Babe.
After taking out the trash,
shall we find something to eat?
Sure.
Park! Tin!
Sit here.
Uncle Tong.
I want the same dish as I ordered.
Park too.
Okay.
Done.
This is your dish, Tin.
This is your dish, Park.
Thank you.
Wow.
Why Park got more than me?
Alright.
Park works hard. He must eat a lot.
Thank you.
That's right.
Eat well, Park.
I'm not complaining anymore.
Park.
I want to drink bubble tea.
Are you not full yet?
I just want to drink it.
Please?
I want to drink it. Please?
Okay.
Just go for it.
Yay!
I'll go with you.
Please?
Park, please?
Just go.
Pao, would you like to go with us?
No.
I will help my dad work.
Let's go.
Bye.
Bill, please.
Oh, sure.
Thank you.
I will come here again.
Thank you so much.
I worked hard but didn't spend a penny.
Wow.
It's very crowded.
It's okay, Park.
I'll handle it myself.
Guys, there are people fighting here!
There are people fighting here!
Hurry up!! Run!!
Run!!
But you don't have to run.
Yeah.
Please make us bubble tea first.
Sure.
What would you like?
I want a little sweet bubble tea.
What? Kana?
You took my queue.
I'm the one who said I
wanted to drink it first.
Just ask Park if you don't believe me.
Do you see? Is there a queue?
I cleared the queue for you.
Therefore, I must be the first in queue.
No!
Can you guys stop fighting?
I have a headache.
Ask Pai and Barbie if they want bubble
tea too, we can get them some too.
I'll ask them.
It's going to run out.
I should've bought 2 glasses.
You're not full yet?
You said it would save
me money, didn't you?
Why are you drinking so much?
I just like it.
You mean bubble tea?
It's you.
What era is it now?
I don't think anyone still
uses this method these days.
It's very old.
Oh. What about my bubble tea?
Here.
Thank you, Tin.
Thank you.
Park...
Huh?
Can I sleep with you tonight?
Sure.
Are you okay?
I'm glad that you can
move on from the past.
Both Aunt Pavini and Uncle Keng.
I am more than grateful to you
for helping me through
such difficult times.
Here.
From now on,
you can sleep with me every day.
Really?
Yeah.
Would you like to stop?
If you don't stop me now,
I won't stop.
Who said I would stop?
Park.
Wake up!
Wake up.
I'm so sleepy.
Can I sleep more?
No!
Ouch!
Today is Lunar New Year.
They set off firecrackers
all over the alley.
How can you still sleep?
Now it's time to pay
homage to the ancestors.
Get up!
Just do it.
But they are your ancestors.
I just...
Park!
Get up!
Alright.
I got up.
So I'll take a shower first.
Please take a shower
and meet me downstairs.
I'll follow you later.
Oh?
Park.
Huh?
Why don't you wear the
shirt I prepared for you?
It's red now.
How am I wrong?
I mean a new shirt.
I hung it up for you.
It's the same.
No.
Take it off.
I'll get you a new shirt.
Yeah.
Here.
Please hold it.
Hey!
Are you going to show off your body?
Why?
Change in the house.
You don't even know about it.
I always have to tell you.
I hung the first shirt for you.
Didn't you see it?
What is it? The other
house has finished.
This house is still trying
to figure out clothes.
How good is it that I'm awake?
Would you wake up if I didn't wake you up?
Make your ancestors wait until next year?
Can you manage anything without me?
Here.
Let's light a candle.
Please cover it for me.
Got it.
Hold it.
It's okay, just assume we've lit it.
Are you crazy?
What is your blessing?
I'm not telling you.
Why?
Sure.
Let's start with this one first.
Because it's a way ticket.
Put it down.
Park.
Huh?
Do you think people who have passed away
will really be able to eat these foods?
Food is placed here, right?
Just by lighting an incense stick,
it can teleport food to heaven?
There is a restaurant in heaven.
The food that we put here,
it's to tell the heavens that we
will order these for our ancestors.
We can light some incense for the
waiter in heaven to take our order.
They would cook it at a
restaurant for our ancestors.
Oh.
We burn paper money to
buy heavenly food, right?
Yes.
Here.
Why did you give it to me?
I have to pay respects to
you on Chinese New Year.
Am I your ancestor?
You are an adult.
You and I don't really differ in age.
Excluding my mother,
you are the only adult
in my family that I have.
They usually use 4-8 oranges, don't they?
Is it enough for you?
You usually eat a pile of oranges.
Here.
I wish you good health.
I wish you lots of sleep and rest.
I wish you to love me,
adore me,
not kick me,
and give me a marriage proposal soon.
Crazy child.
Oh.
Here.
May you live ten thousand years.
You're crazy.
I want to have Lunar New
Year every day, don't you agree?
Aren't you tired?
You wake up early to prepare.
Once a year, it's enough.
I'm willing to do it.
Your question this morning,
if I can do anything without you...
I can't.
I need you by my side.
Thank you
for being with me.
Hey, Park.
What's wrong with you?
Yeah.
Park!
Who is your brother?
Fu... Park!
I'm sorry.
You start first.
I have to say it back.
Yeah.
I am your brother.
It's true.
Why?
It's my business!
Huh?
Why are you upset at me?
You look at me and say nothing.
What do you want?
I don't have the courage to say it.
I don't know your mood.
You don't say what happened to you.
Nothing happened to me.
Come close to me.
I don't sit near you.
You'll get annoyed at me again.
Do I seem so upset?
Huh?
Only with me.
I'm sorry.
But I'm really annoyed
with you today.
I can't be upset with you?
What have I done wrong with you?
Just...
You're annoying.
I was annoyed just
seeing your face.
Park!
Just annoyed to death!
Huh?
[No Park zone]
[I hate Park!!]
[No Park!]
[I hate Park]
Babe.
Let's eat.
Please come out.
No way!
You said you were annoyed
just by seeing my face.
I'm not going out to show
you my face anymore!
I hate you!
Even if you cry?
Well.
If you don't love me then,
I'll go.
Hey!
Park, get out!
Get out!
Let's eat.
No.
You can eat whatever you want.
Then I can apologize to you 100 times.
Stop it.
I hate you.
Don't hate me.
Then I'll go.
Hey, Park!
I won't hate you anymore.
How can I hate you?
I really love you.
I'm just angry that you
said I was annoying.
But my anger subsided
after you asked me to reconcile.
It's frustrating.
Why do you have to make
me love you this much?
I'm sorry.
Can you not be angry with me?
Park.
Are you okay?
Are you sick?
No.
Hey, wake up.
Let's talk first.
Did you hear that news?
Duangjai revealed her boyfriend.
He's younger.
Who?
Huh? You missed the news.
That one from OPD room who
has been flirting with her for years.
Finally, her heart melted.
Young people are good.
People gossip about how
many days they can date.
They are different in age.
No matter... Yeah.
What's wrong with dating younger people?
Has anyone ever told you that
dating younger people is wrong?
They gossip about it.
Hold on.
Why are you bothering about it?
Huh?
No.
You seem suspicious.
- Huh? Park.
- No.
Nothing.
It seems like it struck a nerve.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Or do you prefer younger people?
You seemed to care about younger topics.
No.
If I knew it.
Tin!
You're coming.
Why didn't you come
out and welcome me?
I'm preparing equipment upstairs.
I have to go to college.
Why does it have to be now?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you upset with me?
I'm so tired today.
There are hard cases
throughout the day.
I want to hug you.
But I didn't see you when I came back.
Why wouldn't it frustrate me?
Would you like some orange juice?
I'll make it for you.
Yeah.
Wait a moment.
Is there anything else
I can help you with?
Would you like to hug again?
No.
I have not showered yet.
I just want to ease your tiredness.
Then...
How can it alleviate my tiredness?
Oh? Tin.
How long have you arrived?
You're so late.
I just bought snacks.
Stop complaining.
Where's the snack?
Can I eat it with you?
Will you join the project
that Tiw invited you to?
Maybe.
It makes money.
Park won't be angry with
you if you stop studying, right?
I haven't told him yet.
What if he scolds you?
He wouldn't scold me.
[Sam Khok Hospital]
Park.
Huh?
Let's eat today?
No.
I have an appointment with Tin.
I'm late now.
Okay.
See you. Hurry up.
Bye bye.
Pimdao, when will your father come?
I don't know either.
Just try calling Dad.
I've called.
But your father didn't answer my call.
Oh, Tin.
Stop it.
I have not showered
yet. I'm covered in germs.
Why did you get off work late today?
There were many patients today.
Let's go back home.
Oh?
It's raining.
Are you free on Saturday?
Why?
I work late at night but I'm free
during the day, wanna see a movie?
I can't go.
I have a painting job in other provinces.
I was about to tell you.
It's a big job.
So I had to sleep over there.
It would probably take about 5 days.
5 days?
I go there on Saturday and Sunday.
I'm on leave until Wednesday.
Do you have to skip class?
It's only 3 days.
You can't do it on Saturday
and Sunday, and come back?
No.
I already told them.
Why didn't you tell me first?
I get a semester fee
if I complete this job.
I already told you
that I will pay for it.
I already told them.
I have to go anyway.
This work is an opportunity.
If the work results are good,
I may get more work after this.
If you don't listen to me, it's over.
Tin!
Talk to me first!
Talk to me!
Tin!
Well, I'll go myself.
I'm sorry.
I should apologize to you too.
I'll tell you next time.
No.
Don't skip class next time.
Okay.
I won't skip class next time.
And...
Huh?
I don't want us to fight again.
I was terrified when
you scolded me harshly.
I was afraid we'd be angry
with each other for a long time.
I don't know what the heart is made of.
But it's fragile.
Well.
The heart is muscular and shaped like...
Park.
I don't want to talk to Wikipedia right now.
I'm just being metaphorical.
I think you want to know it.
I'm bored of science students.
Hello, Park.
I have arrived here.
We thought we'd sleep here.
It's convenient for my work.
I can stay here. It's fine.
It's only 5 days.
Please be patient.
I'll hang up. I have to continue working.
Hello, kids.
Oh, Boot.
Hello.
- Hello, you all.
- Hello.
Hello, Tiw.
Yes.
Just do as we agreed.
Okay.
If there is anything missing, please tell me.
Don't be a stranger.
Yeah.
If you need anything,
my restaurant staff can help you.
Okay. Thank you.
Please take care of them.
Sure.
I'll go outside.
Okay.
Okay?
Thank you, Tiw.
Yeah.
What's wrong? Tin.
Your face looks sad.
I want to go home.
Just get your work done
if you want to go home.
I don't want to do this job.
Can I go back first?
Don't be fussy.
Just finish your work and you can go home.
Well, guys.
Let's continue to work.
Tin.
It's really you.
Can you remember me?
You get to do the
work that you love.
You've opened the
restaurant you hoped for too.
You said you always
wanted to run a restaurant.
Do you remember it?
How can I not remember?
There are few memories of my mother.
You wouldn't have any
difficulty now, would you?
It's enough for me to be
able to take care of myself.
My new husband helps and supports me.
I can't open a restaurant by myself.
You probably didn't tell anyone
that you had me.
Tin.
Here's some money and my new phone number.
If you are in trouble or or having
difficulties, you can always call me.
I'm always glad to help you.
Please take it.
It's okay.
Please take it, dear.
So that I don't feel so bad.
Okay? Please keep it.
It's okay.
Please keep it yourself.
Why?
Please take it.
Please?
I don't need money.
I just want an apology from you
that you left me.
You haven't even apologised once.
And this money,
you forced me to take it
so you don't feel guilty.
Did you ever really love me?
Please take it.
Tin!
I missed you so much.
Umm.
Huh?
Park.
What do you have a phone for?
I sent you a message telling
you to buy some delicious food.
Why didn't you read it?
I'm starving to death right now.
Let's go. I'll take you
to get something to eat.
If it was something more important,
wouldn't you know about it?
Let's go.
What would you like to eat?
Please?
I'll take you to get something to eat.
Park.
I'm serious.
What happened to you?
Nothing happened to me.
I just don't like that you
don't read my messages.
I want you to answer me all the time.
How can I answer you all the time?
I have to work.
But I want you to answer anyway.
Please answer me if you are free.
I want you to be with me all the time.
I can't ask for it?
What happened to you?
Are you angry with me?
No.
I just want to try rampaging once.
I'm mad, so I don't know what to do.
Why are you angry with me?
It's like you're chasing me far away.
What's wrong with you?
Why didn't you tell me honestly?
I met my mom.
My mom has a new family.
She has a good life.
It looked like she
was in no trouble at all.
I hate her.
I hate that she's happy.
I'm very bad, right?
But I don't like that she smiles at me
like she doesn't feel guilty.
I will definitely forgive my mom.
But not today.
It's okay.
It's okay that it's not today.
I know I'll be dumped.
You're not getting dumped.
She would leave me,
so she gave me to you.
It would be nice if
she really dumped you.
Huh?
So that you can be with me forever.
Park...
Babe.
Huh?
Do you want to sleep in my room?
I have to do my homework tonight.
I may not be able to sleep with you.
Just working in my room.
I might do it until late at night.
I don't know if I can sleep.
I'm worried that I might bother you too.
I can fall asleep easily.
Don't worry if it will disturb me.
No.
I mean you will disturb me.
I will not finish my work.
But this week we
haven't slept together yet.
Just sleep first.
I'll follow you after I finish my homework.
Alright.
It's not the same right now.
Are you talking to Passorn?
Yeah.
I'm going to sleep.
Don't stay up too late.
Okay.
I'll sleep in the morning.
You're stubborn.
Are you done?
Yeah, it's done.
Do you want to say something?
Huh?
Are you kidding me?
I wanted to give it
to you this evening.
But I saw you had a bad experience,
so I kept it.
But just now.
I woke up and found you,
I want to give it to you right away.
Hold on.
Are you going to propose to me?
You're not romantic at all.
What romance do you want me to have?
It's true.
Just when you buy me a ring,
I'm already surprised.
Because I really want to marry you.
All my life, I only have you.
Whatever I can get,
I want it to be yours.
From now on
if I'm not alive,
I want everything to be yours.
Park...
But now we can't really get married.
I would like to be engaged to you first.
The ring is expensive.
Please take good care of it.
Sure.
I will take care of it as much as my life.
If the two of us can really get married,
I'll ask you for a proposal again.
I'll wait.
I love you, Park.
I love you too.