(Tin Tem Jai)
(Episode 5)
Tin,
do you take Park to be your life partner?
Yes.
Park, do you take Tin to be your life partner?
Can you show your love to everyone?
Kiss now! Kiss now! Kiss now!
Kiss now!
Tin.
Tin!
Huh?
The reason you're smiling is that
is because you're thinking
of something awful, right?
I'm not.
That's it.
I'm really right.
You're so cute when you eat something.
I can see your cuteness
forever if we get married.
Just get married to a dog.
Why?
Did I take care of you so poorly?
But I'm almost everything to you.
Why don't you accept my love?
Please?
We have a brotherly relationship, don't we?
How can siblings get married?
♫ I forget that we don't love each other
even though you walk away from me ♫
♫ If it bothers you, I'm sorry
for still worrying about you ♫
♫ My heart only has you ♫
What's wrong with you?
Why?
Do you have appendicitis pain?
I'm just into heartbreaking songs.
What does it mean
that you're heartbroken?
You don't even have a lover.
Someone always break our hearts even
if we don't have a lover.
My someone is you.
What do you mean?
You're delirious.
Park...
When will your work be finished?
I'm not in a hurry.
I just keep working on it.
You draw once and sing for 5 minutes?
Will it be finished in this life?
It's my business.
Get out of here.
I can't concentrate.
Hey, how are you?
Would you like some oranges?
Huh?
I don't eat...
Park.
You still miss Palm, don't you?
Why should I miss someone
who already has a boyfriend?
She's married.
But the other girlfriend was your ex.
Sometimes I feel like
you still can't forget Palm.
You just imagining it.
Isn't it true?
This is proof.
Romeo in this jar.
What does it have
to do with my son?
Wasn't Romeo the first
goldfish Palm bought you?
I bought it myself.
How is it possible?
You've said before that...
Mom didn't allow me to
raise him back then.
Our house is a restaurant.
Animals can't be raised there.
So I said someone else bought it for me
so she wouldn't complain to me.
My mom always loved others more than me.
I've misunderstood you for years?
Yes.
You buy a new goldfish and give it an old name,
does it mean that you really can't accept it's death?
I've already told you.
What about when you met Palm that day
and you called your name like
you did when you dated her?
I couldn't think of anything back then.
So I don't know how I should call myself.
I misunderstood you.
What do you mean?
I think you still love Palm.
I'm ♫ frightened. It disappeared into the air ♫
You're ridiculous.
Park.
Let's get married.
That's more absurd.
I love you so much
but you don't love me at all?
I'm going to bed now.
Park!
Huh?
Can't you tell me that you
love me before going to bed?
Tell me you love me first, please?
Ouch!
Just hurry up and finish it and go to bed.
Don't go to bed late.
Yes, yes, yes. I know.
Who wants to be
siblings with you?
I don't give up easily.
Keep an eye out, Park.
Park!
Help me, Park!
Hey!
Wait...
What happened?
There are cockroaches in my room.
I think it's a big deal.
I'm scared.
It's as big as this.
Then it flew over my face.
Can I sleep with you tonight?
No!
I don't want to sleep with cockroaches.
Then
you must kill it for me.
You...
You grow up like a
buffalo, but you still...
There was only one cockroach.
If it's a whole family of
cockroaches, what should I do?
It will walk all over my room.
You haven't stopped yet?
I'm afraid of it.
Alright.
Just sleep with me.
Don't touch me.
I get it.
Stop holding me.
I'll sleep here.
Up to you.
Oh?
My pillow is so high.
Sleeping on high pillows is bad, right?
Is there something for me
to sleep on instead of a pillow?
My feet?
The height is just right.
Park...
Isn't it good enough that
I let you sleep with me?
Stop seducing me.
Hey.
Just sleep, you rotten thing.
I've killed it.
Just throw it in the trash.
Tonight, don't bother asking me
to sleep in my room again.
I don't understand
why you're afraid of it.
Why are you holding it?
Throw it!
Yeah.
Park, hurry up. I'm going to be late.
Have I ever made you late?
Yes!
Alright. Just a little more.
Park! Be careful, it's
stuck in your throat!
Here.
Park.
Wow...
Let's go.
Wow.
He really was in a hurry.
Don't come home late.
I know.
You're still arguing with me.
You don't even carry an umbrella.
It rains a lot these days.
Why don't you rush to work?
Otherwise you will be late.
Yeah.
I'll go now.
Bye bye.
Yeah.
I'm going to study now.
[Sam Khok Hospital]
Hello, Pimdao.
Hello, Park.
You're here, Park?
I may not have arrived yet.
I'm just asking you
as a courtesy.
Just kidding.
You haven't gone to school yet, Pimdao?
I'm waiting for my father to pick me up.
Let me see.
What are you drawing?
Tin.
What?
Please go buy snacks with me.
I'm busy.
Just ask your girlfriend.
No, you're the only one who doesn't mess up.
Donut had to waste time washing her hands.
Please go with me.
Okay.
Your change is 10 baht.
Thank you.
What do you want?
Auntie. 1 bottle of soda, please.
Cola?
Okay.
Here.
Thank you.
He's going to pay.
Hey.
Name!
Tin.
You're cute, Tin.
Huh?
We meet again.
It's really a coincidence.
I deliberately do it.
Do you have classes or...
Oh...
I'm doing an exhibition with my friends.
Do you need my help?
Uh... yes?
I have some free time.
My friends are free as well.
But what major do you study?
I study Thai art.
That's cool.
Would you like to
study this major?
No.
You are not good at it?
My brain can't take it.
You both dislike it
and aren't good at it?
Absolutely.
I don't even want to live
when I think about my next project.
I can help you.
Can I accept?
You are a final year student.
Do you have free time?
If it's you, I can give you some time...
a little.
Isn't it weird?
This.
I think it's more like a mini heart.
Uh.
Can I have your contact info?
Just in case.
Please?
Sure.
Thank you.
Where is the cut-out sheet?
It's in the storage room.
I haven't brought it yet.
I told you to bring it earlier,
why didn't you bring it?
I'll go get it.
Hey.
It's heavy. You can't carry it.
- I'll go get it myself.
- It's okay.
Let's go together.
Let's go.
What is it?
It looks like my ankle is sprained.
Name.
You take Donut to sit there and rest.
- Okay.
I'll go get it myself.
I'll help you.
Okay.
Compress it first.
At least it's still cool.
Thank you.
Remember it.
I will never let you get hurt.
Which one?
Hey!!
Are you okay, Tin?
I'm okay.
You're not hurt, are you?
Yes.
What happened to you?
There's a cockroach in there.
Are you afraid of cockroaches?
I hate it.
Just put more work in, it's done.
Hey.
The three of you can go back first.
Me and Donut are going to buy abrasive paper.
Bye bye.
I'll wash your shirt, Tin.
Hey. It's okay.
Take it off. I'll wash it myself.
What happened to you, Tin? Your body is all red.
What happened to you, Tin?
I'm just itchy.
How can you say you're okay?
Your neck is all red.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It will be better.
Are you really okay?
Yes.
I'm okay.
Let's get back.
I have to go now, Plearn.
Thanks for helping me today.
Let's get back.
Wait, Tin.
Do you want me to take you to your house?
It's okay.
My house is not far from here.
Then, get back home safely.
Hey, Plearn.
Why are you only asking Tin?
Hey, isn't your house next to the college?
You can walk there.
It looks like you're flirting with Tin.
Hey, hey, hey.
Or are you really going to flirt with Tin?
If I like him, I have to flirt with him.
If I don't do something,
will he love me?
Hey!!
Hey, hey.
Hey.
Go. Go.
Go.
Just go.
Are you shy?
Why is my heart racing?
Pao!
Oh? Hi.
Please say you
want to flirt with me.
Huh?
Just say it, I know it's not true.
Please say you want to flirt with me.
Are you rehearsing for a stage play?
Yeah.
It's a big event.
Get out of here.
Park will scold you if you keep playing nonsense.
Hey, Pao.
Just do your homework.
I don't have any.
If you don't have one, just go take a shower.
I know.
You didn't even help me.
Tin!
You've come here again.
Your mom came to see me.
She said she wanted me to
take care of Manow for 2-3 hours.
Oh.
It's hard for me and
you again, isn't it?
She said she was going to pick up Manow
after everything was done.
So I would like to ask you to take care of her first.
I have to rush back to the store.
Okay.
Manow, please stay with Tin first.
Bye.
Yeah.
Bye bye.
Level 2.
Level...
3.
Manow!
Mom has come to pick you up.
Let's go see your mom.
Yay!
Let's go.
I'll go now.
Please take care of her.
Okay.
Manow, say goodbye to Tin.
Bye, Tin.
Bye.
I'll go now.
Let's go!
Mom is waiting for you.
Let's go home.
Mom, have you ever thought
of taking me back like this?
Kana.
Kana!
Why are you so absent-minded?
Are you addicted to drugs again?
Are you crazy?
What are you thinking about?
I miss my girlfriend.
Huh?
When did you have a girlfriend?
I thought...
I'd get a girlfriend...
When?
You're ridiculous.
Oh.
Why haven't you gone home yet?
I forgot my house key.
You keep spending time flirting with Park,
so you're forgetful.
Just do less of it.
You're so hedonistic.
Kana, you...
You run after a man.
It's my happiness. So what?
Kana, I want some ice cream.
Just pick it up.
She wants to eat it, why would she tell me?
Kana, how much?
15 bath.
I'll give you your change later.
I see you eat it often.
Is it tasty?
Yes, have you never tried it?
Yes.
Aunt Mam won't allow
you to eat ice cream.
Because your actions are not cute.
Hey.
What right do you have
to say that I'm stubborn?
Get out!
Get out of here.
These kids...
Would you like some ice cream?
Where did Uncle Kai and Aunt Mam go?
My mother went to grandma's house.
My father might go to the casino.
They must have argued when they returned.
Late night. You can
keep an eye out for it.
Uncle Kai is a very kind person.
Everyone is kind to you.
Because I look pitiful?
Huh?
Because I don't have parents.
Because I was abandoned.
So everyone pities me?
What do you mean?
It's a waste of time to
pity a naughty kid like you.
Taking pity on people like
you, pitying dogs is better.
Just stay quiet.
Who said you were dumped?
Isn't your mother still sending you money?
Yeah.
Even though my mother is close by,
she hasn't come to see me.
Don't you want to go see your mother?
No.
Why?
If she wants to see me,
she will come to me herself.
That's it.
It's okay even if you're really dumped.
You still have us.
I mean,
Just having Park is
more than enough for you.
Having us is good because
there are many people.
No one is left behind
in the crispy pork gang.
You can say nice things too.
You keep bothering me.
I'm really sincere.
Your sincerity is the problem.
You can't be sincere without manners.
It's like you didn't grow up with manners.
So you don't know if it's necessary.
Words can hurt people.
Are you scolding me?
Of course.
You even let a kid like me teach you.
You just got home?
I've been home for a long time.
But I forgot my house key.
So I couldn't get in.
So I'm waiting for you here.
Oh.
This is my colleague,
I invited her to have dinner together.
Are you Tin, right?
Park talks about you a lot.
I thought you would be younger.
But you've grown up.
When did I say he was young?
No, when you talk about him, it's
like you talk about a 7-8 year old kid.
They have arrived.
Where is the crispy pork rice
that you brag about often?
What am I bragging about?
Just taste it. I'll let you
kick me if it isn't good.
Hey, I have to taste it.
He is...?
He is Tin.
Oh.
Is he the younger brother
you always talk about?
Yeah.
Is he really this old?
He has a cute face.
He's good-looking like his older brother.
I'm going to eat.
Will you go with us?
It's okay.
I'm not hungry right now.
You guys can eat together.
Okay.
Then we'll go first.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Hey, aren't you really coming with us?
It's okay.
Please enjoy it.
Okay, see you later.
Bye bye.
Enjoy it.
How is Park close to her?
Hey!
Are you shocked?
I'm sorry.
Because you never knocked on my door.
I've never knocked on it,
so I don't know if I have to knock on it.
Do you know what privacy is?
I only know emergency.
So why aren't you wearing clothes?
Or... do you think
something is bad for me?
You bastard.
I just came to borrow the battery charger.
Gosh...
Since you took off your shirt,
you can't make love with me first?
If you don't try to do something that makes
me want to kick you, will it kill you?
What happened to you?
I'm your boyfriend.
Tin.
You haven't stopped joking.
You're really...
I just feel itchy.
I think it's because of the dust.
I help my friend carry things.
Are you really okay?
Is it swollen?
You're just itchy, right?
Yeah.
Are your eyes swollen?
Let me see.
Huh?
Having trouble breathing?
Is your tongue and throat swollen?
Open your mouth.
Park!
I'm okay.
Did you have any symptoms before?
Is your breathing consistent?
Is your heart fluttering or pounding?
For now, it's like that.
Your heart flutters?
Yes.
I blush at you.
Tin.
Can you be serious for one minute?
I'm worried about you.
Don't joke about it.
I already told you that
nothing much happened to me.
It's not a big deal.
You think you're not a big deal to me?
What should I do if
something happens to you?
If I let you die,
your father will never forgive me.
Park.
I'm sorry.
I'll tell you everything after this.
Yeah.
You answer me just only 'yeah'?
How do you want me to answer?
You must apologize to me
that you scolded me too much.
I'm sorry.
I'll be more calm after this.
You haven't eaten anything yet, have you?
Do you want something to eat?
Can you take me to a restaurant?
I want to eat shrimp dumplings.
But you have to dress nicely first.
Here.
I bought it for you.
I see that you are stressed lately.
Just in case it helps you.
Thank you.
How is it?
It's good.
Can you see?
I told you, alcohol can heal anything.
I think it's not because of the alcohol.
Then, why?
Hey.
Are you drunk?
I'm not drunk.
I think drinking makes me braver.
Don't do it again if you don't have feelings for me.
I'll order shrimp dumplings.
Okay.
A big one.
You want dumplings, right?
Shrimp dumplings!
2 plates of shrimp dumplings, please.
Okay, please wait for a moment.
Park!
Huh?
Can I eat meatballs too?
Up to you.
Here.
What do you want?
You can pick it up and put it on the tray.
This one.
Oh.
Oh, it's raining.
Come in here.
This one.
Please spread it, I will help you.
Come in, you're going to get wet.
It's okay, I'll unfold it myself.
I'll help you.
Come in, you're going to get wet.
Look at you, you're all wet.
It's okay. It's just a little bit.
Wait until the rain stops and then you can go.
But my brother is waiting across here.
I must hurry back.
Thank you.
Can you go there?
Slowly cross the road, be careful it's slippery.
Park, look at this!
I got free meatballs.
I help her spread the tarp.
She was very kind.
Yeah.
You did well.
Here.
You're wet like a drowned puppy.
What do you mean, puppy?
Get it!
Tin!
It's wet!
Just eat your meatballs.
How does eating meatballs help?
It can help you from being hungry.
I told you I'm cold.
What do you want me to do?
Take off your jacket and put it on me.
Like the protagonist
of a series.
Cool scene.
How can I take it off?
I'm not wearing anything underneath.
Why don't you wear an undershirt?
I just grabbed what was in front of me.
Who knows?
I think we were just out for a moment.
That's just like you.
Why are you smiling?
What series have you watched?
Huh?
Every series does that.
You don't know anything.
If it were me, I wouldn't do that.
You've never done anything like this anyway.
You've never been romantic.
If it were me, I would do this.