(Tin Tem Jai)
(Episode 8)
Oh.
I overheard Aunt Toy talking to my mother
that she was going to live with her daughter.
She takes care of
her grandchildren.
She would probably
sell this house.
What are you looking at?
You want to buy it?
How do I have money?
I think you want to
come back to your house.
I don't want to.
I'm happy to be with Park.
Why would I move there, right?
If you move anywhere,
I will surely cry.
What's wrong with you?
What?
Or am I missing something?
You were at the
temple the day before.
They have already
agreed to live together.
Aren't they living together normally?
I mean living
together as a couple.
Park!
Why did you choose a
puppy to be your lover?
Kana!
He's not just a puppy,
but a teacup dog!
Tin.
Kana! Get off of me!
Ahem!
You guys have your sweetheart.
I am lonely.
Don't leave me.
Walk slowly.
Let's go.
Uncle Tor.
I want crispy pork basil.
Okay.
I want it too.
Okay. Two dishes.
Plus me too.
Three dishes. Okay.
Hold on.
Why did you order crispy pork
and order crispy pork again?
It's not the same, Pao. Actually,
you can eat at my restaurant, right?
- There's no basil there.
- It's not the same, Pao.
Hey.
You're Kana.
I haven't seen you for
a long time. I miss you.
How are you?
You guys have been
in jail for a long time.
Hey, you know my deal.
Would you like us to
talk outside?
Let's talk. I miss you. I
haven't seen you for a long time.
Let's go.
Hey, I see that you're stressed.
Would you like some cigarettes?
It's okay.
Give it to him.
Try it.
I've quit smoking.
What are you afraid of?
It's okay. Just one cigarette.
Just one cigarette, what will happen?
Alright.
Take it.
That's it.
What did you talk with them about?
Nothing.
Just small things.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
So why did you smoke just now?
Just half a cigarette.
You broke our promise.
Why are you mad at me?
Is it a little thing?
Breaking a promise is wrong.
Ka...
You talk too much!
Kana.
It's salty.
It's the saliva of a mad dog.
You are the one who teased me first.
Go sit at another table.
I stink of cigarettes.
Hey!
I'm not going!
Kana!
Take your seat.
Go!
Park...
Kana teased me.
Right here.
Can you blow it for me?
Abracadabra!
You're better now.
Am I the only one who isn't
used to seeing Park do this?
Pink, I want to borrow your paint.
I'm exhausted.
Do you want to get
bubble tea with me?
Shall we go?
Tin.
Huh?
Would you like to drink bubble tea with me?
Sure.
Let's go.
Give me a moment.
I'm very hungry.
Hot weather makes me sleepy.
I want to drink coffee.
Let's go.
What should I order today?
I would like a cup of sweet jasmine tea.
You want to amputate your leg?
I would like a cup of less sweet bubble tea,
and a cup of less sweet.
You ordered two drinks?
Who did you order it for?
Hey. Who did you order it for?
Yes. Who did you order it for?
I ordered it for Park.
What about us?
Just order it.
I was disappointed with him.
There, there.
You must treat us first.
Treat us to one drink.
I'd like two drinks.
Two drinks.
Well, I'm going to
ask Park for money.
Park!
I'm shocked!
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Why did you come back late today?
I was doing my homework.
I already told you.
Can you come home early after this?
Why?
I love when I come home and
someone opens the door waiting for me.
The gate is very heavy, you know?
I don't have the strength to open it today.
Gosh... Earlier, I thought you missed me.
I miss you too.
I waited a long time for you, you know?
I’m screwed!
Huh?
I forgot the watercolor bag.
I don't know where it is.
Calm down.
Just remind yourself of
where you went today.
Plearn Ta.
Just answer it.
Okay.
I will answer it.
Yes.
Heyy.
Where did you find it?
Thank you so much.
Plearn Ta found it at the bubble tea shop.
What's next?
Does it make you that happy?
Huh?
It's my watercolor bag.
How could it not make me happy?
What happened to your face?
Why are you frowning?
Nothing.
This is your watercolor bag.
Thank you, Plearn.
Why were you standing there just now?
Nothing.
You scared Plearn.
Why is he afraid of me?
I didn't even do anything to him.
I'm jealous of you.
Huh?
What did you just say?
You always say you don't like it
when I say I'm not jealous of you.
I'm very jealous of you just now.
You're doing too much.
I'm sulking.
Hey.
Have you seen Plearn Ta lately?
No.
Now he's disappeared.
We haven't seen him since Tin had
his allergic reaction to almond milk.
Tin.
What is my email password?
Gosh...
You can't remember it again?
How do I know your email password?
Huh?
I never told you?
I can't remember it.
It suddenly disappeared from my memory.
Park!
Huh?
Do you have amnesia?
Watch yourself.
You tend to be absent-minded.
So I asked the experts.
Who?
Google.
Your symptoms are similar to it.
You are inactive, passive and
lack interest in your surroundings.
I think you must have dementia.
Hey.
I'm just in power saving mode.
But I'm worried about you.
You tend to be absent-minded.
I'm not absent-minded.
I just think about random things.
What do you think in your head?
It's you.
You are always knocking around in my head.
I can't express it.
So I have to manage myself like this.
Anyway, do you remember my password?
Let me see.
I'll try it.
It's wrong.
I'll try again.
Okay.
Hey.
It's wrong again.
Get up.
I'll check it.
Get up right now.
It's wrong again.
I think you need to reset your password.
Wait a moment.
What?
Hey!
What password did you enter?
It's your birthday.
My birthday?
Yeah.
Why is it my birthday?
Park...
It's easy to remember.
Is my birthday easy to remember?
Yeah.
Because it's important.
An important person?
What's wrong with you?
Am I very important to you?
You're really...
Just go. I'll keep working.
Park.
Bie sent a message in the group chat.
My phone is upstairs.
Can I use your phone to answer her?
Sure.
Park.
Huh?
Bie invites us to dinner.
Yeah.
Okay.
[I want to borrow money from you, sister]
[How much?]
[Ten thousand baht]
[Why is it so much this time?]
[I have to pay Tin's tuition fee next month]
[Okay]
[Aunt Boot hasn't transferred money for about a year]
[Are you going to take care of him like this?]
[Yes] [Can you do it?] [I can
borrow your money if I can't take it]
[Just tell me. I'll help you]
[Okay]
[But you didn't tell Tin anything?
He would get angry if he found out later]
You haven't transferred money to me
for about a year.
Why didn't you tell me?
How can you do this?
You're causing Park trouble.
You can't burden Park like this.
The reason Park took care of me
was because he felt guilty about my dad.
But it's too much.
It's not Park's duty.
It's because I think you manage my money.
I didn't think it's causing
Park trouble like this.
I believed you would come back to me.
But I really forgot that you threw me
to someone else in the first place.
Uh.
What will they eat?
Hot pot.
I heard Bie wanted to eat it.
But you don't really like hot pot, do you?
I don't dislike it.
I just eat it to get my money's worth.
You don't have to eat
just to get your money's worth.
Just relish it.
But I don't want it to
not be worth the money.
Just relish it.
I'll pay for it.
Hello, Teacher Pao.
Hello.
Hey, why are you in such a hurry?
My house is close to here.
Yes. It only takes 3 steps to my home.
Do you want us to go home because
you want to play with our toys?
You are an adult. Just
play something with adults.
Adults can't play it?
Huh?
Just go back to your homes.
Yeah.
Let's go.
My sky is orange today, Tin.
Pao.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Why are you absent-minded?
I'm just sleepy.
I had to take my father to the
hospital early in the morning.
I had to queue all day.
After taking my father to the hospital,
I had to finish my work at school.
You're sleepy,
so why don't you go home and sleep?
I'm back.
But I don't want to go into the house.
Why don't you want to go into the house?
I could only hear my mother
arguing with Pai when I was there.
I don't want to listen to it.
So I went out.
Aunt Tim is angry with Pai again?
They argue every day, just calling each other.
Pao, are you tired?
Are you tired?
No one has ever asked me that.
You're very tired, aren't you, Pao?
Yes.
You can vent to me
if you have something to vent about.
I wont tell it to anyone.
I promise.
Do you like listening
to boring stories?
Not really.
But if it eases the weight in your heart,
I'll listen.
You're a really good boy.
It's because Park took care of me
until I grew up.
I am a very good child
in my family's eyes.
But at work, I'm just an ordinary person.
Sometimes I'm stupid.
Sometimes I make mistakes.
My job is boring.
Especially society.
I was oppressed by the senior system.
I had to bow to them like a dog.
I had to open my
arms to every task.
I have to accept every task they
throw to me because I was younger.
I want to quit every day.
When someone says they want their children
or grandchildren to work like me.
Why don't they take me as a role model?
I f*cking want to throw up when I hear it.
I'm really disgusted.
I pity myself.
I don't understand it at all.
Sorry.
I vented a lot.
It's okay.
What job would you like to do
if you weren't a teacher?
I don't want to do anything.
I just want to sleep at home.
Play games all day.
It's really true!
I am the master of the
legendary steamed bun king game.
Really?
Of course.
Pao.
Huh?
It looks like it's going to rain.
I think so.
Shall we go back?
Well, let's go back.
Hurry up!
Tin.
How are you?
I have a headache.
Please get up and
take your medicine first.
Come on.
Why are you suddenly sick?
Watch your head.
I have to go now.
Bie.
Please take care of him.
You don't need to
worry. I can help you.
Bie.
I'm sorry to trouble you.
It's okay, Tin.
It's a small matter.
I can do it.
I'm right here.
If you need help, you can always call me.
Park.
Okay.
Umm.
Sure.
Okay.
I'll wipe for him.
Park.
Tin's fever has not decreased.
I just wiped for him an hour ago.
I hurried back without changing my shirt.
I'm going to take a shower first.
Thank you, Bie.
It's okay.
Please take care of Tin.
Park.
Huh?
How are you?
Slow down.
You didn't go to work today?
I'm on leave today.
Is it because of me?
Do you have to take a day off
because of me again?
I'm sorry.
I am really your burden.
I made you tired,
taking care of me like this.
You talk too much.
It's because of me...
Just stay still.
Your temperature is quite high.
Come on.
Eat something first.
So that you can take medicine.
I want to throw up.
Hey, Tin!
How are you?
I'm dizzy because of you.
Are you all here?
Park.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Why do you have to apologize to Park?
Park is getting what he deserves.
When Park got drunk like a dog,
only you wiped Park's vomit.
Aren't you used to growing up
with Park's vomit?
Who do you trouble when you're drunk?
Did you know?
Yeah.
- Get out, Kana.
- Huh?
Get up!
Hey, I'm comfortable right now.
Get up! So that Tin can sleep.
Well, here.
We can share space here.
Come on, dude.
Just lean there.
Alright.
I can get up.
What?
Just sleep properly.
Do you bite your nails?
No...
What is up with you?
What happened?
I can't know if you don't tell me.
Park.
Do you remember Pu At?
What crab stick?
You mean fried crab sticks?
Not that.
I mean Pu At,
the dog that we used to raise.
Yeah.
We couldn't raise it,
so we had to let it go.
Park.
If I give you trouble,
you must let me go like Pu At.
What are you saying?
I know all about my mom.
I'm sorry.
I am not angry with you.
But I just feel very sorry for you.
I got you in trouble.
You always have to take care of me.
Until now, you have had to find a day off
to take care of me.
I caused you trouble.
I caused even Patsorn problems.
She had to transfer her money to take care of me.
I didn't want to bother your family like this.
Also, I'm stubborn with you.
I don't humble myself, right?
When my mom asks you to take care of me,
you can't deny it right?
Because it's about my dad.
But actually,
you don't have to bear it.
If I knew the truth,
I wouldn't be here to burden you.
I don't know what you are talking about.
But I don't want to listen to it.
Park.
Stop talking about it.
If one day Park let you go,
where will you go?
I used to have the same thoughts as you.
I don't want to be in the house
to be a burden on my father.
But I feel empty when I'm really going.
I have no other place to go.
But if asked if I really wanted to go,
I didn't want to go anywhere.
Even now,
I think I don't want to go anywhere.
Now I know who really loves me.
Although we are not related by blood,
we love each other like family.
You may think that you are not part of Park.
But you are Park's whole world.
Please look at it from Park's point of view.
If he doesn't have you, how will he live?
He will never let you go anywhere.
But Park has problems because of me.
He was willing to go to great lengths
to save his whole world.
All you can do now is be
by his side like he wants.
Just repay him when the time is right.
Nobody called love a burden.
Don't worry, Tin.
Park!
You're back?
Yes.
I miss you so much.
I miss you too.
Ouch!
Let me go.
I haven't even taken a shower yet.
I might be dirtier than the germs on you.
Because I haven't showered either.
Hey.
Ewww!!
You really are rotten, aren't you?
I'm only at home.
But I'm saving you water bills.
Stop it.
Go get the food that's
on the motorcycle.
Let's go.
Ouch!
What happened to your arm?
Nothing.
Ouch!
You said nothing, didn't you?
Just a little bit.
Just sit first.
I'll check it.
Oh.
Please help me take the bag off.
Be careful.
What happened to you?
There was a drunken
rampage at the hospital.
So I help him.
And I got pushed down.
My wrist sprained.
Wow.
He's terrible.
Where do you hurt?
Huh?
It's okay.
It can heal if the wrist is not used
for about two days.
I also took a long weekend break.
Hmm? Really?
Yeah.
Then you can rest well, right?
What?
You don't want to go anywhere, do you?
Like going on a trip.
I rarely get long holidays.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I want to be with you.
You really don't want to travel?
You really don't want to go, do you?
I don't want to go anywhere anymore.
Even if you want to go, I won't let you go.
Because if you leave me,
what is left of my life?
Do you want me to apply medicine for you?
It's okay.
Then I'll blow it for you.
Abracadabra!
That's enough.
It stinks.
I've brushed my teeth.
Babe.
Please unpack the snacks for me.
Which ones?
This one?
Yeah.
Is it tasty?
Yes.
But...
I want to drink orange juice
like you did that day.
Can you do it for me?
Babe.
I want to drink orange juice, not orange.
I know.
Just a moment.
It stuck in my throat.
Calm down.
Here, just eat it first.
I'll make you orange juice after this.
Yeah.
Yes, sir.
Please be quick.
Yeah.
Tin, is it done?
I'm here, Park.
Here.
Please feed it to me, babe.
My hand hurts.
Come on.
I will feed you.
Drink it slowly.
It's as delicious as ever.
Babe.
Mama!
Hello.
Umm.
I know.
Just go to bed.
Don't worry about it.
Umm.
Park.
Huh?
I want to know the reason why Uncle Tong
and Aunt Tim didn't let Pai come back home.
They probably had their reasons.
Adults are difficult to understand.
But you are an adult too.
You don't understand it?
I'm not as old as them.
That's right.
I forgot you were in your 20s.
But I see you as being
just like everyone's parents.
I mean you're old like a dad.
You little bastard.
Why do you like old dads like me?
I just like you already.
You want an old boyfriend?
Eat it.
I will keep watching TV.