=Lucky's First Love=
=Episode 6=
Xiaoxi.
What's wrong?
He usually doesn't sleep at this time of day.
And he has a fever.
I'll get my mom here.
39°C.
Nothing wrong with the wounds.
Post-operative fever is very common.
Don't be too nervous.
We'll check
if a bacterial infection has happened.
I'll prescribe him some medicine
in time if necessary.
Observe carefully tonight.
You've stayed here for two nights.
You need to have a good rest.
Let me take care of him tonight.
No.
Let me do it.
Mr. Chu, it's none of your business.
You can leave.
Hello? This is Amy
from Administration Dept. of TIG.
It's me.
Mr. Xia, I was about to call you.
I've emailed you the materials
for the meeting at 2:00 p.m. this afternoon.
You haven't shown up by now.
Shall I postpone it a little?
Cancel it.
As for the meeting with operators,
use videoconferencing.
Okay. Got it.
Oh. Take my computer
to Chaoxin Hospital.
Okay. Got it.
What's up? I'm in a hurry.
Take it.
What's up?
Period stains.
No wonder I have a stomachache.
My dress is stained?
Take the computer to Mr. Xia.
He's at Chaoxin Hospital. Hurry up.
Chaoxin Hospital.
(Are you alright?
I'll wait for your reply)
His condition is not bad.
He's getting better after the operation.
(Xing Yun)
Why didn't Xia Ke answer the phone?
Is Xiaoxi hospitalized here?
But I think Shen Qing would take him
to go to a private hospital.
So, why is Mr. Xia here?
Has he really got a head injury?
If it's true, I'll get into big trouble.
Which Dept. should we go to treat head injuries?
Dept. of Brain. On the second floor.
Come on.
(Five missed calls from Xing Yun
One missed call from Amy)
Mr. Xia, I have an emergency.
I've asked Xing Yun to take the computer to you.
She'll call you when she's there.
Sorry for any inconvenience.
Chu Nan, I hope you think carefully
before you say anything.
I won't let you hurt my sister
or Xing Yun.
Sorry. I didn't watch where I was going.
My bad.
Hello? Mr. Xia.
Where are you?
Wait for me at the Registration Office
on the first floor.
Okay. Hold on.
Mr. Xia.
Come on. Did I really guess right?
Are you here to treat a head injury?
No.
That'd be great.
So, why are you here?
Is Xiaoxi hospitalized here?
Yeah.
I have a meeting this afternoon.
I'm going back.
Tell Xiaoxi
I'll come see him some other day.
Hold on.
I'll send you home.
Xia Ke.
You don't need to see me off.
I'll take a taxi.
What's up?
Amy.
Where?
I mistook someone else for her.
Don't move. There is something on your head.
I just washed my…
Don't move.
…my hair this morning.
I'm telling you.
There is a traffic jam at the east gate.
It's better to go to the south gate.
Hello?
Can you wait for me at the south gate?
That's right.
Can you stop pushing me? Mr. Xia.
Hurry up. There is no time.
38°C.
The fever is going down finally.
Don't worry.
Ms. Lan usually deals with
difficult miscellaneous diseases.
Relax. Xiaoxi will be alright.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Isn't it the east gate?
Why are we here?
We usually go to the ring road
from the east gate.
It's the best route.
Isn't there a traffic jam here?
No. There isn't at this time of day.
Wait! Stop the car, please.
Sir, I'm sorry. I have to get off,
but I'll pay, anyway.
(Are you alright?
I'll wait for your reply)
Chu Nan!
It's really you.
Why are you here?
You said something happened to your family.
Is anyone hospitalized?
Yeah. My brother is sick. I just went to see him.
Is he alright?
Yes. Something is wrong with his heart,
but it's okay now.
Why are you here?
I just took something to Mr. Xia.
Shen Qing's son is also here.
Really?
Don't you know that?
Mr. Xia said
you saw Shen Qing get off here that evening.
Too many things have happened these days.
I can't remember.
Are you okay?
You look pale.
I'm okay.
Sorry. I didn't have time to send you a message.
Never mind. There is nothing important.
Well.
Just go home and have a good rest.
I'm going back to the office.
Bye.
Xing Yun.
Are you available tonight?
Let's have dinner together.
Do you like to have some wine?
I'm good.
This one.
Thank you.
Okay.
Chu Nan! It's a small world.
Who is she?
My girlfriend.
You know,
you have to help Chu Nan
get out of that bad relationship.
What are you talking about?
He's drunk. Sorry.
You're drunk. Let's go.
See you.
Sorry.
What does he mean by a bad relationship?
Forget about it.
He's joking.
Why is dating more exhausting than working?
Miss, you forgot your stuff.
Thank you.
Mr. Xia, the driver is waiting for you downstairs.
You'll give a speech at 2:50 p.m.
You'll give another speech
before the dinner party starts.
As a special guest,
you can take one more person with you.
Who will you…
Xing Yun, come with me.
You're lucky.
This is an annual forum for game developers.
It's a rare chance. Go!
The so-called industry summit?
Exactly.
Hurry up. Follow Mr. Xia.
I'll send the agenda to you later.
Okay!
(Mr. Xia's schedule)
(Special guest: Mr. Fuyu
The writer of many good-selling cartoons)
Mr. Xia, will we join the dinner party tonight?
Yeah. I'll make a speech.
What's up? Are you hungry?
No. I'm just checking.
Oh. Mr. Xia,
the agenda shows
that a lot of industry talents
will join the parallel sessions.
Parallel sessions?
I know you'll give a speech at the main venue.
I'm asking for your permission.
Can I go to the parallel sessions?
I'll be back soon.
I just want to gather some information.
I hope I can do a good job on the project.
Go ahead.
Thank you, Mr. Xia!
Let's welcome Mr. Xia from TIG.
He'll talk about the latest industry trends.
Hi, everyone.
As the bellwether
of cultural and creative industries,
video games have been a pioneer
as for the integration of pan-entertainment sector.
The data analysis shows
60% of gamers are women.
How do you like it?
our VR games are not bad, right?
Actually, I don't think
VR technology is suitable
for shooting games at present.
It makes me very dizzy.
Miss, you don't understand.
VR will become mainstream in the future.
All technical problems will be solved.
You said it makes you feel dizzy.
Some extraordinary people in the industry
will solve the problem sooner or later.
What's most important
is to seize the initiative.
It'll be popularized
when omnidirectional treadmills get cheaper.
VR treadmills are a little like the Kinect.
It takes up too much space.
I remember it broke a Guinness world record
for the most sold electronic device in 2009.
But five years later,
it was discontinued
because of its high requirement for space
and weird operation.
You're a girl. You know nothing about it.
Which company do you work for?
I'm from TIG.
Don't you focus on mobile games?
Stop making comments here.
Go away.
Miss.
I think you know a lot about gaming devices.
I'm flattered. I just love cartoons.
I learned all that from my boss.
I'm Jeremy Yang from Huize. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. I'm Xing Yun.
You said you work for TIG.
What do you do?
I used to be an original animation artist.
Now I'm a planner of Instance Zones.
TIG is the leader of the industry.
Oh. Are you available now?
Can we talk over coffee?
I'm afraid not. Thanks.
I've drunk three cups.
How about juice?
I'm good. Thank you.
Miss Xing.
You have a deep understanding
about the gaming industry.
And your job is meaningful.
You must be a valuable asset to the company.
I don't have a business card.
Just come to me if you want to get a new job.
Thank you, but I'm good.
We can also have business exchange.
It's okay.
Miss Xing.
Mr. Xia, what a coincidence!
I was going to the lounge to see you.
I want to thank you for joining the forum.
Thank you.
You gave a wonderful speech just now.
I just recited my speech draft.
The other two
did a better job.
Mr. Xia, you're humorous.
We just wanted to help them
avoid awkward silence.
I don't think it's necessary for me
to give a speech tonight.
No. Mr. Xia.
Just do it as a mere formality. Okay?
It won't take you much time.
If you don't do it,
I'll be scolded by my boss.
Tell them I don't feel well.
Mr. Xia.
Hold on. Mr. Xia.
We can have a talk about it.
All things have been arranged.
Mr. Xia.
I'm very glad to meet you here
at the game industry forum.
Each of you present here
must be among the best of the industry.
Nowadays, the gaming industry keeps thriving,
which takes an extraordinary opportunity
to us and even the whole pan-entertainment sector.
You work for TIG?
I just heard the speech given by your boss
at the main venue.
He's so hot.
Do you work with him?
You're so lucky.
You'll get tired of something if you're exposed
to it too often, no matter how beautiful it is.
How could it happen?
He's cold-blooded and calculating.
Of course, he just looks cold-blooded.
Actually, he's very warm-hearted.
He treats us like his family.
That's the information you've gathered here?
Mr. Xia, I've drunk too much coffee.
I can't help talking nonsense.
Mr. Xia, can I have your autograph?
It can't help improve
the sales of your games.
Mr. Xia, are you going to get prepared
for the dinner party?
I want to join one more parallel session.
You don't need to wait for me.
It's cancelled. We're going back to the office.
What? Why?
Do you mean Mr. Fuyu, the author of "Haoda Team",
won't give a speech tonight?
I thought I'd have a chance to see him
in person.
I drank three cups of coffee
just to keep myself energetic
and memorize each word he says.
Why is it cancelled?
That's what makes you depressed?
Shen Qing.
Why are you back?
Xiaoxi can't stay in hospital alone, right?
It's okay.
The weather has been awful recently.
It's not easy to take a taxi.
Delivery has become more difficult, right?
It's not so bad.
Don't worry. Just take good care of your son.
Don't lie to me.
Even deliverymen won't work on such bad days.
You'll have to do it yourselves.
And you don't have a car.
Well.
I'll also do delivery these days.
You don't need to do that.
Mr. Chu has been helping us.
What?
Shen Qing, I know you've broken up.
I planned to say no at the very beginning,
but we've got so many orders.
As you know,
people usually order cakes to celebrate birthdays
or anniversaries.
If it's delivered late,
we'll not only be scolded by clients
but also receive complaints on the internet.
So…
Alright. It's not your fault.
Go. Let's work.
Hello? Amy.
Tell the sponsor I'm much better.
I'll give the speech tonight.
Oh. Get one more seat
at the top table.
Thank you again
for your support for "Infinite Unknown Love".
Next, let's welcome Mr. Fuyu.
Hi, everyone. I'm Jishin Fuyu.
It's a great honor to be here with you.
Many of my works
have been adapted to video games
and they are loved by you.
It makes me very happy.
Mr. Fuyu!
I saw the legendary Jishin Fuyu.
And he's shaking hands with me.
He proves himself to be a great cartoonist.
I can feel the strength of his hand.
I'm so happy!
Mr. Xia.
Shouldn't you be at the dinner party?
I asked you to wait for me at the top table.
Why are you here?
I don't like that kind of occasion.
Do you remember what happened last time?
A group of strangers sit together.
Instead of taking the dishes I like,
I have to look at them passing by.
It's kind of torture.
I prefer to stay here and make something do.
Go back.
Now that it's more comfortable to stay here,
why do you ask me to go back?
Thank you.
I'll have the same.
Okay. Thank you.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Mr. Xia, I think
you're radiant tonight.
It's like every single hair is shining.
I've heard animals' eyes can
absorb different light sources
and reflect at night.
Do you think my eyes are particularly bright?
Idiot.
I'll enjoy my dinner.
Are you performing acrobatics?
I just shook hands with Mr. Fuyu.
I want to keep the lingering warmth longer.
I wiped my hand.
What are you doing?
You also shook hands with Mr. Fuyu, right?
Pass the lingering warmth to me.
Look at you!
Just for a second.
Aren't you Chu Nan's…
We met in the restaurant the other day.
Are you also here for the summit?
What a coincidence! It's you.
Don't worry. I won't tell Chu Nan about it.
We all want a little excitement occasionally.
I see.
You can also come to me if you're available.
Oh. You got me wrong.
He's my boss.
Right. Your boss.
You need to get well along with him, right?
Spend some time with me
when you're available. Okay?
What are you talking about?
Why can a person like you
join the summit?
Sorry? Can you repeat it?
I said, why can a person like you
join the summit?
You do not know who I am, right?
I'm the investor of the game.
No big deal.
Mr. Xia is the upstart of the gaming industry,
president of TIG.
So many people want to invest in our company.
You have to wait in a long queue to see him.
Your mind is so dirty.
How could Chu Nan have a friend like you?
My mind is dirty?
You were touching your boss' hand.
I did it to get the lingering warmth of Mr. Fuyu.
Chu Nan will understand.
Pervert!
Pervert?
I'm not. He's just a freak.
So, you went out for a date the other day,
but you told me you'd go to work overtime.
I just had dinner with him.
Then I went back to the office.
Do you really like Chu Nan so much?
His brother is sick.
I think he's been in low spirits recently.
His brother?
He said it's a heart disease.
His brother is also at Chaoxin Hospital.
I think it's serious.
He didn't say too much about it.
Oh. Mr. Xia.
If your brother is sick,
what can your girlfriend do
to make you feel better?
If it were my brother,
I'd ask my girlfriend to see him.
Mr. Xia, thank you very much.
You let me see Mr. Fuyu in person.
It's true that something good will happen
as long as you live positively.
I'm leaving.
Mr. Xia, bye.
Sorry. I came back too late.
It's okay. Xiaoxi is a good boy.
Do you know who took it here?
Nobody else but Chu Nan.
Alright. Eat!
It's late.
You couldn't get food
from the dining hall of the hospital.
The weather is terrible.
No parking is allowed downstairs.
I saw him wrap the porridge and dim sums
in his clothes.
Is it still hot?
He just left. I'm afraid he'll get caught in the rain.
You're stupid.
Why don't you take an umbrella on such a bad day?
You're off duty.
Are you here just to pick me up?
I don't think so.
You came here every day.
Did Xing Yun complain about it?
She's the daughter-in-law I want.
Don't let her down.
Mom.
Xiaoxi is a pitiful child.
Life is not easy for his mom.
If it were somebody else,
I might give her a hand
after knowing all about this.
But you're my son.
She's divorced and she has a kid.
You even haven't entered a relationship.
I won't let you marry her.
Okay.
Wait!
Sir, shouldn't it be a dining room?
It's No. 88, Shixing Avenue, right?
Yeah. That's right.
That's it.
Hi, Mr. Chu.
This way, please.
Chu Nan!
Aren't we going to have a meal?
Try them on before we go.
Try on wedding dresses?
It's said that
girls will want to get married
when they put on wedding gowns.
Actually, the shop belongs to one of my friends.
He asked me to take you here
and then give them some suggestions.
Don't feel pressured.
How could I feel no pressure?
Chu Nan has been acting weirdly
since we came back from the resort.
I'm telling you.
Man is most likely to think too much
when he's vulnerable.
He either wants to
change something of no importance
or change his own behaviors.
Actually, in the final analysis,
he wants to change the current situation.
Forget about it. Let's go back.
Wait. I'll try them on.
It's your friend's shop, right?
But I'll just try them on.
Okay.
Miss Xing.
These wedding gowns
are most suitable for you.
You can have a look.
I'll leave her to you.
So many styles.
Right. There are A-line and fishtail
as well as princess style wedding dresses.
Which one do you like?
This is a hand-tailored one with crystals.
It's expensive,
but you can rent it.
In this way,
you'll also have a perfect wedding.
I'll try this on.
It's suitable for you, too.
It's simple and elegant. I'll get it for you.
The dinner party is very important for us.
Trust me. I'll try my best.
I trust you.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Take care.
See you.
He took the ring in the drawer, right?
He didn't lie.
He said he'd go propose today
and he did.
She's beautiful in it, right?
It's like she's from a fairy tale.
Even I want to get married.
How do you like it?
How do you feel about wearing
a wedding gown for the first time?
I'm not used to it.
I feel like I'm a walking umbrella.
Xiaoxi, where is your mom?
My mom has gone to work.
Xia Ke, my car doesn't work.
Is it out of power?
Let me get a new battery.
Xiaoxi, is it your mom's?
It's vitamin.
My mom takes it every evening.
She takes several pills.
Xia Ke, come and pick me up.
8777.
Mr. Xia.
Chu Nan.
Hello? Chu Nan.
What on earth is on your mind?
You know what?
Shen Qing has to take many sleeping pills
to fall asleep.
You have to make a decision now.
If you choose Xing Yun,
then never show up in front of Shen Qing.
If you choose Shen Qing,
come to Sanhuang Hotel immediately!
Do it now!
Sorry.
I asked her a few questions.
Mr. Xia said
Shen Qing has to take many sleeping pills
to fall asleep.
She's drunk a lot at Sanhuang Hotel.
He asked you to make a decision.
Where is she?
Sanhuang Hotel.
Shen Qing.
I've drunk too much.
Xia Ke, I even mistook you for Chu Nan.
Why did you drink so much?
You even sound like him.
Did it go well with your proposal?
No.
Why not?
She's simple and naive.
Actually, I'm very happy
to see you be together.
But I like a woman with terrible character.
See? You finally tell the truth.
You think I have terrible character.
Why hasn't Xia Ke shown up?
He said he'd take care of me.
Mom. Please come and help her son.
Please!
Why are you here?
That's the end of
my first love.
Xing Yun, it's not your first love.
You knew it,
right?
Why didn't you tell me?
Calm down.
Calm down?
Right.
I'd understand if I stay calm.
You didn't want me to go on a blind date.
You didn't want me to go to Chu Nan's home.
He left ahead of time when we were at the resort.
He did it again when we were in the wedding shop.
You did all these
for the sake of your sister, right?
Xing Yun, I…
Congratulations, Mr. Xia.
You did it.
They're back together.
Thanks to you,
I'm standing here,
seeing the end of my relationship
on such a bad day.
I just don't want you to get hurt.
Are you worried about me?
What do you think I am?
Your pet or mascot?
You're just used to taking advantage of me.
You don't have the right to decide my life.
I can explain. Get on.
Let go of me!
Xing Yun, get on,
or you'll lose your monthly bonus.
I don't care.
I don't want the bonus for this month
and for the next month.
You know how much it costs
to repair the car, right?
Just deduct it from my salaries.
I don't want to see you again.
I think we are a good match.
I want to go further, can I?
Do you know each other or not?
No.
Mom, I won't marry Xing Yun.
What?
I'm here to tell you the truth.
I went on a blind date
just to be with Shen Qing.
You dislike her because she's divorced,
so I planned to marry Xing Yun and then divorce her.
Then I'll be divorced, too.
You're so mean.
You win.
Not too bad. It's alright.
Mr. Xia, as for the follow-up procedure,
I'll let He Yu take care of it.
It happens
you've known each other for years.
I believe the cooperation between Jiawo and TIG
will go smoothly.
Definitely.
Okay. I'll leave you alone.
He's bad at golf, but you even let him win.
You don't need to do that for me.
Or are you really not yourself today?
Where is your mascot?
Why is she not here?
You usually take her everywhere.
She didn't answer the phone. She's crossed in love.
Crossed in love?
You did make them break up.
For the sake of Shen Qing?
It has nothing to do with me.
Chu Nan, let's break up.
Xing Yun, I'm sorry.
Actually, I've never stopped criticizing myself
when I'm with you.
I'm very sorry
to get you hurt.
I'm telling you.
I think he's just your teammate
instead of a boyfriend.
Your task is to enter a relationship.
I suddenly remember someone told me
you're just my teammate
instead of a boyfriend.
Our task is to enter a relationship.
It seems he's right.
I don't know why,
but I feel much relieved
after I said we should break up.
Maybe we have misunderstood
the true meaning of "being in a relationship".
Maybe
I shouldn't call it a relationship.
I must go.