Yun Mo!
Yun Mo, are you okay?
- Gege! -that is great!
Brother, you woke up!
We're all worried, it's been a month.
Could it be that when that day actually comes, I will be even more reluctant to part with you?
Yun Mo, there will always be a place for you here with me.
♪You thought I looked brave♪
Sir, we found Lu Sheng.
He ran-away.
Go find him!
Yes.
Lu Tian you...
Why are you doing this?
I created you and you treat me like this?
Now do you know she's my wife?
In your eyes, I'm just a pet you keep.
No, a dog.
You're just a dog, a stray dog.
you were a watchdog at my disposal!
gross!
What you did to the Foer family is worse than animals!
Where is Tianyou located?
Brother, please wait a little longer, God willing, he will come after finishing his business.
Where did he go?
he...