Let me go, you'll see what happens to you later!
Tian you!
God bless,
I have to do this alone.
Little bitch, are you here after all?
Did you come to kill me?
Fu'er, I don't want his dirty blood on your hands.
I have to do this alone,
otherwise I wouldn't be able to explain it to the dozens of family members in the palace and my parents.
Do you really want to kill me?
This shot is for what you did to Tianyou over the years.
This shot is for Yunwu.
I should have killed you and burned you and them to ashes!
This shot cost the lives of dozens of family members in the palace.
This shot...
is for my deceased parents!
Even if you kill me now, they won't survive.
♪After burning the fire of the world's future,♪
♪he stood alone in the unknown storm, unafraid of sin♪ ♪
Hope explodes in the dust of the universe♪
♪leaving my heart sink in the light of residual heat and ice, in the sky night♪
♪I fled in the ice mountain range and got stuck in the desert♪
It's all over.
♪Forget the world fragmented like quicksand, the most civilized spreads♪
♪I will lurk alone, infiltrating the limits of evil♪
♪I moved the brightest star in the sky and appeared in the sky, which was my last appearance♪
( Todo the drama ends, thanks for following)