Putter has a good family now.
He has everything.
He's happy.
He doesn't need you in his life.
Uncle Peem left?
From now on,
don't go near Uncle Peem again
Why?
Because...
I will be sad.
Can you do that for me?
Yes.
I can't be near Uncle Peem.
Plubpl a told me
our son has a great family now
He doesn't need me in his life
She said
I'm going to ruin his life.
What Plubpl a said is true though
Plubp la is married.
She married Kit.
If you are still pestering her
that's like...
you're hurting her again
But do I deserve to be hated on
deserve to be separated from my son?
Til this day, I still don't know who recorded us and leaked the clip.
Why am I the only one getting punished for it?
The world isn't fair to me!
Putter!
Are you hurt?
No, I'm just in shock
I'm sorry dear.
Sir.
What kind of driving was that?
We almost crashed.
If you are still messing with the man who has an owner,
next time won't be an almost.
What are you talking about?
Are you misunderstanding?
No.
Why did Uncle S aan choose not to work with my company?
I'm actually curious about something.
What is it?
Have you ever shown the contract of your offer
to anyone before?
Why?
V Group'soffer
looks exactly like yours.
But there was one point
where they offered a better condition.
So they won.
I don't know what is happening at your company
but my father made his decision already
He sends his apologies
and appreciation
for taking interest in our restaurant.
If you have no other questions,
I have to get back to work.
Pete.
What are you trying to do?
Do what?
You know what lim talking about
How would I know?
Why did our offer and Kit'soffer
look exactly alike?
Except for one point.
That made him beat us.
If you ire asking me, then who do I ask?
I just went to talk to him
just like you told me to.
If someone is at fault
it should be you
Pete!
Peem.
What are you doing here?
Is there a problem?
No Mom.
Peem just
came to ask about work.
But what do you need Mom?
Oh.
Your father wants to see you.
I don't know what it's about either.
What happened Pete?
How could you let a small steak restaurant like that fall in their hands?
What kind of negotiation did you do?
You can't blame this all on Pete
The offer that Pete submitted
was all Peem's idea
Well Peem?
My mistake.
You see?
Save that for later
Go discuss with Mr Mark about investing with us in a hotel in Rayong
Make sure it's a success.
I went to investigate already
The owner of the land that is the entrance to our land in Rayong,
owns a fruit orchard named Dec h
Then quickly go buy that piece of land.
So we can finally get this going
V Group has already started building their hotel
Tat is on his way to negotiate right now
Remember,
if you mess this up,
I'm going to demote you
Yes, right this way.
Okay.
-You!
Hey.
Don't tell me you're here to talk to the owner about this land?
I should be asking you that!
News travel fast.
I think Kit knows
that Peem's company want this plot of land.
Hey!
Listen to me.
You have to make Peem
not be able to buy the plot of land in Rayong.
You have to be the one to buy it
So your fathe r canseethat you're doing a better job than Peem
He ill appoint you a better position.
Is this all your plan?
I'll get going then.
Pete!
Gosh this son!
What is it?
Why are you here?
Finally you show up.
I've been waiting for so long
What business do you have with me?
Nothing much.
Just collecting the money for my clip that you leaked.
What?
You're odd.
That happened four years ago.
And you're collecting money from me?
Or should I goask from Mr, Peem?
I've been thinking.
Mr, Peem and his father don't know yet, do they.
that you leaked the clip?
If they found out.
what will happen?
How much do you want?
I should have thought of this four years ago
Gosh!
You guys again?!
I told you I'm not selling it.
Go back!
Go!
You haven't listened to my offer yet.
That's right.
My company is offering you way more benefits than his company
Hey.
You're going to play like this?
You want to fight,you gotta be quick!
Fine.
Mr. Dec h.
No.
No matter how good your offer is
I will not change my mind.
Go! Leave!
Don't invite them in next time.
Yes Boss
-Mr. Dec h! Excuse me!
-Wait!
Mr. Dec h!
Wait Mr. Dec h!
- You can't go in!
He told you to leave!
Please leave!
Go!
Leave!
Hey you.
Tell Kit to stop playing dirty like this
The reason why he wants this plot of land
because he wants to prevent Peem'scompany from signing a contract to build a hotel with Mr. Mark!
Have some morals
If business is all about morals
then why even have one?
Wow!
I guess you've been working with Kit way too much
to get that kind of bad habit
Hey.
Are you trying to pick a fight with me?!
Huh?
Who is that woman?
Why does she look familiar?
Welcome.
Our school focuses on having children do extracurricular activities
to enhance their learning skills as well!
How old is your grandchild?
My grandchild isn't born yet.
I'm just checking this place out in advance
That's great.
Parents nowadays are well-prepared for their unborn child.
My friend's child also goes to school here.
Really? That's wonderful.
Dad.
Can I use the restroom?
The restroom is over there.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Can you take me on a tour around the school?
Sure. This way sir
This is their playground
It's for them to...
-Run around and play.
-That's right.
There's different sports here they can play
-Over there, right?
Yes.
Teacher, can l use the restroom?
Play nice. I need to take your friend to the restroom first.
Go.
Are you Putter?
Yes.
-Putter!
-Your mom is here.
Mom is here.
How are you Putter?
Did you cry today?
No, Iwas a good kid.
He did cry a little earlier missing his mom
I guess he needs a little adjustment.
Yes.
Let's go home.
Thank you Teacher
See you tomorrow Putter.
-Bye.
Uncle Peem!
Putter.
Get in the car.
Don't pay attention to him.
Follow her.
10 What?!
Peem knows that Putter is --
Orn!
Sorry.
He knows already?
Yeah.
He planned everything.
He approached Putter
to get a sample of his DNA
So heinous!
So I wanted to talk to you.
If he were to...
file a paternity lawsuit.
I will file a lawsuit
He's my son.
It's not that simple Peem
Because it isn't simple
that's why I need your help.
Aren't you a lawyer?
You have to think this through.
Because if you file a lawsuit, it's going to be big news
Once it becomes big
we won't know if it will be good or bad for us in the end
I don't care
I just want Putter to call me "dad " just once.
Even if it turns out bad,
even if netizens attack me and call me names,
I don't care!
But you won't be the only one that will be affected by this.
Putter will also be affected
Especially when he grows up.
Try talking with him first.
He is Putter's father after all.
If I'm being honest
he has the rights to his son too.
You want me
to let him near my son?
Isn't that his job?
But Putter has Vik it already.
Plub.
Don't mix your personal matter with your son's.
You hating Peem is one thing.
But with your son, that's different.
Hey.
You're abusing your motherhood
to think on your son's behalf.
Do you realize that?
I'm full.
Okay.
Can le at my candy?
Sure.
Who gave you the candy? Your teacher?
Who gave it to you?
Your friend.
A un t Orn?
-You gave it to him?
-It wasn't me.
Who gave it to you?
Your friend who went to my school.
Who?
I don't know.
Hello.
Your son is adorable Plubpl a
Was it you that went to see Putter today?
I coincidentally found out
you and Peem are still seeing each other
So I'm here to warn you.
If you are still messing with my person,
then watch out for your person
What do you mean?
What are you going to do to my son?
Nothing right now.
But next time,
it might not be candy that I give for your son to eat
Remember that!
Putter!
Don't eat anything a stranger gives you, understood?!
Yes.
Putter.
Putter, I'm not scolding you.
You were loud.
I'm sorry.
The candy is...
dirty now.
Do you want to order food?
Something new to eat?
There's a lot of food here.
What do you want to eat?
Order something
-You choose.
-Plub.
Plub.
What did Usa say to you
that you yelled at your son like that?
If you are still messing with the man who has an owner,
next time won't be an almost.
Orn.
Can you go drop Putter off at home?
I have something I need to do.
Oh.
Putter.
Stay with A un t Orn.
Bye.
Where are you going?
Plub!
What is it Plub?
We need to talk.
Sure.
I'm on my way.
Plubpl a?
Why did she call?
I don't know.
I'm leaving.
Peem!
Must be something bad.
Plub
I'm happy that you wanted to see me.
What was that for?
The candy.
Your fiancee gave it to Putter at school.
She threatened me that
if I don't stop associating with you,
she will hurt my son.
What?
Are you satisfied now
that me and my son are being harassed because of you?
If anything happens to Putter,
I will kill all of you!
Peem.
You came to my house to see me
Must be special.
Sa.
You threatened Plubp la and her son?
Geez!
That's such a scary thing to say.
I just gave her a warning.
Since she's married and has a child with Kit,
she shouldn't be messing with my fiance
Sa.
Don't harass Plubp la and her son again.
Don't do this again!
Seeing you get angry like this
I think I'm on the right track.
Are you threatening me?
I can only threaten you.
But the serious one
is my dad.
Just so you know
Dad knows everything
He's not happy that you're still associating with Plubpl a!
If you won't marry me,
I can't guarantee
what Dad will do to Plub pla.
You are forcing me right now!
Yes!
I can do more
just so you'll marry me.
If you're really worried about Plubp la and her son'ssafety.
make a wise decision.
Don't worry.
I will j protect you and our son.
Don't protect me.
As long as you and your fiancee stay away from us!
Fine!
I'll marry you.
Peem is going to marry you?!
Yes Mom!
Peem said we will get married as soon as possible.
I'm so happy Mom
Me too.
I'll go tell your father
to find the earliest auspicious date
Yes Mom.
What is it Kit?
You crossed the line Sa!
You dare threatened my wife and son?!
It was only a warning.
Only because I felt considerate of you.
So I told Dad not to do anything violent.
Don't threaten me with your father.
I don't care how powerful he is!
But if you mess with my wife and son again
you and l are gonna have a problem.
I wouldn't have done it if your wife didn't mess with Peem first.
It's Peem
that keeps bothering Plubpl a.
Handle your person first.
Don't mess with my wife and son again.
Don't worry.
Peem and I are getting married soon.
After that,
I won't let Peem mess with anyone.
Good.
Rest assured.
About what?
I talked with Usa already.
She won't harass you and our son anymore
Really?
She gave in easily.
It's unbelievable.
I didn't want to believe it either.
But right now
Sa got what she wanted.
She won't mess with you anymore.
Got what?
She's getting married to Peem soon.
Right.
Good.
So they can stop messing with us.
Yes.
Most importantly.
once Peem marries Usa,
he will have more weaknesses for us to attack.
Right.
Rest assured.
Putter.
Do you want to go play football?
Yes.
Let's go.
-Come.
-Yay!
Let's go.
Do you want mom to come too?
Do you?
Yes.
Let's go.
Come on.
Higher!
Putter!
Where did it go?!
Putter has a good family now.
He has everything.
He doesn't need you in his life
If you want to hurt his feelings,
you go tell him then
That this man here, the person he loves,
the person he thought was his father
isn't his father
I will do my job as your father
from afar Putter.
Dad!
Yes?
Peem.
Why are you doing this?
I just came to see
to confirm whether what I did was worth it or not.
You and our son are happy
Seeing it makes it worth it
You'remarrying Usa
because you wanted to protect us
You want me to believe that?
You know?
You think l will believe
that you have good intentions for us?
I won't fall for your tricks again
Good
that you don't believe
Because even if you believed me.
it's pointless now.
I never thought
that you would believe me anyway.
You want to blame me
for that clip,
that your grandmother died because of me.
you can be mad and hate me all you want,
or get revenge on me,
I'm not going to make any more excuses.
I just want
you and our son to be happy, that's all.
Why are you doing this?
What's the point of saying all of this?!
Good luck Plubpl a
I hope that your family
is happy as you hoped
As for Putter,
don't worry.
I will not try to form a bond that will cause pain for him because of me.
I will not show my face here again
Sa.
I'm happy that you wanted to see me again
I just came to say goodbye to you
From now on,
we can't meet like this anymore.
Why?
I promised you already
I won't tell anyone about this.
Can you give me a chance?
I will show you
I am just as good as Peem
Pete.
Can you not be sweet like this?
This time
I can't give in to you
Usa.
I'm getting married to Peem.
I won't let you marry him.
Pete.
We talked about this.
Can you not act like a kid?
You're my wife.
How can you marry Peem?!
Don't use that word with me.
We only slept together a few times.
That's not considered being your wife.
Pete!
Enough!
If I can't call you wife
then what do you call this?
Friends with benefits.
Peem won't marry you.
I talked to him already
He said he won't marry you
Oh child.
You believe your brother just because he said that?
Let me tell you.
Peemandl had an agreement
that we will get married as soon as possible.
I hope you will understand me
and be happy for me.
You lied Peem!
You're going to marry Sa?
Yes.
Now you know,
please arrange a wedding for us
Wait.
No wonder
Pete is refusing to come home
He probably knows by now.
I thought you were adamant about not marrying her?
If I marry her,
won't that be a good thing for the company?
Why ask so many questions?
Hey!
I'm your father!
I'm not just the CEO
I asked because I'm worried!
Mr. Thaw ip
threatened you, didn't he?
If he threatened you,just tell me
Who can threaten Peem?
Pete.
No one can!
Pete!
Why do you look like this?
I thought you said you won't marry her?!
You liar!
Pete!
Crazy boy!
Hey!
What's gotten into you?!
What crazy dog possessed you to punch your brother like that?!
-This dog!
-Pete!
The one that is heartbroken
The one that,got his lover stolen from him
Pete!
Pull yourself together!
Listen to me!
I still stand by my word
that l don't love her.
I don't want to marry Usa.
But it's necessary.
You know that if that woman wants something, she will get it!
Why?! Why?!
I promise
I won't touch her.
It's okay son.
" An insider whispered that
finally the young businessman Peem
and Usa,daughter of a politician,
will be marrying soon
It will be a grand wedding.
This is true?
I am not going to get Plubp la and my son back.
I just want to be useful for them.
What are you talking about?
This is gonna be your life.
Don't you think it's too much?
I made my decision.
Stop talking about this.
I'm getting back to work
Gosh Peem.
want you to talk to Plub
to try to convince Peem to call off the wedding.
You want Plub
to convince your friend to call off the wedding?
How could you think like that?!
Because only Plub can stop him
I don't want my friend to suffer because he's marrying someone he doesn't love.
You think your friend is the only one suffering like that?
You're telling me
Plub and Kit don't love each'other?
No!
You just said it though
Let's just say
I can't help you
You're worried about your friend's feelings.
I'm also worried about my friend's feelings
You called me here
What's up?
You probably heard
that I'm marrying Sa.
You're giving me the honor by inviting me yourself?
Don't worry
It's my friend's wedding. Plub and I
will be attending
I don't care whether you go or not.
I just have a favor to ask
You're here to ask for a favor from me?
Tell me.
I will consider it.
I'm entrusting you
to look after Putter and Plubpl a.
They're my wife and son!
Of course I will take good care of them!
It's not your job
to be asking that favor!