You're the best decision
that I've ever made
I'm happy
that you chose me to be right here.
I'm so happy
to have you
and Putter
as my family.
Even though
it's
it's...
a fake family.
But I hope that one day
we'll be a reall one.
Right now I...
You don't have to give me an answer right now.
I understand.
When everything ends
you can give me an answer then.
In the meantime,
give me this chance for me to earn brownie points from you
Who...
wants to go to the mall with me tomorrow?
Me. I want to go buy a robot.
You want to buy a robot?
Should I buy it for you?
You have to come see me if you want it.
Quickly.
I'm counting to three.
One...
two...
Come.
Gosh! You ire starting to get heavy now
What did you want?
Robot.
Sure. I'll buy it for you.
Also,
I want you to go too
I'm going to...
introduce you to Mr. Mark
As...
the company's new marketing manager.
Marketing manager?
Yes.
I'm going to have you and Tong
start working at the company tomorrow
What about Putter?
Will he not bother you?
It's okay.
He won't.
Right?
What did you want?
Robot.
What kind of robot?
Subtitles by.oh sweet haven.com Timing by Cat Attack
Tat.
Are you sure Mr Mark will beat Kit's mall today?
Okay.
I'll handle the rest.
So many toys.
We're here Putter
Wow! I can play all of this?
You can play them but only the ones Aunt Ta en says yes to.
Understood?
Yes.
Don't be naughty.
Don't be mischievous
Don't go places alone, got it?
Yes.
Go!
IN A Go to Aunt Ta en
Come here
Stay with me dear.
We should get going
It's almost time to meet Mr Mark
Okay.
Mr, Mark.
Hello.
I'm Peem from PP World
Oh.
You're him.
What can I do for you?
I want to apologize for missing the appointment.
I really had an important matter to attend.
Right.
It's okay.
Hey.
That's Peem
Mr. Mark
What do we do?
You and Tong hide first, I'll handle it.
Wait Mr. Mark.
-l have a project pro --
Mr. Peem.
Please have some manners.
You're going to do it this way?
As if you've never done this before.
Mr. Mark.
I'm sorry.
But I made a deal with VGroup already
Thailand is one of the top tourist destinations in the world.
A world-famous hotel like Mark is opening a branch
I think
there shouldn't only be one branch
I have a new project proposal
I guarantee you will be impressed.
Mr, Mark.
It's time for our meeting.
I'll have my secretary contact you
This is your last chance
Thank you so much.
Let's go.
What...
What color do you want?
Are you having fun Putter?
Yes but I'm thirsty
Thirsty?
Let's go buy a drink over there.
Come.
No.
Oh you want to stay and play, You don't want to go.
Then wait here for me
Do not go anywhere.
I will go buy you a drink okay?
Yes.
. Okay.
Wait here. Don't,go anywhere.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Excuse me.
Can l have one of this?
Also...
one of this dessert.
Mom!
Thank you.
Putter!
Where are you Putter?!
Oh my god!
Where did you go?!
Putter!
Aunt Ta en.
Where's Putter?
Well.
I just went to buy a drink real quick.
When I got back, Putter was gone.
What?!
I don't know where he went.
Quickly go find him!
- Right now Auntie!
-Okay!
Oh my!
Putter!
Mom!
It's not Mom.
Where is Mom?
Tong.
Did you find him?
Did you?
Did you find him Aunt Ta en?
-No.
He's not over there either.
I think they should announce a missing kid.
The securities can help look for him too.
Go do it then.
Aunt Ta en, can you go look for him over there?
Sure.
I'll go this way.
Putter!
Where are you?
Mom!
Little kid!
You can't go down there
It's going up, not down.
You'll fall down.
I'm going to go see Mom.
Mom is down there.
Your mom is down there?
Yes.
What?
How can she let a kid be alone like this?
Brave One.
What is your name?
My name is Putter.
Your name is Putter?
Brave One.
I will take you to your mom then.
Okay.
Let's go.
Putter.
Where?
Where is your mom?
Mom was just here
Really?
It's okay.
I will help you look for her.
Okay.
Where is she?
Where is Mom? You want to ask the bear?
Where is Mom?
Thank you so much Mr, Mark.
It's a pleasure to be working with a talented person like you.
Likewise.
Please
Kit! Kit!
What is it Tong?
Putter is missing
What?!
Putter is missing?!
Plub and Aunt Ta en are looking for him right now.
Tell all securities to look for my son
Sure.
We should go look for him too.
Where is she?
Do you see your mom Putter?
No I don't.
Putter.
Should we go look for her over there?
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's go find your mom!
Plub!
Plub, did you find him?
Aunt Ta en.
Well?
Is your mom around here?
No.
What do we do?
In that case,
I will go tell the officials and have them
look for your mom, okay?
Okay.
What's your mom's name?
Her name is Plub --
Putter!
There you are!
Aunt Ta en!
Come with Grandmas on
Wait.
He's your grandson?
Yes.
Come on.
M r. Yot got married?
It's none of your business. Don't meddle!
Let's go son.
l've been looking everywhere for you
Mom!
Putter!
Aunt Ta en.
Where did you find him at?
The children's zone
He was with Mr. Peem
-Does he know that Put --
-No he doesn't.
I told him he was my grandson
Plub.
Yes?
want to talk to you
Can you watch Putter?
Sure.
Don't worry.
Let's go To ng.
I think
it's time that we face Peem
You mean...
I will introduce you and Putter
as my wife
and son.
Putter too?
-I think --
-Plub.
We can't hide Putter.
The more we try to hide him,some day
if Peem knows that he's your son,
he will get even more suspicious
What if Peem...
gets suspicious of Putter?
He can only suspect.
If you confirm to him that Putter is our son,
he can't do anything about it.
Geez, you're in a good mood.
Mr, Mark was willing to talk to you?
Yes but the reason I'm in a good mood
is not because of that
met Aunt Tae n's grandson today.
The kid was so adorable.
Aunt Tae n's grandson?
Yeah.
That cop's son.
Yot right?
I think so.
But his giri friend lives in the same condo as me.
didn't see her getting pregnant.
Maybe he...
had a kid with another woman.
I guess that girl got cheated on.
T at, this is the first time
I feel like l want to have a child.
You think if I have a kid with Plubpl a.
how do you think the kid will look like?
Hey, I think you should reconcile with her first.
Do not skip steps
Geez!
This fool!
You --
The one who likes to obstruct happiness!
I don't know what to do any more
Peem is always avoiding me
I go to see him and help with work,
but he's still unhappy.
That woman left years ago.
But Peem is still like this.
No.
I need to have a word with Mr. Puchong.
Calm down.
We're the ones that insisted on this engagement.
So what do I have to do?
What do I do to have Peem stop thinking about Plubpl a
and acknowledge me as his fiancee?
Did you know
people are talking about how l got dumped by Peem before we even got married?
I don't know where to put my face
Damn Peem.
He should be respectful.
How about this?
There's going to be a charity gala dinner.
You're attending.
Yes. So?
We can have our daughter dressed beautifully and take Peem
So they can shut those gossip ers up
Will Peem go?
Peem has to go regardless.
If he doesn't,
I will make him go.
You want me to take Sa to a charity gala dinner?
Yes.
Mr. Thaw ip has been scolding you for not paying attention to his daughter lately
Why do I have to pay attention? I didn't want to get engaged to her.
Mr. Thaw ip forced me to get engaged to her.
But Sa didn't do anything wrong
Fine.
I will fulfill my duty as Sa's fiance one last time.
Last time?
What do you mean?
You're going to call off the engagement?
Yes.
It's time that l call it off
Hey! Wait Peem!
Think carefully before you do anything
If we become enemies with Mr Thaw ip
there will be problems for our company.
That can't be helped.
Let's just say
it's time for you to show your skills in protecting our company.
Because I can't help anyway
Why are you saying this?!
Peem!
I'm sorry son.
That despicable man shouldn't be your father
I will protect you.
Dad.
Do I look handsome?
Let me take a look
Wow!
Very handsome!
What about me?
You look handsome too.
Uncle Tong too.
And..
your mom?
Mom looks pretty like a princess.
Putter.
How do I look?
Pretty like a princess.
Sweet talking like this,
the ladies will be swarming you soon.
But...
Putter is right.
You look very beautiful
Thank you.
Putter.
We should go wait in the car, Come on.
Are you ready?
I'm ready
Don't worry.
No matter what happens,
my hand will always reach out to you
I will never let go of your hand.
Thank you.
Are you doing well?
I am.
- That's good.
Mr. Puchong
Hello Mr. Thawip, Mrs. Umpon
-Hello.
--Are you doing well?
am well.
It's just.
Peem went to go pick Sa up at the house.
They'll be here soon.
Right. They're meeting us here
I got impatient so I came here first
Besides, women tend to get ready slow
I get tired of waiting
Yes.
Have you been well, Mr s. Umpon?
It's been a while since I last saw you
I'm well.
Keep being arrogant.
You think your husband is head over heels for you?
Pete!
This way son.
Greet Mr. Thawip and Mrs. Umpon first
Hello.
You've grown so much Pete
You're a young man now.
He's working at the company now
Peem and Saare here
- Ms. Sa, look over here please.
-Hello.
Please scoot closer together.
Nice. Beautiful.
Okay, one more.
One, two, three
This camera please
- On e, two--
-lf you'll excuse me.
Hello.
- Hello.
-Peem.
You look beautiful Sa.
Am I right Pete?
Yeah.
Usa looks very beautiful.
There's Mr. Mark
I'm going to go say hi to him.
Sa.
Go get to know his business partner
Sure.
Hello.
Oh! Mr. Peem!
saw him in the front
Oh.
You two seem close
Tat isn't just my assistant.
He's my best friend that I trust the most.
Oh.
That's why.
Yes.
Peem.
Hello Mr. Mark
Who is this young woman?
I'm Sa.
Peem's fiancee.
You're all here as a couple today
I heard Mr. Vik it will be bringing his wife and child to this function as well
When did Kit get married and have a child?
didn't know
If you don't know, how would I know?
You guys are friends, correct?
Yes.
Oh, speaking of the devil!
Mr. Vi kit!
Plubpl a.
-Hello Mr. Mark-Hello.
Hello Mr. Mark
- Hello.
-Hey.
This is Plubpl a
My wife.
It's nice to meet you
Your wife is very beautiful.
Yes.
For me,
she is the gift from God.
Stay calm Peem
Hold it in.
You'll ruin it.
Right.
You guys are friends, right?
That's right.
We were friends since high school
My apologies
I have to go greet an acquaintance.
You guys go ahead and talk
Sure.
What's up Peem?
We meet again, Mr. Peem
That's...
Plubpl a.
She was once in the headline with Peem
So how did she ended up with Kit?
It looks like...
Kit brought her here to introduce to everyone
If that's the case.
it's fine.
I think we shouldn't pay attention to the children.
We should discuss about the project in Phuket instead
I thought you wouldn't be attending to night's function
You usually don't like them
Yes.
I usually don't like these events.
But if Sa like s it, I am willing to'come.
I can do it for Sa
When's the wedding?
Soon.
Invite me.
Sure.
I won't have any surprises like you and Plubpl a.
Yeah.
When did you get married and have a child together?
We didn't know about it.
Never mind married
When did you guys even dated?
We dated when l went to study in America
Yes.
We met there
until our relationship progressed and got married
That's strange.
Women dreams of having a fancy wedding
very grand, in which you can give her that.
But why didn't you? Why was the wedding a secret?
It wasn't a secret
But Plub wanted privacy
So we had a wedding where guests weren't invited!
It's still strange
Is there another reason?
Or...
you quickly got married to Vi kit
because you were hurt that I was getting engaged to Sa?
Peem.
Please respect my wife
Hey.
I'm just teasing
my former secretary
Don't over think it.
- Peem!
- That's okay Vi kit
Let Mr. Peem think whatever he wants to think
The last time l saw him, he wasn't acting like this.
I was concern at first
Uncle Peem!
Putter.
Why are you here?
I came with my mom and dad
Come here son
What is this?
You know my friend?
Uncle Peem helped me look for Mom at them all
So it was Uncle Peem.
Thank you
for helping our son.
Putter.
Say thank you to Uncle Peem again.
Thank you.
Mrs. Rak.
Hi.
This is Plubpl a
My wife.
J see you on TV quite often. You're a very talented businesswoman.
Thank you.
You two look very compatible with each other.
Mrs. Rak.
I have something to discuss with you.
Was she the one in the news with Mr. Peem?
Yeah.
She married Mr. Vi kit
She doesn't seem ordinary
I think she's quite bad, don't you think so?
I think so.
Plub.
Are you okay?
I've been through the most painful thing in my life
Just the glares and gossips here
don't hurt me.
You haven't blinked at all
Still yearning for her?
Don't start with me
I'm just reminding you
I don't want other people
to think you're a pedophile
Regretting someone's wife like a young boy.
Hey!
I can tell how you look at her
I can see it from Mars.
IJ just pity my son
Oh really?
As if!
Didn't I tell you I will back away if Peem really loves this woman?
I stopped taking interest in Plubpl a ever since I found out Peem loved her.
Better be true.
True or not, that's your opinion. It's none of my business.
No matter what,
you're not my lawful wife anyway.
Puchong!
It would have been nice if you thought of Plubp la like this from the beginning.
But I still don't trust you.
Just accept it Peem
They're married and have a child together.
I know.
I'm just hurt.
I understand.
I'll get something cold for you to drink.
You'll be in a better mood
Keep it together.
Don't forget
you're still my fiance.
If I wasn't thinking about our engagement.
I wouldn't be standing here
Good.
In that case, do your best as the fiance
Don't humiliate yourself for losing to Kit
Honorable guests
Next up is a special awards ceremony
to the philanthropist who donated the most money to our association for the year
Mr. Peem Pattaratrakul!
Let's go do our job as an engaged couple then.
Please say a few words Mr. Peem.
The truth is
I didn't do charity to get an award
But thank you so much for the award
Before this,
I was a self-absorbed person
But four years ago
I met a woman
who I once insulted
and misunderstood her
Shortly after getting to know her
I saw that she did everything
for others before herself
As long as what she was doing was right
I really feel guilty
Who would believe that a woman of her size
that l once insulted
changed my life til now?
That woman
made me a better person.
I'm ready Plub
What's next?
Plub.
You want to change your mind?
Do it.