Our spy who is the driver told me that
the chairman ordered to find a position in the company for this woman.
Other people will look at me like a product,
a money maker, I don't care!
Not someone in my family!
that the pathway for poor people is filled with gravel
just want a day
where I can walk a smooth path.
The woman named Plubpla really did come apply for a job
Are you shocked to see my face?
Are you afraid of something?
No.
I thought you were afraid that I might know you're an epo baby.
Did you misunderstand something?
I came here to apply for a job on my own
I didn't use any connections.
Better be true
Ready for your interview?
Yes.
Have a seat
From your profile
you've done a lot of jobs
That's right.
Because I'm responsible for all the expenses in my house
So I have to work a lot of jobs.
To put it simple,
you do everything for money
Well,
not everything
With certain things even though it's a lot of money,
I won't do it.
Why do you want the manager position at the cafe?
Because I like drinking i coffee.
Also, I've worked at a cafe before sol think
I have enough knowledge in this field quite a bit.
But this job is hard and tiring
You would have to take care of the customers closely.
Are you confident that you can do that?
l am confident
that I have the heart of service.
That, I believe.
I believe that you
must've had a lot of experience in service work
Yes.
I'll consider that
a compliment.
But you don't have a bachelor's degree.
How do you think
you're suited for this position?
In the application
education level isn't required.
I think I have the right to apply
I didn't ask if you have the right or not to apply.
I asked if you think you are suited for this job or not.
My cafe brand
is high-end.
Yes.
If I wasn't confident, I wouldn't have come.
But I don't think you are.
Do you know why
I don't think so?
Because you
have had an inappropriate job before.
Later,customers will think that my cafe is a dishonorable place.
The customers you have served
might misunderstand that my cafe
have additional special services.
This is the vision of an award-winning global businessman?
Miss!
It's fine.
I want to hear her opinion
What era are we in?
People who are well-off don't discriminate others based on occupations
And no matter what profession you choose,
you should not be looked down upon.
You misunderstood
I'm not looking down on these professions.
But I'm looking down on the actions.
People who work to earn money isn't wrong.
But those who hope to make money from money they didn't earn
now that's despicable
I never expect money from anyone.
I don't believe your words.
I believe your actions.
Fine.
I'll show you then.
You were trying to provoke her in front of the directors.
You're bad.
I can't help it.
I must prevent it to the fullest extent.
My company will go into chaos if we hire this woman.
Where is she?
Hey, they're hiring her?
-Yes.
-What?!
Where are you going?
I want to go see that shameless girl
who dare use Puchong's name to apply for a job here
Scared karma will catch up to you?
Weren't you like this woman?
Hello Mr. Puchong
am a public relations employee at the company
You dare bring that prostitute to work at the company?!
Are you not afraid our clients will think of the company as a brothel?!
I don't care where you take her to fool around at.
But you brought her to work at the company!
Isn't that too much?!
Why are you shallow-minded like this?
Sup ang just want to change herself.
She just wants to have a good job.
Why don't you give other people chances?
You got her pregnant?!
If I wasn't thinking of Pete
or the company's name,
I would have hired that woman in an instant.
Because l want to see karma catch up to you too.
Jerk!
This is such a prank!
I shouldn't have come!
I won't get the job if he's interviewing me himself like this!
Hello.
I'm so happy you called!
I am looking for a job
I want to thankyouverymuch
for being a tour guide for my client like this.
What is this?
You're the one that's always finding jobs for me.
Otherwise I would be in trouble.
You're exaggerating
If you didn't help me, I would be in trouble too.
I don't know what's the matter with kids these days.
Those easy jobs
where they detriment their bodies and get lots of money for it, they take it.
Jobs taking care of customers like this,
it's little pay so they don't take it.
That's good.
More jobs for me.
Look at you!
So that...
job interview,
how did it go? You think you'll get it?
Not a chance.
Why is that?
Well...
it's a long story.
I had a good opportunity like other people
but Satan got in the way.
Oh Plub! You're such a fighter!
If you need help with anything,
you can call me any time. Happy to help.
Sure.
Tell me if there's any job for me to do.
Sure!
I need the money to go pay him back as soon as possible.
Sure. No problem
Thank you.
Think about it.
What crazy woman had so many jobs?
These resumes
can be made up by lots of people
What if the truth
Plubpla isn't a bad woman like you think she is?
You're softening up to this woman now?
No.
I was just thinking
may be we're destroying a good opportunity
for a woman who's struggled all her life
Hi Fred!
Hey!
How are you today?
Great! Thank you!
Plu b!
Suthee!
Hi.
Su thee.
Your tour guide here is great!
Really?
Yeah.
I'm glad that you like my sister.
Whoa!
She's your sister?
Yes.
What a surprise!
Su thee.
Hmm?
I'm working for Cha Cha
I didn't know
Mr. Fred is your client.
Oh, this is his first time in Thailand.
So I want him to be impressed with Thailand.
Oh.
Wow.
I'm very impressed with her. Very impressed
Can I go use the restroom real quick?
You can discuss business with him then.
Okay. Thanks.
Oh!
Peem.
Lately our worlds
have been colliding
I think it's you
that's trying to step foot in my world
You...
are still self-absorbed j like you always have been
I'm being truthful
Like with your company
copying my product.
Unless
I should be happy
that I didn't think to the extent
that you sent your subordinate
to copy me
Hey!
The case isn't over yet.
How do you know who copied who?!
Who did what
knows it in their heart.
Sir!
Is something wrong?
It's you.
My...
My heart is relapsing again.
Huh?!
So what do you want me to do?
Do you want me to call an ambulance?
That's okay
Take me
to that room
I have my medication in my bag.
If I take the medicine.
I would feel better.
Okay fine.
Hey. Hey.
I'll take you.
Can you manage?
Yes.
This way.
Can you manage?
To put it simple,
you do everything for money
Not everything.
With certain things even though it's a lot of money,
I won't do it.
Here's your medicine, Mr. Vi kit.
Do you feel better?
I feel better.
Thank you so much.
Sure.
In that case...
Wait.
To repay you,
do you want to drink with me?
That's okay.
I'm work --
I have another client in another room
That's fine.
I'll repay you some other time then.
It's really okay.
I can't.
I don't want to owe anyone.
Thank you.
Okay.
Excuse me then
Do you want to come have fun in my room?
Who knows, may be tonight Plubpla
might soften up to you.
Entertain or VIP work today?
Peem.
You're someone of two worlds
During the day,you talk all smart and is pleasant to listen to.
But during the night,
you do relaxing jobs where you don't have to use your brain.
You're skillful.
You take both hard and easy jobs.
You're good at selling. Did you find one today?
A client who enjoys the taste of you
who is willing to pay you monthly.
What the hell is wrong with you?!
Always picking fights with me nonstop!
That's true.
It's my job
to choose people to come work at my company.
Not someone who deceives men and only wants their money!
I don't want that.
If my clients know I hired someone like that,
they will think my company
is a brothel.
Look Peem!
I don't care if you won't hire me!
But you have no right to speak ill of me!
You have no right to criticize me for what l didn't do!
You have a dirty heart!
Peem.
Did the toilet clogged up or what?
You have a sullen face
Do you know who I ran into?
Who?
The pitiful Plu bp la of yours!
I saw her serving Kit here.
Really?!
I thought she repented.
Tell HR
to take this girl's name out.
I won't authorize it.
Sure.
Let's go home!
Peem. Hey!
Excuse me!
Peem!
I was right.
What kind of good woman would do that kind of job to detriment herself?
What the majority of them would do
is hoping to get rich the short cut way.
A pitiful heroine does it to survive?
That's a TV drama!
Gosh, just forget about her.
Who cares what she does?
That's her body and career.
I won't get involved
if this woman didn't come to my company
and also mess with my dad.
Thank you 3477
3103477
Wait.
That was...
Mr, Su thee,owner of a construction company
that will be collaborating with us.
Only trapping rich men.
You see? It has n't been that long and she has a new client already
If I hire her,
our reputation will be tarnished.
You're home?
You're not asleep yet?
I was waiting for you
Why are you home late today?
Oh well..
Hmm?
It's just that...
had a dinner banquet with clients
Then you must be drunk.
Let me shower for you.
Tre!
It's okay.
I can do it myself.
Thank you.
But today I want...
I want to shower for you
Tre!
Don't.
I can do it myself. Really
I'm going to go shower now.
Tre.
Yes?
-Tre.
Did you tell Plu b
to pay me back within a week?
Plu b snitched on me?
No.
But my company
hired someone to entertain my foreign client
I coincidentally ran into Plu b.
When she got paid, she gave me the money.
That's how I know.
That's right. I told her.
I felt considerate of you
I told you not to be
Did you know by telling her that.
she has to take on these entertainment jobs?
Gosh!
Don't worry about her!
Plu b has been doing these jobs since she was 18 and 19
You should be concern about your sister a little
Yes.
Well,
I'm going to go shower now.
You should go to sleep.
Su thee!
Plu b!
Now do you know Dad
that you can't do as you please
just because you're the CEO?
It's 160 baht but I'll charge you 150
Thank you!
What plant do you want today?
What do you want?
For three, I'll only charge you 100
Tong.
Where are you going?
School, Grandma.
Oh, classes started already?
Wait.
That means you've registered for classes already
Yeah.
Within this week.
I wired you your tuition money.
Stay focus in school little brother
I will quickly graduate
So you won't have to struggle.
Bye.
Well Plu b?
WER Hearing him say that
do you feel less tired?
Of course.
WER Good.
Hi Grandma
What plant do you want?
Variegated ones.
Variegated ones? Not flowering ones?
I have some.
-Can I see?
Hello.
What?
Peem!
Yeah?
-Peem!
Do you know about the new employee yet?
I do.
My dad's nepo kid
didn't pass her interview so she won't get hired
That's a miss for my dad.
Yes she didn't pass the interview.
But your dad didn't miss.
What do you mean?
There is an announcement of appointing
Plu b pla to be your dad's other secretary.
Secretary?!
Work hard and make the most
of the opportunity given to you.
Yes.
Thank you.
I need to talk to you, Dad
In private.
Komsan.
Look after and show my new secretary the ropes around here.
If you need anything, just let Komsan know.
Speak.
How could you hire this woman
to come work here?
Come this way, Ms. Plub pla.
She's my new secretary How are you involved?
I am involved!
The CEO's secretary
must be the face of the company,no?
Plu bp la can be the face of the company.
No damage done there
There is damage Dad.
You already know what kind of jobs she's done in the past!
So?!
Because you think this way, that's why you never gave anyone a chance!
A chance?
Give her a chance like you gave Su over ten years ago?!
She's become my step mother now
that my mother couldn't tolerate anymore
and had to run off!
Our family is like this
is because of you!
Stop talking Peem!
I'll tell you something.
I might not like Su
but l don't want Pete to encounter what I've encountered!
If you are adamant about this woman working here,
I will be the person toget her fired!
Just you wait and see!
Peem.
Cancel all my appointments today.
Tell the people at the shipyard to prepare a boat for me too
Sure.
Puchong hired that girl to be his secretary?!
Yes.
I heard Mr, Peem intervened her interview
that HR couldn't hire her to be the cafe'smanager
So Mr. Puchong hired her to be his secretary instead.
Where is she right now?!
This is your desk.
Okay.
Hey.
Ill go find the documents for the initial procedures for new employees for you
You sit here.
Sure.
Finally,
I have a good job
I hope this job can make Grandma and Tong
have a better life
You.
Since you chose your own path.
you need to be able to accept
that from now on,
your life will never be at peace.
ASSISTANT EXECU I SECRET AN
SECRETARY
Why are you here?!
You're finally awake?
From now on,
my son and I
will come live here
as your father's wife and son.
Oh, Peem.
Dad.
What is this?
He's your brother.
He recently was born.
She has no one to help raise him.
Sol have to bring her to come live with us until your mother returns.
This is why
Mom left and refused to come back!
Your mother took off on her own!
You can't blame me for it!
What do you want me to do?
Abandon your brother?
Look at your brother, Peem
He's so tiny and adorable
From now on,
you can call me "mom ".
So other people won't know
that you
got abandoned by your mother.
Please watch over us, Peem.
We will soon be one family.
Okay?
Don't touch me.
I hate women like you the most!
You're disgusting!
Hey!
You're being more aggressive by the minute!
How can you speak to an elder like this?
Why can't I?
Since it's true!
If you didn't mess with this woman, Mom wouldn't be hurt and run away like that!
If something bad happens to Mom,
it will be all your fault!
Ohmygod! My goodness!
Gosh, what is this?!
People these days.
-My goodness!
-Let me help
Thank you so much young man.
Thank you.
The wheel came off
I guess I've been using it a lot.
I'll try putting it back on.
Are you in a hurry?
It's okay young man.
The tuk tuk l called will be here soon.
It's okay.
Okay, let's go under the shade and I'll fix it for you.
Okay, Thank you so much.
All done Granny!
Thank you so much
Such a trouble for you
No trouble at all.
I fix the wheels on my luggage all the time.
Oh really? You're skillful
Are you waiting for your girlfriend?
No.
Just getting fresh air
and letting the wind hit my face to bring me back to my senses.
Son, do you know
when I'm in a bad mood
I like coming here to stare at the river
and let myself calm down.
Then Iim no longer pissed.
You're in a good mood and also
use slang words
I have teenage grandchildren
so I have to adjust myself to their generation.
Yes.
Do you want to know
what my secret is to help stay in a good mood?
Yes.
When I'm really suffering
I like to stay still and know where my hand placement is at.
Why?
It's a question l got from the monks.
If we know where our hand placement is at,
how our demeanor is,
that means you are able to get your senses back
It reminds us
we are only living in the present.
Living in the present?
Yes.
Because this suffering comes from a clouded mind from the past
So it makes us unhappy.
Thank you Grandma.
Talking to you
makes me feel at ease.
I feel at ease too.
When you have free time,
stop by my flower shop.
It's on the other side of the river and ask them
for Grand ma Thip's flower shop.
They all know me there.
Sure.
When I have free time,
I will stop by.
Come by.
Yes.
I have to go now before my tuk tuk waits for me.
Do you want me to drop you off?
That's okay. I can go home myself.
Remembers on,
live in the present more.
Your heart will be at ease.
Yes Grandma
Remember that.
Okay.
Thank you.
Since you chose your own path,
you need to be able to accept
that from now on,
your life will never be at peace.
Your threats can't do anything to me!
Plubpla.
Don't pay attention to threats coming from that kind of person.
You need to fight!
Fight! You got this!
Got it?!
Huh?
Here's my internship paperwork.
The hotel auction in Phuket,
I'll let you handle it.
Okay.
Sir.
And in terms of welcoming Mr.
Zhang before the official meeting?
You're right.
I think that's important too
This time, we need to make an impression to Mr. Zhang.
to help him decide to become our partner for our project in Vietnam.
Mm.
In that case,please tell Su to have the PR department arrange someone to take care of it
But I think
you already have the right person for this job nearby.
Why don't you send her to handle this matter?
It will show them that we care.
Who are you referring to?
Im referring to the person who has abilities in this specific area.
You just hired her.
Who knows, if this is a success,
everyone might accept the skills of your new secretary.
The reason you suggested the chairman
to send Plu b pla to look after Mr. Zhang,
you have a plan don't you?
Think about it.
That nepokid Plubpla that the chairman hired himself
gets to do an important job like this
who wouldn't be the most satisfied?
What?!
She just started working here
and they gave her an important task to do already?!
Yes, I heard the other employees gossiping
So I quickly came to inform you
This is too much!
Are you stepping over my head now Puchong?!
Send someone to look after Plu bp la and her family
In case Sup ang does something too violent
and we can help them in time.
What's your deal?
You want to prank her
but you're also worried about her safety?
You're contradicting.
Hmm?
Okay, I'll handle it for you.
I really want to know
if Plubpla meets my stepmother,
how will she defeat her?