What?!
You're the one that leaked Peem's clip four years ago?
The reason Tat called your brother
was to probably talk about this matter.
Why would you do it Mom?!
Why are you asking me that?
I wanted you to end up with Sa.
Mom.
Don't you love her?
I just thought that
if I leak Peem's clip, it would change her mind
Who would have thought
that things would escalate like this?
It's okay Mom.
Don't worry about it
I won't let anyone hurt you.
I will protect you.
Oh.
You're home?
Where's Peem?
Tat called him for an urgent matter.
He left after he dropped me off
He should have told me first!
I cooked a lot of food for him!
Alright.
If you'll excuse me.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I'm just tired.
I'm going to go rest
I...
really have done you wrong.
Yes.
You did me wrong
and our son
More importantly
you did yourself wrong.
I'm sorry.
I know
you were hurt because of this too.
It's okay.
Let's forget the past together.
I love you Plubpl a
l also know
you still love me too.
Let's help resolve this issue together
S But the closer l get to you &
S The more Iknow I've done wrong and made mistakes
P Can you please forgive me
P How much I hated you d
PIc an love you even more
PI'msorry for all the mistakes &
PI want you to try to accept the love that comes from me
PI will give you everything
PIlose to you in every way
P Can I make amends? Let me fix it by asking for your love
It's too late Peem
The two of us has come a long way.
Why?
Why are you giving up?
You're just going to leave things just like this?
But this doesn't just involve us.
I think this is the best solution for us
I don't want Putter to be sad over this.
But we...
can explain to him
and have him understand it
We can't.
Putter loves Vi kit a lot.
Vik it is also my benefactor.
I can't hurt him.
Why do you have to care
about other-people's feelings?
What about my feelings?
And yours?
It's not important?
Don't make me do more wrong.
I don't want anyone else getting hurt over this
Especially our son
Putter!
We came to pick-you up
Yes.
How did you know I was here?
Putter was crying for you.
I called you but you didn't pick up so I called Tong
That's how I know you were here
Dad said he was going to take me out to eat
Come with us Mom.
Okay.
Hello Uncle Peem
I'm happy to see you
I'm happy too
that I got to see you
If you're done with things here, we should get going.
Yes.
Come on Putter.
Let's go.
Come on.
Sooner or later Kit,
I am going to get my family back
Don't worry Mom
Hey!
Peem!
What are you going to do to Mom?!
Do you know what your mom did four years ago?!
I do!
But she did it for me!
I apologize on her behalf!
You're not the person that should be apologizing!
It's your mom!
I'm going to put you in prison!
Bas ed on Plubpla's sister's testimony?
Just that?!
That can put me in prison?!
So you don't feel any remorse?!
Huh?!
Stop! Don't hurt my mom!
Stop Pete!
Stop!
Don't hurt Peem!
Are you okay Peem?
If you're trying to hurt me
or the person I love again
I will not forgive you
Peem!
Uncle Tong!
Dad took me to go eat a big lobster today!
Really?!
Yes.
Tong.
Can you go take a bath for him?
Come on Putter
Let's go!
Let's go take your bath!
I'm sorry
that l didn't tell you l went to see Peem at Aunt Kaew's house today.
It's related to Aunt Kaew's safety
I promised her I wouldn't tell anyone
What do you mean?
Aunt Kaew and Peem
are related how?
Once things clear up
I will tell you everything.
Okay.
You must be tired. You should go rest.
We can talk later.
Thank you.
It's too late Peem
The two of us has come a long way.
I don't want anyone else getting hurt over this.
Especially our son.
No.
I won't allow it Plubpl a.
I'm going to get you and our son back
Why do you have to care
about other people's feelings?
What about my feelings?
And yours?
It's not important?
Mom!
Why are you crying?
Who bullied you?
No one.
I...
No one bullied me.
I'm just happy.
If you're happy
why are you crying then?
Sometimes
people cry when they're happy
But l don't want to see you cry.
Then I won't cry.
So your mom didn't leave you guys
but was attacked and had amnesia?
Yes.
I found her.
Dad and l are looking for the culprit right now.
That's why I came to tell you to help us out.
Just tell me what you want me to do
Thank s Tat.
Oh.
so,
who do you suspect?
Your step mom Mrs. Sup ang?
I did suspect her at first
But after talking to Mom
there's someone else that's suspicious
Who?
Aunt Ump on,
Usa's mother.
Huh?!
Is that possible?
You have a delivery ma'am
From who?
The messenger said there's a card and if you read it, you'll know who it's from.
Next time,don't accept anything if you don't know who it's from.
You can go now.
Yes ma'am.
I remember you like hydrangeas.
See you soon.
Mane ewan?!
You sent a bouquet to Mr s. Umpon
under your mom's name?
Yeah.
I want to know what she will do if she knows that Mom is still alive.
Dad and l have sent an investigator to follow Aunt Ump on around!
I never imagined
that a saint-like person like Mr s. Umpon
would kill someone
I don't want to believe it either
What about your situation'with Plubpl a?
Hello.
Hello Putter's mom.
Putter and his uncle are playing over there.
Uncle?
Yes.
Peem!
Putter, your mom is here!
Yay!
Hey.
Why are you here?
I thought you weren't going to confuse him?
That's before we found out the truth about what happened four years ago.
I have done nothing wrong to you.
So why should l lose you and our son?
We made a deal.
Hey.
You assumed and agreed on everything alone.
I made no such deal.
Putter.
Do you want to go eat ice cream?
Yes!
Do you like ice cream?
" I do!
Then let's go!
Let's go eat ice cream!
I prepared a car seat for you already
23 U8377
Fromnowon, Iwill come pick you up more often okay?
2 U8377
Okay!
Let's go.
Be careful.
Get in!
Hey Peem.
You have no right to take my son anywhere without permission.
Why not?
He's my son too.
Get in. Let's go have ice cream.
Our son is waiting
2 U8377
Is it delicious?
Very delicious.
Then can l have some?!
It is delicious!
You have to put this on too.
You want this on?
I like it.
Putter.
Can you feed me?
Okay.
Thank you.
In that case,
we'll take our leave now.
Wait.
Do you want to play more games over there?
Yes.
Hey!
What is it?
I have to take him home. Where are you taking him?
Let's go play together.
Hey! Hey!
K INFO Peem!
It's here!
The purple one.
What about this one?
The blue one. Go for it.
The claw grabbed the arm.
-It did huh?
-Do over?
-It grabbed the arm earlier.
Take that!
Hurry Putter! Go! Go!
Iwon!
Let's go home now.
Did you have fun Putter?
I did.
But I wish Dad was here.
It would be much more fun
Then let's go home and see him.
I'll drop you off.
That's okay.
I had Tong pick us up already
He's waiting.
But...
That's enough Peem.
Don't even try.
I won't change my mind.
You should also respect Usa.
She is considered your lawful wife right now.
Let's go Putter.
Say bye to Uncle Peem
Go.
We can play again next time.
Okay.
Come on.
I'm not going to give up Putter
We will be together.
Dad!
Putter!
Why are you home so late today?
Where did you go?
Uncle Peem took me to go eat ice cream
Peem went to see Putter at school.
I tried to stop him
I understand.
I know what's he like
So,
was it delicious?
Yes but I wished you were there.
Putter.
Go play with Uncle Tong first.
I want to talk to your mom.
Okay.
Come on Putter
Let's go!
I want to know
how you feel about Peem right now
Do you still want to get revenge on him?
Regarding what happened four years ago,
Peem didn't do it.
I want to stop.
I can't hurt him anymore
You mean
you're going to leave me
and go back to Peem?
No.
I'm not going to go back to him.
Really?
Yes.
But l also...
can't be with you either.
What?
For me,
whether it's you or Peem,
I feel guilty towards both of you
Sol think
I'm going to take Putter and Tong back to live at Grandma's house.
Plub.
Hey.
You're going to divorce me?
It's up to you.
If you want to get a divorce then...
No.
I won't divorce you
I won't lose you
and our son.
Plub.
You and our son
are my family.
You're family to me too.
You're still Putter's father.
But I...
I can't bother you anymore.
You should
really live your life now
Don't let us be a burden for you.
No.
No Plub.
You and our son
aren't a burden for me.
I know you can't love me right now.
But I told you already
no matter how long it takes,
I will wait.
Don't waste your time.
We should
go back to living our lives as it should be.
I'm sorry.
Dad.
I've waited so long to see this day
Finally,
the day has come
Can you not start with me?
You lost to Peem again
How does it feel?
You're an idiot
for getting used by that woman!
Plub isn't what you think
You're still going to defend her?!
I can tell
that woman used sweet words to trick you.
So she can go back to being with Peem gracefully
Stop being stupid Kit
That woman
doesn't really love you.
Her son
isn't really your son.
I know it!
That kid
looks nothing like you!
Enough Dad!
What you just said, I know what is what!
You!
Dad.
Let me live my life.
Just once
Without having you controlling me!
You're sick.
Take care of yourself
If you really are a father,
you would know
there isn't a day
that a father doesn't worry about his son.
Kaew.
I'm going to ask you straightforward
You really don't remember Mr, Puchong?
No one can forget
the person that hurt them the most.
You remember him.
But you refused to forgive him
So you pretend you can't remember him.
remember everything in the past
since I saw Peem.
When I saw Puchong
I remember the pain from the past really well.
Hey.
Kaew.
I saw the way he looked at you.
I know he feels really guilty towards you
Is there away for you to forget
and forgive him?
You're not scared
that if I can forgive him
I would leave you?
I am.
I am scared.
But I want you to be happy
Believe me,
no matter which way you choose
I will understand.
Whether it's you or Peem,
I feel guilty towards both of you
I will not lose you and our son.
Plub!
Putter!
Where are you Putter?
Mr. Putter isn't home.
Where did he go?
His mother packed their belongings and left.
What?!
Mrs. Plubpl a left you a letter.
Why do we have to live here?
Because this place
is our real home
What about Dad? Will he come live with us?
Dad won't be living with us
He has his own home
I want to live with Dad
Why can't I live with him?
Let's...
wait until you're a bit older then I'll explain.
Let's go inside
Come Putter! Let's go inside!
Let's go inside!
Surprise!
Uncle Peem!
Welcome home Putter!
What is this?
Oh.
Peem and Tat knew that you were moving back
so they came to help me clean the place up
How is it?
We organized everything
Thank you.
How did you know I was moving back today?
Tong.
Sorry Plub.
But I wanted Putter to be present with his real family
Plub.
Plubpl a!
Peem!
Hey!
Peem, let go!
Plub.
I won't let you go again.
Are you crazy?!
Let go!
Plubpl a.
Peem.
I think we should stop being immoral.
Immoral?
What's immoral about us being in love?
It's immoral
because we're both married to someone else.
I'm going to divorce Usa.
You already know
I didn't want to marry her from from the beginning.
But I'm not going to divorce Vi kit.
Why not?
Because...
Vik it is the only person
that l ended me a hand when I was struggling
I can't do that to him.
Most importantly.
I don't want Putter to get hurt over this matter.
Plub.
I know
your love for me has never changed.
Even when you resented me,
you still loved me.
Am I right?
Right now,
I'm not worthy of loving you.
Plub.
You should leave.
I'm begging you.
Plub.
No.
I'm not giving up that easily
Kit.
What business do you have with me?
Peem.
Can't sleep?
Just thinking about your mother.
She must hate me so much.
Give her time.
It's karma
that I'must accept.
I hurt your mother so much
Dad.
It's in the past now
Let's not mention it anymore
Really?
Can it really be that way?
You also
have been mad at me.
Or am I wrong?
If you really have repented
you should
try to make it better then
I will find the culprit
that tried to kill your mother
I ill have them be punished to a tone for the sins that l've committed
Besides,
your mother won't have to live in hiding anymore.
I already sent a bouquet to Aunt Ump on to see her reaction just like you asked me to.
Yeah.
But...
she has n't made a move yet.
The only way we can do is threaten the culprit to confess.