(Mount Jiri's morning is clearer than yesterday.)
(Hi.)
(The members have become closer than yesterday.)
(The second day where they became real family begins.)
(Driving along with the cherry blossoms of Seomjin River,)
(they've arrived at the green tea field in Hadong.)
(The fresh front yard...)
(and the zip-line in the next town where they can see Dadohae.)
(They have the greatest looking dishes for dinner.)
(Exclaiming)
(Eyes going wide)
(They can't stop exclaiming the whole day.)
(What events await them today?)
(They spent a relaxing day in Mount Jiri.)
The sound of the stream and burning wood is really nice, right?
(Safely filmed in a campground where the use of burners is granted.)
Byoung Cheol, was there anything you weren't happy with today?
- No, not at all.
- Right?
I love it here.
When I heard you two were coming...
You know how you have the opposite images,
Byoung Cheol and Yoon A.
I was worried if the five of us would get along well.
But unexpectedly, we all got along really well.
(They had a great day where they got along with each other well.)
Because Byoung Cheol doesn't talk much,
he gets along with anyone most of the time.
(The hidden hero of their chemistry today)
We'll make some great memories tomorrow.
You know what we're doing tomorrow, right?
- Zipline?
- Zipline, Yes.
It has the longest course in Korea.
(On the way to their second front yard tomorrow,)
(Dong Il has prepared a special gift for them.)
(It's where you can see Dadohae at once...)
(and enjoy the thrills while dashing through the wind.)
(I love it.)
(The longest course in Asia, the zipline of Mount Geumo)
Zipline is really fun.
All right.
The fire is dying out now. Let's go to bed.
(They go to bed for now.)
We don't wake you up early.
Don't wake anyone if you get up early. Leave them to sleep.
- And go to the bathroom quietly.
- Okay.
All right. You can go in now.
(Si Wan is busy making the bed for the guests.)
- Who's sleeping upstairs?
I'll be sleeping up there.
- And?
- I'll be sleeping here.
- Really?
- Yoon A is sleeping on the floor?
(Si Wan's bed, Yoon A's bed, Byoung Cheol's bed)
I think I'll step on her on my way to the bathroom.
- No, you won't.
- No way.
If you do, I'll get up.
Of course you will.
I'll remove the pillows.
- Oh, no. Oh, my!
- Hey, hey!
What's wrong with him? I can't sleep here.
- Get out.
- I didn't mean it.
- What's wrong with this man?
- This won't do.
- He can't think straight.
I didn't want to step on your blanket.
This won't do.
- I didn't want to step on it.
- She said this won't do.
You shouldn't meet him too often. Call us instead.
I don't meet him that often.
- Are you okay?
- Good night then.
- Sleep tight.
- Good work, today.
- I'll shut the doors for you.
- Thank you.
(Dong Il and Hee Won go to the tent after taking care of them.)
Oh, my!
Yoon A did all this.
- Yoon A did?
- Yes.
My goodness. She made amazing bedding for us.
I'm so glad to have met you through this show.
- I know. Me too.
- It's good to see you both.
Right. I'm really glad.
- And we're sleeping in one room.
- It's really sudden.
- It's such an honor.
- All of a sudden.
You can speak casually to us anytime you want to.
Yes, please do that.
Okay, then. I'll do that from tomorrow.
- From tomorrow?
- Yes.
Good night.
(They promise to be more comfortable with each other tomorrow.)
(With birds chirping, the morning has arrived.)
(The members of House on Wheels...)
(are still deep asleep.)
(Si Wan doesn't even budge and sleeps quietly.)
(Sleeping quietly)
(Even when she tosses and turns, she's beautiful.)
(Byoung Cheol tosses and turns a lot more than others.)
(It's comfortable to sleep with my legs crossed.)
(Meanwhile, in the tent...)
(He gets up all of a sudden.)
(Dong Il got up first.)
(Crawling out)
(Are they still asleep?)
(Enjoying the view of the front yard while everyone's asleep)
(Hello.)
(The green mountain view that stretches endlessly)
(And a clear valley where freshwater flows)
(The morning with a clear view of Mount Jiri)
(The front yard is as beautiful as ever today as well.)
(Peeping)
(They're still sleeping?)
(It seems like they're never going to wake up.)
(Getting up abruptly)
(It's cold.)
(He closes the door tight and gets back to sleep.)
(I'm so bored, but no one's getting up.)
(He brings a firewood box.)
(Rattling)
(He prepares a fire for firegazing alone.)
(After setting all the chairs,)
(he finally sits down.)
(This is nice.)
(He's up already?)
(Clacking)
(Good morning.)
Did you sleep well?
Yes. Why did you get up so early?
I wake up early now that I'm old.
(Laughing)
(Half-asleep)
(Hee Won got up to the noise from outside.)
(Si Wan is up already.)
(Hee Won sits in front of the fire too.)
This is warm and nice.
(Safely filmed in a campground where the use of burners is granted.)
The house owners get up early.
- Sorry?
- The house owners get up early.
(The house owners got up early.)
(Meanwhile, in the house...)
(Blinking)
(Getting up abruptly)
(They're all up early.)
(She ties her hair neatly...)
(and checks herself in the mirror.)
Yoon A is up.
(Yoon A is here.)
Yoon A, did you sleep well?
(Nodding)
Come sit here. It's warm.
Aren't you tired?
Yoon A is beautiful even in the morning.
(Embarrassed)
Firegazing is nicer in the morning.
It's nice to look around and gaze at the fire in the morning.
(She's getting absorbed into the morning firegazing.)
Look at his face.
(I'm sleepy.)
Byoung Cheol is sleeping long. Maybe it's because he's introverted.
He needs to get up so I can ask him to make coffee.
I think Byoung Cheol is up.
- He is?
- I think so.
(Byoung Cheol climbs down carefully.)
(Being careful)
(He got tired from climbing down.)
Did you sleep well?
Hi.
- Really?
- I said hi.
(Hi!)
(Byoung Cheol kept his promise to talk casually to his juniors.)
Good morning, Byoung Cheol.
- I slept really well.
- That's good.
(Shy)
Now that you've gone casual with me,
you should try it with Yoon A.
Yoon A, Byoung Cheol has something to say to you.
- What is it? What?
- What does he have to say?
- He has something to say.
- I do?
Yes.
- What is it?
- I slept well. Did you sleep well?
(I slept well too.)
Are you all speaking casually to each other now?
- Yes.
- Even Yoon A and Si Wan?
Please speak comfortably to me.
(Sure.)
Let's drink something.
(Now that Byoung Cheol is up, let's drink something.)
(He took out the coffee dripper that You Jung gave them.)
(Dripping)
(He gazes at the dripping coffee instead of the fire.)
- Is there any movie you like?
- Me?
The movie you think we all should watch.
- There is one.
- What is it?
- It's called "The Conversation".
- "The Conversation"?
It's a movie by Francis Ford Coppola.
Gene Hackman stars in it.
You kind of resemble him.
- He's way more charismatic than me.
- That's not true.
- He's way taller too.
- I'd choose you over him.
(Thumbs-up)
I like you too, Dong Il.
This is how you become when you get old.
I've always liked movies like "The World Without a Mother".
I've always preferred family movies over action movies.
Those everyday stories between family members.
Something like "3000 Leagues in Search of Mother"?
Yes, something like that. I'm serious.
Movies like "A Dog of Flanders". I cried a lot when I watched it.
I bawled my eyes out...
toward the end during the church scene.
I did a play of "A Dog of Flanders".
My role was the dog.
Of course you had to. You're perfect for it.
I played the lead role.
Of course. Thank goodness...
you didn't have to pull the cart.
(Sticking his head out)
Thank you.
(Here's the coffee you ordered.)
(Sipping)
(Impressed)
(A cup of warm coffee that begins their day)
It'd be really nice...
to have tteokguk for breakfast in the mornings like this.
(Exclaiming)
Make it for us, Dong Il.
- Tteokguk?
- Yes.
Tteokguk?
Should I make it for you guys?
- Do you know how to make it?
- Yes.
- Really?
Great. Let's have tteokguk for a light breakfast.
(He agrees.)
We decide on the menu on the spot.
(I'd like that.)
- That's great.
- I'll go and make it for you.
(I'll make it in no time.)
I wish my daughter grows up to be like Yoon A.
I wish my son grows up to be like Si Wan.
(Nodding)
I don't think I'd want my son to grow up to be like you guys.
(Sure, sure.)
I'm sure I'm not the right role model.
I think Hee Won is not bad.
- Him?
- Yes.
That makes my dad Dong Il?
(Screaming)
(Laughing)
(Yoon A begins making tteokguk.)
Adding lots of meat.
(Sizzling)
(Next, she cracks eggs.)
(Skillfully separating egg yolks from whites)
The heat is too high.
- Could you turn down the heat?
- The heat? Hold on.
- Are you making egg garnish?
- Yes.
(She finishes making egg garnish easily.)
There's less yellow dust today.
The sky cleared up, right?
It's gotten much better than yesterday.
- Look. Look over there.
- The sky is clearer.
I can see it! I can see the Cheonwangbong Peak!
Right. You can see the sun.
(Exclaiming)
(It's the highest peak of Mount Jiri...)
(and the second-highest peak in Korea.)
(They couldn't see it yesterday due to the bad weather.)
The sun is right there.
Si Wan, Yoon A!
We can see the Cheonwangbong Peak clearly now.
Really?
- Oh, he's right. Look.
- Let me see.
The view is clear now.
(I want to see it too.)
You can see it, right?
- Why couldn't we see it yesterday?
- I saw it.
(They can see it clearly now.)
We should've seen the Cheonwangbong Peak yesterday.
I know, the weather should've been nice like today.
The sun is right above the Cheonwangbong Peak.
- Right?
- It's like the view...
- from Mount Everest.
- Is that so?
That's what we wanted to see yesterday.
- It's way clearer than yesterday.
- Right.
We couldn't see anything yesterday.
I can see the peak in detail.
It was foggy up here until yesterday.
I can see every tree on the Cheonwangbong Peak.
You can see four big trees on the right.
(Laughing)
- You can see that? Four trees?
- Can't you see them?
Yes, I can.
- Right.
- Yes.
How high is the peak?
Isn't it about 1,400m or 1,700m?
1,400m or 1,500m? Or 1,450m?
I'll look it up quickly.
You need to be seen as someone who knows everything.
I think it's around 1,700m high.
From 1,700m to 2,000m.
- Or 1,900m?
- Yes, it's 1,915m.
- See? I was right.
- It's 1,915m high.
From what I know,
the Cheonwangbong Peak is 1,915m high.
You are very precise.
Including the memorial stone,
it's around 1,958m.
- The memorial stone?
- Maybe 1,957m. The stone.
Are you saying the stone is 35m tall?
Come on. It's about 3m tall.
It's about 3m or 2m tall.
Anyway, the Cheonwangbong Peak is 1,915m high.
(He's sure of this.)
Gosh, he knows everything.
I lied about my age.
I was actually born in 1938.
(Laughing)
- Is it going well?
- Yes.
Yoon A is really fast.
Are you almost done?
- Yes, it's almost done.
- She's really fast.
- For dumplings...
- Dumplings? We have dumplings?
Yes, bring them.
(These are the dumplings they'll have with tteokguk.)
(Pouring)
(A good posture)
(Frying in a flashy manner)
(It looks delicious.)
- Here, Byoung Cheol.
- Yes.
Try this one.
Okay.
Gosh, so hot. Give me chopsticks.
Gosh, it's so hot because of the oil.
So hot.
(How come you grabbed it with your hand?)
- Thank you.
- Seriously.
Byoung Cheol.
(A dumpling is delivered with chopsticks.)
- Thank you.
- Try it.
(Blowing)
Hey, give this to her.
(He takes a bite of a freshly fried dumpling)
- I'll give it to her.
- It's for Yoon A.
- I'll go.
- Okay.
(Savoring)
- Is it okay?
- It's delicious, but...
- the inside is a bit cold.
- Is it cold?
(Failed)
I did it on purpose.
(If Dong Il says so...)
- An iron hand in a velvet glove.
- That's right.
Is it too cold?
The cold part takes up about...
30 percent of the dumpling.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
(Upset)
We can put lightly fried dumplings in tteokguk.
- We can do that.
- Right.
- We'll use all of these.
- Yes.
(Adding rice cake into the soup)
- I poured rice cake in it just now.
- Yes.
You can bring it out.
- Thank you. Sorry.
- No problem.
Hey.
(Eat some dumplings while cooking.)
Here's the dumpling. Yoon A, try this dumpling.
It's hot.
(Taking a bite carefully)
Is it good?
(Exclaiming)
- Is it good?
- It's perfect.
- Is it okay?
- Yes.
But he added too much oil.
- The oil is dripping.
- Gosh, seriously.
(Here's a pot delivery!)
Okay, good. It'll be done in no time.
(Let me take a look at it.)
(Steamy)
- It's done. Come and ladle it.
- Okay.
Okay.
Hand me the bowl.
Yoon A of Girls' Generation made this tteokguk.
(Please enjoy!)
Dong Il, Yoon A also made egg garnish.
(Impressed)
I've only heard of Zidane, the soccer player.
(Turning frosty)
You should understand him.
Okay.
(A forced laugh)
(Embarrassed)
Here.
(Decorating with egg garnish)
How pretty!
Thanks.
And...
(Add fried dumplings as a finishing touch)
What a tasty meal for a breakfast.
(House on Wheels is known for its visual)
(A warm breakfast of tteokguk and fried dumplings is ready.)
- Is it ready?
- Yes.
- It's done.
- Thank you for the food.
- Let's dig in.
- Thank you for the meal.
(A large mouthful)
Is it a little bland?
It can't be tasteless.
(Exclaiming)
- It's good.
- Yoon A, it's delicious.
It's delicious.
Gosh, I...
I'll make this for breakfast later.
(Yoon A takes a bite after a hard cooking.)
(Savoring)
(Si Wan's shoulder rises when food is delicious.)
It's so delicious.
(It's good!)
I can't believe we can see Cheonwangbong Peak from here.
Gosh, the view of Cheonwangbong Peak and tteokguk. Isn't this amazing?
(Against the beautiful cherry blossom background,)
It's so delicious.
Tteokguk is a good choice for breakfast.
(they eat tteokguk as they take in the view of Cheonwangbong Peak.)
How nice!
It's our first time to eat such a hearty and warm meal...
early in the morning. Thanks to Yoon A.
It's pretty decent.
Pretty decent.
- Pretty decent?
- He thinks it's pretty decent.
(Yoon A couldn't recognize his accent.)
You didn't understand it?
- It's pretty decent.
- Where are you from?
I'm from Seoul.
- It's Seoul, but...
- Where in Seoul?
- Sorry?
- You're being inquisitive again.
Dong Il, I'm from Seoul too.
Gosh. When Byoung Cheol said he's from Seoul yesterday,
you didn't ask or say anything.
I didn't hear him. Are you from Seoul?
- Yes.
- Where in Seoul?
- I'm from Seodaemun-gu.
- Seodaemun-gu.
Goodness, you're a gentleman.
(A delayed reaction)
My grandparents are from Yeongju.
- Right, you said that.
- As I grew up,
I heard a lot of the Gyeongsang Province dialect.
(She's familiar with the Gyeongsang Province dialect.)
My dad...
is from Hwanghae Province.
- I see. He's from North Korea.
- Yes.
He became an orphan during the Korean War.
- Your dad was...
- During the January–Fourth Retreat,
he missed the train.
His whole family?
That's what I heard from Dad.
I was even on a TV show that looks for dispersed families.
(Hee Won was on TV to find his dispersed family?)
- There was that program in KBS.
- Yes, quite a long time ago.
- My gosh, seriously?
- I went with my mom.
How old were you at that time?
I guess I was ten years old.
- You were 10 years old?
- Anyway...
We couldn't find them.
(Sad)
But I had to hold a panel.
It was incredibly hot, but they told me to hold it.
You were only 10 years old.
It was so tiring, but my dad told me to hold it.
He came to Seoul after he turned 20.
Your dad came to Seoul.
He made his first address when he came to Seoul.
So he registered my birth in Myeongdong.
I'm from Myeongdong. That's my place of birth.
So it was Myeongdong.
That's where my dad settled in.
(Kim Hee Won, Born in Myeongdong)
We can tell how delicious this is from the leftovers.
I'd like to express how I feel about Yoon A.
I did the dishes while eating.
(Surprised)
- Thank you.
- Gosh, you emptied your bowl.
There's not even a dried laver flake.
(It's almost a new bowl.)
There's nothing left.
(Groaning)
(Laughing)
There are only scallions left. It's hard to finish.
You can stop eating now.
- Can I?
- Sure.
- Hey.
- That's enough. Oh, you ate it all.
This is all I can give to you.
I can't keep my promise anymore.
(Thank you, Hee Won.)
Hey, we're done now. We should work out.
- Let's clean up and go to see fish.
- Okay.
(That sounds nice.)
The air is definitely clearer than yesterday.
- I know.
- Right, the air is so clear.
(The air became clear in the front yard.)
I can't wait to see it.
- We can see the clouds today.
- Right.
(Flutter of excitement fills their way to see the fish trap.)
Why am I in a flutter when it's nothing special? Right?
Will there be any fish caught?
Am I shivering from cold or excitement?
- It was around here, right?
- Yes.
- I think it was around here.
- Do you see anything?
- There it is.
- It's there.
- Here.
- Here it is.
Oh, it hasn't been swept away.
(Is that the right one?)
(Fish traps have been waiting for the members the whole night.)
(Fish me out! Me too!)
(Will there be some fish in it?)
(How many fish will there be?)
Pull it out.
(Empty)
(There's not even a trace of fish in the fish trap.)
I told you there won't be any.
I guess there's no need to check on it.
Right, just fish it out.
- Don't go into the water.
- Right.
Just fish it out.
(I'll fish it out then.)
- There's nothing, right?
- Nothing.
- Gosh.
- Let's go now.
- There's no suspense about it.
- Let's call it a day.
(Giggling)
It's the same.
- There's nothing.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
(Shocked)
It's all right.
How come we haven't caught one?
Are there any fish here?
(Playing at 30x speed)
(Astonishingly, there was none.)
(They leave the front yard with the view of Mount Jiri.)
Let's go.
(House on Wheels is heading to a new front yard.)
I'm excited.
(Expectant)
(They're all excited to set off.)
(What will be today's new front yard...)
There are so many beautiful places in Korea.
(where they will make memories together?)
(Hadong, South Gyeongsang Province)
(Surrounded by Seomjin River)
(South Sea spreads widely from below.)
(It is beautifully embroidered...)
(along the hillsides of Mount Jiri.)
(Greenish wild green tea fields)
(There are lots of fresh foods...)
(from Seomjin River.)
(Mitten crab)
(Densely lamellated oyster)
(Today's front yard is Hadong.)
(On the way to our new front yard,)
(there's a gift from Dong Il.)
- We'll make fond memories.
- My gosh.
It sounds fun.
(Last front yard, Mount Geumo zipline)
I'm so excited.
(As they drove in a flutter...)
- I think we arrived.
- We're here.
Now it feels like we're on a trip.
I know, right?
Hurray!
(The way to enjoy Hadong to its fullest)
(Enjoying the thrill of sliding through the wind)
Aren't you going too fast?
(Taking in the view of blue South Sea)
It's the longest zipline in Korea.
(It's 3,186m in total, the longest in Asia.)
- We might see Hee Won cry again.
- Are you talking about me?
(They're going to have a memorable experience just as paragliding.)
Can you ride it, Hee Won?
Of course, I can.
(Of course, I can.)
Hello.
(Safely filmed according to the COVID safety regulations.)
Sanitize your hands.
Do we have to weigh ourselves?
(Checking weight for a safe ride)
Large.
- I see. It shows your size.
- Right, approximately.
Wear it as you wear a backpack.
It's yellow and black.
(Wearing safety equipment like a backpack)
(Looks determined)
We have to go up by car.
Will it take about 20 minutes by car?
20 minutes from now?
Shall I set off?
Yes.
It'll be such a good memory.
It's so fun to ride a zipline.
Gosh, I'm excited.
It'll also make me feel like I'm flying.
Have you ever done paragliding before?
No, I haven't.
You must try it.
- But you cried.
- Right, it was worth it.
I want to go paragliding.
Paragliding is mind-blowing.
Hee Won will have one more thing to brag about now.
"You guys should ride a zipline."
(Hee Won has gained another experience.)
We're going up.
(Meanwhile, the car is heading to the summit of Mount Geumo.)
I'm nervous too.
I think it'll be a bit scary.
(Riding a zipline seems scary.)
But I think it'll be fun.
We'll feel cool as we go down on it.
Byoung Cheol will have the brightest look on his face.
(Will I?)
(Like this.)
(Chuckling)
(He's going to be extremely happy.)
(I can't wait to get there.)
- Gosh, it's high.
- Look, we came up so high.
It's good to be up this high.
- My gosh.
- We came up high already.
How high is it here?
It's 849m at the summit.
It's so high.
Right, it feels like we're going up endlessly.
It feels higher than 800m.
- Gosh, this is...
- My goodness.
(The road goes round in a tight curve as they go up.)
Gosh, it's a good thing that we ate our breakfast early.
(Swaying)
This is more thrilling than the zipline.
(Glancing)
(It is high indeed.)
(Grabbing with both hands)
(Closing eyes at the dizzy height)
(The car goes up as if there's no end.)
Oh, dear.
Oh, dear. I'm scared.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
It's too high.
(They arrived at the summit of Mount Geumo at an altitude of 849m.)
(Boarding area for the zipline)
Can you ride it, Hee Won?
Now that I'm here, I'm getting nervous.
(Laughing)
It would've been hard for you to come all the way here.
- It was fun.
- Right.
Gosh, how could they build this place here?
(Exclaiming)
- Goodness, it's so magnificent.
- It's so beautiful.
(They're all gaping at...)
(the beautiful scenery of Mount Geumo...)
(that spreads beneath them.)
(And over the Mount Geumo,)
(you can admire the view of blue South Sea.)
(You can enjoy the cool winds...)
(and the magnificent scenery of Hadong at the same time.)
(We've arrived at the summit of Mount Geumo.)
It feels like we're above the sky.
- Like floating on clouds.
- Right.
How nice.
We're going to take this to go down.
(After admiring the scenery, they noticed the zipline.)
You'll ride in pairs.
- I see.
- One person has to ride alone.
The bravest person can ride alone.
I'll ride it alone then.
So you think you're the bravest of us all?
(That's not what I meant.)
Instead, I'll go last.
I'll decide between the car and the zipline later.
(Byoung Cheol, goodness.)
- You two will go first.
- Okay.
(Extremely nervous)
(It's quite high. Are we going to be okay?)
- Are we going to ride it now?
- Yes.
- Please step on it.
- Okay.
(Si Wan and Yoon A are getting ready to take the zipline.)
(Distant)
(She can't help but laugh at the dizzy height.)
- Are you okay, Si Wan?
- Hold the line lightly.
- I don't feel anything yet.
- Yes.
But if it's too fast...
Now please sit down slowly.
How about the one who makes a sound...
buys something delicious?
- So we shouldn't make a sound.
- Right.
- Okay, without a sound.
- Yes.
- We're not going to make a sound?
- Lean back comfortably.
(Laughing)
Get ready. Ready!
(With a thud)
- Ready!
- What's this? My goodness.
- You made a sound.
- Already?
(Si Wan already made a sound.)
- He made a sound.
- That was level one.
He's out.
- Yoon A, I was startled.
- I won't make any sound.
(Embarrassed)
I won't make any sound.
My gosh, I thought it would start abruptly.
(A deep breath)
- Let's go.
- Are we going? Okay.
Enjoy the cool wind.
(Extremely nervous)
- She's covering her mouth.
- In 3, 2, 1.
Go!
(Si Wan and Yoon A go first.)
(Sliding down along the hillside)
Gosh, this is so fun!
Go!
(Exclaiming)
Gosh, this is so fun!
She said it's so fun.
(Highly excited)
It's too fast.
- Yoon A!
- My gosh, amazing!
(Remarkable speed)
- Gosh, this is too fast.
- My goodness.
(Flying the sky in the zipline)
(Feeling the cool air with the whole body)
(Turning around because of the high speed)
(She holds the helmet in case it will be blown away.)
(Feeling at ease on the zipline,)
(it feels like they're flying in the sky.)
(Exclaiming)
(Bursts into laughter)
My goodness. This is amazing.
(The cool wind and the speed...)
(refresh their hearts.)
(Exclaiming in excitement)
(It's so cool.)
(Chuckling)
It's exciting.
- It's so exciting.
- I can't help screaming. It's fun.
(Their first flight was a success.)
- Please hold the line.
- Should I hold the line?
- Yes.
- Watch your head.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
My legs are trembling.
- I screamed because it was so fun.
- Wasn't it fun?
I know.
- My body was fluttering.
- I know, right?
- Didn't you spin?
- Right. I saw you spinning too.
Right?
So I speeded up like this.
(Chattering on like kids)
- It's exciting. It's really fast.
- It was so fun.
(Meanwhile, older brothers are...)
I think one of us will pass out.
- Why?
- Out of fright.
(Depressed)
- Okay, let's go.
- Yes.
You and I have been together for over 100 years.
It's our first time in 100 years.
(Go down safely.)
- Should I go here?
- Yes. Go up a step, please.
- My legs are already shaking.
- Please stand still.
(Dong Il gets nervous too.)
(Is Hee Won okay?)
- How can I do this?
- You can turn to the side.
- Like this?
- Yes, to the side.
- I see. Like this?
- That's right.
Look, he's already nervous.
(Touching)
- Is it safe?
- It's very safe.
(Don't worry too much.)
Are you ready to go now?
Yes.
- Yes.
- Stretch your legs.
- Oh, really?
Yes. 3, 2, 1.
Go!
(Descending into the distant forest)
(Exclaiming)
(Exclaiming in excitement)
(Excited)
(Letting out a loud roar)
Great!
(They slide over the mountain.)
- Great!
- My goodness.
(Excited)
(Screaming)
(His jacket is inflated with the wind.)
They started.
Oh, there they are.
(Welcome!)
Hee Won!
(Calling out Hee Won while holding his helmet)
(Closing his eyes tight)
(The speed is too high for him to open his eyes.)
(As you slide down along the hillside,)
(it feels like you're running in the sky.)
(Exciting!)
(Laughing)
(It's impressive all the way down.)
(Satisfied)
Amazing.
Dong Il, it's really fun.
- So good.
- Let's get going.
This is so cool.
Let's go.
- He looks like he's swimming.
- Oh, my gosh.
Let's get going.
(Sliding through the wind, Dong Il has safely arrived.)
(Hee Won also landed safely.)
Dong Il, this is so much fun.
- It's cool.
- Isn't it fun?
- Isn't it thrilling?
- Yes.
- So fun.
- It was fun.
- This is very fun.
- He was late.
I kept my legs stretched out.
- Did you do that?
- This is extremely fun.
- Isn't it?
- Yes.
I was wondering when you two screamed.
- I screamed as it's so fun.
- I know.
(Laughing)
Okay. Shall we go to the car now?
(Shall we go to the car and not ride this?)
(He must be more nervous alone.)
It's 1, 2, 3.
(Thud)
(Laughing)
Have fun and release your stress.
I will. Thank you.
It's 3, 2, 1.
Say, "hooray."
Hooray!
(Laughing)
(Byoung Cheol slides down relaxed, unlike others.)
(Good)
- Isn't Byoung Cheol coming?
- Is Byoung Cheol coming?
Where is he coming from?
- Goodness.
- Right there.
- Which side is it?
- He's coming over there.
Isn't he really fast, though?
- It's the left.
- Is he coming?
- Over there, on the right.
- He's there.
- The black dot.
- On the left lane.
(Byoung Cheol is sliding alone.)
(It's nice sunshine.)
(Although the speed is very high,)
(he looks over here,)
(there,)
(and up,)
(Byoung Cheol is enjoying the moments.)
He looks very comfortable.
He's just lying straight there.
Please hold the line.
(He's stretched out straight.)
It will be bumpy.
Welcome.
Hello.
(Hello, everyone.)
- Well done.
- How was it?
It was fun.
- Isn't it?
- Yes. It feels cool too.
- It was easy.
- Don't you feel fresh?
- Yes.
- That's amazing.
It's time to move. Let's go.
This one is long.
It is very long.
It is long.
(The longest course to enjoy the scenery of the archipelago)
- Shall we go first?
- Okay. Let's go first.
(Dong Il and Hee Won ride it first.)
Now, I feel...
comfortable to come up here.
(Bump)
I said, "Let's fixate it."
Please hold the line.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
- It's the longest course. Go!
(Dong Il departs the longest course after getting prepared.)
Hee Won!
Go!
(Dong Il departs comfortably shouting the brother's name.)
- Oh, my gosh.
- Hee Won!
(Oh, my gosh! Goodness.)
(Laughing)
Hee Won!
(They are excited.)
I find it relaxing.
Now I feel comfortable.
(It's comfortable as the speed is lower than the previous.)
(They are enjoying the spring breeze.)
(With the two arms wide open,)
(they are enjoying the silence of the mountain.)
(Over Mount Geumo,)
(the South Sea starts to appear.)
Hee Won, the view is so great.
(My goodness)
(Oh, my...)
(Blue ocean is spread below the feet.)
(The islands are like gems.)
(As if they have promised,)
(both are looking at the scenery silently.)
Dong Il, it's so nice here.
(Yoon A is also sliding...)
(with the breeze.)
(My gosh)
It's beautiful.
(The greenery of the mountain...)
Oh, my gosh. It's so beautiful.
(and the sky blue ocean make the magnificent scenery.)
(Staring)
(The beautiful scenery...)
(before the eyes draws all the attention.)
(Byoung Cheol, on the other hand, slides down relaxed.)
It's Hallyeohaesang National Marine Park.
A number of islands are located in the ocean.
(Official reporter of House on Wheels?)
As I look down there,
right next to the ocean,
fields and paddies are located.
Hallyeosudo looks...
like an Ink wash painting,
and it's very beautiful.
(He doesn't lose his elegance in 800m above.)
(It's already close to the destination.)
(Before letting it go,)
(let's take commemorative photos.)
(While sliding down excitedly,)
(Dong Il takes poses.)
(Its title is, "I hug Hadong into my arms.")
(Hee Won also takes his poses.)
(The title is, "Zipline is a must. It's so good.")
(Laughing)
Hello.
(Yoon A is too shy to take poses.)
"House on Wheels."
(She makes House on Wheels with her two arms together.)
Did you recognize it? It's House on Wheels.
(Did you recognize my House on Wheels?)
- Did you do that on your way?
- Yes.
(This is how Si Wan poses.)
Did they take photos of me?
(Its title is, "Fell into the beauty of Hadong.")
(Byoung Cheol comes in a modest pose.)
It's so cute. Did you see the photo of him?
You're not supposed to be that cute in photos.
Would I look cute indeed?
You are cute.
- Would I look cute?
- You're cute.
I enjoyed it thanks to you.
I had so much fun.
This was the best of this trip. It was fun.
(This will be a precious memory for a long time.)
It was a memorable trip, wasn't it?
- Hadong's zipwire.
- Wire.
(The members are on a new journey to the next front yard.)
- I had fun, really.
- Zipwire.
(This time, they go deep into Hadong.)
(They drive along the Seomjin riverside.)
(Expectant)
Is the river on the left Seomjin River?
- Look at that.
- Oh, my gosh. That is...
- It's very beautiful.
- It's cool.
- Seomjin River road.
- It's beautiful.
(It's today's fellow traveler to guide the members to the yard.)
The water is...
(Seomjin River, the cleanest water in Korea.)
(Its water even cleans out people's minds.)
Byoung Cheol, look how clean the water is.
I can see through the bottom.
Jeolla Province and Gyeongsang Province are...
divided by the Seomjin River line.
(Amazed)
Between Jeolla Province and Gyeongsang Province, right?
(South Jeolla Province, South Gyeongsang Province, Seomjin River,)
- It's amazing.
- It is, indeed.
(Seomjin River)
(I can't stop looking at it.)
(Route 19, along the Seomjin riverside)
- It's also beautiful here.
- Right.
Look at the tall trees.
(A woody pine forest)
(A sandy beach with various living things)
This is cool.
It's sandy here.
(Unspoiled clean nature)
(Byoung Cheol can't take his eye off of it.)
It's amazing.
Dong Il, isn't this beautiful too?
Dong Il, the land here must be fertile, right?
It must be very fertile.
(Fields in Pyeongsa-ri are green with the water from Seomjin River.)
It's really beautiful.
- Isn't it beautiful?
- Yes.
It's so beautiful.
Why haven't I known this place before?
There are many beautiful places in Korea.
Korea is a beautiful country.
(Seomjin River, our treasure, is more beautiful in person.)
What is that?
(Magnificent scenery is not done yet?)
Look over there.
My gosh. Look at that.
I prepared cherry blossoms for you.
- There are so many.
- On both sides. Look at that!
(My goodness)
(The highlight of Route 19)
Cherry blossoms start from here.
(What is up here?)
(The cherry trees are filled on both sides of our house.)
- This is wonderful.
- It's pretty.
(The roads are painted in pink in spring.)
(It's the most beautiful road in this season in Korea.)
It's beautiful.
(It's so beautiful.)
What should I do?
(House on Wheels is joining this endless pink wave.)
It almost looks like it's snowing.
It looks like snow, snowflakes.
(Cherry blossoms flutter like snow.)
I'm enjoying cherry blossoms to the fullest.
That sounds right.
(It's irresistible beautiful scenery.)
(So amazing)
(Welcome to the cherry blossom kingdom in Hadong.)
(It's time to meet today's front yard.)
There's a traditional market in Hadong.
It's one of the top markets in Korea.
What's the market?
- It's Hwagae Market.
- Hwagae Market.
- Jeolla and Gyeongsang Province.
(Jeolla and Gyeongsang Province...)
Do you mean that Hwagae Market?
- Yes.
- The song title, "Hwagae Market"
(Was that Hwagae Market here?)
Byoung Cheol and I will take a taxi...
after we buy...
some delicious things to eat.
- Isn't it known for marsh clam?
- It's known for it.
Marsh clam soup would...
I think the food in Namhae is delicious.
The land is good in Namhae.
Is this the market?
It's nice.
We will go grocery shopping.
- Have a nice shopping trip.
- Okay.
Have a nice one.
The reflection of the sunlight is beautiful.
(It's perfect weather to go to a traditional market.)
(Hwagae market)
Hwagae market.
(Welcome)
Have you been to this Hadong market?
- It's my first time.
- For real?
Yes.
- Isn't it cozy like the old days?
- Yes.
(Hwagae market, full of coziness)
There are so many things to eat.
That one? I see.
(Various vegetables from Mount Jiri)
It's so great here.
(It's full of fresh seafood...)
(from the clean Seomjin River.)
(Here's what caught Dong Il's eyes.)
What are the fries?
- It's fried sweetfish.
- Sweetfish!
Sweetfish is bigger than I thought.
Sweetfish lives only in the cleanest water.
It smells like watermelon.
(The sweetfish smells like watermelon.)
If there is trimmed marsh clam...
- Marsh clam?
- Yes.
Marsh clam. Have you had marsh clam soup?
I have.
- Isn't the soup so good?
- Yes.
With chopped chives in.
(It's a specialty of Seomjin River, chewy marsh clam.)
(Once it's boiled, it becomes savory marsh clam soup.)
(If it's mixed with spicy seasoning, it is spicy raw marsh clam salad.)
(My goodness)
Look at that.
It's a densely lamellated oyster.
Look how big it is.
It is big.
(It's too big to hold with one hand.)
It's called densely lamellated oyster...
because we eat them in the cherry blossom season.
- Because people eat when it blooms.
- Yes.
It doesn't smell fishy and it's tasty.
- I see.
- Do we eat the whole thing?
Sure.
It's huge.
(The specialty of Seomjin River)
(Densely lamellated oyster)
(It's 5 times bigger than regular oysters.)
(The milky clam only available in spring)
(It's even tastier when it's grilled.)
It's already appetizing.
(Me too)
- My gosh.
- Thank you.
(Today's plentiful dinner with marsh clams and oysters)
Traditional markets are...
more vibrant.
I agree. It's full of energy.
It's very vibrant, so I don't know...
- how to handle it.
- Right.
You're right.
(A calm place right in time)
What is this?
- Is it a forge?
- Yes.
(A forge in Hwagae market.)
Don't you love that sound?
I do.
It's the first time hearing it in person.
(This forge makes knives in a traditional way.)
(This is a freshly made knife in Hwagae market.)
Do you have a kitchen knife that's made here?
(Dong Il is looking for a new knife to use in House on Wheels.)
The knives we have are dull.
This looks good.
Do you need a knife at home?
I'm okay.
This looks inexpensive.
- That's a cheap one.
- It's a different one, I see.
(While the two are enjoying Hwagae market,)
(the three are driving towards the front yard.)
How long does it take?
About 10 to 15 minutes.
It's close.
(The front yard is not far from Hwagae market.)
This is the place with great mountains and clean water.
The place in that expression.
This seems to be the right place.
This is so nice.
(House on Wheels goes deeper into the mountains.)
(It's passing the cherry blossoms...)
(and getting close to the mountain.)
We must be going upward over there.
This place...
It's so nice here.
(Peekaboo of green tea fields, a specialty of Hadong)
Is it green tea?
Yes, it's green tea.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my...
The road here is very steep.
(Dizzy)
(Upward along the slope)
(Goodness.)
(My gosh.)
(Oh, my...)
(It's almost like climbing.)
(Shaking)
(Sliding)
(Driving the narrow and rapid slop...)
(and passing green tea fields,)
(when it's close to the mountain peak,)
It's beautiful no matter where I park here.
(today's front yard appears.)
(Today's front yard, Hadong millenary green tea field)
(Fresh green tea fields spread in the front yard)
(With a thousand year of history,)
(Hadong green tea field is...)
(home of wild tea.)
(Different from other regions, it's formed in the wild.)
(The tea leaves are grown with the gift of nature.)
(It's full of freshness.)
(The green tea field offers a nice walk environment.)
(There is a gazebo for the tea ceremony.)
(Today, we live in Hadong millenary green tea field.)
- It's so nice.
- It's nice.
- It's perfect.
- Good.
(Satisfied)
Oh, my gosh.
(Proud)
- Does it look good?
- Yes. What do you think?
Hee Won, come here and look.
Isn't it perfect here?
We have shade here.
- I see.
- Look. If we sit here,
we can enjoy the beautiful scenery.
- It's good.
- Isn't it?
- It is. It's good.
- Yes.
(Green tea field for a 1,000 year)
(House on Wheels surrounded by green tea fields)
(A perfect front yard with the blue sky)
It seems good. Perfect.
(It's nice.)
The wild tea trees grow...
only about up to human height.
Is that so?
It's here.
My gosh.
- My gosh.
- Hey.
Today's guest is here.
(Laughing)
- I will help you.
- You'll be surprised.
Look.
You bought a lot.
These are for Yoon A.
(My gosh!)
I'll show you something special.
Okay.
(Expectant)
You bought a lot.
- Fried sweetfish.
- What?
(My goodness!)
- It's very...
- My gosh!
Is this sweetfish?
(It looks delicious.)
It's sweetfish with a watermelon smell.
Have some now when it's warm. It's not delicious once it gets cold.
- Sweetfish?
- Sweetfish.
Look. Touch it. Isn't it warm?
(Staring)
- Goodness!
- You have to eat when it's warm.
And...
It's millet pancake.
It's very warm.
(Interested)
(Good)
The red bean pieces are big, like the old days.
- The whole red bean.
- Whole red bean.
This is an authentic mugwort rice cake.
That looks yummy.
Do you still need to eat dinner?
(These are snacks.)
Have some when it's warm.
We need to eat before it gets cold. Try it.
(Yoon A takes a bite first.)
They fried the whole sweetfish,
but I asked them to cut in halves as they were too big.
They did it for us. I haven't tried it, though.
I bought this too.
(Crunchy)
(It's delicious.)
(It's good.)
(It's a snack time altogether like a family.)
The meat comes out like this.
Eat this part.
- Take a look.
- Okay.
(Hee Won who drove takes a bite.)
Dong Il, it's delicious.
(Si Wan also rushes to take a bite.)
We don't care about table manners.
(After a bite,)
(Byoung Cheol enjoys the scenery.)
(A snack time in the painting-like front yard.)
I recommend this one.
It's with whole red beans. You have to eat when it's warm.
This is so good.
Have some, seriously.
Have some. It's so good.
Eat the center where there are most red beans.
Okay. I will.
(Savoring)
Isn't it so good?
(Byoung Cheol crumples his shoes.)
(Smiling)
(He takes a bite with a baby smile.)
It tastes like carp bread.
- Carp bread!
- That's right.
Hold it. Hold the left side.
- Where? Here?
- Yes.
Eat it.
(Eating)
(It's good.)
(Dong Il takes a bite too.)
(While everyone is laughing happily...)
- It's not even your family's?
- Why is he acting all poor?
(Poor)
(Lonely gourmet)
(He's so funny.)
I like this one.
There were a lot of millet pancake restaurants,
but only this place had people queued up.
- I see.
- Really.
I can see why.
Bean powder mugwort rice cake. It's like jelly.
(Delicious)
Gosh, this is so soft on the inside. Fluffy, right?
- It's really good.
- Yes.
(Fluffy)
(Byoung Cheol takes a bite too.)
(It's delicious.)
This is really good.
- It's sooft.
- Pardon?
Soft.
Your pronunciation is weird because of the rice cake.
"Sooft".
Even my pronunciation is soft.
- The mugwort rice cake is the best!
- Yes.
- It's so soft!
- The mugwort rice cake is nice.
I got a surprise for you.
Don't eat this.
Here, look.
(What is it this time?)
What oyster?
- Densely lamellated oyster.
It's freshwater oyster this big.
- Densely lamellated oyster?
- When the cherry blossom blooms,
- you eat this together.
- It's oyster,
- but from freshwater.
- Here.
- Oyster?
- Yes. Densely lamellated oyster.
- Look at the size.
- Gosh!
This is freshwater oyster.
(Amazing)
It's almost like a stone.
Do you like this, Yoon A?
Yes.
That was pretty slow.
- I like it.
- The reaction was slow.
- This is my first time...
- seeing a freshwater oyster.
- Me too.
- Really?
- Yes.
Now is the season.
When you come here,
everything's new, so you might get flustered.
This...
(It's too soon to get flustered!)
(Today's seasonal meal gifted by Seomjin River)
(The flower that blooms in Seomjin River, densely lamellated oyster)
(Marsh clams which are small but full of nutrition)
(Densely lamellated oyster bigger than a fist...)
(can be cooked directly on charcoal fire...)
(as barbecue.)
(Marsh clams with bouncy flesh...)
(can be boiled till the white soup comes out...)
(and become refreshing marsh clam soup.)
(And yesterday's front yard)
(Bamboos that spread densely across the mountain stream...)
(will meet Mount Jiri's black pork from yesterday...)
(to form bamboo black pork with green tea scent.)
(Amazing)
(Expectant)
(Look forward to the generous amount of Hadong's seasonal buffet.)
- Byoung Cheol!
- Yes!
I prepared something especially for you and Yoon A.
- Come here.
(What is it?)
- Just leave it, we'll do it.
- Okay.
- You guys are our guests.
- Yes.
We prepared a special space for you two.
Yes.
We're going to put black pork in bamboo...
- and boil it.
- Yes.
Then we're going to pick some new shoots...
and put it in there...
together with the pork.
Then the green tea scent permeates into the pork which tastes great.
- Yes.
- Pick some shoots...
and enjoy the place.
- Okay.
- Travel safe.
Don't become too close with each other.
Of course. Social distancing.
(Yoon A and Byoung Cheol head to the picturesque green tea field.)
On the hill,
- there's a green tea field.
- A green tea field. Gosh.
Have you been to a green tea field before?
I've been to one near Mount Jiri.
- Near Mount Jiri?
- Yes.
It's so pretty!
(Let's get down to business and pluck some leaves!)
Tea leaves...
How do I know which are new shoots?
(Something small and shiny like this is new shoot.)
(High-class tea Oujeon is brewed using new shoots like this.)
(Made with new shoots that grew up first in early spring,)
(Oujeon tea is known for its soft and gentle taste.)
- I see.
- It's here.
- These must be new shoots.
- Amazing.
You're right.
- They...
- About this big?
You're so good at picking them.
(The guests search for new shoots here and there with effort.)
It feels like I'm already brewing tea.
You're right.
(Their hearts feel refreshed as they pick the shoots themselves.)
(A gift-like time provided by the front yard)
We need to start with charcoal fire. That's the urgent one.
(On the other hand, the family starts preparing for dinner.)
We should hurry up because we don't have time.
Once the sun sets...
(The sun is already setting behind the mountain.)
(Safely filmed with the permission of the landowner)
(He hurriedly puts charcoal on fire to cook dinner quickly.)
(He makes faint charcoal fire for bamboo black pork.)
(Meanwhile, the assistant chef checks the kitchen first.)
(What does he have his eyes on?)
I should wash it now.
(The knife they bought at the forge in Hwagae market)
(The assistant chef's task is to wash the chef's knife beforehand.)
Gosh, the knife is so cool.
(The chef's knife is put on hold.)
(Chef Sung finally makes his way into the kitchen.)
You should hurry up, or the sun will set.
(What is the first ingredient to prepare?)
(Mount Jiri's black pork belly)
Gosh, where is the knife we bought?
I already washed it.
- Good, as expected of Si Wan.
- It's here.
(It gets cut so easily.)
Korean knives are the best.
- It's so sharp.
- Gosh.
(Thick)
(For thick meat, you must score it.)
(He thoroughly scores them so the green leaf scent is permeated well.)
Gosh, the scores.
(He measures the size against the bamboo.)
(He cuts them to match the size.)
(He cuts them up into big chunks.)
(Amazing...)
Hee Won's guarding right beside me.
It's reassuring.
This is what family is, isn't it?
Of course, Dong Il.
- You can do it. Should I peel them?
- This...
- Cut off the tips.
- Okay.
(Hee Won's task is to prepare garlic to put into the bamboo.)
(Focused tips of his lips)
(Meanwhile, the main chef...)
(is massaging the black pork with salt.)
(He pours salt on the cutting board.)
(He turns the meat around and coats the outside with salt.)
(Grinding)
(He grinds pepper onto the cutting board as well.)
(Knocking)
(He starts preparing for bamboo black pork in earnest.)
I should wrap one with chives,
and wrap another one with water parsley.
(2. Black pork with water parsley)
(Hee Won is done with preparing the garlic.)
(The garlic Hee Won prepared)
(Once he pushes it in deeply,)
(bamboo black pork is ready to go.)
It will be so amazing that you'll be at a loss for words.
(Swallowing)
(The guests come back after plucking tea leaves.)
It's so familiar.
You must've had a good time.
We had a good time indeed.
(He washes the tea leaves from the front yard cleanly...)
(and gently puts them on the black pork so the scent can get on it.)
I put them in.
- Then wrap it with the foil.
- Yes.
Use three pieces of aluminum foil.
3? 1, 2, 3 layers?
Yes, three layers.
Square shape, 3 to 4 pieces.
Cover it in layers and wrap it with wire.
(Halt)
(Well...)
(He enters with an important task.)
Hee Won. You're okay, right?
(Sickly)
You got an important task.
- Pardon?
- You got an important task.
Exactly. You know what will happen if this gets punctured, right?
I know.
(The most important task is given to Hee Won.)
(Very careful)
I can fold it like this, right?
Yes.
It will be fine even if it's a bit thick, right?
Must the shiny part face outside?
This side is shinier than this side.
Is it like this?
It's fine, it doesn't matter.
- It doesn't matter?
- No.
(He carefully folds it neatly.)
Fold it like this.
Okay!
(Next, he prepares wires to tie the bamboo.)
(Sniff)
(Surprisingly, this is 10 times the original speed.)
(What is another menu he's preparing?)
Marsh clam that Byoung Cheol likes!
Let's just go ahead with it.
(Smiling with his eyes)
There's a lot of marsh clam.
This is no joke.
(Full of bouncy marsh clams)
(I'm so excited.)
- There's a lot.
- There's a lot. Really a lot.
(The assistant chef in charge of preparing ingredients...)
(cuts chives to put into marsh clam soup.)
(Marsh clam soup is ready to go as well.)
This is rice, this is marsh clam...
Everything's ready, right?
(Not yet, Dong Il.)
Just two rounds of wire will be enough, right?
Yes, as long as it doesn't come off.
I'm worried that it might.
I've never been so nervous before.
I must make sure there is absolutely no gap in between.
Absolutely no gap.
(Holding it in place with his feet)
(He uses both his hands and feet.)
(You guys are almost done, right?)
- You guys are almost done, right?
- Yes.
- Almost done, right?
No.
Which way... This way.
- I'll hold it here.
- And you...
(He blocks the opening thoroughly.)
There's no way it will leak out if it's this tight.
(Don't worry, I'll protect the meat juice.)
This is more than enough.
Are you constructing a building?
Dong Il, this will never come off.
That's more than enough.
(No, I can't stop here.)
He has a callus on his hands.
This is nothing.
Gosh, this...
My goodness.
(He's really amazing.)
Have you been to a green tea field before?
- Yes, I've been to one before.
- I see.
- But this is my first time...
- Like a staircase.
- coming to one this steep.
- Staircase.
- On the top, there's a gazebo.
- Gazebo.
From there, the view is really nice.
Is that so?
Hee Won, hurry up. He says the summerhouse view is good.
It's really good.
Let's put the bamboo inside...
and go up there to see.
I don't think one round is enough.
(He can't hear Dong Il.)
One round is enough. It's enough.
Hold this side...
and pull it tight. No, pull it once more.
Pull that side. Yes. Turn it.
- Gosh.
- This is...
Gosh, this is...
I'll cut it.
This is almost like a pressure cooker.
It's done.
(Groaning)
(He used up all his energy on covering the bamboo.)
What is he even making that he's doing that?
I finished so many tasks already and am chilling around.
(Groaning)
Dong Il, high-quality products cannot be simply made.
But you did do really well.
- What?
- You really did well.
High-quality products cannot be simply made.
I should put them in now.
(The bamboo goes right into the charcoal fire.)
How long did we cook last time?
Quite long.
Right? It needs to boil,
and it has to be cooked on the inside.
(The rest of the bamboos get into the charcoal fire as well.)
(While the bamboos Hee Won put in so much effort get cooked...)
Did you put cheese in dried persimmon?
- Right! Should I do that?
- Should we do that now?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Actually, I eat this every day.
Really?
My mom always prepared this as a dessert.
- Really?
- Yes.
(I should step up again.)
My gosh, amazing!
(What is the first ingredient of Hee Won's dessert?)
(Yesterday, as soon as Byoung Cheol arrived at the empty house,)
(he took it out from his bag...)
(and put it carefully in the fridge.)
(Byoung Cheol's housewarming gift, homemade ricotta cheese)
(A picture taken by Byoung Cheol himself)
How did you make the cheese?
I've never seen someone make cheese at home before.
I also only learned it a week ago.
Really?
I searched it up on the Internet.
(Homemade cheese Byoung Cheol made for House on Wheels...)
(and dried persimmon from Hwagae market)
(They will make sweet and salty dried persimmon cheese roll.)
I saw this every day. Can you put it here?
You need to put in cheese here.
(Yoon A puts Byoung Cheol's cheese in dried persimmon.)
(She rolls the dried persimmon.)
Then you need to...
cut it like this.
(The point of dried persimmon cheese roll is the pretty cross-section.)
(Fascinated)
This is stunning.
(Put them on the plate nicely, and dried persimmon cheese roll's done.)
Byoung Cheol made delicious cheese.
(Byoung Cheol is stretching.)
I need to stretch my back.
Just lie down.
(I'm tired.)
(Today was a busy day where he rode a zipline and went shopping.)
(How does Byoung Cheol stretch to relax his tired body?)
(Stretching his legs)
(Stretch)
Gosh, you're so flexible.
(Laughing)
Can you do a split?
(Meanwhile, Dong Il stays in front of the fire.)
(Is it done now?)
(The bamboo with green tea scent is steaming.)
Give me chopsticks.
Gosh, this...
(Half expectant, half worried)
(He pokes in to see if the inside is cooked.)
(Let me see...)
So hot!
I think it's successful!
- That?
- Yes.
(Bamboo black pork with green tea leaves will be revealed soon!)
I succeeded again.
Pass me a pincer to cut off the wires.
I'm so curious about the meat.
The meat is the most important.
This is the most important.
- We're holding an opening ceremony.
- This is making me nervous.
(In the tense atmosphere, he finally opens it.)
(Staring)
What's that?
Oh, this?
This is meat.
(Laughing)
I put the meat in the bamboo.
You used wires for that.
Yes, I asked someone who works with wires for 30 years for help.
- He wraps bamboo as a profession.
- I see.
- This is so funny.
- Here.
He's so doubtful, why did he wrap so many wires?
- Let's check the meat.
- I think the meat's cooked nicely.
- Really?
- Yes.
(He opens the bamboo black pork with water parsley.)
(Come out.)
It's cooked, it's cooked! It's cooked, Byoung Cheol!
- Yes.
- It's cooked!
(Deeply moved)
Gosh, this is perfect.
- This will be really tasty.
- Yes.
(Bamboo black pork with gentle green tea scent)
It's boiled pork.
(He opens the black pork with chives as well.)
Because the bamboo is burnt, it's stuck to the meat.
(He puts down the tool and uses his hands this time.)
He pulls it out with his hands...
and dismantles it for us.
He dismantles.
(How will the black pork with chives look like?)
(Amazed)
(Humming)
(Moist and juicy bamboo black pork)
The chives... Look at this.
(Well-cooked chives)
(Fascinating)
(Really astonished)
Should I cut it thickly?
Yes.
What about Byoung Cheol?
- Slightly Thick?
- Yes.
- Slightly thick.
(He cuts the meat as per the guests' preference.)
- Gosh, the scent!
- Goodness!
(Amazing!)
(Oh my goodness.)
- It's cooked.
- Gosh.
I thought it would be red inside.
This will cook.
(Contrary to their worries, the pork is well-cooked till the inside.)
It looks so good.
- It's really tasty.
- My gosh.
This is seriously tasty.
Let's eat while it's still warm.
(Youngest Yoon A takes a bite first.)
Careful. It's really juicy.
It looks so good.
(This... This is...)
You can talk and eat slowly.
(How good is it that you're acting like this?)
It's so delicious. Seriously!
(Amazing!)
- Is it that good?
- Yes. Really!
- Really?
- Yes!
Move back. Now, Byoung Cheol!
(Next, Byoung Cheol takes a bite.)
- Try it.
- Is it good?
It's seasoned really well.
I seasoned it a bit.
- I can taste garlic as well.
- It's delicious.
(Is that it?)
(Gasp)
(Amazing!)
(That's the taste.)
(Shy)
We should eat this while it's warm.
It's really tasty.
This is that.
This is water parsley.
(His eyes become wide open.)
This is unbelievable. It's so good.
What kind of flavor is this? This is insane!
Try this. It's water parsley.
Can you taste water parsley?
(Simply nodding)
(Intense humming)
- Right?
- Gosh!
(It's really delicious.)
- It's good, right?
- Yes.
- Is that all?
I want to live like him too.
You could be like him.
Not making expressions like this.
- It's tender, yet chewy.
- Right.
- It's very firm too.
- Yes, it's tender, yet chewy.
This has chives.
(Next is black pork with chives.)
We should've put angelica leaves in there.
And fatsia shoots.
Yes, we should have.
(We should've included my cheese too.)
This is a different cut.
- It's very juicy inside.
- There are chives in it?
Yes, it has chives.
It's juicy, right?
(Curious)
(This is it.)
(This is the one.)
It's different from the other one.
Right? Of course it's different.
- It tastes more smoked.
- It does?
- This tastes more smoked?
- I'll step aside.
Is it that good?
- It's good.
- It's really good.
- Is it good?
- How is it?
- It tastes like...
- Does it taste different?
- It tastes like it's smoked.
- So I guess...
- it tastes different.
- It tastes like it's smoked.
(He feeds the members after feeding the guests.)
Here.
It's really good.
Take the whole thing. There's a little piece here.
(He fixes his gaze at the pork.)
How is it?
It tastes different!
- It tastes different, right?
- Yes.
I can smell the chives.
(Gulping)
Let's get ready to eat now.
(He got playful.)
(Sulking)
(He gives a piece to Hee Won who worked hard.)
It tastes different from the previous one.
It tastes like smoked pork.
It does taste like smoked pork.
- It's good.
- It's really good.
(The bamboo black pork even makes Hee Won excited.)
I'll grill the densely lamellated oyster now.
Just one shell takes up the whole space.
(The size of the lamellated oyster is huge.)
I don't think it'll work.
No.
Could you not make that noise?
Why would you make that sound when we're cooking?
I'll try not to make the sound.
Pass me the chicken towel.
- Pass me the chicken towel.
- "Chicken towel"?
- I meant paper towel. I'm sorry.
- It's paper towel.
I can't pronounce the words well...
- with Yoon A next to me.
- He asked for a chicken towel.
Yoon A, it's how we're always like.
I'm so jealous. I love it here.
This is... Look at this, Yoon A. It's marsh clam soup.
Smell it.
It smells refreshing. There are chives in it too.
- Gosh, it smells like the ocean.
- We'll add some pepper too.
It's not from the ocean. It's from fresh water.
Goodness, it smells like fresh water.
(Changing her stance instantly)
You can suddenly smell the ocean?
But he said they're not from the ocean.
(Moving the marsh clam soup to the table)
It smells like fresh water.
(The densely lamellated oyster is starting to get cooked.)
Look at it steaming.
(Opening the well-cooked oyster)
(Exclaiming)
(Their jaws drop.)
(Golden brown)
(The meat of densely lamellated oyster...)
(that's as big as a fist)
(Just two pieces of the oyster fill the entire dish.)
(It's too big, so he cuts them into small pieces.)
- Gosh, it's hot! It's so hot.
- Be careful.
Gosh, it's hot.
There. Let's go.
(How will the dinner filled with Hadong's seasonal dishes be?)
It looks so good.
(It's time to enjoy the feast.)
It's the best dinner we've ever had.
(I need to take a photo of this.)
Let's try it.
- Thank you for the food.
Try them.
(A table filled with Moun Jiri's local specialties)
Hurry up and try them.
It won't be as good if it gets cold.
Go ahead and eat. Eat the pork first.
Try it.
Byoung Cheol, hurry up and eat.
(Yoon A tries the piece of pork.)
- Is it good?
- Yes.
It's good.
It's well-seasoned.
(Byoung Cheol smells the food first.)
- Right?
- It's so good.
(They put in lots of effort into the bamboo black pork.)
It's good.
The meat is so good.
- Is it?
- Yes.
(Sniffing)
It smells so good.
(It smells really nice, right?)
Carry it around to smell it.
- Try this.
- It smells so good.
(The scent of bamboo and green tea sipped into the meat.)
It's good.
It's really surprising.
(He's touched.)
- The meat is so good.
- Right.
(The black pork is soft and tender.)
- Goodness.
- It's really good.
The meat smells amazing. It's really good.
- The pork is...
- Also...
(Getting up)
This is grilled garlic. Try this.
(Having a piece of garlic)
(Garlic, bamboo, and green tea add more flavor to the pork.)
The garlic isn't strong at all.
It doesn't smell like garlic at all.
(Exclaiming)
It doesn't smell like one, right?
It tastes like a potato.
- Hee Won, - It's so good.
it doesn't smell like garlic at all.
It has its scent. Try it.
(Exclaiming)
(Glancing)
Why would you study my face when it's good?
- Hey.
- It smells like garlic a little.
(I'm being honest.)
(It does?)
I need to stir it like this. Clams are piled up at the bottom.
Add some pepper.
(Adding pepper...)
(and chives with much effort)
(He's busy.)
There's a line of customers, so eat it up fast and leave.
Okay, okay.
We need our customers to eat fast.
(Dong Il's marsh clam soup restaurant is doing really well.)
You're busy all alone.
My son is here to help though.
- Oh, he's your son?
- Yes, he came to help me.
What are you saying, sir? When are you going to pay me?
You punk. That's not a thing to say to your father.
How dare you.
(While the members are putting on a skit...)
- Here. Yoon A, you have it first.
- Thank you.
When are you going to pay me?
(Let me try it.)
(Exclaiming)
Here. Let's try it.
(Si Wan slurps in the marsh clam soup.)
(Impressed)
It's so good.
(The owner slurps in the soup too.)
The soup is so good.
It's good.
It's really refreshing.
(The marsh clam soup is neat and refreshing.)
(He takes a piece of marsh clam...)
(and tries it.)
The marsh clam...
tastes like rockfish.
It's crunchy.
- It's really chewy too.
- Right.
That's how marsh clam tastes.
(Byoung Cheol carefully takes a bite of the soup.)
- There's so much in it.
- I think you spilled it on me.
(This is so good.)
(He drinks the soup from the bowl.)
(Exclaiming)
(Having another sip)
(He's gulping down the soup.)
We should give the whole pot to Byoung Cheol.
He loves marsh clam.
(I love marsh clam.)
Byoung Cheol, eat a lot.
Okay. Thank you.
(Have a lot, Byoung Cheol.)
It's so warm and nice.
(He's totally in love with marsh clam.)
This is grilled oyster.
- Try the grilled oyster.
- It looks good.
It looks so good.
My, it looks so good.
We should try the grilled oyster.
Try this. Dip it in chogochujang.
(Dipping the well-grilled oyster...)
(in chogochujang)
(Having a big bite)
Si Wan, it's good, right?
(Thumbs-up)
It's the best.
- Is it okay?
- Yes, it's nice.
(He takes another bite because it's so good.)
It's really chewy.
(The oyster is tender and sweet.)
- We don't need to season it, right?
- No.
It's seasoned well enough.
(It's savory even if you don't dip it in chogochujang.)
It's good.
(It's really good.)
(You can't skip on rice when you have all these side dishes.)
(Exclaiming)
(Gulping)
It looks really good.
(They made rice with multiple grains today.)
It's different from other rice.
- I know. It's nutritious rice.
- It is.
It has all the healthy grains.
- Yes, it has everything.
- It's nutritious rice.
- It looks good.
(Blowing)
(Amazed)
It's really good.
It's a little dry.
I love it.
Do you want to add margarine to it?
That sounds nice!
Dong Il loves margarine.
I used to live next to an American army base when I was young.
If you mix margarine and soy sauce with rice, it's incredible.
- It's better than anything.
- You need to add margarine...
- when the rice is hot.
- Here, here. I'm sorry.
(The margarine lover came back at lightning speed.)
- You need to add it when it's warm.
- Right.
Here, add some.
(Add the margarine.)
Margarine goes well with pretty much everything.
(Adding a spoonful of margarine)
(He's adding that much?)
Are you frying the rice? Are you going to fry it?
- You can add this much.
- Add the soy sauce.
That's enough. You need to add only a little.
Look at the margarine melting.
- It melts in no time.
- It really does.
- Of course.
- It's because I brought it fast.
(But there's still a lot of margarine.)
You can just leave out a chunk if it doesn't melt.
(Laughing)
(He takes a bite as he's worried about its taste.)
(Amazed)
This is it.
You can leave out the chunk.
(He returns the margarine he took.)
He took out some margarine, and it's this big.
(I told you. You added too much.)
It tastes too greasy already.
(He's regretting it.)
Let's have it with margarine.
(Nodding)
(The savory scent of margarine is added to the chewy rice.)
This is incredible, Dong Il.
Let's have the pork on top of this.
(The delicious rice stimulates their appetite again.)
(Having a big bite)
- This is really good.
- I know.
It's so good.
(The top-quality side dishes taste even better with rice.)
If you're enjoying this much, that means it's really good.
The food combination is really funny though.
We're having marsh clams with bamboo black pork.
We basically traveled from the top of the mountain...
to the deep water.
From the top of the mountain.
(A gourmet tour that ranges over the mountains and rivers)
The dishes are perfect for spring.
Right, they're perfect for spring.
(She's happy.)
I ate so well that I feel like the trip was therapeutic.
I enjoyed visiting the places too.
Thank you so much.
(Thank you for making all these dishes.)
- Seriously. It's so good.
- It's not over yet.
We have to eat the dried persimmons.
- There's still more? We ate a lot.
- There's a lot more to eat.
Why are you thanking us already?
Thank you for everything you did up until now.
I'll thank you more later.
- Of course.
- Okay.
I thought you were leaving without eating the dried persimmons.
(Of course I should have it.)
(Having the dried persimmon roll with cheese...)
(with sujeonggwa that helps with digestion)
(Working hard)
(Adding pine nuts as a decoration)
I should make one more thing.
(Kneeling...)
(like a lady)
(Adding a spoon of ricotta cheese)
(Adding another spoon)
(Adding three spoons in total)
(Focusing)
(Pouring a bowl of sweet honey)
(It's done!)
(Getting a tissue)
(He wipes it clean for the finishing touch.)
(Meticulous)
(A special dessert prepared by the guests)
- It looks good. There's honey...
- It feels like a cafe.
and cheese too. Goodness.
(With sweet and salty honey and cheese,)
Byoung Cheol. Goodness.
(they're having rolled dried persimmons in sujeonggwa.)
The white thing here is ricotta cheese.
And I added a bit of honey...
that I brought yesterday.
When you have a bite, you'll be able to taste...
the sweet and salty cheese. I added some nuts too.
You can have it like this.
(Graceful)
(It looks good.)
It's savory and sweet.
It's salty too. There are many flavors.
(Even his description is graceful.)
That's what tteokbokki tastes like.
(Laughing)
Savory, sweet, and salty?
It's salty too.
This is amazing.
(Yoon A also has a bite of the cheese gracefully.)
(How does the honey cheese Byoung Cheol made taste?)
(Impressed)
It's good.
Wow, this is a really good dessert.
I know.
(It's delicious.)
- It's really soft.
- It's soft, right?
It's really good.
Thank you.
It tastes like an expensive dessert.
Right.
It's really good.
(Having sweet dried persimmon roll...)
(with salty cheese)
(They pleasantly end their meal with a delicious dessert.)
It's good.
I'll hold it.
(Looking friendly)
(Smile.)
1, 2, 3.
I had so much fun thanks to Si Wan.
My goodness. Not at all.
(They made another great memory at Mount Jiri.)
(House on Wheels is on Jeju Island.)
(The 10th front yard of House on Wheels...)
(is surrounded by woods.)
(He's finally here.)
(It's really good to see him.)
(The original youngest member, Yeo Jin Goo)
(He grinds coffee beans after a long while.)
(He sets up a tarp after a long while too.)
(The four of them enjoy off-roading.)
(Jin Goo, keep your guard up.)
(Shaking)
(Grunting)
(Jin Goo is still a good cook.)
(Slurping)
(It's the best ramyeon in the world.)
(I'm so happy today.)
(The complete members of House on Wheels...)
(will have another enjoyable trip next week.)