♪Oh rebirth♪
♪Oh rebirth coming soon♪
♪When the afterglow of the sky
illuminates the horizon♪
♪Let the darkness retreat
and light appear♪
♪Even if you are towering
and proud to the extreme♪
♪I will also step on bones
and ride the wind♪
♪Oh legend of rebirth♪
♪Don't let yourself forget♪
♪Coming soon♪
=The Gold Behind the Stone=
=Episode 19=
(300 million?)
What?
You're scared to death of the price?
That friend of yours, Mr. Mo, must have
run away in fear.
I... I'll cover you,
so you can escape.
It's not that bad, Sister Wan'er.
(His right hand has recovered?)
You're so pretentious.
If you can't afford it,
you'd better admit it.
(Although the skin of this stone
looks ordinary,)
(there are hidden signs of blackness.)
(The flat reveals old texture)
(and good transparency.)
(It's a rare piece of imperial green.)
(It's worth it.)
(It's truly worth it.)
(It's just that Mr. Mo is not here.)
Don't hold on to it.
You don't have the face for it.
Unless this piece is full green,
it's not worth 300 million.
It's too risky.
I won't bet on it.
If you can't afford it,
you have to admit it.
Do you have the nerve
to blame the stone?
Don't you want
to show off your wealth?
What's that got to do with
the quality of the stone?
Exactly.
That's the lesson I want to teach you.
You gentlemen,
even if you're rich,
you can't buy indiscriminately.
Otherwise, you'll be treated
like a sucker
and a big fool.
Nonsense.
Keep pretending.
So speechless.
(This is a very rare violet jadeite)
(from the Pakan field in Mian.)
(The flat shows a deep purple color.)
(Not bad.)
(It weighs...)
(It weighs about 18 jin.)
(Purple is also called "Chun"
in the jade industry.)
(It should be)
(a pinkish purple color in this stone.)
(The price tag is...)
(500 million)
(The price tag is 500 million?)
Are you going to buy it or not?
- No money, no time-wasting!
- Exactly.
(This stone is so big.)
(If I buy it,)
(I should make more than 500 million.)
(But...)
(But where's Mr. Mo?)
(I don't have any money with me!)
What?
Are you going to lose money
even if you buy this one?
Why don't you give up all three pieces?
Just say you don't have any money!
Wan'er,
I really don't understand.
How could you fall for
such a liar and pauper?
I really doubt...
I also doubt
whether I'm your biological child
or not.
You...
Anyway,
if he says it's no good,
it's just not good.
I trust him.
Sister Wan'er,
buying this piece can be profitable.
- It's just...
- It's just that he has no money!
He finally admitted it.
Why pretend to be rich when you're not?
He doesn't even look at himself.
- Yes, indeed.
- Why pretend?
Young Master,
I've just finished buying that piece.
Here's your card.
Mr. Mo,
what did you
just call him?
Mrs. Su,
I forgot to introduce you.
This is our Young Master.
Mr. Mo's Young Master?
Wei Jianhao,
since your backup has arrived,
with your current wealth,
you should be able to afford it.
Mr. Mo,
this piece is marked
at 500 million yuan.
Your centurion card
has no spending limit.
Buy it.
My dear,
don't buy it
if you'll lose money.
It's worth it.
This one's different from that one.
This one can make a lot of money.
Don't have to check the rest.
Go on.
Keep pretending.
I'll see how you'll end up.
My dear,
why don't you check that piece
before deciding?
What if you lose money?
I mean, I won't buy the other one.
Come on!
I really find it meaningless
to compare
who's the richest like this.
I feel like
a rich douchebag.
I really don't understand
why you rich kids
have to develop such a habit.
Mrs. Su,
I suddenly feel that I don't need
to prove to you
whether I have money or status.
The reason
why I am willing to buy this stone
is because this is a charity sale
run by Mr. Su.
As for what you think of me,
it really doesn't matter
to me and Wan'er.
Mr. Mo,
buy it.
Yes, Young Master.
Wei Jianhao,
don't act like it's real.
Your money is
from your lovers, right?
What do you mean?
I just asked around,
and it turns out you're the grandson
of the Ye family.
I knew that
no good can come
from a bad family.
You're just like your sister Ye Sijie.
Even though you're rich,
you're worthless.
By the way,
I also heard from Ye Sijie
that you gave your own sister
to the Su family's fool
in order to get in touch with them.
The money you're holding now
is your sister's usual charity, right?
You're quite amusing,
taking the Su family's money
and acting like a lord.
Young Master Bai,
you're disrespecting
the Su family's guest.
You're just the president
of Chongjiang Jade Association.
If I'm polite to you,
you've forgotten your own status.
You...
Mr. Mo!
How dare you touch my people?
Today, you'll meet your end here.
- My dear!
- Wan'er!
Mom!
It looks like you want
to burn me to death.
Burn him.
Burn him!
Molten Flame!
Domain!
How dare you resist
my second realm's blazing flame
with only an air shield?
I've never seen this before,
so I'm letting you
run around a little longer.
Control.
How can you control my fire?
Impossible!
What kind of mysterious skill is this?
I learned a lot of skills
the other day,
but I've never used them.
Would you like to experience them?
Explode!
Where did it explode?
Where's my fireball?
Useless.
Bluffing...
Don't make the domain so large.
The smaller it is,
the more explosive it is.
(So that's how it works.)
(But why is there a delay?)
Oh my.
What's going on?
Isn't he already in the second realm?
How could it be...?
Am I blinking?
Is it possible that this person
has already reached the third realm?
Nonsense!
Only the heads of major families
can really reach the third realm.
How could
such a young lad possibly do it?
But he used just one finger
to defeat someone in the second realm.
You are not in the second realm.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Although I don't have much affection
for the Ye family, I don't want to see
something people like you
insult it at will.
Also,
you shouldn't have mentioned my sister.
So...
Is he going to kill with his finger?
Stop it!
Wan'er, tell him to stop!
My dear, you can't kill him.
How dare you!
I'm the Young Master Bai.
I told you to stop the nonsense.
Hurry and go to the hospital!
Be quick!
Take him to the hospital!
Hurry up.
Aunt,
he hit me.
- He tried to kill me!
- Go to the hospital.
Go...
He was still struggling when he fought
the Judge before,
but now it seems
that the Ever Realm
not only healed his injuries
but also allowed him to level up.
If he truly is the domain master
of Ever Realm,
his real abilities are far beyond this.
It seems like it's time
to meet with him.
How dare you injure someone
from the Bai family!
Mrs. Su,
can't you see that he started it?
So what?
How can someone
like you disrespect the Bai family?
So, Mrs. Su, you mean
I should have just stood there
and let him beat me to death?
It's disrespectful to strike back
at a man of honor?
You beat Ge like this.
The Bai family won't let you go.
We, the Su family,
won't let you go either.
My dear,
don't be afraid,
I will bear it with you.
Mrs. Su, I think
Bai Ge was right.
People with money
aren't necessarily worth it.
That should be you, Mrs. Su.
Sister Wan'er, rest assured.
I'll still help you,
but I can't stay
in this place any longer.
Are you
my real mother?
You're siding with this brat
to bully your mother!
Are you really my daughter?
I hope
I'm not.
What are you doing?
Today, you have to
get engaged to Chase Rodford family.
From now on,
you're not allowed
to see that rascal again!
Wan'er, are you okay?
Where is Wei Jianhao?
I told him to get lost.
What now?
Aunt Bai,
I told you,
he's an honored guest
invited by Grandpa.
Grandpa already knows about the mess
you two made just now,
so you have
to give an explanation today.
Alright.
I happen to want to ask Master Su,
why he allows a brat
to bully our Bai family.
Wan'er, are you alright?
Dad,
do you know what you've done?
Are you questioning
why I kicked that poor guy out?
He severely injured Bai Ge.
And instead of stopping him,
you came to question me.
How dare he beat up someone
from our Bai family?
Not to mention in the Su family.
Don't you think
that those people outside
will think that
Su family is easy to bully
and even a brat
can mess with us?
Do you know
why I had to come to Chongjiang
to hold this betrothal banquet
instead of in Jinling?
Because of that brat?
He has no family background
or connections.
Ge is countless times better than him.
He can marry the Su family,
but our Bai family can't.
What a joke.
Use your brain
and think it over carefully.
If he's really just
a poor kid with nothing to lose,
why would President Mo
of Jade Association
call him Young Master
and why would Mr. Mo give him
500 million to buy stones?
That's because
his Grandpa is Wei Changming.
♪The last time I met you♪
♪Time slowed down♪
♪I understood♪
♪That I must confess to you♪
♪My youth and my romance♪
♪Have all flown away with you♪
♪My fantasies and my recklessness♪
♪Have all melted because of you♪
♪My tears and my smile♪
♪Have all been warmed by you♪
♪My skies and oceans
have been kissed by you♪
♪With different colors♪
♪As long as I have you with me♪
♪Enjoying our own sweetness♪
♪Even at the end of the world,
we can hear♪
♪Our song♪
♪My tears and my smile♪
♪Have all been warmed by you♪
♪My skies and oceans
have been kissed by you♪
♪With different colors♪
♪As long as I have you with me♪
♪Enjoying our own sweetness♪
♪Even at the end of the world,
we can hear♪
♪Our song♪