♪Oh rebirth♪
♪Oh rebirth coming soon♪
♪When the afterglow of the sky
illuminates the horizon♪
♪Let the darkness retreat
and light appear♪
♪Even if you are towering
and proud to the extreme♪
♪I will also step on bones
and ride the wind♪
♪Oh legend of rebirth♪
♪Don't let yourself forget♪
♪Coming soon♪
=The Gold Behind the Stone=
=Episode 24=
Tang Wan'er,
come out!
Aunt Bai.
Mom, what are you doing here?
Is she your mom?
Hello, Aunt.
Call me Mrs. Su.
Who are you to get close to me?
That's it.
You don't remember me?
The only one I can remember now
is Sister Wan'er.
Only Wan'er?
You've lost your memory,
why do you still remember her?
Look at you,
you're even worse than before.
What right
do you have
to be with our Wan'er?
Mom, he's the one I like,
can you stop being so snobbish
towards him?
Am I wrong?
He was poor
and unsophisticated before.
Now it's even worse,
and he doesn't even have a memory.
What's the difference
between him and a fool?
Don't talk about him like that!
Sister Wan'er,
don't argue with your mom because of me.
Truly, a grown daughter
can't be kept at home.
He hasn't said
he'll be responsible for you yet,
are you so anxious to protect him?
Without the antidote,
he'll never get his memory back.
Do you want to live with such a fool
for the rest of your life?
Mom,
can you get the antidote for him?
Why should I help him?
I've already made a deal
with Young Master Chase.
He's willing to forgive
your previous mischief,
and
he's also willing to engage with you.
I don't want to marry him!
Is it that marrying
Young Master Chase will...?
Sister!
Aunt Bai,
why did Wan'er come to Chongjiang?
Why did she run away
from home for two years?
It's because
you had to force her
to marry someone she didn't want to.
So don't threaten Wan'er with this.
She won't go back with you.
You're not welcome here.
Please leave.
Alright.
If Wan'er doesn't want
to go back with me today,
I won't force her.
But please recognize the situation.
The great families of Chongjiang,
led by the Ye family,
have already sided
with the Chase Rodford family.
Do you still want to rely on this fool?
He can't protect himself anymore.
(Chongjiang Jade Street)
Even if you go back now,
Young Master Chase is so cunning.
You might not be able
to get the antidote.
What to do then?
Who... who let you in? Get out!
I have important information.
Excuse me.
From what I've seen,
as soon as Gu Dan returned,
not only was he overly concerned
about Jianhao's poisoning,
but Qing'er
was also missing.
Based on what I know of him,
he's got a problem.
After Qing'er's disappearance,
I sent someone to look for her.
Why don't you suspect
that Gu Dan likes Qing'er?
Impossible.
I'm quite familiar with his tastes.
(Gu Dan not only knows
about the basement,)
(he also knows about the Wei bloodline.)
(He's definitely coming
for the Ever Realm.)
(But how did he know about it?)
(Could it be that
the Chase Rodford family sent him?)
According to my speculation,
he's an undercover agent
sent by someone else.
He's ostensibly being nice to Qing'er,
but he's actually
prying for information.
Dare to play undercover in front of us?
I...
I'm going to kill him.
Stay calm.
With Gu Dan's intelligence,
why don't we
play an infernal game with him?
You're not on the same side?
Of course not.
Previously,
I was deceived by his rhetoric.
Moreover, as the sister-in-law,
how can I just watch him
take away Qing'er?
I'm the former sister-in-law.
Is there a problem?
He's
mine now.
(The Chase Rodford family
has made their move.)
(It's too dangerous for Jianhao now.)
(I won't let anything happen to you.)
Alright.
Young Master Chase
is underestimating us
by placing an undercover agent
beside us.
It's a hard time.
Let's put aside
our personal feelings
and be united to fight.
I hereby announce
that the Traitor Elimination Plan
has officially begun.
Let's call ourselves,
the Sister-in-laws' Alliance.
What are you doing?
(Chongjiang Jade Street)
(Why do I remember)
(there is something important)
(to me here?)
(What is it?)
It looks much more comfortable this way.
(That Xia Changyin is really...)
(Why are there so many stones here?)
(What exactly is)
(the Ever Realm they mentioned?)
Ever Realm,
where are you?
Can you
sense me?
Help.
Help!
Say it.
Who sent you to be an undercover?
Ladies,
what undercover?
Qing'er is missing.
Where did you take her?
Also,
why are you investigating
the entrance to the basement
and the Wei bloodline?
How do I know
where she is?
All I know is
that the Chase Rodford family
is sending a master of the fifth realm.
Hasn't Chief lost his memory?
I was afraid
he wouldn't be able to fight,
so I asked a few more questions.
Is it really necessary to tie me up?
How did you know the Chase Rodford family
was sending someone?
When did you collude with them?
I...
Collude with them?
Still pretending to be confused, huh?
Wan'er.
Pretty boy,
if you lie,
I'll scratch your face.
Don't...
This face is all I have left.
Let's talk this over.
Please don't make a move.
I'm sick of your face.
Wan'er, slice him.
Xia Changyin,
you wicked woman!
How ruthless you are.
Didn't we just break up?
You don't have to retaliate
against me like this, do you?
Stop morally blackmailing me.
You want the top
or the bottom?
Choose one.
I want both.
Then tell me,
who ordered you to come here?
I think you'd better confess.
Who is it?
Grandpa...
Is Brother Wei here?
Grandpa, save me!
Why has Mr. Gu come?
Take him to the basement.
Okay.
Brother Wei.
Mr. Gu, why are you here
all of a sudden?
I heard from Gu Dan
that Brother Wei had been poisoned.
I came to see him.
What a coincidence.
He just went to the hospital.
He's not here?
A rat
was just caught.
It seems I've come at a bad time.
I'll come back later.
Take care.
Wei Jianhao died of poisoning?
You rascal.
You rascal,
why are you like this again?
Weren't you already better?
Wake up.
Don't make me a young widow!
Stop wailing!
You'll kill him if he doesn't die.
There's a heartbeat.
He's passed out again.
We'll cultivate together.
There are so many people here.
How did you get down?
If you want to buy a stone,
please look upstairs.
I don't buy stones.
I'm looking for someone.
Who are you looking for?
I'm looking for someone
who can open the entrance to Ever Realm.
(Why does that voice sound so familiar?)
There's no one here you're looking for.
You're so pretty,
and you're lying.
You'll get beaten for lying.
Being unreasonable
is the only way to get beaten up.
If you don't want to be thrown out,
leave now.
Want to fight?
You'd better not.
If you're afraid,
then get out.
I'm afraid I'll hit you too hard later
and cripple you all.
Then I'll cripple you.
(Wan'er is already in the first realm,)
(yet she can't even touch)
(this mysterious man.)
(Could this person be
in the third realm?)
The pressure
of the fifth realm?
The person I want to find
has already been found.
I won't play with you anymore.
Wan'er, be careful!
♪The last time I met you♪
♪Time slowed down♪
♪I understood♪
♪That I must confess to you♪
♪My youth and my romance♪
♪Have all flown away with you♪
♪My fantasies and my recklessness♪
♪Have all melted because of you♪
♪My tears and my smile♪
♪Have all been warmed by you♪
♪My skies and oceans
have been kissed by you♪
♪With different colors♪
♪As long as I have you with me♪
♪Enjoying our own sweetness♪
♪Even at the end of the world,
we can hear♪
♪Our song♪
♪My tears and my smile♪
♪My skies and oceans
have been kissed by you♪
♪My sky and ocean have all been♪
♪With different colors♪
♪As long as I have you with me♪
♪Enjoying our own sweetness♪
♪Even at the end of the world,
we can hear♪
♪Our song♪