♪Oh rebirth♪
♪Oh rebirth coming soon♪
♪When the afterglow of the sky
illuminates the horizon♪
♪Let the darkness retreat
and light appear♪
♪Even if you are towering
and proud to the extreme♪
♪I will also step on bones
and ride the wind♪
♪Oh legend of rebirth♪
♪Don't let yourself forget♪
♪Coming soon♪
=The Gold Behind the Stone=
=Episode 13=
How is that possible?
You're only in the first realm.
Brother.
Chief!
Still want
to fight?
You can fight me
when you're stronger.
Go back and tell Mr. Ye
that Qing'er will never return
to the Ye family.
Young Master.
They've gone.
Why don't they show up?
- Wei Jianhao.
- Brother, how are you?
- Chief.
- Quick, go inside.
- Be careful.
- Slow down.
- Hurry, be careful.
Hurry.
(Wei Shop)
Brother,
are you in pain?
It's just a small injury.
It's nothing.
Don't worry,
it's almost healed.
You call this small injury?
Chief,
you're playing it cool with your life.
I'm really worried.
You're even coughing up blood.
Hurry and go to the hospital with me.
Why are you worried?
I'm just concerned.
Aren't you worried about him?
(How dare)
(the Judge hit him so hard!)
Brother,
thank you.
I'm your brother.
What are you thanking me for?
I need to heal him,
it's not convenient to be seen.
All of you
can go rest now.
I'll take care of this.
Do you know how to heal?
My master is a miracle healer.
Trust me.
We don't know if you can heal him.
We want to watch.
Do you want to see him naked?
Can you heal him?
Should we go to the hospital?
Trust me.
Let's go.
Let's go...
- Go!
- Don't push me.
Go on.
Mr. Mo.
- Take me to the basement.
- Okay.
Come.
(There's a basement here.)
(Wei Jianhao is going)
(to the basement to heal his injuries.)
(The entrance to Ever Realm)
(should be down there.)
Young Master,
I'll stand guard up there,
don't worry.
Why haven't I been sucked in yet?
Is it
because my Jade Buddha hand is crippled?
That's not right.
The last time I was crippled,
it was my right hand as well.
The entrance to Ever Realm
can only be opened by the bloodline
of the Jade Buddha Hand's heir.
(Wei Shop)
Indeed, it's the aura of Ever Realm.
Qing'er,
you came in a hurry.
I'm sure you didn't bring anything.
You can wear this pajama for now.
Tomorrow,
I'll take you to buy a new one.
Thank you,
Sister-in-law.
I'm not.
I just saw you always
protecting me in front.
You were more nervous than I was
when my brother was hurt.
I thought you two were already...
Your brother hasn't
taken a liking to me yet.
Let's go.
I'll show you your room.
Brother Dan,
think about it.
The bumpkin and Ye Qing'er are siblings.
Isn't he the Young Master
of the Ye family?
Then why do the Ye family's men
still dare to hurt him?
Now you know he's the Young Master
of the Ye family.
You regret calling off
the engagement, don't you?
I...
Not at all.
What kind of person do you think I am?
He was definitely kicked out
by the Ye family.
Otherwise, why wouldn't he
dare to go back?
You want to marry him
as the Ye family's Young Mistress?
Keep dreaming!
You...
So annoying.
Who wants to marry him?
(Even if he was kicked out,)
(he's still a member of the Ye family.)
(He's still better than Gu Dan.)
The Ye family won't let it go.
Wei Jianhao can beat them off this time,
but he may not be able
to do it next time.
We need to find a way
to get into the basement
and move all the stones out.
This room belongs to Qing'er now.
Get out.
Why should we give you the room?
We're already sharing one room.
Where else can we move to?
I don't care.
You two can go wherever you want.
You...
Should we give up?
It's okay.
Alright.
It's up to you.
Let's go.
- No way.
- Let's go.
What are you doing?
No way!
Why should we give it to them?
There's hope for us
to live in the basement.
That's not right.
Last time, I just touched it,
and the injuries healed when I went out.
Change one.
Why is there a tortoise here?
There is also a...
Who is the tortoise?
You are the tortoise,
you brat.
Who is it?
Why are you insulting me?
You called me a tortoise.
Is it wrong for me to call you a brat?
You're just a tortoise,
with a snake on the body.
It's called Black Tortoise.
Have you heard of Black Tortoise?
You are illiterate.
Black Tortoise?
Vermilion Bird's husband.
Black Tortoise!
Black...
Senior.
Senior?
Senior, are you still there?
Did I say something wrong again?
You really are
the grandson
of that rascal Wei Changming.
You piss me off to no end.
You know my Grandpa?
I'd know him if he was a ghost.
Did he offend you?
Can you not irritate me
with Vermilion Bird and your Grandpa?
It sounds like you have
some stories to tell.
Talking about them brings tears.
I don't have time to chat with you.
I can't say much,
and I have to be dormant again.
Senior, are you going to sleep now?
I have to go to recover from injuries,
you fool.
How come you and your Grandpa
have such different ways
of making people angry?
Senior, are you injured?
I've been recovering
on the Blue Planet for 100 years.
Tell me,
how do you want me to help you?
You can help me?
Then my injury...
If you touch
the snake head behind me,
I'll give you some energy.
Then I'll recover?
How do you think
you recovered last time?
Last time,
I touched that stone,
not only did I recover from my injury,
but also my left hand
had its powers activated,
and I reached the first realm.
That's what I did with the stone.
It took a lot of effort.
Can't you just take a few more steps
and come over to touch this snake head?
Thank you, Senior.
I don't know how to repay you.
Then just collect more jade.
Put them in the basement.
The better the jade,
the more energy I will give you
in the future.
Is that possible?
No wonder my Grandpa
put so many stones in the basement.
Alright,
I'm tired.
After you touch the snake head,
just leave.
Thank you, Senior.
I'll do my best.
You seem more sincere than your Grandpa.
I'll give you some extra energy
to help you break through.
♪The last time I met you♪
♪Time slowed down♪
♪I understood♪
♪That I must confess to you♪
♪My youth and my romance♪
♪Have all flown away with you♪
♪My fantasies and my recklessness♪
♪Have all melted because of you♪
♪My tears and my smile♪
♪Have all been warmed by you♪
♪My skies and oceans
have been kissed by you♪
♪With different colors♪
♪As long as I have you with me♪
♪Enjoying our own sweetness♪
♪Even at the end of the world,
we can hear♪
♪Our song♪
♪My tears and my smile♪
♪Have all been warmed by you♪
♪My skies and oceans
have been kissed by you♪
♪With different colors♪
♪As long as I have you with me♪
♪Enjoying our own sweetness♪
♪Even at the end of the world,
we can hear♪
♪Our song♪