Well...
Check the back of the couch
and the crack.
Okay?
Take it seriously.
Maybe
it's because of the dim light.
We all drank a lot.
Maybe someone
put it
in her own bag
by mistake.
Check your bag
and see if it's in it.
Look closely.
Open your bag
and check it.
(It happened just as I expected.)
(It was not)
(a victory party,)
(but a class reunion.)
(Liu's jade pendant)
(somehow)
(popped up in my bag.)
It's in my bag.
How could you
steal from your roommate?
No, I...
I didn't take it.
I don't know
why it's in my bag.
It can't be Qian Wei.
It's a misunderstanding.
It's obviously a misunderstanding.
We all drank a lot.
And the light
is dim.
She must've taken it
by mistake.
All right. All right.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's just a misunderstanding.
(Liu certainly trusts me.)
(But the scary thing is)
(that after that night,)
(people started
to spread rumors at school)
(that I was caught stealing)
(because my father is sick)
(and my family has no money.)
(Liu Shiyun)
(forgave me in the spirit
of being a bigger person.)
What is she doing here?
As a thief, she still joined
the Municipal Merit Student Selection.
Does she have no shame?
What happened?
She is the one
who stole stuff.
Why would she do that?
(There were even people)
(posting blogs anonymously
on Renren.com.)
(The story gets weirder.)
(I want to clarify it,)
(but it's hard to prove
that I didn't do anything.)
(How should I prove)
(that I didn't?)
(Qian Chuan)
(What to do now?)
(We have to do something about it.)
She's the one who stole stuff.
(You won't know how scary)
(rumors or cyberbullying are)
(until you experience it.)
(I quit)
(the Municipal Merit Student Selection)
(of that year.)
(I almost got depressive
and hid at home.)
(Rumors ran wild.)
(But there were still people
who can tell the truth.)
(Clarification)
(They secretly put up a notice for me.)
(It was the only light)
(in those dark days.)
(Clarification)
=Legally Romance=
=Episode 17=
=Fight Back Rumors=
Not in the toilet.
No?
That's weird.
The jade pendant was lost twice
with different causes,
at different times,
and different locations.
The people involved are different, too.
But the same thing
is that Liu met Mo Tao,
and Mo Tao gave Liu a hand.
The 18-year-old Qian Wei
was an innocent girl
who just swallowed it.
But now
I won't let this happen again.
I'll teach him a lesson this time.
Qian Chuan.
Pass me the bag.
Here.
If I'm guessing it right,
the jade pendant
should be in my bag.
You know what,
the strange thing is
when I left home this morning,
I just felt that the universe
snapped its fingers again
in my head.
I knew someone
would set me up
today.
Liu, do you trust me?
Of course
I trust you.
What happened?
I don't know.
But I think
we'll find it out soon.
Little girl.
You're a law school student.
Don't be so superstitious.
You sound like a fortune teller.
Since we found it,
you should have fun now.
Everything is just fine.
All right?
I have other things to do.
I got
to leave.
Mo Tao.
You didn't do it, did you?
Zixin.
What are you talking about?
What does this have to do with me?
I
met you
and bought you and your classmates
drinks with good intentions.
What's wrong with that?
The two of them
went to the toilet together.
How would I know
what they were doing in the toilet?
Watch your mouth!
Young man.
Don't be so angry.
I still have
a business meeting.
You can't afford to delay me.
Business is not important.
So
there is still no one to admit
putting the jade pendant
in my bag, right?
It's okay.
Let's call the police.
With the camera and the fingerprints,
it's easy to find out.
This is a victory party.
There's no need to do that.
It's just a misunderstanding.
If the police come,
we're not going
to be able to sleep tonight.
I think
you law school kids
are just
melodramatic
and troublesome.
We've found the jade.
We all drank a lot.
It's very normal.
It should be a happy thing
for you to hang out together!
Why do you have to
make it awkward?
All right. All right.
Have fun.
Don't bother with such a little thing.
No way.
No one can leave this room
before we find out
who did it.
Otherwise, this misunderstanding today
will become the story
that has been spread for long
in school tomorrow.
Sir.
Especially you.
You can't leave this room.
Little brother.
I have a business to deal with.
Don't be childish.
I said you can't leave.
Qian Chuan, close the door.
Check it carefully.
The crack and other places.
Look closely.
And the back
of the couch.
See if it's in there.
Look closely.
Maybe it's too dark here,
and someone put it in the bag
by mistake.
Or
you can check your bags.
Mo Tao!
Do you have no shame?
You stole from my friend!
No.
I didn't steal.
Well,
how can you
call it
stealing?
Her jade pendant got loose
and fell off.
I took it
so it wouldn't break.
But she got drunk.
I worried she would lose it.
So I put it back.
How can that be stealing?
Stop making excuses!
I'm not making excuses.
All right.
Don't give me that look.
Listen,
Mo Zixin,
if you promised
to give me my money back,
would we be
in such an awkward situation?
- Are you trying to hit me?
- Don't move! Don't move!
See?
He started first.
I'm going to defend myself!
How dare you
sling mud at me!
You are a criminal suspect now.
You can talk
after I bring you to the police station!
No,
wait!
Sir.
How am I
a criminal suspect?
You must be kidding.
Mo Zixin is my younger sister.
My biological sister.
I don't know him.
Wait,
wait!
Speak up for me!
Listen,
if I go to jail,
your father will call you from jail
and ask you
to get me out.
Say something!
You deserve it!
Come on.
We're family. Stop the nonsense!
That's embarrassing!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
It's Mo Tao's fault.
He deserves
to be punished.
Fortunately,
you didn't lose the pendant.
Otherwise,
I really don't know
how to face you.
It's fine
that Mo Tao
acts like a rascal to me.
I can't believe he did this to you guys.
If our classmates
know it,
what would they think of me?
You are
not him.
This has nothing to do with you.
But they will know
that I'm no longer
a rich girl,
but the daughter
of an economic criminal.
Isn't your father
a stock market expert
who published a book?
He was.
But later
my father was convicted of bribery
and manipulation of securities markets.
He got arrested.
The perfect life
I used to have
just burst
like a bubble
on that day.
Because
he was arrested abroad,
and it involved trade secrets,
the case wasn't released to the public.
Plus, news didn't spread
as quickly as nowadays,
so a lot of people
don't know it.
But I didn't mean to lie to you.
I just don't want too much attention.
I don't want to tell other people.
I don't want them
to take pity on me
or look down on me because of that.
It's your privacy
anyway.
You have every right not to tell us.
What's more,
you are so sweet and beautiful,
and you have good grades.
You made your first bucket of gold
in college
by investing in stocks.
Even without a great family background,
you're still an excellent person.
Who are we
to take pity on you?
Yes.
I'm not going to hold him accountable.
No.
It's not fair
to you and Qian Wei.
I'm okay.
I have no hard feelings.
You know what,
I have an accurate sixth sense.
I'm one of those people
who can make lemonade
when life gives me lemons.
Don't think
that I have hard feelings.
Listen,
don't be sad.
Right now
my sixth sense
is telling me something
again.
I'm telling you
that you will become
an extremely
excellent woman one day,
a gentle,
beautiful and generous woman.
And
you don't even need a rich boy,
you can be rich
on your own.
You'll be a strong woman.
That's right.
Thank you.
Thank you, Shiyun.
You're welcome.
How's it?
Who stole it?
Xun.
What's going on now?
Can we leave?
I have classes tomorrow.
Actually,
no one stole anything.
Sorry
that I kept you waiting.
Then why did you call the police?
Such a hypocrite.
What do you mean?
Who are you calling a hypocrite?
Calm down.
Who stole it?
Not your sister.
Liu Shiyun decides to let it go.
Just forget it.
Just forget it?
The jade
was found in my sister's bag.
If we don't find the thief,
what will they
think of my sister?
I'll talk to Liu.
It's your sister's decision.
Can we control
what other people say or do?
Trust me.
I'll do everything I can in my own way
to protect her.
I won't let her get hurt.
(The merit student-to-be
turns out to be a thief.)
(Reveal the true colors of Qian Wei,
a top student of grade 11 in law school.)
Stop.
Stop watching it.
What are you watching it for?
I haven't replied yet.
Why would you reply?
I'm not even angry.
What are you angry about?
Well,
follow me.
Don't be angry.
If you get angry, devils get hungry.
How can I not be angry
about it?
Not only that I should be angry,
I'm also going
to vent your anger for you.
It's fine that it affected
the Municipal Merit Student Selection,
now rumors are spreading on the Internet
that you stole stuff
because your father is sick
and your family is poor.
Your family
has been brought into this.
How can you still be so calm?
And Fawei Online...
I know.
Professor Zhang and Mr. Zhen
told me about it.
In this case,
if I don't fix this,
it will affect teachers' opinions of me.
What's more,
it will also affect
the Fawei Online review.
Then why are you still so calm?
What can I do?
I can't be sad
about something
I didn't do.
Listen,
you can't
let these things
affect your moods.
These bystanders
are just fence-sitters.
Especially those who started the rumors.
They want me
to be upset
and in a bad state,
so I will quit the selection.
But I won't.
If I knew the public opinion
would become like this,
I wouldn't have let you drop the case.
I know you're worried...
All right.
Now that I've dropped the case,
it means
I'm ready
to take the consequences.
I also hope
you won't let this
affect your moods.
How can I not be affected?
It's hard not to be affected
when there are rumors.
You, Qian Chuan, Liu, and me,
which one of us is not going to be hurt?
It's a good thing
that you don't let
public opinion influence you.
But we can't let it
escalate
in the wrong direction.
Right?
All right.
Time is up.
Now I'll explain these questions.
Come on, everyone.
Keep your heads up.
In this multiple-choice question
of theft,
many of you
missed choice A.
Let's see what choice A is.
(Which of the acts constitutes theft)
A college student
was eating in the canteen.
Student A usually saves the seat
with phone and wallet first
before going to buy meals.
Student A's friend, student B,
took the wallet used to save the seat,
which of course constitutes theft.
Therefore, everyone,
don't be misled
by the so-called friendship
in this question.
Sir.
I have a question.
Does it need
behavioral evidence
and outcome evidence
to convict student B of theft?
Of course.
If someone spreads rumors
about student B
committing theft
without evidence,
does it constitute
an infringement of reputation right,
even defamation in serious cases?
That's right.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just think
this could be
a key point in the Judicial Examination
next year.
I hope you don't forget.
Okay.
That's it for this question.
Let's see the next one.
This is the Qian Wei I know.
Everyone, look at it.
Listen to me.
It's really a key point
of next year's Judicial Examination.
It's the most important right
in the property right in work.
When the copyright legal system
was built...
The right to privacy...
I posted a clarification online.
But an anonymous account
opened a new topic
and said
Qian Wei not only
stole the jade pendant,
but also stole my phone
to whitewash what she did.
What's wrong
with that person's brain?
There she is.
That's the one.
Let's go.
Wait.
She's not a thief!
What are you looking at?
Come back!
(Clarification)
(The truth is as follows...)
(A witness of the event.)
It's this clarification again.
Again?
I mean,
how can
there be such a kind person?
It's a friend.
Looks like
there are sensible people in our school.
What?
After my analysis,
I think
this statement
is logical
and sharp.
His
written communication skills
are excellent.
The style of writing
is also great.
I believe this kind man
will become
a great lawyer
one day.
Cool.
Right?
(Clarification)
(Printing Center)
Stop.
I knew it was you.
Great style of writing.
Logical and sharp.
Don't you hate
street posters the most?
Now you put them up everywhere.
I'm helping our classmates review
the General Principles of the Civil Law
and the Criminal Law.
Fine.
You're stubborn.
Sop putting up posters.
I'll turn you in right now.
As the light of law school,
you took the lead
in breaking the school rules.
I mean,
it's fine
that you don't want to explain.
But how can I not explain?
I'm your boyfriend.
Can I watch those people
throw dirt at you,
spread rumors about you
and make jokes?
No matter how terrible the rumor is,
just give it two weeks.
Two weeks later,
people will lose interest.
Then they'll look for
new rumors.
I think
the most important thing right now
is to focus on
finding the person
who started the rumor.
All right.
I'll keep putting up posters
for another two weeks.
Overruled!
It was you
who clarified the truth for me silently
at that time.
It has always
been you.
Don't be too grateful.
Just buy me milk tea.
Okay.
I'll buy you milk tea.
How many cups?
Half a cup.
I went to the teacher
and thought maybe the school
could issue an official clarification.
But the teacher asked me
why I dropped the case
and what happened exactly.
Who stole it?
I can't tell you.
But it has nothing to do with Qian Wei.
I dropped the case
because I didn't want it
to become complicated.
But I didn't expect
it to turn out like this.
Do you know Les Misérables?
It's Victor Hugo's work.
A world classic.
Jean Valjean
stole a loaf of bread
in order not
to starve his sister's child.
Later,
he stole silver and escaped from jail.
What is stealing
compared to survival?
Hugo would turn over in his grave
if he heard what you just said!
I'm the one who lost a jade pendant,
which was put on renren.com.
I've posted a clarification.
Why are you still
stirring up trouble?
Liu.
Please be civilized in public.
We are having an academic exchange.
Do you want to join us?
Do you know
Bakerhaas's swan experiment?
A swan placed in a flock of geese
couldn't fly up
from the ground.
Because opportunities and environment
would determine a person's
room for growth
and the way he behaves.
Family background
often determines fate.
You...!
Liu.
You're too simple
and you always trust
the people around you.
You don't know that humans
are complicated in nature.
You...!
Qian Wei's father is ill
and her family needs money badly.
We feel sorry for her.
But,
she stole from her roommate
to deal with her emergency.
She should pay the price.
The worst case
is that she gets disqualified
from the Municipal
Merit Student Selection.
Nonsense!
I think you want to get a hit!
Apologize.
Why should I apologize?
Go away!
Apologize!
What does it have to do with you?
You won't apologize?
Then you're responsible
for what you said,
this classmate.
Apologize?
You want me to apologize?
Ms. Wu.
If he
doesn't apologize first,
to Qian Wei,
and to all the students
who believe
that knowledge can change their fate,
I'm not going to apologize.
Li Chongwen.
What's wrong with you?
All the teachers and students
who know you told me
that you're
a gentle
and mature student.
What's wrong with you today?
If you can't come to an understanding
with the student who was beaten,
you'll get a demerit.
With your resume,
it's a done deal for you
to graduate
as the Municipal Outstanding Graduate.
I can give up
honors and scholarships,
but he
must apologize!
I'll call your parents.
Ms. Wu.
There is no need to make a phone call.
No one will answer it.
His father died young.
His mother
is working elsewhere
and not at home.
Over these years,
I've been taking care of him.
I'm kind of his parent.
Just talk to me.
Mr. Zhang.
Li Chongwen is a promising student.
But hitting people
is against the school rules.
Ms. Wu.
What about that guy?
He spread false statements
and defamed Qian Wei.
Is that in accordance
with the school rules?
Lu Xun!
How can you use a mistake
to cover up another mistake?
Then it depends on
which mistake
is more serious.
It would determine a person's
room for growth
and the way he behaves.
Family background
often determines fate.
This video
wasn't just posted on renren.com,
but also on Weibo.
Many people are waiting
for the school's response.
Our school launched
humanized subsidies
for poor students earlier,
and it had an overwhelming response.
But if this event
is handled sloppily,
if you only punish Li Chongwen
and turn a deaf ear
to the allegedly discriminatory remarks
that magnify the gap
between the rich and the poor,
what do you think
those netizens will react?
I also came from a poor family.
I need to talk
to this student.
I've been teaching for years,
but I've never done anything immoral
for fame and money.
What's more,
Qian Wei is also my student.
He accused Qian Wei
of stealing without any evidence
and even got her sick father in this.
In this case,
you should also ask
his parents to come.
Did he
start the rumors
on the Internet first?
No.
Mr. Zhang.
I heard about it
from my students.
He followed suit and made comments.
But he didn't start the rumors.
Ms. Wu.
If that person
wants to hold Li Chongwen responsible
for civil liability,
tell them to contact me.
I'll get Li Chongwen
the best lawyer.
What are you thinking?
Let's go.
Goodbye, Ms. Wu.
So cool.
Thanks.
For what?
I should thank you.
Isn't it your style
not to give others
a break?
You two said everything.
What should I say?
It wasn't the guy who posted it.
I know.
But it's okay.
We're gonna find out who did it.
I got water into your computer earlier,
and your glasses were broken today
because of me.
Sorry.
Let me help you.
Not just me,
and them.
Come on, Qian Wei!
(Protect the rights of Qian Wei)
Come on! Come on!
You got our support!
(Internet rumors)
Come on!
(Granny's pension)
(The Qian Wei we know)
(Sweat factory Laws and regulations
Protect rights)
(Qian Wei is innocent Support Qian Wei
Reliable evidence)
Sister, come on!
(Qian Wei, come on)
Come on, Qian Wei!
(The swimming team
fully supports Qian Wei)
(Say no to rumors and cyberbullying)
Qian Wei.
We've had debates with you
many times.
Will we be afraid of this?
The Guanghua Debate Team
volunteers to join the battle.
You're
under our protection.
Those who use rumors
to hurt others
will get hurt by rumors in the end.
The voices supporting
Li Chongwen on renren.com
are the best proof.
Public opinion
is a double-edged sword.
Why can rumormongers use it,
but we can't?
Am I right?
Yes!
Qian Wei, you got our support!
- Support Qian Wei!
- You have a point!
Support Qian Wei! Support Qian Wei!
Okay.
I won't put up with them this time.
Come on, Qian Wei!
Come on!
You can do it!
Come on, Qian Wei!
(The wise doesn't buy rumors,
but should we stop the rumors?)
(Law students)
(all have a strong sense of justice
and they are ready to help the weak.)
(We can't)
(pull out a knife
when we see injustice,)
(because it's against the law
to use a knife.)
(But if we can't even)
(make sounds,)
(if we can't tell what's right
and what's wrong,)
(if we let the rumors run rampant,)
(how can we face our conscience)
(and say we believe in justice?)
(Clarification)
(Qian Wei.)
(Mo Zixin)
(I also want to help.)
(I can afford to suffer some damage)
(in order to fight with them.)
(But if it will hurt you,)
(I'd rather not fight
this public opinion war.)
(Don't get yourself in this.)
(I'll leave the debate team to you.)
(You got my back.)
(We are in this together.)
Mr. Zhang.
Here is a document for you.
Why are you
delivering the debate team's
training records recently?
Where is your team leader, Qian Wei?
Is she fooling around in school
with the team members again?
They are busy putting out fires.
As for the debate team,
I'll do as much as I can
to help.
What?
There are people
putting up posters in school?
Tell me where it is.
I don't have a choice.
Now that I'm on your boat,
I have to work with you guys.
Hurry.
Okay. Thank you, Mr. Zhang.
Mr. Zhang!
I'm on my way out to catch them.
Why did you lock the door?
Well,
my bad.
That student
just got me
all confused.
I thought there was no one in there.
Wait a moment.
Let me find the key.
Hurry up, Mr. Zhang.
I just put it here.
Where is it?
Wait.
Hold on a second.
Hello.
Shiyun.
You should leave now.
Stop putting up posters.
We've been reported.
I'm going to tell Qian Wei
and others now.
Don't worry.
I know what to do.
Lu Xun.
We've been reported.
They're coming now.
Where is Qian Wei?
Qian Wei!
Hurry up.
All right.
Don't rush me.
Hold on!
The teacher is coming.
Hurry.
Get in there.
I haven't put it up yet.
Where?
Are you sure
we should hide in the toilet?
It's the ladies' room.
I don't think you should be here.
What can I do?
Get in.
Stop talking.
There's a door.
Get in there and hide yourselves.
Don't worry.
Don't make any noise.
I'll deal with the teacher.
No,
wait.
Mo... Mo Zixin...
(Cleaning Tools Room)
Ms. Wu.
You...
Mo Zixin?
What are you doing here?
Our club has an activity today.
I'm putting up
(Guanghua Comics and Animation Club)
posters for the Comics and Animation Club
in the Art Festival.
Ms. Wu, take a look.
In this way,
we can let more people
know about the two-dimensional world.
Are you here alone?
The other students
are changing in there.
We'll have a rehearsal later.
Well, Ms. Wu.
You seem to be interested
in comics and animation, too.
Mr. Zhang
has promised us
to be a guest actor.
Do you want to try
the Shana of the Blazing Eyes?
I'll dress you up.
Have a try!
Your hair will look good
in that look.
I don't think so.
No, no, no.
Ms. Wu!
Don't you want to try it?
Is she gone?
What?
I...
Well.
Listen.
We should
find a way
to get rid of these things,
or we can hide them on us.
Well,
you have a thick waist.
Hide them on you.
Then even if
the teacher finds us,
there will be no witness
and no proof.
Right?
Otherwise, we will get caught
with the posters.
Look.
Well...
Hurry up.
My waist is thick?
Hurry!
Don't talk.
Cover them with your clothes.
Okay, okay.
I can do it.
I'll do it myself.
Hurry!
Hold this for me.
You must be quick.
You know.
Listen,
you can
also loosen the belt
and put some in there.
Is there no other way?
There is no other way.
What else can we do?
To eat them?
Isn't this too much?
Can you put them in the back?
In the back?
I won't watch.
When I walk on the street,
it will make me look...
You won't walk on the street.
You can cover it up
with your coat.
My butt will look bigger.
Am I entering a beauty contest?
You can do it.
You'll look sexy.
Hurry.
Just tell the teacher
you've been working out.
Hurry.
Do you have to
insult me
when you put things on me?
Qian Wei.
I won't watch.
I won't watch. Hurry.
I think it's enough.
It can't fit more?
Let me do it.
Come on.
No.
Listen.
Don't move.
It's here.
Here!
Come out. The teacher has gone.
Well...
We're destroying the evidence.
Yes.
I'm also
working out my cute butt.
Zixin.
Thank you today.
Otherwise,
the whole debate team
would be caught.
It happened
because of me.
Actually, I owe you
an apology.
But putting up posters
won't solve the problem for good.
What are you going to do next?
We put up posters
to let these rumormongers
feel that this event
is beyond their expectations now.
They're flustered now,
and they will create
more rumors crazily.
If that person continues
to spread rumors,
these rumors
will become less credible.
If he still doesn't
want to give up,
he will have to
stand out and find a way to stop me.
Look.
We flushed
this rumormonger
out today.
We have the number of the person
who reported us,
and we know when and where
he made the call.
It's probably someone
in the debate team.
It's very possible
that the person who reported us
is the one who posted rumors online.
Anyway, Liu
went to check
the Internet protocol address.
The Education Department
should also have caller ID.
If we follow the clues,
we will find him anyway.
The rumor counterattack
is going to succeed!
If that person
is in the debate team,
I think I know who it is.
Hello.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Well,
I'll go to the police station first.
Wu Zhongyou was transferred
to the detention center?
The police told me
the results of the investigation.
Wu Zhongyou
contacted me
after he saw the information
on Fawei Online.
But he didn't see it
from the website.
Someone gave it to him.
It's Yu Tian.
Mo Zixin and Liu
also found out
the number of the person
who called the Moral Education office,
and the Internet protocol address
of the rumormonger.
It's also Yu Tian.
I just don't get it.
There is no grudge
between us.
Why would she
try to hurt me
again and again?
On the other hand,
I mean,
she is my superior
in the debate team.
There's no conflict between us.
Could it be an emotional motive?
Wait.
She...
I...
We...
She is jealous
because she likes me...
I don't think it's possible.
After all, I don't know her
very well.
She only tutored me.
Do you know what I mean?
During the debate.
But if she did that
because she likes me
as you said...
Not you.
What is it?
A love letter from my teammate
in the debate team.
She put it in my file.
You're popular.
I'll send it back anyway.
Here.
Well,
I should go.
It's Li Chongwen.
Which means
it was also Yu Tian
who put a love letter for him
in the file.
I have an idea.
You asked me out on the weekend.
Are you ashamed to see others?
See it by yourself.
(Saturday)
(Police Blotter)
(Guanghua University)
What do you mean?
You have every right to hate me.
But you introduced me to a fraud,
spread rumors on the Internet,
and reported your teammates
who have been working with you,
don't you think you've gone too far?
Are you not afraid
that they will get punishment?
Didn't the police tell you
that I only gave
your contact information
to Wu Zhongyou?
I didn't ask him to hurt you.
I thought you would be late
for the show at worst
and have a fight with Lu Xun.
I didn't know he would do that to you.
Besides,
the law does not punish
numerous offenders.
Even if they
get caught by the dean,
you're the one to be punished
as the leader.
You dragged everyone into this
because you want
to keep your qualification
for the Municipal
Merit Student Selection.
If you really care about them,
you shouldn't get them involved.
The debate team
is not your harem.
I'm not withdrawing the application,
because I'm not a thief.
I deserve the honor.
They help me
because they trust me,
they know me,
and they see me as a friend.
Have you ever thought about it?
No matter what terrible rumors
you spread online,
no matter how serious it becomes,
those who trust me
will always be on my side.
They are fooled by you,
but I won't.
Who else could it be?
If you didn't do it,
why did you just let it go?
Do you think I'm a fool?
I let it go
and Liu let it go
because there is
someone we want to protect.
To be frank with you,
the one who stole the jade
wasn't any of my classmates
that night!
The debate team
is the most united club in the school.
You told me that
when I joined the debate team
as a freshman.
No matter who's in trouble,
the rest of the team
won't shirk their responsibility.
If someone else
is surrounded by rumors,
I would stand out and do the same thing.
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪I've got countless things to do♪
♪Possibilities never end♪
♪I force myself to do it all♪
♪I'm lucky to have you in my future♪
♪Who will do everything with me♪
♪Even if I have to lose♪
♪Numberless things♪
♪Even if I have to lose everything♪
♪I can't live without you♪
♪One of seven billion♪
♪I also cherish your soul so much♪
♪Girl I swear I love you♪
♪Without reservation Be my only girl♪
♪You're my only girl♪
♪The most beautiful memory♪
♪The most special definition♪
♪Yeah baby♪
♪I'll fight the world for you♪
♪I want to grow old with you♪
♪And travel around the world together♪
♪Wherever you are♪
♪It's my whole world♪
♪I'm your umbrella♪
♪I'll shelter everything for you♪
♪Let's travel
across the most beautiful border♪
♪Without saying goodbye♪
♪What has excited us♪
♪Our love in the precious life yeah♪
♪Lie down and enjoy the sky♪
♪I hold you in my arms♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪Even stars can't be as shiny as you♪
♪In such a world♪
♪I love no one but you♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪You still need me♪
♪How to prove♪
♪You know♪
♪How much I love you♪
♪You're the one for the rest of my life♪
♪I got crush on you bae♪
♪I can't hide all my feeling♪
♪For the rest of your life I will♪
♪Keep all my promises♪
♪For you♪
♪What's to be continued♪
♪Prediction♪
♪You're exactly the one
for the rest of my life♪