♪The surging clouds will remember♪
♪Its love for that forest♪
♪But the journey's end is a hug♪
♪I want to transform into your scenery♪
♪With you, I fearlessly cross mountains♪
♪Now I will run towards you again♪
♪From rainforests to icebergs♪
♪Every breath, after evaporating♪
♪I wish to ride the wind♪
♪In the quest to travel the world♪
[Love in the Tea Garden]
[Episode 1]
Stop!
Come on!
Over there!
♪The surging clouds will remember♪
♪Its love for that forest♪
♪Gathering into primordial raindrops♪
♪Flowing from the mountains for you♪
♪Perhaps frozen in winter♪
I was in a really bad mood today.
But the moment I decided to help you,
my mood seemed to improve.
♪I want to transform into your scenery♪
♪With you, I fearlessly cross mountains♪
♪Now I will run towards you again♪
♪From rainforests to icebergs♪
♪Every breath, after evaporating♪
♪I wish to ride the wind♪
♪In the quest to travel the world♪
[Three years later]
Mie Mie.
Good sheep.
Rumors say Ye Xiyan, CEO of Ye Group,
is involved with a male star.
The gossip is now trending online.
What should we do?
The rumors are getting so out of hand.
They're having a big impact.
We'll remove the searches now.
Remove?
I want to fan the flames even more.
We can't miss out
on this free attention.
When the public opinion ferments,
I'll announce I've signed him
as our spokesperson.
This is a huge win.
We'll save a lot on marketing expenses.
Brilliant move, Miss Ye.
Dad,
lately, there's been a surge in slander
against our group.
I suspect someone is behind it.
Are you saying it's Cui Group?
Cui Group also wants that land.
We must act before they do,
and seize the opportunity.
[Ye Group
Acquisition and Renovation Proposal]
Hello, sir. We've captured her.
OK.
Take her.
Yes. Let's go.
How are you? Are you OK?
Put me down.
Be quiet, I'm trying to save you.
Sir, have mercy.
You're so handsome.
There's no need to do this.
If you want money, I can give you money.
If you want me,
I can also give you money.
Just don't do this anymore.
Enough, shut up.
Unless you want to be taken by them.
Let's go.
Over there! Let's go!
Hurry!
Hurry up!
I misunderstood.
He was actually saving me.
It seems he's a good person.
Why did it start raining suddenly?
And so heavily.
Today,
thank you for saving me.
Who are you really?
Can you tell me?
Why were those people
trying to kidnap you?
I am...
Who am I?
I can't remember.
I... Who am I?
Could it be that car accident?
You lost your memory?
Don't worry, take your time.
I can't remember...
I can't remember anything now.
You won't just leave me, will you?
From what you said,
are you planning to cling to me?
Cling sounds so unpleasant.
Let's call it helping instead.
You want me to help you?
You need to offer something in return.
Wait,
you're not asking me to marry you,
are you?
Try to remember quickly.
I have things to ask you.
Until then, I'll help you.
None of you
could get a clear look
at his face?
He's very skilled.
Clean up the scene and keep searching.
Keep searching!
Yes, sir!
Search in teams!
This is to guard against gentlemen,
not villains.
What do you do for a living?
Why do you carry everything with you?
Go to sleep.
♪The surging clouds will remember♪
♪Its love for that forest♪
♪Gathering into primordial raindrops♪
♪Flowing from the mountains for you♪
♪Perhaps frozen in winter♪
♪There will be banks on the way♪
♪But the journey's is a hug♪
♪I want to transform into your scenery♪
♪With you, I fearlessly cross mountains♪
This is sunrise in my hometown.
Come, everyone take a look.
Hello, everyone.
I'm a new live-streamer, Su Qiqi.
Today,
I'll show you around
my hometown, Guyan Village.
Follow me so you don't miss me.
Come.
Hello, Aunt Wang, Uncle Zhao.
And Jiang Shengsheng.
Thank you, friends and family,
for your support.
Come, let me show you
our Guyan Village.
It has beautiful mountains and rivers,
and picturesque scenery,
right?
Yes, those are our fields in the back.
Beautiful, right?
Mingyu?
Who's that in his arms?
Did I just discover
a big scoop?
Why are they sleeping here, huh?
I think he looks like Lu.
No way.
I can't see clearly.
They're waking up.
Look closely.
Who are they?
Look at these two sleeping here.
How shameless.
My Mingyu
is taken by someone else!
It's hopeless
to have Lu as my son-in-law.
Xiufen?
It's you! You're back?
Who?
Isn't this Xiufen from the east end
of the village?
When did she come back?
I can't believe she took my Mingyu.
You're Xiufen?
Xiufen?
I'm Xiufen?
♪When I opened my eyes,
I saw your heart suddenly crowded♪
♪Each stroke of what word
gradually becomes clear♪
♪After 300 thousand time units,
wishes ignite shooting stars♪
♪When cherry blossom petals fall,
they travel much more than 5cm♪
♪Planets attract each other,
bringing us closer together♪
♪Love is like a lighter,
a touch creates an echo♪
♪I've also walked alone
through lost dreams♪
♪Finally awakening because of you♪
♪As swift as a monsoon,
you suddenly appear♪
♪Raindrops from across the sea
give me all the courage♪
♪Kissing your eyes
as our shoulders meet♪
♪My traces are in your starry sky♪
♪Like the night sky summoning
shooting stars, you descend for me♪
♪Standing at the world's center,
I hold your hand in mine♪
♪The sound of heartbeats hitting walls♪
♪That feeling is probably called love♪