♪The surging clouds will remember♪
♪Its love for that forest♪
♪But the journey's end
can only be to embrace you♪
♪I want to become the scenery
that always accompanies you♪
♪With you, I fearlessly cross mountains♪
♪Now I will run towards you again♪
♪From rainforests to icebergs♪
♪Every breath, after evaporating♪
♪I wish to ride the wind♪
♪In the quest to travel the world♪
[Love in the Tea Garden]
[Episode 15]
I'm sorry.
I lied to you.
I actually haven't lost my memory,
but I was greedy for your protection.
I got used to the sense of security
you gave me.
I was afraid of you
not being by my side.
I'm really sorry.
Actually,
she had already told me the truth.
I just didn't realize it.
Maybe they'll find me soon.
I can't implicate Xiyan.
♪Longing always overflows
whenever loneliness strikes♪
You broke up with Xiyan
over such a trivial matter?
You clearly love each other.
Why break up?
I don't care what your concerns are.
We won't allow you to do this.
Exactly, we won't allow it.
You can't do that.
We won't allow it, no way.
We won't allow it.
We've decided,
you must get Xiyan back.
If there are difficulties,
we'll face them together.
Only by having her lover by her side
can she be protected.
Love is too deep,
and the pain is too intense.
The wise don't fall in love.
But as the biggest fan of this couple,
I can't keep shipping them.
I can ship them again now.
Xiyan,
I was wrong,
terribly wrong.
Can you give me a chance?
You want me to give you a chance,
so I have to give you a chance?
No one...
No one will wait for someone forever.
You don't have to forgive me,
but you'd better stay by my side.
I'll be right here. I won't go anywhere.
Qiqi said
I can stay for as long as I want,
right?
Come on.
What era is this?
Stop with these cliché
tragic romance plots.
Please.
Be sweet together, no more angst.
It was sunny just now.
Why did it suddenly start raining?
I'll ask Cui Zihao to pick me up.
No way.
I have an umbrella.
I'll take you home.
Then go.
Xiyan,
I'll show you a trick.
If you laugh,
does that mean you'll forgive me?
Go ahead.
I'm not one to laugh easily anyway.
Three, two, one.
The rain stopped.
And there's a rainbow.
It's beautiful, how did you...
Just a little trick, boring.
Well, Chief...
Don't be discouraged.
Success belongs to the persevering.
It seems
she doesn't give me any chance at all.
Mingyu,
think outside the box.
This time we need
to go against the usual tactics,
and pretend to be weak.
What do you mean?
Simply put,
the bitter ploy.
Mingyu,
act a bit more vulnerable.
I'll post this on my social media.
If Su Qiqi sees it,
she'll see it too.
Besides,
we have a strong support team
to back you up.
Xiyan, are you still mad at Mingyu?
If I don't give him a bit
of a hard time,
how can I justify all the tears
I've shed for him?
Mingyu got drunk,
and is sick? It's seems serious.
Isn't it a bitter ploy?
Who'd believe that?
Yes, he's fainted several times.
Hurry.
He's in a critical condition.
Let's go check on him.
Quick, hurry up.
Mingyu is unconscious.
Come and help.
Did you hear that?
Hurry up.
It might be true.
It's very troublesome.
What's his temperature?
Xiyan,
he's been saying your name.
Go check on him.
I hope Mingyu seizes this opportunity
and win back his love.
Lu Mingyu.
Wake up, I'll get you a glass of water.
You came to see me.
Does this mean you forgive me?
I'm just
doing
a good deed.
Xiyan,
I'll tell you the truth.
My enemies have found me.
I was afraid of implicating you.
But now I understand,
we should face it together.
I won't hide from you
or push you away anymore.
Your acting is pretty convincing.
A drunk man's acting is touching
that it'd make me cry, right?
I...
I just wanted to create an opportunity
to explain things to you.
Xiyan!
Folks, we need to pull out
all the stops now.
Don't move!
Who are you?
Who sent you?
Knowing too much isn't good for you.
Come with us.
Don't be afraid, I'm here.
As long as I'm here,
no one can hurt you.
Don't be afraid, I'm here.
As long as I'm here,
no one can hurt you.
Let's go.
You have to trust me.
Follow my lead.
I'll count to three,
then hold onto me tight.
One, two, three.
Let's go.
But you have to trust me.
Follow my lead.
I'll count to three.
You count to three,
and I hold onto you?
♪Kissing your eyes as our shoulders meet♪
One, two, three.
♪I open my eyes and see you,
my heart suddenly becomes full♪
Mingyu, it's me!
Take it easy.
Shengsheng?
Village chief?
How about it?
Dad.
The lighting, the atmosphere,
did I set it up well?
The village has really
gone through a lot
for you two.
It's exhausting.
Mingyu knows he's done wrong.
Give him a chance.
Exactly, Xiyan,
I know you still care about him.
Since you love each other,
don't leave regrets.
♪Raindrops from across the sea
give me all the courage♪
So it's been you all along,
110901.
♪Like the night sky summoning
shooting stars, you descend for me♪
♪Standing at the world's center,
I hold your hand in mine♪
♪The sound of heartbeats hitting walls♪
♪That feeling is probably called love♪
♪I open my eyes and see you,
my heart suddenly becomes full♪
♪Every stroke of the word
becomes clearer bit by bit♪
♪After 300 thousand time units,
wishes ignite shooting stars♪
♪When cherry blossom petals fall,
they travel much more than 5cm♪
♪Planets attract each other,
bringing us closer together♪
♪Love is like a lighter,
a touch creates an echo♪
♪I've also walked alone
through lost dreams♪
♪Finally awakening because of you♪
♪As swift as a monsoon,
you suddenly appear♪
♪Raindrops from across the sea
give me all the courage♪
♪Kissing your eyes
as our shoulders meet♪
♪My traces are in your starry sky♪
♪Like the night sky summoning
shooting stars, you descend for me♪
♪Standing at the world's center,
I hold your hand in mine♪
♪The sound of heartbeats hitting walls♪
♪That feeling is probably called love♪