♪The surging clouds will remember♪
♪Its love for that forest♪
♪But the journey's end
can only be to embrace you♪
♪I want to become the scenery
that always accompanies you♪
♪With you, I fearlessly cross mountains♪
♪Now I will run towards you again♪
♪From rainforests to icebergs♪
♪Every breath, after evaporating♪
♪I wish to ride the wind♪
♪In the quest to travel the world♪
[Love in the Tea Garden]
[Episode 24]
Xiyan.
Cui Zihao and his dad
have been brought to justice
and sentenced for their crimes.
Ye Group's reputation has been restored.
Everything is back on track.
You've endured so much during this time.
Look at this.
Dad, you're letting me go?
I know you can't bear
to leave the tea plantation.
Go, kid.
Do what you want to do.
Thank you, Dad.
That tea plantation
is his dream.
I promised him and the villagers
of Guyan Village,
so I'll be responsible for them
to the end.
[Guyan Tea Plantation]
♪When you're wronged,
I stand up for you♪
♪Baby, don't be afraid of the dark,
I'll protect you♪
♪I shed tears for you
until my eyes are red♪
♪For you, I'd even stand
against the world♪
♪Yet not a single tear
can reach your heart♪
I used to be a very rational person.
Romance, confession, lover,
they all seemed so distant to me.
But
since meeting you,
I've realized
being loved
can indeed be as beautiful
as a fairy tale.
When I'm sad,
you're like a beam of light,
dispelling the darkness
and giving me warmth.
What took you so long?
When I'm in danger,
you protect me without hesitation,
shielding me from the wind and rain.
In times of happiness,
you watch over me
and you seem even happier than I am.
♪You brought me
this earth-shattering love♪
♪I love you far more than you imagine♪
Last time, I didn't respond
to your confession.
So this time,
let me make up for that regret.
[I want to tell you]
[I really love you]
So...
[Will you marry me?]
♪You're like an unfinished movie♪
♪You took away all the air around me♪
♪I can't move or make a sound♪
♪You brought me
this earth-shattering love♪
♪I love you far more than you imagine♪
♪Small emotions, once cared for,
become meaningful♪
Where are you going?
Xiyan.
♪As swift as a monsoon,
you suddenly appear♪
♪Raindrops from across the sea
give me all the courage♪
♪Kissing your eyes
as our shoulders meet♪
♪My traces are in your starry sky♪
Leave the proposal
to me.
When did you prepare this?
♪The sound of heartbeats hitting walls♪
♪That feeling is probably called love♪
♪As swift as a monsoon,
you suddenly appear♪
♪Raindrops from across the sea
give me all the courage♪
♪Kissing your eyes
as our shoulders meet♪
♪My traces are in your starry sky♪
♪Like the night sky summoning
shooting stars, you descend for me♪
♪Standing at the world's center,
I hold your hand in mine♪
From the first time I met you,
I fell in love at first sight.
It was my first time feeling this way,
and it'll be the last.
Meeting you
is the best thing
that's ever happened to me
because I'm certain
you're my one true love.
This DR diamond ring
can only be given
to one person in a lifetime,
symbolizing
a lifetime of love
for just one person.
It bears witness
to my lifelong commitment to you.
We've been through many trials,
but I only want
to protect you wholeheartedly.
Xiyan,
will you be with me for a lifetime?
I will.
♪The surging clouds will remember♪
♪Its love for that forest♪
♪Gathering into primordial raindrops♪
♪Flowing from the mountains for you♪
♪Perhaps frozen in winter♪
♪There will be banks on the way♪
♪But the journey's end
can only be to embrace you♪
This heart-shaped ring
is custom-made for you.
Do you like it?
♪I want to become the scenery
that always accompanies you♪
Then I'll accept your heart.
♪With you, I fearlessly cross mountains♪
♪Now I will run towards you again♪
♪From rainforests to icebergs♪
Everything I have is yours.
♪Love won't disappear like clouds♪
♪Longing makes it fall to the ground♪
♪If I still fail to reunite with you
the next century♪
♪Then I'll wait through
more stormy seasons♪
♪Every breath, after evaporating
♪I wish to ride the wind♪
♪In the quest to travel the world♪
[Guyan Village Tea Plantation]
[Investment Signing Ceremony]
On this journey,
I'm grateful to everyone present.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be standing here today.
I once promised
to lead everyone to prosperity.
Today is just the beginning.
In the future, while developing
tea products and tourism,
we'll also strive to make Guyan Tea
an international brand
and conduct global business.
- Bravo.
Please.
After you.
- Bravo.
Happy cooperation.
It's really great.
Exactly.
Hello, everyone.
Today, I'm introducing
a new white tea
from our Guyan Village.
This is a new product
for this year.
When brewed,
it may not
have the strong aroma of old white tea,
but its taste is very refreshing.
We have a special promotion today.
Where's the sun?
When you buy our white tea,
we'll give away
three small incense sticks
with the tea's fragrance.
That's great.
When I'm not live streaming,
you can go to my homepage
and place your orders
through the shop window.
Kids,
that's all for today's class.
Keep drawing at home.
- Goodbye, Sir.
Goodbye.
Stay safe.
Be careful when you run.
Go home for dinner.
Be careful.
Right,
I'll leave the link
in the shop window.
So if you want to buy
when I'm not live,
you can go to my shop window
and click on my homepage.
Everything is there in the shop window.
You can place your orders there.
Place the order yourselves.
Order yourselves.
Exactly.
When I'm not live,
you can go to my homepage
and place your orders
through the shop window.
The links are all there.
Just pick what you like
and buy it directly.
OK,
that's it
for today's live stream.
See you next time, everyone.
Is your class over?
Do you like it?
I do.
But if your photography skills
were as good
as your drawing skills,
or even better,
that'd be perfect.
Alright, I'll work on it.
[Aren't they Shengsheng and Qiqi?
The perfect match.]
I forgot to turn off the live stream.
Everyone saw it.
Perfect,
we can announce it officially.
♪The surging clouds will remember♪
♪Its love for that forest♪
♪Gathering into primordial raindrops♪
♪Flowing from the mountains for you♪
[They're so sweet.
Qiqi, be happy.]
♪Perhaps frozen in winter♪
[Guyan Tea: Fragrance Worldwide]
♪There will be banks on the way♪
♪But the journey's end
can only be to embrace you♪
The development of Guyan Village
is now on track.
What are your plans next?
Growing tea.
Having children.
♪With you, I fearlessly cross mountains♪
♪Now I will run towards you again♪
And spending my life with you.
♪From rainforests to icebergs♪
Well,
you've already accomplished
the first two.
♪Longing makes it fall to the ground♪
♪If I still fail to reunite with you
the next century♪
♪Then I'll wait through
more stormy seasons♪
♪Every breath, after evaporating\♪I wish to ride the wind♪
You mean...
That's wonderful,
Xiyan.
[Guyan Tea: Fragrance Worldwide]
♪If I still fail to reunite with you
the next century♪
♪Then I'll wait through
more stormy seasons♪
♪Every breath, after evaporating
I wish to ride the wind♪
♪In the quest to travel the world♪
[The End]
[Yunhe Terraces]
♪I open my eyes and see you♪
♪My heart suddenly becomes full♪
[Yunhe Terraces]
♪Every stroke of the word♪
♪Becomes clearer bit by bit♪
[Yunhe Terraces]
♪After 300 thousand time units♪
♪Wishes ignite shooting stars♪
[Guyan Painting Village]
♪When cherry blossom petals fall♪
♪They travel much more than 5cm♪
[Guyan Painting Village]
♪Planets attract each other♪
♪Bringing us closer together♪
[Jiulong National Wetland Park]
♪Love is like a lighter♪
♪A touch creates an echo♪
[Jiulong National Wetland Park]
♪I've also walked alone♪
♪Through lost dreams♪
[Jiulong National Wetland Park]
♪Finally awakening because of you♪
[Changting Beach]
♪As swift as a monsoon♪
♪You suddenly appear♪
[Changting Beach]
♪Raindrops from across the sea♪
♪Give me all the courage♪
[Damu Mountain Tea Plantation Park]
♪Kissing your eyes♪
♪As our shoulders meet♪
[Damu Mountain Tea Plantation Park]
♪My traces are in your starry sky♪
♪Like the night sky summoning
shooting stars, you descend for me♪
♪Standing at the world's center,
I hold your hand in mine♪
♪The sound of heartbeats hitting walls♪
♪That feeling is probably called love♪
♪As swift as a monsoon,
you suddenly appear♪
♪Raindrops from across the sea
give me all the courage♪
♪Kissing your eyes
as our shoulders meet♪
♪My traces are in your starry sky♪
♪Like the night sky summoning
shooting stars, you descend for me♪
♪Standing at the world's center,
I hold your hand in mine♪
♪The sound of heartbeats hitting walls♪
♪That feeling is probably called love♪