♪The surging clouds will remember♪
♪Its love for that forest♪
♪But the journey's end can
only be to embrace you♪
♪I want to become the scenery
that always accompanies you♪
♪With you, I fearlessly cross mountains♪
♪Now I will run towards you again♪
♪From rainforests to icebergs♪
♪Every breath, after evaporating♪
♪I wish to ride the wind♪
♪In the quest to travel the world♪
[Love in the Tea Garden]
[Episode 13]
Now can you tell me
who you really are?
I...
I'm Ye Xiyan now.
Whatever the answer is,
I can accept it.
But can you please not hide it from me?
Xiufen,
it's all thanks to you,
we got so many orders this time.
The order is a small matter.
The main thing is
it helped our village
gain pride and recognition.
Yes, Xiufen,
you've transformed completely
after being away for a few years.
That aura you had just now,
if I didn't know,
I'd think you were really
Ye Xiyan.
It's just acting,
an extraordinary performance.
It's getting late.
Let's hurry back.
OK, let's go home.
You're not feeling well. Let me help.
♪When you're wronged,
I stand up for you♪
I didn't expect you to care about me
so much.
Of course.
Just like now.
Your ears are turning red.
♪Yet not a single tear
can reach your heart♪
♪Time will erase the traces
of my existence♪
♪Longing always overflows
whenever loneliness strikes♪
♪Every decision you make♪
After the trade fair,
I thought there'd be a barrier
between us.
That doesn't stop me
from being good to you.
Things are complicated.
Can you give me some time
to think about
how to tell you everything,
alright?
♪I can't move or make a sound♪
♪You brought me
this earth-shattering love♪
♪I love you far more than you imagine♪
Be careful not to catch a cold.
Aren't you being a bit dramatic?
I can manage on my own.
I know you can,
but I want to help,
especially when you're not feeling well.
Wait for me a moment.
Here.
♪When you're wronged,
I stand up for you♪
Here.
♪Baby, don't be afraid of the dark,
I'll protect you♪
♪I cry my eyes red for you♪
♪For you, I'd even stand
against the world♪
♪Yet not a single tear
can reach your heart♪
♪You're like a spontaneous journey♪
♪You're like an unfinished movie♪
♪You took away all the air around me♪
♪I can't move or make a sound♪
♪You brought me
this earth-shattering love♪
♪I love you far more than you imagine♪
♪Small emotions, once cared for,
become meaningful♪
If one day,
you find out
I'm not really me.
♪You took away all the air around me♪
♪I can't move or make a sound♪
♪You brought me
this earth-shattering love♪
Will you take all of this away?
Since I'm willing to give,
it means you're worth it.
Why would I take it away?
What's...
going on with you?
Why are you all looking at me like that?
Xiufen,
we have something important.
Come with us.
Is this...
Have I been exposed?
She's here.
She's here!
Xiufen, Xiufen is here!
Xiufen, we've been waiting for you.
It's all thanks to you.
Yes.
Thanks to Xiufen.
This child is truly excellent.
Yes.
What's this?
This trade fair was a huge success.
We want to hold a ceremony
to thank the Mountain God.
Everyone has seen your hard work,
so we want you to join in.
No wonder everyone is so serious.
But why me?
Xiufen,
you're our benefactor
and have helped the village greatly.
So, we want to ask you
to be one of the main celebrants,
to bring blessings and joy
to the tea plantation.
What do you all think?
- Of course!
Let's pick tea!
- Let's pick tea!
[Fragrance of Guyan Tea]
Let's pick tea!
- Let's pick tea!
Come on, cheers!
Cheers!
Bao, eat more.
That's a good thing.
Everyone, quiet down.
Quiet down.
Every year,
I give the opening speech.
Xiufen.
Not me...
You're the greatest contributor
to the village.
Say a few words.
Just what I feared most.
Everyone, applause.
Let me speak...
Say a few words.
Say something, Xiufen.
I'd say
the greatest contributors
are all of you.
Because
you grew such good tea,
I had the confidence to tell everyone
our tea is the best.
Cheers to everyone!
- Good. Cheers!
Living like this wouldn't be so bad.
There's warmth,
kindness, and love.
Here, give this to Xiufen.
Xiufen, I have a painting for you.
Thank you.
Get ready.
Cuifang.
Marry me.
Marry him!
- Marry him!
Bravo!
Come, eat while it's hot.
Here you go.
Stop eating!
I just called Xiufen.
She's an impostor.
An impostor?
Is that right, Ye Xiyan?
Ye Xiyan?
She is the daughter of CEO of Ye Group?
This is
[Acquisition and Renovation Proposal]
the acquisition plan from Ye Group.
She pretended to have amnesia
and impersonated Xiufen
to investigate our tea plantation
for acquisition.
We've all been deceived by her.
How could this happen?
She's just a fraud.
She's a fraud, she deceived us!
Fraud.
What are you doing?
Why did you
do this to us?
Xiyan,
it's really you.
Are you alright?
Is what Xiufen's mom said just now
really true?
I want to hear it from you.
I admit at first,
I pretended to have amnesia
and impersonated Xiufen
to acquire the tea plantation.
So at the beginning,
you were willing to come with me
all because of the tea plantation?
Yes.
So you watched me like a clown,
performing a one-man show,
step by step achieving your goal?
At first,
at first, it was all fake,
and insincere.
But later, didn't you feel
those real,
beautiful moments?
Maybe it was too beautiful.
I don't know when it was sincere
and when it was fake.
Now that the truth is out,
we have no reason
to pretend to be a couple anymore.
Let's end it here.
♪You're like a spontaneous journey♪
♪You're like an unfinished movie♪
♪You took away all the air around me♪
♪I can't move or make a sound♪
♪You brought me
this earth-shattering love♪
♪I love you far more than you imagine♪
♪Small emotions, once cared for,
become meaningful♪
♪When I opened my eyes,
I saw your heart suddenly crowded♪
♪Each stroke of what word
gradually becomes clear♪
♪After 300 thousand time units,
wishes ignite shooting stars♪
♪When cherry blossom petals fall,
they travel much more than 5cm♪
♪Planets attract each other,
bringing us closer together♪
♪Love is like a lighter,
a touch creates an echo♪
♪I've also walked alone
through lost dreams♪
♪Finally awakening because of you♪
♪As swift as a monsoon,
you suddenly appear♪
♪Raindrops from across the sea
give me all the courage♪
♪Kissing your eyes
as our shoulders meet♪
♪My traces are in your starry sky♪
♪Like the night sky summoning
shooting stars, you descend for me♪
♪Standing at the world's center,
I hold your hand in mine♪
♪The sound of heartbeats hitting walls♪
♪That feeling is probably called love♪