♪The surging clouds will remember♪
♪Its love for that forest♪
♪But the journey's end is a hug♪
♪I want to transform into your scenery♪
♪With you, I fearlessly cross mountains♪
♪Now I will run towards you again♪
♪From rainforests to icebergs♪
♪Every breath, after evaporating♪
♪I wish to ride the wind♪
♪In the quest to travel the world♪
[Love in the Tea Garden]
[Episode 2]
[Xiufen's suffering]
Father died early, wicked stepmother
and spoiled brother.
What kind of melodrama script is this?
Never mind.
I know you lost your memory.
Let me introduce myself directly.
My name is Su Qiqi.
I've been your best friend
since we were kids.
If you have any questions later,
just find me anytime.
But I need to livestream soon,
so I need to go.
We're from the same village.
Why does everyone know me
except you?
I returned to the village a year ago,
and I haven't met everyone yet.
Are you sure you want
to come back to this house?
I...
Xiufen?
You're back!
I have to tell mom the good news.
Mom, Xiufen is back!
See?
They aren't completely heartless.
Finally, someone is here
to do the chores.
We can sell the donkey now.
So I really am Xiufen.
I must have escaped this hell before.
Now, to regain my memory,
I have to jump back in.
Xiufen!
How shameless you are!
I'll teach you a lesson today.
Let me.
What are you doing?
Mom!
I'm back!
You missed me, right?
You wretched girl, let go of me.
No!
No, I still want
to take good care of you.
Let go of me!
No!
Let go!
What secret is she hiding?
Why is Hydra going to such lengths
for her?
Calling me mom won't help.
You still have to do chores.
Ridiculous.
Ripped pants
are very trendy this year.
Trying to escape?
Still not going?
Are you setting a fire?
Yes, I plan to end it all.
Didn't you say you'd help me?
I can't stay here any longer.
Did you remember anything?
No.
Why are you so invested
in me regaining my memory?
Wretched girl,
are you trying to kill me?
Time is money.
Meaning,
Tom is Mary?
Oh my god, you guys have no talent
for language at all.
What a fool.
Are you being racist, excuse me?
Learning English to us
is like a piece of cake.
But do you speak Chinese?
Let me show you how talented
Chinese people can be
when it comes to learning a language.
Do you speak Korean?
Do you speak French?
Do you speak German?
Do you speak Japanese?
I'm saying all this to tell you,
don't discriminate
against Chinese again.
Wait,
aren't you a junior high school graduate?
Right.
Why does my language talent
seem embedded in my DNA?
Why?
Xiufen couldn't possibly know these.
Are you OK?
Loser.
You can't do anything right.
All the efforts put into raising you
were wasted.
You shouldn't have come back.
This is the house my mom left me.
Why can't I live here?
According to inheritance law,
I'm the first in line to inherit.
You're the ones occupying my house.
I can kick you out anytime.
You ungrateful wretch.
Could she be the one
who saved me back then?
Could you have grown up without me?
I've prepared this long ago.
I raised myself.
Be reasonable.
How dare you talk to my mom like that?
And you,
you failed college entrance exam
five times.
You even hired a private tutor.
Tom is Mary?
You should spend money
checking up your brain.
So the folks were telling the truth.
Mom, Xiufen's personality changed
because she lost her memory
in an accident.
I wondered why you brought her back.
You're the culprit, right?
Don't slander a good person.
He saved me.
He didn't hit you?
Then why did he bring you back?
He's clearly guilty.
We need compensation.
You can be shameless,
but I still need my pride.
You!
Don't talk nonsense. Don't hit people.
Chief,
I don't want to live anymore.
He hit Xiufen.
And he wants to hit me, Chief!
I don't want to live.
I've investigated.
It has nothing to do with Mingyu.
Xiufen's mom, apologize now.
Our village depends
on Mingyu's tea plantation to prosper.
But he slept with Xiufen.
Everyone saw it.
Exactly.
You ruined Xiufen's reputation.
How will she get married?
You have to take responsibility.
How should I be responsible?
Marry her.
The dowry won't be much,
just 200 thousand.
- You're daydreaming...
- Sure.
You can have the money.
But I'll take her.
Thanks to you,
I escaped the nightmare.
By the way, you have
a tea plantation, right?
I'll work for you to repay the money.
No rush.
Did you remember anything this time?
I can't remember anything.
Have you thought about
who you might have provoked?
I don't know.
♪Will kissing you
feel like tasting a fruit?♪
♪You're like a little bear,
with a clumsy personality♪
♪A little bear with a cute exterior♪
♪The more you grow,
the more you harmonize♪
♪Giving all your passion to me♪
♪And you carefully wrap me♪
♪Our palms still tightly clasped♪
This is a farm.
Life here must be so comfortable.
We're home.
Did I hit the jackpot?
You can unpack.
I'll take you around the village later
to help you recover your memory.
Xiufen, you're back.
I picked apples, try some.
Wait...
Eat up.
Thank you.
Xiufen, you're back.
Take some buns,
you haven't eaten, right?
Try these buns.
Thank you.
They're delicious.
Is there a strange woman
in the village?
No.
Sir,
have you seen
a strange woman in the village?
Strange woman?
Mie Mie.
When will you pay the balance?
When will you pay the rent?
Let's settle it.
Refund your rent? Dream on.
Ungrateful wretch,
I've raised you for so long,
and you ask for a rent refund?
She's with me now.
If you keep pestering,
I guarantee you won't get a penny.
CEO talk plus a hug.
Is he discreetly
confessing to me?
Explain to me.
Sir, have you seen a strange woman?
No.
It's confirmed.
He
loves me.
Dang.
Is the countryside this open now?
Let's go. She's not here.
Let's go.
That's thrilling.
What's your excuse this time?
I slipped.
Though I like straightforward people,
you're too blunt.
What do you mean?
Keep pretending.
[World-class Bodyguard]
Hydra's people showed up again.
She must have
clues about them.
♪When I opened my eyes,
I saw your heart suddenly crowded♪
♪Each stroke of what word
gradually becomes clear♪
♪After 300 thousand time units,
wishes ignite shooting stars♪
♪When cherry blossom petals fall,
they travel much more than 5cm♪
♪Planets attract each other,
bringing us closer together♪
♪Love is like a lighter,
a touch creates an echo♪
♪I've also walked alone
through lost dreams♪
♪Finally awakening because of you♪
♪As swift as a monsoon,
you suddenly appear♪
♪Raindrops from across the sea
give me all the courage♪
♪Kissing your eyes
as our shoulders meet♪
♪My traces are in your starry sky♪
♪Like the night sky summoning
shooting stars, you descend for me♪
♪Standing at the world's center,
I hold your hand in mine♪
♪The sound of heartbeats hitting walls♪
♪That feeling is probably called love♪