Let's go!
Cut! Okay!
Wow, the action was great. Good work!
Thank you!
Alright, we're done so let's move on to the main character's scene!
Okay!
Good work, good work.
Geez!
Wow, saying "good work" doesn't change anything for the better.
How did I become like this?
- Blegh!
- Joon Ki, your phone. It's been ringing since earlier.
Thank you.
Hello?
What?
Darn!
Please clap along.
Housewives  Singing Lesson with Shiba Woo Sik
What? I'm busy. I'm in the middle of a class.
What? Darn!
K B Kook
Yes, there is only one more ball left.
Player Gook Gi Bong, who has yet to let a ball be hit or run for all nine innings,
everything is hanging on him.
It's three balls and two strikes right now.
Gook Gi Bong needs to be really careful about throwing into the outfield right now.
It's because Player Sato is probably aiming for the outfield right now.
Yes, this is a very nerve-wracking moment.
Player Gook Gi Bong is headed for the countdown!
And...
Strike! He succeeded!
That was great. What a great win!
Thank you, Sato!
Everyone, player Gook Gi Bong led the team to a win!
That was great, Player Gook Gi Bong!
Hurry and get up!
Hey! Gook Gi Bong!
Oh, I won! So cold!
If it wasn't enough that you're passed out,
but you're even dreaming?
Do you want to rot in this state forever?!
Sorry, Coach, but I've got a call.
Hurry and just take it.
Hello? What is it? I'm in the middle of training.
What?! Darn!
What? Why are you running?
Where are you going?
Guest House Waikiki
Waikiki
How is it? The interior is clean and great.
- It's good, right?
- Yes.
And on top of that, the location is great so it gets a lot of business!
You can use all of it as it is.
- It's nice, right?
- Yes.
Think about it well.
This is going to drive me crazy. Why aren't they here?
Everyone that comes here has become successful!
We've had movie directors, reporters, mall owners, and even a pâtissière .
They're all successful!
Boss!
Who is this?
- Who are they?
- Oh, only these people are weird.
I'm serious.
I'm going to give it a bit more thought, and I'll let you know. Goodbye.
No, you should look a bit more closely! There's more to see!
- If you just--!
- No, no!
Geez. What are you guys doing?
Boss, how could you put this up for sale without even discussing it with us?
You could pay your rent first. Do you know how behind you are?
Rent? Could you give us a week? We'll figure it out.
One week? Do you know how many months it's been that you've been saying that?
I think it's been about four months and two weeks.
Alright. I'll give you one last chance.
Exactly one more week. Pay up all of your late rent.
Look at the state of you all. Are you guys a traffic light or what?
Thank you! Goodbye!
What's the point of this guesthouse?
Look who's talking.
- Hey, Red Light. Stop. Red Light!
- Don't touch me!
Hey!  I called you so long ago. Why are you coming now?
Hey, I ran over as soon as I got the call. Can't you tell by the fact that I'm still in my wig and costume?
Gosh, I even brought this all the way here.
This is driving me nuts. How are we going to get all that money in a week?
I know, right?
Hey, do you have some money?
If I had money, do you think I'd be living off of you here?
Yeah, you don't have money. Never mind.
But, why do you look like this today?
That's what I'm saying. From Newsroom's Song Jun Seok to this...
Hey, look at me. A famous actor like me
is only doing these kinds of side roles. Does that make sense?
- Are you even that famous? You still haven't come to your senses.
- Shut up.
That's why you get dumped by girls.
Hey! I told you not to talk about Chewbacca— I mean, Seo Jin.
And, I wasn't dumped. We agreed to break up. Did I not tell you?
Alright, alright. I'm just going to go shower.
Suddenly a shower? You're really the worst.
Hey, wh-why are you dancing?
You stuck your tongue out? Don't shower, the water bill will be high!
Shut up! This is all because of you, so you take responsibility.
Why? Why is it my responsibility?
You're the CEO.
We're just investors.
You said we'd get tons of money if we invested. You said we'd be earning piles of money if we remodeled!
See the thing is with the global economic state and the whole gueshouse—
Be quiet! I'm the fool for trusting you and investing.
I'm the CEO only in moments like this.
Hey, hey. Look at that.
People have gathered to watch the meteor shower.
So, what? What about it?
Just that a lot of people are there.
But who's Yoo Seong Woo?   (T/N: Phrase for meteor shower in Korean)
What kind of person is he that there's that much fuss? A singer?
- An actor?
- Hey, are you kidding me?
Oh, a soccer player?
Wow.
Wow, I'm the one that's crazy for trusting you guys and living here.
It's all my fault! It's my fault!
So who's Yoo Seong Woo?
I feel like something good will happen.
Are we in a situation to be relaxing and watching the meteor shower?
Hey. This is the biggest meteor shower in history! We have to watch it.
You never know. If we make a wish on a star, money might fall right from the sky.
It's going to fall apart. Give up.
Why are you so negative all the time?
Then, what? We might be on the streets in a week. Is this a time to be positive?
That's why it's positive!
Woo Sik, listen to me.
Hey, Beanpole. Look.
Look at each other.
- This is the absolute worst, you know?
- So?
That's why I'm saying we've hit rock bottom.
Then, all that's left is for us to go up!
Do you think things could get worse from here?
This is the most positive situation there could be! Right?
Do you think that makes sense, you crazy bastard?
Yes!
Just die! It's a waste of oxygen for you to breathe. Just die!
- Hey, hey! Stop!
- Die!
Oh, hey! It started!
There! There!
Wow. So, that's a meteor shower. How amazing.
Right? Wow.
Hey, hey. Look at it.
Oh, hey look. That's so big, right?
- Right? It looks as if it's falling above our heads.
- Yeah.
- Right, Woo Sik?
- Whatever.
- But, isn't that getting a bit too close?
- Not sure.
Hey, it really might end up falling on our heads.
Grand Opening
A hundred million stars falling from the sky.
Hey, oh my gosh.
Hey. Where are you?
Did a meteor really fall?
On our guesthouse?
I think so.
So that's a meteorite!
Right?
This is so cool! How amazing.
That's so cool, right? Isn't it? It's a meteorite!
You said nothing could get worse.
You said all that was left was for us to go up! That we had hit rock bottom!
I mean, it's true that we hit rock bottom, but I didn't think we'd go through the bottom.
Shut up! Oh, look at that.
There's a hole on the ceiling, too.
If the landlady knows about this, we won't be kicked out. We'll be sued! Do you know that?
Hey! Is it our fault that the meteorite went through the floor?
- It's gravity's fault!
- Do you think she'll believe us?
Last time, when it hailed so much that our windows broke,
she blamed it all on us!
That was hail, but this is a meteorite in our guesthouse! It's a meteorite!
What do we do?
Gosh, now a meteorite has fallen on us.
Why isn't anything working out for us?
Oh, hey, hey!
Hey, are you okay?
Hey, what do we do? Hey!
What a genius! A true genius!
Are you able to eat that right now?
- Yeah, it's yummy.
- Yummy?
Hey, what if the boss catches us?
Gosh, stop whining!
I'll figure it out myself.
- What will you do?
- Just watch from afar, Sir.
You need to use your head.
Oh, I think this hole has gotten larger since last night.
See! It's done! It's done!
Wow, the TV's so huge!
Tada!
- What's this?
- Hey.
We should sell anything to get every single cent we can, even if it's valuable to us.
Let's see. Where was it? Oh, here!
- What's that?
- You know Randy Johnson, right?
The major league's legendary pitcher.
This is a glove with Randy Johnson's signature.
- If we sell this, we should be able to make some money.
- Really?
Gook Gi Bong, please be happy. I wish for your family's happiness. From, Randy Johnson. ^^
This is Randy Johnson's signature?
So, Randy Johnson wrote clearly in Korean and knows the phrase "I wish for your family's happiness?"
Well, he must've learned Korean.
Hey! Does that make sense?
It's fake! Fake!
No, it's not! I asked my senior for a favor and paid him ₩1,000,000 ($1K)!
And, look! What about this signed bat?
Gook Gi Bong-san! Please be happy-desu! - Ichiro
Alright, let's just say Ichiro learned Koren.
- Still, would he write "desu" in Korean?
- Oh.
"Oh"? Hey, Gi Bong. Use your head!
Shut up! So loud. I can't even eat.
Is it a crime that Gi Bong's stupid?
Come here, Gi Bong. As long as you're healthy, that's all that matters.
You're tall, and you're still growing!
I'm going to go insane.
What's this? Where'd this microphone with Jo Yong Pil's autograph come from?
I think this is Woo Sik's.
What are you doing? Get up!
- What?
- We have to fill that hole. Come back up.
Wow, this hole is bigger than we thought.
Since we have to cover it with the sofa, bring the sofa here then push it that way. Okay?
Alright.
Gosh, I fell in here! Why'd you push so hard?
You told me to push more! Why are you getting mad at me?
- Geez, you're so tall and strong, but so dumb!
- What?!
Hey, my foot's stuck here!
What are you doing? Hurry and help me out.
Wow, you are so much work.
CEO Cha? Are you here?
- Isn't that the boss's voice?
- Why is she here so early in the morning?
Hold on. She can't know about this!
- Hurry, hurry.
- CEO Cha!
I'll go down first and do something about her. You pull him out!
Alright.
Hello, Boss! What brings you here?
Oh, I just thought that I lost my earring here yesterday. Have you seen it?
Earring? No, I haven't.
Really?
Use some more strength!
I already am!
But, why isn't your foot budging?
What was that noise?
Wasn't there a noise just now?
A noise? No, I didn't hear anything.
Did I mishear?
Oh, but, where is it?
You must be busy, boss. I'll find the earring and bring it to you later.
No, I'll find it myself.
You heard that, too, right, CEO Cha?
A sound? No, I didn't hear it.
No! I heard it for sure.
I think it came from the ceiling area.
What are you doing right now?
So... Well, I love you.
What?
For a long time, I have loved you, Boss.
What are you saying?
It's a bit hard to tell you here.
Let's leave first! Let's leave and talk!
Come here!
Let me go! Geez, it hurts! Ow!
I'm sorry.
So, is that true?
- You love me?
- What?
How long has it been?
Well...
From six months ago.
Six months?
Is that why you didn't leave even though you were criticized so much?
- Yes.
- Oh, my.
So, that's why.
Oh, I never even expected this.
Even so, this really isn't right. There's such a big age difference between us.
And, I have a child. You know that.
A young man like you and me? That wouldn't make sense.
Right? Yeah, it doesn't make sense.
Of course not. This really isn't right.
I was being too ambitious. I apologize.
I'll be off then.
- Try being ambitious.
- What?
You can't just cut off your feelings for someone like that.
So...
You should be ambitious.
I like ambitious men.
What?
- You decided to date the boss?
- Yes.
Today's the first day of our relationship.
We have to go on dates now.
Why would you lie about something like that?
- What do I do now?
- No, no.
It's for the better. She won't ask for rent for a while.
Would she ask for rent from her boyfriend?
- Then, I'm supposed to keep dating her?
- Yeah!
Hey, that's a scam!
It's not! You can just officially date her.
She's an alright woman.
She has a lot of buildings, money, wrinkles, and years of age!
Look at yourself. She's overflowing with generosity compared to you!
Do you think that makes sense right now?!
Then, should we just start living on the streets?
This is driving me crazy. Why did things turn out like this?
Think about it. It's an opportunity!
I'm here.
Hey. Did you come back from your part-time job?
Yeah. I had three part-time jobs today. I feel like I'm dying.
What's up with him?
He has his reasons.
What's this box?
What's with this photo album?
Oh, that's our high school yearbook.
Oh, really? Should I take a look?
Oh, you all are so young.
Who's this? She's surrounded by so many boys.
Who?
Oh, it's Soo Yeon! Han Soo Yeon.
Our first love.
- First love?
- Yeah.
- "Our"?
She was the first love for all of you guys?
Yeah! She was! Not just us, but all the boys in our entire school!
Really? She's not even that pretty.
Hey! Kim Jeong Eun!
Gosh, you scared me. Why'd you yell?
You're being too harsh. Soo Yeon's not pretty?
Soo Yeon was a goddess! A goddess!
Hut, hut! Hut, hut!
Hey, hey! Huge news!
What is it that you're freaking out about?
There's going to be a transfer student in our class today. A girl!
She's supposed to be super pretty.
I thought it was something big. We're not interested in things like that.
Oh, here she is!
Gosh, I said I wasn't interested.
Move!
As soon as we saw Soo Yeon, we fell in love.
She had a nice face, body,
and even a bright personality.
She was perfection itself.
Not only was her family rich, but there was also elegance exuding from her entire body.
So, what happened? Did you confess?
Of course we did.
Knock, knock.
Have a drink.
Alright. Thanks. I'll drink it well.
If you drink it, we're dating.
Oh, what do I do?
I already saw you take a gulp.
So, today's our first day of dating?
That day, Soo Yeon vomited all her gastric juice, but also her bile.
Without a droplet remaining.
What about you, Gi Bong? What happened?
Hey, Han Soo Yeon!
With this ball,
if I hit it into that can,
we'll be dating.
That was the first day Gi Bong's pitch resulted in a home run.
His first love ended right there.
How pathetic. So pathetic.
What about you, Woo Sik? You didn't confess?
That doesn't concern you.
Geez.
What's with him all of a sudden?
I'm not sure. He's like that whenever Soo Yeon is mentioned.
Right?
Oh, it's the stunt director.
Oh, yes, Director?
One more person?
Yes, I know someone who can do it. Yes.
Alright, got it. I'll see you later!
- Hey, you said you're not training today, right?
- No, why?
The stunt director just called, and he said one of the actors didn't show up. We need to go.
Come with me.
- Stop it!
- Hold on.
Alright.
Hut!
It's no joke!
Hey, hey! Quiet down.
From now on, listen to me carefully.
This scene is where the gangsters' mountain hideout is discovered by the police.
It's a fight scene with the police officers.
So, you just need to follow exactly what we practiced. That's it.
- Do you understand?
- Yes!
Okay. Now, then...
- Oh, what was your name?
- Gook Gi Bong.
Oh, Gi Bong! Alright.
Gi Bong, since you're the first person, you'll be hit in the head by the police officer's baton.
Then, you'll be dead instantly. Just like that. Okay?
Don't close your eyes. Never! Keep them open. Then dead instantly!
I'm going to die with my eyes open?
I told you, you die instantly!
- Instant death!
- Okay.
And, Joon Ho...
I'm Joon Ki. Lee Joon Ki.
Oh, Joon Ki. Sorry, sorry. Joon Ki.
Joon Ki, you'll fight the police,
but you'll be holding the fire extinguisher and die instantly like that.
- Instant death.
- Instant death!
- Yes.
- Alright.
Okay, got it.
Instant death.
Oh, uh, what was your name?
Excuse me?
Go along with it.
Gook Gi Bong.
Oh, Gi Bong. That's right.
Gi Bong, so, what should we do with you?
Gi Bong, since you're the first person, you'll be hit in the head by the police officer's baton.
You already told me.
Instant death.
Oh, I told you?
Gi Bong, instant death. Yeah! Don't close your eyes.
- Oh, and, Joon Bong.
- It's Joon Ki! Joon Ki! Lee Joon Ki!
Oh, Joon Ki! Joon Ki!
Joon Ki, you'll fight the police,
but you'll be holding the fire extinguisher and—
You already told me! Instant death!
- Lee Joon Ki, instant death!
- Oh, I told you?
Okay, instant death. Okay. Everyone knows what they're doing, right?
- Okay, Director. We're ready.
- This is the director.
- It's me!
- Director, we're ready.
He's gotten worse.
Joon Ki, isn't he a bit strange?
He's always like that. He got an injury to the head while doing a stunt, so his memory only lasts three seconds.
Oh, I see.
Just be understanding.
So, Gi Bong, you'll die instantly!
Oh, I'll die instantly, too!
Joon Ki, you're dead today!
Ready, action!
Instant death!
Ow, ow!
Hey!
No, no! No!
No!
Cut, cut!
Hey, quiet! Director, it seems as if there's a problem with the fire extinguisher.
I'm the director!
Hey, hey!
Open your eyes! Hey!
Ow, ow, it hurts! I can't open my eyes.
My eyes won't open.
Hey, why would you hold your fire extinguisher like that instead of dying?
And how could you kill a guy who's already dead?
I'm sorry.
Hey, hey.
This is so sad. Here, hold on.
Just rest here.
- Thank you.
- How sad.
But, who's the one next to you? I haven't seen him before.
Oh, how many times do I tell you he's my friend?
Oh, really? He's your friend? Why is he here, though?
Obviously he came to film!
No, never mind. He came to visit.
Oh, to visit? Okay.
Oh, you did well coming to visit.
It's cool, right?
- Cool?
- On to the next scene.
Gosh.
Well, then...
Hey! What are you guys doing here?
Are you not filming?
We're resting because our eyes hurt! You told us to!
Oh, I did that?
Okay, I'm sorry. Just rest.
Geez! I'm going insane.
It's getting worse. Geez.
Ouch.
Stop it! Stop it!
I told you that you should should eat slower.
Oh.
Yes.
Why? Are you really that nervous to be with me?
What?
Oh, yes.
How cute.
I should've caught on sooner.
It must have been so difficult on your own.
I'm sorry, CEO Cha.
Oh, no, I mean,
- I'm sorry, Woo Sik.
-   Woo Sik?
This is driving me insane.
Hey, Cha Woo Sik? How much longer will you take this?
Even though you need to pay rent, this isn't right.
Yeah, that's right. I'll just be honest with her now.
- Boss.
- Yes?
There's something I must tell you.
What is it?
The thing is...
Hold on.
Hello? What? It was a lie?!
Don't you know that I can never tolerate lies?
What do you mean what are you supposed to do?!
Put him in prison this instant!
How dare he lie to me? You can't go easy on scum like this.
Even if I have to put all my assets on the line, I'm not letting him slide!
Whether it be a 100 or 1,000 lawyers,
have it so that he doesn't see sunlight again for the rest of his life!
I'm sorry. It's another new tenant.
But he lied. The thing I hate the most in the world
is lying.
But, what was it you were going to say?
Oh, about that...
I wish time stopped like this.
Oh, my. What do I do with you?
Gosh, I fell asleep.
Ow, it hurts.
What is this? Why is it so quiet? Hello?
Hello? Is there anyone there? Ouch!
Hello?! Hello, Director?
Is there nobody there?
Gosh, you scared me!
What is this? Why'd you yell?
Sorry, sorry.
Hey, it's weird. I don't think anyone else is here.
Do you think they left us here after filming ended?
Hey, hey. Call the director quickly!
Okay, good idea.
Are you calling him?
Hey, hey! We left our phones earlier. You fool!
Oh, right! Hey! What do we do now?!
How do I know, you fool?
Gosh, how could they leave without us when we can't even see!
Hello?
Hello?!
- Hello!
- There are people here!
Hello?! Hello!
Hello! There are people here!
How nice. I haven't walked with a man like this in so long.
But... Why have you been so pale and sweaty since earlier?
Are you sick?
No, it's not that.
What is it, then?
Oh, I can't with you!
Is this good enough? If you wanted to link arms with me, you could've said so!
You fool.
I'm going insane.
If she finds out the truth, it'll be a mess.
But, still, this isn't right.
I'd rather go to prison, I can't fool my conscience anymore.
Boss, I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Well, the thing is...
- Mom!
- Well...
Oh! My son!
Woo Sik! Say hi. This is my son.
- Hello.
- Mom!
Oh, my son!
Woo Sik, say hello. This is my second son.
Oh, h-hello.
Who is this?
It's someone I decided to date starting today.
My sons, you understand me, right?
Of course. We're fine as long as you're happy.
But... Didn't he approach you because of your money, like last time?
Oh, no! He said he's loved me since six months ago.
But, he finally mustered the courage and told me now.
What a relief.
Excuse me.
We won't let you be if you make our mom cry.
Woo Sik's not that type of person!
Oh, didn't you say you had something to tell me earlier? What was it?
Well...
I was just going to say it's a shame we must part ways.
Oh, my. Wow, you really say all you want! Even in front of my kids!
Hey, Joon Ki! Let's go together!
Just hurry and follow! Where are we?
Are we even going the right way? What is this?!
We should've just stayed there. They could've come back for us.
What? Come back for us?
I've known that stunt director for eight years.
But, he still doesn't know my name! As if he'll come back to look for us!
Still, how could we go on like this when we can't even see?
We'll just get on the street and find a taxi. Just follow me!
Alright. Geez.
- Hold on.
- What?
Oh, my stomach hurts all of a sudden!
Geez, I told you to eat only a little! You had three bowls!
What can I do about being hungry?
Gosh, where's the bathroom?
How can you go to the bathroom when we can't see anything?
Just do your business anywhere!
Alright.
But, do you have tissues?
Why would I have tissues in the middle of the mountain?!
- Just wipe it with your necktie!
- Okay.
Why do you keep getting annoyed?
How can I not be annoyed?!
Go do it. I'll be here.
My stomach.
Hey, Gi Bong! There are tissues here!
Scent Of The Woods Camping Grounds
How about we play a silent 007 game?
- That sounds good.
- If you make a sound, you'll get a punishment. I'll start first.
Oh, my stomach. Ow.
Ow, my stomach.
It's quiet. There must be no one here.
Geez, I thought I'd die.
Oh, right, my tissues.
Gi Bong!
Gi Bong! I had tissues!
What is it? What's this sound? Who are you with?
- Joon Ki!
- Yeah?
I pooped.
Waikiki Guest House
We couldn't get money and our eyes got hurt.
We just got utterly humiliated.
How could life be like this?
It's better than my situation.
I have to go to a theme park with the boss and her sons tomorrow.
She wants me to buy cotton candy.
I have my own sons now, too.
How come nothing works out for us?
I lived as best as I could.
Why does life never turn out right?
We had pretty great lives in the past, right?
Yeah, that's true.
When I think about the old times, I thought that by now,
I'd be in Carnegie Hall with an orchestral group
and having an amazing concert there.
I thought I'd be in Hollywood and getting an Academy Award.
I thought I'd be in the Major League and have my arms around Ryu Hyun Jin and Choo Shin Soo.
But, you know,
it's not over for us yet, right?
It's not time to give up, right?
Of course not. I'm never giving up.
Of course not. It'd be such a waste to give up now.
I have to strike out Choo Shin Soo before I give up.
Hey, hey. We're all Koreans here. Let's not be like that.
Don't be so harsh on Choo Shin Soo.
Is that so? Well, then,
I won't give up until Choo Shin Soo gets a homerun from my pitch.
- Yes, that's good.
- What?
Alright. Let's cheer up. Success is for those who don't give up.
- There's a saying like that. A yet seong in (ancient saint) said that once.
- Yeah.
Let's just try our best until the end. It'll work out somehow!
But, Woo Sik, who's Yet Seong In?
What?
You said Yet Seong In said those words.
Is there a last name of "Yet" in our country? I've never heard that surname before.
Hey, hey, don't do it! You'll feel worse.
Let's just sleep. I'm tired.
- Alright.
- Hold onto me.
Hey, take me, too! Who is Yet Seong In?
- Hey! Is he a scientist?  He's Chinese, isn't he?
- Shut up!
Hey! Take me, too! I can't see, either!
Be careful! Ow, it hurts!
Hold on.
Oh, I can see!
Wow, what is this?
Oh, my gosh! What a relief.
You guys live like this? Why?
But, what happened to Woo Sik?
Woo Sik?
He went... somewhere.
Mom, Mom! Let's just ride the carousel one more time!
- One more time! One more time!
- Again?
Woo Sik, you're fine if we ride one more time, right?
Whoa, Ajussi, you're the best!
Ajussi, you're the best!
Your Wedding
Oh, yes!
Hey, hey. I'm getting the first scoop.
Hey, if you're going to be like this, work at a ramen company!
One chopstick full.
Just take a little!
- You should just eat little.
- I didn't even take anything yet!
- I'm here.
- Hey, sit and eat ramen.
Hey. How was the theme park?
Hey, that headband suits you really well.
Did you buy her sons cotton candy?
Wow, do her sons say, "Thank you, Father!"
"Daddy, Daddy!
Shut up!
What is this? What is this?!
Why do those grown men like the carousel so much?
I rode that more than 30 times!
Just be patient until we get enough money for the rent and repair costs.
- Yeah.
- What?
With all those combined, it costs almost ₩ 10,000,000 ($10K).
You're telling me to keep this up until we save that much money?
Well, do you want to be on the streets, when it's all cold and windy out?
I'm going insane.
Who is it now?!
Oh, yes, Noona?
Oh, really? Okay! I'll be there soon.
What is it? What happened?
It's a sunbae who is a wedding planner. She said someone bailed on the congratulatory song for a wedding and wants me to fill in.
You're going so soon? Have some ramen!
Should I be eating ramen right now?
I'm going to get money as soon as I can and break free from this horrible situation.
So, you guys shouldn't be playing around!
Go out and get some money! Got it?!
Ouch!
Hey, it's time for my part-time job.
Hey, hey! Let's go together!
Let's keep eating.
- Noona.
- You're here!
I'm sorry for calling you so suddenly. The congratulatory singer got into an accident.
No, I'm thankful. I needed money fast, so it worked out well.
Really? That's good, then.
Let's greet the bride and groom first. Follow me.
Alright.
- Thank you.
- You're so beautiful.
Your dress is so pretty!
So pretty.
Han Soo Yeon?
Why are you being so shy? Let's go greet them.
Hello, Bride!
What's with you? Are you crazy?
Noona. Let's leave first. Please.
How can we leave suddenly?
Oh, I'm sorry, hold on!
Hey! Don't do this! What's with you?
Let go!
- What's with you?!
- I'm sorry.
Noona, I'm sorry, but look for another person. I'll be off.
Hey! Where are you going? Why are you being like this?
Don't ask. Just let me go.
No, but there's 30 minutes left before the ceremony. How can we find another singer?
You said you needed money fast!
Even if I need money fast, this isn't it.
I'm really sorry.
Alright, alright. I'll give you double the pay. ₩1,000,000 ($1K).
Noona, money isn't the problem right now!
- ₩1,500,000 ($1.5K).
- I can't do this!
₩2,000,000 ($2K).
Alright. Whatever. I can't take this any longer!
I have a favor to ask then.
Oh, yes, I wanted a consultation for a loan.
Oh, my employer?
I don't have one.
A collateral? I don't have anything.
Oh, a car? I have one!
Her name is Rebecca. She's a 2001 or 2002 model...
Hello? Hello?
They hung up again.
Gosh, I'm being looked down on.
What are you doing?
How much ramen did you use so calmly?
Eight packs.
Hey, we should eat a lot to get strength to work.
Alright. Keep eating. Eat up.
So hot.
Can't a pack of money fall from the sky?
A few days ago, a meteorite fell on a greenhouse in Rome.
- It fell here, too!
- They're calling it a lottery that fell from the sky.
- I wish.
- In the past, for a rare 500g meteorite,
it was sold for ₩500,000,000 ($500,000K).
The exterior is seriously blackened, however since the interior is denser than most rocks,
it is a defining factor to show that it might be a meteorite.
I'm serious! It's true!
It fell on the store a few days ago.
Yes, yes. The Grand Coffee Shop? I know of it.
I'll see you later, Professor. Goodbye!
Joon Ki, what'd he say?
He's an expert on meteors said that he'll see our pretty little thing before he buys it.
- Let's go.
- Hold on.
You're going to take Rebecca?
Yeah.
I don't want to get in that.
It smells weird inside.
Hey, she'll be hurt when she hears that. You smell even worse! Just go.
Hey! I'm serious.
You smell worse!
Let's go.
What's this? What's wrong with this?
Oh, it's fine. You said she smelled weird, so Becca's feelings were hurt!
Just close the door so that we can go.
I'm sorry.
It's totally fine.
You can just close it really gently. Like patting a baby.
I'm sorry, Becca!
Is this AI, or what?
It's fine! We can close them together.
All at once.
Let's go. One, two, three!
Joon Ki!
This is great!
But, how much do we have to sell this for?
Earlier, the news said it's ₩500,000,000 ($500,000K) for 500g.
Then, this much... Maybe ₩1,000,000,000 ($1M).
No, no. ₩2,000,000,000 ($2M)!
- ₩2,000,000,000?
- No, no.
We'll sell this, pay our rent, then...
I'm sorry to Rebecca, but we'll buy a great car.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Then, what else?
I want go to a fancy buffet and eat all I want.
- Oh, yummy!
- Then...
We'll go to the best sushi restaurant and have the best sushi.
Then... We'll have the best Hanwoo beef from the best restaurant.
Hey, hey. Hold on. What are you doing?
He's my meteorite. Why are you making plans?
Your meteorite?
Why is it yours?
It fell on my guesthouse!
You guys said that I'm the CEO and you are the investors!
So, I can just pay you for your investments.
If you're going to play it like that, then the boss is the true owner! How is it yours?!
How do you know?
I'll call her myself. Myself.
- Hey! Are you crazy?
- What do you want to do?
Do you want to go splitsies or not?
Or, I'm just going to call the boss!
Hey, don't do it, or you'll die! Don't do it!
So, hurry and answer me!
If not, I'm going to press call.
Yeah? Okay! You want to do this, huh? Then go for it.
Try it! Try it! Try it!
Hey, hey! Alright! I'm going to call!
You see it, right? I'm halfway there.
It's about to be connected!
If I let go, the call is going to go through!
- Don't do it!
- Hey!
So, let's go splitsies!
Hey!
Focus on driving!
Alright, now, the star of the day, the bride, will enter.
Please give her a big round of applause!
The bride is entering.
She's beautiful as always.
Because of money, I'm singing the congratulatory song at my first love's wedding.
Life sure is crappy.
- You animal.
- Shut up!
You scumbag.
Hey. We're going to split it exactly in half, okay?
If you say something else,
I'm going to call the boss right away. Got it?
Okay, okay!
Gosh, you're so cheap. Focus on yourself.
Hold on! Why are you holding it? Let's hold it together.
Oh, are you being suspicious of me right now? You think I'll run away with this?
You're just the type of guy to do that.
Hey, just get out.
How can we both get out as we both hold it?
Why not? I'll leave this way, too.
- Okay, then.
- Yeah, get out!
Hey. Hey!
Get out.
Hey! Lee Joon Ki!
Hey, you!
I told you not to play tricks!
- You're dead.
- I won't run away!
I won't run away!
- Let go!
- No!
Ouch! Do we have to go this far?
People are watching. It's my meteorite!
Let go, then. I'll take it myself.
No! You're not even my friend, you cheap bastard.
Then, if we're not friends, don't talk informally, Mr. Lee Joon Ki.
Oh, I'm sorry, Mr. Gook Gi Bong.
What do I do? The coffee shop is that way.
- No, it's not. It's that way.
- It's this way!
- You little...
Ouch!
My ₩2,000,000,000 ($2M)! My meteorite!
No! No!
Oh, my ₩2,000,000,000! My meteorite!
Is it not broken?
Hey! Hey!
What are you doing?
Han Soo Yeon.
There she is.
It's really Soo Yeon.
Wow, our first love is getting married.
It's a strange feeling.
Yeah. If one of us had succeeded with our confessions, we could be standing next to her now.
- Right?
- It could've been me.
Next, the congratulatory song is in order.
Please give a big round of applause!
What is that?
What is this?
What a peculiar congratulatory singer.
- You are all surprised, right?
- Is this the Masked Singer or what?
This person is a new singer who will be debuting soon.
So, he said that he cannot have his face shown.
We ask for your understanding.
Well, let's listen to the song. Please applaud!
There is a song that the bride and groom wanted,
but I do not know that song well, so I prepared another song.
What are you doing here?
Oh, Soo Yeon!
Oh, were you scared? I'm sorry. What are you doing, though?
Oh, I'm arranging the song I want to sing at the concert.
You're performing at a concert? Can I go?
Oh, yeah, of course. I'll give you my invite.
Really? Thanks.
The next song is class 2-3's Han Soo Yeon's request.
- I requested this song! How is it?
- It's good.
It's my favorite song.
Oh, really?
Should I practice this song and perform it for you in the future?
Really? You promise?
Promise me.
I sincerely congratulate you two.
Oh, and to the bride, please be happy.
Goodbye, Soo Yeon!
Be happy, Soo Yeon!
Next... The greetings will be made to the parents.
Good work! We survived thanks to you.
Here's your money.
No, thanks. I'm good as long as I kept my promise.
Promise? What promise?
- What about the money?
- Give it to them as a congratulatory gift.
Hey, hey! It's the masked man!
We enjoyed your song!
Gi Bong! Joon Ki!
What? Who are you?
It's me!
Hey, why are you here?
You... You're the masked king that sang Soo Yeon's congratulatory song?
Well... About that...
Why are you guys here? What's that rock?
This... This rock.
Whatever. Just leave. Let's go out and talk.
Yeah, yeah. Let's go.
What's he doing?
Over there!
What is this? What's going on?
This is a common scene from the movies.
Isn't that Soo Yeon's ex-boyfriend?
Sir, the company went bankrupt!
Leave!
- Bankrupt?
- Joon Gi, what's bankrupt?
♫  Hold my hand, follow me, Waikiki Waikiki  ♫
♫  It makes me happy every day  ♫
♫  Let's go, Waikiki Waikiki  ♫
Soo Yeon, let's leave.
My meteorite!
That's my meteorite, Gi Bong!
Hey! It's mine!
No! My meteorite!
Just let him go!
Let go!
♫  Hula hula hula hula hula Babe hula hula  ♫
Gosh. My phone is broken.
My meteorite! My meteorite!
My ₩2,000,000,000!
Who the heck took my meteorite?
Why would you come here with that?
Did we know this would happen?
It's good manners to watch your first love for the last time as she gets married!
And, you, you sang the congratulatory song to your first love!
That was for money!
Whatever! Our money is gone now.
For the last time,
can we just watch the security footage? Just once more.
We've already watched it ten times. Let's just go.
Once more.
- Give up!
- Once more.
You never know.
Hurry up!
Wait. Joon Ki, wasn't the trunk open earlier?
I don't know! It just opens and closes by itself.
I want to go back!
My ₩2,000,000,000!
The wedding hall was turned upside down!
Oh, they bragged so much about how rich they were,
they went bankrupt, the creditor came, and it was a huge mess.
Lee Joon Ki, I'm a fool for trusting you.
- Gosh, shut up!
- You and your ₩2,000,000,000!
It was my meteorite! Geez!
Stop fighting!
- Shut up!
- Stop fighting!
You shut up, too! We lost our ₩2,000,000,000!
- You call this a car?
- It's all wasted.
It's an automatic door now!
Geez.
Hey, hey, are you okay?
Hey!
Whatever. There's nothing to steal, anyway.
- Just throw this crappy car away!
- Go in!
Geez!
Wait! Hold on. There's a noise from the car.
What kind of noise would come from the car?
You must be going insane.
Shut up. Just go inside.
Come in.
Hey, hey.
What's with this? How strange.
What is it?
It's... Something's in there.
What is it? Move aside.
Hey, if you're fooling around with the meteorite, you're dead. I have a meteor trauma now.
What would be in here?
Ah!!!!!
♫  Why am I like this  ♫
♫  In my heart  ♫
♫  There are butterflies I can’t control  ♫
♫  When I’m in front of you  ♫
♫  It's always like this  ♫
♫  Please hold my hand tonight  ♫
♫   Waikiki Wonderland   ♫
♫  Let’s fly to the sky and go to heaven  ♫
♫  I’ve fallen for the fairy tale that is you  ♫
Preview
We met our first love for the first time in ten years.
We should leave a good impression.
- Is this the time to be talking about "first love?"
- Woo Sik!
That's your girlfriend?
- Should I just stay the night?
- What?
The boss has a mental problem.
She has a mental problem.
- I can't believe this.
- Action!
Are you Bidam?
- You—!
- Director! Hold on.
The bugs. The dust!
Kang Min Ho, come to your senses!
Oh, what's there?
We're stuck!
What's inside all of this?
- What do you mean? It's all for you.
- This?
Oppa.
I'm sorry. There's nothing I can do.
- Who is it?
- We're Soo Hyeon's first loves.
What about it?
♫  I want to look at you all night long  ♫
♫   Waikiki Wonderland   ♫