Who did you say it was?
What?
Hey, you scared me!
What's wrong? Who is it?
N-Noona is coming.
What!
Your sister is coming?
Is Yoo Ri really coming?
Yeah, yeah. Hurry and lock the front door!
- Hurry!
- Okay!
Hi.
My screw up, have you been well?
You're still as screwed up as ever.
Oh, look at you, my big bear. Your head's gotten bigger. How much bigger is it going to get?
Soon enough, you'll be tall enough to see all of Seoul!
Oh, Jeong Eun! Long time no see!
You've become much more masculine.
Oh, our...
I don't know you, right?
No.
Sorry. Sorry.
My cute brother! Have you been well?
Enough. Why did you come?
Why do you think? I came to see you.
I saw you on the show! Huam-dong Goat Man.
Be quiet. You saw me.
Just go now. I can't stand you acting like this any longer.
Go already.
You're too much. How can you do this to me?
I did everything to raise you without Mom.
That cold, winter day when you were boiling with that feverish cold,
I carried you on my back and crossed over three mountains.
I crossed that icy creek in my bare feet and ran to the clinic. Did you know?
There was no mountain in our neighborhood.
And we had a general hospital right next to our house!
Alright. Don't believe me if you don't want to.
There's nothing I can do.
If you tell me to go, I'll go.
Be well, everyone.
I'm going.
Sprinkle some salt.
Waikiki
Woo Sik, I'm going now.
Be careful not to catch a cold.
Make sure you eat all your meals.
- Be well, Woo Si—
- Bye.
Geez. He didn't fall for it.
He's gotten smarter since I last saw him.
Alright, Brother...
You're going to be like this? Okay.
Let's try it.
I Saw The Devil
- Is she gone?
- Yeah.
Weren't you too harsh on your sister? She was crying.
That was all acting.
Everything she does, besides breathing, is a lie.
You think this is the first time I've suffered because she fooled me?
Yeah. She's bothered us so much ever since we were young.
I know. It makes my teeth rattle just thinking about it.
Right. She's a dangerous person.
Anyway, this is an emergency.
Everyone, be on your toes. Don't ever accept her calls.
Don't talk to her. Don't even make eye contact with her.
If someone breaks these rules, you'll be kicked out. Okay?!
Okay. Of course.
- We got it.
- Ugh.
Be careful! Always remember.
Why did she show up out of nowhere?
Was I too harsh?
Oh, whatever. She'll go to Dad if she has nowhere else to go.
It's weird.
Why did my heart race when she was just applying medicine for me?
No... Do I have heart disease?
No, they didn't say anything during my health check-up. How weird.
What are you talking to yourself about?
It's nothing.
What...
Hey, Joon Ki.
Let's say that a girl does something to you that really isn't a big deal.
But, your chest was thumping and pounding all of a sudden. Why is that?
- Your chest was pounding?
- Yeah.
Your chest?
But, since your nipples are here, then your chest must be here.
Do you want to die? Don't say pointless things. Just tell me why.
What do you mean? It's because you like her.
What? Because I like her?
Of course. If you didn't like her why would your heart race?
Why? Do you have someone you like?
What, no. It's not me, it's my friend.
Friend? You don't have any friends other than us because your personality is horrible.
I do! Who do you think I am?!
Look at that.
That's why you have no friends!
So cold. Geez. Why is it so chilly?
What is this?
Noona! What are you doing?
Are you not going home?
Hey, Gi Bong.
Honestly, the thing is I don't have anywhere to go.
What do you mean you don't have anywhere to go?
Well... My roommate took our deposit money and left. I got kicked out.
Oh, I see.
Oh, Woo Sik said I'm not supposed to talk to you.
I see.
Well, I've done so many bad things before. It makes sense.
But, Gi Bong, do you know that feeling?
It's like... You've been thrown away and are alone in the entire universe.
That feeling.
It's like when you're on a baseball team, and no matter how hard you throw the ball,
throw the ball, and the throw the ball again, no one notices you.
If someone at least said, "Gi Bong, Fighting! Gook Gi Bong, Fighting!"
If they at least said that, those words would give you strength and you could get back up.
But, no one is by your side. They just call you loser and useless.
People just point fingers at you.
You know that terrible feeling?
I know.
I know that better than anyone else.
It was really hard all this time, right?
Yes.
Now, I'll be rooting for you.
Stay strong, Gi Bong.
- Gook Gi Bong, Fighting!
- Noona.
If someone held my hand,
or even my pinky, I'd be able to get back up.
- I'll hold it.
- Gi Bong.
I'll be on your side, Noona.
Even if Woo Sik ignores you, I won't!
- Gi Bong!
- Noona!
That bad bastard!
So, I really like Soo Yeon?
Geez, that doesn't make sense.
But why was my chest pounding?
I'm going crazy.
You're crazy! How could you not be if you're...
Hey, Cha Woo Sik, are you crazy?!
Yeah, I'm crazy. I'm sure of it.
Oh, I'm crazy.
Oh, what do I do?
Gosh!
Hurry up.
Oh, my heart's racing. I was so scared that we were caught.
I know, right? But, what's wrong with my brother?
I don't know.
Anyway, you should sleep in the guest room today. We have no other empty rooms.
Really? Wow, you guys must be doing great business.
But who was that girl I saw for the first time earlier?
She's our high school friend. Han Soo Yeon.
Is that so?
But her name sounds familiar.
Han Soo Yeon...
Oh! Isn't she Woo Sik's first love?
How did you know that?
Of course, I know. I read it all in Woo Sik's journals.
He had so many hearts by her picture in his journals.
Really? Wow, Woo Sik...
Wait. You read his journals?!
What? Hey! That's not important right now.
Right. I'm sorry.
But... Why is she here?
She rejected Woo Sik.
Oh, well, Soo Yeon had some special circumstances.
Anyway, you have to leave before Woo Sik wakes up tomorrow.
If I'm caught, I'm kicked out, too. You know?
I got it. Stop worrying!
It's warm. I finally feel like I can live.
Gi Bong, turn off the lights. The lights.
Yeah.
- Have a good rest.
- Alright. Goodnight.
You woke up now?
Yeah. Why are you up so early?
Oh, I have a part-time job. Do you want some bread?
No thanks.
Do I still like her?
No but why?
Does that make sense?
Why are you staring at me like that? It's making me feel bad.
When did I..?
Am I looking at you if I'm looking in that direction? Do you think you're a princess or something?
Wh-What? You really...
Hey. Why do you keep getting annoyed at me?
When did I? When?!
Forget it.
That little... Look at her and her attitude!
Why does it have to be her?
Wait. Is it because I've been single for so long?
It's been so long since I've touched a girl's hand
that it makes sense for my chest to pound.
But, what if it isn't?
What? You want me to put this on you?
Is this why you woke me up?
It's urgent. Just put that on my scar.
No! You do it yourself! Why are you asking me?
Hey! Just do it once!
Can't you do this for a friend? Have some loyalty!
Alright, alright. Geez.
What is this? Why  isn't my chest pounding?
Oh. Is it because she didn't blow on it?
Jeong Eun, I'm sorry, but can you blow once on it?
What? Are you crazy? I don't want to!
Hey, this is important to me!
So, just blow on it once.
Blow on it! Just once!
Gosh, what's with all of these requests?
- Is that good enough?
-   What is this? My chest pounding
seems to have been prevented by morning breath.
But, Soo Yeon and Jeong Eun are both girls.
Why isn't my chest pounding?
No. They're not both the same girls.
Jeong Eun is closer to a boy than a girl.
Now that I see it, her face looks just like Kim Dong Bae from when I was in the army.
That's it! This is why my chest isn't pounding.
My chest will definitely be pounding when another girl does it for me.
I need to find another girl. Another girl.
What the heck? What's with him?
Alright, let's go clean.
She's probably gone, right?
What are you doing there?
What?
You didn't leave yet? You said you'd leave before Woo Sik woke up!
Well, I was going to, but I'm not going to leave.
What?! Hey!
You said you'd be leaving!
I said that yesterday,
but I've had a change of heart. I'm sorry.
Wait. Noona, are you really going to be like this?
Alright, whatever. Do what you want.
I don't care if you get kicked out or not after Woo Sik catches you.
Oh, you will care.
I'll hold your hand.
I'll be on your side, Noona.
Even if Woo Sik ignores you, I will never!
This. What is this? When did you–?
Gi Bong, we're on the same boat now.
So, you should convince Woo Sik to let me stay here. Got it?
Geez. How can a noona like you exist?!
Gi Bong, let's change the sheets.
Gi Bong?
Gi Bong! What is it? Who are you with right now?
T-That, well...
What is it? Who are you with?
What is this? What are you doing in this guesthouse?
Oh, yes, got it.
Alright, continue with what you're doing.
Ha!
- What did you do just now?
- What was I supposed to do?
But, still, you did that without my permission—
You're the one that said if we're caught, we'll both be kicked out!
Gosh, I'm going to go crazy because of you!
That's why if you don't want to go crazy any longer, you need to quickly convince Woo Sik. Got it?
Whatever!
That little cutie.
Hey, hey! Hey!
What happened just now? Who was that?
Well... It's a guest.
Hey, a guest?!
Then, you kissed a guest?
Guest? Who? Who? Who?
You don't have to know! Hey. Where's Woo Sik?
Why are you searching for Woo Sik? Who was that girl?
- Hey.
- Where did all the female guests go?
Woo Sik. Woo Sik!
- Are you not worried about your noona?
- What? Why are you bringing her up?
It's just because I'm worried!
She seemed to have no place to stay when we saw her. How about we just let her stay here?
What are you saying? Don't you know what kind of person she is?
She can never stay.
Hey, she's your biological sister. Are you not even worried?
I said no, so that's that! What's with you?
You rude little bastard. Forget it!
Where are you going? Who was it?
Why did he bring my sister up out of nowhere?
Oh, another girl.
Oh? It's a girl.
Yeah. If this girl applies the medicine, my chest will pound.
I'm sure of it.
- Please do it.
- Alright.
What? Why isn't my chest pounding?
This girl is a girl, like Soo Yeon.
Why isn't my chest pounding?
No. They're not the same.
This girl is Japanese and Soo  Yeon is Korean.
Even though they're both girls, Japan is hundreds of kilometers away from Korea.
They're psychologically different, too.
We have a heartbreaking history between them, too.
So, that's why there could be an invisible barrier between us.
That's true. So, of course, my chest won't pound.
If a Korean puts it on, my chest will pound for sure.
I need to find a Korean. A Korean!
No! No!
My first kiss. I saved it for so long.
My first kiss was stolen by that devil-like creature.
I have to wipe off that devil's traces!
Wipe it off!
What? Gi Bong was kissing a guest?
Yeah! He was!
He was in the hallway. It was a passionate kiss!
Oh, wow, that's amazing!
Bunny
Gosh, this person is calling again.
Why? Who is it?
It's a part-timer I work with.
But, they keep calling me and following me around. I'm so sick of it.
What? They're doing that to   you?
- Wow, that person has such an extreme taste in women.
- Do you want to die?
It's a joke! A joke! Joke.
- I told him I didn't like him. I don't know why he keeps it up.
- Why don't you like him?
Well, our personalities clash.
- And, he looks like a bunny.
- A bunny?
Yeah! He has long front teeth and huge ears.
And, he has a long mustache like bunnies.
How could such a person exist? Geez, you and your lies!
Why does appearance matter? As long as their heart is kind, it should be enough.
- What's that? I think it's Bunny.
- It's not me.
Then, what is it?
What's this? Isn't this Gi Bong's phone? It's Coach.
Yes, Coach? I'm Gi Bong's friend, Joon Ki.
Oh, Gi Bong? Yes, hold on, Coach.
My stomach. Ow, where is the bathroom again?
Gi Bong?
- Gi Bong?
- What do I do?
Give me a minute, Coach.
Hey, what are you doing?!
Gi Bong?
Gi Bong. Are you here?
Wh-What is it?
Take the phone. It's the coach. It's urgent.
Oh, well, I'm not able to accept the call right now.
What are you saying? It's the coach! Why are you...
Oh?
Four?!
Four legs?!
H-Hey. Gi Bong.
What are you doing inside there?
Gi Bong. Ah!
Oh, yes, I got it.
Hi, Coach. Gi Bong can't come to the phone right now.
Yes, if you tell me, I'll deliver the message to him.
What are you doing right now? Are you crazy?
What would I do, then? I was almost caught by Joon Ki.
Why would you come in here, though? Hurry and leave!
Go!
This is driving me crazy.
So, convince Woo Sik quickly, okay?
Get out, I said!
Is that good?
What the? Why isn't my chest pounding?
This girl is a  girl just like Soo Yeon. She's Korean, too.
Why isn't my chest pounding?
Maybe
your hometown is...?
Jeju Island.
- Of course.
- You startled me.
Of course. Their hometowns are different.
This girl is from Jeju Island, but Soo Yeon is from Seoul.
Even though they are both Koreans,
Jeju is an island with a lot of wind, rocks, and women.
Jeju has many clementines, too.
A girl from Jeju who was raised eating a lot of clementines. Soo Yeon, a girl from Seoul who was raised smelling a lot of air pollution.
Of course they won't be similar.
That's true. That's why my chest isn't pounding.
If I ask a girl from Seoul to do it, it'll work.
I need to find someone from Seoul. Seoul.
Geez!
Hey! Tell me! Who is that girl?
Stop it!
Oh, Woo Sik!
- What is it this time?
- Can't you just accept your sister?
Why do you keep bringing her up?!
She's your one and only sister! Just accept her!
Let me live, please!
Stop! I said no!
You have no blood or tears. You're a bad man!
Gosh!
Why does he keep bringing her up?
Woo Sik, I have amazing news.
Gi Bong was in the shower with—
I don't care! I'm busy.
I got my first kiss stolen by that devil-like woman.
I even showed her my naked body.
Bear, I'm hungry.
I don't care if you starve to death.
Wow, we haven't eaten pizza in so long.
Jeong Eun! Jeong Eun, are you there?
What the heck? That's  his  voice!
"His"? Who? Oh, the bunny!
Tell him I'm not here, okay?
Hey! What are you saying?
What kind of man is he?
Is Jeong Eun here?
No. I haven't seen her.
Is that so? She hasn't been picking up. Where is she?
Jeong Eun!
Jeong Eun, hold on! Jeong Eun!
Jeong Eun, hold on!
Jeong Eun!
What are you doing? You didn't even knock.
I'm sorry. This isn't the time for that.
- Jeong Eun!
- What do I do?
Please just talk with me, Jeong Eun!
Hey, hey!
Gi Bong, if he comes in, tell him I'm not here.
No, tell him that I died. Okay?
What are you doing right now?
Why isn't Gi Bong picking up?
I'm so hungry.
How could a person look like a bunny?
That's so cool.
Gi Bong must be hungry, too. I should give him some pizza.
Who is it this time?
- Why are you here?
- I'm in huge trouble!
- Gi Bong!
- Oh, shoot.
Move! Move!
Are you crazy? Hey!
Gi Bong, you should have pizza. Wow, you have so many legs.
Two, four, six.
Six legs?
SIX LEGS?
Hey! Gi Bong! Are you doing that here?
Joon Ki, it's not like that.
Oh, yes, I got it.
Gi Bong, I guess this isn't the time for you to eat pizza.
Fighting!
Joon Ki, it's not like that!
- Fighting!
- Hey!
Geez! Noona, what are you doing?!
Is Joon Ki gone?
Is the bunny gone?
- Unni!
- Jeong Eun!
This is driving me nuts.
It's harder than expected to find someone from Seoul.
Should we start our interview, then?
Let's see...
Your name is Han Soo Yeon?
Yes.
Oh, your address is Huam-dong.
Yes! I've been in Huam-dong ever since I was born.
Oh, I see. Your father is bankrupt?
Yes, my father was scammed and had to claim bankruptcy.
That's how my engagement was broken off as well.
I'm living with my friends from high school right now.
Excuse me.
What is this? Why isn't my chest pounding?
She's a girl like Soo Yeon, another Korean, born and raised in Seoul.
Her engagement was broken because of her father's bankruptcy too.
She's living with her high school friends. Her name is the same!
Why isn't my chest pounding?
Geez!
What is this? So, I really do like Soo Yeon?
It's been ten years since I graduated high school.
I still have feelings for Soo Yeon?
Does that make sense?
No way. No, no.
Woo Sik!
Woo Sik, where are you coming from?
Hey. What's wrong?
Are you sick?
No way.
No! No, I said!
No!
What? What's with him?
Please, please...
God, our Gi Bong...
Are they still outside?
Yeah, they're right outside the door.
Anyway, you can't tell Woo Sik that you saw me.
Yes, Unni.
This is driving me nuts. Woo Sik will be here soon.
What are you going to do now?
Hey. First, you should get Joon Ki and that bunny-looking man away from here.
Gosh, alright.
You're still here?
Ah, well, Jeong Eun went inside this room, but she's not out yet.
No, Jeong Eun isn't in there.
No, I saw her go in there.
Oh, really?
If you're hungry, would you like some pizza? Do you want some carrots?
No! I hate carrots!
No! You look like you'd like carrots!
Gi Bong, what happened?
- What were you doing on the bed?
- It's not like that.
What do you mean? I saw it!
I saw those six legs. Two of those were yours.
Whose are those four legs?
I'll tell you later, so let's talk upstairs.
Really? You'll tell me everything? It better be in detail!
Gosh, okay!
Gosh, you scared me!
- You should come, too.
- Me? Why?
I'll tell you fun stories and I'll give you carrots. So, hurry!
I hate carrots!
Come! Come!
Unni, no one is here. Come out!
Noooo!
Why was my chest pounding again?
I guess I really do like Soo Yeon.
Oh, this is driving me nuts.
Oh, how did this come out by itself?
Oh, it wasn't this pen, though.
Oh, yeah, it's this one!
Wait.
Brother. Hi!
Leave this instant!
I can't take responsibility for your troubles anymore. Get out!
I won't cause any trouble.
I'll live quietly. Yeah? Woo Sik, please.
No! I won't take it anymore. Go, leave quickly.
Hey. You're being too harsh.
You allow that Soo Yeon or whatever, your first love, to stay here,
but why can't you allow your sister to stay?
You said she wronged you a long time ago, too.
So, you tried to curse on her and ripped her pictures!
What? How'd you know that?!
Why wouldn't I know? It was in your journals—
What?! You read my journals?
Oh, right. You like her, right?
Like her? Who said that?
- I heard everything you just said.
- You heard wrong!
What? Is that so?
I guess I really do like Soo Yeon.
When did you...?
Hurry and delete it.
Why? I guess Soo Yeon can't find out about it?
Is that so?
Thank you.
Brother, cola.
Okay.
- Pickles.
- Okay.
Here.
How yummy.
What's with you?
You said you'd never accept her this time.
Huh? Well, she seems to have reflected a lot on herself.
And, she's my one and only sister. I can't ignore her.
♫  I'm now even scared of tomorrow  ♫
What happened all of a sudden?
Hey, Gi Bong, that girl from earlier. I mean, those two girls.
What's with them? Who were they?
You don't need to know.
Girls?
Gi Bong had his first kiss with a girl he met for the first time,
and had a shower with her—
- So, that was Gi Bong's first kiss?
- Yeah!
Oh, I see!
Bastard!
♫   In that world   ♫
Loko's Vacation - Audition
- Look, sir, do I have the face of a king?
What are you—
Seeing how you can't respond, my face must be ambiguous—
Let's change the question.
Director, do I have the face of the main role or a supporting role?
Or...
the face of someone who won't pass at all?
Seeing your expression, I feel like I'll not pass.
Go on and tell me!
Do I have the face of the main role or the supporting role?
Why? Why does it have to be Han Soo Yeon?
I'm becoming more of a fool.
I'm crazy.
Woo Sik!
What's this?
Why are you two here?
You left your phone, so I came to give it to you. Here.
- Oh, thanks.
- Yep.
Oh, but why are you here, Soo Yeon?
Oh, Unni kept telling me to go with her.
Oh, I just wanted to show her where you work.
And, I was thinking about having tea here, too.
You know what this means, right, Brother?
What's wrong with you?
But, now that I look at it, you two look good together.
You're like a couple.
What are you saying?
Well, looking at it now, you two look great together. I can't believe it.
It's meant to be!
Noona, let's have a talk.
Hold on.
What are you trying to start?
Start? This is all for you.
All for me?
You said you like her,
so you should do well.
I'll set up the right atmosphere for you,
so you can just trust me.
- Just me.
- Are you crazy?
Did I ask you to set me up with her? I don't want to become more of a fool,
so just, please, don't do anything about it.
A fool? What's he saying?
The Story Only I Didn't Know
What? Director Ho Bael Suk recommended me?
That's what I'm telling you.
Let's work well together.
Oh, thank you! Thank you!
I was feeling a bit depressed lately because I had been failing a lot of auditions.
So, thank you so much!
But, what kind of role is it?
Oh, you're the main character's—
The main character?
Stand-in.
Stand-in?
Our main character has a similar vibe
and appearance to yours, Joon Ki.
But, a stand-in is a bit...
If you help me out here, I'll give you an important role in my next project.
Really? Oh,
I'll work hard!
I'll do great!
Yes!
Oh, then, who is the main character?
Oh, he's here.
Y-Yoo Min!
Welcome.
Why'd you tell me to come? I was busy.
Who is this?
This is your stand-in.
Greet each other. Joon Ki, you know Yoo Min, right?
Of course! Who wouldn't know Korea's top star, Yoo Min?
It's such an honor to meet you. I'm Lee Joon Ki.
Oh, well, I don't need to know your name.
Let's work well together.
Oh, okay.
Just drink that and leave. I have to work.
Alright, I got it.
Soo Yeon, I heard that you're Woo Sik's first love.
What? Oh, that's what I heard.
Oh, I see.
Then, is Woo Sik your first love, too?
What? No!
Why would mine be a loser like him?
Unni, I have another first love from high school.
He's super handsome, cool, and—
What's wrong with my brother?
He's the only person in our family that has an IQ over100.
He's been 15th in his class in elementary school, too. What's wrong with you?
- Noona.
- What?
Stop it. That's nothing to brag about.
Of course, it is. Fifteenth is pretty amazing.
Woo Sik!
Oh, yes, Boss?
This is a singer who's going to be performing starting today. Say hi.
Oh, hello.
- Hyung?
- Woo Sik!
Soo Yeon!
Oppa.
Wow, it's been so long.
It's the first time we've met since graduating high school.
Right? Have you been well?
I've been alright.
But, how did you end up living in the same house?
Huh?
Well, we have a bit of a situation.
Is that so?
Anyway, it's nice to see you guys. Let's have a glass.
We have no more beer.
I'll bring some more.
Alright, thanks.
But, you seem to have gotten prettier.
You've gotten cooler, too.
High School Band Association, Opportunity Performance
♫  All day today I only think of you  ♫
♫  It always makes me smile  ♫
It's Soo Yeon!
Why is she here so early?
I Love You
Oh, yes.
Oppa, are you going to be playing here from now on?
Of course.
Brother. Who's that man?
I was in a band with him in high school.
Really? Well, the atmosphere is a bit suspicious.
They have something between them, right?
Tell me. What's their relationship?
Soo Yeon's first love.
What? That's her first love?
So, you liked Soo Yeon, but she liked him?
I don't know.
It's not like that?
Oh, my brother's so pitiful. What do I do?
Alright, it's a good day. Let's have a glass.
What kind of man is being annoying and crying?
It's me.
Oh, Oh Dae Sik.
For ten years, I cried and regretted everything.
Did you really have to do it? My sashimi restaurant.
My mom, too. Did you have to take all of them?
Did it make you feel better?!
Do you know where this is? Do you want to die?
Okay! Done.
You can just do it like Joon Ki did.
Got it, Yoo Min?
Alright.
Okay, let's film.
Good work.
Excuse me.
That rude bastard.
Good work.
Joon Ki, I'm sorry for making you stand-in during rehearsal too.
It's fine. Don't worry about me.
My sashimi restaurant, and my mom, too.
Did it make you feel better to take them away?
You bastards.
Do you know where this is? Do you want to die?
Hold on.
Cut!
What is it, Yoo Min?
Oh, I have to film an ad this week. The stand-in should film the action scene.
The stand-in? But, you should at least do this much–
Will you take responsibility if I get a scar on my face?
No, no. Alright.
Hey, Joon Ki!
- Get in here!
- Yes, yes.
Also, don't fall to the ground when you get hit.
You should fly back and hit that table– No, that's too small.
Yeah, that one. You should fall down on that table
and break it. That'd be good.
Oh, there's no need to go that far.
This is my first action movie. Did you not know?
We should film properly so that my image lives on.
And, you know that we got investments for this movie because of me, right?
Alright, well, we'll go with that.
Joon Ki, fly over and fall.
On that table.
Okay?
Oh, okay. I got it.
Alright. You can do it.
Alright, let's go again.
Again.
Do it properly to make it seem real. Don't mess up my image.
Yes, I understand. Yes.
Oh Dae Shik, you've gotten weaker.
You're already weak?
Did you really have to feed me medicine?
Does that make you feel better?!
You little...
Cry. Cry!
Hold on!
Cut! What is it?
Let's go with the stand-in here.
I can't bruise my knee.
It's almost summer. I can't wear shorts, then.
Alright.
Lee Joon Ki!
Get in here.
Yes, yes. I'll do it.
Did you really have to feed me
black bean paste noodles on my last path to make you feel better?
Black bean paste noodles.
Hold on.
Cut!
Director, let's go with the stand-in here.
I'm not good with chopsticks.
Alright. Lee Joon Ki.
Get in here.
Yes, yes.
Gosh, this smell of pain relief patch. Are we eating patches or rice?
How many patches did you use?!
I don't know. My body hurts everywhere.
Why would you get a role that doesn't show your face and you suffer so much?
The director said that if I do it, I'd get a role for his next project.
I have to do it.
Hello?
Yes. What?
Oh, yes, got it. I'm on my way.
What is it? Who?
It's Yoo Min. He wants me to go to his house right now.
I'll be going.
Eat slowly.
Bye!
Things need to work out for Joon Ki. I feel so bad for him.
Gi Bong. You should get a job yourself.
From what I see, I feel worse for you.
What?
I'm better than you. You're living off of people younger than you.
What? Living off of?
Living off of? You!
Shut up! What are you doing when we're eating?
Gosh, you scared me.
- Is anyone here?
- Yes!
Who is it?
Seo Joon!
Gi Bong!
It's been so long.
- Who is it?
- I heard you guys met.
He's an upperclassman from high school.
What's up?
Oh, it's just been so long since I saw you guys, so I visited.
Good doing. Come this way.
What is this? Why'd he come?
Maybe it's because of Soo Yeon.
How do I know?
Brother! Brother!
He'll be worried now.
Well, I can't help but interfere now.
What is it?
Where is he?
- Do you see him?
- No.
Yoo Min Oppa...
He ordered something!
What is this?
Sir, tell us!
No way!
Your black bean noodles.
Gosh, I called you so long ago. Why'd you come now?
I came as soon as I got your call, though.
But, why would you make me have a disguise?
None of your business. Just take off your clothes.
What?
What? You want me to act like you're here?
You saw all the fans and paparazzi out there.
I have something important to do today, so do me this favor.
Why? You don't want to?
I'm your stand-in, but doing this is a bit...
Alright. Quit, then.
I'll have the director find a new stand-in.
A new...?
No! No! I'll do it.
I'll do it, yes.
You should've said that earlier.
Don't stay locked up in the room. Sit on the sofa so it's less suspicious.
Good luck.
Wait.
This is too much.
It was called Huam HS Volcano. They were legends!
Oh, you were the leader of Woo Sik's band?
He's good at singing and he's handsome, too.
If you said Yoon Seo Joon from Huam HS Volcano, everyone knew.
Right, Soo Yeon?
Yeah.
A lot of my friends would follow him because he was handsome.
Well, this guy here's alright, too.
In terms of face, Woo Sik is pretty good.
What? Noona. What are you saying?
Well, from what I see, you're more handsome. What about it?
Woo Sik is average compared to Seo Joon.
Well, he's handsome in an old-fashioned way. Sorry.
But, Woo Sik? He's handsome in terms of today's standards.
Girls these days like boys with a face like Woo Sik.
No way.
Then, should we ask other people? Let's bet. ₩100,000 ($100), deal?
₩100,000? Okay. Deal.
- Deal!
- Noona, let's talk.
What's with you?
Noona, what are you doing? Why would you make that kind of bet?
Brother, this is all for you,
- so just stay still.
- What?
What kind of nonsense is that?
From what I see, that guy is still interested in Soo Yeon.
What if Soo Yeon likes him again?
Are you going to have her taken from you again?
What am I supposed to do, then?
So, you have to be clear that you're handsome too,
that your looks are better than Seo Joon's.
You have to show that you're better than him.
You have to make Soo Yeon realize these things.
That's why Soo Yeon will be more interested in you. Don't you think?
Is that so?
Of course.
What kind of girl doesn't like a handsome boy?
I am on the cuter side of the spectrum.
I do look a bit rich too.
Of course. You're my little brother, after all.
From what I see, you'll win at this for sure. So, just trust me.
Alright, Noona.
Alright, should we make a judgment now
on who is more handsome?
So, let's start the vote.
You'll win at this for sure.
Just trust me.
Cha Woo Sik
Cha Woo Sik! Okay.
See?
I said Woo Sik was better.
Noona, stop it. You're embarrassing me.
There's no way.
Next!
Yoon Seo Joon.
It's a tie, neck-and-neck.
That's it.
Cha Woo Sik
Yoon Seo Joon
Cha Woo Sik I -
Yoon Seo Joon II
Yoon Seo Joon.
Yoon Seo Joon. Yoon Seo Joon.
Fourteen to 1?
There's no way. Does this make sense?
See? What'd I say? This isn't even a game.
But, who's that one person who voted for Woo Sik?
Their standards are different from everyone else.
Was that you?
No, it wasn't. I didn't vote since I'm a judge.
- Who is it?
- Who voted for Woo Sik?
Mr. Cha? Mr. Cha?
No one?
But, it was written in red. Cha Woo Sik.
Cha Woo Sik.
Who's the person who had the same feelings as me?
What is this?
No way. Woo Sik, did you write it?
No! What do you take me for?
Cha Woo Sik!
So, you wrote your own name?
You're really the worst.
There's no way. It was unexpected.
I can't approve of this!
Give me the ₩100,000!
Look! What's wrong with this face?
He looks like Park Bo Gum! If you look from a certain way, he looks like Gong Yoo's twin.
Look, in this way.
This way. Right?
Can you please stop?!
- Brother!
- Geez!
Brother!
Hey! Take back what you wrote!
How long do I have to be like this?
Oh!
Hey, it's our show!
When did he film this?
What if I appear?
We're meeting actor Yoo Min, who's all the rage these days.
Yoo Min, you picked up an action film this time. How is it?
Well, I am very lacking.
But, I just hope that I am not a burden to this show.
But, is acting not hard for an action show?
It's hard.
Yes, it's hard and tiring, but I am personally trying my best.
I could choose to use a stand-in, but that's rude to the fans.
- Oh, that's amazing!
- It's no big deal.
That's something that should be obvious.
I'm a huge fan of yours, Yoo Min.
Thank you.
Yes, Sunbae?
Are you doing well?
Yes, yes.
What are you doing? Who are you talking to?
The person I told you about.
Oh, the person you placed at home? The scarecrow?
What are you saying? When did I say that?
Scarecrow?
I'll be there soon, so keep it up.
Wait, wait.
What? Scarecrow?
Yoo Min, you're looking down on me, aren't you?
Thanks to you, Noona, I'll be eating so much!
Noona, I'll eat this well. Thanks!
Woo Sik, thanks for being ugly!
Shut up and eat.
I'm sorry, Noona.
It seems like the mood has soured because of me. Should I show you something funny?
What is it?
Alright.
Look carefully.
What is it?
- This tissue has nothing, right?
- Yeah.
With this tissue, I'll cover the glass.
Alright.
What do you think happened?
I think the coin disappeared.
Alright, look carefully.
Nothing happened at all.
Soo Yeon, give me your hand.
My hand?
Abracadabra.
Alright, your hand is going down.
Wow, awesome!
That's awesome! Wow!
It disappeared!
Look! Woo Sik! The glass disappeared!
You call that a talent?
In terms of talent, Woo Sik is the best.
What are you saying?
What? You have a talent, too.
It's more fascinating than that.
Woo Sik?
No way. What kind of talent would Woo Sik have?
- Are you looking down on Woo Sik right now?
- Yeah.
You want to bet? This time, we'll bet ₩200,000 ($200). Okay?
₩200,000, okay, sounds good!
Hold on, Noona. Let's have a talk.
Noona, why do you keep doing this?
You have to retaliate!
Didn't you see Soo Yeon like that magic trick?
So, what am I supposed to do?
What else? You need to prove that you have talents, too.
You need to show that your talents are way cooler
than Seo Joon's.
You have to show that properly.
But, a talent competition? How childish.
Childish?
Alright, don't do it.
I don't care if you get your love stolen from you like a fool,
so just do what you want.
I do have one talent.
What?
Stop it!
Why?
Don't you know? The mood was ruined.
This isn't going to work. We'll have to make the winning move.
The winning move?
Don't do anything. I'll take care of it.
Just trust in me.
Alright, that was just practice. This is the real one.
Cha Woo Sik, get in place!
Everyone, be prepared to be startled.
We're going!
What are you doing right now?
What? We have to do this much to win.
Woo Sik,
you're the winner now.
What?
Winning like this is so meaningless.
I'm going crazy because of you!
Woo Sik, where are you going? You won!
You win!
Win? The player left, so it's a forfeit.
Alright, I won some money!
Joon Ki?
What is this place...
Joon Ki!
Gi Bong, you're here!
Wow, so this is Yoo Min's house. What are you doing here?
None of your business. But, is this what I told you to borrow?
Yeah. Why'd you ask me to borrow this? And, why'd you want the signed bat?
I need them.
Alright, should we start?
What do we do now?
What else?
We're going to have some fun.
Fun? How?
How? Like this.
- Like this!
- Stop hitting me!
You're dead today.
Ow! Ow!
Joon Ki, come down!
What are they doing?
What are they doing? Wow!
What is that? Don't take pictures!
Top Star Yoo Min Has a secret, special hobby!
Who is the cat woman that appeared in Yoo Min's House? // Yoo Min's peculiar personal life revealed!
Yoo Min #1 on trending
Top Star Yoo Min Has a secret, special hobby!
Wow, they're so fast. The articles are already up!
Can we do this?
Don't worry. I'll figure it out.
Oh, it's Yoo Min!
- Superstar Yoo Min, what's up?
- Hey.
What is this article? Just what did you do in my house?
What? What did I do?
Are you asking because you don't know? You better explain to them that it isn't me.
Explain that you were my stand-in today!
Stand-in?  No way.
Aren't you a person who does everything himself and doesn't use a stand-in to not be rude to your fans?
- What?
- Hey.
You're rich, popular,
and you even have a girlfriend. Why did you
have to take everything from the side actors?
Did it make you feel better?!
- What did you say?
- Hey.
Just wait a little bit.
I'm going to succeed and make you my stand-in. Got it?!
There's not much time left, so just wait!
I'm hanging up!
Good going.
Because of Noona, I did that in front of Soo Yeon.
This is such a humiliation!
What are you doing here?
S-Soo Yeon.
Why are you here?
You weren't coming in, so I came looking for you. Why?
Why'd you go overboard? How embarrassing.
Yeah, it was embarrassing.
Meeting your first love for the first time in ten years and doing that in front of everyone...
must've been so embarrassing.
What? First love? Who?
I know.
Seo Joon is your first love. That's why you'd always come to our rehearsal room.
What are you saying? He isn't my first love.
Yeah, right. I didn't even know and
I wanted to play you your favorite song,
so I'd practice guitar all night and end up with bloody fingers.
But, whatever. I'm a fool for misunderstanding.
It wasn't a misunderstanding.
What?
That wasn't a misunderstanding.
Can't believe someone like you was my first love.
What? What are you saying?
My first love is you! Cha Woo Sik, you were my first love.
You said I wasn't yesterday. You said it was someone else.
Well, how could I just admit it with you right there in front of me?
Do you remember the time we met in the music room?
That wasn't a coincidence.
Live Forever!
Volcano
What are you doing here?
Oh, you startled me.
Oh, Soo Yeon.
Were you scared?
I was just passing by and I heard the guitar.
Really?
Then, what about what happened on the day of our performance?
What do you mean?
On the day of our performance, in the rehearsal room,
you and Seo Joon kissed. I saw it.
What? What are you saying? Kiss?
It wasn't like that.
Soo Yeon.
It's not the time for the performance yet, why are you here so early?
Oh, just because. Where is Woo Sik?
I'm not sure. He'll come by soon.
Thanks.
Oh, wait, no.
What are you doing?
Soo Yeon, what's wrong?
Are you crazy?
Why would you do that out of nowhere?
Didn't you like me?
What did you say? No!
Give me the bouquet!
Cha Woo Sik, you fool.
To be honest, I like you.
I was waiting for your confession, but I'm confessing first.
Good luck on your performance today. Fighting!
Is that true? You should've told me!
How could I tell you? You didn't even talk to me after that day.
You always avoided me and ignored my calls.
Hold on. Then, all this time, did you get all annoyed with me and criticize me because of that?
No, it's not like that.
Yeah, even though you're a loser, you can't be that much of a loser.
It's cold. Let's go in.
You can go in first. I'll go in later.
Alright. Hurry on in.
Darn!
So, I was her first love?!
So, I've been resenting Soo Yeon for ten years without knowing that!?
Gosh, you fool! You fool!
Geez!
Ow!
♫  Hold my hand, follow me, Waikiki Waikiki  ♫
♫  It makes me happy every day  ♫
♫  Let's go, Waikiki Waikiki  ♫
♫  Let's love ye~~  ♫
Preview
Her first love was me!
Woo Sik, are you seeing someone lately?
Did you really meet her?
Like you said, I think Soo Yeon really does like me.
Sell my dream?
Nothing's worked out for me lately.
You're not going to use the bathroom until tomorrow?
There was an audition I wanted to do for a movie, and they told me to do it!
I'm going to buy my dream back.
"Dream Value"
Yeah!
Gi Bong, good luck today.
-  You, too.
- Don't be too startled.
He's superstitious, he has to do everything four times.
He's in the same team?
I need to finish it with this ball.
No matter what!
Let's go!
♫  Let's go, Waikiki Waikiki  ♫