Episode 1
From time immemorial, there were two suns in the sky,
as well as two moons.
Thus, the days were extremely hot, and the nights were very cold.
All of creation was in chaos, and mankind was miserable.
Then, a hero appeared and used arrows to shoot down one sun and one moon.
Only then was there peace in the world.
It is true...
Isn't that right, nephew?
Even though he was born out of a different womb
he considers his half-brother as within his own bloodline.
That is why...
There are villainous groups forming that treat Prince Ui Seong as the king.
So, what can we do?
We cannot sit and wait patiently for a hero to appear.
I apologize, but I do not understand the deeper meaning of the words the Queen Dowager is using.
Become the savior.
Prove your loyalty.
When His Majesty waivers so that he can't act directly...
Become the hero by acting forcefully.
There is only one sun in the sky and there is only one throne in the palace.
The very existence of Prince Ui Seong is a threat to the king's tenure on the throne.
He is a "sun" that must be shot down at any cost.
Subtitles brought to you by the Eclipse Team @ viki.com screenplay by jin suwan
(Prince Ui Seong- King Seong Jo's
younger half brother)
Who gave you an order to kill me?                                                                      Whose orders are you acting under?
What's wrong?
What's going on?
Where do you think you are going at this time of the night?
Didn't you sense it too?
It was a murderous aura for sure.
Even if you go, there is nothing you can do.
Nevertheless, I am compelled to go.
That person...
That person is in danger!
A-ri!
Ari!
Halt!
It has been awhile...
Lord (Prince) Ui Seong.
You, who came and went through my doorway so freely...
and you who tried to use me as a means of support to gain power...
Did you find a different tactic?
Or did you find a different person to support?
I did.
I'm thinking about supporting the king now.
Didn't you say that even a dog or a cow desires power lately?
Isn't it true that politics are for a worthy person...
Not for just anyone?
His Majesty is not a person to be swayed
by a false conspiracy!
His Majesty ...
Who do you think he will believe?
Unfortunately, there will be no chance for you to meet His Majesty.
Before you can ever meet him,
I will guide you to the heavens.
Do not fear...
Your best friend, Lord Dae Seon...
will be waiting ahead for you.
Why did he...
WHY HIM?!?!
All the so-called criticsm he sends up are all aimed at the king's maternal relatives.
It's no wonder that the Queen Dowager, the King's mother, is unhappy.
It is a beautiful night.
If the moonlight accompanies you,
then going to the grave isn't so bad.
Follow her!
This belongs to a shaman from the Royal Office of Shamans. [Seongsucheong]
Search around here carefully!
If she's alive, we must kill her.
If she's dead, we must find her body!
Yes sir!
The Chief Shaman is here.
Where is Ari?
That is-
Ari..
Ari, is it?
She is said to have divine powers.  She and Nok Young are candidates for the future Chief Shaman position.
She is wounded so she couldn't have gone far.
We're searching the entire forest so, soon...
Love between a royal and a shaman?
It seems as though the heavens are aiding us.
I do not know what you mean.
That girl, Ari, was a slave in Prince Ui Seong's home.
If there were something between those two, then a lot of people probably know about it.
Then isn't it more dangerous?
Why is that?
For a woman, love includes sacrificing herself for love.
It is not impossible that, risking death, that girl, who witnessed everything, is rushing to the palace.
If we can't immediately find the girl .....
What if she hopes that the person she loves should sit on the throne,
and she has created a talisman to fulfill that hope?
It is in the realm of probability.
However,
we don't have any evidence of that girl using a talisman.
The Chief Shaman of the Office of Royal Shamans does my bidding.
What is the problem?
Marshall your forces.
On imperial orders arrest the traitor.
[King Seong Jo]
Are all the contents of the letter true?
There seemed to be a conflict among the traitors.
Minister Hong Man Ho atoned for his sin by dying.
He wrote a letter and committed sucide as a punishment for his crime.
I'm guilty.
It is because I didn't do my best. I missed the opportunity to catch all the traitors.
Your Majesty, please mete out my punishment.
Your Majesty.
Show respect for the Chief Shaman from the Hall of Royal Shamans!
Chief Shaman...
Tell me everything you know about that talisman.
This talisman will enhance the sun's power.
Are you sure?
In front of Your Majesty, how would I dare to utter an untruth.
This talisman will certainly strengthen the sun's power.
Tell us also to whom it belongs!
It is a talisman made by the shaman Ari from the Royal Office of Shamans.
It is assuredly that child's creation.
Where is this shaman named Ari?
They say she is fleeing.
Make sure you arrest that shaman.
What is going on?
Why is it so noisy?
Th-th-there, a person!
No...a body. N-no a person!
Let me down.
The baby will be shocked madam.
Please, go back into the palanquin!
A person is dying, how can I ignore that?
Are you coming to your senses?
I will clear...
your name...
This won't do! Put her inside now!
Huh?
How could we put a person in the palanquin without knowing her identity...?
Look here, I need your assistance!
Halt!
What seems to be the problem?
We are looking for a fugitive who is wanted for high treason.
I need you to open the palanquin.                                   A person who committed high treason?
It can't be done.
How can you look through a palanquin with a lady in there?
Ah!
Is there a problem?
Why have you prevented us from going?
We are looking for a fugitive wanted for high treason.
Please come out.
I am on my way to offer devotions for my soon to be born infant.
It is a bit uncomfortable for me to get out, but if you still harbor any suspicion, you may follow me to my house.
What will you do?
Will you go together with me?
I am deeply sorry.
Let us go.
Stop!
You are going to have to step out...
Oh my!!
Blood! Blood! Blood is visible!
The doctor said to be careful too!
Please, allow us to be on our way!
If we don't go, something terrible could happen!
It is the Chief Scholar's child!
If something goes amiss, will you accept responsibility?
Clear the way!
Go! Go! We must hurry!
Madam! Please wait a bit longer!
I don't know how I can repay this kindness.
Because of me, this lowly thing, you ruined your beautiful garment and lied about starting labor.
It wasn't a lie.
I really felt like I was dying earlier.
Not I, but this child saved you.
The girl is as radiant as the moon.
Then, this baby is female?
And so it is.
You said you are a shaman, so it must be true.
I have been wishing for a daughter.
Is the baby really a girl?
Yes, it is.
A girl born with an honorable fate....
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
I just got a little dizzy...
Will you be all right by yourself in this condition?
Please do not worry about me.
The kindness you have bestowed upon me
will not be forgetten even if I die.
I'm no shaman, but I can judge character.
You are not a bad person.
Madam!
I will protect your child no matter what, even if I die.
Stop.
Who commanded you to make this?
I have no knowledge of that talisman.
It's still not too late.  If you are honest, your body will be intact for burial.
I did not write that talisman,
So how could there be
someone to command me to do it?
There is incontrovertible evidence of your abetting the traitor!
Will you continue to deny it to the end?
Did you just say traitor?
Evidence you say?
If you aren't a traitor by fabricating this false accusation, then who could be the traitor?
How dare you lie!
Will you not believe it until you see it, you low wench?
You scoundrel!
Do you think I am the only one who witnessed it?
Do you think that if you get rid of me, it is the end?
Wrong, you prevaricating knave.
The moon in the heavens was watching you.
That person's blood isn't the only thing which drenched your sword blade that night.
There is also the moonlight from that night.
Wait and see!
Some day the moonlight will reveal all your deeds.
One day that moonlight will end your life!
WHAT ARE YOU ALL DOING?
What are doing that you're all distracted?
Resume the torture quickly!
Yes!
Just for a short moment.
If anyone discovers this,
our heads will roll.
Ari...
Ari!
How can you.
How can you be such a fool?
What did I say? I told you there was no hope if you went!
I never hoped that he would ascend to the throne.
That person thought the same.
I know. How can I not know your innocence?
Then that's enough.
If you know the truth, that's enough for me.
What do you mean that's enough?
I know and I couldn't do a thing about it!
Neither can I save my friend from being unjustly accused!
Do not shed tears for me.
All of this...
...is heaven's will.
What's the use of this fatalism?
Who cares about the heavens!
It would be better to tell everthing to His Majesty.
And you and I-
There is a child you must protect in my stead.
Although getting close to the sun will cause devastation to her family,
The child is one whose fate is to protect the sun.
You must protect and keep the child safe.
What are you talking about?
Look here!
Quickly come out.
Who is the child I need to protect?
I am not long for this world.
You must survive and protect the Office of the Royal Shamans.
Who exactly is this child?
Look here!
Let's go.
Ari!
Quickly go!
Two suns and...
...one moon.
I pray you three will survive what is to come.
She really is as beautiful as the moon.
Yeom, isn't your little sister really pretty in your eyes?
Yes, she's really pretty.
Child, your name is Yeon Woo, Heo Yeon Woo.
Your father gave it to you
before he was sent as an envoy to China.
Do you like it?
There's a child you have to protect for me.
Subtitles brought to you by the Eclipse Team @ viki.com
You're here.
Where did the red parasol and the box that was here go?
Madam, the honey fruit that was on the table has disappeared.
Have you seen the garments which were put here?
Crown Prince, Your Highness, it is time.
A lot of time has already passed.
Please quickly don ...
Hidden Moon Building
Yeon Woo!
Why are you not coming out?
Oh my...
You don't get motion sickness?
Make haste.
or you will miss your brother's good show.
Minister of the Interior Yoon Dae Hyeong.
Office of Special Advisors, Chief Scholar, Heo Yeong Jae.
Subtitles brought to you by the Eclipse Team @ viki.com
Yeon Woo.
Look over there.
Your older brother is right there.
Although he isn't as good as my son,
Woon also has great looks.
By Woon you mean?
That's right. You must have never met him.
That person over there is called Woon.
Along with Putera Yang Myung, he was taught by your father.
They are your brother's closest friends.
You know that, right?
The top students in literature and military strategy, they all studied under your father.
It looks like a great feast must have been prepared this time.
It looks like the valley will be empty again.
He was still here an hour ago, he must still be in the palace.
If the King finds out about this, both you and I-
will suffer dire consequences.
Move quickly!
At once!
Yes!
His Majesty is here!
Start the music!
Bow down and pay your respects!
I can't ruin my complexion.
Top Literacy Student Heo Yeom
and Top Military Student Kim Jae Woon,
come foward.
Second place Kim Sae Min
and third place, Im Byeong Wook,
come forward.
Just look at your father.
He looks so happy.
Look.
Do you see how the ends of his lips are pointing down?
That's the expression he has whenever he forces himself not to smile.
From what you are wearing, you don't look like a palace maid. Why are you in the palace?
As for you, why are you climbing the wall?
I will be asking the questions.
Are you unable to answer?
Don't you know that breaking a palace rule is a major crime?
I'm here for my brother's ceremony, he is getting an award for Top Military Scholar.
And how am I supposed to believe that?
Believing it or not is up to you.
But I can't stand someone stealing things from the palace.
I should be calling the guards right now.
Palace guards, to say I stole something from the palace?
I was simply searching for a way out.
I also came to see my brother get the Top Literacy Award.
No...
I came to see my brother get the Top Military Award.
This is... that is.. His Majesty bestowed it upon my brother.
Over here! A thief is in the palace!
Here in the Hidden Moon Building!
Who's there?!
Subtitles brought to you by the Eclipse Team @ viki.com
This is because of you!
If it weren't for you, there would be no need to run this far!
Did you just tell me to follow you in informal language?
Isn't it obvious, as you must be younger than me.
How are you so sure that I am younger than you?
What is your age then?
Subtract 2 from your age.
That means you're barely 11 years of age.
So how...
So then you're 13 years old!
Look at that.
I'm two years older than you.
Where are you going?
Like I said before, I'm going to the palace guards and...
Didn't I already say?
I'm not a thief!
I came to see my brother who came in top for the military exam.
How is it that whenever you open your mouth you blame others and come up with lies?!
The top military student is my brother's close friend.
That person doesn't have any younger siblings.
I-Is that so?
That person doesn't have younger siblings?
I understand.
I'll tell you everything.
What's the use of hiding things any longer?
I wanted to meet my hyung.
Do you now have an older brother who passed the military exam?
No.
Not at all.
My older brother...
...was born from a different womb.
More than anyone else I know, he is warm.
He is skilled in everything
but he is someone that cannot participate in the civil service exam.
He is an important member of the country,
but he is someone that cannot advance in position.
He respects his father,
but he is someone that cannot receive his father's affection.
Though he receives love from many people,
he is someone that cannot do things in front of many people.
It is my fault that my brother has to live like that.
Maybe he's afraid of his father's harsh glare, but it's been a long time since he's visited me.
And that is why I was personally going to go and visit him.
Has my explanation satisfied you?
Why are you blaming yourself?
What?
You being a legitimate child, and your brother being an illegitimate child...
It's not something you have decided by choice.
So why are you putting yourself at fault?
Before didn't you scold me for blaming others whenever I open my mouth?
A man of virtue, doesn't blame the heavens
and people, is what I've been taught.
You've read Noneul?
Plus, a farmer doesn't blame the fields and a musician doesn't blame the instrument.
The problem is in the person that became the owner,
it is not in the object.
If your older brother is warm-hearted as you, Young Master,
then...I believe he doesn't blame you.
Therefore, Young Master, don't blame yourself or others.
Truthfully, aren't policies about legitimacy something His Royal Majesty the King is supposed to determine?
If it's something that prevents talented people from succeeding and breaks brothers apart
then shouldn't it be fixed?
There are many parts of Joseon's laws that do not make sense.
Noblemen and slaves are all the same people but it's strange to place ranks.
And my father always says it's going against laws for women to read too much.
So the King isn't managing politics correctly,
is that what you mean?
That's not it.
This time it looks like I should go to the palace guards.
Please don't do that.
Then...what should I do?
Just..pretend you didn't hear my words earlier.
Then do you now understand that I'm not a thief?
No.
Why?
What else is the problem?
Where did you get the items in your bag earlier?
They are mine.
Everything is mine.
Are you done now?
They were all expensive items.
How could you possibly have those kinds of things?
I tolerated you because I thought you were cute.
But now you're out of line.
Are you showing me disrespect now?
I am this land Joseon's-
eunuch.
It's been over an hour since she's been missing.
She didn't go to her palanquin so she's definitely still in the palace.
Please find her for me.
Please find-
Please tell me.
How much are eunuchs paid that you're able to acquire such things?
Yeon Woo!
Mother!
Oh, my child!
Stay still. Just stay still.
Where have you been?
Don't say a single thing.
Not a word.
If you open your mouth, I'll make you have a hard time.
Excuse me!
I acknowledged my crimes, and handed myself over to the authorities.
Are you now satisfied?
Ah! The items I've stolen are all at the Hidden Moon Building
so let's go there.
Wait a second miss!
Wait a second!
I was told to give this to you.
By whom?
He said you'll know if I say "Hidden Moon Building Young Master."
Ahh, you're talking about that eunuch.
But, what is this?
There are many things I want to say.
But I'm frustrated that I can't.
Tell her that the more I think about it, the more angry and wronged I feel.
If she's a smart child, then she'll understand what this means.
Were there any other messages?
Tell her, to be careful at night from now on.
-was what he said.
He's worried about my safety at night. As expected...
He wasn't a bad person afterall.
So what tempted you so to try and leave the palace?!
What does the palace lack that you keep attempting to leave the palace?!
I just wanted to meet Yang Myung Hyungnim
and discuss our studies together.
You should be discussing your studies with your teachers!
I'm sorry to say this but I
was never inspired by any of my classes and educators.
What?
How can I break down walls when there is not even a single debate?
How can I face the world when I'm never questioned?
Those things that are impossible to be done here...
are possible when discussing with Hyungnim.
So that is your excuse for climbing over the wall?!
Since both the front and back are blocked,
for a moment, I looked to my side.
How did you all serve the Crown Prince to come to this point?!
Transfer all the educators, and until new educators are selected ___ should take over.
Crown Prince, from now on you will study into the night to compensate for the time you wasted.
Plus you will not take part in trips to the temporary palace.
Queen Dowager, the Minister of the Interior is here.
Enter.
You asked for me?
Welcome.
Isn't this a bonsai tree?
These days I'm quite entertained in raising them.
What do you think?
The structure of the branches are gaiety and matured.
It's glorious, as if it's a pine tree growing in the desert.
Do you know what the purpose of bonsai trees are?
Isn't it about raising a small thing to your liking?
You're right.
But the thing about bonsai trees is
that it's more difficult than you think.
If you miss the timing, it becomes quite difficult for you to arrange the structure you want.
I heard the Crown Prince's education department faced some chaos.
It looks like there will be a large-scale acceptance of new officials.
Our Crown Prince should meet a proper teacher this time though.
I am quite worried.
What does a position in the Crown Prince's education department mean?
It's a position to "raise" the future power of this country.
I've already taken action.
For the Crown Prince, who will ascend the throne,
and for the future of this country,
our family's clan has a lot of work to do.
Especially your responsibility is crucial.
Please forgive the Crown Prince, Your Majesty.
[Jung Jeon Han]
He has no close friends, and he lives a life bombarded with responsibilities.
Please allow Yang Myung to freely enter the palace.
You sent Yang Myung, who isn't even married yet, out of the palace very young
and don't even allow him to frequently enter the palace so Crown Prince grows more lonely...
It's not a position that can be protected by childish actions.
All the previous kings went through the same thing and then came to the throne.
One who is to supposed to hold onto the people of this entire country, isn't able to
keep his personal feelings in check
is something you want me to be understanding of?!
However, Your Majesty...
I must rest now.
Queen, return to your quarters.
Is anyone outside?
Escort the Queen.
He commanded that no one be allowed in.
[Hee Bim (Royal Concubine) Maiden Name Park}
I am gravely sorry.
It is not your fault.
Is Yang Myung not even visiting to pay his respects these days?
I heard that he left the city for a trip.
His Majesty's cold glare looks deadly, so he must not feel comfortable entering the palace.
When he returns tell him to visit my quarters to pay his respects.
It'd be even better if he visits the Crown Prince's quarters first.
Give me a good price.
I want to buy some presents for my friends.
I haven't seen you around before.
Are you a newcomer?
I'm just passing through but
I just caught some game for fun.
Let's see here.
They're wild right?
Of course.
It's real wild game that only ate morningdew high up in the mountains.
Morning dew? Hahaha
Tisk!
Pheasants don't live just on morning dew.
What is that line for?
A blind shaman child who can diagnose illnesses perfectly.
On top of that, they sell amulet like rocks.
Rumor has spread that it heals all illnesses.
So everyone is lining up to buy one.
Heals all illnesses?
Yes, heals all illnesses.
I was in a dilemma about what to buy as presents...
..should I buy some of that?
Now, the child shaman whose powers surpasses the Hall of Royal Shamans' Chief Shaman,
Nok Yeong's powers
The mysterious rock that heals all illnesses.
For one rock, only 5 nyangs (coins).
Now, there aren't many left so getting a waiting number.
Now! Now!
Take one. Take one!
There really aren't many left.
It's over there. They are the ones that are using a child and falsely making claims. [Jang Nok Young]
After starving and abusing the child, if it dies then they buy another one and continue business.
Sometimes they even hand them over to brothels.
I need to go and see it for myself.
Now, numbers 41 to 45, enter!
Wait a second.
You must pick a number first.
I'm sorry, but I am before you.
In Joseon's sky, two suns.
There are evil auras around your shoulder, so you must feel aches.
Soo goong! Soo goong!
Shaman Soo Goong is saying that there is bad energy on you.
It is a very vicious energy.
Two suns.
Use the mysterious rock. It's 20 nyangs (coins).
Thank you sir!
Hey, what are you here for?
As for me,
I twisted my leg while hunting a boar.
Oh dear.
Next customer!
You hurt your leg that's filled with the energy of a wild animal...
Oh? I see a light in you sir!
A very beautiful golden color?
Or is it a red color?
A light?
What kind of light are you talking about?
I'm hungry.
Soo Goong! Soo Goong! Soo Goong!
Shaman Soo Goong says that for your leg injury a level 4 rock will do.
Though her body is frail, your stomach is bloated and makes a strange sound.
This is probably because her stomach is ruined and is the cause of her poor energy.
What is this punk saying?
I'm sure it's because of starvation and exhaustion.
Do you want to be hit by the mysterious rock?
This bruise near her neck,
These scars! How many injuries are there?
This wretch easily bruises.
Open your eyes.
This wretch!
I'm hungry! Hungry!
They're con men!
Please call for some guards.
Ahjussi! You're running too fast, I'm getting dizzy!
That's because you've been so starved.
Wait just a little longer
because I'll take you to a doctor.
And! I'm not an ajusshi, kid!
Come here!
Ahjusshi!
I don't like it! I don't want to get hit!
Be quiet!
Let go of that child immediately!
What is this?
Move!
Catch him!
Let the kid go, alright?
I'll send her to some restaurant and ask them to raise her well.
Because of you, we lost our day's wages,
and we can no longer stay in this area.
Now do you know your wrongs?
Don't get me angry
It will be very dangerous for you if I get angry.
If I get angry, it will be even more dangerous!
I'm warning you again
If you get me any angrier, it'll be really dangerous.
Did I tell you that my martial arts teacher came in top place at this year's civil service exam?
If your martial arts teacher passed the civil service exam
Then my father is the king, you punk!
I know the king a little...
And he's never mentioned a son like you.
Subtitles brought to you by the Eclipse Team @ viki.com
Your Majesty
I've returned safely from my trip.
Please forgive me for paying my respects outside of the palace.
Have you been well too, Crown Prince?
I'm not going to run away
so let's stop now.
If I told you I was the crown prince, your nagging would probably increase.
But I'll probably never have the chance to meet you again anyway.
Ha Won Seo Bang
Meaning, if you draw it it will be round and if you write it will be straight.
I understand this one.
Myo Saeng Yoo Sa?
The rabbit lives, and the rooster dies.
What could this mean?
Miss! It's Seol!
You're still in the same position?
Seol, if the rabbit lives and the rooster dies, what would happen?
If the rooster dies, then who will wake us up in the morning?
Just go to sleep now.
Do you want to be scolded by your father again?
In the moonlight,
I hoped for maybe some hidden words would be revealed.
"If the rooster dies, who will wake us up in the morning?"
Morning...
Myo Shi: 5am to 7am
Myo Saeng Yoo Sa
Born at Myo Shi (5am~7am) and die at Yoo Shi (5pm~7pm).
Myo Shi - 5am ~ 7am
Yoo Shi - 5pm ~ 7pm
If you draw it is is round and when you write it is it straight.
The thing that rises at Myo Shi and descends at Yoo Shi!
The day, meaning the sun!
Are you showing disrespect to me right now?
I am this land Joseon's-
Sun.
Could it be? We might see each other again?
Are you the Crown Prince?
You don't know how relieved I am that we won't ever see each other again.
It was good seeing you again, Heo Yeon Woo.