I'm in extreme agony right now.
Furthermore, the agonizing pain
in my heart that I didn't wish for,
is impossible to get rid of.
So I need you to remove this pain.
This pain which has been filling my heart,
I need you to calm it down.
Are you able to do that?
Answer me. Can you do it?
Your Majesty, please allow me.
If Your Majesty consents,
I'm willing to protect Your Majesty
from bad luck and disaster.
I'm willing to block it for you.
Lift up your head.
Lift your head up. This is an order!
I'm just worried about
His Majesty's royal body.
This matter, you don't need
to report it to His Majesty.
Is there anybody outside?
Yes, Your Majesty!
At your command, Your Majesty.
Call the royal physician.
Your Majesty, are you feeling unwell?
It isn't me, it's her.
You mustn't, Your Majesty.
What do you mean?
The royal physician is only
for treating the royal family,
How can he treat a shaman?
Isn't she a living talisman that blocks
bad luck and disaster on my behalf.
If her body is unwell, it will affect me too.
This isn't for her, but for me.
Get him here quickly.
But, Your Majesty.
A command.
It's a command!
Why did you come out?
His Majesty has ordered everyone
to leave his chamber.
What is that?
While searching the shaman
we found this.
It seems like a letter.
It seems that the shaman has written
a love letter for His Majesty.
Take a look.
Your Majesty.
His Majesty's expression was
like a man looking at a woman.
This pain which has been filling my heart,
I need you to calm it down.
I'm willing to protect Your Majesty
from bad luck and disaster.
I'm willing to block it for you.
What is this?
This was discovered while
searching the shaman.
Apparently, it was meant to
be given to Your Majesty.
If Your Majesty doesn't want to
look at it, I will take it away.
Put it down.
Weeds are good for nothing.
Though weeds are not beautiful,
they still have their uses.
Shamans which aren't seen as human beings,
are still there for the people.
Although shamans aren't seen as human beings,
we are still Your Majesty's people.
Since you are not a human,
how dare you touch my body?
Shamans are commoners and people too.
Please do not ignore me.
A short but powerful blow.
It's very rare that a shaman
is able to read.
It's amazing that a shaman is able
to write such beautiful words.
Have a look at this letter, Hyeong Seon.
How can one believe that this is
a 13 year old girls literary talent?
And I was thinking how
smart she is, but she's really foolish.
- How.
- How can I forget you?
Your Majesty.
Why are you calling me?
That girl... is only a female shaman.
Who says she isn't?
I have served Your Majesty
for many years.
So, how would I not be able
to read your thoughts?
Your Majesty's sacred heart
must not waver.
So you're saying that I will
be moved by a Shaman?
She... is not Miss Yeon U.
No matter how similar they are,
Miss Yeon U is already...
Don't say that. Don't say it. Don't say that!
Your Majesty!
I don't want to see you, so turn the other way!
Last night, the Queen came to the
palace hall but left soon after.
The Queen put aside her
self-respect as a woman,
took a step forward with much difficulty,
but turned and left.
How would the Queen feel inside her heart?
So please, Your Majesty, I ask you to
empathise with the Queen's feelings.
Your Highness!  Your Highness, my Queen.
Why are you shouting?
His Majesty wishes to come
over to your chambers.
Bring my clothes and jewelry
here immediately. Quickly.
Yes!
Did you say that His Majesty has gone
over to The Queen's chamber?
Yes, Mother.
I just came back from there.
Until now the Queen has been
continually heavy-hearted,
but I think her sincerity must have
opened His Majesty's heart.
It's really surprising.
What?
Ever since the female shaman entered the palace,
all matters have become smooth-sailing.
But how can you say that it's
because of the shaman?
It's because your efforts in
caring for His Majesty's health,
have moved Heaven.
Only because she has been at his side has
the royal body been able to recover day by day.
Relationships within the palace are
unexpectedly running smoothly.
She is worthy of being
Shaman Jang's spiritual daughter.
It looks like we'll need the Physiognomy Office to
select another auspicious date for the consummation.
What? Hasn't a date already been set?
Due to His Majesty's disinterest,
every time we selected a suitable
date it was a wasted effort.
Now that His Majesty's royal body is healthy,
the relationship between the two
seems to have become more relaxed.
How can we let slip this
golden opportunity?
However, after reading the
universe's movement,
there won't be many dates
that are suitable.
The Heavens are helping us.
How can we wait for a whole month?
We have to use all possible
methods to make this work.
You don't look well.
Is there something troubling you?
For me, other than thinking
of Your Majesty's well-being,
what else is there for me
to worry about?
It's only that I couldn't sleep last night.
I heard you... came to my chamber last night.
Your Majesty, please forgive me.
I acknowledge my mistake.
I was worried about your health.
What were you trying to monitor?
What? How could Your Majesty say monitor?
Regardless of what you saw,
or what you heard,
there wasn't anyone in my chamber.
If you did see someone,
it was only a talisman sent by
the Office of Physiognomy.
Is it in a month's time?
What are you referring to?
The day of our consummation.
The physicians and the Office of Physiognomy
have warned us repeatedly.
Until that day, we must keep our
distance and meditate to purify our minds.
Thus, don't come again to my chambers.
Is that what you mean?
Looks like you finally understand.
What are you trying to hide?
What's the reason for warning
me not to come?
Your Majesty, what is it exactly
that you want to hide from me?
Are you in love with someone?
Not only is a dead person
constantly in your mind,
now you're trying to keep a lowly
shaman close to your heart.
Court Lady Jo.
Yes, Your Highness.
Take a look and see if there's one of the king's
palace maids that we can secretly use.
What?
Why do you want a secret palace maid?
When you find someone to use,
tell her to secretly monitor the shaman
who spends each night with His Majesty.
I want her every movement
secretly reported to me.
Your Highness.
Female shaman?
Carefully look at my face.
Can't you remember the woman
that was here with me last time?
Ah! I remember.
She was so elegant and demure I thought
she was the daughter of a professor.
She was a shaman?
Has she not come here since?
From what I remember
she never came back again.
I understand.
Just wait a little longer.
I'll take you to a physician.
And I'm not an ajussi, girl!
(Ajussi - older man, uncle)
Because of her despicable crime, she's already
been expelled far away to the border.
Thank you for your good intentions.
At the moment I'm residing at a safe place.
The shaman records don't have such a name,
and she committed a crime of promiscuity,
which is why we wanted to arrest her.
I am Wol.
One of them is definitely lying to me.
Who is she? Why is there a
need to lie to me?
Orabeoni!
(Orabeoni - older brother)
Me...? Orabeoni...?
You're alive.
Wait! Wait.
Looking at you, you don't seem like a gisaeng to me.
(Gisaeng - female Korean entertainer)
How can I be a gisaeng? One look and
you can tell that I'm a Celestial Hall shaman.
A Celestial Hall shaman?
The magic stone, don't you remember?
You're that kid who could see
through someone with your eyes shut.
You've become a grown up young lady.
I almost didn't recognize you.
Have you been doing well?
Thanks to my spiritual mother
who offered me shelter.
I'm not a fake shaman anymore.
I'm a real shaman.
That's a relief.
Just now, you said you're a shaman?
Yes, I am from the Celestial Hall.
The safest place for a female
shaman in the capital city.
A place where a female shaman is
safe to come and go freely in the capital.
Among the Celestial Hall's shamans,
is there a shaman named Wol?
Wol...
I told you to watch your tongue.
Do you want me to sew your
mouth shut so you can only hear?
Turn a blind eye and a deaf ear.
How many times have I told you?
Did I say something wrong again?
Things like Sun and Moon,
just dare try and say another word.
Regarding agassi's matters,
if you dare try and say anything again,
(Agassi - young lady)
see if I don't tear you
limb from limb!
I don't know.
This is the first time I've
heard the name Wol.
Don't be like this, try to remember.
I said I don't know.
There isn't someone called that
in the Celestial Hall.
Hey, Jan Sil!
Yes, coming right away.
Hurry up and come. How long
are you going to fool around?
Orabeoni, if it's fated we'll meet again.
W... Wait!
If she's not in the Celestial Hall,
then where could she be?
You left all excited because
you were going to the market.
Why is your expression like that now?
Sorry, orabeonni.
I'm really... really sorry.
Agassi!... Agassi!
Agassi, what's wrong with you?
Did you have that dream again?
It's been a while since you last
had it. Why did it start again?
I know.
This time too, you weren't
able to see his face?
This time I really wanted to see it.
This time I should have
been able to see it.
Agassi,
do you really want to see his face?
Every night, aren't you by his side?
You used a letter to me to strike back.
I fully experienced the depth of
your resentment towards me.
I don't resent you.
Though you say you don't resent me,
your written words were
clearly rebuking me.
Did I misread it?
Words of advice out of loyalty, and
grudges with personal emotions
are two different things.
So you weren't complaining,
but you were still rebuking me?
I only wanted to say,
that just like a pebble by the side of
the road has a reason for its existence,
a shaman like me,
one of Your Majesty's people,
also wishes to do what
she can for Your Majesty.
You are clearly rebuking me.
You're saying that as this country's king I'm unable
to fully understand the thoughts of the common people.
Are you trying to make me
understand my own incompetence?
It has nothing to do with
the writer's intentions.
If the reader is filled with
prejudice and preconceptions,
then misunderstandings are
bound to arise.
If Your Majesty misunderstood
my intentions,
that would naturally be the reason.
So what you're saying is
that I'm filled with prejudice
and that I have misunderstood
the true meaning of this letter,
and also make political mistakes.
That wasn't what I meant.
Though I have shown much affection to
you lately, you're now crossing the line.
Have you forgotten to whom
you're speaking?
I'm the Joseon's...
Is anyone out there?
Yes, Your Majesty,
please give your order.
I feel suffocated in here.
I'm going to take a walk,
make preparations immediately.
The night wind is cold,
why not leave it until tomorrow...
I feel troubled, didn't you hear?
Hurry and get ready to go out.
What are you doing?
What?
Didn't you say that you would
block bad luck for me?
Why aren't you fulfilling
your duty now?
You're my talisman, so follow me.
All of you step back a little further.
I said you should all step back.
Un, you should also step back.
You remain here,
since you're my talisman.
Step back a little more.
Let go!
Yeon U! Yeon U!
Is it here,
hidden deep inside Your Majesty's
painful memories.
That person who was crying here in the past,
was it you, Your Majesty?
What exactly did you see?
Were you using your shaman's
abilities to see?
That's right.
Then try to use your shaman's
ability to make a guess.
To guess what?
What do you think I'm
going to do next?
Today Hyeong Seong said
something strange to me.
What do you think?
Do you think I will pay attention to
a mere shaman like you?
Why are you like this...?
What are you doing?
Quickly catch up.
You. Who are you exactly?
I am Shaman Wol.
No, you aren't Wol.
Then who else could I be?
I have always lived my life as
a shaman without a name.
It was Your Majesty who
gave me the name, Wol.
Are you really...
not able to recognize me?
Have you...
really never seen me before?
Your Majesty, are you looking for
traces of that person in me now?
Facing me now, whom do you see?
Is it that girl called Yeon U?
Why did you allow me to
stay by your side?
Is it because I resemble that woman?
But, I'm not that woman.
Shut up!
You really are crossing the
line right now.
Just because I allow you to remain by
my side doesn't mean that I like you.
You're only a living talisman,
aside from that you're nothing.
Who do you think you are
to actually dare...
Who do you think... you are exactly?
To actually dare...
confuse me like this.
Don't come near me.
If you cross the line again,
I won't easily forgive you.
Tonight I'm going to sleep alone,
you don't need to follow me.
Un.
Silently escort her back.
Don't let her know.
Apart from this, I need you to go
somewhere on the way back.
Just because I allow you to remain by
my side doesn't mean that I like you.
You're only a living talisman,
aside from that you're nothing.
Why are you standing outside now when you're
supposed to be by His Majesty's side?
Has something happened?
Shinmu.
Who... exactly am I?
You said that when I was young I was
abandoned by my parents to wander the streets.
You saw my shaman's abilities
in me so you took me in.
Why are you suddenly asking me this?
During the past few days,
I've been seeing some strange images.
They're certainly someone else's memories.
It feels exceptionally real,
like I've experienced it before.
This makes me extremely confused.
This is because your psychic
ability hasn't matured,
creating a temporary illusion.
So, stop dwelling on the past.
I couldn't... possibly be the owner
of those memories, could I?
No matter how I resemble her,
I can't become that person?
Who is it?
Prince Yang Myeong! You startled me!
I did it to scare you.
Why do you have to jump over the
wall every time you come here?
That's because,
I'm more familiar with the wall
than the front entrance.
Besides, it's already past curfew.
It was really hard trying to
hide away from the patrols.
Come, come. The weather is so cold.
Let's go inside and have a drink.
Ja Un. What brings you here this late?
You scared me.
How could you just appear
without any warning?
Is it possible you jumped over
the wall to come in like me?
After all it's already late.
Do you come here as a royal messenger,
or come here as a close friend?
His Majesty has ordered you to
make a trip to the palace, Uibin.
(Uibin - Prince Consort)
Suddenly calling me to the palace,
has something happened?
Pretend I didn't ask. Unless
His Majesty says to do so,
you absolutely won't tell me.
Since I have relayed the royal command,
I will be going now.
Going so soon?
I've already left my position
long enough.
That's my birthday present
made by our Yeon U.
So, is this your sister's handwriting?
Absolutely.
She was truly exceptional.
Not only in painting and calligraphy,
but also fluent in literature.
It's really a shame she was born a girl.
On top of that,
she was a considerate and
respectful child.
But, why are you suddenly asking this?
It's only because I saw her
handwriting that I asked.
Who sent you here?
Why were you spying on
the Uibin's residence?
What is your objective?
That person...
Kim Chae Un has unexpectedly
showed an interest in a woman.
That's pretty rare.
It's unprecedented.
What woman? It's not like that.
Don't quibble.
Anyway, a woman is a woman.
Contrary to what one might expect from you,
I hear that you have a lover.
I guess it was Princess Min Hwa
who said that.
Is it true?
I thought it was only a joke,
but it's actually true.
What kind of person is she?
Yes...
In fact I don't know either.
What?
Do you know that 8 years ago,
the night before the final selection day,
I climbed over the walls of this place.
Do you want to go with me?
Doesn't matter if it's the position
of a prince
or the title of Prince Yang Myeong,
I'll abandon them all,
and take you far, far away.
But, do you know how your
sister replied?
This joke is not funny.
Her sparkling eyes looked so resolute,
I was unable to say anything more.
Prince!
But, if that day, I...
hadn't used a smiling face to
hide my true feelings...
Deceiving your inner heart
and living in disguise,
isn't it something that's
really torturous?
If I'd taken more courage and
extended my hand out to her,
if I'd shown my true feelings,
and asked her to run away with me,
then would she now...
be by my side?
Haven't you gone to sleep yet?
I wanted to ask you where
you've been so late at night.
You are hurt.
How did it happen?
I made a mistake while
practicing with the sword.
Come here so I can take
a look at your wound.
Really, I'm fine.
The clothes just got ripped,
there's no wound.
Where exactly did you go?
Just...
My previous owner's house.
They must have been good people,
since you still visit them now.
Yes.
They really were extremely good people.
While others treated me like an animal,
they treated me like a person.
They gave me the name "Seol",
such a beautiful name.
Agassi, that's the kind of person you are.
Both of us have changed.
In my memories, your sister...
is still 13 years old.
Never back down when you
have already taken a step forward.
You clearly taught me that.
A person's heart is like that too.
It's not easy to change a person's
heart once it's made up.
So no matter what happens, I...
can never disappoint
His Highness, the Crown Prince.
Are... Are you a g-ghost or a person?
Aren't you...
It's me, Orabeoni.
What are you doing here so late?
I'm sorry, Orabeoni.
I was wrong.
What are you sorry about?
The person that you're looking for,
I'll help you meet her.
Orabeoni.
Because you're my savior,
I will surely repay your kindness.
No matter what happens to me
I'm going to repay you.
I'ill make sure that you'll
meet her again,
so don't be too sad.
Who do you keep looking for in me?
Through me, who do you see?
You should go back to your
room to rest.
I will be fine by myself.
No.
Until you're feeling better,
I will always stay by your side.
Thanks to you Princess
I'm feeling much better now.
I won't be sad anymore...
Mother.
Why are you here too,
Princess Min Hwa?
Since yesterday she's never left my side
because she's afraid that I will be sad again.
You've taken a lot of trouble.
I'm very grateful.
How can you say that when
we're a couple?
My husband, are you entering
the King's palace?
Yes, last night I received
an imperial order.
Why are you only telling me now?
If you had told me earlier,
I could have gone with you.
I'm very sorry I didn't think of that.
Next time, I'll make sure to tell you first.
I'm going now Mother.
Don't let His Majesty feel vexed
or worried, and act prudently.
Are you angry that you can't go?
It's not that I'm angry,
but because I'm uneasy.
Uneasy? What are you uneasy about?
That, it's because if my husband
enters the palace?.
Teacher.
Why do you stay at home
and not go out?
If I didn't take the initiative to invite you,
you wouldn't have come to see me.
Your Majesty,
please have a seat so that
I can greet you properly.
No need for that.
Come, quickly prepare some
tea and cake.
And I want to chat with
the Teacher in private.
Don't let anyone disturb us.
All of you may leave now.
How could the Uibin visit the palace?
This is ridiculous.
He should have lived quietly for the
rest of his life until the day that he dies.
Isn't that what an Uibin should do?
How dare he randomly visit
the palace in broad daylight?
That's true. Since ancient times
the position of Uibin
has always been banned from
political activities, the study of
knowledge and all such external activities.
This is what the law states.
This matter is very dangerous.
Thanks to him,
my ranking in the palace will drop.
What... ranking?
In the past, when there was
a popularity rank inside the palace,
after Un, wasn't it me?
His appearance in the palace
will sway the rankings.
You have the power to change it.
But in case
this is the King's plan to gather
the dispersed faction of scholars...
But Heo Yeom isn't the kind of
person to incite the scholar faction.
Heo Yeom is a strong, symbolic figure
among the scholar faction.
His existence itself can move them.
I'm afraid,
his influence will surpass his
father's, Heo Yeong Jae.
Heo Yeom has already lost his power,
so why did he visit the palace?
What is... this?
It's my sister's last letter,
that she left behind.
I wanted to forget about it,
because it was in the past.
But then, even though it's late I thought
I should pass it on to it's real owner.
This is what should be done.
Is it really...
Yeon U's letter which she left for me?
That's right.
Yeon U, left for me...
While my sister was still alive,
there was only one husband in her heart.
That was Your Majesty.
Because this letter is from a sinner,
it was supposed to be burned.
If Your Majesty can personally burn it,
if you really can personally do it,
my sister in heaven, would be happy.
So please, from now on,
please forget my sister.
Your Majesty, you already
have the Queen by your side.
Please don't make the Queen
lonely anymore.
If Your Majesty continues to be unable
to break free from that child's shadow,
that is not what my sister
would have wished for.
This is a sincere request from
my sister and me.
Please fulfill it.
Your Majesty.
Everyone...
keeps telling me to forget all about her.
Uibin, My Lord,
from now on I hope you will
visit the palace often.
Even though His Majesty
doesn't show it,
he actually misses you a lot.
Being an Uibin,
how can I randomly visit the palace?
So, please be with him.
Take good care of His Majesty.
Uibin,
you should have been the one
to accompany His Majesty.
Your Highness, Crown Prince.
With my last ounce of strength,
I'm writing to you this letter.
This may add to your troubles.
Maybe,
this letter will not be
delivered to you.
But I'm still picking up
this pen to write.
This girl,
before departing,
was able to meet Your Highness,
and for this I'm extremely grateful.
Therefore,
I'm asking you not to
blame yourself again.
Please just forget about me.
Keep me in a corner of your memory.
Father will bring my medicine soon.
So,
afterwards, I'll never be able
to see you again.
I'm asking you to forget me.
Please take good care of your health.
I hope you can be honored
as a great monarch.
She was worried about my health,
at the moment she was
about to leave this life.
Using her last bit of strength
she wrote down this letter...
But I...
Your Majesty.
She must have been in a lot of pain.
How much she must have suffered.
Her writing at the end of the letter,
is so loose and weak.
Hyeong Seon.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Issue an order to Court Lady Jo.
Ask her to find the box
and bring it to me.
Yes.
I can't remember,
Yeon U's handwriting.
I can't remember.
I must see it.
Those letters that she wrote to me.
I want to see them again.
I will... obey your order, Your Majesty.
After taking a walk at night,
His Majesty ordered that
the living talisman
not be allowed near his chambers.
A walk?
Late at night,
both of them went for a walk?
Even before,
whenever His Majesty reads at night,
he often goes out to take a walk.
So,
did anything happen after that?
It didn't...
Ever since Lord Uibin came
over during the day
His Majesty has been very troubled
and suddenly ordered one of
the ladies to bring him a box.
A box?
Yes.
It looks like a normal storage box,
but on the box is engraved
the word "rain".
Just now,
did you say "rain"?
(Rain - U)
Please order me.
Bring Wol...
Bring Wol here.
Immediately bring Wol over now!
You... Do you recognize me?