Episode 17
You don't have to see me out.
Then, leave safely.
You,
won't leave suddenly,
or something like that, right?
Even if I wanted to . . .
Since I am a criminal, where can I go?
That's right.
You are a sinner.
You are sinner and Shaman Wol.
Aren't you too much?
Never mind.
I like it so much that,
you are a sinner and Shaman Wol.
Then go in and rest.
Assassins . . .
Yeon Woo.
Is this real?
What is?
You aren't a spirit?
Are you really...
The King?
It's not an imagination.
I really...
came to find you, Yeon Woo.
At last, I recognize you.
I am a fool.
Hyungnim!
Prince Yang Myung!
Hyungnim.
I'm fine.
Where are we going?
Excellency, Excellency!
A vacant mud hut is over yonder.
We had decided to meet there, taking YeonWoo,
if it became dangerous.
You lost the woman?!
Woon and the King appeared.
Also, Prince Yang Myung came
and completely disappeared somewhere with the girl.
No matter how you do it,
you have to find that girl.
Also,
kill Chief Shaman Jang of Seongsucheong
without a trace.
You are the only eyewitness, as well as
the main culprit, of the Crown Princess' death.
Until this case is disclosed,
you must stay alive. It is the King's command.
Hide yourself somewhere for now;
until we call for you.
If, by chance, you flee or
try to commit suicide,
there will be dire consequences.
Unni, where are you going?
Let's go together.
Let her go.
We all know where she's going.
What if she goes
and doesn't come back?
It is also obvious that she will be back.
So don't worry, just follow me.
Your Majesty!
Bring the royal physician!
DON'T!
Today,
about me leaving the Palace,
has to be kept secret.
But, Your Majesty . . .
Yoon Dae Hyeong.
Hyungnim.
Prince Yang Myung.
Prince Yang Myung!
What...
Mother . . .
Yang Myung!
-Sir
-Yang Myung.
I don't know who you are,
but I need to get him inside.
So please help me.
Please rely on me.
Yang Myung.
Your Excellency.
I'm Chief Scholar,
Heo Yeong Jae's daughter,
Heo Yeon Woo.
By any chance,
are you the daughter of the
former Chief Scholar?
Yes, I am.
What is it?
Why do you hold someone in your heart
that will hurt yourself.
I don't know how you are alive.
And, I won't ask the details.
However,
I can guess how.
Yang Myung visited me once
and asked if I believed in reincarnanation.
He said he can throw away power, loyalty,
and everything else.
But that one person,
is something he couldn't let go of.
He probably wanted me to see.
To show me what kind of person
he held dearly in his heart.
He calls a mother, such as I, a mother.
Bringing his injured body
all the way here.
They weren't even at Jung Eung Temple.
Yes.
Follow me.
I've prepared it as you commanded.
Everyone, except Hyung Sun, get out.
Give me your sword.
Yo . . . Your Majesty, why are you like this?
Take off your clothes.
This....
isn't fun.
If I brandish a sword at you, you should,
at least, pretend to be surprised.
Or else it isn't fun.
Your Majesty,
why are you like this?
My liver almost dropped.
Since you were investigating
in the cold weather,
you must be tired.
Go in.
I've ordered this to be prepared for you.
I cannot.
Go in.
It's a command.
Your Majesty.
Not obeying a command is treasonous.
It would also be disloyal if all the evil aura
that is in you comes to me.
Also,
being torn between my brother and I
is revolting.
Make sure he goes in.
And if he comes out within two hours,
strike him with that sword.
Your Majesty . . .
Woon,
Although, I cannot give you a higher position.
I treasure you above all others.
So please don't be sick/hurt.
If you have a cold,
I will have it, too.
So this is how it is done.
That is made out of Hyang Gam.
Are you awake now?
I'll see if the breakfast has been prepared.
Has your body recovered?
I...
thought that you would have left
and wouldn't be here any longer.
I thought I should see you before I left.
I waited till you woke up.
Can you walk for a moment?
Yes.
Since when
have you known?
Subtitles brought to you by 'Eclipse'@Viki.com
Was it really
because of the problem-solving rock?
Wouldn't it be more weird if I hadn't known?
'Hea Woo Suk' (problem-solving rock)
was the name I made up
before I gave you the rock.
There is no one else who knows it.
But, why did you act like you didn't know?
I didn't want to know.
I wanted to act like I didn't know
to the end.
Since you came back to life,
I was extremely glad to see you.  And yet,
at the same time,
the moment I accept that truth,
it seemed like everything would all fly away.
Do you know?
When I open my eyes in the morning . . .
Knowing there is a place to go . . .
And there are things for me to do there . . .
And, there are people who need me . . .
And, I am able to see the person I long to see . . .
I was so happy.
During that time, I . . .
was happy, too.
Whenever I had to face the dark reality,
you
were a light for me.
Thanks to you, even for a while,
I was able to set aside my worries.
I was able to smile.
Both as Shaman Wol and Heo Yeon Woo,
I was always thankful.
And,
I was always
sorry.
However,
to you, Excellency,
I am not able to give you
So please be free now.
Find a new destiny and
be happy, is my wish.
This is the only thing I can give you,
sincerely from my heart.
Then...
Please be healthy.
In the past life,
you were his person.
At least, in this life,
can't you be...
by my side?
That can't happen.
Escort Princess Yeon Woo away.
Hyungnim,
do you know what you are doing now?
Fleeing with the King's woman
is an act of treason.
Are you trying to get rid
of a person who has commited treason?
If I wanted your neck,
I could have used my power as a King.
What does that mean?
I am giving you a chance
to kill me.
The sword you are holding in your hand
is a real sword.
If you now
kill me here,
you will become the ruler of this country.
When you finally sit on the throne . . .
Do you think you will have everything?
If I sit on the throne, at least,
I won't be charged with treason.
Then,
kill me.
Why are you hesitating?!
Kill me!
Today . . .
It is you who lost the chance.
So never,
look for another chance.
Did you rest?
Yes.
Can I ask
one thing?
Please ask me.
Did I . . .
bring you here,
when you didn't want to come?
If I didn't want to,
will you send me away?
When my heart already belongs to you.
What is there to be so worried about?
Can I . . .
open the door?
Do as you please.
Open it.
Subtitles brought to you by 'Eclipse'@Viki.com
Come closer.
Come even closer.
Why are you like this?
You may leave.
Yeon Woo.
Yes, Your Majesty.
When my heart is already yours.
What are you so worried about
Your Majesty,
To where are you headed?
I am returning to my palace for a rest
after conducting some work.
Do you have something to tell me?
I heard that lately
you encountered some big trouble
when you were out in disguise.
Are you unhealthy somewhere?
It is certainly strange.  The only people who knew
about my disguised undertakings
are the assassins and me.
How is it that you know about it?
How can a person serving the King not know
what is going on?
Everything that happens to you is the council's business.
Anway,
thank you for your concern.
Oh I forgot.
I heard you like to hunt.
Why are you asking that?
Isn't there military training coming up soon?
I would like to learn how to hunt that day.
Would you like to teach me your secret method?
I am not that good.  However  . . .
Once I choose a quarry,
I chase it to the last without giving up
and capture it. This could be a kind of secret.
So then . . . Once, a quarry is chosen,
chase without giving up,
finally capturing and killing it?
Ahhhh, I won't forget that.
What are you doing?
I'm reading a book.
When I asked earlier, didn't you say the you were reading a book?
Aren't you bored?
I don't get bored.
So please focus on your work.
What book are you reading?
It is written by Han Feizi
(a philosopher and legalist).
Is that book so interesting?
Yes.
It's very interesting.
Your Majesty.
Is that book so interesting
that you didn't notice me coming in?
When did you come in?
I meet you again after an 8 year separation
and I am not more important than Han Feizi?
Are you
jealous of Han Feizi?
Jealous? Yea right.
I just feel frustrated.
Why do you feel a sense of frustration?
I didn't even look at anyone else for the past eight years.
While living in a palace full of flowers,
do you know how hard it was to control myself for that long?
Do you really need strength in order to keep your virginity?
Of course!
How can you know how a man feels at night.
Exercising is a MUST! A must!
However, about you saying that you didn't look
at any other woman.
isn't it a lie?
A lie?
Who did I ever look at?
Weren't you shaken by
Shaman Wol who stayed by you every night?
Nonsense! I was shaken very briefly.
That is...
Wait...
Isn't Wol you?
But still, you were interested in Wol who wasn't really me.
So you were shaken.
Why are you laughing?
Are you being jealous by any chance?
Jealous? Nonsense.
Why do you keep laughing?
Isn't it funny that you're jealous of yourself?
I said I'm not.
Anyway,
I am going to finish reading my book.
So you should focus on your petitions.
It is funny that you're jealous of yourself, but
since I fell for the same woman twice,
That's not quite normal either.
Heo's daughter is still alive?
What kind of nonsense is this?!
How can a girl who was buried 8 years ago
be alive?
8 years ago . . .
What did you believe of me
to have me send a curse?
Who did you think that evil spirit will go to?
Nok Young you...
You dare...
The King must have already known.
How would the King know her whereabouts?
Ever since Jang met the King at his palace,
Heo's daughter has hidden herself
from the medical relief center.
What do you think this means?
Both of them have been hidden by the King.
I'm sure of it.
But if he knows the whole truth and
hasn't done anything yet.  It means
he is covering up the truth that he's found.
He might be waiting for the right time.
Or he hasn't found out about
the last part of the truth.
Whichever it is, we need to find both of them
and silence them fast.
Even if the King does find out . . .
If the two people who bares witness
to the truth isn't alive,
the truth will be buried forever.
Subtitles brought to you by 'Eclipse'@Viki.com
Inform him.
YOUR . . . MAJESTY,
THE . . . DOWAGER . . .  QUEEN . . . IS HERE REQUESTING . . . TO SEE . . . YOU.
YOUR . . . MA . . . JES . . . TYYYY!
-DOWA...
-Open the door now!
I am exercising.
What brings you here,
Grandmother.
There was something I had to tell you.
Why didn't you just call me over?
King.
Yes Grandmother.
Do you remember that time
when I saved Shaman Wol?
How could I forget that?
I remember.
Then,
do you remember
when you said you would grant me
a favor for helping you?
How would I forget?
This Grandma,
came today to request the favor.
Please tell me what you want.
Seongsucheong's Jang and
her Spiritual Daughter, find them.
And, give them to me.
Why are you looking for them through me?
That is because . . .
you are hiding them, of course.
Why are you thinking that way?
What makes you think that I...
I heard you are investigating the incident
from eight years ago.
That . . .
don't do it.
And just cover it up.
Do you remember what I said eight years ago?
Just stay still.
And keep it a secret.
When the previous King covered up this case,
there was a reason.
What are you...
trying to hide?
That is,
I am trying to hide what you are trying to find out.
Why are you trying to hide it?
It is all for your sake.
To speak more clearly,
it is to save the people you treasure.
If it is someone I treasure,
who are you talking about?
That is
something you already know.
Think about it carefully.
Who do you
want to protect the most?
Now,
will you give me the answer about my request?
Why is there no answer?
You quoted "A man's word is as good as bond".
Of course,
I should grant your favor.
But,
it will take some time to find them.
If you just wait and believe in me,
I will make you meet them,
so don't worry.
However, that will be in the Court.
As a witness, an assailant, and a victim.
Orabeoni.
I was ordered to secretly investigate the incident
from eight years ago.
Yeon Woo is in there sick.  How can you tell me
to stay away from her?
How can I protect the Crown Prince when
I cannot even protect my own sister?
Yeon Woo.
Subtitles brought to you by Eclipse Team @ viki.com
Who are you?
Why are you prowling  about?
If you don't show yourself, I will raise an alarm.
You.
Who are you?
This lowly girl is Seol, Young Master.
Seol?
Ah..
You were Yeon Woo's servant, that child, right?
Yes.
What you said is correct, Young Master.
Why did you jump over the wall like a stray cat,
instead of using the front door?
I was just
passing by, while walking,
and thought of the old days and...
It was pretty late, so...
Right.
How have you been?
I am...
living well
with a new master,  sir.
That's right. I am no longer your master
due to my status.
But, in my heart, you are always my master.
Just like that time when you gave me
the name of Seol.
Why are you like that?
Do you have something to tell me?
Yeom, what are you doing there?
Oh mother, the girl who used to help Yeon Woo is...
I heard you talking to someone.
Who came by?
It was nothing.
But why did you come out here?
Ever since the Princess went to see your father,
she has been sick for three days.
I was thinking about taking her into the Palace
and having her see the royal doctor.
I wanted to know what you think about that.
Do you want me to take her?
No.
I haven't replied to the letter that I received from the Queen.  So, I will take her.
Yes, then please do it that way.
I was about to go see the Princess.
Would you like to come with me?
Yes, Mother.
I will take you to her.
When the King Former covered up that incident,
there was a reason.
It was all for your sake.
To say it more clearly,
It was for you and
everyone you treasured.
Your Majesty.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I was thinking.
It is late, you should go to bed.
Same for you,
why aren't you asleep?
Because you aren't asleep.
I am sorry for
putting you in a stifling room all day.
I am with you.
As long as I am with you,
even if it is in a secret room or
in hell, I do not care.
Come out.
Let's take a walk since it is dark outside.
Subtitles brought to you by Eclipse Team @ viki.com
The last time I met you in the Hidden Moon Building,
why didn't you tell me you had regained your memory?
Why did you hide it?
Even if you had told me . . .
I didn't have the heart to tell you.
The Queen is at your side.
Why are you like this?
Did you have a nightmare again?
Isn't it strange?
What is?
I don't hear a cry from the Hidden Moon Building,
anymore.
That is probably because the Seongsucheong shamans are using talismans to stop it.
I think that is why it has disappeared.
No, that's not it.
The owner of the Hidden Moon Building
is back!
Your Majesty.
Heo Yeon Woo, that child,
is somewhere in the Palace.
Please stay strong.
My father . . .
I told my father to make that child disappear-
No, it isn't.
If father sees me in this state,
he'll be disappointed.
Lady Jo.
That court lady of the King's chamber,
bring her here.
Yes?
At this late hour?
What are you doing?
Bring her here immediately.
When I am known to be dead,
and reappear alive again,
I know it will bring chaos to the palace.
And also,
it was foolish of me to not remember you.
So, how could I proudly tell you that it was me?
What are you trying to say?
The reason you went through all the suffering
was because of me.
When you were going through pain and death,
it was my fault that I didn't do anything.
No, it isn't.
For you to not forget a girl,
such as me, for eight years,
I have no complaint.
So,
During all the days I have left,
even if you forget me,
I will remember you even more,
and live with eagerness.
I . . .
will never forget.
The people who have caused you this much suffering.
I will find and punish them.
Also restore the innocent people and
return things to as they should be.
Your Majesty,
please let the past stay in the past.
When the previous King covered up the truth,
there must have been a reason for it.
"I believe in you."
"I believe that you will find out the truth."
Weren't you the one who encouraged me like that?
But, why?
I believe in you.
But,
I'm afraid of the truth that might hurt you.
I . . .
don't have anything more to expect
than being by your side. So,
You are in a room that barely has light.
Do you like being there that much?
Since I am next to the sun,
I don't need any other light.
Where are we going?
This place...
This place
is where this nation's politics start.
In this place,
I hear the nation's stories and
I think about what I should do for my nation.
Why did you bring a person like me
to a sacred place like this?
When I first met you, you told me
about the flaws and the wrongdoings
of the Kings.
That then, I was so young...
"In a child's eyes,
the whole world can become a problem,
the whole world can become an answer."
Your brother,
my teacher,
that was the first warning(teaching) he gave me.
So,
if something is making a child feel unsafe,
there is a problem.
So ever since I became a King and
had to face making a decision . . .
If it was you . . .
If it was Teacher . . .
What would they have said?
I tried to think of it.
Do you see that?
In my Princely days,
I commanded a man to create a hairpin
that resembled the meaning of that view.
To give to you...
A request . . .
for you to be my moon.
This hairpin . . .
'The Moon Embracing The Sun.'
And of the two,
I gave one to you.
The other one . . .
When you became my official wife,
I was thinking to give it to you here.
Your Majesty.
All your personal belongings
in the medical relief center,
I've ordered that they be brought here.
Now,
we have become one.
Subtitles brought to you by
The Only Eclipse Team @ viki.com