♪I wish to share both joy
and sorrow with you♪
♪One thought tangling
into gentle softness♪
♪Strands of black hair can't compare
to your glance back♪
♪The melody plays softly
and my heart can't be reclaimed♪
♪A touch of love in exchange
for red beans♪
♪Drifting for thousands of miles,
but settling in your heart♪
=Fairy Charge Forward=
=Episode 1=
(There's a rumor going around.)
(Nowadays, there exists a mountain
called Changliu.)
(On that mountain, there's a sect
called Changliu Sect.)
(The Changliu Sect is nothing
but an evil sect beyond redemption.)
(Its newly appointed leader,
Zheng Lipei,)
(is an even more ruthless woman
who kills without blinking an eye.)
You killer,
what do you want?
(But no one knows,)
(I, Zheng Lipei,
clearly abide by the law)
(and am entirely innocent.)
(The only misfortune
I've encountered is...)
(losing money as if cursed.)
This place is truly poor.
Indeed.
Exactly.
Look.
Take whatever you can.
Alright.
The sect leader carries
a curse of financial misfortune.
Alas,
(Liu Yimei, senior disciple of Changliu)
with our fate of losing money,
(Elder of Changliu Sect)
our sect will grow poorer in the future.
(Zheng Lipei, Sect Leader of Changliu)
But you can't blame it all on me.
If you must blame someone,
blame Master Jinse
who wrote "Chronicles of Changliu."
(Guo Xuefu, disciple of Changliu)
Why else would we be this poor?
In the novel,
he portrayed me
as a monstrous villain
and us as an evil sect
committing wicked deeds.
Villagers are terrified
whenever they see us.
How could we possibly earn a living?
Sect leader, don't worry.
Last night, I observed the stars
and gained insight into divine secrets.
Perhaps if you accomplish this task,
you can alter your curse
of financial misfortune.
What is it? Tell me, Elder.
You only need to go down the mountain
to find a suitable husband
and this will alter it.
(I go down the mountain
in search of a husband,)
(but my true purpose)
(is to find that heartless author,
Master Jinse,)
(who ruined the reputation
of our Changliu Sect.)
(Reward of 50 taels
for bringing Master Jinse)
(Reward of 20 taels for useful clues)
A reward of 50 taels of silver.
Well,
I tell stories written in
Master Jinse's novel every day,
but I don't know him personally.
Coincidentally, my bookshop
just received new copies
of "Chronicles of Changliu."
I'll go back and ask the printer
how to contact the author.
Alright.
I happen to be
the illustrator for that novel.
Do you know where he is?
It seems I've only interacted
with his servant,
so I'm not sure
of his whereabouts.
Hey there, sir,
are you trying to do something shady?
Mind your own business
or I'll beat you up!
(Xiao Ziqi, Senior Master of Yongzhou)
What are you planning
to do in broad daylight?
Oh, look! Look at that!
Oh my, evil people get
what they deserve.
Serves him right!
Zheng Lipei?
(The first person
to open the marriage token is)
(destined to resolve
your financial misfortune)
(and help Changliu
restore its former glory.)
Miss,
is this yours?
My dear.
Lipei,
could this be your destined match?
And he's so handsome.
Go report to the authorities.
I'll talk to that master.
You must succeed!
Miss, you've been following me.
Can I help you?
I'm Zheng Lipei.
Yes, I know.
Master, are you married?
Not yet.
The Wang family offers 18 coins
and the Li family nine.
And the enrollment situation
in Yongzhou?
- Ten taels of silver.
- Ten taels.
(Changliu Mountain)
Hurry up, we're going to miss lunch.
Changliu Mountain?
Don't worry, we're not some evil sect.
Let's go.
Come on.
Hurry!
Elder!
Elder, bad news!
The sect leader kidnapped someone.
What? Kidnapped?
Yes!
Well...
Oh no.
Elder.
I'm back.
Why did you kidnap him?
Elder.
Huh?
Look.
Oh.
You must be
the first one who opened
the marriage token.
That's correct.
Marriage token?
Although you're indeed the destined one,
if you want to become the husband
of our Changliu Sect's leader,
you must first pass a series of tests.
Yes.
Husband?
♪In the mortal world,
I sail a small boat♪
♪Beneath the moon,
the flowers seem frail♪
♪Until you, like a lone wild goose,
fell into my sight♪
♪Once I raised an empty cup
to confess my feelings♪
♪Lamenting a fleeting dream♪
♪Yet I wish to walk with you
until our hair turns gray♪
♪When the flowers bloom,
I send you a letter of longing♪
♪The spring breeze can't wrinkle it♪
♪We watch the sunset,
drifting in the painting♪
♪Falling behind you♪
♪At first sight of your beautiful face♪
♪What seemed like a fleeting moment
was meant to last forever♪
♪From then on,
listening to your whispered words♪
♪We stayed together, never parting♪
♪I wish to share both joy
and sorrow with you♪
♪One thought tangling
into gentle softness♪
♪Strands of black hair can't compare
to your glance back♪
♪The melody plays softly
and my heart can't be reclaimed♪
♪A touch of love in exchange
for red beans♪
♪Drifting for thousands of miles,
but settling in your heart♪