♪I wish to share both joy
and sorrow with you♪
♪One thought tangling
into gentle softness♪
♪Strands of black hair can't compare
to your glance back♪
♪The melody plays softly
and my heart can't be reclaimed♪
♪A touch of love in exchange
for red beans♪
♪Drifting for thousands of miles,
but settling in your heart♪
=Fairy Charge Forward=
=Episode 2=
This...
This is an ancient divine artifact.
It contains hidden mysteries.
(Isn't this just made last month?)
What do you think, Master?
Let me take a look.
Hey, you...
What...
What's this?
Get a fire stick.
Hey,
isn't this our sect's forbidden ground?
So the legendary treasure
is truly hidden there.
It seems there's hope
for revitalizing our Changliu Sect.
What's the next question?
There is no next question.
Master Xiao, you're very intelligent.
The revival of Changliu Sect
will depend on you and the sect leader.
Oh my,
isn't this too hasty?
Oh, with Master Xiao overseeing you,
your misfortune
will surely improve significantly.
Alright, enough talking.
Since he's passed the test,
let's make arrangements.
We'll get married.
Nonsense.
As the sect leader,
how can you treat marriage lightly?
We must choose an auspicious day.
Let me calculate.
Oh,
today is fine.
Huh?
Quickly, make arrangements.
A quarter to six tonight,
we'll hold the wedding.
Good.
Let's go.
Wait, I...
(I need to know if this place)
(has already colluded with Shaozhou.)
(Changliu Mountain spans the borders
of Shaozhou and Yongzhou)
(with treacherous terrain.)
(It's difficult to attack.)
(Bandits often occupy this area.)
(Now, with Shaozhou
stirring up trouble,)
(there might be changes.)
(On this trip,
you must investigate secretly)
(and find out everything.)
(I won't fail you, Father.)
(This is a Shaozhou style sword.)
(Have they indeed secretly...)
Here.
Try it on.
Do we really have to get married?
Can't we just sworn instead?
No.
Put it on.
If not, then...
Here,
let me help you.
Hey, no need.
Don't run away.
No need.
Stop running.
You...
Stop chasing.
Don't run.
Hello, Elder.
Hey, you...
You...
What are you...
Is it so difficult
to put on the clothes?
Stop chasing!
Stop running.
Lipei,
bad news!
Elder has been knocked unconscious.
What?
Here.
Who was trying to harm you?
Quick, that person
took the map and headed
to the Immortal Pavilion.
Is he your accomplice?
What are you talking about?
The treasure of our sect
has been hidden for years
and no one has ever deciphered it.
How did you know?
Well, that thing looks so crude.
It looks like it's meant to be broken.
And the hidden message technique
using fire
to reveal writing is a basic skill.
It's just writing on paper
with sugar water.
Stop!
Smarty-pants.
You're the smarty-pants.
Huh.
What did you give me?
Seven-Day Soul-Draining Pill.
There is no antidote.
You'll die within seven days.
You're indeed an evil sect.
Stop arguing.
Quickly, find the secret treasure
before the thieves do.
(Immortal Pavilion)
This should be it.
Yes.
Let's go.
Evil spirits inside.
Keep out.
Stay here and I'll go check.
Are you sure?
If you dare to escape,
you'll die within seven days.
The outer area of the forbidden ground
is a maze based on the Eight Trigrams
and there are traps everywhere.
It's hard for ordinary people
to get out.
Why am I back here again?
What kind of place is this?
♪In the mortal world,
I sail a small boat♪
♪Beneath the moon,
the flowers seem frail♪
♪Until you, like a lone wild goose,
fell into my sight♪
♪Once I raised an empty cup
to confess my feelings♪
♪Lamenting a fleeting dream♪
♪Yet I wish to walk with you
until our hair turns gray♪
♪When the flowers bloom,
I send you a letter of longing♪
♪The spring breeze can't wrinkle it♪
♪We watch the sunset,
drifting in the painting♪
♪Falling behind you♪
♪At first sight of your beautiful face♪
♪What seemed like a fleeting moment
was meant to last forever♪
♪From then on,
listening to your whispered words♪
♪We stayed together, never parting♪
♪I wish to share both joy
and sorrow with you♪
♪One thought tangling
into gentle softness♪
♪Strands of black hair can't compare
to your glance back♪
♪The melody plays softly
and my heart can't be reclaimed♪
♪A touch of love in exchange
for red beans♪
♪Drifting for thousands of miles,
but settling in your heart♪