An Xiang.
An Xiang, are you okay?
It's fine, you're awake now.
Godfather, he...
An Xiang, are you alright?
An Xiang, whatever you just saw,
none of it was real.
What on earth is going on?
You were poisoned.
Poisoned?
So I was poisoned too?
Alright, alright.
An Xiang, drink this.
It's an antidote.
After ingesting those poisonous mushrooms,
people start hallucinating.
Drink up.
Miss He,
what... what is this stuff?
Didn't Old Lu just say?
It's an antidote.
Drink it, you'll be fine.
Uncle Min, you drink it.
It's not bitter.
Clap your hands together,
Fine, Fatty, I'll drink it.
This is called Paris polyphylla.
It has seven leaves in a ring,
with a flower blooming in the center.
They say even in the wild,
if you're bitten by a venomous snake,
this can neutralize the venom.
But we didn't eat any poisonous mushrooms.
Mushroom spores are floating all over this cave.
On top of that, the light is dim,
so I didn't pay attention.
All of us
had hallucinations, right?
So why are you fine?
What's there to question?
Everyone has a different physical constitution.
Look at Old Chen,
strong as an ox.
Old Chen's got capillary hyperplasia.
Uncle Min's got a big eye on him too,
so shouldn't he have stayed clear-headed?
And yet he was still all twisted up.
Nonsense.
Did he end up in your arms in the end?
Can we please drop this subject?
Chen Youxi,
what actually just happened?
Right before we entered the water,
Shu Tong.
Shu Tong!
What are you looking at?
A flood's coming, everyone move!
What are you all standing around for?
Run!
Move it, everyone!
There's no time!
The flood's coming, hurry up!
Get moving!
Once she calmed down, I turned around,
and every one of you was staggering all over.
Ridiculous.
It must have been from inhaling the toxic spores.
Everyone got poisoned to varying degrees.
The hallucination I had just now
was absolutely terrifying.
Guess what I hallucinated.
What?
Braised offal stew,
stir-fried liver,
boiled tripe,
mutton hotpot.
All floating right in front of me,
and I couldn't grab a single one.
Now tell me that's not terrifying.
Even without being poisoned,
don't you fantasize about that stuff anyway?
Advisor He,
what did you hallucinate?
A serpent monster.
I saw some kind of
fire-breathing salamander.
Then that doesn't make sense.
You see, all of us,
because of the places we've been,
and what we've seen,
form an image of fear
deep in our subconscious.
That's what we end up seeing.
I don't know, I'm not sure either.
Fatty.
Scout ahead.
Wait, me again?
Hurry up.
Clap your hands together,
on the first day of the first month.
In that hallucination of yours,
you saw more than just the serpent, right?
What do you mean?
From your unnatural expression earlier,
I have reason to suspect
that I appeared in your hallucination.
I didn't realize you'd become so narcissistic.
Let me ask you,
just now,
did you really not have any hallucinations?
Mine is just capillary hyperplasia,
not a radar signal.
What could I possibly feel?
But before, in Yunling and Nanyun,
the Lingxiao Pearl
stimulated your brain waves, causing hallucinations.
So I suspect
we might not be poisoned.
Rather, deep within Mengna Valley,
there's some kind of substance
that stimulates our brain waves,
thus producing hallucinations.
So you suspect
the disappearance of the Mengna Valley civilization
is related to these hallucinations?
The sudden disappearance of ancient civilizations
is usually linked to sudden plagues,
climate change, or foreign invasion.
The epic poem Dawang gave me mentioned
that Mengna Valley,
due to its expansion
and oppression of surrounding regions,
once triggered uprisings and campaigns against it.
But when they gathered together
and arrived at Mengna Valley, they found
that Mengna Valley had suddenly vanished overnight.
The poem mentions no plague
or climate change,
and the war had not even begun.
So I'm wondering,
what exactly caused
their destruction?
The Mengna Valley civilization
began with that sacred pearl in the queen's hand.
So that sacred pearl
is most likely the Lingxiao Pearl.
Do you think all of this
might have also ended because of it?
It seems only by finding the Lingxiao Pearl
can we uncover the truth.
Exactly.
You know what, I think
there's really something off about you.
Ever since you woke up,
you've been constantly on edge.
What are you thinking about?
I think I
remembered the scene of my parents' car accident.
But I don't know if it's real.
Still, for things like this,
it's better to forget.
If you really want to know what happened,
the best way is to find a witness.
Track them down, compare both sides,
and you'll know exactly what happened.
But this witness,
where am I supposed to find them?
Yeah, after all these years,
where could you find them?
Found it!
Old Chen, I found it!
Right up ahead!
Over there!
Go up, go up, just head up there!
Old Chen.
The eyeball pattern.
Yeah.
This pattern...
is in the Baoji Hero's Epic Scroll.
It was mentioned in there.
Nebulae surrounding the
serpent god's demonic eye.
They called it Xuanlei
Black Crystal Mountain.
Never mind what mountain it is.
Figuring it out is what matters.
Remember the Bingpo
Domain-Quelling Mountain?
Sounds like a mountain, but
it was actually a wolf.
This isn't a mountain or a wolf.
It's a tunnel leading
to the altar grounds.
The altar grounds.
Xuan... what does Xuanlei mean?
If this is really the path
to the altar grounds,
it must relate to the Mengna Valley
ceremonial rites.
Xuanlei is likely a mechanism
to punish those
who intrude during the ceremony.
These symbols on the door...
Miss He,
could these possibly be numbers?
Exactly.
Dots and dashes.
They can be combined freely
to form different numbers.
Hey, why is sand flowing here?
Look! What is that?
We triggered a trap, didn't we?
Get back, hurry!
A trap?
Don't panic.
We must have triggered
the door's linked mechanism.
If we solve this puzzle correctly,
the arrows won't fire.
Now we even have a shield umbrella.
Why aren't we opening the door yet?
What's the rush?
Based on Fatty's years of
trap-triggering experience,
I think these arrows
won't be firing anytime soon.
You all find cover first.
I'll give it a try.
Okay, alright.
I'll go with you.
It's fine.
Leave the Vajra umbrella with me.
Take good care of Old Lu.
You be careful out there.
Go, take the umbrella, take it.
Fall back!
Uncle Min, what's he going up there for?
You always hide in the back when
danger appears.
This time you rushed to the front line.
Either you've lost your mind,
or you've got a plan up your sleeve.
Brother Chen, let me tell you,
the Mengna Valley worshipped queens.
The queen passed her throne
to one who resembled her.
Power passed down through generations,
showcasing the queen's eternal rule.
What is this?
This is a grand cycle of reincarnation.
Look here.
Six sides.
Do you think it's a coincidence,
or does it hint at the Six
Paths of Reincarnation?
An Xiang,
you don't look so well.
Are you feeling unwell?
Maybe it's the long journey,
just running out of energy.
I watched you grow up.
Whether you're physically unwell
or have something on your mind,
I can still tell clearly.
True.
You, Aunt He, and Godfather
have watched me every step of the way.
Of course.
Your adoption paperwork
was all handled by me personally.
Then in my file records,
is there information
about my parents?
If I tell you,
Uncle Min will definitely
be very unhappy.
So you do know.
What exactly do you want to know?
I want to know about my parents.
And whether my parents also had
an eyeball scar on them.
Old Chen is really something.
Come on, let's go up.
Move!
Hey, Brother Chen.
Could this really be
Xuanlei Black Crystal Mountain?
It's not black at all.
A door.