Look at the time.
Did they cancel the date?
I'm sure he's at home.
If they cancelled their date today,
it means our job is done.
Sisters united can overcome anything.
Do you remember
their expressions after you said that?
It was like a bolt from the blue.
They were dumbfounded on the spot.
There is no disease we can't cure.
Oh my god, no way.
Let's go.
I want to leave a good impression.
It's okay.
Just wait for me in the park.
I'll be there after I change.
Don't worry.
I won't be late for our first date.
What should we do?
Calm down.
Looks like all three of our plans failed.
Grab the weapons and hit them hard.
No.
We can't let things go on like this.
Grab the weapons.
Let's fight.
What are you two doing?
We were about to ask what you two are doing.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
Yuanbao, Qingyun.
Gong Yu, what are you doing?
I heard you're a good fighter.
I heard you're not bad either.
Mu Qingyun, I know you are the top guy in Zhicheng.
But for me,
I don't like being an underling.
I only like being the boss.
So give up your position.
Sure.
Take it if you can.
Alright, let's see how well you can fight.
Gong Yu!
Qingyun!
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Grandma!
Grandpa!
Are they classmates?
Apologize.
Come, shake hands.
Wenying,
it's you.
It's you.
Yeah,
it's been so many years.
To think that my grandpa and Yuanbao's grandma
knew each other when they were young.
Yeah.
The thing is,
it seems they're
more than just acquaintances.
You don't know my grandpa.
After he went back that day,
he combed his hair, looked in the mirror,
and even dug out old photos.
Do you think it's possible
between my grandpa and Yuanbao's grandma?
You sure have a wild imagination.
I think it's highly likely.
I think if we just give them a little push,
and help them out.
Is it appropriate?
I don't know how your grandma
has been doing all these years.
But I think it's been tough
for my grandpa alone.
I hope after I go to college,
he can find a companion to spend the rest of his life with.
When you guys go to college,
you wouldn't want Yuanbao's grandma
to be home alone either, right?
How about we talk to Yuanbao about it?
Let's not tell Yuanbao for now.
Because she still seems to have some prejudice against you.
Besides,
we don't even know
our grandparents' true thoughts, do we?
My grandpa is a rare, good man.
You won't find another one like him.
Our grandma raised Yuanbao and me.
She is known as the queen of virtue.
So many old men are lining up to woo her.
She has high standards.
She wouldn't settle for just anyone.
My grandpa is quite a gentleman too.
He wouldn't just like anybody.
My grandma's cooking smells amazing,
and she's great at everything inside and outside the house.
My grandpa's skills aren't bad either.
He dances square dancing so well
that the old ladies in the team fight to be his partner.
When my grandma was young,
she almost became a singer.
Even now, her voice is as good as Li Guyi's.
Well, my grandpa...
My grandma...
How about this?
I'll think about it.
Okay, but hurry up.
Since you are in Zhicheng now,
I'll cover you from now on.
Alright, I'll count on you.
Where did you get this dirt from?
So that's how it is.
I'm sorry.
I misunderstood you.
I'm sorry. I apologize to both of you.
Gong Yu.
I'm sorry.
What a mess.
You guys were so secretive
and kept me in the dark.
Good thing the date didn't happen.
Wait.
Why shouldn't they
give dating a try?
You planned this for days
without telling me.
She's my actual grandma.
What do you mean?
What do you mean she's your actual grandma?
Isn't she
the same as my actual grandma?
Besides, nothing's set in stone yet.
If you knew earlier,
it would've been ruined.
It's not too late now.
Good thing it's ruined.
For something so important,
how could you decide so easily?
Besides, what kind of person he is,
we still don't know.
What are you talking about?
Gong Yu.
Sorry about that.
She didn't mean it.
She doesn't know you well yet.
It's fine.
It's just that Grandpa and Grandma were quite embarrassed just now.
A perfectly good date was ruined.
Since you know about this,
you should think it over carefully.
We'll see.
Gong Yu, take Ruirui home later.
What? Take Ruirui home?
No.
You two.
Let's go.
Grandma is waiting for us to go home for dinner. Hurry up.
You two.
Those two.
Don't pull me.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
Mu Qingjun,
you're really getting more and more opinionated.
My friends,
my grandmother,
you can make decisions about them
without my permission.
Gong Yu is no good.
His grandfather is even worse.
Yuanbao.
Yuanbao, listen to me, Yuanbao.
Gong Yu is really a very good person.
Trust me.
Lately,
I've been intentionally distancing myself from you.
I apologize for that.
Actually, I'm really not good at making friends,
especially with girls.
If I said anything that hurt you,
I'm sorry.
Why are you
telling me all this so suddenly?
Actually, I'm not very good at expressing myself,
whether it's with friends or classmates.
So I haven't made any good friends.
As for Mu Qingjun,
we became friends after a fight.
And I happened to meet your grandparents.
Do you have any dreams?
My parents are both doctors.
So,
they hope
I can be a doctor in the future.
What about you?
I
want to be someone like Liu Xiang.
To become an Olympic champion
and win glory for the country.
Your dream is so great.
You can definitely do it.
You see, we both have our own dreams.
So,
I really don't want to affect you.
And,
I'm really not good at being friends with girls.
I understand what you mean.
From now on,
I won't force you to be friends with me anymore.
Aren't we already friends?
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Let's go.
If Gong Yu's grandpa and my grandma get together,
wouldn't Gong Yu become my older brother?
If years later,
Ruirui and Gong Yu get together,
wouldn't Ruirui become my sister-in-law?
Oh, my God!
Gong Yu even hits girls.
No, no, no.
No, no.
I absolutely won't allow it.
I can't let them be together.
What am I thinking?
Study hard. Study hard.
It didn't happen. It didn't happen.
Leaving it at the door all night, aren't you afraid of attracting mice?
Honestly, who apologizes like this?
Don't think a piece of cake
can buy me off.
Every falling baby's breath
is like the apple falling
on Newton's head.
Thump, thump.
Landing right on my heart,
making my heart flutter.
So much so that ever since then,
whenever I see this flower,
I feel inexplicably excited.
This silly blockhead
always brings me joy and sorrow.
Brother,
Yuanbao,
something happened.
Look.
Someone posted Yuanbao's photo on the forum.
Who did this?
It's you again, isn't it?
What are you doing?
It wasn't me.
Don't falsely accuse me.
Mu Qingyun.
I believe everyone saw it on the forum.
Yes, that was me.
Thanks to the anonymous kind person for helping me promote it.
From now on, if you have empty water bottles,
you can give them to me.
It really saves me a lot of effort.
I don't have to look for them everywhere.
Keep it up, Yuanbao.
Yuanbao.
Keep it up.
Keep it up, Yuanbao.
Thank you, everyone.
Who is in charge of the sophomore forum?
Yes, yes, it's me.
Go delete the post about Xiong Yuanbao right now.
Do you hear me?
O-okay.
N-no problem.
Go.
Let's go.
Will they go to the dean?
Really?
Class,
before we finish, I have an announcement.
The triennial
citywide middle school drama competition
is starting soon.
The rules require
that the play cannot be negative
or vulgar.
The school will select one performance
from the junior high and tenth grade
to participate in the city competition.
Of course,
if you think it'll interfere with your studies,
it's fine if you don't want to participate.
No, no, no.
Mr. Tian, we will participate.
We're in. We're in.
I knew you guys would want to join in.
All right. Since you are in tenth grade
and still have some free time,
I'll give you this chance.
Do you have any good suggestions for the theme?
The judges this time are no longer limited to adults.
The evaluation of peers
also accounts for a large proportion.
So our topic selection this time
must also take into account the preferences of young people.
I have also thought about this problem.
Xing Yaqi, what do you think?
Mr. Tian.
I personally prefer foreign movies.
And my favorite is "Gone with the Wind".
I think the plot in it is very good,
and the lines are also great.
If we can take some classic clips
and perform them,
I think it should be quite good.
Don't just say quite good.
If we do it, we should do the best, right?
Yes.
Mr. Tian.
I think domestic classics are also good.
'Dream of the Red Chamber' is pretty good.
If we add some music to it,
we can perform Jia Baoyu and Lin Daiyu's
poignant love story.
Come on.
Which girl in our class
looks like Lin Daiyu?
They look like Cheng Yaojin.
Once they're on stage,
"Brother Bao, where are you going?"
Isn't that ridiculous?
Don't you like 'A Chinese Odyssey'?
Why didn't you say it?
Everyone is talking about world classics.
If I said 'A Chinese Odyssey',
wouldn't I be laughed at?
That's true.
'A Chinese Odyssey'.
'A Chinese Odyssey'?
The one with Stephen Chow?
'A Chinese Odyssey'.
Why did you choose this?
Because all the classmates like it.
Do you like it?
What about you?
I like it.
And you?
See? The classmates all like it.
Meng Jingu,
you support this too?
'A Chinese Odyssey' has elements of a Chinese classic,
comedy and tragedy,
and it fits the aesthetics of today's young people.
This movie is
quite popular among young people.
Since it's a drama,
no one says it has to be played like a classic.
We can take a different approach and be original.
Maybe we can win at one stroke.
That sounds good.
Sit down.
So, what does everyone think?
Sure, it's good.
Agree.
Let's perform this, sir.
All right.
Since you have decided,
let's perform 'A Chinese Odyssey'.
Although I think this is a bit risky,
I'll say it again:
As long as you work together
and try your best in this competition,
you are the champions in my heart.
Okay.
Since we are going to participate in the competition,
should we
choose a captain to plan it?
Meng Jingu
used to be a student council cadre
when he was in Peiying Middle School,
and he participated in the school anniversary of Peiying Middle School.
So in this aspect,
they might have more experience.
So I propose that
Meng Jingu and the class monitor, Xing Yaqi,
be in charge of this planning.
Does anyone have any objections?
No.
Okay, as for the participants,
you can decide for yourselves.
Voluntary sign-up is fine,
and voting by everyone is also fine.
But let me make it clear first.
The midterm exams are coming up soon,
so studies come first.
Especially the bottom ten students in the monthly exam,
if you don't do well this time,
see how I'll deal with you.
Got it.
I'm looking forward to Yuanbao's version of Fairy Zixia.
Also, whose turn is it for classroom duty?
Teacher,
our group.
Gao Jingyi,
regarding the toilets today,
we still need two people to clean.
Please arrange it.
But, um,
Wang Fei and Zhang Jiadong took sick leave today.
They didn't come.
It seems we don't have enough people.
Are there any students
who would volunteer to clean the toilets?
Who would be so foolish?
Teacher,
I
volunteer.
There really is someone so foolish.
Yuanbao, one person might not be enough.
Teacher,
leave it to me.
I can do it alone.
Okay, thanks for your hard work, Yuanbao.
If you need more hands, remember to find a helper.
Okay, sir.
Alright, class dismissed.
School is over!
Let's go home.
Our school used to be
a prince's mansion.
When the whole family was executed,
many infants under a month old were killed.
When night falls,
they come out to seek revenge.
Help!
There's a ghost!
What's wrong?
There's a ghost inside!
A ghost?
I think you just have a guilty conscience.
No.
Listen, there really is a sound inside.
It's so scary.
Wait a minute.
Wait, don't go in.
There's nothing here.
This side up.
It's just a little kitty.
Why is it crying like that? It's so scary.
Special period.
What special period?
You don't know this?
Animals
go through something called heat.
When they're in heat...
Stop talking.
I get it. I get it.
Why are you two here?
To see if you need help.
The teacher asked me to come and check.
The teacher didn't ask me to come.
But we live opposite each other.
Since you're done cleaning, I'll get going.
Wait. Wait.
Why don't we go together?
It's all Shang Ningyu's fault.
Telling ghost stories every day.
Scared me to death.
Mr. Liu.
Hello,
You scared me.
Why haven't you left yet?
Xiong Yuanbao just finished cleaning the restrooms on two floors.
Okay, I'm leaving then.
Wait.
I'm here to use the restroom.
You scared me so much I almost forgot.
Well,
Mr. Liu, should we wait for you?
No need. You'll affect my performance if you stay here.
Alright, we'll leave first.
Won't Mr. Liu be scared alone?
You think everyone is like you?
There are no ghosts in this world.
They're all made up by people.
I know,
but I'm still scared.
If you're really scared,
you can sing.
The funnier the song, the better the effect.
Give it a try.
Really? I'll try it.
The river flows east.
The stars in the sky follow the Big Dipper.
I think I feel a bit better.
Give a roar when you see injustice.
Strike when it's time to strike.
Are you crazy?
Desk mate,
I'll be leaving now.
Okay, bye.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Why are you so nice to your desk mate?
He's a new classmate,
and my desk mate.
He also helped me.
What's wrong with being polite to him?
What, are you jealous?
Me, jealous?
Are you thinking too highly of him,
or too highly of yourself?
Why would I be jealous?
Why are you so mad?
Didn't you already go back?
Why are you here again?
I just forgot something and came back to get it.
Thanks for today.
For what?
Thanks for suggesting to everyone
that we perform "A Chinese Odyssey".
I just said it in passing.
It wasn't for you.
You're not nice to me at all.
Why would I suggest performing "A Chinese Odyssey" for you?
Don't flatter yourself.
Who do you want to play?
After thinking it over,
Great Immortal Pansi suits me best.
I'll just compromise
and play Great Immortal Pansi.
Compromise?
Don't you just want to play Zixia?
Yeah, so what?
What do you want to play?
Since you're playing Zixia,
then I...
Since we were kids,
for this kind of performance,
haven't you always been the boss?
I'm hungry. Let's go eat.
Why are you eating again?
How about you play Zhu Bajie?
You're the biggest eater here.
You should play Zhu Bajie.
How about you play the Bull Demon King?
Then you play the Spider Demon.
Bull Demon King!
Spider Demon!
You are the Bull Demon King!
Spider Demon! Bull Demon King!
You're so silly.
Look at me, the Pansi Fairy.
So silly.
I'm not afraid to be alone.
Courage as my blanket.
Not afraid.
No matter how dark the night is, I'll pretend not to see.
The sun will definitely appear.
Hello, look at me.
What are you afraid of?
Aren't you going on a business trip in a couple of days?
Let's go see them first.
Okay, let's go early tomorrow morning.
It's been so many years.
They should be the ones visiting us.
All right, all right.
Keep it a secret.
We can never let the kids know.