Mutou.
Oh no.
How do I piece it back together?
Right, there seem to be words on the back.
In the future, I
wish...
Wish I...
Wish I what?
It should be some kind of blessing.
Wish I live as long as the Southern Mountain.
Wish I
eat a lot but never get fat.
Wish I become more and more beautiful.
If he finds out
that the gift he carefully picked for me
was ruined by me like this,
he will definitely be angry.
What exactly is in here?
Now this secret has truly become a secret.
Forget it.
Since it's a secret,
let it be a secret forever.
I can't possibly go ask him
what is written inside.
Wouldn't that give me away?
No way.
I just won't tell him.
I wonder if
she has looked at the puzzle.
Goodbye, Grandma.
Goodbye. Take care.
Grandma,
where did Yuanbao go then?
She didn't call you?
She said she'll be studying at the library these days.
I happen to be going there too.
Well,
Grandma, you should go back inside.
Okay.
Is she going with Meng Jingu?
Do you know how to work?
What are your big eyes for?
Look at all this fog.
Here, there, it's all fog.
Wipe it over there.
I'll wipe it right away.
Why are you
so clumsy?
Can't you even mop the floor properly?
Spilling everything everywhere.
Do you like wiping?
Go away!
Dad!
Sorry.
I thought you were a bad guy.
I saw a little girl walking alone at night.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You are quite strong.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you wait for me after school?
I saw you were too busy with work.
I can go back by myself.
My daughter has grown up.
But Dad still worries about you.
Let's go home.
Your mom made delicious food for you.
Really?
Let me guess.
Ribs or braised fish?
Both.
My three lovely fairies.
Good morning to you all.
Everyone will have to work hard again today.
But we still need to do our best.
If you...
If you are tired, we can take turns resting.
You can call me anytime.
I'd be happy to take turns with you.
Always remember
that we will always be a family.
Let's do our best!
What's wrong with him today?
Is he crazy?
Spare my life, young hero.
Let's talk this out.
Is being a bubble tea shop manager such a big deal?
If you ever dare
to boss your employees around again,
I'll make sure you can't walk.
If you want to play the big boss, I'll leave you bedridden.
I-I'll never do it again.
Never again.
It hurts.
Shang Ningyu.
Yuanbao,
Auntie, where is Mutou?
Weren't you two going to attend
your classmate's birthday?
Yes. Did he leave first?
This kid. Why didn't he wait for you?
It's fine. I'll go by myself.
Then be safe on the road, Yuanbao.
Okay.
This kid.
Bro,
you're doing this to let Yuanbao relax.
But you're making me bleed out.
I might not even have enough for food.
How much short?
Three hundred.
Don't tell anyone else.
Don't worry, bro.
My mouth is like a safe,
so tight
it doesn't even let air out.
Doesn't let air out, huh?
My mom fed me
a lot of sweet potatoes last night.
Sorry, bro.
Hubby, here.
Jingu, are you going out?
I have something to do.
Good morning.
Good morning, Uncle and Aunt.
Xinrui, come in.
Xinrui, why
are you here?
Didn't I tell you I was going out today?
I was bored staying home alone.
Where are you going? Take me with you.
It's not very convenient for me.
You used to take me with you when you went out.
Just let me go with you.
Exactly.
Xinrui just came back.
You should take her out more.
I'm not going out for fun.
I really have something to do.
What important things could a student like you have to do?
No matter where you go today,
you must take Xinrui with you.
Otherwise, you can't go either.
You guys...
Jingu, just listen to me.
Don't you still want to buy that medical insurance?
Please, take me with you.
I promise.
I won't bother you.
I'll just stay quiet, okay?
Son.
Come on, eat and drink whatever you want.
Today,
it's my treat.
Come on, brother. Let me toast you first.
It's been eight cans, serve some food.
I'm so full.
Let's drink first.
I can't swallow it anymore.
Have another drink. Have another drink.
When will the hot dishes be served?
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Still waiting?
What time is it now?
Wait a little longer.
I really can't swallow it anymore.
Yuanbao, over here.
Everyone is here so early.
We're all waiting for you. Hurry up.
Yuanbao, come sit here.
Move over.
We've been waiting for you.
Then let's start.
Come on.
I'm lighting the candles.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday.
Thank you, everyone.
It's so great to have you all here.
Happy birthday to my little brother.
May you get beaten less by Mom from now on.
Bro, what are you saying?
Shang Ningyu, I wish all your dreams come true.
That's a great wish from Ruirui.
I wish you speak with eloquence
and stop talking nonsense.
Xiong Yuanbao,
I found that you have learned bad things now.
It's my turn.
I wish you, my brother,
a very happy birthday,
never to return,
and gone.
Once you go,
it's all over.
Alright.
Smooth sailing!
Shang Ningyu,
wish you good health and all the best.
Thank you, class monitor.
Success in your studies!
Thank you.
You guys have said almost all the good words,
and left nothing for me.
Then, I wish...
Got it.
Got it, bro.
Longevity and good fortune, right?
I get you.
Shang Ningyu,
happy birthday.
I hope all of us good friends
can always be by your side.
Thank you, Qiao Yan.
It's great that you could come.
Thanks.
Is everyone here?
Let's cut the cake.
Time to cut the cake.
Cut the cake. Cut the cake. Cut the cake.
Didn't you invite someone else?
Who?
Right, right, right.
I invited Meng Jingu.
Look at my memory.
I even forgot the person I invited.
Let's wait a little longer.
Cheers, cheers, cheers.
Jingu.
Happy birthday.
Hello, everyone.
Xinrui is here too.
Well,
have a seat.
Sit down.
Xinrui,
come and sit here.
Sit here.
Okay.
Happy birthday, Shang Ningyu.
I heard from Jingu that it's your birthday today.
But I didn't know what you liked.
No need.
So I brought this,
an album signed by Jay Chou.
It's for you.
This...
It's really an album signed by Jay Chou.
Yeah.
My uncle's friend organizes concerts,
and got it specifically for me.
Bro.
I figured this birthday of yours is totally worth it.
You hit the jackpot.
Xinrui, you are too kind.
Well, I know.
I just got here,
so we might not be very familiar yet.
Before I came, I was afraid
I would spoil everyone's fun.
I hope you don't mind.
Not at all.
Why would we mind?
Of course not.
That's great.
Yuanbao, you don't mind either, do you?
Why would I mind?
I'm glad you could come.
I was actually afraid
you would misunderstand me
because of the notebook incident.
I wouldn't. It's in the past.
By the way.
I know you all like Jay Chou,
so I got a few extras for you guys.
Thank you.
I hope you like them.
Thank you. I don't like Jay Chou's songs.
I like them.
Thank you.
This is for you.
I don't like them either.
Bro, you like them. Did you forget?
Take it away.
Ruirui.
Yuanbao.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
I gave it to Jingu's family already.
I know.
You all probably don't know me very well.
Actually, I don't have many friends.
Jingu is my only friend.
That's why he brought me here today.
I just joined this class,
and I really want to fit in with everyone.
But I didn't know what you all like,
so I brought these.
From now on,
just tell me what you like from now on.
I'll share whatever I have with you all.
I used to think
pretty girls like you would be hard to approach.
I didn't expect you to have such a great personality.
What do you call this?
This is truly beauty and brains, like a lotus rising from the water.
Gentle and lovely.
No, you flatter me.
I'm not that good.
Actually, I think
the most outstanding girl in your class
is Yuan Bao.
To be liked by so many classmates,
she must have something special.
Yuan Bao, please take care of me in the future.
I was worried before I came.
I didn't expect everyone to be so nice.
Why would you be worried?
Everyone welcomes you, right?
Yes.
We should also thank Gu Xinrui
for the gifts she brought us.
Let's applaud and welcome Gu Xinrui.
Welcome, warm welcome.
Thank you.
You guys are so nice, really.
Really, thank you.
Are you done talking?
Sorry, I might have talked too much.
You, come downstairs with me to order.
Actually, it's just right.
Meng Jingu, what do you mean?
You knew perfectly well that before the summer vacation,
everyone was unhappy
because of the notebook incident.
Yet you brought Gu Xinrui here.
Are you intentionally making things difficult for Yuanbao?
I had no choice but to bring Xinrui along.
No choice?
What, did she threaten you with her life?
I can't explain it to you clearly.
Anyway,
it's not what you think.
Also,
I genuinely came to celebrate Shang Ningyu's birthday
and make everyone happy.
I didn't know Xinrui would say so much.
You didn't know?
Gu Xinrui kept saying
that you wanted to bring her.
You saw the atmosphere just now.
A perfectly good classmate's birthday party
turned into a welcome party for Gu Xinrui.
What is this?
Where does that leave Yuanbao?
I don't want to argue with you today.
I'll clean up the mess I made.
I have nothing more to explain to you.
I'm going to order food.
Autographed?
What are you doing?
Yuanbao.
A toast to you.
If you consider me a friend,
drink this.
If you don't drink,
I'll assume you're still mad at me
over the notebook from the other day,
and I'll be heartbroken.
We can't drink alcohol.
Let's just have water.
You are not kids anymore.
It's just a glass of beer. It's fine.
I have really never drunk alcohol before.
How about we just have soft drinks?
Come on.
Xinrui. Xinrui. Xinrui.
We can't drink alcohol.
Although she usually acts like a tomboy,
she probably hasn't even seen alcohol.
I offered you a toast on purpose
to clear up the misunderstanding.
It's too disrespectful if you don't drink it.
Gu Xinrui, that's enough.
It's meaningless to keep acting up.
No, what did I do?
I just offered her a toast.
Why make it sound like I'm deliberately making things difficult for her?
Aren't you?
Okay.
Soda is fine, right?
Deep feelings, let's see who drinks more.
I'll go first.
Yuanbao.
All right.
Xinrui.
Bei.
Yuanbao, you...
Stop drinking, you two.
That's enough, Xinrui.
That's enough.
Deskmate.
Jingu.
Yuanbao.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, guys.
I'll make it up to you next time.
I'm leaving now.
Jingu.
Wait for me, Jingu.
Jingu, what's wrong
with you?
What do you think?
What's wrong with you today?
Why did you keep picking on Yuanbao?
I wasn't picking on her.
I brought her a gift and offered her a toast.
Why do you say I was picking on her?
Jingu.
You said she's just a deskmate.
Are you sure?
No matter what you think,
Xinrui,
I want to tell you clearly today.
We are grown up now.
We can't be like when we were kids.
I have my own life and friends.
Please don't interfere.
Also,
we are brother and sister.
Why?
Yuanbao.
I had a terrible attitude before,
so please forgive me.
You are a smart
and capable girl.
Although you were clumsy at first,
you quickly got the hang of it.
Here,
I wish you success in your studies
and a bright future.
This milk tea is still very sweet.
But this summer vacation
is full of strange flavors.
I was busy taking extra classes, picking up bottles,
and interning at the milk tea shop.
For some reason, Mutou
suddenly rarely came to see me.
Maybe I was too busy.
I managed to find some free time
and finished watching the TV drama 'Struggle'.
The secret behind Meng Jingu's puzzle
remains a secret.
At Shang Ningyu's birthday party,
Gu Xinrui's sudden appearance
made me feel extra uneasy
about the new semester.
Yuanbao.
The puzzle I gave you last time,
did you finish it?
Puzzle.
Yes.
Oh no. He still remembers it.
What should I say?
Yuanbao.
I finished it.
Then,
the words on the back,
you saw them too?
If I tell him I ruined the puzzle
and couldn't figure out
what the secret behind it is,
will he get angry?
Are you willing to?
Here's the thing.
I think,
since it's your secret,
we better keep it low-key.
Don't worry,
I will definitely keep this secret for you.
My lips are sealed.
What is it? A leaf again?
No.
Let's go back.
What's wrong with Meng Jingu today?
He's looking at me weirdly,
and what he said is strange too.
Yuanbao.
Okay.
What happened to you?
I fell during the city training.
How did you end up like this?
Don't ask.
Mu Qingjun.
Don't let sitting together affect your studies.
Don't worry, sir.
I have an announcement to make.
The autumn sports meet is coming up soon.
Every sophomore class in the school...
we will hold a men's basketball tournament
to help everyone integrate into the class better.
The rules are simple.
The science classes will compete first.
The winner
will play the winner of the humanities classes in the finals.
Some of you might think
it's a waste of time and delays your studies.
But Zhicheng
has always emphasized
comprehensive development in morality, intelligence, physical fitness, aesthetics, and labor.
We will never let you just study all the time.
So, you need to balance your studies and health.
Teacher,
what about us girls?
The girls in each class
need to prepare a cheerleading squad.
Even though cheerleaders don't compete,
I still hope you can do a good job.
Given that some students in our class
in your freshman year,
had experience in the drama competition
I'd like Meng Jingu
and Xing Yaqi to be in charge of this activity.
Do you two have any problems with that?
No problem.
No problem, Mr. Tian.
As for the class monitor,
I'll leave it to Xing Yaqi.
Does anyone have any objections?
No.
Good.
Then we'll have self-study for this class.
Xing Yaqi, organize the class.
Okay, Mr. Tian.
Oh my god.
I didn't expect that in our sophomore year,
our homeroom teacher
would still be Mr. Tian Yong.
And our chemistry teacher is still Da Meili.
What kind of fate is this?
And I heard
that Big Rooster He Qing,
Ms. Xu, and Mr. Zhong
all followed us to sophomore year.
Really?
Don't you love ribs?
I got two portions for you.
Eat.
If it's not enough,
I'll get more.
It's enough.
Thank you.
What are your plans now?
It's fine.
I'll rest for a year and try again next year.
You're so energetic.
Of course.
Any progress with Grandpa and Grandma?
Yuanbao is unwilling, so what progress could there be?
What about you two?
Someone suddenly got in the way.
If it's really good for Yuanbao
and helps her future studies,
I'll back off.
That doesn't sound like the Mu Qingjun I know.
How can you give up?
Miaomiao, did you hear?
Shui transferred schools.
Which Shui?
You know,
the former top guy at Yuhong.
He transferred to Peiying for his senior year.
Is it that Shui
who had a grudge against Mu Qingjun because of Xiong Yuanbao?
Yes, that's him.
I heard that after he transferred schools,
he seemed to have dropped out
and fights outside every day.
Such boys are so annoying.
I think boys should be clean and fair,
love to study,
just like Meng Jingu.
Speaking of Meng Jingu,
I saw him
eating with Xiong Yuanbao in the cafeteria a while ago,
and he kept putting food in her bowl.
Why do boys with good grades
always hang out with girls
who have average grades?
Chang Yu, when do you think
a top student will put food in my bowl?
You'd better study hard.
Let's go.
Are you really quitting the cheerleading performance?
I have no choice. I have to take a vocal grading test.
There's a schedule conflict.
Then who will be the captain if you leave?
Well,
Mr. Tian will probably arrange something.
Summer has quietly passed, leaving behind a little secret.
Today, a kid from Class Seven
passed out after running two laps in PE class.
The doctor said
it's hypoglycemia and a lack of exercise.
Kids these days
really have poor physical fitness.
Exactly.
Let me tell you,
this tradition at our school is really great.
Once kids reach their sophomore year,
the academic pressure is immense.
They need good health to survive these two years.
That's why this basketball tournament
not only builds up the kids' bodies,
but also keeps their enthusiasm high.
Yeah.
I remember when we were in school,
we paid a lot of attention to physical exercise.
Now that we are working,
we are busy and stressed, so we don't have time for it anymore.
All right.
Class, stop writing.
I have an announcement to make.
Class monitor Xing Yaqi
has a vocal grading exam soon,
so she can't join the cheer squad.
I propose
that the cheer captain
be Gu Xinrui.
Any objections?
I disagree.
Mu Qingyun recommended Xiong Yuanbao.