What are you doing?
Is this fun?
I don't know what you are talking about.
Move. Don't block my way.
I'm asking you. Is this fun?
Don't you know if it's fun?
I didn't slander you.
Was I wrong?
Xiong Yuanbao.
Are you afraid of others exposing your faults
and calling you an orphan?
What are you doing?
What's going on?
It seems Qiao Yan brought up
Yuanbao's parents first.
Mu Qingyun.
What are you doing? Tearing down the classroom?
You just wait.
Mu Qingyun. Mu Qingyun. Mu Qingyun.
Yuanbao.
Don't come over.
Yuanbao,
listen to me.
I really didn't mean to
tell Mr. Men about your background.
Please don't do anything foolish.
I just...
Mutou,
they are right.
Since I was little, everyone has said the same.
I am an orphan,
a wild child with no parents.
Yes, I am scared.
But being scared
doesn't mean I need others' pity.
Xiong Yuanbao,
how can you say you are
an unwanted wild child?
You have your grandmother
and me.
My parents are your parents.
Whether you admit it or not,
it is the truth.
I know this
has always been a wound in your heart,
untouchable and unspoken.
But you can't live your whole life
like an ostrich,
burying your head in the sand
and refusing to look forward.
If your grandmother knew you were like this,
how sad would she be?
Think about it,
she can look forward with optimism and grace.
Why can't you live in the sun?
Yuanbao.
What are you doing?
Yuanbao, promise me first.
No matter what difficulties you face in the future,
don't ever think about taking your own life.
If something happens to you,
how can I explain it to Grandma?
Who wants to take their own life?
Didn't you tell me to live towards the sun?
I'm just feeling the breeze and the sunshine.
Okay?
Seriously.
You really didn't think that?
No.
Then let's hurry back.
Come on, I'll carry you.
Why?
This way we look more imposing.
What happened to you two?
Yuanbao, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Go back to your seats.
Class.
Taking the opportunity of this class meeting,
I'd like to apologize to Xiong Yuanbao.
Yuanbao.
I was too impulsive today.
I blamed you without finding out the truth.
I didn't think it through,
and acted unfairly.
But teachers are human too,
and we make mistakes.
So right here,
I sincerely apologize to you.
It's fine, teacher.
Qiao Yan.
I talked too much.
I shouldn't have talked behind your back
and said so many mean things.
I hope you won't take it to heart.
I'm sorry.
Being in the same class
is a great destiny.
I hope
you can cherish this destiny.
Shake hands and make up.
Then we need a friendly hug.
Right, let's hug.
Yes.
Yes, exactly.
It doesn't feel good to be talked about behind your back, does it?
Let's go. School is over.
Stop fighting.
Yuanbao.
I know you're suffering.
I'll always be with you.
My sweet daughter.
My sweet daughter, over here.
Yuanbao.
Come here.
You called them?
Why are you just standing there? Go.
Yuanbao, we're here to pick you up from school.
107.
108.
109.
The competition is on Yuanbao's birthday.
Such a special day.
What can 109 do?
My mom is so stingy.
Mom and Dad.
I'm going to Shanghai again.
And it happens to be on my birthday.
Did you arrange all of this?
May the trip to Shanghai
be smooth
and safe.
I must win the award.
Xiong Yuanbao,
you can do it!
Second interview site.
New thinking, new expression, real experience.
Thank you for just now.
Anyone else would have done the same.
I'm waiting for a car here, so I don't need the umbrella.
The rain might get heavier later.
Take it and go home quickly.
Thank you.
But I'm not a local.
I just came to Shanghai yesterday for a competition.
How about you leave me your contact info?
I'll return the umbrella to you then.
No need.
Wait a moment.
Brother.
Why did it take you so long to answer?
I thought something happened to you.
Me?
I'm at a bus stop near the exam center,
taking shelter from the rain.
Then I'll wait for you.
Call me when you get here.
You don't need to return the umbrella. I'm leaving.
How can I just take your umbrella for nothing?
No.
Give me your contact info,
or your address.
I'll mail it back to you.
I'll be going now.
Thank you!
Wait.
What is it?
Watch out for cars.
Yuanbao.
Why are you so late? I've been waiting for a long time.
Sorry, sorry.
Exam is over. How was it?
I almost didn't make it in.
As long as you took the exam, it's fine.
What was the topic?
I wrote about my parents.
Let's go. I'll take you to a good place.
Since we're here,
whatever you want to play or eat,
just tell me.
Like roller coasters
or something.
Keep bragging.
Aren't you afraid of heights?
That was when I was a kid.
I am not afraid of anything now.
Just watch my performance later.
Hold on to me if you're scared,
got it?
Don't say I know you.
Yuanbao,
I thought you would be touched by the scene
and think of your parents.
That was the last birthday
they spent with me in this life.
I was quite anxious before coming here.
I thought I would be afraid
and resistant.
But after coming here,
I feel much more relieved.
Thank you, Mutou.
No need to be polite with me.
Didn't you say
that we are like
biological sisters?
Shouldn't sisters
share through thick and thin?
Before, when I said we were sisters,
you always said we were brothers.
Why admit you're a beauty today?
Come on.
Since it's your birthday,
sister, don't push your luck.
Wait a second.
I ran too fast just now.
It's a sense of ritual.
Sense of ritual.
I couldn't find candles.
I'll use a glow stick instead.
Come on, make a wish.
Mom and Dad.
I'm at the amusement park for my birthday again.
Mutou is with me this time.
Do you see?
Yuanbao, send me some messages.
To give me courage.
My mom signed me up for cram school.
The teacher kept us late today.
It's a bit dark on the road.
And I'm a little scared walking home alone.
Ruirui, don't be afraid.
I'm with you.
Be safe by yourself.
Let me know immediately if anything happens.
Okay, I'll let you know when I arrive.
I feel much better talking to you.
You really are my little sunshine.
Don't be afraid.
I'm right beside you.
They won't dare to do anything.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
It's not safe for a girl to walk at night.
Don't take the small alleys anymore.
Gong Yu.
Well.
Let's go.
How much were these green beans?
Three-fifty a catty. What about yours?
Mine were three.
Yours were cheaper, Mrs. Xiong.
They're pretty good.
Yeah, very fresh.
I also bought these.
Mrs. Wang, Mrs. Xiong.
Just got back from grocery shopping?
Hey, Li.
Your scarf is exactly like mine.
It really is.
My son heard
that buying mom a red scarf this year
will bring her health and longevity.
Look.
He even insisted I wear it.
My daughter said the same thing.
That shows
your kids care about you.
You should be content.
Content? How could I not be?
Well, you guys keep chatting.
I have something to do, so I'll get going.
What we just said,
did she take it the wrong way?
If Mrs. Xiong's son were still around,
he would have bought her one too.
It's a little pricier.
Because the material is good,
the original price was ninety-nine.
Now it's fifty.
What about this one?
The thin one.
Ma'am, listen to me.
The original price of this thin one is fifty.
Now it's thirty.
Thirty is enough.
Just thirty.
Thirty for this.
I can't do thirty.
I'd be losing money at thirty.
It's the wholesale price.
Try it on.
You guys try it on and see.
Grandma.
Are you hungry?
I'll cook right away.
We'll eat soon.
Grandma.
Didn't they say
giving Mom a red scarf this year
would bring her health and a long life?
I dreamed of my dad yesterday.
He asked me to give you
a brand-new red scarf on his behalf.
Offer one to your mom too.
Your mom loved red the most.
Grandma, come here.
Look.
Grandma, I'm
a little late.
I also bought you a red scarf.
Okay.
Put them both on. It's double the effect.
I'll wear them both.
Auntie Wenying,
try it on.
I thought I could give you a surprise.
I'll wear them all.
I'll put them all on.
It looks beautiful, Grandma.
Mom, I bought this one for you.
Put it on.
I have one too?
Of course.
Here, child.
You wear it too.
Thank you, Grandma.
Here.
Put one on Yuanbao too.
Put one on our Yuanbao too.
Thank you, Grandma.
We're all happy.
Right, to celebrate Yuanbao
winning the essay contest,
Auntie bought you pig trotters and ribs.
Grandma.
Mom.
This brat, really.
The kids have grown up.
They are sensible now.
Yuanbao won a prize in the essay contest.
Tiejun and Aihua can finally rest in peace.
Yes.
For the kids,
you've taken on so many part-time jobs.
You've worked hard.
Not at all.
This way, we owe them a little less.
Owe?
Alright.
Don't dwell on it.
That very night,
after I sent you the message,
I was walking alone on the path home.
The situation was tense.
There were a few delinquents
whistling at me.
He
suddenly appeared behind me.
He escorted me through that
most dangerous and darkest road.
But the situation was so urgent at the time.
I was terrified.
I didn't even ask for his contact information.
I only heard someone call him,
Gong Yu.
Don't you think it's frustrating?
Right.
Oh no. It got smudged by the rain.
How am I supposed to return his umbrella?
Who is it? Someone new?
A guy or a girl?
It was after that essay competition.
It suddenly started raining.
Then I almost got hit by a car.
And suddenly a guy appeared and saved me.
He even gave me his umbrella.
I just want his contact info
and return the umbrella to him.
Oh my.
This is more like an idol drama than my life.
Is he handsome?
A little bit. He looks like Aaron Kwok.
Aaron Kwok?
Oh my.
You must be regretting it so much.
It's fine.
It's just that I can't return his umbrella.
Will he think
that I don't keep my word?
Here, why don't you leave the umbrella with me?
So you won't get upset looking at it.
Oh my.
This is your favorite Hu Ge sticker.
Best friends share everything.
Give me the notebook.
Are you sure this is okay?
It does look a bit weird.
Forget it.
Let's just go with it.
When I want to see the whole face,
I'll come to you to piece it together.
When you met that guy,
how did you feel?
It's a feeling deep in your heart.
It's like this person is braving the wind
and coming just for you.
You start to frequently
and involuntarily think about it.
You're done, bro.
You've fallen.
What is this?
Self-Cultivation of Charming Boys.
What are you doing?
Why aren't ours growing?
I don't know either.
Maybe we should eat more papaya.
By the way.
This is
the latest magazine my dad brought back
from his business trip to Guangzhou.
It's full of the most popular clothes,
makeup, and hairstyles right now.
This is good. This is good.
This is good.
Why does this look...
It looks a bit like a delinquent girl.
This is good. Long hair, short hair.
This suits us.
I didn't give all my New Year's money to my mom.
Let's go. Hurry up.
What's with this look?
Does it look good?
Ruirui forced me to do it.
I still think
your previous look was better.
Then I'll go wash it off.
Luckily it's temporary.
Saying I'd turn into a princess.
It's all a lie.
You care so much about my opinion.
Are you trying to get my attention?
Is it okay now?
I'm talking to you.
Isn't it the same as before?
What's wrong with my face?
Forget it. It's hopeless.
Crazy.
The floor is slippery.
Be careful when you walk next time.
I'm leaving first.
Mu Qingjun.
Stand up.
Hello, teacher.
Hello, students. Please sit down.
Today,
we have a new student transferring to our class.
Let's welcome him with a round of applause.
Mr. Tian, is there anything wrong?
I'm fine. Are you?
You went to the wrong class.
Sorry.
What are you all laughing at?
You two, come in.
This is so unreal.
He actually transferred to our class.
Is God finally awake?