We checked Li Xiulan's withdrawal records.
On the day Bai Tao died,
she withdrew twenty thousand yuan.
What exactly did she need that money for?
Thank you.
Is it possible that Bai Tao was blackmailing her?
She originally intended to give the money to Bai Tao.
If she planned to pay,
then why would Li Xiulan still commit murder?
Could it really be as Li Xiulan said,
that Bai Tao accidentally fell to his death?
But Bai Tao's autopsy report shows
he was already dead before the fall.
But that would be too strange.
If she was willing to pay,
there was no need to kill.
Maybe their negotiation broke down.
A crime of passion.
Then Li Xiulan is lying.
Captain Qin, Bai Fan has been found.
Yanyan actually wanted to come see you too.
Don't let her come.
Even if she wanted to, she couldn't come.
It's not allowed.
Yanyan.
Is she doing okay?
She's fine.
But your case isn't looking good.
This is the medical record you forged, right?
Do you realize that by doing this
you've basically ruined her whole life?
But don't worry.
She doesn't know yet.
I haven't told her anything.
Thank you.
Aunt Xiulan.
You can't hide anything from me anymore.
I really want to help you.
Yes.
We all have regrets about what happened back then.
They deserved to die.
But the law doesn't care about feelings.
If you kill someone, you have to pay the price.
It's all my fault.
I'm the one who killed them.
If I have to go to jail or be executed,
I'm not afraid.
But what about my daughter?
If I'm gone,
how will she live?
Here.
Lawyer Lin.
You said you wanted to go over things to watch out for in court.
Why did you ask me to meet here?
To help you pick out an outfit for court.
Do I need special clothes for court?
Yes.
We need to make a good impression on the judge.
How you present yourself in court is very important, trust me.
These clothes are expensive.
I don't want to spend money carelessly.
I'll just find something at home.
As long as it's clean and appropriate, it's fine.
Don't worry.
I'm very confident about this case.
What you need to do
most importantly, is cooperate with me.
I'll give you the outfit.
Lawyer Lin.
Isn't this outfit a bit inappropriate for court?
My mom doesn't like me wearing skirts.
It looks great.
It's very appropriate.
You really didn't need to bring so many things.
I have everything you need at my place.
Lawyer Lin,
In exchange for helping my mom,
it's not about money,
it's me, right?
As a lawyer,
it's my duty to help my clients win their cases.
As for you and me,
we missed our chance before.
Now, I don't want to miss it again.
Starting today,
you'll live here.
Please make sure you keep your promise.
I will do everything I promised.
I asked you to move in
partly for easier communication,
and on the other hand,
it's for your safety.
Besides, you cook two meals a day for me,
and help Nian Nian with homework.
This is also to repay me
for handling your mom's case for free.
That's fair, isn't it?
As long as I can save my mom,
I'll do anything.
It's a deal.
Li Xiulan, let me ask you again.
How did Bai Tao really die?
He slipped and fell to his death.
I advise you to tell the truth.
I am telling the truth.
Aren't you curious about what the report says?
We found Bai Tao's blood sample
on Wang Guocheng's truck.
Bai Tao didn't die from a fall at all.
He was hit and killed by a vehicle.
You already know the result.
So why are you still asking me?
We're giving you a chance to confess.
We’ve already been to your house as well.
We found these things.
According to the investigation,
on the night of August 9th,
you withdrew money from several ATMs
with a total withdrawal of twenty thousand yuan.
From Wang Guocheng's account,
thirty thousand yuan was also withdrawn.
The total is fifty thousand yuan.
Traffic surveillance footage shows
that at the time of the incident,
you did hand this paper bag to Bai Tao.
After that, Bai Tao was killed.
Then this paper bag appeared in your home.
We've also reviewed the contents of this USB drive.
So can you tell us again
what happened that night?
The person—
I was the one who hit and killed him.
Wang Guocheng doesn't know anything.
He has nothing to do with this. The car—
I stole it.
Stole it.
Since you decided to give the money to Bai Tao,
why did you suddenly change your mind?
I didn't intend to kill him.
I also never really meant to give him the money.
Aunt Lan
What do you mean?
You ambushed me.
I went through all that trouble to get you two the USB and the video.
And now you want to run me over.
Let me tell you,
if I die here today, you won't get away.
You want to run me over, right? Go ahead.
Come on, I won't run.
Come on, drive, do it!
You're just a fishmonger, do you even dare?
Who are you trying to scare?
Li Xiulan, let me tell you,
because of this,
your tens of thousands aren't enough anymore.
Go home and think about it.
How much is your precious daughter worth?
Why did you choose to
dispose of the body somewhere relatively close to your home
to dump the body?
That building
has been abandoned for four or five years.
There have always been rumors it's haunted, so no one ever goes there.
I thought if Bai Tao's body was to be discovered,
it would take at least a few years.
So you dragged Bai Tao to the unfinished building
to leave footprints.
You even deliberately got mud on yourself.
You also put on Bai Tao's shoes.
You created the illusion of one-way footprints.
But unfortunately, you overlooked something.
You faked everything,
but you couldn't fake the real characteristics of someone who fell from a building.
He deserved to die.
He used those photos of my daughter to blackmail me.
Didn't he deserve to die?
So you
chose to kill him,
didn't you?
At that moment, I had only one thought in my mind:
how great it would be if this person just disappeared.
Li Xiulan,
didn't you ever think
that if you killed someone,
what would happen to Li Yan?
Li Yan would lose her only mother as well.
Captain Qin,
Bai Fan is awake.
I want to see Qin Yang.
I'll only talk when Qin Yang is here.
Captain Qin,
Li Xiulan has gone crazy.
She tried to kill me.
She wants to kill everyone.