You absolutely must not tell my mom.
Here you go.
You're not leaving, are you?
Get up, quickly.
Make her leave.
These videos recovered by the tech department are crucial.
Li Yan behaved abnormally after waking up last night.
She was irritable at one moment,
and crying the next.
There was an expert consultation this morning.
They said it was schizophrenia.
The video recorded by the landlord
isn't 24-hour footage either.
Last night, Sister Xiaoqin and I checked everything
and found this segment.
If we keep investigating along this line,
we should be able to find
some evidence supporting her schizophrenia.
Very good.
Keep playing it, let's see Li Xiulan.
Captain Qin, it's this one.
Chlorpromazine hydrochloride tablets.
This...
This medicine bottle is for epilepsy.
But the pills inside are chlorpromazine hydrochloride tablets.
That's a medication for mental illnesses.
So that means
Li Xiulan has been giving Li Yan
schizophrenia medication all along.
And then she
put the pills in an epilepsy medicine bottle.
Right.
If we follow this line of thinking
and collect new evidence and witness statements,
the case should be solved soon.
So when did the revenge plan start?
Since you and your mother moved to a new place,
wasn't it to start over?
Start over
Li Xiulan
You never told us before
that your daughter Li Yan
suffers from severe schizophrenia
So what?
I supervise her taking her medication every day
She has improved a lot
Does she know that herself?
She forgot
She forgot everything
Slow down, slow down
We’ll rent a bigger house
That way, Yan Yan
will have her own room
This place is pretty good
The light bulb is broken
We’ll replace it later
There’s a dining table over there
I’ll go take a look
If it works, we can save some money
Mom
Besides being alive
eating
drinking
and sleeping
what else can I do?
What did you say?
Nothing
Let’s take another year to recover
Get your health back, then make some adjustments
If you want to practice piano
I’ll take you to the music store after work
I’ve already talked to the owner there
and got a good price
Yanyan
Mom
Go to the market.
Tidy up your things first.
I don't want her to remember these experiences.
As long as she doesn't remember,
her world will stay simple
and beautiful.
Isn't that right?
I'm at the market five days a week.
I have to get up at three in the morning.
Other people run their stalls as couples.
They can take turns resting.
But I'm all by myself.
Some people suggest I only work the morning market
or hire someone for the evening market.
But I can't do that.
Yanyan is very considerate.
After she got better,
she told me
she wanted to make things easier for me.
She found a job at the cultural center.
The pay isn't much,
but we
we're finally living a normal life.
So do you think Li Yan herself
sees life the same way?
Captain Qin, you're here.
Are you feeling better?
Officer Qin
If my mom didn't kill anyone,
would she still be charged with something else?
Yes.
Li Yan, I know this is very hard for you.
What I'm about to discuss with you
might make you uncomfortable.
If you feel any discomfort
you can tell us at any time.
We'll stop right away, okay?
Please try to remember carefully.
When you met Lin Nian's father at the youth center,
that is, before Lin Yi,
are you sure you hadn't seen this person before?
I'm Nian Nian's father.
You and your mother, Li Xiulan,
came here eight years ago.
Is that right?
Then can you briefly describe to us
what it was like
after you came here?
I'm going to the market.
Pack up your things.
Don't go outside.
She often locked me in.
She wouldn't let me go out.
She thought she was protecting me.
But...
I was so scared.
In my mind,
I would remember
those painful memories from the psychiatric hospital.
Mom.
No, Mom.
Why do I...
Mom, I want to go home.
Mom.
Mom, don't leave me here, Mom.
I don't want to, Mom.
Mom.
I don't want to be here, Mom.
I want to go back.
Take me back.
Mom.
Li Xiulan.
If I die here,
you'll pay with your life, you lunatic.
Mom, Mom.
Relax.
Don't move.
You'll feel better after the injection.
What do you remember about your past life?
I...
Mom...
Being together.
I can play the piano.
Going to school.
It was very happy.
And then?
I was disobedient.
I was sent here.
It's not because you were disobedient.
You came here because you were ill.
What's your name?
Li Yan.
Li Xiulan told me to take medicine.
She wants to kill me.
How is that possible?
Owe today
Yanyan
Older sister
Fifty cents
Etc.
Xiao Jun got rich, also
Five hundred yuan
Would you like to be friends with me?