Help me take off my gloves.
Captain Qin.
Captain Qin, here are the gloves.
How did the car end up here?
They probably didn't see the warning sign.
That warning sign fell into the sea.
It might have been blown away by strong winds.
But we can't rule out the possibility of sabotage.
Let's go in and take a look.
Slow down.
Sun Mou, put on the shoe covers.
What's the current assessment from the traffic police?
We took the evidence back and compared it.
The current assessment is that it's a single-vehicle accident.
Sync the car owner's information as soon as possible.
Send the body to the funeral home for preservation first.
Contact the forensic doctor for an alcohol test.
Sun Mou.
Go check the victim's social connections.
You didn't go out for socializing?
You're already home at this hour.
Why did you come back?
Didn't I tell you to go out and lay low?
Why should I hide?
Who am I supposed to hide from?
I think the one who should be hiding is you.
Manman called me today.
Half a year ago, you transferred money to Zhang Xiaochuan.
Two million.
What was that money for?
Since I invested in Zhang Xiaochuan's repair shop,
that kind of transaction is normal.
Why are you checking my accounts?
My dear husband,
this wasn't a business-to-business transfer.
This money was sent by you
to Zhang Xiaochuan's personal account.
There are some things I just can't figure out.
Since you invested in Zhang Xiaochuan's auto repair shop,
why did you have to transfer so much money privately?
Is there something going on between you two
that I don't know about?
Now he's suddenly dead.
I don't know what the police would think
if they found out about this.
Please come and confirm.
This is the birthday gift I gave my son.
Please calm down, Ms. Bai.
Hold on, hold on, Ms. Bai.
Ms. Bai, Ms. Bai.
It's all my fault.
It's all because of me.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have ended up like this.
He wouldn't have ended up like this.
Please calm down.
He argued with me a couple of days ago.
He said he didn't want to live anymore.
I even scolded him.
I told him he wasn't a real man.
I pushed him too hard.
Calm down. I pushed him too hard.
Calm down. I should have understood him.
Calm down.
I should have understood him.
Okay, okay, okay.
Boss, give me a fish.
What kind of fish do you want?
How big?
Let your mom pick one for me.
I want a big one.
Yanyan.
You don't remember me?
Watch the stall, I'm going out.
Yanyan, Yanyan.
Who is that?
What did your mom go do with her?
I don't know either.
I think she's a friend of my mom's.
A friend?
My son is gone.
What?
Bai Tao committed suicide.
Did he come to see you?
What did you say to him?
It has nothing to do with me.
I didn't say it had anything to do with you.
It's my fault.
I pushed him too hard.
If he hadn't come here, he wouldn't have died.
I've already taken him back.
I'll hold a funeral for him in a couple of days.
My condolences.
You keep it.
What are you doing?
Mom.
Did Bai Tao come to the market before he died?
He only came to see you once.
Yes.
Who is that woman?
I heard you talking about the person who died.
Who are you talking about?
Bai Tao.
Help me peel the potatoes.
Bai Fan was our former neighbor.
Bai Tao was her son.
We weren't very close.
Just neighbors, that's all.
Mom.
I don't remember any of this.
If you don't remember, then you don't remember.
Back then,
you were still little.
He wasn't anyone important anyway.
Did Bai Tao ever come to see you?
He was a troublemaker.
I'm just worried.
When he lost control, he could do anything.
I've never met him.
Mom.
Will Bai Fan come to see you again?
She lost her son.
She's heartbroken and can't get over it.
Just like if I lost you,
I wouldn't want to live anymore.
Mom.
How long has it been since we went back to Shigang?
Almost ten years, I think.
Why isn't sister coming back with us?
She doesn't know anyone there.
Why choose this place?
Who knows.
Is that girl Xiao Tao's friend?
Which one?
I haven't seen her before.
Her mother is probably Bai Fan's friend.
My condolences.
Bai Fan.
The child is in your care.
Is this the result we have now?
Are you still going to argue with me today?
Today, here,
we gather with heavy hearts
to mourn Mr. Bai Tao.
He has left us forever.
Please observe a moment of silence.
The moment of silence is over.
Will the family please come up to give a thank-you speech.
Thank you, everyone.
for attending my son's farewell ceremony.
I see Officer Qin, who is in charge of the case,
is also here.
Thank you.
You must all be wondering
why I chose this cold storage plant
to hold this farewell ceremony.
Because here
is where Bai Tao's father used to work.
It was also here that I met him.
We had the fruit of our love.
My greatest gift,
my son, Bai Tao.
Things remain, but people have changed.
I have lost in this world
my only family.
Actually, when Bai Tao was alive,
he didn't achieve much.
But he respected his teachers,
was filial to his parents,
and was always willing to help others.
I'm proud to have had a son like him.
But I wasn't a good mother.
Before my son took his own life, he sent me a message.
He told me about how hard life was for him.
But at that time, I blamed him.
I said he was useless.
I said he was incompetent.
I think at that moment,
he must have needed my support the most.
But I didn't help him.
I didn't give him any help at all.
I'm not a qualified mother, I'm not.
I know
that I am the one
who was the last straw that broke him.
It was me who killed him.
Bai Fan.
Don't do anything rash.
You crazy woman.
Calm down.
I thought you wouldn't come.
I had to come see him one last time.
From now on,
no one will disturb
the life that Yan Yan and I have anymore.
I hope this is
the last time I see you as well.
Thank you.
Yan Yan.
If we don't leave now, we'll miss the bus.
Mrs. Bai, my condolences.
Thank you, Teacher Yang.
I'm here on behalf of the school to see Bai Tao off for the last time.
Five, six, seven, go.
Five little monkeys jumping on the bed.
One fell off and bumped his head.
Mama called the doctor.
The doctor said,
Four little monkeys jumping on the bed.
One fell off and bumped his head.
Class is over, you can go.
Nian Nian, Nian Nian.
Come here.
Teacher Li just noticed
that you didn't make a sound when singing.
Can you tell me why?
I'm afraid I won't sing well.
How could that be?
Your pitch is the best.
Shall we try it together?
Okay.
Come on.
Do.
Can you hear it?
How was school today?
All she does is play games.
Mr. Lin (Nian Nian's father).
Teacher Li.
There's something I need to talk to you about.
Go ahead.
It seems that Nian Nian's hearing has declined.
Her hearing has declined?
I'm not quite sure what you mean.
I suggest you take her to the hospital for a checkup.
If there's a problem, it's better to find out early and deal with it early.
Okay.
I'll take her to the hospital for a checkup tomorrow.
Thank you for letting me know.
We'll be going now.
There's something important. Come to the theater.
Li Meng.
Li Meng! Li Meng!
I let you run.
Go away.
Leave.
Is it good?
It's you.
I wrote this.
I want the kids to perform it at the showcase.
What do you think?
The kids will perform this at the showcase.
Is it watchable?
Did I scare you?
I just wanted to test the performance effect.
Why is my name on this?
And my mom's name too.
Are you reading it?
It's just the beginning.
This chapter is called—
The Death of Zhang Xiaochuan.
Don't go.
It's not over yet.
Don't you want to know who the killer is?
Li Xiulan.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Why are you nervous?
A made-up story
will never be more dramatic than real life.
The story isn't over yet.
And life goes on.
It can tell the past,
and also predict the future.
My dear sister.