You're awake.
Li Xiulan.
Is my son still alive?
Did you set this up with them?
Did you hide my son?
I'm asking you a question.
Where is my son?
He's dead.
Now we need to keep a close eye on Bai Fan's movements.
Captain Qin, Bai Fan is missing.
His phone is off.
We can't find him either.
Dafei, Xiao Zhang.
Notify the traffic department.
Check all the highways.
Yes.
Xiao Wang.
Notify patrol units in all areas.
Search along the routes.
Yes.
Dongzi.
Contact anyone you can at the municipal department immediately.
Ask them to assign someone to help retrieve
the road surveillance near Bai Fan's home.
Yes.
Xiao Qin, stay at home and be on standby.
Uncle Wang, where's my mom?
I've called her many times, but she didn't answer.
Let's talk inside, let's talk inside.
Alright.
Yanyan.
This isn't something I can explain in just a few words.
Go pack your things first.
Don't make it too complicated.
Just pack enough for a day or two.
I'll take you to find your mom.
The bamboo basket next to the TV.
The bamboo basket, the bamboo basket.
That's the one.
Hurry up!
Give it to me.
Quick, quick!
Go quickly!
Hurry!
Yanyan.
Sit in the back.
Uncle Wang
The police called me.
Don't answer.
Turn off your phone, Yanyan.
Uncle Wang
Did my mom kill someone?
You know, don't you?
Right?
Yanyan
There's some misunderstanding here.
Don't ask so many questions right now.
Come with me, your mom is waiting for you.
City surveillance shows
Bai Fan was likely kidnapped by Li Xiulan.
A detention warrant has been requested.
Everyone, move out immediately.
Split up and search.
Make sure within twenty-four hours
to find Li Xiulan and Bai Fan.
She hasn't set up her stall these past two days?
I didn't notice.
Thank you.
Is there any?
No.
Go upstairs.
Didn't get any information.
Let's go.
Do you have any water?
I'm thirsty.
You killed my son.
I killed you.
If you have the guts, kill me.
You think I won't?
If I could kill Bai Tao,
I can kill you too.
How could you bring yourself to do it?
You should ask your son that.
If I had known he would turn into a monster,
I should have killed him long ago.
Back then, I was the one who wronged you.
It was all my fault.
I've already paid the price.
Can you let me go now?
There's nothing inside either.
Nothing at the market either.
Nothing at home either.
The captain is here.
What's going on?
Captain Qin.
All the places Li Xiulan might have gone
we've already checked.
There are no leads.
Li Yan didn't come to work either.
We can't reach her by phone.
Any feedback from the transportation department?
No.
We haven't received any
information about Li Xiulan leaving the city.
But at the market,
we found out something.
Not sure if it's related to Li Xiulan.
The market.
Got it.
Get in the car, come with me.
You should go. Don't worry about what happens next.
If I don't take care of it, who will?
It's already come to this.
You're still drawing lines with me?
I've been with you for so many years.
I don't owe you anything.
Hurry up and go back.
If the police ask, just say
that I stole the car.
Xiulan.
I'm already involved in this.
I can't get out now.
And I've already said
that I did all this willingly.
Let me say it again.
My business is none of your concern.
Go.
Why are you being so stubborn?
I just can't get through to you.
I'm doing this for you and your daughter.
I really don't want anything to happen to you.
I don't need your kindness.
If something happens to me, it's no one's fault.
We're just using each other.
I've gotten what I needed from you.
I don't need you anymore.
Do you understand?
You cripple.
You think I actually like you?
Get lost.
The farther you are from me, the better.
Xiulan.
Are you okay?
Get out of here! Go away!
I said get out of here!
You cripple.
Don't let me see you again.
Xiulan.
Stop following me.
Xiulan
Everything is packed up.
Mom.
Why did you kill Bai Tao?
Aunt Lan.
For you and your precious daughter,
I got these videos.
It really took a lot of effort.
Now I’m asking you for
two hundred thousand. That’s not too much, right?
I don’t have that much money.
No money?
I heard that online these days,
a lot of people like these kinds of videos.
If I sell them,
I could make quite a bit, couldn’t I?
What are you doing?
Robbing me in broad daylight?
Li Xiulan.
I’ve given you enough respect.
I even call you Aunt Lan.
Why do you have to be so shameless?
Give it to me.
If you hurt me today,
My mom won’t let you off.
Pull me up.
Help me!
Give me the stuff.
Pull me up first.
I’m telling you, Li Xiulan,
these are only some of the videos.
If you don’t pull me up,
you can forget about getting the rest.
Pull me up.
Help me!
Some people
once their desires are satisfied
become a bottomless pit
unless they die
otherwise, it will never end
so I chose to let go
I won't let anyone hurt you
Silly girl
With mom here, there's nothing to fear
Mom has already made all the arrangements
Let's move somewhere else to live
Wherever mom is
that's where home is
Hello
The police have gone to the dock
Who are you
The number you have dialed is not in service