Begin Again
Episode 10
What a "perfect" timing.
She chose today to have dinner with us.
How am I supposed to face Ling Rui?
Today is just...
Just having a dinner.
It's kind of a job.
Qin Yujiang,
the ex-fiancee of Simon,
is a very important partner
for Deer Sing.
So today's dinner
is kind of important to me.
OK.
Sorry to bother you
to come have this dinner with me.
It's alright.
-Um...
You go first.
Shall we go inside?
That's what I was gonna say.
Let's go.
OK.
Sis Yujiang.
I've waited for you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thanks.
This is my husband, Ling Rui.
Hello, sis Yujiang.
You are indeed a good match.
Fangning, it's been a while since the last time
we took picture together.
Let's take a picture.
Sure.
OK.
-Come on in. This way.
-Alright.
Ling Rui looks good.
Fangning surely has a good taste.
Come on. Just take a seat.
Nice arrangement.
Here.
Sis Yujiang.
What's taking Simon so long?
Do I have to invite him?
Just kidding.
He'll be here in a minute.
How's it going?
Quite good.
Look, he just called.
Yujiang.
What do you want?
Why do you invite Fangning?
Simon,
we're all here.
We're waiting for you now. Hurry up.
Don't keep us waiting here.
Although I didn't give you a heads up,
you don't have to be so anxious.
Fangning and Ling Rui have arrived.
You're the last one. Hurry up.
He has become
more and more impatient now.
Sis Yujiang, I'm sorry,
but I have to ask
you and Simon are really fine?
Because I think that
it'll be more appropriate for us two to discuss about
the cooperation between
Deer Sing and Jiang Cheng.
I had a good talk with Yiyao.
Why would you think so?
Don't worry.
Our partnership will work.
You can sit here. I'll open the wine
and get it prepared.
Thanks.
What did she mean by that?
It's appropriate? It will work?
That sounds so weird.
It's not like they're back together.
Could it be
settling the old matters?
How is this? Do you guys like it?
Your helper has great cooking skills.
Come here anytime if you like.
You are late.
Uncle.
You need to drink for punishment.
Come sit down.
I'll tell you what.
Fangning is really fortunate
to meet someone like Ling Rui.
What took you so long?
Come on. Welcome you all,
especially Dr. Ling.
Uncle?
Fangning, you need to drive.
You can't drink.
-I'll drink for you.
-You can drive too.
I have night blindness.
You're night blind?
Yeah, exactly.
He's night blind.
Cheers.
Uncle.
Thank you for your hospitality.
-You're welcome.
-Thank you.
I remember the last time
the three of us got together
was when I was on a blind date.
If Fangning hadn't
cut me some slack that time,
I'm afraid I couldn't have got a chance
to be Yiyao's girlfriend.
Dr. Ling,
how did you two meet?
Fate.
When it's the right time,
you'll naturally meet the right person.
We have friends in common.
So what do you love about Fangning?
He likes me because I'm pretty, gorgeous,
noble, independent,
smart, and very rich.
Of course,
it'll take more than a meal time
to talk about all my good points.
Right?
I like her because
sometimes be reckless,
fearless,
unreasonable,
and occasionally
doesn't care about the consequences.
She is like a shooting star
who came into my unexceptional life.
After hearing your description of me
why do I feel like
I'm a giant octopus?
How lucky Fangning is.
Well, he's lucky, too.
Didn't you say you liked me
being reckless and unreasonable?
Why are you avoiding me?
I thought you said you're like an octopus.
I don't like octopus.
Fangning.
It's healthy to eat more greens.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I remember that Fangning
never liked to eat
all these vegetables.
She apparently changed her taste
after getting married.
Yiyao.
As her uncle,
I think you should review yourself.
I don't really like the wine today.
Well...
Any other wine?
Let's open another bottle.
Why are you avoiding me?
I'm not.
Yes, you are.
Look, look.
You are avoiding me right now.
I've had enough.
I'm done with playing reserved tonight.
Why are you avoiding me?
I got it.
It's because that night
we didn't make a deal.
So that's why you're avoiding me.
You're clear about that
I would love to make this work.
Let's change the topic, Fangning.
Ling Rui.
You're not cut out for coquetry, Lu Fangning.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Go to the bathroom?
Can you solve the problem then?
Yujiang.
What are you doing?
Can't you see?
Well, think again.
I don't want to think.
You tell me now.
You are always like this.
Whatever she asks you to do,
you'll try everything you could.
But you never paid even
the slightest attention to
what I asked you to do.
I used to think it was weird.
Now I know.
You're in love with someone
you can't love.
So it doesn't matter
who you get married with.
I just happened to show up,
and happened to be the perfect fit
to become your perfect wife.
You didn't need to pay any effort.
Yujiang.
Lu Yiyao.
Although you don't know me,
I know you very well.
Ever since we got engaged,
how many times we should dine together every week,
how many times you should send me flowers,
sent me gifts for our anniversary,
and drove me home,
on all these things
you've never made a mistake.
But she's the only reason that
you would ignore all the standards recklessly,
and call off the engagement
with a single text message.
If it wasn't for Lu Fangning,
would it be anyone else?
So you invited them here today
to tell her all the truth
or to threaten me?
Lu Yiyao,
you underestimated me.
I just wanted to see
how rattled you are.
You didn't let me down.
Ling Rui is indeed a great man.
I thought they were perfect for each other.
Well, that's disappointing for you, isn't it?
I'm not disappointed.
I just want her to be happy.
No.
What you want is
her happiness is brought by you.
I'm the one who made the mistake.
I don't want her involved.
OK.
Well, in that case,
I'm gonna give you a chance.
I've changed my mind, Lu Yiyao.
You can either make yourself
fall for me truly,
or I'm gonna tell her
the truth why you called off
your engagement ten years ago,
and the person that
you truly loved
deep down.
You're done?
When are we gonna try again?
Lu Fangning, I have to tell you...
Try it again.
Come, try the cake I made.
You can make a cake?
Thank you.
But you always seem to like
fruit flavor, right?
It's alright.
I've always wanted to try
some other flavors.
When I was a kid, I wanted something new,
so I said that I liked fruit cake.
From then on, there had been
only fruit cakes at my home.
No other choice.
Yummy.
Fangning.
Didn't you just tell me that
your stomach ached
and you wanted to go home?
Me?
My stomach hurts.
You just told me.
Yeah, it hurts.
It just came out of nowhere.
I'm so sorry, sis.
We should probably go first.
Simon.
Sorry, sis Yujiang.
Thank you for your hospitality today.
She's always like this.
We're gonna go home.
It's okay. I'll walk you out.
What a pity, all these foods.
-Are you all right?
-All right.
Come on.
You OK?
Watch the steps.
Drive carefully.
Thank you for the dinner.
Ms. Qin.
We may excuse ourselves.
Bye.
Ling Rui.
Thank you for today.
It's alright.
Fangning.
Uncle.
Well, I gotta go.
You two get some rest early.
Uncle.
Are you all right?
-I'm fine.
-Fangning.
Flies.
Are there flies in this season?
There's so much greenery here.
Of course there are flies.
Simon.
In short,
I hope you don't take that too personally.
I'm leaving.
You didn't drive here?
Let me drive you home.
Alright.
-Let's go.
-Fangning.
I have something to talk to you.
What is it?
I'll take a cab.
Uh...
Bye.
Be careful, uncle.
What's up?
Let me answer it first.
Hi.
Friday?
Reunion?
Will Mr. Yu be there?
If he'll be there,
then I'll go, too.
Bye.
So,
what did you want to tell me just now?
You look good today.
Thank you.
Nothing else?
Nope.
Well, I'm leaving then.
Drive carefully.
What did he mean?
He likes it this way?
Why is he still avoiding me?
Can we talk it through or not?
Avoiding me?
Dislike me?
That's impossible.
How could anyone dislike me?
Am I not pretty enough?
I am pretty indeed.
He can't dislike me.
I can't try it again.
What does he want then?
Are we gonna continue the contract or not?
Or should I get another man?
Ms. Lu, Ms. Qin from Jiang Cheng Group
insists on meeting with you.
She should be here any minute.
OK.
These prices are okay.
This one's too high.
All right,
I'll talk to them again
and try to keep the costs down.
Alright.
Give me a minute.
Hello.
She's going to meet Ms. Lu?
Okay, I got it.
Are you all right?
Director Lu.
I'm sorry.
Never mind.
What's the hurry?
What's going on?
You know all about it?
What did she say to you?
No matter what she said,
you can't believe it.
She was just
venting her anger.
I didn't expect that
she would tell me not
to prepare the contract.
Nothing else?
What else is there to say?
Alright.
I'm gonna go talk to her again
and try to make a difference.
No need.
I thought Qin Yujiang
was a reasonable businesswoman.
It turned out she's not.
I don't believe that
Infinity has to
rely on their
production line.
I've got people looking for
a backup manufacturer.
You can rest assured.
It's a little tricky.
But it's better than them disdaining Deer Sing,
and making a fool of you.
All right, I'm leaving then.
Yujiang.
What the hell do you want?
Lu Yiyao.
Not too much time for you.
Hope you can consider my offer.
Or the next time I go to Deer Sing,
perhaps it would be something else
that I would tell Lu Fangning,
other than calling off the deal.
Hello?
I've checked on the manufacturers
that we could find
in this city and nearby.
But the manufacturing process
is special,
all the materials should be consistent with
environmental standards,
and subject to strict quality control.
Every product, from material to finished product,
has to go through a rigorous operation of
over a hundred processes.
So a large portion of the manufacturers
find it difficult to finish
the manufacturing process
within the expected time.
Two of them
could barely do this,
but their prices
are 20% more expensive than Jiang Cheng's.
How about the factories further?
We've also consulted
the factories in Zhejiang and Jiangsu.
It's just the shipping
is going to bring up our costs.
In this case,
if we forced it into production,
Deer Sing's fund flow would become
very difficult to handle.
How about this?
Adjust the current design and technology.
But in that case,
Infinity's launch date
might have to be postponed.
I don't think it matters.
We haven't officially announced
when to launch the product.
But the news
has been spread all over the industry.
It's not a good time to postpone.
Well, here is the thing. At the beginning,
there will be some
cash flow pressure.
But by the time
the first batch hits the market,
it'll be better soon enough.
Ms. Lu,
in order to launch Infinity,
you've fought so long.
If we postpone now,
I'm afraid that the board of directors
would make a big deal out of this.
It's gonna ruin everything.
The risk of capital flow,
how do we solve that?
Ms. Lu has prepared
for two years
for Infinity project.
We can't just give up
because of
the potential risks.
Besides,
cash flow issues have happened
a few times before,
and Ms. Lu solved them successfully.
Not to mention the fact that we have director Lu here.
I think
there's nothing to worry about.
Director Lu.
Gao Erfan
just has so much faith in us.
Gao Erfan.
Yes.
I never liked
to invest all my money into my ideas.
It's not really my style.
About this matter,
I'll go discuss about it
with the Design Dept.
Let's leave it at that for now.
Director Lu.
You can contact with other manufacturers.
Back to your work now.
OK.
Wait for me.
What's the matter with you this time?
It's a little unusual.
Why did you decide to go to the reunion?
I haven't seen Mr. Yu for a long time.
Why can't I go?
I think if they see
you got yourself a rich wife,
what their faces will look like?
Peng Bo.
Okay, I won't say it.
I thought we have done discussion.
Why are you still at work?
I'm waiting for you, Ms. Lu.
For what?
This...
You finally decide to quit your job?
How is that possible?
I can get such good benefits,
highly paid,
and especially,
I've a charming boss like you.
I'm not going anywhere else.
Ms. Lu,
this is my
annual leave application.
Your plan to travel the world
hasn't changed at all.
You dare to ask for a leave
at such a busy period of time.
Only because you came back
every year,
or I would think that
you're running away.
Ms. Lu.
Call me again.
If you call me like that again,
I will not let you go.
That's disgusting.
Thanks, Ms. Lu.
Well, may you have a good weekend
with Dr. Ling.
I'm leaving.
Dr. Ling doesn't have a weekend.
Friday?
Reunion?
If Mr. Yu will be there,
then I'll go, too.
The weekend is coming.
Friday.
He used to wear those
corny clothes.
You don't even know why...
But he was still handsome.
Come on.
Don't I look good in it?
Does he look as good as me?
You're just jealous.
Who are you talking about?
Curly.
Curly Peng.
Don't call that, okay?
Either you call me Dr. Peng,
or just Curly.
Who's Curly Peng?
Look at yourself.
Has your curly hair ever changed?
I'm so jealous.
Don't get your hands on me.
Control yourself.
You've become bolder.
This must be Ling Rui.
We're supposed to call you
Dr. Ling now, right?
Hello.
Guys, Dr. Ling is here.
-Ling Rui.
-Dr. Ling.
Sit down.
Dr. Ling,
are you a physician
or a surgeon?
I'm a surgeon.
Surgeon.
Do you do heart operations?
Don't only have him in your eyes, okay?
Am I not handsome? Why don't look at me?
You? Forget it.
Ling Rui is more handsome.
Exactly.
Well, where's Mr. Yu?
Mr. Yu?
He hasn't arrived yet.
We're all classmates.
Yeah, let's get together sometime.
But if Mr. Yu knows that
Ling Ri is here,
he's gonna fly here.
He is slow, okay?
I'll give him a call.
We must get together sometime.
After all, we're classmates.
Hi, Mr. Yu.
But we're classmates and old friends.
Ladies.
Alright.
Look,
Mr. Yu got lost while driving.
I'm gonna go pick him up.
Why don't you come with me?
-I'll go, too.
-No.
Don't go.
You just go by yourself.
Leave Ling Rui with us.
Exactly.
Are you afraid that we're gonna eat him?
Hey, guys.
Ling Rui hasn't seen Mr. Yu for long.
He misses him so much.
How about this?
Let him pick up Mr. Yu.
And I'll chat with you.
I can talk too, right?
-No, no.
-I don't want that.
We haven't seen Ling Rui for a long time.
-We all miss him so much. Right?
-Exactly.
I'll take him away.
Curly, you...
So annoying.
Let's get out of here.
Or they are gonna eat you up.
What are you doing?
Take care of the boys.
Alright?
We want Ling Rui.
We are all classmates.
Why all the differences?
We just want Ling Rui.
You're not as handsome as he is.
Don't speak.
-Oh my.
-That can't be changed.
We're both so good-looking.
Why...
Mr. Yu, this way.
Mind your steps.
Ling Rui,
are you usually that busy?
All these years,
I haven't seen you at all.
You didn't say this
when you saw Ling Rui.
I mean, he just put on an act.
Who of each and every one of you here
doesn't know that?
We all know that
how he used to be like?
What's wrong with that?
He is handsome all the time, okay?
You women are so shallow.
What else could you care other than his pretty face?
His face is enough.
Listen to me,
Mr. Yu called on the entire class
to help poor students.
I donated him a big down-filled coat.
I just don't know if he still wears it or not.
Come on.
He is a surgeon
at a major hospital.
Why wear your cheap down jacket?
The other day,
I heard from the doctor at Ling Rui's hospital that
someone saw his wife
who looks very rich.
Her bag,
and her clothes...
How much salary can
Ling Rui get every month?
They don't even care about that
little amount of money.
You know?
See? What I was saying?
What did I tell you?
When I came in, he was like
"Hello."
I mean, who was he trying to fool?
I'll tell you what.
With a rich wife,
life is easy.
He just did the grand.
What's the big deal?
Who is this?
Who are you looking for?
Do you know her?
Excuse me.
For me, Lu Fangning,
Ling Rui is quite amazing.
Who are you?
I'm Ling Rui's wife,
Lu Fangning.
If you don't know,
you can Baidu my name.
Thanks.
He brought his wife...
Fangning.
...to the reunion?
This wine
is so terrible.
After all, this is a reunion.
How could you drink such terrible wine
with your teacher?
I'll have my assistant
get two bottles of fine wine
from my personal winehouse
to celebrate with you all.
I was just wondering
why you had to invite Ling Rui.
It turns out you want him to pay for this.
What do you mean?
How could she say like that?
Forget it, Fangning.
You're Lu Fangning.
She's Lu Fangning,
who is very rich.
This lady,
please mind your behavior
and don't mess with our
reunion party.
What?
Who is exactly rude? Can't you see that?
You're all here for reunion.
Some people are just speaking ill of others.
Is that good manners?
Is it?
By the way,
you're the classmate
who gave clothes to Ling Rui, right?
It occurred to me that
I meant to throw away
that coat for so many times,
but Ling Rui refused.
I can see that it really means a lot
to Ling Rui.
But I've changed my mind.
When we get back today,
I'm gonna take that coat
and make it a pad for Doudou.
By the way,
Doudou is our dog.
What do you mean?
What do you mean, Ling Rui?
You got a rich wife, that's fine.
But now you're having your wife
humiliate your old classmates?
I'm not humiliating you all.
I'm only humiliating
the two of you.
But you know what,
in your whole life,
it'll be considered as an honor
to be humiliated by me.
Just so you know,
it's not easy to be depended on by Ling Rui.
I was gonna give him tens of millions
He refused it and called me shallow.
Now it took me so much effort
to get him depend on me.
Even if he's gonna make this place a mess,
I'm gonna let him do it.
What can you say about that?
A mess, huh?
Just do it!
What are you doing?
What?
It's all right, teacher.
Ling Rui's got this.
But I don't wanna make it a mess.
Let's go.
Are you all right?
I'm angry.
Mr. Yu, I'm sorry.
Ling Rui.
Don't beat her!
Mr. Yu, don't worry. He won't do that.
What are you all doing?
Huh?
Ling Rui.
Why did you drag me out?
I'm not done talking.
They just taunted you like that.
How could we let them
finish this meal?
That kind of snobs
need to be defeated by our strength.
Why are you so angry?
Because...
Because those people
are a bunch of losers,
they're nasty,
and nobody would tolerate them.
Okay, even though I know
I'm still impressive even I don't
wear high heels,
but my biggest regret today is that
I didn't wear my
11-centimeter heels here.
Or else when I saw
that stinky man just now,
I could do like this.
And I could look at him this way.
What are you laughing at?
What's so funny?
At times like this,
should I just kiss him?
Someone else is around.
Well, that's fine.
Should I kiss him?
Do it.
I'm not mad.
So,
don't be mad.
I...
You're not mad?
Then why did you just
do that
and like that?
Because they're right.
When I was in school,
my family was really poor,
and we took a lot of help from others.
Well, they couldn't say that about you anyway.
These things
are part of my life.
I'm not trying to hide it.
As for
what they said about you,
that's true too.
You're really awesome.
I don't have your good temper.
He has such a good temper,
so he should be done
being mad at me about last time, right?
It was different last time.
Why does he know what I'm thinking?
That's annoying.
Fangning.
What's up?
Can I just
ask you a favor?
Is he a freak?
Cut it out.
He looks funny.
Let's go.
Go?
You back to your house,
and me back to my place?
What's up?
I'm feeling sorta uncomfortable.
Every time I have my period,
I don't feel so good.
I need someone to take care of me.
Well, I'll send you back to your house.
What's the point of going back there?
You're not there either.
Besides, who would take care of
me at that place?
I want to go back to the apartment.
Alright, I'll send you back.
Take a seat.
You know, because of the whole marriage thing,
I've been a little busy,
so I haven't cleaned up this place.
It's not always like this.
You know me.
I go get you some hot water.
Just a minute.
It hurts.
Fangning.
Where's your hot-water bag?
Why would I have hot-water bag?
What do you do when your hurts?
I never...
I just endure it.
I just want to go to my room
and clean up a little bit.
Oh, it hurts.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
One really can't lie.
Why it hurts all of a sudden?
This really hurts like hell.
Come in.
Fangning.
I got you some hot water.
You'll sleep better after drink this.
Thank you.
Careful, it's hot.
Aren't I supposed to
drink brown sugar water?
Drinking brown sugar water or hot water
doesn't have difference in
helping with your symptoms.
Hold this over your belly.
Thank you.
It hurts so much.
Have more hot water?
I don't want any water.
I want you.
Then go to sleep.
Sleep?
Well, I mean
you sleep on your own.
Alright.
Yeah, of course.
I mean, I'm like this, right?
I have to sleep alone.
Where are you going?
I'm like this.
Can't you just
stay with me?
Stay, please.
It hurts.
Much better.
Put your feet up.
Don't get cold.
You know what,
I do feel better this way.