Begin Again
Episode 08
Colds
are contagious.
The effect's so strong?
What is that soup?
Whatever, come on.
-No.
-Why are you hesitating?
-What are you doing?
-Come down.
We have to
talk about it tonight.
Why are you tying me up again?
I don't feel comfortable like this.
Ling Rui.
So,
you married me
just to legally get...
my...
Alright.
I completely understand
why you, Lu Fangning,
would do this.
It's just... Why me?
Why not you?
You're handsome and well-educated.
You have good personality.
Of course it's you.
Besides, you still owe me money.
You have to pay your debt.
It's perfectly fair.
Don't worry.
After I have a baby,
I'm not gonna stick to you.
Our marriage
will, as we agreed on the contract,
automatically end in one year.
Of course,
I get the baby when it's born.
But you're still the father.
You can see the kid whenever you want.
I would never stop you.
However,
if one day
you have a new relationship,
I'm not gonna let the baby
call that woman mother.
So,
you never had any intention
to keep the father of the child?
I'm perfectly capable of handling
the risks and responsibilities
when raising a baby.
Besides,
I have a stable financial income
to give the kid the best possible life,
education,
and all my care and love,
to help him grow up.
Why
does he need to have a father?
It's not a question of necessity.
Then what's the problem?
Ling Rui.
You've got to open your mind.
Think of it as
helping a lovely girl
who wants a baby
but can't have one by herself.
I can't do this alone.
I can't do mitosis.
Of course I need your help.
Ling Rui.
Look at me.
With a girl as attractive as me,
someone else would be attracted a long time ago.
Someone else?
So if it's not me,
you would find someone else
to carry out your plan?
Can't I?
You can't!
Two mature adults
raising a child together
would meet a lot of problems.
Not to mention the fact that
you're childish and ridiculous.
Childish?
I thought of your feelings
and your ego,
so I stayed in there
for such a long time,
and you call that childish?
Immature?
How do you know I'm immature?
Have you ever seen
before you say that?
Anyway, I'm not going to
have a baby with you.
A baby should be a gift
to two adults who are in love.
We're not.
How do you know we're not?
I love you.
I like you.
No.
It's not up to you.
You're just saying no to anything.
Why are you such a pain in the ass?
Anyway, I'm not gonna
have a baby with you.
And neither will you
with someone else.
I'm going home for a few days.
Ling Rui.
-Don't come to me.
-Ling Rui.
Ling Rui!
One more.
How about I feed it into your mouth?
Have you ever stopped eating?
Ling Rui.
At such late hours, why you're back?
I have something to do.
What is it?
Why are you home so late?
Where is your coat?
My coat...
I left it at the hospital today.
I had surgeries all day.
I'm too tired.
I'm gonna go get some sleep.
Did you
have a fight with Lu Fangning?
Fight?
How could I possibly fight with her, mom?
Not like that.
I'm going to bed. Good night.
Well, off you go.
Are you hungry?
No, I'm fine.
What happened to Ling Rui?
Came back to mother's house
in the middle of the night.
What are you talking about?
How could you
say that?
He's a man.
Can't he just come home?
She's not wrong.
You're his mother.
Sister.
Why don't you go back to sleep? It's late.
Alright, go to sleep then.
Don't you want to sleep? Still eating?
Go to sleep.
No.
You...
Wait a minute.
Hurry up.
Why are you in such a hurry?
I'm just using the toilet.
Keep your voice down.
Look.
Ling Rui has been
cleaning it since this morning,
from this side to that side
and back and forth
for such a long time.
Isn't it normal
for him to clean the table?
Cut the crap.
Is that normal?
When was
the last time he was like this?
Last time?
When was the last time?
No such thing happened before.
No.
Yazhi, go ask him.
Go ahead.
Ling Rui.
Did you have a fight with Fangning?
Give back my money.
I'll leave you to it then.
See? I told you I can't.
Why sent me to ask him?
Sister, why don't you go?
Me?
He has always listened to you since he was a kid.
He'll do whatever you told him.
You're his mother, let's go together.
Let's go. Yazhi.
Ling Rui.
Today is weekend.
Why don't you stay with your wife at home
but come here?
Son, will you stop doing that?
You have been doing this
from here to there
and the other way around.
You didn't take any rest.
Good boy, come here. Take a break.
Take a break,
okay?
Be good.
Hi.
Mom and aunties,
here comes your daughter-in-law.
What are you doing here?
Here.
Help me get the stuff inside.
Fangning is here.
Hi.
What's going on here?
I'm going to visit
a friend of mine who lives nearby.
Her little baby
is one year old.
These are all the things
that I plan to give her.
You still have friends
who live in places like this?
Of course.
All right, you take a seat.
I go get you some fruits.
Mom, please sit.
Hold on, hold on.
Sit here.
What is this?
This is socks for
the little babies to wear.
With their little feet inside,
it's so cute.
It's so soft and tender.
Mom, look.
What's this for?
It's supposed to be for babies
to put their heads on.
With their little heads on top of it,
it's so nice to think of this view.
This one's so soft, too. Mom.
Feel it.
You opened the things
that you're going to give others.
How are you supposed to give it away?
No problem.
I'll just put it in later.
When I think about that
little babies' little arms,
little feet
like that little lotus roots,
soft and tender.
Thinking they kick their little legs
and stretch their arms,
I feel it melts my heart.
Do you like kids?
Of course, mom.
In the future,
when you have your own
grandchildren,
I'm sure you'd love them.
Take a look.
Ling Rui.
Mom.
Do you remember your card-playing friend?
Which one?
Rarely talks, but plays fast,
and always lets you win.
Ever since she got a grandson,
you haven't seen her anymore.
Didn't you tell me that
she cried and told you
after having a grandson,
she was surrounded with diapers and milk bottles,
and had to take care of the baby all night?
So,
you think it's going to be
troublesome for you to have a baby?
It's a real pain in the ass.
I don't think
I'm gonna take care of your kids.
Is that right, sister?
Yeah, we won't.
Mom, I haven't...
Didn't you just say that...
Mom, I...
You know what? Never mind.
Please ask Ling Rui about this.
What's going on?
What the hell is going on?
What's up with all that?
Fangning.
Sit over there.
Move over and let me sit down.
Fanning.
Try this tea.
Thank you, auntie.
When I went out
last time for inspiration,
I watched the old farmer cook this.
Auntie.
I've been preparing for pregnancy,
so I can't drink tea.
Look.
A lot of people think that
career-minded women like us
don't have time
to take care of the kids.
But it was a misunderstanding.
Look at me.
I've fully prepared
to welcome
the baby.
Because motherhood is strong.
Our children are our backbones.
Isn't that right?
Auntie.
I'll drink it.
I apologize on behalf of Fangning.
She definitely didn't mean that
a woman without children is weak,
and her life is imperfect.
That's not what I was saying.
I know.
I won't take it personally.
Actually,
it's nice to have a kid.
But people like me
who choose not to have children
and live on their own
are also living in
a good lifestyle.
Yes, of course.
Oh, Fangning.
Your language skills
are pretty bad.
"Motherhood is strong."
That's not how it's supposed to be used.
Auntie Yazhi.
I'm here.
Come, sit.
Auntie,
haven't you been
trying to find a job
and sending out resumes online?
Resumes?
Go ahead, that matters more.
Au... Auntie?
I'll send out resumes.
Oh, I forgot to tell you that
auntie Yazhi divorced,
and her ex-husband got the baby.
Be careful
with your words.
It's tasty.
Mom.
Come on in, kid.
Come on in.
Close the door.
Come on, come on.
Let me ask you something.
Sit, sit.
Out there, you just said
you want kids
and then you said you don't.
What exactly were you thinking?
I don't actually
want a child
very, very much.
Besides, mom, you don't
want it that bad either, do you?
I didn't say that...
Of course I do.
You just said that
you don't want to raise the kid.
No.
I was sitting next to Ling Rui,
so I had to say that.
Or else he would
feel embarrassed.
Mom.
You might not
gonna be able to have a grandson for a while.
What do you mean by that?
Since Ling Rui and I got married...
Never mind, it's okay.
What's going on? What do you mean?
Since you are married, then what?
We're not like a couple.
Not like a couple?
It's exactly like what you're thinking.
There's nothing wrong with my son.
Nothing wrong?
No problem.
Who knows.
A little orange peel.
That's enough.
-Oatmeal.
-Oatmeal won't do.
Don't move, don't talk.
Plus wolfberry, black sesame, and green beans.
What is
Ling Rui thinking?
How am I supposed to know what he's thinking.
Perhaps he doesn't love Fangning.
What are you talking about?
How could he not
love a girl like Fangning?
All right, stop talking.
It's already a mess.
Just figure out a way to fix this.
Alright.
Why are you still here?
Why should I leave?
I'll be right where you are.
Where else would I go?
Listen to me,
whatever you're planning
is not gonna work.
What are you talking about?
What could I possibly have planned?
Of course I should stay
with my husband.
Right?
Mom, Ling Rui doesn't want to drink it.
Come on, Ling Rui, drink up.
Drink up.
Drink.
OK.
Mom, Ling Rui still refuses to drink it.
What's wrong with you, Ling Rui?
Just drink it.
You don't listen to mom now?
Go wash the cup.
Okay.
He drank up.
Come here.
I'll take shower first.
OK.
Come here, come here.
Come here.
Later,
he's in the shower now,
you should just sneak in.
-Shall I do that?
-Don't let him hear you.
I'll lock the door.
No one can see you.
Keep your voice down. Don't talk
Mom, no.
Stop talking.
Forget it, forget it.
Be good.
Just get in there.
She's shy, you know?
Excuse me.
Go, go, let's go.
I won't be back for a few days.
No way.
My families are gonna be suspicious.
I've talked to Dad...
I've explained to uncle Lu that
I got something to do at home.
I'll stay a few more days.
All right.
No matter what,
I'll stay with you.
OK.
You can stay here.
Sleep on the floor.
No.
Mom wants us to sleep together.
Also,
don't you forget that according to the contract,
in the rest of the year,
you have to fulfill every requirements
as my husband.
Then I suggest that
you should carefully read
the fifth item in section six
in the contract.
What?
The contract clearly states that
if you, party A,
coerce me, Party B,
to do anything unethical,
or illegal,
I would have the right to break the contract
without any legal responsibility.
Oh, I need to add one more.
All the rights and duties
stated in the contract
have to be done
without violating the law.
I, Lu Fangning, am the general manager
of Deer Sing Group.
Why would I do anything illegal with you?
I'll add this anyway.
Very good.
Well, since you've
made up your mind like this,
I'll find someone else
to cooperate with me.
Bye.
Lu Fangning.
Marital infidelity
will be considered as your fault.
Your money,
your house,
and your favorite Deer Sing,
are all gonna be half mine.
You sleep on the floor.
Comfortable.
Leader,
do you think it's going to affect
director Lu's brain waves
and let him adopt your plan
if you keep staring at this?
I really don't want to work overtime anymore.
I'm the one who's working overtime, not you.
Look how well I did.
If he doesn't like this,
it certainly won't be
because of my ability.
It would be...
You know, the perfect couple
sometimes starts as enemies.
Siyu.
Again.
It's quite good, isn't it?
Left Patronus.
Assistant He, what can I do for you?
Director Lu demands
all of us in the Planning Dept
to gather at the exhibition center immediately.
Make sure you bring all the plans.
In our plan,
we have three days to set up.
But right now,
something came up at the last minute.
No construction this weekend.
So we're gonna have to
get everything set up
within today.
But soon we'll be off work.
I don't want to...
Working overtime again?
Overtime again?
If you don't want this to happen,
you should have taken the emergency
into consideration
when making the plan.
Do you want the company
to pay for the failure of the plan?
The layout of the exhibition must be finished today.
Is there any problem with this?
-No problem.
Speak up.
Once again.
No problem.
All right.
Let's get busy, everyone.
The earlier you get this done,
the longer you can sleep
after going back home.
And if you all slow down,
you might straightly start the next day's work.
Let's get started.
He's so determined and does all the things first.
He's getting more attractive.
Staying here is better.
I dare not even breathe
with director Lu around.
Director Lu is handsome.
Moreover, wearing a suit,
he is extremely charming.
Working overtime with him
heals my eyes.
But Lu Yiyao is too scary.
People don't dare to speak with him around.
What woman could stand him?
You can.
Come on, you can.
-You can.
-You.
I think you might be more efficient
if you just shut up.
Mi.
What's going on with
the labels on these bottles?
Anything wrong with that?
Don't you see?
The words are all blurry.
Look at this.
This is the last
batch of scrap labels, right?
It's supposed to be new.
As long as the information is right.
We'll put new ones on later.
I mean, we've done with all these.
We can't just
do it all over again.
Besides, it's too late.
No one will notice.
But if these...
I have a stomachache suddenly...
I'll go with her to the toilet.
-It hurts so much.
-What do you want to drink, Siyu?
I'll get you one.
You guys are going to the toilet
or to buy drinks?
Who is it?
Must be him.
At times like this,
the leading character would definitely come to help.
Why are you doing all alone?
I...
This is the division of labor chart.
All personnel must follow it.
Do not leave your position, understand?
Also?
Also,
don't ignore the details
just because the time is running up.
Do everything perfectly.
Did you guys all hear me?
Cai Siyu, why you did that?
We didn't say we weren't gonna do it.
Exactly, what's the point of snitching?
I didn't.
Assistant He.
Do check in the way
like putting the price tags on
every time when a job is done.
If we have a similar problem,
keep me posted.
OK.
What did you check?
All right, go ahead.
What did I check?
Let's go.
He not only helped me,
but also avenged for me,
and tried to keep me out of trouble.
What kind of perfect leading character is this?
I screwed you the first three times.
I am so sorry.
But without those three accidents,
how could we get to where we are today?
Come and get something to eat.
Here, take that away for a second.
Come on, come on.
The red ones are beef burgers
with beef and onions.
And this one is chicken burger
with fried chicken and tomatoes.
Siyu, which one do you want?
Can I have both?
I know I can't.
Then I'll have the chicken burger.
-Here you are.
-Thanks.
Director.
We have beef burger and chicken burger,
which one do you want?
Beef burger.
Alright.
Hi, this one, no onions, thanks.
OK.
What?
I finally got a chance?
That's enough.
Give them more.
I thought you didn't eat beef.
Here, chicken burger.
No?
Have a little more.
A little more.
Director Lu.
What's the matter?
Thank you.
For what?
You know, because of the price tag matter,
you've reassigned jobs.
I was trying to improve
work efficiency.
What's up?
You thought it had something to do with you?
Is it on?
Are we getting into the
enemy scene again?
So unimaginative.
Enjoy your meal here.
Cai Siyu.
I didn't know
how you convinced Ms. Lu
to let you get into Deer Sing.
But I hope
that you're capable enough
to do your job,
or I'm going to ask you to leave.
See?
That's usually how it goes.
You won't be willing to let me go later.
Save me in time of danger.
What an old plot.
Bu it's so good.
Are you OK?
This is for you, director Lu.
No onions.
Ms. Lu.
What are you doing?
Why do you call me here to check on
the exhibition at such late hour?
Director Lu.
Fangning.
Look.
All the arrangements
are done already.
We can open in two days on time.
Let's take a look over here.
Let's go. Mr. Li, come to have a look.
This couch was designed by
Infinity's designer Gavin.
It's also the main presentation
of our exhibition then.
In the interview part,
we'll have the designer up here
and take the interview.
I think it's all good here.
Why don't we look at somewhere else?
Wait a minute.
I think there's something wrong with
the couch's position.
What do you think, Simon?
Maybe it's the light.
I'll tell you what.
Mr. Li.
Why don't you go up there and try?
It's more intuitive.
It's all good.
Don't make a big deal out of it.
Making furniture
is all about precision in details.
Besides, this couch really matches
a successful man like Mr. Li more.
Have a try.
Please.
Mr. Li, don't be so nervous.
You've seen everything.
This couch really matches
you perfectly.
Turn a little bit to the left.
Simon, do you think it's better
to turn right?
Let's turn right.
Maybe it's the light.
Look how pale
Mr. Li's face is.
Mr. Li, sit down, don't worry.
Director Lu,
even though we don't have much time left,
but we still have to do our best
to make it perfect.
Yeah, time is limited.
Otherwise,
we can do better than this.
The plan was made in advance.
Why did the exhibition hall
suddenly change their mind?
What do you think
about this, director Lu?
People
are easy to be manipulated.
Ms. Lu, are we done here?
With this light,
my eyes are turnining blurry.
That's all right, Mr. Li, thank you.
What's wrong with this, Lu Fangning?
Right.
What's wrong with this, Simon?
Sorry, Mr. Li.
I forgot to tell you that
this light right here
almost hit
our own staff.
I've checked on it.
Someone did this on purpose.
On purpose?
Thank God Mr. Li sat here in advance,
or it might hit somebody else.
And that's gonna be bad.
Lu Fangning.
Would you like me to call an ambulance?
No need.
Call it when I'm dead.
Let's go.
How absurd.
Ms. Lu, I'll go check over there.
Go ahead.
When this light is fixed,
we're almost done here.
The rest of the place has been checked.
No signs of tampering.
Don't worry
about the exhibition.
You've done a lot, Simon.
It's alright.
What? In a bad mood?
Why do you say that suddenly?
I saw you come here
with a long face.
You didn't even argue with him and just directly went to the point.
Had a fight with Ling Rui?
No, we're fine.
Fangning.
If you have anything bothering you,
remember that you still have me.
If anyone bullies you,
I can beat him up for you.
If you just want to
let it all out,
I could do boxing with you.
In short,
don't keep it all to yourself.
It always takes
some experience to grow up.
You told me this.
If I tell you,
you might just
beat the crap out of me.
Hold on, I'm gonna borrow someone from you.
Simon, bye.
Let's go.
What does she want from me?
And with this vibe...
Is it too early for
the break up scene?
How's your work recently?
It goes well.
What can I do for you, Ms. Lu?
Have you
ever been in love?
I...
Yes, I think.
That's good.