Begin Again
Episode 13
The proposal that you just gave me
is not like what you said.
Have a look at it.
Okay, I'll check it.
I'll give it to you in a while.
Okay, give it to me later.
I'm sorry.
These flowers...
Director Lu threw
these flowers away last time.
I bumped into you accidentally last time.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter.
Director, we have good news.
We've found a replacement factory.
The equipment specifications of the production line,
quality data,
price, and location are all very suitable.
Who negotiated this factory?
Manager Wang from the production dept.
Is there a problem?
Let's talk about it in my office.
He's so cute.
My heart, oh my.
A boy crazy.
I like the feeling of
dining with my family.
I'm willing to cook for them.
This is the President of Shanghai Cuisine
Professional Association,
Expert of Jiangnan Food Culture
Communication Centre,
Honorary President of the
Yangtze River Delta Famous Chefs Association,
Chairman of the World Chinese Cuisine Association,
Master Guo, known as the King of Jiangsu and Zhejiang Cuisine.
May I ask Ms. Lu,
what kind of dishes would you like to learn today?
As long as you can say it,
there is nothing I can't cook.
Stir-fried vegetables.
Isn't it a bit too perfect?
Add more.
Smart.
Sadfishing is not my style.
You're back.
I'm back.
Change your shoes, here.
I'll do it by myself.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'll help you.
Thank you.
How was everything going in the hospital today?
How was your work going?
Were you busy? Tired?
Quite well.
That's good then.
I'll go wash my hands first.
Well, the vegetables you like,
fish,
Mapo tofu,
this is the soup I made.
I cooked all these in person.
These...
Did you really cook all these?
Of course,
I've learned from the chef
for several hours.
The chef also praised me,
as expected, a smart person
can do everything well.
He said that I had
a little talent in cooking.
Have a try.
If you think they're good,
I'll cook for you frequently in the future.
Let me get you some soup.
Thank you.
Try it.
Taste it.
Is it good?
Is it a little salty?
You know it's my first time.
And,
the chef wasn't with me either.
Maybe I'm not quite sure about
the salt.
But I will
work hard to improve.
If you have time,
you can also teach me.
Fangning,
I said,
I don't want you to act like this.
What do you mean?
Didn't you say before
what you like most is the feeling
of dining with families?
That's why I tried hard
to cook so many dishes.
I want you to feel at home.
You
don't like it?
Like it?
Lu Fangning,
although we
started this lie together,
I really don't like to lie.
I more dislike your lies
one after another.
I'm not lying.
I'm showing you
my sincerity.
Really!
Because I love…
Okay.
If you don't like it,
I won't say anything.
Okay?
But I want you to know that,
Ling Rui,
no matter how you try to avoid,
you can't
resist my heart.
Why do you want to escape?
Are you sure you're sincere?
I saw the takeaway packages for
these dishes
in the trash can outside.
Don't tell me
someone else has ordered
the exactly same dishes
as these on the table.
But how can takeaway food
taste so salty?
In order to pretend that you've cooked all these by yourself,
you, as a very smart person,
deliberately sprinkled so much salt on them.
Lu Fangning,
like,
love,
sincerity,
can never be
said out loud in a casual way.
You can keep saying
them over and over again in a casual way,
because
for you,
lies can be easily done.
Whether cooking a meal this time,
or the auction last time,
you always think that
money can solve all problems.
But you never consider
other people's feelings.
You just want to achieve
your own purposes.
This may be your
way of doing things.
But please don't do it in
such a way
to disturb my heart,
my life.
Let's calm down.
I don't want to eat.
I don't consider your feelings?
You know what?
It is you who
don't consider other people's feelings,
trample on other people's heart casually.
Not me.
Ling Rui,
do you think
I lied about everything I said?
Then what should I do?
Like stories in the romance novels
and idol dramas,
there is truth in wine, right?
As if no matter what the person says,
as long as he is drunk,
people will believe what he has said.
It's okay.
You don't believe me, do you?
I'll show you today
when wine is in, truth is out.
Drinking will not solve the problem.
Lu Fangning,
give it to me.
Give me the wine.
Don't drink it!
Give it to me. Give it to me!
What are you doing?
Don't worry.
I can't get drunk.
Why?
Because, for social activities,
I drink some wine at home every day.
Hence, I can't get drunk.
If I can't get drunk
in my life,
will you never trust me
in your life?
I, Lu Fangning,
was not like this before.
If I did
something good in the past,
I would broadcast it
and let the whole world know that
I had done this thing.
If I cut
one of my fingers,
I would bandage
all the rest fingers
and show them to you.
But, what about now?
I worry about personal gains and losses every day.
I'm cautious.
All I can think about is
whether you will be happy or not,
whether you will be delighted.
What I have done is wrong?
You think that I
have disturbed your life.
Haven't you
disturbed mine?
Ling Rui,
if you don't like me,
you can reject me.
Reject me!
Why do you
repeatedly
deny my heart for you?
Deny my love for you?
Is it because it makes you look
particularly holy and great?
Lu Fangning.
Stop talking. Stop!
I hate you!
Ling Rui,
from now on,
I hate you.
Fangning.
Ms. Lu's parcel.
Okay, thank you.
I suggest you checking it in my presence.
Okay.
Then, please help me open the package.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I worry about personal gains and losses every day.
I'm cautious.
All I can think about is
whether you will be happy or not,
whether you will be delighted.
What I have done is wrong?
If I cut
one of my fingers,
I would bandage
all the rest fingers
and show them to you.
Let me help you?
No, no, no.
I'll do it. Leave me.
I'll do it by myself.
Stir-fry it.
It's burnt.
Let's try it again.
If Tang Ping hadn't showed up suddenly,
things wouldn't turn into this result.
Your wife has expended much care and thought on it.
She had three plans, ABC,
for she didn't wanna cause you any trouble.
See, I have some money.
I'm going to give you all my money.
I... I don't want it.
Fangning.
You really don't like me at all?
Okay, it's done.
Oh my, I'm hungry.
How about you?
Me too.
Come on,
Dr. Ling, Dr. Liu,
Dr. Peng,
Nurse Wang,
come here.
Thank you for your hard work.
Have some water.
Thank you.
Thank you for your
service to our plant.
Come on, drink some water.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Take a break first.
We'll continue at 1:30 in the afternoon.
Okay. Please have lunch
in our cafeteria now.
Don't underestimate
our cafeteria.
The chef
was specially invited by
the Jiang Cheng Group.
He's very good at Sichuan cuisine.
The factory of Jiang Cheng Group
is also here?
Yes.
The whole area belongs to Jiang Cheng Group.
Amend these again.
Okay.
You guys go back first.
Okay. Okay.
Dr. Ling,
what a coincidence.
Hello, Ms. Qin.
I happened to do volunteer medical consultation nearby.
It's not exactly a coincidence.
I want to talk to you.
Talk to me?
Is Dr. Ling here
to speak for Fangning this time?
I don't know the commercial intercourse between you two.
I'm not trying to persuade you.
But I want to do
something for her indeed.
And I happened
to meet you here.
Sometimes, I do
envy Lu Fangning.
She speaks the bold truth.
She lives freely.
Now,
she has a good husband like you.
No one can really understand
other people's lives.
Maybe,
she envies you, Ms. Qin.
She told you this?
I don't believe it
Maybe,
she likes you.
She likes me?
What does she like about me?
There are many
similarities between you.
During this period,
I don't know
myself very well.
What do I look like?
What do I really want?
Perhaps, it's not that you don't know yourself.
You just don't dare to face yourself.
Ms. Qin, do you know
fever
is actually a way for the body to
protect and repair itself.
It's the white blood cells that
fighting against viruses and bacteria.
When they win,
the symptoms will naturally be cured.
The immune system will also be strengthened.
So, instead of forcing the fever down,
leaving it alone
may be better.
No need to worry about it.
No need to be afraid of it either.
Human beings are very strong.
When you heal,
you will naturally become a better yourself.
What are you trying to say?
I want to say that
I hope Ms. Qin can
recover soon.
Consider it as heartfelt thanks.
For you don't make Fangning bear the
harm that caused to you in the past.
These are the factory's production line data that
you have submitted
and the results of our recheck.
Are they?
Is there any difference?
This number is different by 0.01.
The factory was definitely very careless.
They are too irresponsible.
I'll get even with them later.
Director,
in my opinion,
Manager Wang is still reluctant to tell the truth.
However,
I've recorded
what he just said.
As an evidence, it should be enough.
Bring the recording and these materials
to the lawyer.
Ask him to look into it.
Director Lu, Director Lu,
I'm wrong. I'm wrong.
Please forgive me this time,
just this time.
I'll go find a new factory right away.
About what you said,
you should have realized them
before you did these things.
Director, I don't want it happen either.
This tiny difference
can be negligible.
Otherwise,
I'll return all the money that
I've received before.
I can even return the money to the company.
Really, director Lu,
I did know I'm wrong.
I promise,
I promise to be loyal to the company,
to work like a horse from now on.
It seems that your problem
is more serious than I thought.
What?
Although we
found out that data was wrong,
we don't have any direct evidence
to prove that you took bribes.
Now, since you've admitted it by yourself,
we can only leave the rest
to the lawyer and the police.
Lu Yiyao,
you played tricks with me.
We didn't expect that
you would show your hand so easily.
Take him out.
Lu Yiyao.
Go.
Lu Yiyao, you're away too far!
Lu Yiyao,
Lu Yiyao, you'll be sorry!
The terms of cooperation are better than before.
After all,
it's my problem this time.
I refuse.
With such preferential prices,
it's very difficult for you to find other suppliers.
I will find one.
How about the quality assurance?
You have to think it carefully.
In such a short period of time,
it's hard for you to find this kind of manufacturing technology,
and a partner with inexpensive prices.
There is always a solution.
I certainly believe in Jiang Cheng.
But, sis Yujiang,
you're the one who broke the rules of the game.
You broke the contract an re-signed it at will.
Deer Sing Group
doesn't need such an emotional partner, who
can't make a clear distinction between public and private interests.
Ten years ago,
Simon made a mistake.
But ten years later,
it was you that used the wrong method.
I've adjusted the product design
of the main series of Infinity.
I don't need Jiang Cheng anymore.
And I won't be threatened by anyone.
I'm sorry.
It's really my problem this time.
I hope that
we can still have the opportunity to work with Deer Sing again.
This is a new manufacturer.
I know the owner.
He's not bad.
This information should be useful to you.
This
accords with your
game rules, right?
Okay.
I accept it.
However,
please don't tell Lu Yiyao that
I provide this line.
You
really do not want to give it a try?
My uncle is single.
You're single too.
No.
He has a place in his heart where
I neither sit in nor ignore.
So, for the health and harmony of
the rest of my life,
forget it.
Does he have a girlfriend abroad?
In this world,
there is only one person who
can make him cry,
make him laugh.
But, this is his secret.
I'm not qualified to tell anyone.
Well,
it's pity.
I'm quite satisfied
with you, as my aunt.
You can help me make money.
I'm leaving.
You should say thanks to Ling Rui.
Ling Rui?
He did the volunteer medical consultation in our factory area.
He specifically came to see me.
He wanted to do something for you.
You must have had a miserable life
in your previous existence.
God compensates you
a Ling Rui in this life.
I'm leaving.
Don't you want to talk with me?
It's a nice day today.
Let's go.
Okay.
When I passed by here,
I thought of our dates before.
Besides having dinners, watching movies,
and listening to the music concerts,
we didn't seem to do
anything else.
Can you remember
what else we did before?
It seems nothing else.
Right?
That's why I'm very unreconciled.
I can't
get rid of it.
Lu Yiyao, you
didn't even know that
I like you so much?
I want to hear the truth.
In the past,
in my opinion, you just thought
we were perfect for each other.
But now...
Probably, you just hate me.
As expected.
I'm sorry.
Actually, you know what?
As long as you say something,
do something,
I'll be fine.
I'll forgive you.
Forget it.
I hate myself
to be like this.
I've come to this point.
But, I still can't
express my feelings frankly.
I can only pretend to blame you, which
is easier for me to blame myself.
It's okay.
You can continue to blame me.
Forget it.
I'll forget you.
Yujiang.
Lu Yiyao,
just stand here,
I'm leaving.
Simon.
There is only one person in this world who
can make him cry,
make him laugh.
Since her sister died,
Fangning has locked herself inside
for several days.
She didn't eat.
She didn't cry or make a scene.
She's going to have problems.
My sister gave me this candy.
She wanted my future life
to be sweet.
But, I can't see her anymore.
Aunt Gao,
what are you doing?
Where's uncle?
I don't know what happened.
He suddenly said he was leaving.
He packed his baggage simply,
and left.
He also said that he would call off the engagement.
Fangning.
You're back.
I put the contact information of a new manufacturer
on your desk.
This manufacturer was recommended by someone else?
An acquaintance recommended it.
You can contact them.
And carry the work forward as soon as possible.
I have something to do. I'm leaving.
Wait a minute.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm fine. I'm leaving now.
Look, he's calling now.
Why did you invite Fangning?
In my memory, the three of us
gathered together last time.
It should be at the time when I
had a blind date.
If Fangning hadn't
let me off the hook at that time,
I'm afraid I wouldn't have had the chance
to be Yiyao's girlfriend.
Yiyao,
as her uncle,
you should make a self-criticism.
Do you have other wine?
Open another bottle.
Fangning,
since the production line's problems
have been solved,
should we find time to celebrate it?
No.
I'm quite busy these days.
How about next week?
Let's talk about it next week.
Cai Siyu.
Director Lu.
Let's dine together after work.
Cai Siyu.
Ms. Lu,
when did you and Simon
become so familiar that
you can dine together?
That's right.
When?
Hasn't the story already ended?
I hope I've overthought everything.
Could it be that as long as I have a secret crush on someone,
a director will be sent to me?
I don't have to do anything.
And director Lu just came to me?
What are you thinking about?
What did you say?
Came to you?
Do you buy a lottery ticket?
I…
Do nothing.
Someone can come to me?
You really want to do this?
We're here now.
No more crap.
He cut off your factory's leeway.
He got us into trouble with the lawsuit.
He, Lu Yiyao,
didn't give us any leeway.
What are we afraid of?
Here comes him.
Get ready to go!
What are you doing?
Beat him!
Beat him hard!
Security!
They're here! Come here!
Let's go.
Director Lu, are you okay?
I'm sorry. I'm late.
You were shouting loudly.
It was an emergency.
You...
Next time, you run first
and then call someone, understand?
There's no next time.
How about you?
Shall we call the police or go to the hospital first?
No need to call the police.
I'll handle it by myself.
Then, how about your wound?
Thank you.
I'll do it.
No need. Let me help you.
Another classic scene,
I've made it.
I'm sorry. It hurts?
I'll do it gently.
It seems that you are laughing?
No, I'm not.
You're my boss.
You're injured.
I'm worried about you a lot.
Of course,
I still have some other thoughts.
Director Lu,
I want to know
what you think of me?
Why?
Why did you suddenly invite me to dinner?
Nothing.
I think you are too tired because you work overtime.
I'd like to express my sincere solicitude.
It's okay. I'll do it by myself.
What's wrong?
Okay, it's late.
You should hurry back home.
Director Lu,
do you really have nothing to tell me?
I don't want to talk it to you today.
Maybe another day.
You have the chance now.
I'm leaving.
Director Lu,
it's okay if you don't say anything.
I'll do it.
I knew it.
A relationship without effort
will not be so easy to succeed.
It is written in the novels.
Director Lu,
I like you.
Can you be my boyfriend?
You don't have to answer me now.
I'll go back first.
Shouldn't he stop me?
Why doesn't he stop me?
Come on!
Okay!