That's amazing
Don't be lazy, practice dancing
Yu, if it is not for you,
I can't
even do this,
learn these
And it is at this critical moment,
you borrowed me 4 million yuan.
I will learn to dance with every effort
If it is not you who
took your repeatedly trial and fail,
and repeatedly fail and trial as an example
to inspire me,
I would
have gave up already
the dream of dancing,
Only 4 million yuan. It's worth it
We two families
are going to meet
What if in the future. Wait a second,
Meet?
If my father knows,
we met each other here,
he will absolutely break my legs
We, do not make ourselves
scary for now
By then,
I don't know who you are
I will be the one,
a beautiful lady who got divorced
Then
Then I don't know you either,
I will be the one,
the black swan with broken wings
This is good
Leg, continue
tiptoe,
knees,
downwards of shoulder blades
Today, it is presumptuous of me
to invite Mrs. Ling and your family
to come to our home
I know this invitation might be
not appropriate for our
traditional Chinese etiquette
The event of marriage,
not child's play
But the two young men,
they are really busy
I think good things should not suffer much,
so,
if anything I am not being thoughtful,
please excuse me.
Yes,
it is truly of a bit hurry,
But I think
but as long as they can
live together
happy and satisfied,
we
will be relieved
Mrs. Ling, thank you for saying so,
I am also relieved
I have
heard from Fangning
about Mr. Ling's status
in a brief way
So today,
in such an occasion,
I would like to hear from Ling himself
personally
and officially introduce himself
to me and Auntie Yang
Tell us something about yourself
Mr. Lu, I am... Dad!
Dad, I don't think this is necessary,
I have already
told you several times,
age, job and native place
And all his family
is sitting here, isn't it?
What else do you want to know?
Mr. Lu,
actually
I have been a major in medicine
I am now in the city public hospital,
as an surgeon
Maybe you don't know much about me,
so
you worry about that,
however,
I will assure you and Mrs. Lu,
and you can be relieved that
in our marriage
I will do whatever I can
to be good to her
Good, good, good, OK,
OK
Now Ling Rui
is an associate chief physician
After so many years,
we have actively been working hard to
pursue advanced studies in Germany
In the future,
when he come back from Germany,
I think
he will be really awesome
By the way
If in the future, you
do not feel well,
you can go to Ling Rui in his hospital
Right, Mrs. Yang
Aren't you not hearing well?
You can ask Ling Rui for help
I will have a baby with Ling Rui in the future,
it will also save a lot of trouble
Associate chief physicians
How much is your salary per month?
Every month with bonus
approximately
fifteen thousand yuan
This is far too less,
Aunt Gao in my home
is about the same number
That's not the same,
the value is not the same
That's true
Our Ling Rui is also a volunteer
He is very kind and warmhearted
Social contribution is not the same
This is cooked by
Mom!
Aunt Gao
Your favorite
Have some more, the dishes got cold
Right, right!
Fangyu is right
Just kept talking,
you see, the dishes almost got cold
Come on.
Let us toast
to welcome Mrs. Ling and her family
to come to our home
Welcome. Welcome, come on
Welcome
Cheers
This time, it is of hurry,
I am not being a good host
Next time, shall we
find a good restaurant?
Yeah, that's good
Let's have a tea time
for the date of wedding
let's make some plans
That's great
But you are being so kind
We have a big family
No problem
We have a lot of rooms
Just come
Lu Fangning
Why it is you?
Or what, you?
Doctor Ling,
Why are you suddenly going to
marry Lu Fangning?
Do you owe her money?
You must owe money to Lu Fangning
Lu Fangning
So despicable of you
You actually do that for the money
You forced Doctor Ling go with you
You see that,
we love each other for real
Lu Fangning
What are you doing?
Refining the make-up
You, what are you doing? Don't move
Help you
Clean up
Doctor Ling,
Dr. Ling
Good job
You deserve to be the straight A student
It feels so good just now
You did well
It feels like that I have already graduated from elementary school,
and went straight up to the college
Next how about
keep up further studies?
What? What do you mean?
I mean
the pace of the development,
I am very satisfied.
Drive carefully
First of all,
based on the principle of equality and mutual beneficial,
and after friendly negotiation, both sides
agreed to voluntary marriage
Of course in this marriage,
we shall not intervene each other's freedom
If irreconcilable contradiction comes up,
a negotiable divorce can be achieved
Secondly, if necessary,
you have to fulfil
all obligations of a husband
It is because my identity
is special
Sometimes you may have to
be the husband of Lu Fangning,
to cooperate with me
Just like today
If we are close to
get caught by somebody else,
we will have to make some moves
Such intimate behavior
Definitely
If you feel that
you lose,
we can add one thing,
I can be your wife
and cooperate with you to
finish all your shows
What about the third rule?
This is all based on my
personal kindness,
I will protect your
privacy
Your personal information,
your photos
will not be published on any
social media
Of course if one day,
it is necessary to go public
about or relationship,
I will cover your photos
with mosaics
before posting
The next rule
is not that important
Just have an idea about that
It is mainly about us,
the division of our properties after marriage
If one day
in our marriage,
we generated some common achievements,
party B have to give up with no conditions,
that is to say
yours are yours,
mines are mine
Those look like ours,
are still mine
What do you mean by look like ours?
Legal terms
have a lot of such
plausible expressions
It is not important.
You see the rest are some
standard issues
Sign please
Plausible words on the contract,
they are meaningless,
just delete
By the way
I'd like to add one thing,
in the contract,
the mentioned privileges and obligations,
have to be implemented
in accordance with the laws
I am the General Manager of the Deersing Group,
Lu Fangning
shall I do illegal things with you?
It has to be added
Let me tell you,
bed number 52,
this patient,
is condition is quite special
You should remember to
observe him more,
OK
measure the temperature at any time
Understand?
Observe his conditions
Mr. Lu,
Are you here to see me? Yes
Doctor Ling, you can stick to your work,
I will go to my office
OK
Mr. Lu,
What are you here for
today?
Nothing
Just check up on you
Did I disturb you?
Of course not
Are you worrying
Fangning and me?
Actually, Fangning
is not a
very talented one
She made the achievements as of today
is totally due to
her tough mind
You think she is beautiful,
but not that beautiful,
a little bit not feeling like a woman
Actually there are no rules to define
what is a woman like
or a man like
So what is Fangning like?
She is the one I admire
Sometimes,
she may be a bit
arbitrary,
self-willed,
unreasonable,
or kind of
independent and different
But if everyone in the world
can understand her,
your daughter,
how mediocre could she be?
Ling Rui
I know why she
is fond of you
About the marriage,
have you two truly determined?
Mr. Lu,
About the marriage,
I can't promise much,
but at this moment,
I am willing to marry Fangning,
and stick to all the marriage related
promises
Ling Rui, tell me,
did she had
something on you?
So you have to marry her?
It's all right, you can tell me
I will make it up for you
How about this
Later
I will get you some shares
as some sort of defence
Getting married is a really troublesome thing
Actually there is supposed to be one more
step
Wedding
Forget it
Wearing
a heavy wedding dress
standing on the stage like a doll
most of the guests
unfamiliar
It's no more than a big party
It's just so awkward
I don't like that
So you don't need a wedding
Of course if you need,
it's not quite impossible
It's up to you
OK
Then just cancel it. Happy cooperation
Happy cooperation
Guys
Before we begin
the vote
for Infinity,
I have something
to let you know
I have formally invited
the founder
of Nowegian brand Kasa
and their design director Garvin
as our
design consultant
and at the same time
to provide
the material support that Infinity needs
I have concluded the business
at the best price
Now
let's vote for the project
of Infinity
Deersing Group
The vote begins
All is here
Hello everyone
Hello! Mr. Lu
Long time no see
Indeed
Don't stand up
Just sit
I will
I heard from
Fangning yesterday that
today we
are going to reach an important decision
I'm curious about it
So I just came over
Hope that I'm not bothering you
I'll just listen
Fangning
Have you told your ideas
to everyone?
Yes
OK?
Has the vote started?
It just started
Who voted?
Tang
Did you vote yes?
How about Liu
we...
Zheng! OK I'll vote immediately
I'll vote immediately
Ma
What's your opinion?
I...
Why Lu Wenbin came over at this moment
this vote
Really annoying
What does this have to do with him?
It's
very serious
It concerns
the development of the company
so
All I can say is
just vote
as you are supposed to
All right?
Go on
The vote continues
Director Yang, look
It doesn't matter
even Lu Webin is here
Good for nothing
Ning
It's not that we don't support you
You see
It's a democratic vote
Mr. Lu also joined in
How about
we put it off
Director Yang is right
Just put it off
Right? Put it off
Put it off Okay That's good
Wait
Sorry guys
I'm late
Late for a meeting?
I vote
yes for Infinity's
brand project
Director Xiao
You are new here
You don't know very well about the company
I've known
very enough
And I look forward very much to see
how would a household brand
created by Miss Lu
would be like
You will not be disappointed
What the hell
Mr. Lu
Miss Xiao wasn't here just now
Let's re-vote
The vote begins
OK
I announce that
the Infinity brand project
Approved
Thank you!
I'm still very curious
Why Miss Xiao
changed his mind all of a sudden
You are not allowed to run around like that
anymore
Dear Xin
Why are you crying?
He just fell down while running
Fell down?
The knees hurt?
No
That's good
Dear Xin
You can't run around
in the hospital
You know that?
The patients
need quietness
It's not so good
to disturb them
You have become a man now
A man never
cries because of small matters
You know that?
If you want to play outside,
I'll play with you
when you get better
Really? Yes
Doctor Ling,
You are
a colleague of Miss Lu's
It's really surprising that someone like her
would have you as her friend
A person like her
knows nothing about life
but devoted herself totally to inventing
living stuff for others
But you are different
So warm, so optimistic
You both seems belonging
to two different world
Maybe we are different from each other
however,
But everyone has the right
to live his life
as he wants right?
I respect her understand her
And
we are getting married
Marry
Congratulations!
It seems that
I have to prepare
the wedding present
I never knew that
he was you fiance
But he really made some point
Maybe I shouldn't
tag you too soon
Congratulations!
Happy Marriage!
Thank you!
I don't care whether you are truly getting married
or not
But from now on,
your life is no longer
of your own business
Whatever
Anyway
Thanks for your support
Congratulations
Finally it passed
The board have decided that
we should invite Garvin for a visit instantly
to affirm the designs
And
Push the contract with
the material suppliers
and the production line
These materials are unusual
Very few domestic manufacturers
can produce such kind of materials
Gao Erfan, you...Miss Lu
I'm afraid that besides this
there is another
more urgent thing
to be solved at first
I heard from
The wedding this weekend
Wedding
Who are robbing my money from my pocket?
Your...
My...
Your... What?
After the meeting,
all of the directors have received
from Mr. Lu
the invitation to
your wedding
The wedding invitation cards are well prepared
This weekend
Who is going to have a wedding
I'd like to see him
Wait for a moment, Miss Lu
Miss Lu, Just think about it
on this particular occasion
We'd better follow
Mr. Lu's mind
After all it's a hard-won success
Besides,
Getting married is a happy thing
We should tell everybody
It'll bring good luck
to every one
Telling everybody?
True
Such a time-wasting
and vigor-consuming thing
Since we did it,
it must be worth our while
OK
Infinity has just founded
and the inner conflict is also solved
It's time
to invite our business friend
to offer some support
That's it
Invite all of our business partners
to the wedding
Turn it
into a propaganda
for Infinity
Well that
is your call, Miss Lu
As for the invitation cards,
our product brochure would be enough
One for each
Stress on the procedure of the wedding
the rest does not matter
however,
Make sure enough time is left
for speaking out our slogan
Infinity
To give you unlimited love
in limited time
Pressed on the first page of the cards
Awesome! Miss Lu
It is what they called a century wedding
My rent my meal
my boyfriend
and the gossip headlines
of this month
all count on you
I want a south-facing room
It'll be three hundred higher than this one
I'm not demanding about the food
Take-out is ok
Sea urchin gunkan-maki
Durian Pizza and Harakomesi
Moreover I wish that I could
met someone
maturing mysterious powerful as my boy friend
Was that too much?
Just let me reach the target
of this month
Give me a big news!
Lu Fangning
The daughter of Deersing Group,
general manager Lu Fangning
held a big wedding
at Coli Hotel
It'll be the most splendid
wedding in this city this year
The bride Lu Fangning were wearing
simple
white hand-made wedding suit
and lace veil
plain but decent
The groom wearing a bow-tie
was dressed with a black suit
with logo L
They walked in the banquet hall side by side
This press release
consists of nothing
besides flattery
for myself
There is no mention
of any Infinity's
brand features
let alone
the listing time
Is that I didn't make the job clear
or you are not qualified for this
Miss Lu
After all it's your wedding,
the emphasis...
The emphasis is to make
a stunning stage pose for Infinity
Do it again
The wedding is beginning in a minute
I will check it
as soon as you've done
And it must be issued immediately after the wedding
Any problem?
No
Ling Rui
Never heard of this guy
So lucky
to marry Lu Fangning
He must be of some capabilities
to marry her
I'm wondering
what kind of capability that would be
to overwhelm her
Yes
My son-in-law
should be great
Think about it
Only an extraordinary person
can take fancy to my daughter
How smart I am
to choose such
a suitable dress
How comfortable it is
Wen, go get some rest
Hard work, thank you
Let's go
OK
My daughter-in-law Mom
Fangning, elder aunt,
younger aunt. The bride is so beautiful
Come on! Have a sit
You are gorgeous today
My daughter-in-law
I know you don't need money
But mom have prepared a red pocket
for you
Wish you happiness
for all the life
Mom!
one-three-one-four is
my favorite number
We are supposed
to become a family
Fangning. Come here
Congratulations
this looks
too valuable. Just accept it
Thanks aunt
Open it
Like it?
This
represents the deepest wishes for you
from us
Yes, I felt it
Ardent
Then tell me
What do you feel?
It's getting married
not a thesis defense
Fangning
My present
is sent to your mobile
Congratulations
Check it when you get home
Really mysterious
Don't look at it now
Ling Rui will know
tonight
Let's go
Don't disturb the bride
Mom, aunts
Then I won't be accompanying you
Go to Gao Erfan if anything is needed
I've arranged
Ok, go
Alright
Enjoy yourself
So beautiful. Let's go
My daughter-in-law
We gotta go
Bravo
I am happy today
I'll go for Miss Lu
What do you want?
Get out of my way
You can't go
Keep off
Get out
Lu Fangning
Tang Pingping
You are really bold
OK?
I don't want you
to marry him
Don't tried to drag Ling Rui into the water
I warn you
Don't get crazy here
Your dad is here
So what?
Gao Erfan
Miss Tang, this way
Sorry
Who are you? Get off me! No
Get off me! No
What do you have to do with Lu Fangning?
It's none of your business
I don't know her. It doesn't matter
An evildoer is not entitled to have a wedding
It's justice to stop it
Madwoman
Get off me
What do you want?
My dress
Tang Pingping
Your dress
is not of good quality
You?
It's much better
It's more like a
bridesmaid
Lu Fangning
I'm here. I'm here
What's up?
How about this?
Later
you get on the staging wish a best marriage
for Ling Rui and I
as a bridemaid
OK?
Impossible!
I'm gonna tell everyone
that you forced him to marry you
Shut up!
Tang Pingping
Have you lost your mind?
I...
Fangning
Sorry
You see a badwoman
Sorry to bring you the trouble
That's okay, Uncle Tang
If she cannot
control herself,
I think it's better
not to let her out
What do you think?
You?
Don't worry
I will keep a close eye on her
Don't disgrace me here
I'm off
Sorry
Dad
Look what you did
Too shameful
We can't stay here
Go, Go
Go
Sorry
We will just see!
Bye, Be careful! Go! Go!
What's the matter, dad?
Come over
Go. Dad
Who are you?
Cai Siyu
I'm asking about your job
A passer-by
Reporter?
I'm not...Miss Lu! Gao Erfan
Give her a reporting admission
We haven't invited
any press
There is no reporting admission
Then make one
Invite Miss Cai
as our
only designated reporter
Yes
Thanks, Miss Lu
But all of your interview
must be examined
by GM Assistant Gao
Any problem?
No problem
Thanks
Bye bye
Your boss is so cool
Ling Rui
Tonight you are mine
Miss Lu
Are your legs and feet flexible enough?
What do you mean?
I'm afraid that
you will step on my dress
we will both fell down
Don't worry
I'll not let you fall down
OK
I can hear you! Just say
My face?
No need for ps
You thought I were Tang Ping?
I don't need beauty
I need Infinity
Focus on Infinity
Ling Rui
Hold it for me
just one minute
It's alright
All the press release
must involve
the logo of Infinity,
closely printed
The logos are necessary
even using watermarks
Got it?
OK
Gao Erfan. Listen to me carefully
Find someone
to push these news
to all of the social networks
Hear that?
Headline
Focus on Infinity
Got it?
It really hurts!
What's the matter?
I sprained my ankle
while toasting
And
Do not reveal any information
about the groom
Cover the faces with masaic
while toasting
Come on! Let me help you
Open it
Post-marriage Happiness Direction Article One
Getting familiar and closer
What's the matter?
I can't move
Can you
carry me there?
Which foot?
This
Whatever
Is such a minor thing
really worth asking?
I can't see it's swollen
Here, here
Sit, I'll get the ice bag
OK
That's it
Here?
A long day
I'm exhausted