(Episode 81)
This is all the evidence we need.
Let's go straight
to the chairman's office.
Hold on. Let me see that.
And what are you going to do with it?
If you didn't steal it,
you'd have no reason not to show me.
I guess it was stolen, then.
- Watch your mouth.
- That's why I'm asking to see it.
I'm not going to take it from you.
What's the big deal?
Is it going to cost you money
or take any effort?
If it were me, I'd just show you
and get it over with.
Hand it over
while I'm still asking nicely.
- I'm afraid I can't do that.
- You might get hurt.
It'll be pretty humiliating
when I take it from you by force.
Go ahead. Try me if you're confident.
But just by looking, it's pretty obvious
we're in different weight classes, right?
You're a lightweight.
And I'm a middleweight.
What did you just say?
How dare you call me a lightweight?
Why you little...
Bring it on!
Hey!
Where did they get this?
- Stay still.
- How dare you manipulate sales and steal?
And you expect to be called the CEO?
This could get you kicked out of Mingang.
I said, stay put!
You think this will destroy the evidence?
Just you wait.
I'll make sure the chairman, the board...
No, every single employee...
will know exactly what you've done.
Give it to me!
Hey, let go of this! Get off me!
- I said, you're not getting up!
- Get off me!
I told you to stay down, you hear me?
Hey, I said let go!
Why you...
What do you all think you're doing?
What a mess.
What is the meaning of this?
Have you no respect?
Is she your friend?
You wouldn't even treat a friend
this horribly.
Forget treating her like your stepmother.
You should at least show some courtesy.
Are you okay?
- Are you hurt?
- I'd rather be the one who gets hurt.
I just couldn't stand by and watch them
burn our brand-new products.
What are you talking about?
Who would do that to our new products?
Are you going to tell him? Or should I?
What are you waiting for?
The chairman is waiting.
Gosh, what is this?
It's not going to hurt us one bit.
You clearly don't know how things work.
Even if he is the chairman,
firing and hiring a CEO...
is not something he can do on his own.
The board isn't a pushover.
Really? If it's not going to hurt you,
then why did you try so hard to stop us?
From what I saw, you were fighting
like your life depended on it.
That's because...
it does no good to make a scene.
My point is,
if you hadn't faked sales with bulk buys
and siphoned off products,
there wouldn't be a problem, would there?
So you're determined to
blow this out of proportion?
Over something so trivial?
"Trivial?"
You call
putting the CEO position at risk trivial?
If things had gone wrong,
someone could have died.
Died?
What on earth are you talking about now?
Are you really asking
because you don't know?
Because of what you did.
You know what? Never mind.
The truth will come out
one way or another.
And we all know how this will end for you.
So let me get this straight.
You're saying she used bulk buys
to steal inventory?
She hid it in the warehouse,
and you caught her.
I caught them just as they were about to
burn the products to destroy the evidence.
Is everything she's saying true?
That you faked sales, boosted performance,
and used a troll farm?
And that you tried to burn new products
we haven't even sold yet?
I could forgive the rest,
but does it make any sense for someone...
in the distribution business to destroy
a brand-new product with their own hands?
It's not like that, Father.
I would never do something like that.
It's all a misunderstanding.
Why would I?
Who do you think you're lying to?
Is the chairman your friend?
Why are you doing this to me?
I beat you fair and square.
Are you just being a sore loser?
What did you say?
Aren't you going to tell the truth?
Don't fall for it, Father.
You think I can't see what you're doing?
You're just framing me because you lost.
You have to turn my father against me,
so you can take
the CEO position officially!
Then call in Director Moon Tae Kyung
and ask him yourself.
He's seen the fake sales records,
the doctored shipping labels,
and the warehouse where the new products
were sent. He's confirmed everything.
As you can see here,
large quantities were bought with one ID,
and we can confirm they were all shipped
to the address in question.
- And where was that?
- A warehouse.
Our livestream products
were stacked up in there,
and according to the workers there,
they were ordered
to incinerate everything.
By Ms. Min Kyung Chae
and Lawyer Kim Sun Jae themselves.
If you'd like, I can bring them in
to confirm their story.
No, that's not true, Chairman!
I mean, Father.
He's lying too.
The two of them are in on this together.
Why are you all doing this to me?
Do you really think the chairman
is going to fall for your act?
You little...
Who's the one who's lying here?
Are you really going to lie
to your own father to the very end?
I told you it's not true.
Why would I do that to you, Father?
Please believe me.
I swear, I didn't do any of it.
Are you really going to deny it
to the end?
Do you want to see the chairman
collapse again?
So, what happened?
You should have denied it to the end.
I did.
I insisted,
whether they believed me or not.
Good.
Now the chairman can't rush to judgment.
I know Father better than anyone.
He might let the other things slide,
but he'll never forgive me
for trying to burn new products.
So what do we do now?
This isn't going to blow up
in our faces, is it?
I don't know, okay?
The nerve of that brat.
A distributor treating products like that?
The buyer list, the troll farm they used,
the malicious comments about our products,
and even the sabotage of our sales.
I can provide proof for all of it.
- If you want, I can do it right now.
- That's enough. I've heard all I need to.
She inflated sales, bought her own stock,
and even tried to burn the products.
What more is there to say?
If word of this gets out,
our partners will be in a tough spot too.
So we should just bury it?
This is no small matter.
Let's keep this internal for now
and start by correcting the sales records.
We could get hit with a hefty fine
for reporting false revenue,
so let's contact the relevant department
and have them fix the data.
I can't believe what she's stooped to.
Seriously, how did Kyung Chae
get so messed up?
So on the livestream, your sister won big,
and your stepmom completely bombed.
She never should have gone up
against Kyung Chae.
She's no match.
That's because you don't know
the whole story.
Mom just had a bad day on the broadcast.
It's not like she's worse than Kyung Chae.
Why? What happened on the broadcast?
My mom is allergic to seafood, like me,
and she just had to pick that one.
Manager Gong, you know, right?
Mom went to the hospital that day.
That may be true,
but Madam Jung brought it on herself.
- No one else picked it for her.
- Exactly.
She picked it with her own two hands
in front of everyone.
Luck is a skill.
Nobody said it wasn't.
She won't let me get a word in edgewise.
Why is she so eager to defend her?
Her own daughter wouldn't even
defend her like that.
Ms. Se Ri, if you keep this up,
I'm done covering for you.
What are you talking about? What did I do?
Even Ms. Ja Kyung says so.
No matter what anyone says,
Ms. Kyung Chae is the rightful CEO.
Who said she isn't?
Please don't be like that.
Ms. Kyung Chae
is working so hard right now.
She got on the chairman's bad side
because of that last incident,
and she's working hard to make up for it.
Kyung Chae's been the CEO for a long time.
That's all the more reason for her
to aim for the chairman's seat.
No matter how much you like your mother,
you should be on your sister's side.
Blood is thicker than water,
and you should stay loyal.
- I don't care either way!
- But you should.
Chairman Min is being tougher
than I expected.
Then again, rather than being sent
to a nursing home,
letting Mingang be ruined would be
even more unacceptable to him.
After all, he's a man who values
his company more than his own life.
But he can't force Min Kyung Chae
out by himself.
The board will push back,
especially since they've always pushed
for family management.
- Then Min Kyung Chae's fate ultimately...
- Rests in my hands.
No. I have to make it that way.
To do that, I must be officially appointed
as CEO, no matter what.
If we can exclude Min Kyung Chae
from management somehow,
Kim Sun Jae will leave of his own accord.
The board is the problem.
If I can just get the board's approval,
I'll be able to breathe a little easier.
Why are you just standing around
instead of working?
Do you have something to say to me?
We need to talk.
Why are you backing me
into a corner like this?
What do you mean?
If you had competed fairly from the start,
none of this would've happened.
Who was the one who brought you
into Mingang in the first place?
Who was the one who trusted you
and stood by you through every crisis?
Why are you turning your back on me now?
Whatever you feel for Lucia,
she's with another man now.
There's no future for you with her.
What on earth are you talking about?
If it's not that,
do you really think siding with them
guarantees your future?
- It's definitely not that.
- Then why are you doing this?
Why are you making things so hard
for me at every turn?
Listen here, Ms. Min Kyung Chae.
Have you ever heard the saying?
Your sins will always find you out,
and your good deeds will be rewarded.
There's a reason they say
life is like a boomerang.
Because what you throw out comes back
to hit you.
That's why you have to live
an honorable life.
Because that's what life is all about.
(Mingang Distribution)
Yes?
It's about the chain store's payment
for the livestream event.
Sales were so low.
It's practically nothing.
I never would have shown their products
on the livestream if I'd known.
We would've made much more
if we'd run a sale at the store.
This position is too much for you
after all.
You fought to be the lady of the house,
but the company is another story.
The CEO position is no small thing, is it?
Since you lost to my sister,
shouldn't you step down as interim CEO?
You haven't heard the news, have you?
Min Kyung Chae...
will never sit in this chair again.
What do you mean by that?
But there's such a huge gap
in the livestream sales.
She really got on the chairman's bad side.
Forget being the CEO. She'll be lucky
if she doesn't get fired.
What does she mean,
"on the chairman's bad side?"
Come to my office now.
What is it?
I just heard something strange coming
from the CEO's office.
What on earth is going on?
Did something happen during the livestream
that I don't know about?
If I ask Kyung Chae directly,
I know she'd be too proud to tell me.
How can I help if I don't know
what's going on?
And what could you possibly do to help?
That woman, Lucia,
said Kyung Chae will never become the CEO.
Lucia said that?
She seemed so sure of herself.
Don't tell me you and Kyung Chae
cheated during the livestream.
So the chairman found out.
Then he'll call a board meeting soon,
won't he?
And you still think
you don't need my help?
It's not like everyone on the board
is on Kyung Chae's side.
The board requires a unanimous vote.
So go on, let's see how you do.
You want me to ask Soo Jung for help?
Are you crazy? Why would I do that?
This is no time for pride.
At the board meeting,
if Soo Jung's right-hand man,
Director Oh, votes against you...
And you want me to go groveling
to Soo Jung?
Besides, a board meeting
hasn't even been called yet.
They probably will, and soon.
You said it yourself.
That the chairman wouldn't
just let this slide.
Even so, I'm not bowing down to Soo Jung.
Normally, I wouldn't push you like this.
But with Lucia by the chairman's side,
there's no telling what she'll make him do
to you.
Even so, you think Father
would kick me out himself?
No.
He won't have to.
Lucia will be more than happy to do it.
Being a regular employee would be fine.
What more can he do?
He won't call a board meeting.
He knows perfectly well
I have my people on the board.
Father wouldn't go that far.
Who becomes the CEO of Mingang
is a crucial matter for us too.
What are you talking about?
What difference does it make to us?
Is it going to make us money
or put food on the table?
- You're like a pickled radish, Mal Sook.
- A pickled radish? What does that mean?
- You're simple, ignorant, and a pain.
- Why you...
Think about it, okay?
If the in-law's older daughter returns,
it's a given she'll take over Mingang.
Where would that leave Ji Seop's chances?
And what if her young stepmom
takes over instead?
In that case, he might not become CEO,
but could be a director.
The young stepmom has no company allies.
And the chairman won't be around forever.
In a company, if you don't have allies,
you're toast.
So, to build her own base of power,
- she might take our Ji Seop on her team?
- Exactly.
You're not a pickled radish after all.
The eldest has a strong board behind her.
Would she even notice Ji Seop?
Oh, my goodness!
Now that you mention it, that makes sense.
Your sneaky little brain is one of a kind.
- What? Sneaky little brain?
- Yes.
Come here. See how you like a headbutt
from this "sneaky little brain."
Hey! You blockhead! Gosh, that hurts.
- Your head's a rock.
- How dare you mess with me?
Gosh, seriously!
You blockhead!
(Chairman Min Doo Sik)
As interim CEO,
I can only handle urgent approvals.
It's just frustrating being so limited.
If I were officially appointed CEO,
I could be so much more helpful to you.
It's not that I'm greedy for the position.
I just want to be more helpful to you.
I know,
but that requires the board's approval.
If all else fails,
I'll use my authority to push it through.
Please don't.
I need to go through the proper channels.
I must earn the CEO position legitimately.
Otherwise, this unfair appointment...
will come back to haunt you.
I'll handle it. Just call a board meeting.
(Chairman Min Doo Sik)
Send out the official notice
for the board meeting.
And make sure you contact
every single director.
The agenda?
Motion to dismiss CEO Min Kyung Chae
and appoint Jung Lucia as the new CEO.
What did you say?
So you're saying
he gave that order officially?
He said to post it on the intranet.
Then, of course, it's official!
See?
I told you they'd call a board meeting.
The board is full of my people.
I didn't think he'd make a move so easily.
I'm telling you,
that woman put him up to it.
That's why you have to go to Director Min
and ask for her help now.
You're finished if this goes through.
Once the board approves it,
there's no going back.
What's the occasion? You actually knocked.
Of course I should.
I didn't want to interrupt your work.
It's kind of scary
seeing you act like this.
I think you've got me all wrong.
I just wear my heart on my sleeve,
that's all.
I don't play games.
Is that right?
Fine. What do you want?
- You know about the board meeting, right?
- I saw it on the intranet.
- And?
- Director Oh is your man.
I need your help.
Why would I do that?
We're sisters, aren't we?
And wipe that strained smile
off your face.
So, are you asking me for a favor now?
Yes.
I'm asking for your help.
Once the board meeting is called, I'm sure
the directors loyal to Min Kyung Chae...
will vote against her dismissal.
If that happens, you'll have no choice
but to step down.
Exactly. There can't be two CEOs at once.
Even after the mess Min Kyung Chae made,
you think they'll still vote against it?
They'll probably just cover it up,
considering how deep their collusion runs.
Then we have no other choice.
We must use those connections to win.
Oh, and before that, tell Min Soo Jung
to work her magic on Director Oh.
If Director Oh votes no, it's all over.
Min Kyung Chae has probably already gone
to her office.
She's likely pleading with her
as we speak.
So what's your plan?
Are you going to go plead with her too?
No.
That's not the way to handle Min Soo Jung.
So...
you want me to have Director Oh vote
for Min Kyung Chae's dismissal?
Director Oh is your man, isn't he?
Fine.
Easy enough.
Give me the chairman's stake,
and it's a deal.
- That matter is closed.
- Then it's no deal.
Is that so?
Then I suppose your position
won't be safe forever, either.
My sister came to ask for a favor.
But you're here threatening me.
Even if Director Oh votes no alone,
it won't change the outcome.
It will only delay the inevitable.
I'll become the CEO one way or another.
Then why did you even bother coming here?
I'm giving you one last chance.
A chance to get on my side.
- Excuse me?
- A chance to side with the one in power.
It's the only way to survive.
Since you clawed your way up...
as an illegitimate child
of the Min family,
you should know better than anyone.
It's all about the power dynamic.
And who's on top.
Since you went to such lengths,
I'm sure Director Min will do her part.
This is so demeaning and petty.
An interim CEO is one thing,
but if that woman gets formal approval
from the board...
and it's reported at the general meeting,
it can't be undone.
- We can't let that happen.
- Exactly.
I'm telling you, you have to be ready
to bend over backward for Director Min.
You want me to do more than that?
I was in her office, fawning and smiling.
I did everything I could.
Just put up with it
until the board meeting tomorrow.
Is there any coffee left?
Here, have mine.
I can count on you
at the board meeting tomorrow, right?
The way you're asking,
I can't exactly refuse.
Well, then,
why don't you get on your knees?
Right here?
Fine.
What does it matter where I do it?
Hey, I was just messing with you.
Are you really going to do it?
Why wouldn't I?
What are you doing?
It's nothing.
Okay, I see how important this is to you.
I'll think about it.
Wait, you weren't actually about to kneel
to Soo Jung, were you?
I must have seen that wrong, right?
You saw wrong.
So, what are you going to do about
the board meeting tomorrow?
If you actually get fired
and that woman becomes the CEO...
That's not going to happen,
so don't worry!
(Mingang Distribution)
Don't you worry.
Director Oh has sent word
that he won't be attending,
and that he'll abide by
the board's decision.
Oh, really?
Looks like Soo Jung pulled
some strings after all.
See? Desperate times call for
desperate measures.
Once you humbled yourself to Director Min,
everything was resolved.
I've already made a reservation
at a nice wine bar.
It's a foregone conclusion.
You're right.
The board would never vote to dismiss me.
They know which side their bread
is buttered on.
Even the chairman couldn't touch you,
knowing the board was on your side.
So what makes that woman think
she can change their minds?
It's almost too easy.
This vote is just a formality.
Maybe you should start getting ready
to take back your CEO position.
I don't think I'll be able
to keep a straight face.
Even so, you have to keep a poker face.
This is a serious meeting.
Should I look all pitiful and anxious,
maybe even shed a tear,
worried that I might get fired?
This meeting is to decide on the dismissal
of CEO Min Kyung Chae...
and the appointment of Jung Lucia,
who has been recommended as the new CEO.
Members of the board, please state
your positions on this matter.
Someone like you?
In your dreams.
They'd jump if I told them so.
There's no way they will dismiss me
and appoint you CEO.
We, the board of directors,
cannot possibly accept the motion
to dismiss CEO Min Kyung Chae.
Of course.
It's absurd to consider another CEO.
Yes, there was a minor misstep
during the livestream,
but to fire her overnight
for that is ridiculous.
She can be held accountable
for that mistake in other ways.
But to use it as an excuse to replace her?
This is an upstart trying to take over.
If it's not CEO Min Kyung Chae,
we will not recognize
anyone else as our CEO.
Then we will proceed to the vote.
All those in favor of the motion
to dismiss CEO Min Kyung Chae,
please raise your hand.
(Mingang Distribution)
And now, for her successor.
All those in favor of Jung Lucia,
please raise your hands as well.
Have you all lost your minds?
(The Woman Who Swallowed the Sun)
I'm not stepping down like this.
No way I'm letting that woman become CEO!
You need to lie low and ride this out.
It's how you'll get another chance.
Congratulations on your first day,
CEO Jung.
You'd better get your act together.
If you pull something like that again,
I promise you, you're finished.
So you're saying
there's no way out of this?
The chairman's will gives us a chance.
When the time's right,
you can take over
and make everything right again.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)