(Episode 51)
I flew to the US after that,
as if I were fleeing.
The thought of returning kept me going.
I know that feeling.
I felt exactly the same...
when I boarded the plane to the US
after my parents died.
People think
you can forget it all and move on.
But some memories...
become clearer as time goes on.
You can't forget.
You shouldn't forget.
That's why...
I need you just to watch what I do.
Don't try to stop me.
I'm doing this
because I know how it feels...
to fail to protect a loved one.
Director.
Fine.
Do whatever you want.
If that's the best you can do.
But I, too,
will do what I can.
Don't do that.
I told you that's no good for me.
Why won't you say anything?
It's not something
we can pretend didn't happen.
What do you mean?
Clear up whatever misunderstanding
you have in my presence.
CEO Min, you apologize first.
You assaulted her.
Don't do this, Chairman.
I don't need an apology.
Don't just stand there.
You knew I had a guest over,
but you returned drunk out of your mind...
and grabbed her by the hair.
That's vulgar and crass.
Apologize immediately.
If you apologize first.
Apologize for giving away Mother's ring.
I bought your mother that ring.
The cardigan she wore
was a present from me for Mom's birthday.
How dare she wear that?
I suddenly felt a chill.
I'd wanted to impress your family,
and the nerves had gotten to me.
I went in not knowing it was your room,
and I wore the first thing I noticed.
You did know whose room it was.
Manager Gong said she told you.
Is that what she said?
It was an innocent mistake.
I wouldn't have touched it if I'd known.
You lie at every turn.
If the chairman
likes you enough to marry you,
do you think Mingang will be yours?
That thought never crossed my mind.
It never crossed your mind?
You approached him on purpose.
What do you think you're doing?
You should be ashamed!
Don't make things any worse and apologize.
Anyone would say you were in the wrong.
Father!
If you won't apologize, pack your things.
Don't think of seeing me again,
and stay well away from the company.
You won't give in?
Get out!
I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry. I feel even worse.
How dare she...
My goodness.
I hope you understand.
Will you calm down?
Relax.
Talk to me. Who made you so angry?
That woman.
What happened this time?
I apologized to her.
I, Min Kyung Chae, had to apologize!
She has more pride
than anyone in the country.
Why would you antagonize her?
Do I have to care about that?
She's nothing without her pride.
You worry a great deal about her.
She's the only connection you have.
You wouldn't want her to go down.
Are you making such a fuss because
you consider the chairman your connection?
Not yet.
If I use that connection to do something,
you will suffer the consequences too.
"Madam. Please spare me."
You'll beg on your knees.
"Madam?"
Yes, "madam."
If you want to survive,
pick your side wisely.
I should side with you?
Who knows? I might show you some mercy...
for old times' sake.
That darn brat.
Say no during work hours.
He might be the chairman,
but you can refuse to visit his office
for personal reasons during work hours.
I can't say no.
Shall I refuse for you?
- Director.
- I told you...
I'd do things my way.
Before, I didn't know about your plan,
but now that I know what your plan is,
I can't let it go on.
I told you that doesn't do me any good.
Let's say I'm doing what's good for me.
I will protect you for my sake.
How's that?
I'm allowed to protect my loved one.
I don't want to lose anyone close to me.
Is that too much to ask for?
Your hurt.
It's not just yours anymore.
I gave you a hint.
Why won't you do anything?
What do you mean?
I told you about Lucia's relationship
with the chairman.
Was I mistaken?
Don't you have feelings for her?
I care for her...
only as a subordinate and nothing else.
That's a lie.
Soon, you'll regret telling that lie.
What is it that you want from me?
You get to protect the woman you love.
And I get to protect my father... No.
I get to protect the company.
Get that woman away from the chairman.
Others might fail,
but you, of all people, can do it.
Madam.
Your husband seems to be out.
He's at home.
Why? Do you want to talk to him?
Yes. I'd like to ask him something.
He's in that room. Go see him.
He won't let me anywhere near the place.
Okay.
Money's rolling in, rolling in like crazy.
It's rolling in endlessly
from all directions.
Cash, money...
Excuse me.
You are not excused!
How dare you come in here?
I'm so sorry.
Your wife said you'd be in here.
So you waltzed in? Get out immediately.
Outsiders are banned from this room.
Sorry. I had no idea.
Exactly how big is your house, sir?
The site is 755m²,
the floor space is 390m²,
this room is 8m²,
and this safe is 0.33m², okay?
Now get out!
That's a pretty decent floor area ratio.
Why do you care about that?
Yes, sorry. Let's see...
He has no idea what room this is.
Not even the National
Intelligence Service is allowed in.
These secret documents
are worth a fortune.
"How much are they worth, Pan Sool?"
Tens of millions of dollars.
Mingang's shares are divided
in a way that's unique to the industry.
His family has an absolute majority.
On top of that,
Min Doo Sik set up many safety measures...
in case someone unrelated to them...
were to take an influential position.
He's so thorough.
The bottom line is,
the company stays within the family.
If you marry into the family,
you have no choice but to help them...
keep control of the company.
Yes.
Min Kyung Chae and Min Soo Jung
are still single,
and there's the youngest to consider.
The three future sons-in-law...
will affect the succession.
He'll say you're his
and that he'll look after you,
but I think Min Doo Sik...
will suspect and test you
until the very end.
Don't worry.
I'm getting through each day
thinking it's an endless trial.
Father, you can't just eat your food.
I'm watching what I eat.
That's not what I mean.
You should say something.
The house
was turned upside down last weekend.
We deserve an explanation.
Yes, Father.
You should tell us about that woman...
so we can think about it.
If you don't say anything,
our imagination will run wild.
We'll imagine scenes from third-rate films
that we'd rather not.
Can't you tell?
He invited her home.
It means they're dating.
Dad. Will you marry that lady?
Finish your meal.
You might as well answer.
I'd like to know too.
You're not considering marriage, are you?
Have you lost your mind?
What? Is there a reason I can't?
(Mingang Distribution)
Why did you want to see me?
To confirm what you said to me before.
If I were to "sort out" Lucia for you,
you said you'd give me what I wanted.
Did I say that?
Yes. Give it a go.
You won't ask what it is that I want?
Do I have to?
I'll give you anything.
Promise me one thing, then.
That if you were to find out
some new details about me,
you won't use it
as an excuse to change your mind.
"New details?"
It must be something disappointing.
Sure.
Even if you wore a mask
and pretended to be someone else,
I'll let it slide.
Getting rid of that woman is my priority.
Very well, then.
I'll come to your place...
and speak with the chairman.
It will be much more effective...
if he were to hear it in person.
I tested them both.
Oh Pan Sool is practically impenetrable.
He must have something on his wife,
because she's not allowed
anywhere near the room with the safe.
The only option is to hope
that he has a change of heart.
That's impossible.
His daughter is married to
Min Doo Sik's son.
He won't let the Min family go down.
What should we do, then?
Min Doo Sik offered to repay
my gambling debt.
That was why I turned myself in
and said I caused the accident.
Mr. Jo.
That means there must be...
a gap between the accident
and when you turned yourself in.
Of course.
Your parents died in the accident
at Mucheon Roundabout,
and I was somewhere else.
By the time Min Doo Sik
had sent me to the scene of the accident,
quite a lot of time had passed.
Hang on.
If the police accepted your statement
because there were no witnesses,
in other words, we just have to prove...
you weren't there
when the accident happened.
Do you think so?
Mr. Jo. When you were somewhere else,
were you with someone?
Let me see.
The person I was with then...
(30 years prior)
It wasn't me.
I didn't steal it.
Why would I take a woman's underwear...
when I can't sell it for anything?
Don't make excuses.
You look exactly like the person
the victim described.
Come on. If that's the case,
let's check the CCTV footage.
What sauna has surveillance
in the locker room?
Are you allowed to jail the innocent
based on a victim's statement?
It really wasn't me!
I didn't take anything!
Come back!
I was accused of petty theft
and locked up in a holding cell.
I had a long record,
so they didn't believe me.
I was released
only after they caught the real thief.
I got Min Doo Sik's call
just as I was leaving the police station.
There must be a record, then.
I'm sure the police keep such records.
If we can confirm that,
we can apply for a retrial.
A retrial?
Another trial, you mean?
Yes. If that works out,
the car accident
will be expunged from your record.
Are you sure?
A bucket list?
Yes, a bucket list.
You list up things you want to do
and then do them all.
I know what it is.
You're saying you want to do that with me.
You don't want to?
It's not that I don't want to.
Will you make me do weird stuff?
What will we do?
It's a secret.
It's childish to have secrets.
Okay, then. I have to do what you ask.
I have no say.
What will you do?
Lawyer Kim will come by soon.
He'll tell my father about that woman.
I don't know what he'll say,
but I hope it's enough
to change the chairman's mind.
I would hope so.
I regret...
telling the chairman to find a good woman.
I'm sure it wasn't anything you said.
I have a bad feeling about it.
Your late mother's ring and cardigan.
And the way she makes you look bad.
That woman
has something against your family.
You need to watch out.
It's game over
if Father crosses the line with her.
I almost passed out
when I heard what he said.
I thought he'd say no
when you asked if he'd marry her.
We're not just any family.
Do you think this even makes sense?
She's an employee
and young enough to be his daughter.
If the word were to get out,
people would say Father was senile.
I get what you're saying,
but what influence do we have?
It's his life, and he gets to decide
what he does.
I think so too. It's Dad's life to live.
You two are acting weird.
I thought you'd be
hopping mad and against it.
I respect his decision.
It depends on how you think.
Me too.
What got into them?
What if you and I
are the only ones to object?
No.
There's one other person
who will give her life to object.
Kyung Chae?
We must join forces, then.
I'm not exactly on good terms with her.
This isn't the time to be timid.
Your subordinate
could become your stepmom.
Why did Father
have to pick her of all people?
Why don't you go to the office tomorrow
and see how things are?
I got these for the chairman's office.
If I can't do everything at once,
I'll take small, gradual steps...
to change him and his surroundings.
You will change him? Know your place.
Who do you think you are?
I don't want to have to say this,
but I think you need to hear it.
Don't you think
you should watch your language?
What?
I'm not just anyone.
I'm dating your father.
Telling me to "know my place..."
It's disgusting to watch you act
as if you're an item.
He gave me a ring...
and introduced me to his family.
Doesn't that make us an item?
I'd like you
to watch your language from now on.
Good morning.
What are the flowers for?
I want to brighten up your office.
This is what a chairman's office is like.
Here's my bucket list.
You want to do this with me?
Yes.
At my age? It's embarrassing.
What about your age?
Today is the youngest you'll ever be.
Will you do it with me?
Are you free this weekend?
I'm not. Lawyer Kim will come over.
Let's do it some other time, then.
Yeon Ah.
Kim Sun Jae will bring the ledger
to the house this weekend.
Be careful, okay?
He knows you.
Don't you worry.
I'll do this for you.
What are you doing in our office?
Why put on an act when it's just us?
Shall I speak freely, then?
Why are you here?
Who do you want to spy on now?
I decided to show some grace...
before dropping the bomb.
What?
I'll see the chairman this weekend.
So what?
I have other business too,
but the biggest topic is you.
I'm going to tell him who you are.
My past will come up too,
but I'd rather risk that
than let you marry...
my chairman.
You should've stopped when I told you to.
You'll get kicked out of Mingang...
if your past were to come up.
I thought about that,
and I don't think they'll make a fuss
about a past relationship.
If they want me gone...
But you know,
they can't fire me first.
I have something on them.
What is it this time?
It's the knight in shining armor.
That makes Moon Tae Kyung your third man.
I'm your first,
and Min Doo Sik is your second.
What was that about?
Goodness.
If the chairman realizes who you are,
things will get much more dangerous.
He'll think you deceived him.
I don't get it.
Why didn't Lawyer Kim
use that against you if he knew all along?
It's because...
What if he was waiting...
to use it to cause more damage?
He's...
my daughter's birth father.
What?
What did you say?
Hang on.
Then Lawyer Kim and you used to...
We met at our university.
I quit my studies to support him.
Then I got pregnant...
Not another word.
He wanted to be successful,
so he abandoned his girlfriend...
and his daughter.
Are you disappointed in me?
No.
I'm surprised, though.
You came here and were reunited
with someone you can't stand.
That must've been so tough.
I hope the lawyer likes the food.
They're his favorites, so he will.
I'm sorry to make you come over
on the weekend.
It's fine.
I said I'd like to help
whenever you need it.
Are you worried?
Your sister said she'd manage.
I'm worried anyway.
What if Sun Jae recognizes her?
It's too late to tell her to back off.
Kim Sun Jae will be there by now.
I should go there myself.
Hello.
Can I have a word first?
You really won't tell me?
Hear it from the chairman later on.
Are you sure it's big enough
to get rid of...
Lucia for good?
Nothing much has changed.
I'm handling...
the slush fund, window-dressed ledger,
and shell company well.
It's not that I don't trust you.
I need this as an excuse
to see you at home.
Of course.
You sly old man.
I hope this is enough.
It's not just enough. It's a true feast.
Thanks for everything.
Can I use your toilet before I leave?
Sure, you can. Thanks for the help.
You're welcome.
Actually,
I have something more important
to share than the ledger.
It's more important than the ledger?
I'm going to tell you...
about someone's past.
The table is set.
Let's eat first if it's not too urgent.
Excuse me for a moment.
You little rat.
You dare take my ledger?
(The Woman Who Swallowed the Sun)
Yeon Ah!
Why do you want confirmation
of something as embarrassing as that?
I need that confirmed
if I'm to clear my name.
Did Soo Jung say she was all for it?
That's why we should
put our feelings aside...
and team up
when it comes to Father's love life.
What was that
you didn't get to say yesterday?
Whatever I say,
you must trust and believe me.
Many years ago, I dated...
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)