[English subtitles are available]
Youth Melody
Episode 5
- Wow! This is it?
- Go in there.
- Yeah.
- Go on in!
It must have cost a lot of money.
This is huge!
Come on in!
Biao, this...
What's wrong?
This is the best rehearsal room in the sports section.
It not quite the same as I thought it would be.
You're gonna just have to try to bear with it.
It might be a little tough for us,
but we're gonna rise from the ashes and kick their asses.
Now.
Let's starting cleaning.
She's right, I think.
They all do this in TV shows.
They always live a tough life for a while
before they become big and successful.
Start cleaning already!
Nope.
We can't use this rehearsal room.
It's OK.
If we want the lamps fixed,
we can go to the school's repairman.
We can clean
everything in here ourselves.
Good.
I'll go find out if there are other classrooms.
I'll go with you.
Chiyi, let's go, too.
Let's go find other rooms.
Where are you going?
Come back!
[Try to bear with it!]
Try to bear with it!
If Yan Ke is not here, we can't go on with the formation.
Yeah. We've not got the right one.
I'm sorry, guys.
I'm late.
Let's start now.
Yihan, what's wrong with you?
You were late.
Yes. I was late.
Only for a few minutes.
Do you really have to be like this?
What's the reason?
The one who is disrespectful to the team
is not qualified to be here and practise.
In this team,
we don't welcome people who are late.
Yihan, that's enough.
Yan Ke.
Not every association
can use this room in the music association.
You're looking for me?
I'm only passing by.
Yu Muyang.
Are you happy that you have made everyone
hate your guts?
I'm not.
He left himself.
Fu Yunzhe.
Not everyone is obligated to meet your expectations.
If you let someone down,
he is surely not obligated to wait for you.
Yu Muyang.
Have you ever thought about it from my point of view?
Yu Muyang!
What's happening?
Isn't that Yu Muyang from the music association?
When I was working
in the student union with Fu Yunzhe,
I found out that
he had been paying a lot of attention
to Yu Muyang.
Do they bear grudges against each other?
I heard they grew up together.
They grew up together?
Then why would head go and argue with him?
I feel that when head sees Yu Muyang,
he forgets all about us.
Then what should we do now?
What can we do?
Let's just do the practice and the rehearsal ourselvers.
[Quanlong Fight]
Stop!
Put in more strength.
Relax your waist.
Relax.
You gotta relax so you can gain strength.
One more.
Get up.
How did you lose weight again?
You can't be so thin.
You have to keep up with the weight gain plan
OK.
You have to strictly follow the training plan
I made for you.
Change your clothes.
Warm up.
Mimi, time for dinner.
Mimi.
Time to eat, Mimi.
Time to eat.
Mimi.
[Cheering for Music Association]
Thanks.
♫I won't say goodbye♫
♫Your faith♫
♫is my faith♫
♫Coronate declaration♫
♫before the sun rises♫
Have some rest, everyone.
Go get some water.
OK.
[How's the music association lately?]
[It's OK. We did find some new members.]
[But everyone seems to have not enough impetus.]
[Don't feel down. I believe you can.]
[How about you? How's it going?]
[We all miss you.]
What do you think?
It isn't bad here, huh?
Are you watching something interesting?
It's nothing.
I'm just looking through some chats with Luoluo before.
I saw some encouraging words for us
and then I soon felt powerful.
Luoluo?
Hasn't he contacted you?
Why are you looking at old chats?
Luoluo must be very busy lately.
I'm afraid I would disturb him.
So I have not spoken to him.
[My Home Boiled Fish with Pickled Cabbage and Chili]
[Submit Order]
Luoluo sent me a message.
He ordered some food for you.
I'll go get it.
Let's eat together when I get back.
Really?
Really.
Luoluo is the best.
I knew he wouldn't bail on us.
Are you Lin Mo?
Yes.
OK. Thanks.
If you don't gain weight, how are you going to fight the game?
I don't wanna fight.
I want to rehearsal in the New Sound Association.
What New Sound Association?
Do you remember what your goal is?
Fighting champion.
How do you become the champion by singing and dancing?
I've said it several times.
It's been your dream to become a fighting champion.
Not mine.
Yan Ke!
Hey, you.
Do you know Yan Ke?
Kind of?
OK. Give him this.
Watch him.
Tell him to finish this.
OK. I will.
Thank you.
Here, here. Food is here.
Luoluo ordered all of them for us?
Here is a card!
But the handwriting is awful.
[Fighting! Music Club!  Luoluo]
Maybe the man for takeaway wrote it.
Luoluo is so kind-hearted!
He is concerned about us!
Well, you should dine first.
I should leave now. I have something to do.
Lin Mo!
Where are you going?
You should eat something!
[Xinsheng Club]
What are you looking at?
I want to find Yan Ke.
But it doesn't look like he's here.
I gotta go.
What are you doing?!
I'm sorry.
Yan Ke.
Your father asked me to give you this.
Thank you.
And he let me tell you that
you must finish this meal.
Did your father cook this?
Yes.
[Youngster's Tea]
Youngster's Tea?
What's this?
This is white tea.
When I was quitting carbonated drinks,
I couldn't find an alternative drink.
So he gave me this kind of tea.
Light sweet,
it tastes good.
I didn't expect that
your father is really thoughtful
but with a fierce face!
My father
is a kickboxer.
He won the championship at the municipal level
and was second runner-up at the provincial level.
But he didn't get good grades
in the national competition,
and didn't get any better grades after that.
He wants me to keep boxing
and to realize
his dreamy goal.
So, the wounds on your face...
They were from my dad when we were training.
Have you heard about the rumors
about you on our campus?
I can't control what they say.
Nothing but I always fight with others.
Or more exaggerated,
I always fight and skip classes,
so I'm a heinous young man.
I'm used to it.
Is that all?
But I heard that
you were stopped by neighboring school students,
you struck down one of them like this,
and kicked one like this.
Anyway, you defeated all of them!
Hi, Mr. Li.
Go away.
Li Mingfan, Li Mingfan.
She is going to win the gold medal.
I'd better
be a single handsome man silently
and sacrifice my whole life
to biology.
Your father...
Today he...
Does he always...
No, he doesn't.
In the boxing ring,
he always hits me so hard.
But at ordinary times,
this was the first time he beat me.
I made out that
your father
loves you so much.
Are you talking about this?
He customized this meal for me.
He wants me to compete in man's over 45-kg boxing,
but
my body weight is not high enough.
So he let me gain weight this way.
But I can't finish it
every time,
I can only throw the leftovers away.
Well, do you really like boxing?
Yan Ke, have you ever thought that
you would be truly happy
only when you do what you stand for and love.
Lin Mo,
your stomach is rumbling.
You didn't even eat to
bring me this meal, right?
Come on, eat it quickly.
That's OK,
I'm full.
Then I'll not stand at the ceremony.
Just eat!
I'll eat a little bit.
My father checks my lunchbox everyday,
and he will criticize me
if I don't finish the meal.
Then... I''ll eat it.
Go on!
Let me try.
I'll eat it.
Sure.
How about it?
It's delicious!
By the way,
the mid-term exam is drawing near.
How is it now?
Do you have any preparation?
I'm practicing boxing or rehearsing
in my break.
I have no other time to study.
What about your pledge to our director?
Mo,
it's all your fault!
Alas!
You were in Xinsheng Club at that time!
Whatever.
Mr. Li teaches us extra lessons in our music club.
Would you like to study with us?
Music club?
I don't think it's appropriate for me to go.
That's OK! Lin Xuanhao is also there.
You don't need to worry about it.
Hello, Ms. He.
Where is Mr. Li?
He was here just now.
Mr. Li,
Ms. He is looking for you!
He is here.
Mr. Li!
Hi, Ms. He.
I'm learning biology questions.
What's the matter?
Well,
I have run out the Sanqi leaves you gave me.
Run...
Just put it there, Ms. He.
Then I'll leave.
Stand on it.
How much?
One kilo heavier than before.
You are gaining weight steadily recently.
Just keep it.
Change your clothes and warm up,
prepare for our pair training.
Dad,
I want to have a rest.
Again!
I'm exhausted!
You can only rest for 20 minutes.
Clear it up.
Come in.
Mr. Li.
Ms. He.
What's wrong?
Mr. Li,
Are you... okay recently?
I'm fine.
What's the matter, Ms. He?
Why do I feel that
you are avoiding me these days?
Avoid, avoiding...
That's impossible.
Maybe I'm too...
I'm too busy recently, Ms. He!
I have too many classes.
Are you coming to the bilology lab for other things?
Didn't you say
you were going to help those kids with their tutoring?
Yes.
I think the midterm exams are getting closer and closer.
Can you start earlier?
How about tonight?
Tonight?
Yeah, I've informed them.
They'll be here tonight.
Then they're counting on you, Mr. Lee.
Yan Yan Ke.
My brother said he wants you
to go to the biology classroom tonight at 7:00 for tutoring.
Let me go to the club first.
Don't be late!
My brother will scold me to death if you are late!
Before tutoring,
students,
I need to know your weak subjects.
And according to the weak subjects
to make the appropriate study plan.
So you have to tell me
which subjects you are not learning well.
We will go by focus to cram those.
In this way, you will have more room for improvement.
Teacher.
I'm not very good at math,
and physics.
Usually, I can't get a score for the last big question.
For me, all the subjects were pretty average
except for language and English.
My greatest strength is that I am not biased.
Anyway, if it's going to be worse, it's going to be worse together.
I just started my first year of high school,
and I'm struggling with every subject.
It is more normal for Lin Xuanhao to be like this.
It's okay.
How about you, Yu Muyang?
I am poor in science.
OK.
Then we will start with math today.
Let's take out the test papers first.
Let's spend thirty minutes doing multiple choice questions.
Does Yan Ke come or not?
Did you inform him for me?
I made sure I informed him.
I'm sorry.
I took the javelin by accident.
But you do not pay too much attention to it.
Listen well.
She absolutely did it on purpose.
She must have done it on purpose.
Our Yan boxer
is running all the way from the ring,
it seems that today's training is up to standard.
Come on, sit down.
We've already started.
Mr. Lee.
This is Yan Ke.
Did you ask him to come?
[Twenty-one The Orchid Pavilion]
You don't say that
mock question is so hard today.
Isn't it?
The dead brain cells
can only be made up for by a delicious meal.
It's them.
The thing is,
they are having a fan meeting here.
Why don't we go take a look?
OK.
The few inks in my belly told me that
there is a saying that if you know your enemy, you will never lose a battle.
Let's go spy on the information.
OK.
But
will we be discovered
if we go there like this?
I feel a little awkward.
It's okay. Let's disguise ourselves.
This is a mall.
What can't we get?
Go, go, go.
So many people!
Let's go!
Go! Go! Go!
Forget about it.
Hey, Lin Mo.
How can you recognize me
after I've dressed up like this?
I have noticed you guys as soon as you walked by.
And
who would wear sunglasses indoors at night?
This is the standard for handsome and trendy men.
Help.
I have an urgent need to ask for your help.
What is it?
Come and say it. Come and say it.
[Hu Xinyi, Mao Weijia, Shen Ying]
I don't know.
Why haven't they come yet?
[AKB48 Team SH]
Let them wear our clothes to replace later.
Follow me.
Now we can only let them help us.
They have arrived.
What's wrong?
As you can see,
we are holding our fan meeting here today.
But we had members
who couldn't make it in time for our opening act.
So we'd like to ask you for a small favor.
It is
to replace our members
and support our opening act.
I don't know if it's possible.
You are kidding, right?
No.
We are serious.
And we just thought about it for a long time,
until we saw you guys.
But we are boys.
Boys.
It's okay. It's okay.
We have clothes,
and we also have wigs that the members usually use for performances.
- So, please, please.
- Please.
What do you think?
I feel a little excited.
Are we going to wear women's clothing?
I've never worn women's clothing
in my life.
Lin Mo, I'll listen to you.
Lin Mo, don't think twice about it!
We can help you.
But for us,
we might need super-duper oversized clothes.
It doesn't matter.
Because we can help you
find the largest size as we can.
All right.
What's wrong? You don't want to wear it?
No.
I can wear,
wear.
Well, I want to go to the toilet.
What are you doing there?
I'm going to change clothes.
Change your clothes, huh?
If you're going, let's all go together.
Go, go, go.
These are the new members we are training.
We hope you can give them a chance
because today is their debut stage.
We will do our best
to do our best.
Do not be anxious, do not be nervous.
Forget the thing that we are wearing women's clothing.
Imagine
this is our stage.
Lin Mo, this skirt is a little short, isn't it?
It's very easy to expose.
You take it.
No, thanks.