My professor said this
when he explained perspective:
The bigger the comparison object is,
the smaller a person looks.
Right now,
I'm the ant inside that picture.
Mom,
I got a part-time job.
It's so embarrassing
I want to crawl into a hole.
I just can't bring myself to tell you
what kind of job it is exactly.
But
with the money it pays,
I can cover your hospital bills.
If you can get healthy again,
my pride
is not important.
I'm still young,
but I think I've toughened up a little.
If it means your surgery goes well,
I can endure anything
and
do anything.
Good morning.
The tenth one.
Give me your luggage.
It's okay.
I'll do it.
Not even a "hi"
or "hello."
Really feels like
I'm just a product or something.
You're the tenth art student
my secretary selected for me.
I only sleep with art students.
I have three rules.
First,
come whenever I call.
Second,
keep your distance from everyone
except me.
Third,
absolute
obedience.
Keep my distance from everyone?
Even my professors,
my friends,
and my creative world?
What about my Monday classes?
Do you understand?
Yes.
Understood, sir.
What’s this scar?
Does it hurt?
Right now,
it doesn't.
If you break my rules,
I can make you hurt more than this.
You understand?
That's about enough.
So you do lose control too.
Come in.
I left the contract period and pay blank.
You decide.
The upper limit
is whatever you can handle.
Mom's surgery fees
and my tuition...
Just endure it.
This night might be
a turning point in my life.
Han Jaehun?
He's just a client who hired me.
All of this
is just work to me.
Then...
1,000 dollars
for one night.
Do I look pitiful to him?
Sure.
But
2,000 dollars...
means it might hurt just as much more.
Can you handle it?
Ah!
What was that look?
If you don't like it,
you can say so now.
No.
I'm fine.
Relax.
From now on,
you'll get used to everything.
Your kissing skills
are better than I thought.
Not bad.
From now on, your time,
your body,
and, at times, even your heart...
All of it belongs to me.
You're crazy,
sir.
Yeah.
I'm crazy.
Take a good look.
This is what you wanted.