=Stand By Me=
=Episode 9=
Who do you think those people are?
They even impersonate
as the Anti-traitor Corps.
How do you know they're impostors?
They don't even have a badge.
Of course they're impostors.
The Anti-traitor Corps has badges, I see.
You seem to know a lot
about the Anti-traitor Corps.
I don't know much.
I just heard about them.
(Did I just expose myself?)
(If he knew I'm lying to him,)
(he wouldn't kill me, right?)
(Judging from this kid's reaction,)
(he must be one of
the Anti-traitor Corps.)
(Punish the traitors and eliminate evil.)
(I never took him to be this brave.)
(Huang Weijie, you dummy.)
(He doesn't even realize
he exposed himself.)
(I need to think of a way)
(to get him and the Anti-traitor Corps
off my back,)
(so they won't ruin my plan.)
(Feng Guanyu made Zhao Qian
and Sun Li lie low outside)
(over a blind date?)
(Maybe he really isn't a traitor?)
(But where is that batch of opium?)
(I need to think of a way to find out.)
What's over there?
What is it?
I read a piece of news today.
It said a traitor got assassinated.
It seems like the work of
the Anti-traitor Corps.
I'm worried for you,
so I'm here to protect you.
Really?
But what is there for you to worry about?
I'm just another respectable businessman
and haven't done anything treasonous.
You wouldn't suspect me
of being a traitor, would you?
No, no, no.
How could I possibly suspect you?
I was just thinking.
Since you run a legitimate business,
if President Ma's opium
is really with you,
shouldn't you hand it over
to the Anti-traitor Corps
to save yourself from a lot of trouble?
You aren't with
the Anti-traitor Corps, right?
No, no. How could I possibly be one?
There's no way
I'm part of the Anti-traitor Corps.
Didn't you say I'm brainless?
That's impossible.
I trust you.
You will never lie to me.
Of course, of course.
For you.
For me?
My father gave me this gun.
He hoped that I will use it
to protect the Feng family and myself.
Now,
I'm handing it to you.
This... This is too significant.
It's inappropriate.
- It's fine.
- It's really inappropriate.
- Take it.
- It's inappropriate.
- I'm sorry.
- You...
Don't get angry.
I didn't do it on purpose.
- You...
- How about this?
I'll give you something in return.
Okay? This...
(Anti-traitor Corps)
(Crap! I got exposed.)
(The more I don't want to expose you,
the more trouble you cause.)
Incompetent and full of flaws.
Let's go.
Have you done what I told you to do?
As per your instruction,
the opium was transported
to the eastern warehouse.
But we haven't found out
who is Long San's boss yet.
Keep investigating.
Yes.
Young Master,
I would like to remind you again.
We must not get involved
with the Japanese.
Aren't you done yet? Are you even Chinese?
This batch of goods was shipped in
using the Feng family's port.
We have the responsibility
to stop Japanese's opium
from harming the people.
But you mustn't forget the motto
the master left behind.
Be careful of everything.
My father also said
never be a traitor.
- But...
- Get out!
How many guards are posted
at the eastern warehouse?
We've arranged ten men
to guard it day and night.
Remove these guards tomorrow night.
Then, think of a way
to leak this information to Huang Weijie.
Don't tell him directly.
Young Master, may I ask why?
We'll do it right away.
(Weijie, here's your chance.)
(When the Anti-traitor Corps finds this opium,)
(you will complete the mission.)
(You can finally leave this place.)
(I will face the danger)
(from the Japanese alone.)
No one is on opium guard duty
tomorrow night.
Where is the opium?
The eastern warehouse.
Do you think he heard it?
I don't know.
This won't do. Young Master said
to make sure he heard it.
Come on.
He's here. No one is on opium guard duty
tomorrow night.
Where is the opium?
The eastern warehouse.
Has he heard it?
I don't know.
Come on.
No one is on opium guard duty
tomorrow night.
Where is the opium?
The eastern warehouse.
No one is...
No one is on opium guard duty
tomorrow night.
Where is the opium?
The eastern warehouse.
No one is on opium guard duty
tomorrow night.
Where is the opium?
No one is on opium guard duty
tomorrow night.
Come on.
No one is on opium guard duty
tomorrow night.
Where is the opium?
The eastern warehouse.
No one is on opium guard duty
tomorrow night.
Where is the opium?
The eastern warehouse.
What did you two just say?
♪I only realized after taking a few turns♪
♪That you helped me on every path♪
♪I was wrong in thinking
you had no fire♪
♪That you couldn't set me on fire
and refuse to be by my side♪
♪On the day you disappeared♪
♪We became one light year apart♪
♪Chaos blurred your youthful face♪
♪But I never forget my longing for you♪
♪On the day we met again♪
♪We became one light year closer♪
♪I want to use the remaining time♪
♪To fulfill our promise♪
♪On the day you disappeared♪
♪We became one light year apart♪
♪Chaos blurred your youthful face♪
♪But I never forget my longing for you♪
♪On the day we met again♪
♪We became one light year closer♪
♪I want to use the remaining time♪
♪To fulfill our promise♪