[Who Am I (我是谁) by Jolin Tsai (蔡依林) & Jony J (肖佳)]
♫ Used to the depth of the darkness ♫
♫ No matter how wild, there is no fear ♫
♫ Waiting for a star to fall to see who its afterglow will illuminate
(I tell myself to keep pushing on by feeling, it’s history in the making)♫
♫ Of the same kind as the banished ♫
♫ Hiding the loneliness in defense
(Climbing mountains and cliffs)♫
♫ But gentleness is always invincible
(I’m earth-shatteringly alone, with no purpose and no worry, just so I can push on harder)♫
♫ Refusing to compromise with fate
because my heart has a home ♫
♫ It's yours; I don't belong to anyone else ♫
♫ (But let me know who I am and give me a destination) ♫
♫ Who am I if I didn’t meet you? ♫
♫ (You took away what I care about and all my attention) ♫
♫ Who am I without you? ♫
♫ (But let me know who I am and give me a destination) ♫
♫ When a puppet hanging on a string has experienced warmth ♫
♫ The pupil is no longer black, white, or grey
(You took away what I care about and all my attention) ♫
(But let me know who I am and give me a destination) ♫
♫ You know who I am ♫
[The Wolf]
As long as we can save the Ma Family Army, then I am willing to try.
Since Commandery Princess Ma is willing to take the risk...
As a member of the Ma Family Army, I'm also willing.
I will accompany you to the end then.
Wen Yan, immediately give Commandery Princess
the herbal pill for suppressing her Soul Separation Syndrome. I'm in a hurry.
Mo Xiao, send a messenger pigeon to Hai Die.
We'll be in the capital by noonday. Tell her to have a horse ready at the bottom of the mountain.
This is the small path you mentioned?
Unless someone has wolf-like skills, otherwise, how does one get down?
From the bottom of this cliff, it's a straight walk to the capital.
But... how do we get down?
I told you before, this road is risky.
Could it be you've climbed down from here before?
I haven't.
Then, Your Highness...
Why am I feeling so dizzy?
It could be the medicine that Wen Yan gave you for suppressing your soul from being detached.
It's taking effect.
Why is it now?
Then, the Ma Family Army...
Your dizziness won't last long,
so don't worry. There are times when I'll still need you to be awake.
I didn't lie to you.
I've never climbed down from here before,
because no one can climb down this cliff.
Today, with you as an extra, whether you will be safe or not
will only be determined by the heavens.
Master!
Go. Let's stop the rebellion.
The Prince of Bo has yet to appear and His Majesty is ignoring us.
Then you can't blame the Ma Family Army for not having any reservations.
It's noonday! Attack the capital!
[Ma]
Sacrifice our lives for the truth!
Your Highness, are we still not releasing any arrows
at this time?
Are you stupid? My father-in-law
is still in the Ma Army's hands.
If I order the arrows to be released, he will die.
It's Your Highness.
I overlooked that in my panic.
Archers, prepare!
Seek the truth!
Release the arrows!
- Everyone--
- Commandery Princess Ma is here!
It's the Commandery Princess! Commandery Princess!
- It's really the Commandery Princess!
- Commandery Princess! Commandery Princess!
Commandery Princess!
- Commandery Princess!
Brother Fengcheng. Ma Jing. Please stand up quickly.
- Commandery Princess, you're still alive!
The heavens are just. The heavens are just.
The Ma Family Army will follow the Commandery Princess until death.
Follow the Commandery Princess until death.
Follow the Commandery Princess until death!
Brother Fengcheng, it's all thanks to Wen Yan and His Highness, Prince of Bo.
They saved me in time.
General Ma, you are wholeheartedly loyal.
I should not have suspected His Majesty.
An investigation revealed that the actions on the night Commandery Princess Ma was injured were done by someone on the inside.
That traitor was the Young Master, Gu Qingping, from Tongzhou.
This is the evidence of him colluding with the enemy.
[Emperor of Jin: I have decided to pledge allegiance to the Kingdom of Kin...]
Commandery Princess, the Young Master of Tongzhou, did he really ally with Jin to conspire against us?
This tiger seal was found on the Young Master of Tongzhou.
The tiger seal of the Jin people.
It cannot be wrong.
He wanted to take me away with him, but I was saved by the Prince of Bo.
Furthermore, the assailants that entered the Ma Manor did, in fact, have the tiger seal in their hands.
I witnessed everything.
His Majesty is here!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Ma Fengcheng, you want nothing more than for me to swear a poison oath, right? (T/N: oath if broken curses the swearer)
I will take a blood oath right here that
I'm willing to vow to in front of everyone.
"If General Ma Ying's death
was heartless and an act devoid of justice done by me,
I will be condemned by the heavens, where even death is not a sufficient punishment!"
Your Majesty.
Zhang Jing.
I will now sign this blood oath!
[Signed Blood Oath sworn to by the Emperor of Yang that he had nothing to do with the death of General Ma.]
From this day forth, the Ma Family Army will be surrendered back to the Imperial Court!
We surrender to Your Majesty!
- We surrender to the Imperial Court! Surrendered to His Majesty!
- Surrendered to the Imperial Court! Surrendered to His Majesty!
Surrendered to the Imperial Court! Surrendered to His Majesty!
Father, please wait patiently in heaven.
The Ma Family Army and I
will definitely avenge this blood feud on behalf of the whole Ma family.
Commandery Princess.
Enter.
- Greetings to the Commandery Princess!
- Commandery Princess!
- Commandery Princess! What is this for?
Kneeling like this is not enough to repay the debt of gratitude I owe all the soldiers who, for the sake of Father,
did not hesitate to lead troops into the capital and all who sacrificed their lives in this battle.
I, Zhaixing, thank you on behalf of my deceased father.
- Commandery Princess! Please don't!
- Commandery Princess!
Commandery Princess, if you don't get up
then I will also keep kneeling!
Hurry, hurry, hurry! Come!
Hurry up and get up.
Commandery Princess.
We're doing this of our own free will.
In the future, you don't have to thank us.
We're one family.
This cake is something I made myself!
Whenever I'm unhappy,
I will eat this and it will dissolve my worries!
Commandery Princess, give it a try!
Ma Jing!
Commandery Princess, you must find this laughable.
This younger sister of mine,
her martial arts skills are average,
but when it comes to eating, she's unbeatable!
- Brother!
- Eating wherever she goes.
Half of the army provisions for the Ma Family Army
were all eaten by her!
Brother, you!
Commandery Princess, don't worry. I'll take good care of you!
I'm just grateful that you're safe.
Protecting everyone in the Ma Family Army,
that has always been my father's longstanding wish.
From now on, I will take on this responsibility.
Commandery Princess.
Now, the Ma Family Army and the Imperial Court already have suspicions of each other.
Although His Majesty said he was not going to pursue the matter,
the will of the emperor is unpredictable.
From now on, repairing the relationship between the Ma Family Army and the Imperial Court
must be the goal I work hard toward.
Commandery Princess, you're putting your all into the Ma Family Army,
can't you leave some for yourself?
This time, it was not easy for you to avoid getting murdered by the Emperor of Jin
and also the violent treachery of the Young Feudal Lord of Tongzhou.
Oh, right! You...
are you hurt anywhere?
I was able to survive the calamity this time all thanks to being rescued by the Prince of Bo multiple times.
That's how I was able to come back unharmed.
Speaking of which, the Prince of Bo is my savior.
Commandery Princess, listen to me! I've heard that
the Prince of Bo is surrounded by an evil aura!
He is a demon with a cold temperament!
So if you meet him in the future, you must keep your distance!
Remember that! All right?
While on the road, although the Prince of Bo didn't say any comforting words,
he forced me to face reality and helped me to solve all my problems.
Even when the Young Feudal Lord of Tongzhou was holding me hostage,
he got injured while protecting me.
Brother Fengcheng. Ma Qing! I just remembered something.
I'll step out for a moment!
Commandery Princess! Commandery Princess!
The wounds on your body weren't healed to begin with
and adding the haste of traveling, they have opened up again.
Master.
Master, I've ordered the servants to bring a basin of ice water.
Apply the ice onto your wound for at least one incense stick's time. (T/N: Around half an hour).
You must not go too fast.
I know it now.
You may go now. I can handle this myself.
Commandery Princess Ma.
How did Your Highness know it was me?
I know the sound of your footsteps. What are you doing here?
I came here to check up on Your Highness's wound.
Just then I saw a servant carrying a basin of water, so...
This is not the first time that you've seen my bare skin.
Commandery Princess Ma, isn't it too late to be shy about it now?
Last time, I was too lost in my own thoughts
and forgot about the propriety between males and females. How is that comparable?
What about this time then? Can you leave?
You're injured. Let me take care of you!
No need.
You mustn't move around! Sit still!
Sit still!
These best-quality external wound medicines must be used along with an ice compress
in order to let the medicine have a greater effect.
Your Highness is already injured and it's hard to put on medicine.
Please don't reject my good intentions. Let me return the favor.
Has Your Highness
been through a lot of hurtful experiences?
Are you testing me again to see if I'm the person you knew?
I've already given up on the idea that you're Wolf Boy.
After all, there are a lot of lookalikes in this world.
I just think Your Highness has a high tolerance for pain.
These wounds must have opened up during the haste of travel,
but all the while you didn't utter a word of pain.
But... how can it not hurt?
When you get hurt often,
you get used to it.
If enduring pain can become something you get used to,
then you must have experienced a lot of unimaginable hardships
and sufferings.
May I ask Your Highness,
if you can teach me how to endure pain?
You've always been alone
and enduring things on your own.
During the Soul Separation Syndrome, you forced yourself to wake up.
For the sake of the Ma Family Army, you pulled yourself together.
You're already strong enough, why do you still need me to teach you?
Commandery Princess Ma, no matter the time or place,
you should never shed any tears.
Tonight, in the imperial garden, His Majesty
has invited his officials to a banquet.
That includes all of the generals in your Ma Family Army.
I thank you for the notice, Your Highness.
I understand. I will retreat now.
Your Highness.
Let's hope that from now on,
neither of us will need to endure pain again.
You really know how to act!
His Majesty has arrived.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
The Auspicious Dragon Phoenix Goblet?
Could it be that His Majesty has something important to announce?
The last time he used this goblet
was the day I got married. Why was it brought out today?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
All of you may be excused.
Many thanks, Your Majesty.
You may return to your seats.
Today's incident at the city gate,
no one is allowed to talk about it from now on.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Great! I like it very much!
Sit, sit, sit.
I toast Prime Minister!
The Ma Family Army have been disrespectful on multiple occasions.
Although His Majesty is kind and has granted us no punishment,
I'm willing to drink as a punishment.
I kindly ask Prime Minister to disregard our past misgivings!
Feudal Young Mistress has overstated!
I deeply respect General Ma's wholehearted loyalty!
As His Majesty said,
eliminate enmity with a smile, ending it here!
Zhaixing, looking at you sitting here with ease,
shouldn't you thank another person?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Prince of Bo.
There are no words that can express my gratitude. You saved my life.
The Ma Family Army and I owe you a favor.
We will repay it one day.
Cheers.
Yougui,
don't you think the Feudal Young Mistress and the Prince of Bo are a match?
I'll have her married to Prince of Bo and be my daughter-in-law.
How about it?
Father, I have the same feeling.
They are a perfect match.
(T/N: Idiom - Talented man and a beauty)
Also, Third Brother doesn't have a wife yet.
As a brother, I'm worried for him.
I don't know what Third Brother is thinking.
Third Brother.
The world is uncertain.
Since I'm always in the military, I never thought about getting married.
I'm afraid I'll neglect her.
Father, what Third Brother said, he went around and agreed.
Commandery Princess, don't mind. My son...
He is always...
burying his head in being busy with managing military affairs.
He is a bit unromantic.
I heard that when you were in Kuizhou City,
you were quite picky with all your marriage suitors.
Are you going to dislike
my son, Prince of Bo, too?
Your Majesty, the Commandery Princess absolutely will not!
Sit down, I didn't ask you.
An imperial wedding;
the significance is beyond a romance between a man and a woman.
It is the uniting of a royal and his subject in matrimony.
Naturally, it will dispel Jin Kingdom's scheme to sow discord between us.
It will also better demonstrate my gracious favor towards you,
as well as the Ma Family Army's loyalty towards me.
Commandery Princess, what do you think?
Could it be that you
have something else in mind?
My son won't be a match for you?
Please forgive me.
I don't have anyone in mind.
Then, why are you still wavering?
It is only because I have yet to take revenge against my family's enemy and our country's rival.
Your Majesty, I'm willing to marry Prince of Bo.
I just ask Your Majesty
to permit us to hold the wedding after the two of us have obliterated the Jin Kingdom!
Good!
Then, the wedding
will commence after you complete your wish.
I will now betroth you to the Prince of Bo.
You and I are one family now.
From now on, move into the capital.
On behalf of Ma Ying,
I'll take good care of you.
I thank you, Your Majesty.
Prince of Bo, are you going to come here and thank me with the Feudal Young Mistress?
♫ Without you and without me ♫
Thank you for granting our marriage, Your Majesty.
Yes! Today, I'm happy.
- Zhang Jing.
- Here.
The Dragon Phoenix Goblet! I bestow to the Prince of Bo and the future Princess Consort of Bo a goblet of wine!
Yes, Your Majesty.
♫ People who are in love ♫
♫ Yet have no way to stop and stay ♫
After drinking the wine,
you two will officially agree to get married.
♫ How painful is giving up ♫
♫ Blame me for falling in love with a wild beast
who has lost his way ♫
♫ Paying with my freedom ♫
♫ I stand at the intersection facing you ♫
♫ Personally burying this tenderness ♫
All right, all right. Rise.
Emperor Father has used this Auspicious Dragon Phoenix Goblet to bestow the wine.
It is clear he values this marriage quite considerably.
This joyous occasion has been a long-time coming for the imperial family.
Congratulations, Third Brother and Commandery Princess Ma.
Thank you for your auspicious words, Second Brother.
Go back and sit down.
Play joyful music!
I toast all of my officials!
We thank you, Your Majesty.
Come!
Fill up, fill up!
♫ Even if I hurt again and love again ♫
♫ Do not say again ♫
♫ Seeing you yet I cannot walk forward ♫
I will toast again to good things coming in pairs!
Come.
Please, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
I can't drink too much alcohol so I'll go back and rest.
Oh, all right.
Hurry and rest.
I'll take my leave.
Prince of Bo...
Wolf Boy,
this is my wedding liquor.
I'm sorry.
I can't wait for you anymore.
Today, I have been bestowed a marriage.
The two of us, in the end,
were destined to meet but not fated to be together.
It's you.
Father ordered me to take you back to the palace.
Please.
Let go!
Even if you're ugly,
you're ugly just like him.
Feudal Young Mistress, please conduct yourself.
It's time to go back.
Stop telling me what I should do!
Who I should marry!
I just want to see Wolf Boy right now.
You don't have Wolf Boy's scar and sincerity.
You and Wolf Boy have such different identities and status.
Who are you to look so much like him?
So what about Prince of Bo?
Feudal Young Mistress Ma,
the person you always mistake me for,
is he... very important to you?
If not important,
why leave a lantern riddle with "wolf" written on it?
(T/N: One type of Lantern Festival Riddle Game)
You're still thinking about him.
Actually,
you are Wolf Boy. Am I right?
♫ Used to the depth of the darkness ♫
♫ No matter how wild, there is no fear ♫
♫ Waiting for a star to fall to see who
its afterglow will illuminate ♫
♫ Of the same kind as the banished ♫
♫ Hiding the loneliness in defense ♫
♫ But gentleness is always invincible ♫
♫ I am already used to viewing from high above
in the mountain alone ♫
Wolf Boy,
I truly,
truly from my heart, wanted to tell you this.
♫ I have yet to encounter any challenge that I find difficult ♫
♫ Even going against the tides, my vision is still steady,
manners is still fierce ♫
♫ I tell myself to keep pushing on by feeling ♫
To me, your existence
is just a stumbling block.
I really wanted to kick you away.
Wolves and humans can never be together!
Don't you understand!
In other peoples' eyes, you're just a monster!
Get lost!
Don't be stupid.
I‘m not the Wolf Boy that you can easily betray.
I don't care about what you say!
You just not worthy of me!
Get lost!
♫ But gentleness is always invincible ♫
Feudal Young Mistress! Feudal Young Mistress!
Where are you, Feudal Young Mistress?
Feudal Young Mistr—
♫ The pupil is no longer black, white or grey ♫
Feudal Young Mistress!
Feudal Young Mistress! How come...
How come you fell into the water?
Stand up quickly.
Are you all right?
Come.
Slowly.
Are you all right?
How did you fall into the water? What happened?
Wolf Boy.
This is the palace. How could there be a Wolf Boy?
Just now, he...
really was here.
I chased him away.
Wolf Boy.
Let's go back.
Wolf Boy...
you left.
It's good you left.
You left...
so that you cannot see Xing'er getting married.
You've suffered, Feudal Young Mistress.
Let's go back and rest.
It's all right, don't cry.
Wolf Boy will be happy for you. Let's go back and sleep.
Let's go home.
- Let's go.
- Wolf Boy.
Where is my and Second Highness's horse carriage?
Prime Minister, please ease your anger. I will go urge them immediately.
Lord Major, you are the biological cousin of the Fourth Prince
and the biological nephew of the late empress. Did you see the prime minister?
He didn't say anything when he left.
He...
[Major Yang Hou]
...is just relying on the fact that he is the father-in-law of the second prince.
But he is not aware that
that son-in-law of his is nothing but the offspring of a Bozhou military prostitute.
As for if he is actually of His Majesty's true dragon bloodline,
(T/N: Chinese emperors were said to be descendants of dragon gods)
I‘m still suspicious of it.
Prime Minister,
I didn't think that even though I came so late,
my horse carriage would already be here.
I can tell with one look that your horse
has an unbridled wildness.
It is quite normal then for it to go on a rampage.
It seems this person is like his horse, reckless yet with a mouth that cannot shut up.
Father-in-Law!
There's no need.
Major Yang,
you always tease that my royal mother has a military prostitute background.
You may not be tired of saying it,
but I do not hear anything new.
All these years, you have been repeating it over and over again,
could it be you only have this one trick?
If you continue and don't think of how to improve on it,
even I will feel ashamed on your behalf.
Second Prince has a virtuous character,
but I am afraid that Major is in the prime of his youth
and is as reckless as his horse.
There will be a day when both he and his horse will get thrown off their feet. (T/N: They will suffer a crushing defeat)
Prime Minister has overstated.
If you want to flip over a horse,
that will be hard.
This treasured horse comes from Qitan, it is one of the best warhorses!
It is not some crossbred horse
and is even less likely to be a wild horse from an unknown origin.
Its blood is pure,
just like the Fourth Prince, who will be returning from Qitan sooner or later.
He is the only biological son the empress had before she passed.
No one can compare.
You-- You mock Second Prince!
I, his subordinate,
will wholeheartedly await Fourth Prince's return.
I'll take my leave.
I won't send you off.
[Flowing Backward by Jolin Tsai 蔡依林]
♫ Separation is not unbearable ♫
♫ What is unbearable is when two hearts
are not truly separated ♫
♫ I had to move forward, but I did not say ♫
♫ That the only one who can change me is still you ♫
♫ I really want to run into your embrace ♫
♫ Thank you for indulging me to be superstitious ♫
♫ Flowing backward to when we started to love,
when there is still no hurt ♫
♫ Forever being together ♫
♫ Going backward to that second in time ♫
♫ Firmly holding your hand and keep walking like that ♫
♫ I am willing to wait, wait until you understand ♫
♫ Eternity actually is hiding within the love that we believed in ♫
♫ I really want to run into your embrace ♫
♫ Thank you for indulging me to be superstitious ♫
♫ Returning to when we started to love,
when there is still no hurt ♫
♫ Forever being together ♫