[Who Am I (我是谁) by Jolin Tsai (蔡依林) & Jony J (肖佳)]
♫ Used to the depth of the darkness ♫
♫ No matter how wild, there is no fear ♫
♫ Waiting for a star to fall to see who its afterglow will illuminate
(I tell myself to keep pushing on by feeling, it’s history in the making) ♫
♫ Of the same kind as the banished ♫
♫ Hiding the loneliness in defense
(Climbing mountains and cliffs) ♫
♫ But gentleness is always invincible
(I’m earth-shatteringly alone, with no purpose and no worry, just so I can push on harder) ♫
♫ Refusing to compromise with fate
because my heart has a home ♫
♫ It's yours; I don't belong to anyone else ♫
♫ (But let me know who I am and give me a destination) ♫
♫ Who am I if I didn’t meet you? ♫
♫ (You took away what I care about and all my attention) ♫
♫ Who am I without you? ♫
♫ (But let me know who I am and give me a destination) ♫
♫ When a puppet hanging on a string has experienced warmth ♫
♫ The pupil is no longer black, white, or grey
(You took away what I care about and all my attention) ♫
(But let me know who I am and give me a destination) ♫
♫ You know who I am ♫
[The Wolf]
Lord Bo barged into the ancestral temple to save me. Can he come back unharmed?
[Episode 9]
It's not difficult for Lord of Bo to escape unharmed.
The difficult thing is your opinion on Lin Guang's case.
I knelt in the temple thinking about this.
By doing so, I have concluded that, first, Lin Guang is not an assassin.
Otherwise, he'd rather die than get caught.
Second. If he really wanted to kill himself,
or he knew he would be dead if he followed the prime minister
but he still went with him,
that means he was willing to sacrifice himself
to protect someone or something.
Your reasoning is almost the same as Master's.
I'm impressed.
Of course! Our princess is very clever.
As for my opinion on Lin Guang's case,
since I was the one who chose to believe in his kindness,
I'm not going to force out the truth on what he was trying to protect with his life.
I will regard this case as a rock dropped in the sea.
Housekeeper Wen, you especially came here to talk with me about this.
Is it not just to remind me that there are things in the court
that I shouldn't get to the bottom of?
Lord of Bo also warned me before
and now I get it.
Feudal Young Mistress is sensible, pretty, and intelligent.
You're a good match for His Highness.
Master asked me to invite you to meet him in the adjacent courtyard tonight.
Adjacent courtyard? Which courtyard?
Is that the one where others are not allowed to go in?
Exactly.
It seems Master sees you in a different way now.
May I ask if you're willing to come?
Not going.
These are gifts from Feudal Young Mistress Ma.
Since it's her kindness,
take it all.
- Thank you.
Don't thank me, though.
Master, sorry for being bold.
Back then, I was afraid you were just being rash,
so I didn't dare to throw it away.
Will she come on time?
Her reply is, "Not going to leave if I don't see him."
Feudal Young Mistress, please go in.
Master has been waiting for you for a while.
Thank you.
This way.
Fireflies flitting the hall during sunset, while I wallow in thoughts and my heart is at a loss.
The lonely lamp wick burned out, yet I still could not fall asleep.
By slowly counting the drumbeat of the clock, the night began to grow long;
Looking at the bright faraway sea of stars,
until a ray of light is spitted at the east.
The dead and the living were parted for a year now;
Her soul came not in dreams to see the brokenhearted.
Your Highness also knows "The Everlasting Regret"?
Bai Juyi also now under the name Letian.
His name means easy and relaxed,
yet he wrote a poem like "The Everlasting Regret."
I want to know what he is resenting?
Can he stop hating in the end?
And does Your Highness have the answer?
The last two verses answered it.
The boundless sky and endless earth may pass away;
But this vow unfulfilled will be regretted for aye.
Has Your Highness forgotten the two verses before those?
If our two hearts as firm as gold should remain;
We will meet again in Heaven or on Earth.
On the seventh day of the seventh month, let us meet at the Long Life Hall;
Whispering in each other's ear during midnight when no one is around.
On high, we'd be two lovebirds flying wing to wing;
On Earth, we'd be two trees with branches twined from spring to spring.
So, how do you interpret that?
I think as long as it's in the middle of the night, when no one else is around,
when the fireflies are dancing, anything could happen.
Bai Letian said that if two hearts remain as firm as gold,
they will eventually meet whether in Heaven or on Earth.
That's the imagination of a poet.
I like this imagination
and your courtyard, too.
It's just your courtyard is so beautiful,
why do you forbid others to come?
Why did you invite me to come here today?
Because the sago palm has bloomed.
You're the first person to come to my forbidden area.
Do you know why I saved you?
Because I thought our betrothal was all about self gains
so I had prejudices against you.
Until last night,
I accidentally discovered that you are indeed a kind-hearted person
who will persist until the end and disregard the misunderstanding of others
just to protect what you believe in.
Thank you for your kind words.
I have prepared a feast for you.
Please.
I can't drink much.
I'm afraid I'll be like during our wedding betrothal night and trouble you.
I promise not to put any blame on you.
That night, you mistook me for someone else.
Ma Jing once told me you had a friend as a child,
named Wolf Boy, raised by wolves.
I guess he must be the friend whom you said looks like me.
The chronic injury on your leg was also due to him.
Wolf Boy was my important childhood friend.
The day we parted,
we both got hurt.
I just had an injury on my leg.
But he was hurt badly due to my deception.
I knew that his chances of survival were almost zero,
but I'd rather believe that he's still alive.
It's just we haven't met yet.
There's so much I want to say to him,
but there's no more chances.
I have many things I want to experience with him,
but that's impossible, too.
How did he call you
when you were together back then?
He called me...
Xing'er.
Xing... Xing'er.
All these years,
I always hoped Wolf Boy would call me Xing'er again.
But even if he was still alive,
he would only feel hate towards me.
I betrayed him.
But you didn't mean it.
Your cruelness was to protect him.
Even though he's dead,
he surely knows that everything you did was for him.
He would only feel grateful and guilty towards you.
I know you are just trying to comfort me.
I was a bit confused earlier and thought that Wolf Boy had forgiven me.
Xing'er,
Wolf Boy will forgive you.
Although you both look similar,
you aren't him.
How would you know what's in his mind?
But he surely knows that you have suffered a lot.
He was gone.
You were put in confinement.
All these years, did you ever truly feel happy?
♫ Looking past the starry night ♫
I once was.
Once.
♫ Wait for me; Falling down for you ♫
♫ Falling down; Igniting the fireworks of love ♫
On Langshou Mountain,
we were running together.
He showed me the wind.
♫ Silence; Falling down soundless ♫
♫ Falling down ♫
Let me hear the sound of butterflies flapping their wind.
He ate meat buns with me.
He took the candied hawthorns from me.
Wolf Boy still likes to eat meat buns.
Really?
What about candied hawthorns?
Yeah.
Xing'er, what about you? Do you still like to eat them?
Meat buns. Yes.
They just don't taste good anymore.
Candied hawthorns. Yes.
They're just not sweet anymore.
No matter what I do or eat,
they are not as tasty or sweet anymore.
I didn't like to eat meat buns before.
But they became tasty because I ate them with Wolf Boy.
Candied hawthorns also became sweet when I ate them with him.
Back then, the day after you disappeared,
I bought a stick of candied hawthorns
but it was so bitter.
So bitter.
All these years, all candied hawthorns are bitter.
Bitter...
Not anymore. Not anymore.
As long as Wolf Boy returns, I won't feel bitter anymore.
Wolf Boy can't come back.
Just let it go.
You've been blaming yourself for so long.
It's time to put the past behind you.
Live your life.
♫ I have always been guarding ♫
♫ Nothing has changed ♫
♫ Like that star a billion years ago ♫
♫ Still twinkling ♫
Was that kiss real
or was it just my imagination?
Whose kiss?
You scared me!
What are you doing here?
I'm supposed to be here.
But you, Young Feudal Mistress,
were out all night.
That's not normal.
Tell me everything.
Under such a perfect night,
you and Lord of Bo were all alone in his courtyard.
Did you...
No! Absolutely not!
I was drunk and confused.
Drunk and confused?
Well, in that case, when you were drunk,
you were asking Lord of Bo to kiss you?
I didn't take him as Lord of Bo, but Wolf Boy.
Wolf Boy?
How come?
Young Mistress, come on.
You're Lord of Bo's wife now. Right?
How could you think about another man?
You're right.
I should stop taking him as Wolf Boy.
Even if he shows me kindness out of a moment of confusion,
I shouldn't be careless.
Did you...
Wen Yan,
how do you judge the current situation and respond accordingly?
I think each has its own merits.
May I ask who the enemy is so I can decide what to do?
Please enlighten me.
If it's not a friend, then it's an enemy. Don't you see?
Is it so hard?
I can't believe you and Mo Xiao don't have a plan!
Sorry.
Master, may I dare to ask if Feudal Young Mistress is a friend or foe?
Neither of them.
I see.
Master, it turns out you're seriously picking your clothes this early in the morning to please the Feudal Young Mistress!
No need for all this trouble. Just tell it to me directly.
I'll just ask Ma Jing what clothes the Young Mistress likes on men.
That solves it, right?
Must I have a reason to try on clothes?
If so, I'll give you one.
Besides warding off heat and cold, warding off wind and rain,
covering our bodies, making us look beautiful,
clothes also show etiquette and honor.
Are those enough?
I'm sorry. Forgive me, please.
Leave it. You are so unprofessional.
I should have asked Hai Die.
The one on the left.
Didn't he wear that the day before yesterday?
Maybe he likes it a lot.
Master.
You disobeyed the imperial edict for her, then invited her into your forbidden courtyard.
Does this mean you will completely obey the imperial edict
and treat her as your wife-to-be?
Then, shall I still continue to keep an eye on her?
No need to monitor her like a criminal,
but keep her safe.
I went to the palace to rescue her. Father knows it.
But rumors are already spreading in the court.
Many political enemies have been hiding in the shadows, waiting for their chance.
They dare not hurt me, but Ma Zhaixing will be an easy target.
I will send the Night Fiends to better monitor the activities of court officials.
Listen up.
As long as she's the princessconsort bestowed by His Majesty,
I will keep her safe.
Yes, Your Highness.
Wen Yan, did you get the things ready?
No offense. But will Young Mistress like that kind of gift?
She will.
Prince of Bo asks you to go to the training field.
Feudal Young Mistress.
After last night,
you should be closer to Lord of Bo.
Why are you nervous?
That's exactly the reason why I'm nervous.
When we meet later, it'll be so awkward.
Young Mistress, where are you going? Come back!
His Highness is not afraid.
What are you afraid of?
Isn't he handsome?
Young Mistress, look.
Your future husband looking so valiant and mighty is so charming!
Come out here!
Come out, Young Mistress.
Calm down.
Three moves will be all.
Don't be shy.
You are here.
You must be curious as to why I asked you to come here so early in the morning.
Martial arts can help you defend yourself and make you strong.
It's good for your leg recovery.
You want to teach me martial arts?
How did you know I'd always wanted to learn to use weapons
but my mother disapproved,
so I never got a chance.
I'm glad you like it.
Come on.
What kind of weapon do you like?
Be careful.
A long weapon isn't suitable for you.
Pick something else.
Please help me choose one.
Wen Yan.
Yes, Your Highness.
So you had prepared it beforehand.
It's a wolf bow.
A part of my collection.
Since you gave me a gift, that is my gift to you.
What's more, a bow and arrow is a powerful long-range weapon.
It's perfect for you.
It has a beautiful totem.
It must be pretty expensive.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Come here.
♫ Eternity ♫
♫ May not be ♫
♫ Far away ♫
♫ Lingering on love for one more day ♫
♫ My heartbeat kept repeating ♫
How did Master know that Feudal Young Mistress would love that bow?
Look at them.
Is Master teaching the Young Mistress how to shoot arrows or is he courting her?
♫ Always kept thinking about it ♫
♫ No space to step back to ♫
♫ Already surrounded by love ♫
♫ One more gaze ♫
♫ And let's see who will melt whom ♫
♫ One more ♫
♫ Hugging practice until perfection is achieved ♫
♫ A little bit more ♫
It seems that you're talented.
I have a good teacher.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Come back to the palace with me.
I found an imperial physician to treat your leg.
♫ Lingering in love for one more day ♫
Imperial Physician,
Young Feudal Mistress has delicate health and is afraid of pain.
You'd better be careful.
Yes, Your Highness.
It's okay.
Go on.
Young Mistress, I am done with my examination.
Is it possible to heal her leg?
Lord of Bo, the injury has been too long ago.
Her muscles, blood, and bones are weak.
The right leg is worse than the left.
But luckily, you stopped her from kneeling too long,
or else the consequences would have been dire.
I want you to do everything you can to cure her.
Yes, Your Highness.
I will surely do my best.
But Young Mistress' legs will be too hard to cure even if Hua Tuo (best ancient doctor) is reborn.
Fortunately, it doesn't affect her daily activity.
I'm going to prescribe some medicine that can strengthen her bone, muscle, qi, and blood.
Take it once a day and have it for a month.
Remember not to put pressure to your legs during the course of
the medication, like riding a horse.
If you get hurt again, it'll be worse.
Your Highness,
if there's nothing else, please excuse me.
Did you hear what the doctor said?
It's an old illness. All these years, I've seen many doctors.
They all said the same thing. I can even recite them.
I will ask around for excellent physicians among the commoners.
The world is big.
There must be someone who can cure your legs.
It wasn't your fault.
Why would you do so much for me?
Because you are betrothed to me.
It is my duty.
You will do your duty.
And I will do mine.
I'll try to be a competent princess consort.
Your Highness,
His Majesty asked you to meet him in the imperial study
and discuss the emissary's visit.
Get some rest. I'll be right back.
Father has summoned me.
He'll be here in a minute.
How are Feudal Young Mistress Ma's legs?
The vital part was not damaged, right?
She is fine.
How are you?
I'm standing right in front of you. I'm fine.
Or do you think I'm the one who's supposed to be badly hurt?
It's me who found out the truth behind Lin Guang's case.
Well done.
Though it's late, will you accept my apology?
This case almost jeopardized the innocent Zhaixing.
Thank God, she's fine,
or I'd surely make you explain.
Your Majesty is here!
Greetings, Father Emperor!
Those are the memorials from the ministers in the levee.
They all plead on your behalf, Prince of Yun, begging me to allow you to make up for your crime by leading the army.
I'm shocked.
But my words are to be taken seriously.
I've already asked Prince of Bo to take care of the Minister from Qitan.
If you really want to make up for your mistake, you may assist him.
I'd like to see that.
Prince of Bo, what's your opinion?
Father Emperor,
Second Brother's diplomatic skills have always been better than mine.
If he's willing to help me, it'd be great.
Yougui, what do you think?
I made a terrible mistake.
Yet Father and Third Brother are willing to give me a chance to make up for it.
I will not dishonor Your Majesty's grace.
I'll try my best to assist Third Brother.
Great that you know to reflect and repent.
Five days from now,
a little princess will come instead of an ambassador.
Three years ago, you sent Youzhen to Qitan.
Have you seen her there?
Emperor Father, Princess Bao Na is like an old friend.
She is the favorite little princess of the King of Qitan.
When I was there,
I saw with my own eyes that the king listened to whatever she said and favored her.
Father Emperor, I think taking good care of Princess Bao Na
will help us in borrowing manpower from them later.
Good point.
Girls are indecisive and soft-hearted.
Prince of Bo,
I command you to be polite to her. No negligence is allowed.
Don't piss her off.
You two handle this matter well on my behalf.
As for borrowing manpower, I will not allow failure.
I will obey your command.
Your Highness!
I asked you to wait inside. Why did you come out?
I've rested for a while.
I came out after taking the medicine prescribed by the imperial physician.
Don't be nervous.
Greetings, Second Prince.
No need to be polite.
Didn't you meet with His Majesty to discuss the coming ambassador?
Why so glum?
Did somethiing go wrong?
No.
It's just the coming ambassador is actually Princess Bao Na.
Isn't that better? It means the King of Qitan takes this visit seriously.
I am afraid she's coming for personal matters.
Does she have something to do with Prince of Bo?
I have nothing to do with her.
Years ago, Third Brother and I escorted Fourth Brother to Qitan.
The young princess fell in love with him at first sight,
and even asked the king to decree that she marry him.
If it weren't for their tradition disallowing the princess to be married off to a faraway land,
I'm afraid that a marriage engagement would have been made at that time.
I never thought that the cold-faced Prince of Bo was so popular with girls!
[Flowing Backward 倒流 by Jolin Tsai 蔡依林]
♫ Separation is not unbearable ♫
♫ What is unbearable is when two hearts
are not truly separated ♫
♫ I had to move forward, but I did not say ♫
♫ That the only one who can change me is still you ♫
♫ I really want to run into your embrace ♫
♫ Thank you for indulging me to be superstitious ♫
♫ Flowing backward to when we started to love,
when there is still no hurt ♫
♫ Forever being together ♫
♫ Going backward to that second in time ♫
♫ Firmly holding your hand and keep walking like that ♫
♫ I am willing to wait, wait until you understand ♫
♫ Eternity actually is hiding within the love that we believed in ♫
♫ I really want to run into your embrace ♫
♫ Thank you for indulging me to be superstitious ♫
♫ Returning to when we started to love,
when there is still no hurt ♫
♫ Forever being together ♫