I'm just trying to do my best.
So I can you know,
get it over and done with.
Move on with my life.
Get out of here and go back
to my life as a designer.
That's my job,
help you to finish your
community service quickly.
So you can go back to the life
that you want.
Have I not made myself clear?
I never intended to stay
here in Sorsogon.
I don't want to get involved
in that Pili nut business.
With the same logic
that I have a life in Manila.
I'm a fashion designer there.
I have so much on my plate.
I have no time for this.
My life is there.
So anything under my name,
you can do whatever you want
with it.
Even if you feed that
to whale shark, I don't care.
You are annoying.
This project has nothing to do
with her.
It's just a coincidence,
that's where we want to go
where she's making a mess.
I've been watching her
videos lately
and she seems to be doing
pretty well.
She spearheaded the waste
management program in an area.
Please, Dad, the last thing
that I want to happen there
is to mingle
with your girlfriend.
Hello?
I just want to tell you
that there will be a change in
your community service tomorrow.
We're leaving earlier because
where we are going is far.
So prepare yourself because you
will have a long day tomorrow.
So don't call me anymore
because I have to go to sleep.
It's already late. We have
to be early tomorrow, right?
So fussy!
The two are still like cat
and dog.
That's only in the beginning.
I knew those two very well
since they were kids.
No matter how deep the wound is
in a person's heart
time will heal it.
I'm so annoyed.
Someone keeps on calling me
about the schedule change.
Who?
The one who handles
my community service.
Well in that case,
if you're early tomorrow
I won't keep you up.
I just called because
I wanted to inform you
that Tiffany is going
to Sorsogon.
She's doing a school
project there.
I'm thinking that
this is a good opportunity
for the two of you
to become close.
It's your ex.
Why is she texting at this hour?
- What are you talking about?
- Give me the phone.
- Oh my gosh...
- Tiffany...
- you two are talking again?
- give me the phone.
You know what, stop the car!
Stop the car! What's with you?
Tiff?
I want to be alone.
Leave!
Fine.
Wow!
About the other day,
I'm sorry if I offended you
when I said that I don't
have anything to do
with the Pili nut business.
It's just that I'm under so much
pressure with Celestial.
If she is very eager
to leave this house,
for me, I can't wait for her
to get out of our lives.
I don't know
why you still believe
that this person
will have a heart.
Sebastian, enough!
Is there no closer community
service?
I can throw away
our neighbor's garbage.
I mean that's still the same.
It's taking a long time.
I feel so exposed in this car.
We're here.
Do you need help?
No.
Is this it?
Mother, why do we need
to come here?
Because the most beautiful
handicrafts
in Sorsogon are here.
Isn't it that you want to be
a fashion designer one day?
You can get inspiration
for your fashion show.
You can also use these materials
to make bags, belt
or even accessories.
Why are the handicrafts
better here?
Because these are made by hands.
Look at this.
There's a tight knot here,
there is a loose weaving.
There are uneven parts here.
Like this one?
Yes, it's not perfect.
There are mistakes.
It's like reminding us the most
important lesson in our life.
Which is?
That nobody is perfect.
But it doesn't mean, my child,
that if we did something wrong
or do something bad
our lives will no longer
be beautiful and colorful.
Isn't that beautiful?
You can put this on the side
of a shoe.
That's something unique.
Even this one?
You can maybe...
- Maybe...
- Can we use this on a dress?
Yes, it can be used on a dress,
right?
You have a lot to...
Tiffany, it's your fault.
You have the guts to walk out,
but you didn't bring
your phone with you.
You left it with Clau.
And you have no cash.
Oh my gosh, how can you be
that stupid?
That Cynthia girl is right.
Maybe I'm really not that
bright.
Where am I?
I've already walked a long way.
Maybe I'm already in Cebu
or Davao...
or Palawan.
Oh my gosh, I need to be
in Sorsogon.
How mad this is,
how mad this is.
It's hopeless.
I'm so thirsty, I'm so tired.
Oh my God...
Hey!
Oh my gosh.
There's a tight knot here,
there is a loose weaving.
There are uneven parts here.
There are mistakes.
Look at this.
It's like reminding us the most
important lesson in our life.
Which is?
That nobody is perfect.
But it doesn't mean, my child,
that if we did something wrong
or do something bad
our lives will no longer
be beautiful and colorful.
You know you should watch where
you're going.
Miss, do you own this road?
Why? Do you own this road?
Do you have sapak ?
(Problem with the head)
What is sapak ?
But it sounds so negative.
Do you think this face
has sapak, really?
Okay.
There's an arrogant
tourist again.
Are you from Manila?
People from Manila are crazy.
You know what whatever
that is...
that negative remark, whatever.
What is your problem
if I'm from Manila?
I'm sorry if you're just
a provincial guy.
- Okay.
- Wait, wait...
Can you help me?
Now, you're asking for help.
Because my boyfriend
abandoned me.
I have no cash and cellphone.
So...
can I borrow your phone?
Thank you.
There's no service here.
You just said you need a
cellphone, not a signal.
Okay, Miss, let's go
where there's a signal.
You should come with me.
But I have to deliver
something first.
Let's go?
Miss, do you a need signal
or not?
What?
Sorry, Mom.
James and I fought.
He's been a jerk.
I'll have you picked up.
You should go home.
No, Mom. Please don't.
Of course, Mom, I won't let
that jerk
ruin my academic records.
And even affect my work to
graduate with high honors!
Besides, I'm with a friend.
Actually, I'm using
his phone to call you.
Can I talk to your friend?
Sure.
Can you pretend that
you're my friend?
All of a sudden I'm her friend.
Hello?
Yes, I'm your daughter's friend
here.
She is safe.
Don't worry.
What is your name?
Sebastian, you can
also call me Basti.
Basti, can you really make sure
that she's safe?
Yes, Ma'am. She's safe here.
Okay, can you please send me
your full name and your address?
And I hope you don't mind
I'll call this number first
until she gets her cellphone
back.
And also I'll send you
her emergency fund.
Is that okay?
Yes, no problem.
Thank you so much.
Can I talk to her again?
Okay.
Mom?
Tiff, I don't like this.
Maybe we should call your dad.
Mom, please don't.
Please.
He will just ask me to go
to his mistress.
If only I don't have an
important business meeting,
I'll go there.
I know, Mom. I know.
Promise, I'll call you
from time to time.
Can you just trust me on this?
Please, Mom?
I trust you.
Once my business engagement
is over, I'll go there.
I love you.
There's a charge for that.
It's three thousand
five hundred pesos.
Sure, I'm rich.
Wow, she's arrogant.
What did you say?
Nothing. I said humble...
- Humble?
- Humble.
This is a nice place.
Wait...
only locals would know
that there's a signal
in this area.
Me of all people.
I'm pure-blooded Uragon.
I know Bicolandia and all the
areas here that has signal.
Well...
you're exactly the right person
I'm looking for.
Well, this is a surprise.
Is Tiffany missing again,
that's why you're here?
Tiffany is out of town
for a school project
and I'm here because I want
to talk to you.
It's not our intention,
but this place became a
destination for women.
Single mothers or women
who are unnoticed by society.
What we really want
is to give jobs
and make the people
of this community
and the other Barangays
that they have a place to go
if they need a livelihood.
But more than that,
we want to promote our tradition
in handicraft making.
That's why, we're happy
that you're here
and giving us a little
attention.
Someone who is accomplished
and a known fashion designer.
What can I do to help you?
Promoting us is more than
enough.
You know with the low cost
of materials from China,
it affected us a bit.
But if you will promote us,
maybe we can fight
because there's a respected
fashion designer
who believes in us.
The truth is we know you.
We know your mother Lucinda.
A lot of people here say
that you already forgot
where you came from.
I told them that one day
you will go back
and introduce us to the world.
If you need handicrafts
or materials just tell us.
We will give you a discount
like what we gave your mother
back then.
Thank you.
Look at these.
Basti will pay you.
So, now what?
You want me to be your assistant
here in Sorsogon?
You should pay me
two thousand pesos.
Not an assistant, Basti.
I just need someone to guide me,
so I can execute properly
my project here in Sorsogon.
If you need a Tour Guide,
you should go to the Tourism
Office.
That's the problem, Basti.
The tourism officers only show
the good side of Sorsogon.
For me, I want to know
the whole Sorsogon.
Okay, I'll think about it.
How much are you?
Hey, I'm not after the money.
Plus five thousand pesos?
Deal, five thousand kisses
on my butt.
You're rude.
You're rude too.
Whatever!
Can I borrow your phone?
I need to call Clau.
Maybe she's coming.
I just need to check, okay.
There's a signal here.
Tiff, are you okay?
What happened?
Is that James?
So are you done being insecure?
I don't want to see your face!
That's enough!
Bro, that's enough.
Who the hell are you?
I'm just the one
who promised her mom
that I won't allow a fool
like you to disrespect her.
I'm a fool?
Is that it?
- Do you want a fight?
- James!
James, what's with you?
Is there a problem here?
I'll handle this. I'm okay.
Tiff.
Bro, do you have a problem?
Maybe you have forgotten,
this is my territory.
James, let's go.
That's enough.
James, James!
Thank you. I'm okay.
Okay.
There you go.
That's right, Celeste.
You know it takes years to be
an expert in making handicrafts.
But with you, it's natural.
No, you are better than me.
There should be a rhythm.
That's important.
Not too fast, but not too slow.
Are you done?
I want to go home.
Why? Is there a problem?
I just want to go home.
That concludes our business.
With your investment,
you are now a part
of my group of companies
as a minority stake.
Why are you doing this?
It's about Tonito.
What about Tonito?
I'll make you a daily report.
You already rendered
thirty hours.
Just record it,
so we're synchronized.
By the way, you don't have
to pick me up tomorrow.
I'm okay, I can manage.
Why?
He is such a know-it-all person.
He told me "I know
the real you".
What's that?
Why are you laughing?
I'm thrilled.
Girl, why are you thrilled?
She's very different.
She's just wearing heels and now
she thinks so highly of herself.
She dresses up in fashion
and she's very good now
at speaking English.
But she's the same person.
She is still an Uragon.
I even made her eat
chili ice cream.
Does that local guy like you?
Or maybe it's you who likes him.
Don't talk to me ever again,
you bastard!
If I were to set myself up
for another rejection,
it must be for something
worth fighting for.
I still love Tonito
more than I will ever admit.
I'm just on a water break...
Didn't I tell you
that you can't accept calls
while you're on duty?
What do you mean
you don't understand?
Something wrong?
Do you think I still haven't
proven anything, cousin?
What do you mean?
Am I still that worthless
fresh graduate
that my sister Vivian
said before?
Celeste is just tough now,
but you can soften her heart.
There's nothing love cannot do.
I'm really, really sorry.
That's another 100 hours added
to your community service.
What?