This is just my opinion.
I really feel that
there's something with Mikoy.
What do you mean something?
What else? He still likes you.
Who's there?
Why didn't you lock the door?
I'm leaving...
This is sickening.
You can't trust that guy.
Babe, please don't act
like a child.
We've already talked about this.
I know but sleeping beside him
is not part of the deal.
He might do something to you.
He's going crazy.
You know we're quits already.
I fooled you before.
You saw me naked today, right?
- It's fair.
- Celeste!
Mikoy!
May-May, you should slow down
with your drinking.
I have no plans of taking home
two drunk women.
I saw everything.
As in everything?
Yes, in his naked glory.
Alcohol really does something
different.
Earlier,
you could not look at me.
Now you're talking
as if I don't exist.
I need to pee.
I'll just go to the bathroom.
Is that okay?
They say that if you're drunk,
you can say what you want
that you can't say
if you're normal.
Okay, game. Let's test.
Pretend that we didn't
part ways.
Okay, it didn't happen.
Tonito boy didn't come
into my life.
We're still a couple
and I'm like this.
Like this, like me
and all that jazz.
Will you still love me?
Why are you speechless?
Last night was terrible.
I was so wasted.
I drank a lot.
You don't remember what you did
and you've said?
Did I say something distasteful?
It's more like naughty.
- Naughty?
- No, more of kinky.
Kinky?
- No.
- You shouldn't drink
what you can't handle so you
won't do anything outrageous.
I don't feel well.
It's like I have a fever.
I'm hot.
You're not hot today.
You were hot last night.
Mikoy, what's with you?
Don't be like that.
My goodness, this is beautiful!
I'm in awe.
Wow!
You have a headache earlier.
What? Let's go home?
Take a rest.
No, I feel better now.
It's beautiful here.
Do you like it?
I love it.
Wait, why did you bring me here?
This is where we'll do
community service?
Yes.
We're going to pick sunflowers
because there will be an event
later in the city hall.
There's a cooking contest.
It's sponsored by the LGU.
So technically,
this is your community service.
Wait, is Grandmother Ikay
included the cooking contest?
Yes. It's the best of the best
who cook pinangat.
There will be a chef judge
from Manila.
But she's a local from Sorsogon.
Wow, for sure Grandmother Ikay
will win.
Her pinangat is delicious.
You can't really say.
Yes, her pinangat is delicious
but sometimes, people's taste
also evolves, right?
Just like you,
you have a lot of attitude
that you got from Manila.
Got it?
You're really picking on me.
You know you will miss me
when I go back to Manila.
For sure, I will miss
you're being a troublemaker.
And what you say
when you're drunk.
What did I say when I was drunk?
Nothing, but you're more active.
Animal.
Let's go.
This is beautiful.
Wow!
It's beautiful.
Wow, look at the colors.
You know,
sunflowers always face...
- the sun.
- The sun,
that's why it's called
sunflowers.
Oh my God.
And at night?
They sleep.
It's beautiful.
I love it.
Grandmother Ikay.
Hey...
good thing you arrived.
I have supporters now.
I'm so nervous.
Grandmother Ikay, you can do it.
Your pinangat
is already a winner.
Thank you and you still believe
in me.
But I heard they will make
a secret recipe.
My only secret in cooking
is being happy.
Because if you're happy
with what you do,
your food will be delicious.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Let's fix this.
That's beautiful.
- Wait, I'll fix this first.
- Are you okay, Grandmother?
Yes.
What else do you need?
Can you still manage?
You might pass out
before you cook.
Yes.
Mr. Nanding, thank you
for letting us stay here
in your house.
I'm also sorry last night
if you didn't fall asleep
right away.
No, that's okay.
It's us who should apologize
to you because we disturbed you.
That's nothing.
Besides, you're no longer
a stranger to us.
When the time comes that you
and Sebastian will get married,
you should get me
as your Principal Sponsor.
Yes, of course, Mr. Nanding.
You have to be our godfather
so when Tiffany becomes my wife,
there's someone
who will give us advice
if we have a misunderstanding.
She is the jealous type.
Basti, who would not be jealous?
Your dimples attract women.
You, too. You know Tiffany,
I fell in love
with that dimples of yours.
Why?
- There's a mosquito.
- Yes, there's a mosquito.
- Thank you, James.
- Mr. Ben!
Good morning.
Sir, is your jeep okay now?
- It's okay now.
- Good.
You three can go home.
Yes!
You should eat first.
Have a seat.
- Your breakfast is delicious.
- Let's eat, Sir.
Hey, Celeste
is really very beautiful.
Grandmother, you startled me.
You're caught already.
Now, tell me you're not in love
with her.
You talk too much, Grandmother.
It just so happened
when you saw me
the camera was focused on her.
I'll be taking a video
of everything.
You're denying it.
You're caught already.
You talk a lot.
Celeste might hear
what you're saying.
Hey...
- There's nothing.
- What are you arguing about?
Nothing.
Grandmother is getting ready.
- Yes.
- Go ahead, Grandmother.
Good luck, Grandmother.
Thank you.
Good luck.
We will time this contest.
The contestants
will begin simultaneously.
We will give 30 minutes
to cook the famous dish
here in Sorsogon.
That is the pinangat or tilmok.
Whoever the judge will choose
is the winner.
The judge's decision is final.
And the time begins now!
Your saliva is dripping.
Hello, Basti?
Yes, we're okay.
Bye.
You were just together earlier.
What is this?
Don't tell me you've decided
to be his real girlfriend?
Is this a part of your scheme?
James, he was just asking
how we are.
Why didn't he call me?
Because you are always fighting.
You're always jealous.
It's because I see something
to be jealous of.
You know you are sweet.
You hold hands. He hugs you.
You have a lot of pictures
together than the two of us.
You sleep next to each other.
It looks like
you're enjoying it.
And you're doing this
in front of my face.
What? We will fight about this
again?
James, don't you get it?
It's just a freaking show,
James.
For me, it's not.
This is not a show.
You like him.
You can't deny that to me.
How dare you!
Take back what you said.
No.
That's what I see.
- And that's how I feel.
- So that's it.
Do you see your girlfriend
as a flirt?
If that's the case,
we should break up
because it's embarrassing
for you.
You are a very good person
and your girlfriend is a flirt.
The presentation is beautiful.
Your presentation
is also beautiful.
Did you put this?
Did you put a lot?
Let's taste it.
You put this and you have that.
Did you put a lot of chilies?
It's delicious.
Grandmother Ikay?
Mikoy!
Grandmother Ikay, this is Hazel!
Grandmother Ikay!
There's nobody there.
Do you know where Mikoy
and Grandmother Ikay are?
Grandmother Ikay
is in the capitol.
But I don't know where Mikoy is.
Okay, thank you.
Hazel, is that you?
May-May.
Hey.
I just arrived.
Have you seen Grandmother Ikay
and Mikoy?
They're inside.
I dropped by to see them.
Let's go. Come with me.
I want to see Mikoy.
You go ahead.
I'll just park this.
Okay, take care.
Okay.
Of course,
the first prize winner
is no other than
the Eatery Queen,
it's Grandmother Ikay!
Congratulations!
That was very delicious.
- Thank you so much.
- Nothing is as delicious.
Thank you.
Congratulations,
Grandmother Ikay.
- I told you.
- Grandmother.
- Oh my...
- I told you, you would win.
How is your wound?
This is nothing.
It's nothing serious.
You are the Queen of Pinangat.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
I'm also happy for you.
Even if you and Mikoy
didn't end up together,
I'm still happy
because you fulfilled
your dreams in life.
Despite you being glamorous,
being modern,
being a good person
is still in your heart.
I love you, Grandmother Ikay.
Thank you, thank you.
You talk too much.
You're really something else.
- It's beautiful.
- Yes.
- Another trophy for you.
Mikoy?
Hazel.
Grandmother Ikay!
Hello...
congratulations.
Thank you.
Hi...
I'm Hazel.
I'm Mikoy's girlfriend.
Come on, let's talk.
Excuse me.
Grandmother.
What are you doing here?
Is that how you will welcome me?
What I mean is
what are you doing here?
I missed you.
You know what I mean.
Well, I just wanted
to surprise you.
You know me.
But the truth is I missed you.
I know it was my idea
to study abroad.
And I'm always going
to be forever grateful
that you allowed me.
You supported me
and you understood
all my decisions in life.
Actually, it went really well.
I got a good offer
from a big company abroad
after I finished my MBA,
but even if everything
is going so well,
it's like I'm not happy.
Then it hit me.
Do I want to establish myself
away from my family,
away from roots?
Away from the person I love,
away from you.
It was so foolish of me to think
that there's a better life
waiting for me in America.
When all I ever need
is right here,
with you.
So here I am,
asking you
if we can start again.
Can you give us another chance?
Hazel is the name of the one
who hugged Mikoy.
You know, it's really none
of my business.
Even if they kiss, I don't care.
Basti, what do you want?
I just want you to taste
my mother's cooking.
But if you're not in the mood,
that's okay.
I will leave.
- Wait.
- You know Grandmother,
I think there's nothing wrong
if we try to start again.
We had a good relationship.
Not once did she give up on me.
Are you sure about that?
I was really surprised
that Mikoy had a history
with that woman.
His taste for women
is already a bit doubtful.
Wait, aren't we talking
about your former boyfriend?
I'm also surprised myself
why I fell for him back then.
So, you think Aurelia
is being desperate?
- I don't know.
- You don't know
or you just don't want
to say it?
Good morning.
We have a visitor.
It's Hazel? What is she doing
there?
I have no idea.
But I feel
there will be a cock fight.