As far as I remember...
after you carved that,
you wanted to kiss me.
But I didn't want to.
I didn't allow you.
You're terrible.
We just became ex-lovers
and you edit the truth.
I said I love you so much.
Will you not answer me?
I love you so much, Celeste!
I love you!
What? Do you remember now?
By the way, this is Mikoy,
my childhood friend.
He actually took care of me
when I got stranded.
I owe my life to him.
If weren't for him
maybe something bad happened
to me.
What are your plans
for the wedding?
All I want to do is make Celeste
the happiest woman in the world.
I never dreamed of finding
the right woman.
And now I just want
to be the right man
for the woman I will love.
Oh my God. Why is it like this?
Why am I thinking of Mikoy?
Can I erase, erase, erase?
I think that fool casts
a spell on me.
Oh, Mother.
What's this?
Mother, why is it like this?
I'm so confused.
Why is it like this?
Why am I thinking of Mikoy?
He's coming in my mind.
Why is that?
I'm so confused.
Wait a second.
Come here. Wait a second.
There.
Hold it for a second.
Where did you learn that?
I'm a boy scout.
I'm always prepared.
Just wait.
- Here?
- Yes.
My foot is dirty.
That's okay.
It's okay now.
Come here.
You're cold, right?
Just go to sleep.
I'll watch over you.
Close your eyes.
Ready, ouch!
You're heavy!
Let's go?
I'm not eating anymore.
But I love Tonito.
I love Tonito so much.
Tonito brings out
the best in me.
He's so good to me.
He's my biggest blessing
and we complement each other.
I can't live without him.
Likewise, Love.
I also can't see myself
being without you.
Tonito...
have you been there that long?
You heard everything I said?
Yes...
Why?
Is there anything not true
with what you said about me?
I'm the only Tonito
in your life, isn't it?
Of course, Tonito,
you're my one and only.
Your mom is so beautiful.
I hope that we can visit her
someday.
Well, I think it's time
that I'll introduce her to you.
Mr. Ben, is it still far?
We're almost there, Basti!
- We're almost there!
- Hello, Mom?
We're doing an ocular.
So, Mom, this is a remote place
so I might lose signal.
Okay. Your Auntie Vivian
just called.
Your dad moved
a very important meeting
to fly to Sorsogon.
Did you meet him already?
He's here?
And he didn't
even bother to call me.
I'm sure he chose to be with her
girlfriend than me.
Don't feel bad about your daddy.
You know that we both have
the same goal
for your Dad, right?
And that is to make
our family whole again.
Your dad is not
the enemy here.
The only obstacle to our goal
is none other than Celeste.
What you can do is call him
and ask him to see you.
Don't let Celeste have him
all alone to herself.
Hello Mom?
Mom?
Tiff, did you hear me?
Mom, hello?
Mom?
Tiff?
Is that all?
You have nothing else
to tell me?
Grandmother, what else
do you want me to say to you?
I already told you everything.
It's just the two of you
together.
Nothing happened
between the two of you?
You know, Grandmother,
sometimes I would like to think
that you also have a dirty mind.
You're saying a lot of...
what are you watching?
You fool.
At my age,
you even think badly of me.
What I mean is, didn't you
and Celeste patch things up?
What will I expect
from your love story?
Grandmother, she is now
with the man she will marry.
You are embarrassed.
You can't say a word.
You have nothing to expect.
Besides, that's nothing to me.
So it's really over
for you and Celeste
even if lightning strikes you?
See?
You can't say it because
lightning might strike you.
Hi, Mother.
I'm sad that you're not here
in person
to meet the man I will marry.
But I know you're happy
wherever you are.
But still,
I want to introduce you to...
the person whom I really prayed
to come into my life.
This is Tonito.
Hello, Mother.
I hope you will allow me
to call you mother.
Celeste and I will get married
in four months.
That's why I'm here to ask
for your consent
to marry your daughter.
And don't worry...
I promise
that I will love her forever.
I will take care of her
and I will never ever make her
cry.
I know, even if I regret
my mistakes...
I can no longer
bring your life back.
I hope that I can make
our daughter feel the love
that I wasn't able to give you.
I hope that way,
I can make it up
for all my shortcomings to you.
Lucinda...
I have long asked
for your forgiveness.
I hope that Celeste
can also forgive me.
I have long suffered
from my sin.
I no longer ask that
she'll accept me.
I just hope that...
she can forgive me.
Hey, Mr. Ben might see you.
What's your problem?
-Just give me a moment with her.
- Wait.
Dad is calling.
Stay there.
Quiet.
Hello, Dad?
Hello, Tiff.
We're on our way to your hotel.
Just wait for us there.
Sorry, Dad,
but we're on a location.
Is that so?
I'm with your Auntie Celeste.
She wants to see you.
It's okay, Dad.
Just enjoy your day with her.
No. I want to see you.
I miss you.
I won't go back to Manila
without seeing you.
Don't you want to see me?
Tiff...
I'm waiting.
Okay, Dad, but how?
Just text me where you are.
Somehow there's a restaurant
there.
We'll meet you.
Okay. I'll just ask around.
See you later, Dad.
All right. You take care.
Celeste?
Sir, Ma'am...
you might want
to join us for snacks?
Tonito, I think it should
just be you and Celeste.
Adora and I still have
to attend to some matters.
We will deliver pili
products in Donsol.
Are you sure?
Yes.
There will be next time.
- So, what now?
- Okay.
Anyway, thank you
for your invitation.
Welcome, Sir.
Don't call me Sir.
Call me Mr. Patricio
or it would be better
if you just call me father.
Just call me father.
Okay...
father.
Okay.
We should go.
By the way, Celeste, where is
your phone that got wet?
Give it to me. I can fix that.
It will still work.
No need, Father.
I can manage.
No, Celeste.
Let's not waste it.
I can fix that.
Let's just let Celeste
have it fixed in the mall.
I can still fix that.
Why let others fix it?
I'll do it.
Celeste...
Okay, Father.
It's in my room.
Just get it.
Okay, Celeste.
I will fix that.
I can still fix that.
What a pity if
we don't fix it.
You can still use that.
Okay, let's go.
Let's leave now.
You will see your dad?
Yes...
even though I don't want to.
Why not?
He is with his fiancé.
Fiance?
You ask a lot of questions.
Just leave her alone, Man.
James.
Where will you meet your dad?
There in front of the beach,
by the entrance.
Okay, I already texted him.
Boys...
I'll leave
the two of you here.
Can you guys promise me
that you will behave?
I can't hear a promise.
Okay.
Promise?
Promise.
James?
Okay.
Can you guys
at least, smile at each other?
It looks really good.
- Yeah.
- Tender.
Hi, Dad.
Tiff...
Say hi to your Auntie Celeste.
Tiff, take a seat.
You know,
I ordered a lot already
but if there's anything else
you want, you can order again.
No, thanks.
Dad, I feel bad about you.
Is she more important than me?
Tiff, don't do that.
That's not good!
I really mean for her
not to understand.
Honey, how's your project?
Your Auntie Celeste and her
family would love to help you.
I'd rather ask a stranger
for help
rather than ask her
or her family.
Besides, I already found
someone who will help me.
Tiff?
Don't call me Tiff.
We're not close.
Tiffany...
where are your manners?
Why do you talk that way
to your Auntie Celeste?
Dad, what's wrong with that?
Is it wrong to express
what I truly feel?
Tiffany...
I hope you can give me a chance.
You know,
I feel that we can get along.
And why would I do that?
You're the one who ruined
my family
and you want me
to get along with you?
Hell no, Celeste.
Tiffany, your Auntie Celeste
and I didn't come here
for you to disrespect her.
You apologize to her now.
No way.
Tiffany...
your Mommy and I
didn't raise you
to be disrespectful
to someone older than you.
And soon, your Auntie Celeste
is going to be my wife.
Is that how
you're going to treat her?
I apologize for being rude
and for being honest.
But if you're trying
to attempt to get my sympathy...
I feel so sorry for you...
because my loyalty
is with my mom.
Again, I apologize
for being so real.
Dad, I'll just call you.
Tiffany?
Excuse me.
Tiffany!
Dad, I'm sorry.
I'm really not that rude.
I just can't...
Dad, it's hard for me.
How can you and mommy
be okay
if Celeste is in your life?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry
for disappointing you.
But I just don't want
to give you false hopes
that your mommy and I
will get back together.
We have our own lives now.
How about me?
Didn't you even include me
in the equation?
Am I not your daughter too, Dad?
Didn't you even consider me
when you decided
to live separately?
I'm really sorry that you got
involved with our problem.
But please, don't hate us.
No, Dad, I'm just hurting.
Because every day...
every hour, I'm still hoping
that you and mommy will be okay,
that we will be complete again.
Honey...
we're still family...
even if your mommy and I
are separated,
I still care for her.
And the most important thing is,
that we both love you.
Even if I'm married
to your Auntie Celeste...
I will still be your dad.
And your Auntie Celeste
can be your mom.
No, Dad.
For me, she's a homewrecker.
Why do the two of you
need to get married?
Can it be you and mommy again?
Even just for me, Dad?
I know that you're mature enough
to understand all of this.
And I know...
that one day,
you'd be able to accept this.
Things are hard right now...
but things are going to get
better.
Just remember...
I'll always be here for you...
right?
Don't you know that
you're my honey?
My baby monster.
And I will always love you.
So please,
don't feel bad about daddy.
I love you so much, Dad.
Please don't ever change.
I won't.
I promise.
And I love you too, very much.
And I promise,
I will never change, okay?
But I still don't like
Celeste...
and I feel like I never will.
Well...
all I'm asking is for you
to give her a chance.
I know that you'll get along.
I'm sorry, Dad,
but can you just request
something else?
Goodbye, Dad.
Hey...
I'm sorry you
and your daughter argued again
because of me.
No need to apologize.
I guess, we just have to give
her some more time
to adjust to the situation.
You know what, Love?
It seems like I don't want
to leave yet.
I want to spend more time here
with you.
You should eat.
So, Love,
welcome to Bulusan Lake.
This is amazing, Love.
You're so blessed
that you were born here
and grew up here in Sorsogon.
This is paradise.
It is, right?
Well, I've gone through a lot
here,
that's why
I don't want to come back.
Everything happens
for a reason.
I'm just so happy
that somehow you and your father
are getting okay.
I don't know.
But it's like my father
and I are not yet okay
and even my stepmom.
I find it hard to forgive them
after everything.
I didn't know that the wounds
of my childhood is deep.
It makes things hard, right?
I wish I don't have baggage
with my family.
Who would want that?
But maybe if mother
is still here,
it will be easier for me
to forgive them.
Well...
one forgives to the degree
that one loves.
You are a good person, Celeste.
You are loving.
And I'm confident that sooner
or later,
you will be able
to finally forgive them.
You'll be able
to finally forgive yourself.
Smile, Love.
I'll guess who you will meet.
It's Celeste.
The truth, what happened?
The reason why Mikoy left...
You should tell me.
Do you think this is all real?
What's with you, James?
Are you crazy?
I'm just acting.
Our business
is our top priority, Tonito.
Our family worked hard for it.
We are your family,
not Celeste.
If he didn't scare me
and told me
that there was a big bat there,
I wouldn't be traumatized.
He took advantage
of my vulnerability
with a vested interest.
- Where are we going to sleep?
- Here in my house.
Come on, let's go to sleep.
Where is the shower here?
It's over there!
I took a shower there!
Okay.
What are you doing?