I just really want to visit you.
Sorry for leaving you so soon,
Love.
Next time we should go out again
with Tiffany.
I know she still has
a resistance
to our wedding plans.
And I'm willing to wait
when she's ready.
I'm sorry.
My jeep can't be fixed today.
How will we go home?
You can sleep at my house
tonight.
Let's go to sleep.
Where are we going today?
- Paguriran.
- The lagoon?
Is that where the big bats are?
There's something
I will admit to you.
Actually, there's no bats.
I just made that up
when we were kids
so we can be close.
You should forgive Mikoy.
I'm sure he has done
a lot of good things.
He only made a mistake once.
You should forgive him.
What's with you?
I'm annoyed with him.
I noticed you're the only one
who is eating.
Why don't you feed Mikoy too?
That's a lot.
Do you want some more fish?
Cuz, let's stay here
for a while.
There will be a drinking session
later.
And there will be dancing,
like this.
What a waste if we'll leave...
It looks like Mikoy will ask me
to go home later.
I'll take care of Mikoy.
I'm sure he also wants
to be with you.
Of course, he wants
to make it up to you.
You know.
It's annoying.
It's petty but it's annoying.
Cuz, do you notice something
with Mikoy.
This is just my opinion.
I feel that there's something
with Mikoy.
What do you mean something?
What else?
He still likes you.
May-May,
it's just your imagination.
Plus Mikoy knows
that I'm getting married.
He's just helping me
with the community service.
That's it.
I don't know.
I feel something different.
I have a gut feeling.
Oh my, anyway,
where is the shower here?
It's over there.
- I took a shower there.
- Okay.
Should I come with you?
No, I'm okay. I can manage.
Okay, take care.
Yes.
What's that?
What are you doing?
I won't allow that fool
to sleep beside you.
James, we are together
in the room.
Even though.
I don't trust that guy.
You can't trust that guy.
Babe,
Basti is not that type of guy.
Why are you always
defending him?
- I am not.
- Yes, you are.
I'm just being reasonable.
Babe, please don't act
like a child.
We've talked about this already.
I know but sleeping beside him
is not part of the deal.
He might do something to you.
And do you think
I will allow it?
James, can we just stop this?
We've talked about this already.
Besides,
this is not going anywhere.
There you go! Finally,
I was able to send the message.
Sorry, I messaged
Mother and Father.
They might worry.
Wait, are you okay?
Can we go in?
I'll go inside.
Excuse me.
Keep your hands to yourself.
Don't ever think about it.
He's going crazy.
Are you trying to peep?
Oh my God, no. I just arrived.
Why didn't you knock?
Why didn't you lock the door?
I'm not used
to locking the door.
My Grandmother is the only one
with me in the house.
I'm going.
This is sickening.
Is it sickening?
May I join you?
Will you leave if I say no?
Actually, no.
I asked May-May where you are.
She said you're here.
You know, I'm sorry
for what happened back then.
I just did that
because I want you to notice me.
I'm naughty then but you know
that I love you so much.
Even if...
I always tease you,
but you know...
that I won't allow
anyone to hurt you.
Even if I'm the one
who gets hurt
as long as it's not you.
What am I saying?
Well, should I still be ashamed?
You have seen everything in me.
I'm sorry if I walked in
and you were naked.
It's your fault.
You didn't lock the door.
I'm not used to locking the door
in the house.
Grandmother Ikay is the only one
with me in the house.
She doesn't go
inside the bathroom.
What? I'm sorry.
You know we're quits already.
I fooled you back then
and you saw me naked today,
right? So, it's fair.
Am I right?
What?
I'm sorry.
Celeste!
Mikoy!
Hey, hello.
Hello!
Hey.
I'm okay.
May-May, you should drink
slowly.
I have no plans of taking home
two drunk women.
Drunk?
Me, drunk?
I'm not drunk.
Who is drunk?
Just kidding.
Come on, let's just dance.
Let's imagine
that there's music.
It's just like this.
Step, step,
dance!
There.
Step, step,
dance!
Like that! Step, step,
Step, step,
dance!
Like that.
Go ahead. Drink some more!
Step, step,
dance!
Dance, dance!
Step, step,
dance!
Like tha, right?
That's enough.
Come on, let's dance.
- What?
- Right?
- Hey!
- Wait, are you okay?
- Just kidding.
I'm okay.
Step, step,
dance!
Like that!
I directed you
to the wrong bathroom.
It was Mikoy
who was taking a bath.
Oh, I saw everything.
As in everything?
Yes, in his naked glory.
- Without any cover?
- Nothing!
Side A, side B.
You should've brought me along
so I could see it too!
What a pity.
- Do you want that?
- You didn't bring me along.
- What a pity.
- The spirit of alcohol
does something different, right?
Earlier,
you couldn't look at me.
Now, you're talking
as if I don't exist.
- Wait.
- It's him.
Mikoy...
wait, wait.
Time out.
I need to pee I'll just go
to the bathroom.
Is that okay?
You lock the door!
Step, step,
dance!
Is that what you learned
in Manila,
to be a drunkard?
What's with you?
Let your hair down.
It's time to celebrate
your individuality.
I'm not used
to seeing you drunk.
What in this?
Why did I get drunk so quickly?
That was quick.
They say that if you're drunk,
you can say what you want to say
that you can't say
if you're normal.
Really?
Okay, game. Let's test that.
Pretend that we didn't part
ways.
Okay, it didn't happen
and Tonito boy didn't come
into my life.
We're still a couple
and I'm like this.
Like this.
Like me and all that jazz.
Will you still love me?
Why can't you answer me?
Okay, I'll switch
the lights off.
Don't.
That can't be.
I can't sleep
if the light is on.
Me too, I can't sleep.
Go ahead Mr. Nanding.
You can switch the lights off.
Anyway, you own the house
and we're just guests here.
Besides you might lack sleep.
That's dangerous.
Your blood pressure might go up.
My Father is also like that.
Okay, I'll switch it off.
Let's go to sleep.
Okay.
Mikoy, here.
Mikoy,
is Celeste drunk?
Yes. She and May-May drank
earlier.
Oh my....
Do you have lukewarm
water and a face towel?
I have.
Wait, I'll get it.
Okay.
I'll wake up Adora
to attend to her.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
Just a second.
How are you?
Grandmother is just buying
medicine in town
but she's on her way back.
You still don't want to go home?
Okay, you can stay here.
Here, I brought lukewarm
lemon juice.
You should drink this.
Can you manage?
You know, that's what my Mother
and my Father used to give me
when they were still alive.
Go ahead, drink some more
to get rid of the flu quickly.
Is it delicious?
What?
Do you still feel cold?
Here.
Not anymore.
Just rest.
Thank you, Mikoy.
You're always taking care of me.
What will happen to me
if you're not around?
I will never neglect you.
I'll just be here by your side
until we get old.
That's my promise.
I'll take care of you.
You should rest first.
Do you still feel cold?
If you only knew
how happy I am to see you happy.
I really want to answer
your questions earlier.
Especially what if
we're still together?
Then I'll be the happiest man
in the whole world.
Ouch...
What was that?
What happened?
Nothing.
- What did you do?
- Nothing happened.
Let me see.
Hey, go look somewhere else.
I'm just concerned.
Maybe an insect with venom
bit her.
Maybe she's not immune to that.
She might have an allergy.
You want to touch her,
don't you?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Hey...
you should go to sleep.
What are you fighting about?
Go to sleep.
I'm sorry.
Let's go to sleep.
That light is not turning off,
okay?
And you Basti, please stay away.
Where will I go?
There's no space here anymore.
And you Tiffany,
you should turn back.
Yes, I will.
But please, don't make trouble.
Please.
- Let's go to sleep.
- James, go to sleep.
Just relax. I'm here.
Mikoy, don't leave me.
I won't leave you, okay?
Come here.
Cuz, I noticed that you are
the only one who is eating.
Why don't you feed Mikoy too?
Is that so?
Okay, let's roll this
so it will be delicious.
That's a lot.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Do you want fish?
Delicious.
What are you doing?
Let's pretend
that we didn't part ways.
Okay, it didn't happen
and Tonito boy didn't come
into my life.
We're still a couple
and I'm like this.
Like this, like me
and all that jazz.
Will you still love me?
Oh my gosh, my head hurts.
There you go.
Celeste, you're awake.
Your Auntie Adora
prepared breakfast for you.
She cooked you Arroz Caldo.
Are you going to eat?
Ouch. My head hurts.
I drank a bit too much
yesterday.
You know Celeste,
Mikoy just came home.
He watched over you
the whole night.
Did he change my clothes?
Of course not.
Your Auntie Adora did that.
But Mikoy didn't leave you.
What?
You should eat the porridge.
Just in time, it's still hot.
I just put it there.
Father, I don't eat carbs.
But can you scoop the egg?
I'll have the protein instead.
Just egg?
Okay, Celeste, I'll do that.
Just egg.
Why are you ignoring my calls
and messages?
Tonito,
are you still mad at me?
I don't think
this is the right time
to talk about that, Aurelia.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that.
I know it's not...
right
but maybe it's just part
of my frailties being a woman.
You know what I mean.
I don't want to be rude to you,
Aurelia.
I respect you
and I don't want
you to lose that.
You'll have to excuse me.
Last night was terrible.
I'm so wasted.
I drank a lot.
- Too much.
- My head hurts.
You don't remember
what you did and said?
Wait, what?
What did I say?
Wait, are you the one
who dressed me?
Did I dance on the table?
I danced...
did I say something distasteful?
- More likely naughty.
- More?
- Naughty?
- No, more like kinky.
Kinky?
- No.
- You shouldn't drink too much.
Look, you did some outrageous
things
but I didn't look.
Can I possibly be absent
from the community service?
It's like I don't feel well.
It's like I have a fever.
- There's your drama again.
- It's true.
- Check it.
- You're hot?
I'm hot.
You're not hot today.
You were hot last night.
Mikoy, what's with you?
Don't be like that.
Those dimples of yours,
that's where I fell in love.
You know you will miss me
when I go back to Manila.
For sure I'll miss
you're being a troublemaker.
And what you say
when you're drunk.
Hey...
Celeste is really
very beautiful.
Tell me that you're not in love
with her.
There's nobody there.
Do you know where Mikoy
and Grandmother Ikay are?
You're jealous.
Because I see something
to be jealous of.
It looks like
you're enjoying it.
I heard that they will make
a secret recipe.
My only secret in cooking
is being happy.
Have you seen Grandmother Ikay
and Mikoy?
They are inside.
Mikoy?
Hazel.