♪I've been tracing back♪
♪Went through all the sweetness and sorrow♪
♪Chasing a dream till it starts♪
♪All the subtle things♪
♪You can't erase memories♪
♪They lead my life going on♪
♪You make my heart beat♪
♪It travels from silent darkness♪
♪To starry nights♪
♪We hold our hands back to the home bay♪
♪I feel love♪
♪I just wanna keep a promise♪
♪I feel us♪
♪When you slowly fall into my arms♪
♪You're the one in my life♪
♪Baby you make my world so perfect♪
♪Stars miles away♪
♪Shining in the sky♪
♪We can find true love♪
♪This special moment♪
♪When I see your smile♪
♪My dream is realized♪
=The Love You Give Me=
(Adapted from Shi Dingrou's novel of the same name)
=Episode 14=
Mr. Xin.
You should at least eat
or drink something.
It's your own health.
Mr. Xin?
I never swim in this pool.
This sofa.
I never even sit on it. Change it.
I'll have it changed tomorrow.
Change this one too.
This one too.
Look at this dining table.
Do we even have
that many people eating here?
Why do we need such a big dining table?
Change it!
I'll change it tomorrow.
Why do we need such a huge house?
What's the point of living alone?
All I see is your face!
What's wrong with my face?
I think I look okay.
What's the point
of venting your anger at me
when she's ignoring you?
Yes, Min Hui?
Hardy, this is Quanquan.
It's Quanquan.
Are you with Xin Qi?
I wanted to call Xin Qi.
But Min Hui didn't have Xin Qi's WeChat
on her phone.
Luckily I've memorized
your phone number.
I'm smart, right?
Yes, Quanquan. You're the smartest.
Quanquan,
listen to me carefully.
I'll tell you my phone number.
So please memorize it, okay?
Okay.
Quanquan.
(Who are you calling?)
(Xin Qi.)
Quanquan,
ask your mommy
why she doesn't have my WeChat
on her phone.
Min Hui, why isn't Xin Qi's WeChat
on your phone?
I blocked him.
Why did she block me?
Why did you block Xin Qi?
He knows why.
She said you know why.
Okay.
Your godmother said
your mommy is not well.
Is she feeling better now?
Min Hui, are you sick?
I'm fine now.
She's okay now.
Xin Qi, how much longer
do you have to travel?
When will you come home?
(I'll be busy for a while.)
(It will be a while
before I can go home.)
(Listen to Mommy)
(and don't mess around, okay?)
When I come back,
I'll take you out to have fun.
Okay?
Okay, you better keep your promise.
You...
Xin Qi said
he'll take me out to have fun!
Sit down.
I went through
the quarter's financial report today.
Dad,
let me explain.
I did screw up on the investment
by the Blue Jay Group.
Be Agile intercepted the deal
at the last minute.
But don't worry.
I've invited Professor Dong
from the Medical College
to endorse our cancer screening plan.
And Professor Dong
is a famous cancer specialist in China.
So with his support,
I believe we can get funding soon.
Guanchao is my life's work.
It'll eventually
be handed over to you and Yiting.
Don't let me down.
I won't, Dad.
Dad,
can you stop talking
about work over mealtime?
If you didn't find
a capable husband, like Qirang,
do you think I can rely on you?
Dad, you mustn't say that.
I can't live a single second
without Yiting now.
Thank you.
Yeah, exactly.
Qirang alone is enough for Guanchao.
Are you not happy
that I can accompany you and Mom?
Of course,
I'm happy.
Let's eat.
Cheers
to your health.
Thank you.
Cheers.
(Listen to your mom. Eat well)
(and take your medicine on time, okay?)
My phone's battery is almost dead.
See you, Daddy.
Did you fight with Xin Qi again?
No.
Adults are so complicated.
They pretend to be happy
when they're not.
They even deny it
when they're in a fight.
Yet, they always teach kids like us
to be honest.
Quanquan.
Come here for a bit.
Well, here's the thing.
Xin Qi and I
couldn't agree
on something
very important.
So
he'll move back to his own place
for a while.
But it won't change the fact
that he's your dad.
Can I still see him in the future?
Of course, you can still see him.
You can meet him.
Didn't you ask him
to take you out to play today?
Can we go camping?
Many kids in my class went camping
with their parents.
I want Daddy and Mommy
to take me camping too.
No problem.
I promise you.
Camping! Camping!
Daddy and Mommy
are taking me to go camping!
I'm so happy and excited!
You don't have to send me off.
Dad, make sure to stay safe.
Okay.
Sleep early
and don't work late into the night.
Okay.
See you guys around.
Good night.
Dear.
Come back. Dear.
Dear,
thank you for what you did today.
If you weren't here,
I don't know how to handle your dad.
If you know it's not easy
to handle my dad,
you should focus
your attention on Guanchao.
If you want Dad to hand over
the company to you without worries,
you need to prove to him
that you're truly capable.
I understand.
Don't worry.
I'll certainly prove myself after this.
Then I'll head back to the company.
You should get some rest early.
Okay?
Go ahead.
He said he'll hand over Guanchao to me.
But look what happened?
All the shares are still in the hands
of that old man and Zheng Yiting.
If it weren't
for the old man's failing health,
would he let me be the CEO?
No way.
But one day,
Guanchao will belong
to Cheng.
I have faith in you.
I really do.
Besides, I'll do my best to help you.
By the way,
I heard there's an intelligence summit
in Shanghai next week.
And Guanchao has a special session.
What do you think about us...
You're not suitable.
Why?
I spent hundreds of thousands of yuan
to get this session.
I want Guanchao's
cancer screening technology
to be the focus of the entire summit.
I've already handed it over to Mr. Qiu.
I'm also the head of the R&D department.
Why can he represent Guanchao
to attend the summit
but I can't?
Besides,
I heard that Min Hui from Be Agile
will also be there.
I want to take this opportunity
to kill her limelight.
Don't you remember
how you became
the head of this department?
Am I really that incompetent to you?
Fine.
Go and find Min Hui.
Look at you pulling a tantrum again.
Min Hui.
(Be Agile Medical Technology)
High-Tech Summit?
(Invitation)
Yes, I just received the invitation.
The organizing committee
(Invitation)
is very interested in your research
on AI cardiac modeling software.
They want to invite you
to give a speech.
That's great!
This is a perfect opportunity
to showcase my AI technology
and meet
some like-minded partners.
I can also strengthen my research team
and attract better investment.
Will Xin Qi be unhappy
if he hears that?
I don't care if he's happy or not.
How long is the summit?
Probably around a week.
I'll go with you
as a representative of Be Agile.
Will He Haixiang give up
this opportunity to shine
and let you take the spotlight?
Compared to taking the spotlight,
he'd probably rather not
travel with you.
You have a point.
Wait a minute.
If both of us go,
who'll take care
of Quanquan?
Let Xin Qi take care of him.
Absolutely not!
Why?
No means no.
What's going on?
He's trying to take back Min Quanquan?
He's delusional.
It's true
that good-looking guys
are never good people.
The more handsome, the worse they are.
The more I think about it,
the angrier I get.
He didn't even ask if you,
the godmother, agreed or not.
That's right. I don't agree either.
Take Quanquan with you.
Consider it a holiday.
Don't worry.
Can't two of us handle only one child?
The conference schedule
isn't that tight either.
Trust me.
You're right.
Quanquan will definitely be happy.
Yes.
Here you are.
Mr. He.
Ms. Min, I was on my way to see you.
Here's the thing.
Let Mr. Ding
go to the High-Tech Summit
in your place.
Why?
(Female Director
of Be Agile Seduces CEO)
Well, I think
it's enough to lose face
in Bincheng alone.
Be Agile will be too embarrassed
if the news travels all the way
to the High-Tech Summit.
Min Hui is going
to the High-Tech summit,
not some gossip reporters' gathering.
Mr. Ding, you're going?
Then are you familiar
with the AI cardiac modeling software?
The people in the audience
are all professionals.
You might embarrass Be Agile if you go.
It's just a PowerPoint presentation.
One just needs to be able to read
and can give the talk.
What do you mean by that?
Are you planning
to have me write the speech
and then have Ding Yifeng deliver it?
My name is on the invitation.
Even if you don't want me to go,
you can't let Ding Yifeng go.
Worst case scenario, just don't go.
It's just one missed opportunity
for Be Agile to showcase its strength
to the capital and the industry.
If HQ finds out,
it might not be good, right?
Mr. He,
what do you think?
No, Ms. Cao.
It's all right.
Since Ms. Min thinks it's not a problem,
it means I'm overthinking it.
Mr. He...
Who's the one messing around?
(Female Director
of Be Agile Seduces CEO)
This is clearly setting you up
so you'd be criticized
during the summit.
No matter who uploaded it,
I won't let them succeed.
(Female Director
of Be Agile Seduces CEO)
(His wife is just next to him.)
Well...
I want you to investigate
who uploaded these.
Okay.
Mr. Yan is here.
Do you want to reconsider?
There's nothing to reconsider.
Tell him to come in.
Okay.
We're here.
He looks handsome even when he sleeps.
How nice it would be
if I could see him every day.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
We're already here.
Let's go.
Then
I'll get going.
Okay.
Then...
Be careful on your way back.
Okay.
Chen Jiajun!
Don't leave today.
Don't leave tomorrow either.
Never leave again.
Do you dare to stay?
Okay.
What are you doing?
You scared me.
Aren't you going to Shanghai
in a couple of days
to attend the High-Tech Summit?
I'm packing your luggage for you.
There's no need to rush.
There are still a few days left.
Has Mr. Yan sent the documents
that I asked him to draft?
Yes, he has sent it over.
Just waiting for you to sign it.
I won't go to the office today.
I need to take care of something.
Okay.
Then I'll unpack your luggage.
Mr. Xin, good morning.
Morning.
Are you here to see Ms. Min?
Where's she?
She went to Shanghai
to attend the High-Tech Summit.
But isn't the summit still
a few days away?
Ms. Min took two days off in advance
to take her child to Shanghai
for a little vacation.
She's probably on the way
to the airport by now.
Mr. Xin, do you have something urgent
to discuss?
Should I give her a call?
No need.
Let her enjoy her vacation.
My matter can wait.
But
he looked like he was
in a hurry just now.
(Be Agile Medical Technology)
Hello, book a ticket to Shanghai for me.
The sooner, the better.
Help me pack my luggage.
Sure.
Didn't you just say
I didn't need to pack?
Quanquan, what did you put in here
that it's so heavy?
Okay, come sit down.
Let me fasten your seat belt.
Okay.
Hello.
I'm the flight attendant
in charge of this flight.
We noticed in your passenger information
that your son had heart surgery before,
is that correct?
Yes.
But I didn't fill out any information.
I'm sorry.
I'm not too sure about that.
But I received an instruction
from our ground staff
that the captain has decided
to upgrade your seats.
Why don't you and your son follow me?
What does it mean to upgrade seats?
Upgrading means
we'll offer you a bigger, wider,
and more comfortable seat.
Do you want to go?
Yes. Min Hui, let's go and take a look.
If I don't like it,
we won't go.
If you don't like it,
then we won't go, okay?
Then we'll go and take a look.
Okay.
Thank you.
Also, please thank the captain for us.
No problem.
Please take a seat.
Min Hui, look how big
and comfortable it is here.
We'll stay here.
Thank you for everything.
Don't mention it.
Thank you so much.
It's okay.
Let us know
if you need anything.
Okay.
(Attention all passengers.)
(Flight K1825)
(from Bincheng to Shanghai is...)
Let's go.
It's so beautiful here.
Yes, it's pretty.
Welcome.
Hello.
We're here
to attend the High-Tech Summit
and the organizing committee
has booked our room.
Please wait for a moment.
Sir.
Hello, Ms. Min.
Congratulations.
You're the 2,888th guest
of our hotel this year.
According to our hotel tradition,
we'll automatically upgrade your room
to a larger suite.
Thank you, but we don't need it.
Our original room is just fine.
Please don't get me wrong.
This is not a disguised marketing ploy.
It really is our hotel's tradition.
How about this?
Let me take you to see the room first.
Hey, kid.
Would you like to see the room?
Thank you, mister.
Mommy, let's go see it.
Quanquan.
Sorry about that.
Please take us to the room.
Okay.
Ms. Min, this way, please.
Please come in.
It's so beautiful here.
Captain America.
Sir,
we didn't have much time to prepare.
This is the best we could do.
Okay.
Who told you to set this up?
No one.
What he was trying to say
was that we couldn't determine
who the 2,888th guest
would be.
So
we decorated it for a family of three.
I'm sorry.
We cannot stay in this room.
Please book
the room we originally had.
If you're concerned
about hidden charges,
we can sign a contract with you.
That's not what I meant.
I just don't feel comfortable
accepting things
that I don't deserve.
Please book
the room we originally had.
Thank you.
Quanquan,
come here.
We're not staying here.
Let's go.
Mommy, we're not staying here?
Give this to me.
Listen to me.
Next time,
I'll let you stay here
with my own money.
Okay?
That's a good boy.
Thank you.
(Hello?)
Godmother, we've arrived in Shanghai.
I figured you would've arrived
by now too.
How was it, Quanquan?
Did you have fun on the plane?
Yeah, it was fun.
The pretty flight attendant even gave me
some chocolate to eat.
But Mommy wouldn't let me stay
in the Iron Man and Spider-Man room.
What room?
What do you mean?
(Go wash your hands quickly.)
(Later, I will take you out to eat.)
(See you later, godmother.)
(Bye-bye.)
(Listen to your mommy, okay?)
(I'll be there in a couple of days.)
Okay, go on now.
Quanquan, wash your hands carefully.
Okay.
Cao Mu,
did you tell Xin Qi
that I was coming to Shanghai?
What? I didn't say anything.
Cai Wenji said he was looking
for you this morning.
It must have been her. What's wrong?
No way.
Did he follow you there
so he could pursue you?
He's really going
to the end of the earth like this.
Stop talking nonsense.
He's not here.
But his hand is pretty long.
What do you mean?
I knew it.
All my life,
I never won any prizes ever.
Firstly, he upgraded my seats.
When I arrived at the hotel,
they were saying
about upgrading our room to a suite.
I could easily guess
he's the one behind this.
It's that romantic?
How is this romantic?
He just wants to win Quanquan
over with these sweet tricks.
I won't give him that chance.
Yeah, I'm not going
to give him that chance.
You're right.
We cannot give him the chance.
Besides, do we lack money?
It'll be on me next time.
Ms. Cao, you sure are generous.
Remember what you said today.
(Next time, I'll let you take me)
(to stay somewhere nicer.)
By the way, Cao Mu.
How's the preparation
for the brand promotion?
The deadline is too tight.
I'm definitely going to
work overnight these next few days.
That's all. I won't talk to you anymore.
I'll get back to work.
Okay, go ahead.
Ms. Min refused to stay in this room,
and we can't force her.
Sorry about that, Mr. Xin.
It's okay.
Just clear everything.
Okay.
Let's clean up the place.
I knew it won't be easy to trick her.
Come on, Quanquan.
I'm taking you to the Bund, okay?
I want to go camping.
We're not going camping.
Why don't we go to the Bund instead?
- No, I want to go camping.
- Xin Qi.
Surprise!
Do you miss me?
She kissed Daddy!
Quanquan,
let's get out of here.
Come on.
Why did you kiss me?
Min Hui!
Don't get it wrong.
Mr. Xin,
what a coincidence.
You can continue where you left off.
Don't get it wrong, Min Hui.
Let me go.
So you're Min Hui.
Then you must be Quanquan.
Who are you?
Why did you kiss my daddy?
Even Mommy hasn't kissed him yet.
Quanquan...
Xin Qi,
tell them
Who I am.
Let me introduce you
to Cindy,
my older sister.
Older sister?
Yes.
The Chairwoman of RG
and also
my boss.
Hi.
You're even cuter in person
than in your photos.
I've fallen in love with you
at first sight.
That's not how you use the phrase.
Where did you get my photo?
Xin Qi sent it to me, of course.
I thought you've returned to Beijing.
I was supposed to
but I was delayed by some things.
Hardy also said
you'll be attending
the High-Tech Summit.
So I decided to postpone my stay here.
Or else I wouldn't be able
to meet my adorable nephew
and...
You can call me Min Hui.
Okay.
Min Hui,
you're also more beautiful in person
than in photos.
You have all five flavors.
[*Well-rounded characters]
That's not how you use that phrase.
Where did you learn
all these weird idioms?
I just started learning.
I think it's cool to speak
in four-word phrases.
Did he send you my photos too?
I sent photos of you
and Quanquan together.
I couldn't cut you out.
No, no, no.
You sent me a family photo
of the three of you.
Ignore him.
He's always been like this.
He speaks...
He speaks without thinking.
That's right.
You're very good
at the Chinese language.
It looks like you're not only cute
but also smart.
Love you.
He's too cute.
I booked a restaurant for tonight.
Let's have dinner together.
- I'm busy.
You two pretty much clicked.
Cindy,
I have a meeting tonight.
So I don't think
I'll be able to make it.
I'm going...
It doesn't matter what you want to do.
Min Hui, I rarely come back from abroad.
I even extended my stay on purpose
so I could see you and Quanquan.
All right, then.
That's great.
It's decided then.
What do you want to eat?
(Guanchao)
Dear,
what brings you here?
What is this about?
(Female Director
of Be Agile Seduces CEO)
Dear, you were there that day.
You know this has nothing to do with me.
That woman drank too much...
I was having afternoon tea
with friends today,
and this became the talk
of the whole place.
Everyone was asking me about it.
Even my mom called from out of town
asking what kind of relationship
you have with Min Hui.
This is already in the past.
Why would someone want
to bring up the past?
It has to be...
Who would be interested in this matter?
It's either interested in Min Hui
or...
Cheng Qirang,
I don't care what you do out there.
But don't embarrass me
and make me clean up your mess.
Keep an eye on
the people you need to take care of.
If this kind of thing reaches
my father's ears,
don't blame me for not helping you.
Dear. Dear!
I think that's it.
Let's leave it at that.
Okay.
Oh, by the way.
Give me four pails of soda water.
Four pails?
She meant four bottles.
All right, just a moment.
Now, where was I?
When Xin Qi first came
to our house as a child,
he didn't dare to sleep alone at night.
He had
to hold a small teddy bear every night.
I even gave him a nickname,
"Koala".
Do you remember that?
It's really hard to imagine him
being like that now.
You have no idea.
Okay, that's enough.
Are you done?
You've been talking
without stopping.
I'll tell you more slowly in the future.
Quanquan.
It's our first meeting.
So I prepared a gift for you.
What is it?
Take a look.
Thank you.
It's a phone watch.
This watch is awesome.
Do you like it?
If you like it, call me Aunt.
Aunt!
That feels amazing.
You're so adorable.
You're so sweet.
You have such a good temper.
You're so easy to get along with.
You're not like Xin Qi at all.
Cheers.
It must be hard taking care
of Quanquan alone.
Xin Qi also asked me the same question.
I showed Quanquan's medical record
to a heart specialist abroad.
He said the surgery was perfect.
So you don't have to worry anymore.
Did Xin Qi show you the record?
Yes, he did.
Actually, he has been worried
about Quanquan.
As you know,
Xin Qi's heart condition only started
to improve slowly
after his surgery five years ago.
Over the past twenty years,
he almost died several times.
So I understand
the difficulties of taking care
of a child with a heart condition.
You have a successful career too.
If it were me,
I wouldn't be able to juggle both.
Did Xin Qi tell you all this too?
No, he didn't.
I did a little digging myself.
There's a saying,
"Know thyself, know thy..."
What was it again?
"He who knows himself and his enemy
shall never be defeated."
Yeah, that's right.
I just wanted to understand you
and Quanquan better.
So you wouldn't have
to struggle so much in the future.
We can take care of Quanquan...
No need.
My son is my responsibility.
I don't need you.
Quanquan, come with me.
I haven't had a bite yet.
Let's not eat here, okay?
I'll take you to eat something else.
Come on.
What's the matter?
I think I should be asking you, Xin Qi.
First, it was a cabin upgrade,
then a room upgrade.
Now you suddenly have a sister.
Aren't you going too far in your efforts
to fight for Quanquan's custody?
No, I didn't mean it that way.
Then what did you mean?
I'm warning you one last time.
I won't let anyone
take Quanquan away from me.
Don't even bother trying.
Let's go.
What's wrong with her?
What did you say to her?
I didn't say anything, I think.
I just talked
about how knowing oneself
and others can help.
Then I said
we can take care of Quanquan.
But then she got upset
and said she can take care
of Quanquan herself
without our help.
Miss Cindy,
do you know
what "know yourself and your enemy,
and you will not be defeated" means?
Isn't it about understanding
oneself and others
so we're able to help others?
I think you meant to say empathy, right?
Actually, "know yourself and your enemy"
means the opposite.
Is that so?
It's about understanding oneself
and the enemy to win battles.
Min Hui already saw me
as the enemy.
Look at what you did.
She's definitely going
to think I'm up to no good.
Stop misusing the idioms.
Sorry, I didn't mean it.
Oh, you didn't mean it?
What about trying to take her son away?
Was that done not on purpose?
I have to explain this to you.
This was what Hardy told me.
He said
you have a son.
But the child's mother
didn't allow you to meet your son.
So I planned to file a lawsuit.
Jeez, Hardy and his miscommunication.
Later, you explained everything to me.
So I got a clear picture.
Yes,
Min Hui worked so hard
to raise Quanquan.
We shouldn't take him away.
It wasn't us.
It has nothing to do with you.
What do you mean it's not related to me?
Didn't you hear Quanquan
calling me Aunt just now?
I really love the sound of it.
Jason,
why
don't you two get married?
Once you're married,
you can raise Quanquan together.
Problem solved.
Get married?
Did I say anything wrong?
I can see you like Min Hui.
Then you should get married.
It's killing two birds with one stone.
You mean, achieve two goals
with one strike.
Wait.
When did I say I like her?
Don't tell me you don't even know
that you like her.
Can't you tell
from the way you look at her
and how nervous you were
while explaining that I'm your sister?
Even a three-year-old
can see that you like her.
You should check your eyes.
You can lie to anyone
but don't lie to yourself. OK?
What do you call this again?
That's called self-deception.
I got it right?
Yes,
I'm improving.
Min Hui.
Min Hui!
What's wrong?
Did I burn your scalp?
If you keep blowing like that,
my hair is going to catch fire.
Are you in a bad mood?
No, I'm not.
I'm happy
that I'm on vacation with you.
Every time you fake a smile,
you look so ugly.
How could you say that about me?
So you admit you were faking your smile.
Min Quanquan, you're growing up
to be quite mischievous,
aren't you?
Did Xin Qi bully you again?
Tell me if he bullies you again,
and I'll take care of him for you.
It seems like
you love me more
than you love him, right?
Of course.
But if he asked you
to live with him,
you wouldn't agree, right?
I would.
You would?
As long as you are there too.
And if it's just you and him,
without me,
would you still want to?
Of course not.
Of course, I won't agree.
I'm glad to hear that.
I didn't dote on you for nothing.
Why are you asking me these questions?
You're not going to give me
to Xin Qi, are you?
Min Hui,
I know raising me is tiring for you.
But soon,
I'll grow up and be able
to take care of you.
Don't give me to Xin Qi.
Even though Xin Qi is great,
I still love you the most.
Quanquan,
you're so adorable.
How could I bear
to give you away to someone else,
right?
Then I don't have to worry anymore.
Go take a shower now. You stink.
Excuse me for a moment.
Hi, handsome.
Are you alone?
Do you want to have a drink with me?
How about adding my WeChat?
My son.
My son's mother.
It's a pity.
(Xin Qi,)
(you can lie to anyone.)
(But don't lie to yourself.)
(You've slept together.)
(Does that mean
you won't be separated forever?)
(Don't tell me)
(you don't even know)
(that you like her.)
(Can't you tell
from the way you look at her)
(and how nervous you were)
(while explaining that I'm your sister?)
(Even a kid knows you like her.)
(I wanted to thank you)
(for not making me regret
reuniting you and my son.)
(You're really cruel.
Do you know that?)
I can accept you hating me
and venting
all your anger at me.
I can take it all.
But not Quanquan.
No one can take him away from me,
not even you.
(From today on,
you won't see Quanquan anymore.)
♪I couldn't see the past clearly♪
♪The hidden touching moments♪
What can I do other
than lying to myself?
♪Gradually open up the heart♪
♪I'm glad my hidden pain
is recovering slowly♪
(Five years ago)
♪I've been tracing back♪
♪Went through
all the sweetness and sorrow♪
♪Chasing a dream till it starts♪
♪It's the thread of fate
that ties you and me♪
♪Like old dreams that come back♪
♪I'm shedding tears, again♪
♪When misunderstandings♪
♪Befall us like a heavy downpour♪
♪My heart is gone♪
♪Whenever I forget,
astonishment reminds me again♪
♪Everything feels like yesterday,
just what can I say?♪
♪'Cause I always love you♪
♪The love you give me from all sides♪
♪And I can't lose it no matter what♪
♪'Cause I always love you♪
♪How much the memories must tremble♪
♪To evoke your empathy?♪
♪My love♪
♪The lonely hourglass
flowing to the end♪
♪Make peace with the past♪
♪After rain comes the rainbow♪
♪I will have the love
that I've looked forward to♪
♪'Cause I always love you♪
♪How long have we been
lingering around?♪
♪We still wander around
the threshold of time♪
♪'Cause I always love you♪
♪Waiting for your heart
to be met by mine♪
♪Don't ever let our love
be in vain again♪
♪My love♪