♪I've been tracing back♪
♪Went through all the sweetness and sorrow♪
♪Chasing a dream till it starts♪
♪All the subtle things♪
♪You can't erase memories♪
♪They lead my life going on♪
♪You make my heart beat♪
♪It travels from silent darkness♪
♪To starry nights♪
♪We hold our hands back to the home bay♪
♪I feel love♪
♪I just wanna keep a promise♪
♪I feel us♪
♪When you slowly fall into my arms♪
♪You're the one in my life♪
♪Baby you make my world so perfect♪
♪Stars miles away♪
♪Shining in the sky♪
♪We can find true love♪
♪This special moment♪
♪When I see your smile♪
♪My dream is realized♪
=The Love You Give Me=
(Adapted from Shi Dingrou's novel of the same name)
=Episode 24=
Since this acquisition meeting
involves our trade secrets,
I've arranged
this third-party meeting room for us.
I hope you don't mind, Mr. Xin.
I don't mind.
Okay.
All of us are here today
to have a final discussion
on the financing issue
of the MBO.
If there's no further issue,
it's better for us to sign
the contract today.
Based on
the investment plan
that I've drawn up with Ms. Cao,
Blue Jay will invest
500 million in this.
The executives will retain
the original percentage of the shares.
The plan is still the same.
And I'll give you an extra 0.5%,
making it 4% in total.
Mr. Xin is indeed
a decisive entrepreneur.
You are so resolute.
I'm not done yet.
I know that you'll have
more investors coming in.
I have only one request.
No matter how many investors you have,
they can't have
a higher percentage than Blue Jay.
We want to have absolute control
over Be Agile.
Mr. Xin, don't worry.
So far, other than Blue Jay,
there are two other venture capitalists
that we are working with.
One of them is willing
to offer us 300 million.
As for the other one,
we'll know when Min Hui and I
meet them later.
I promise you
that Blue Jay will be
our biggest shareholder.
Okay.
No more questions from me.
Okay then. Min Hui,
please...
Where does the barking come from?
I'm sorry.
I set an alarm.
Mr. Xin, your watch
is very unique.
Ms. Cao, you have great taste.
This is from my son.
My son has a matching watch too.
The one-and-only pair of watches.
Even his mother doesn't have it.
What do you think?
Does it suit me?
Yes.
It suits your outfit today very well.
Mr. Xin, if you have no other questions,
we can sign the contract now.
Yes, Mr. Xin.
Let's get down to business first.
(Be Agile Medical Technology)
(Be Agile Share Acquisition Agreement)
Mr. Xin.
Is there something wrong
with the contract?
There's nothing wrong with the contract.
But after all,
this is a 500-million project.
I have to think about
what I'll get in return.
You don't have to worry
about that, Mr. Xin.
You'll be satisfied with
what you'll get in return.
With this reassurance from Ms. Min,
I can rest assured.
How are you, my princess?
Come, baby.
Be good.
You are so pretty.
Dear.
Can you give me a hand?
My arm...
Dear.
Don't you want to know
how I got hurt?
I'm not a doctor.
Why do I need to know?
I just want...
I just want to receive
some care from my wife.
You don't need it.
You are just forcing yourself
to stay in the Zheng family,
because you want to be
the president of Guanchao, right?
We are just taking
what we need from each other.
There's no need to put
any feelings into this.
No, dear. Actually, I...
Sensen.
When you get hurt next time,
remember to protect your face.
After all, the PR Department
will have to spend
a lot of money to push down
the news
about Guanchao's CEO getting hit.
Okay.
I have a business dinner tonight.
I won't be back for dinner.
Go ahead.
Mr. Xin, Mr. He.
This is as far as I can go.
Ms. Cao is still waiting for me
for the next meeting.
Okay. Go ahead.
Farewell.
Mr. Xin, I have some work to do as well.
Pleasure working with you.
I'll take my leave now.
There's no one here.
Someone will see us.
We don't have to pretend anymore.
You did well just now.
You deserve to be praised.
That's it?
What about the reward?
The reward?
You just signed the contract.
And you already want a reward?
I signed the contract with Be Agile.
I want the reward from you.
Stop. Someone will see us.
Stop it.
I'm not afraid.
Why are you so afraid?
Here's your interest.
You can get the rest
tonight.
Okay?
Okay.
You can go now.
(Spectrum Theatre)
Zizhu, I'm sorry.
I got off work late today.
Here are your flowers.
I bought these flowers for you.
I don't want your flowers.
You...
May your love last for eternity.
Zizhu, wait for me.
Zizhu.
Detective fiction.
(The Love You Give Me)
Zizhu.
Please keep quiet in the bookstore.
(The Love You Give Me)
Since you are here,
don't waste your time.
Put these back.
I don't want them anymore.
Zizhu.
Are you exhausted?
Do you
want to take a rest?
There's a famous cafe ahead.
We can go there together.
No.
Well.
How about we watch a movie together?
A new horror movie has been released.
You love horror movies, right?
Let's watch it together.
I don't want to watch it.
What do you want to do then?
I'll keep you company.
I want you to shut up.
Hardy should've been back with Quanquan
by now after their game.
You don't have to look
at your watch every 30 seconds.
Quanquan
must have chosen
this watch for me with care.
I asked him.
He didn't have enough money
after buying me the necklace.
Only this watch was at a discount.
So, it was basically
a buy-one-free-one watch.
Is it that hard for you
to admit that our son
loves me more?
If we were at the company,
I would say that our son loves you more.
But we are at home now.
How is that different?
You are our major shareholder
at the company.
So, I have to make you happy
But at home,
you are my boyfriend
and the father to our son.
You have to make me happy instead.
So, you know.
You've been looking at your phone
the whole time we are eating.
You have such a handsome man
sitting right across from you.
But you don't even spare me a glance.
You want to buy a house?
No.
You want to sell your house?
I've thought about it.
The only way to get a lot of money
in such a short period
is to sell my house.
You don't have to do that.
I can lend you the money
if you really need it.
Then, you can slowly pay me back.
If you sell your house now,
what about you and Quanquan?
Where will you stay?
Why are you smiling?
I'm not.
I saw you smiling just now.
Selling the house quickly
is indeed the only way.
Have you found yourself
a property agent?
Not yet.
Not yet? I'll find one for you.
Hello, Hardy.
Get a property agent for me.
To sell a house.
Not me. It's Min Hui.
Another thing.
Where are you now?
What are you doing?
Okay.
Be careful.
Where are they?
Are you full?
Not yet.
You should stop eating anyway.
You only paid the interest
this afternoon.
It's time for the final payment.
The final payment?
Here's your final payment.
You...
- Stop eating.
- Xin Qi.
Hurry up. They won't be back
for another two hours.
Hurry up.
You asked me to quit and I did.
When can I return to Guanchao?
I'm going to be bored to death.
How about
you do something for me?
What is it?
I heard that Cao Mu and He Haixiang
are planning to execute MBO.
Come up with a way
to find out
how much they are going to offer
in the takeover bid.
Are you really going
to acquire Be Agile?
No.
Is it because of Min Hui?
Of course not.
She doesn't deserve my attention.
I want to acquire Be Agile
for Guanchao's future development.
Be Agile has developed at a fast pace
for the past two years.
It doesn't matter which company
will acquire it in the end.
It'll still become a major threat
to Guanchao in the future.
Rather than letting that happen,
we should take control of it.
You are right.
But Min Hui...
I promise you
that once I acquire the company,
I'll fire her at once.
(Yitang Serviced Apartment)
Ms. Min.
Your house is in a good condition.
It's open, spacious and in good shape.
The garden and
the management here are great too.
If you put it on sale,
I'm sure it'll be a great hit.
But the only problem is,
you want to get the payment in full.
And you want to sell it quickly.
If you do that,
you can't sell it at its best price.
I understand.
I'll sell this house for 3.5 million.
I'm sure that's a reasonable price.
Indeed.
I'll put this house on sale then.
If I have someone
who's interested in this house,
when will it be convenient for you
to show them the house?
Any time.
You can inform us
at any time.
Okay.
I'll put it up on sale when
I go back to my office then.
If there's nothing else,
I'll take my leave now.
Okay. Let me see you out.
Thank you.
You don't have to see me out.
I'll leave it to you then.
Okay.
Why are you so excited
about me selling the house?
Is it wrong for me to help you?
I'll admit it.
After you sell your house,
you'll have nowhere to stay.
So, does it mean
that you and Quanquan
will move in with me?
I knew it.
I know that you want
your personal space.
It's okay.
My house is big enough.
Not only can you have
your personal space,
it can also be like Inception.
Min Hui, I really want
to see you every day
when I wake up.
Can you sacrifice a little bit
for me?
Just a little bit.
I'm sure Quanquan
will be happy about it.
It's indeed true
that I don't have a better place
to go right now.
Yes!
Let's pack up your things.
Bring whatever you need
and for those you don't need,
we can just ask them to clear those out.
I'll do the packing.
Good morning.
I've made breakfast for you.
Eat it while it's hot.
Such a luxurious breakfast.
You even cooked egg, my favorite.
Do you want milk or orange juice?
Milk.
Let me pour it for you.
What are you hiding? Why so mysterious?
Here you go.
By the way,
if you have nothing to do tonight,
can you come back earlier?
Why?
Nothing.
It's just that you've been
so busy lately.
So, I want to treat you
to some good food.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
Here's your milk.
(Yitang Serviced Apartment)
We just talked about packing up
and you already have five boxes.
Are you testing me?
Stop.
I just want to pack a little bit
whenever I can,
so that it won't be too overwhelming
when we have to move.
What's wrong?
Are you reluctant to sell the house?
From down payment to mortgage,
I bought this house with the money
that I had saved up little by little.
Look at this sofa.
Quanquan's toys.
And the design of this house.
I did it all by myself.
I really thought
that this house
would be me and Quanquan's forever home.
Don't cry.
Maybe
we shouldn't sell it.
Let's not sell it. I don't want to move.
Sell it.
You have to sell it.
You can't keep it.
I know.
I'm just
emotionally attached to it.
It's a house.
I know.
After I sell it,
I can buy it again
when I have the money.
A house
is not a home.
Home is where your family is.
I belong
with my family.
Quanquan and I will be your home
from now on.
It'll be yours too.
All of you belong to me.
(Good morning.)
(Goodnight. Have a good sleep.
I'm a little bit tired today.)
(Are you awake?
You have been blacklisted.)
I need Min Hui.
She's a woman.
I'm sure she knows what to do.
Come in. No need to change your shoes.
Why?
What are you doing?
I plan to sell this house soon.
So, I'm packing up.
You are going to sell the house?
Min Hui.
Where is Quanquan's Iron Man helmet?
It's just in there.
Look carefully. I'm sure you'll find it.
Yes. I plan to sell it.
You are going to lose
great neighbors like me and Quanquan.
But the good news is,
you are going to get the set of books
that you've always wanted.
Is it because you can't
take them with you?
It's painful for me to part with them.
Let me inform you
that I've officially become
Min Hui's boyfriend.
Her future husband.
So,
keep your distance from her.
You are just dating each other.
Does she have to sell the house?
Can't Min Hui be my neighbor?
I'm not the one who wants
to sell the house.
The executives of Be Agile
plan to purchase Be Agile together.
So, I need a huge amount of money.
I've misunderstood you.
Are you going to become
a businesswoman after this?
Stop joking.
We'll have to succeed
in acquiring it first.
By the way,
I'm going to meet someone
from a private equity firm
this afternoon with Cao Mu.
Have a seat.
Where can you sit?
It's okay. You don't have
to entertain me. Just do your thing.
Okay. I'll get back to packing.
Iron Man.
You are so rich.
But why does Min Hui need
to sell her house to get the money?
I want to give her the money.
But she doesn't want it.
You look so despicable.
At first, I wanted
to give you some tips.
But now, I've changed
my mind.
I don't need tips from you.
But there's something
that you can help me with.
You look so despicable.
Mr. Cai is just like Xin Qi.
He comes from a family of investors too.
But the scale of their investment
is not as large as Blue Jay's.
And he's quite new
to the medical technology industry.
Of course.
Not everyone is as capable as Xin Qi.
Look at how proud you are of him.
I wonder who's the one
saying
that she would never get back together
with Xin Qi.
I wonder who's the one
saying that
she's so afraid of falling in love.
But now, you are in such
a passionate relationship
with Chen Jiajun.
I just hope that he won't be irrational.
Did you fight again?
If only we were fighting.
He's going to propose to me.
Really?
Yes.
I even saw the ring.
And our names are engraved on it.
I never thought
that he would be such a brave young man.
Not bad.
Excuse me.
Now is not the time to praise him.
You know
why I broke up
with my previous boyfriends, right?
I know. You don't want to get married.
Maybe Chen Jiajun
is different.
Yes.
He's different
from my previous boyfriends.
But it doesn't mean
that I'll accept marriage for him.
Okay.
What are you going to do then?
What else can I do?
I'll just stay away from him.
He's here.
Let's get down to business first.
Hello, Mr. Cai.
Ms. Cao.
You know each other?
What a coincidence.
That's great. Please have a seat.
Please have a seat.
Excuse me.
Turn it off.
Stop cleaning this place.
There's a puddle of water
in the office kitchen.
Go and clean it up.
It'll be bad if someone slips on it.
Here. Let me help you.
I can do it myself.
Go. It's over there.
Okay.
(G.M. OFFICE)
I'm sure you are hiding
something from me.
(Be Agile Medical Technology
MBO Proposal)
He Haixiang.
Even you are going to discard me.
Mr. Cai.
Although Be Agile doesn't have
many patented technologies,
I can assure you
that each of our project
surpasses other inventions
in the same industry,
especially
the AI heart modeling technology
that we have mentioned just now.
For that technology...
About that,
you already told me enough info
when we met last time.
Mr. Cai.
I'm really sorry for last time.
I didn't take care
of my personal matter properly.
I apologize for that.
Why?
Do you think
that I'm someone who holds a grudge?
Of course not.
When I met you last time,
you made a good impression on me.
Especially when you talked
about your field of expertise,
your confidence was quite attractive.
Thank you.
Yes.
Min Hui is a workaholic.
And she's very capable.
She's one of the best researchers
in this industry in Bincheng.
Everyone acknowledges it.
She leads the R&D
of all of Be Agile's core technologies.
She's the core of our company.
I believe that.
I have a rule of thumb
in my investment principles.
And it's to value talents.
Since Ms. Min is in Be Agile,
it's worth the investment.
I look forward to working with you.
I'll revise the contract and
send it to your e-mail account.
Okay.
I have another appointment later.
I have to leave now.
Okay. Let me see you out.
You don't have to do that.
Farewell, Mr. Cai.
You are amazing, Ms. Cao.
You closed the deal so easily.
You should learn from me.
Come. Let's eat.
Actually, I think Cai Wenbin
is a good man.
If Xin Qi didn't interrupt you
last time,
you might have gotten together with him.
Do you dare to say this
in front of Xin Qi?
Of course not.
He's our God of Fortune.
I wouldn't dare to offend him.
Your God of Fortune is here.
Hello, Mr. Xin.
Hello.
Why are you here?
Zhou Ruji told me that he has a friend
who wants to look at the house.
So, I'm here to pick you up.
Look at you now.
How did you pretend so well in front
of He Haixiang and the others?
You have to ask her.
Ms. Cao, let us send you back.
No.
Forget it.
I don't want to become
the third wheel.
I'll get going now.
Min Hui.
Remember to call Mr. Cai tomorrow
to thank him properly.
Me?
Mr. Cai?
Who is he?
The investor we've just met.
He's young and handsome.
He even went on a blind date
with Min Hui before.
He's going to invest in us
because of Min Hui.
Min Hui.
You are amazing.
Blind...
Blind date? Which one?
The one that you don't know.
Who is he?
You don't know him.
He's no one.
Cao Mu.
You need to let your man
feel some sense of crisis.
It's a free tip from me.
Mr. Xin, I'll get going now. Bye.
Thank you, Ms. Cao.
Cao Mu! Who is he?
He's no one.
Who is he?
Zhou Ruji must be waiting for us.
Zhou Ruji is waiting for us.
Let's go now.
This is not important.
Cao Mu.
Ms. Lin.
No. I forgot.
You are no longer
the director of Guanchao.
Cheng Qirang is so unmanly.
He has discarded you after using you.
I heard
that the executives of Be Agile
are pooling their funds
to execute the MBO.
If I'm not wrong,
you are not included, right?
Are you planning on leaving Be Agile?
What do you mean?
I'm sure you've heard
that Guanchao plans to acquire Be Agile.
Once we acquire it,
Mr. Cheng will have the power
to decide who to stay and who to leave.
You've been in Be Agile
for so many years.
You've always been eclipsed by Min Hui.
Don't you want to shine for once?
Nothing comes for free.
I'm sure it's not as simple as that.
Of course.
According to Mr. Cheng,
as long as you can
find out the amount
of their takeover bid for us,
you'll become the future deputy director
of the R&D of Be Agile.
According to Mr. Cheng?
Although I've quit Guanchao,
I'm sure you know about my relationship
with Cheng Qirang.
There are a lot of things that I'm doing
on his behalf because he can't do them.
It doesn't matter
if you don't believe me.
Just don't regret it in the future.
Help me inform Mr. Cheng
that I will
get him what he wants.
Your house is beautiful.
And my budget is very close
to your selling price.
If there's no problem with you,
I can sign the contract
tomorrow morning.
And I'll pay you in full
by the afternoon.
Mr. Qian.
Don't you have to compare it
with the price of other houses?
Just call me Qian.
Or Qian Dele.
You are Mr. Zhou's friend.
And this house is in a prime location.
The price is also reasonable.
I don't want to cause any delay
and lose it to someone else.
He has been looking
at different houses for a month.
He has checked out
all the houses nearby.
So far, this is the one
he likes the most.
If that's the case,
I'll draw up the contract later
and we can sign it tomorrow morning.
Okay.
Yes. But I'm in a hurry to move in.
So...
I understand.
How about this?
After you sign the contract
and settle the payment,
I'll move everything out in five days.
Five days?
Well...
After all, I have so many things here.
How about three days?
Give me three days.
Okay.
It's a deal then. Three days.
Okay. It's a deal.
Deal.
I have other things to do.
I have to leave now.
Okay. I'll see you out.
See you later, Qian.
See you later.
The lift is right in front of the door.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Where is he?
He has already left.
What's wrong?
Ruji.
I think I have a love rival.
I hope I'm thinking too much.
Cao Mu.
Take a seat first.
- Cao Mu.
- Chen Jiajun.
Don't say anything. Let me talk first.
Let's
break up.
Why?
Do you know me?
Why would you propose to me?
Do you even know what I want?
I thought that you wouldn't want
to get married at such a young age.
If I had known,
I would tell you
that I don't plan to get married now.
But...
But you can't break up with me
just because
I want to marry you.
Why not?
If we have different
future expectations,
breaking up is the best choice.
Although I'm reluctant
to break up with you,
if you want to choose someone...
I can accept it.
I can really accept it.
Actually...
Actually, I don't really want
to get married too.
It's just that last time,
you said that you don't need me
to take care of you
because I'm not your husband.
So, I thought you were hinting at me
to propose to you.
No.
I was not hinting at you.
You scared me.
Well.
Maybe I was overthinking it.
When I think
about breaking up with you,
I feel so upset.
Let's be together
as usual.
We'll not get married
and we won't break up with each other.
I'll go and take a bath first.
Then, I'll freshen up
and we can go out
to have some good food.
Wait.
Let me fill the tub with water first.
Wait for me.
(Marry Me)
Can I
kiss you?
(You can't.)
(But I can.)
Moving is so tiring.
Oh my goodness.
Your house is so small.
Why are there so many things?
Are you saying
that I have too many things?
I'll move them back now.
No.
You've fallen into my trap now.
You can't run away.
I'm not trying to run away.
But I'm a little bit hungry now.
Do you want to grab a bite?
Let's eat out.
Before that,
let me have an appetizer first.
Wait.
Hello, Mr. Cai.
Okay.
Please wait for a while.
I'll go there at once.
Which Mr. Cai?
Is he the one Cao Mu mentioned?
Why is he looking for you?
He wants to discuss something
with me in person
about the project.
So, I have to meet him for a while.
He can go to Cao Mu instead.
Why did he call you?
He wants to talk
about the technical part of the project.
Only I can give him
the answers he needs.
It's not Cao Mu's field of expertise.
I can't eat with you today.
But
if you feel bored,
you can unpack the things for me first.
Thank you. I'll get going now.
Mr. Xin, I've already cleaned out
the outside of the house.
Ms. Min Hui.
Why is she leaving?
I thought that she took a leave
for moving today.
Clean this place up.
How can I do that by myself?
What is it?
Are you avoiding me because
you know that you've done
something wrong?
Mr. Ding.
Mr. He is the one
who approved my transfer.
I have done nothing wrong.
Do you think that
by working with Min Hui,
she can protect you forever?
Let me be truthful to you.
Her good days will end soon.
What are you talking about?
What's going to happen to Ms. Min?
Not only her,
He Haixiang,
Cao Mu
and the other executives
will find themselves in serious trouble.
Guanchao is determined
to acquire Be Agile.
Min Hui and the others are planning
to execute MBO.
They are fools.
After Guanchao acquires Be Agile,
who will have full power
over the R&D teams?
You are a smart person.
I'm sure you know.
You are too kind, Mr. Ding.
I don't know what you are talking about.
When I become
the deputy director of the R&D,
I'll appoint you as the project manager.
All you need to do as an assistant
is to find a chance
to put this listening device on Min Hui.
That's it.
Think carefully.
(Reading Mi)
Thank you for today.
You are willing to help me out
despite being so busy.
I feel hopeful for Be Agile to have
a future comrade like you.
It's an honor.
Actually, these two
are quite useful too.
You should read them as well.
More books?
When can I finish them?
With your reading speed,
I'm sure it won't be a problem.
Why is it him again?
Looks like the trick last time
didn't work.
I have to learn more
from you after this.
You are too humble.
Be careful.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Did he hit you?
No. I'm fine.
Thank you.
And he's still trying to woo her.
(The Love You Give Me)
Excuse me, are you going
to buy this book?
Yes.
The counter is over there.
You can check out later.
Okay.
Mr. Cai.
You can check out your books first.
I want to buy some toys for my son.
Okay.
♪It's the thread of fate
that ties you and me♪
♪Like old dreams that come back♪
♪I'm shedding tears, again♪
♪When misunderstandings♪
♪Befall us like a heavy downpour♪
♪My heart is gone♪
♪Whenever I forget,
astonishment reminds me again♪
♪Everything feels like yesterday,
just what can I say?♪
♪'Cause I always love you♪
♪The love you give me from all sides♪
♪And I can't lose it no matter what♪
♪'Cause I always love you♪
♪How much the memories must tremble♪
♪To evoke your empathy?♪
♪My love♪
♪The lonely hourglass
flowing to the end♪
♪Make peace with the past♪
♪After rain comes the rainbow♪
♪I will have the love
that I've looked forward to♪
♪'Cause I always love you♪
♪How long have we been
lingering around?♪
♪We still wander around
the threshold of time♪
♪'Cause I always love you♪
♪Waiting for your heart
to be met by mine♪
♪Don't ever let our love
be in vain again♪
♪My love♪