♪You are my forever love I swear♪
♪Love and hate entangle us♪
♪I saw you in countless glances♪
♪Never want to part again in this life♪
[Circle of Love]
[Episode 6]
How's it going?
Luckily, the bullet hit her
just below the shoulder blade.
There is still some distance from the heart.
It's been taken out.
Is she out of danger?
I'll prescribe some medicine.
Make sure you will watch her drink it.
She may have a fever at night.
Don't let the wound get infected.
Let's see if she can get through the night.
OK. Thank you.
Please.
OK.
Am I going to die?
Without my permission,
the King of Hell dare not accept you.
It looks like even though I'm dead,
I'm going to hell.
Take the medicine first.
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
Mr. Xiao, is this
how you treat your lifesaver?
Drink it.
Rumeng.
Get out of the way.
Mr. Xiao ordered
no one can disturb Miss Rumeng during her recovery.
You…!
Miss Zhou, please.
You are setting me completely free.
Do you think it's possible?
One bullet for one fetter.
I paid too much, didn't I?
Do you think you suffer losses?
What do you want?
Even though I saved your life,
I dare not bargain with you.
♪I thought my deep affection♪
♪Could stop your journey♪
I'm just a little hungry.
Hungry?
♪I can't tell if love is lucky or not♪
♪You came into my world by chance♪
Here.
♪It's no longer calm♪
I can't lift my hand.
♪Your comings and goings determine my mood♪
♪Your words and actions manipulate my expressions♪
It's hot.
♪Can't hide the sound of crying♪
♪My tears are too stubborn♪
♪You come like a storm♪
♪Invading my scenery♪
Is that better?
It's OK.
♪But my passion was dampened by you♪
Then have it quickly.
♪Taking away my love♪
♪Only the traumatic past is left♪
I didn't expect
he is gentle sometimes.
Be careful. It's hot.
♪Reflections of you are everywhere♪
Here.
He is very good at taking care of people.
♪Your comings and goings determine my mood♪
♪Your words and actions manipulate my expressions♪
♪Can't hide the sound of crying♪
♪My tears are too stubborn♪
♪You come like a storm♪
♪Invading my scenery♪
♪Giving me a thorough heartbreak♪
Take the medicine first.
♪My love being woken up♪
♪But my passion was dampened by you♪
♪You are like a passing storm♪
♪Taking away my love♪
♪Only the traumatic past is left♪
♪Later I met someone else on a sunny day♪
In the future, Rumeng will be my personal maid.
She only takes orders from me.
♪Invading my scenery♪
The treatment of an ordinary maid
and a personal maid
is completely different.
This will be your room from now on.
If you need something else,
I'll send someone to buy them.
He looks indifferent but is warm-hearted.
♪Taking away my love♪
♪Only the traumatic past is left♪
♪Later I met someone else on a sunny day♪
♪Reflections of you are everywhere♪
♪Turns out the sunshine appears after you leave♪
People who know you know you are a maid.
People who don't know you may think
Hongye invited you here.
Fresh air
contributes to good health.
When did you become so weak?
You are using this to seduce Hongye.
Get up.
Stop it!
Hongye,
she doesn't look like a maid at all.
I asked her to stay here.
Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
I feel a little cold.
If I had Miss Zhou's fox fur cloak,
I may feel very warm.
You…!
Give it to me.
Hongye, she is acting.
Forget it.
It's just a cold cough.
It can't be compared
with being shot.
Give it to me.
On the battlefield,
Cheng Ming and I went through fire and water.
It depends on absolute obedience.
If such a situation happens again in the future,
do whatever I ask you to do.
Understand?
At this moment,
don't preach anymore.
I'm not preaching.
Saving people is not a life for a life.
All right.
You know best.
Of course.
♪Be alone, lost in thought♪
♪Be solitary for the rest of my life♪
♪Many years have passed♪
♪Sighing you have been born♪
♪But I have not been born yet♪
♪Times change but I am still waiting♪
♪Alas, you have been born but I have not yet♪
♪Seedlings grow only staining my springtime sorrow♪
♪Alas, we are far apart♪
♪Falling flowers carry my affection♪
♪Alas, you have been born but I have not yet♪
♪The heart can only hold one person♪
♪Tears fall like rain♪
♪Broken string, silence, still wind♪
♪Alas, you have been born but I have not yet♪
♪Seedlings grow only staining my springtime sorrow♪
♪Alas, we are far apart♪
♪Falling flowers carry my affection♪
♪Alas, you have been born but I have not yet♪
♪The heart can only hold one person♪
♪Tears fall like rain♪
Mr. Xiao.
♪Broken string, silence, still wind♪
What is it?
We got something.
Mr. Xiao, according to our survey these days,
the guys in the dance hall case
are hiding in the east of the city.
Don't startle the snake.
Yes, Mr. Xiao.
This time, I promise to catch them all.
By the way.
What about the thing I asked you to investigate?
I have got some clues,
and keep following up on them.
I want to know her whereabouts
for the last two years.
Not a day can be missed.
Yes.
Sulfuric acid!
Who are you?
Who's there?
Mr. Xiao, spare me. Mr. Xiao, spare me.
Who sent you here?
Hongye,
what are you doing in the middle of the night?
Miss Zhou, I beg you to save me.
I don't know you.
Miss Zhou, you can't turn your back on me.
Didn't you say
as long as I destroy the face of Rumeng,
you will pay off my gambling debts?
And
you asked me to get someone last time
to defile Rumeng.
Please.
You can't leave me alone.
Or the governor will beat me to death.
Shut up!
Miss Zhou, you can't do this to me.
Mr. Xiao! Mr. Xiao! I was wrong.
Mr. Xiao, I was wrong.
I was wrong, Mr. Xiao.
Go.
Mr. Xiao, she put me up to it.
Mr. Xiao, she did it.
She did it.
Mr. Xiao, I was wrong.
What do you have to say?
Yeah, that's right.
So what if I did it?
That girl is trying to seduce you.
I am just trying to teach her a lesson.
What right do you have to teach my maid?
Hongye, I am your fiancée.
In this house,
don't I have the right to make decisions?
This house?
Make decisions?
You're staying here too long.
You have the illusion of being a hostess, don't you?
What do you mean?
It's been many days.
You should go back.
Xiao Hongye,
my father is the commander.
How dare you kick me out?
Cheng Ming,
send her back.
Xiao Hongye,
you actually drive me away because of a maid.
I'm telling you, I won't let her go.
Miss Zhou, the car is ready.
Let me help you.
This is the ancestral medicine of my family.
It won't leave a scar.
Does it hurt?
No.
You are still trying to be brave at this time.
If I say it hurts,
so what?
♪Many years have passed♪
♪The sight stirs up my feelings♪
♪Leaning on the table, eavesdropping♪
♪He recites poems at night♪
♪How to forget it♪
♪Be alone, lost in thought♪
♪Be solitary for the rest of my life♪
♪Many years have passed♪
♪Sighing you have been born♪
♪But I have not been born yet♪
♪Times change but I am still waiting♪