♪You are my forever love I swear♪
♪Love and hate entangle us♪
♪I saw you in countless glances♪
♪Never want to part again in this life♪
[Circle of Love]
[Episode 13]
Father.
Mother.
Although the Gu family was unpardonable,
they also paid the price.
As for Gu Meng…
Punish her to stay with me all her life.
Please forgive me for being unfilial.
Mr. Xiao, what are you doing here?
This is the Governor's Mansion.
Of course, I can come whenever I want.
You are right.
You come here late at night.
What can I do for you?
I have something to ask you.
♪The moon hangs askew, pure and flawless♪
♪The breeze brushes the leaves
and lightly taps the red tiles♪
What is my only advantage?
Advantage?
♪Play chess and cut candles with you♪
Being cheeky is your greatest advantage.
♪The world is tumultuous and noisy♪
♪Picturesque rivers and mountains
Hard to tell good from bad♪
Duplicity is your greatest weakness.
It's too late. I'm going to bed.
♪Plant a few clumps of acacia♪
♪Blooming in the corner, in the fence♪
This is for you.
My mother left this to me.
It can keep people safe.
It is a family heirloom.
Such a valuable thing
should be left to your wife.
I'm going to bed.
♪Will swallows be returning to my home?
♪Spend the rest of your life together♪
♪No need to look for an idyllic world♪
♪Beauty floats between your eyebrows♪
♪Who would want to covet beautiful things♪
♪As unreal as fleeting clouds♪
♪Be with you in this life♪
Be careful, all of you.
Put them there.
OK.
Take care.
Hongye,
look at what I have prepared for you.
No need.
The wedding is canceled.
What?
Hongye, we are going to get married soon.
I won't marry you.
Did that bad woman Rumeng
play tricks?
This is my decision.
Hongye,
have you forgotten
how you promised my father?
I can give you one more chance.
I'll ask someone to send you back.
Good for you, Xiao Hongye.
Wait and see.
You can take it this time.
You broke off the engagement.
Mr. Zhou…
Rest assured.
I'll take care of it.
♪That cloud fell into my eyes♪
♪I can't see your expression♪
♪I thought my deep affection♪
♪Could stop your journey♪
♪The rain fell on my heart♪
This is chicken soup with ginseng
I specially asked the kitchen to make.
♪You came into my world by chance♪
♪It's no longer calm♪
Here, drink it while it's hot.
♪Your words and actions manipulate my expressions♪
♪Can't hide the sound of crying♪
♪My tears are too stubborn♪
♪You come like a storm♪
Shall I call a doctor?
I'm fine.
I smelled the oil
and felt kind of queasy suddenly.
I tell Cheng Ming
to change the cook.
It's me who doesn't feel well.
What does it have to do with the cook?
♪You are like a passing storm♪
♪Taking away my love♪
Let me take you to your room for a rest.
I can walk by myself.
Put me down quickly.
♪You come like a storm♪
♪Invading my scenery♪
This is the haw jelly from Fuwang Store.
This is the sour plum candy from the Yun's Store.
This is the most famous jujube pastry in Luo City.
Mr. Xiao,
we bought back all of the snacks
that can whet the appetite.
You can leave.
Yes, sir.
♪Only the traumatic past is left♪
♪Later I met someone else on a sunny day♪
That's a bit much.
♪Reflections of you are everywhere♪
The most important thing is that you like them.
♪Turns out the sunshine appears after you leave♪
It tastes a bit off.
Here?
It's a little sour.
I don't know what's going on recently.
I like this kind of sweet and sour food best.
Then I'll buy more next time.
Mr. Xiao,
Mr. Zhou brought people here.
I'll be right back.
No matter what,
I want to be with you.
OK.
Xiao Hongye,
you broke off the engagement again and again.
You are humiliating me on purpose.
Your wings are hard now.
How dare you humiliate my daughter.
You really don't care about me.
I dare not.
I'll give you one last chance.
You either
hold a grand wedding party
to marry my daughter
or
kill this girl right now.
Mr. Zhou,
I can't do any of that.
What if I kill you now?
Mr. Zhou,
this is the Governor's Mansion.
If something happens to the governor,
none of you will live.
It's easy.
Let him marry my daughter right now.
Otherwise,
I kill all of you.
I, Xiao Hongye,
will not marry anyone else in my life except Rumeng.
Father, kill this bad woman.
What did you say to Mr. Zhou just now?
It's just what he's interested in.
Iron ore, munitions, stuff like that.
It's all because of me.
Sorry…
I don't want to hear an apology.
I…
Not even thanks.
Let me say something that you want to hear.
What?
Aren't you always curious
what the advantage is?
That is, I like you.
With this advantage,
even though your faults are as numerous
as the stars,
it doesn't matter anymore.
Say something.
Action is better.
♪In the blue sea♪
♪The secrets of the wind are surging♪
♪But being eavesdropping by the moon♪
♪Crying loudly deep in the sea♪
♪Your broad and soft fins♪
♪Are out of reach♪
♪Leaping into the air♪
♪Embrace the tides like the moon♪
♪Fearless of the distance between sea and sky♪
♪The flying fireflies fly toward you♪
♪As obsessed with you as I am♪
♪You come from the blue sea♪
♪Don't understand my loneliness♪
♪And I wander in this world♪
♪To get joy for you♪
♪How I wish one day♪
♪You could accidentally♪
♪Find I have been staying♪
♪In your eyes♪
♪You come from the blue sea♪
♪Don't understand my loneliness♪
♪And I'm hiding in a sea of faces♪
♪To sell love to you♪
♪If one day you could♪
♪Jump into the sky for me♪
♪You will find traces of my love for you♪
♪You come from the blue sea♪
♪Don't understand my loneliness♪
♪And I wander in this world♪
♪To get joy for you♪
♪How I wish one day♪
♪You could accidentally♪
♪Find I have been staying♪
♪In your eyes♪
♪You come from the blue sea♪
♪Don't understand my loneliness♪
♪And I'm hiding in a sea of faces♪
♪To sell love to you♪
♪If one day you could♪
♪Jump into the sky for me♪
♪You will find traces of my love for you♪
You're up.
Did you sleep well?
Not good.
You snored loudly.
You can hear me snoring.
It seems that you were not tired enough last night.
I'm talking nonsense.
You dare to talk nonsense.
See how I punish you.
I correct the mistake immediately.
Shouldn't I be rewarded?
How do you know that the punishment and reward
is not the same thing?
♪After a long night with a long dream♪
♪Sorrow welled up in my heart♪
♪The evening breeze plucks at the heartstrings♪
Is this sugar sweet?
Less than you.
♪Because of my shallow thoughts♪
♪Only then did I write some poems♪
♪Make a wish to the little fairy♪
♪Wish we meet every year♪
♪Wave the fan lightly♪
♪Hold cheeks, look up at the crescent moon♪
♪Want to chat with the spring breeze♪
♪Invite it to the banquet and chat all night♪
♪Why the moon doesn't understand me♪
♪Have a sleepless night♪
♪Only the faint fragrance of flowers♪
♪Slack off, take a break♪
♪A girl's troubles are as light as a butterfly♪
♪Fall asleep when drunk♪
Do I really have no chance?
♪Looking into the mirror♪
What do you think?
How thick-skinned you are.
Even if Rumeng refuses me a hundred times,
I will protect her one hundred and one times.
♪Only remember the breeze
but not the fleeting time♪
He's still watching us.
Miss Rumeng, there's a letter for you.
[It was Xiao Hongye who killed the Gu family]
♪Like the quietly approaching moon♪
♪The pure, bright moonlight falling into the lake♪
♪Like a flying butterfly in spring♪
♪Making my heart flutter♪
♪Just a glance with you in the sea of people♪
♪I swear I will love you forever♪