That is the uniform
worn by Jeongjingak's mages.
You will maintain your dignity
as Jeongjingak's mage
and do your best to master spells.
That is the Spirit Plaque
given to Jeongjingak's mages.
Those who possess it
are given full access to everything
in Songrim and Jeongjingak.
That is the Book of Regulations.
You will follow our rules,
and if you violate them,
you will be punished accordingly.
Jang Uk, stand up and bow to the leader.
Jang Uk, turn around
and bow to your fellow mages.
From this moment forward, Jang Uk,
the eldest son of the Jang family,
is a mage of Songrim Jeongjingak.
-Hey, Uk.
-Jang Uk.
-Congratulations.
-You have come a long way.
-All right, everyone.
Tonight, we have a welcome ceremony
for our newest mage, Jang Uk.
Let us all meet up at Chwiseonru.
The Jang family has already paid
for every bottle of alcohol
and food at Chwiseonru.
So everyone,
get ready to drink until you drop.
Chwiseonru!
-Chwiseonru!
-Jang Uk!
I remember when Jang Gang came here
with a newborn baby like it was yesterday.
I cannot believe this day has come.
I cannot believe it either.
Here.
Eat this.
What is it?
It is a raisin tree pill.
Take it before you drink.
The kids are going to drink
until they drop.
The least we can do is try to keep up.
I do not need this to prevent a hangover.
You should think of your age.
What about my age?
Look. I think I see some gray hairs.
The sunlight is fooling your eyes.
My goodness.
Do you not see how silky my hair is?
Look at how beautiful my hair is.
I shall hold on to this.
Yes, take it.
Madam Do-hwa.
Young Master Jang
has become a mage of Jeongjingak,
just like Master Jang.
You must be thrilled.
You have come a long way
since the day we first met.
I knew the moment I saw you.
You are my master.
Naksu.
I want you to be my master.
What original nonsense.
If you survive,
I will be your master.
Master.
I finally did it.
Mu-deok.
How do I look? Does it suit me?
I am not sure. What would I know?
Master, how does your pupil look?
This uniform did not seem too bad
on Seo Yul and Park Dang-gu,
but it looks impeccable on my pupil.
That is enough.
I cannot breathe.
Master.
Thank you.
All right, Mu-deok. Let us go and drink.
Uk, wait.
-Uk--
-Young Master, you look exquisite.
Young Master.
Take this before you drink.
Master Heo gave you a raisin tree pill.
A raisin tree pill?
We should share it.
Raisin tree pills are the best
at preventing hangovers.
Here you go, Maidservant Kim.
Maidservant Kim.
I was going to give this to you.
I am serious.
Maidservant Kim, come back here.
Take this. It is as good as new.
Maidservant Kim, take it. Please.
The one born with the King's Star
has entered Songrim.
His father, Jang Gang, performed sorcery
by unsealing the ice stone,
and his birth was
the result of that sorcery.
That child is a disaster to Songrim.
Why do you think
Jang Gang chose to do what he did?
He could have made his son king
and used the ice stone to master Hwansu.
Then he would have ruled the world.
Why do you think
he closed his son's gate of energy
and sealed the ice stone instead?
Because he was weak.
He sealed everything and fled
because he did not have
what it took to handle it all.
Do you think Gil-ju
might have been killed by Jang Gang?
If he has returned…
Jang Gang would not have done it
out in the open like that.
I suspect Master Lee.
We need to gain more power
before Songrim gets more involved.
Ten years ago, we succeeded
in getting our hands on the ice stone
that was sealed by Jang Gang.
You have finally found it.
Bu-yeon.
Hand over the ice stone to me.
She was so young,
yet she managed to find the ice stone.
I must admit,
her divine powers were truly astonishing.
I heard Jin Ho-gyeong is
unaware of her daughter's death
and is still looking for her.
That is why I plan to find her.
I will find the daughter
that she so longs to find,
and make Jin Ho-gyeong become my puppet.
How are you going to find a dead girl?
I will find someone.
Someone who will make her believe
that she must be her daughter, Bu-yeon.
Here. Eat this.
Have you not eaten anything
since you left Sari Village?
Goodness.
Here.
Eat this.
Eat slowly.
Why is a blind girl
heading to the city all by herself?
She is in search of a friend.
Her friend apparently stole
all of her things
and fled to Daeho Fortress.
Oh, dear. Poor girl.
Do you even know where to go?
What is your friend's name?
Mu-deok.
The name of the friend
I am looking for is Mu-deok.
-"Mu-deok"?
-How is she going to find her?
Have some tasty taffy!
-We have fresh fish!
-Try our delicious honey biscuits!
-Welcome!
-Come and have a look!
-Take a look!
-Have some rice cakes!
Goodness. The weather is nice, right?
Mom, can you buy that for me?
I do not have money for that.
Please buy it for me.
What is with you today?
All right. Just a moment.
My goodness, where is it?
-Where is my purse?
-What is the matter?
My purse is gone.
-Dear me.
-Where is my ring?
-I lost my ring too!
-Oh, dear.
What?
This is it?
This ring is cheap too.
I chatted away,
but it was all for nothing.
-Thank you.
-Pour me another glass.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
You knew who I was all along.
Seeing that you have it
instead of your friend,
I am guessing that friend is gone.
Young Master Seo?
Mu-deok.
What are you doing out here?
Are you not going to drink?
No. I have already had enough.
I am a little tipsy.
You seem fine.
I am tipsy,
which is why I am lost.
I easily get lost
whenever I am not clearheaded.
How can anyone get lost in here?
Get up. I will take you home.
You cut yourself, right?
That was dangerous.
Are you scolding me again?
Can you please save it today?
I am in no position to scold you
for I am also making a grave mistake.
You?
Yes.
I have always walked the right path.
I never did anything wrong.
But I have gone astray.
And now, I am holding your hand.
I do not know
which way I will end up going.
You will end up following me.
You are holding my hand.
Let us go.
The reason you get lost
when you have a lot on your mind
is that you are focused
on too many things.
When that happens,
just try to focus on one thing.
Right now, just focus on me and follow me.
All right. Right now, I will focus on you.
Young Master Seo, may I ask you
something that has been bothering me?
What is it?
You said that you saw an illusion of me.
What did that illusion say?
She said she was in love with me.
-What?
-Why are you so surprised?
You said that yourself quite often.
Well, that was because…
Was it really all a lie?
I am in love with you, but…
Yes, that is right, I am.
It is my token of gratitude.
Does he really believe that?
I really hope he does not.
That is enough.
This is all thanks to you, Master Heo.
I am sure Madam Do-hwa
would be happy as well.
I finally feel like
I have done something good
to make up for my guilt toward her.
You did nothing wrong.
I was the one who brought her
to Sejukwon from her hometown.
That is how she ended up
meeting Jang Gang.
Do-hwa was so kind at heart.
I cannot believe he would even think
that she would do something like that.
Jang Gang, that damn punk.
Master Heo, you are drunk.
This is all your fault!
What did I do?
The reason I brought Do-hwa to Sejukwon
was so I could set her up with you.
But what happened?
Goodness gracious.
How could you fail
to win over a woman's heart
with such good looks and competence?
You are unbelievably frustrating.
Yes, I remember.
Master Heo pretty much
set the table for you,
but you failed to take the opportunity.
I did
everything I could.
I wrote her poems.
I gave her gifts.
But you never confessed your love.
"I am in love with you."
"Will you be mine?"
You always circled those words,
never saying them out loud.
Eventually, you lost her to a man
who was much more straightforward.
Must you say your feelings out loud?
You should just be able to tell.
You can be very frustrating.
You act interested, but you stay distant.
Then you suddenly become intimate.
You need to tell a woman how you feel
so that she can make up her mind
and decide to wait for you.
If that love is fickle just because
I did not express my love out loud,
then I do not need it.
If a woman chooses to leave me
and love someone else,
then so be it.
"So be it…"
Enjoy the rest of the night.
Where are you going?
I am leaving.
Maidservant Kim.
Just stay here. Stay here and drink…
Stay here and drink with us.
Maidservant Kim. Come back, all right?
-I will be waiting.
-My goodness.
-Maidservant Kim.
-He will get rejected once again.
Maidservant Kim!
So this is where worldly people drink.
Everyone is waiting for you.
You should go inside.
My training forbids me to drink alcohol.
I have run out of tea,
so I must return to Danhyanggok.
So just pack me some food.
I will, sir.
The smell of women's perfume
and the wonderful scent of alcohol.
This is not the kind of place for me.
He loves me.
He loves me not.
He loves me. He loves me not.
He loves me. He loves me not…
Gosh, what in the world am I doing?
Forget it.
Oh, dear! My goodness!
What am I going to do?
Right.
My gosh.
You are a mage.
Master Lee?
You are Master Lee, are you not?
I am a maid working for the Jang family.
I serve Young Master Jang.
Thank you.
No need to thank me.
Goodness.
I think it got tangled
when you held onto me.
Wait. Let me do it.
Excuse me for this.
All done.
I have been waiting for you
to show up today
so I could thank you for what you did.
There we go.
Where did he go?
Master Lee?
Is it because I have not taken
chaste herb tea for a while?
SEJUKWON
Master Heo is not here right now.
But he has been waiting for you to arrive.
Please come inside.
A welcome ceremony
for a new mage at Jeongjingak?
Master Heo will come home drunk.
We both know
how much Grandfather loves alcohol.
Young Lady,
should we also head to Chwiseonru?
Your future husband will be there.
-What?
-Madam Heo told me everything.
I heard your grandfather has picked out
a few mages to be your future husband.
Among them are Park Dang-gu,
the heir of Songrim,
and Seo Yul from the Seo family.
I am not here to get married.
I am here to help out
at the royal infirmary.
Do you think the Crown Prince
is also on the list?
-With your beauty--
-Sun-i.
Your fussing has already
embarrassed me once.
Have you forgotten?
Oh, you mean that arrogant mage?
We should have asked for his name
so we could tell Master Heo.
You are right.
I should have asked what his name was.
Are you all right?
I wonder if I will ever…
get to see him again.
That is enough.
Uk, you owe me one,
so promise me this.
-Promise you what?
-That one day,
when I ask you to do something,
you will promise to do it no matter what.
All right. I promise.
Oh, wait.
Before you make your promise,
there is something I must clarify.
I am asking you this because
you are acquainted with Master Lee.
By any chance, have you been
taking the chaste herb tea for training?
No, I have not. Never.
So you are not practicing celibacy?
Of course not. I want to get married.
That is just ridiculous.
Then all is good. Here.
You are also a candidate now.
All three of you are candidates.
Do not forget to thank Master Lee.
If he did not vouch for you,
things would have gotten complicated.
Of course.
You almost had people
get the wrong idea about you
by mastering Tansu,
which was Naksu's specialty.
Uk even wanted to become Naksu's pupil.
What do you mean?
Pardon?
He was frustrated that he could not find
a master to open his gate of energy.
So he said it as a joke.
Did you really
say that?
Yes, I did.
Yul, I want you to tell him
what kind of punishment is given
to mages who perform sorcery.
If you perform sorcery,
your entire energy flow will be cut off,
and you will be unable to cast any spells.
Then you will get banished from Daeho,
and your descendants will never
be able to become mages.
Remember that.
Do not ever say anything like that again.
Why is it wrong to perform sorcery?
What?
Regular magic can kill people too.
On the contrary,
sorcery can help save someone's life.
Rather than differentiating
between the two,
a person's true intention behind the spell
seems a lot more important.
Then are you saying
you are open to using sorcery
if it means you could save someone's life?
If I can use sorcery to save someone,
then I do not think it would be a problem.
You damn boy! How dare you!
You are a mage of Jeongjingak.
How dare you say that
you are open to using sorcery?
If this is how you are going to be,
give me back
the torrent of energy I gave you.
-My lord.
-What is it?
The Crown Prince is on his way here
to meet Jang Uk.
Your Royal Highness.
Hello, Your Royal Highness.
The Crown Prince has arrived!
Formally greet him with respect!
I came because I heard
there was a celebration.
But it seems like I have ruined it.
If you think about it,
all this is being held thanks to me,
which makes me a welcome guest.
So why the heavy atmosphere?
I am sure that deep down inside,
you were wishing for my funeral
instead of a party like this.
So the least I can do
is greet you solemnly
with a straight face.
Whether it is a party or funeral,
it is always important
that there is alcohol.
So I brought you a jar of alcohol.
What if they get into another fight?
My lord, you should go down there.
Let us wait and see what happens.
To congratulate Uk on defeating me,
I will pour him a drink.
You have mastered Ryusu
and became a mage of Jeongjingak
in less than two months
since your gate of energy has opened.
This is to congratulate you.
I may have lost the duel against you,
but I am extremely happy
as the Crown Prince.
Daeho was blessed
with a great mage like you.
That is definitely something
worth celebrating.
Drink this
and become the best mage
that this country has ever seen.
Make Daeho proud.
Jang Uk.
Thank you, Your Royal Highness.
I will also pour you a glass.
I hope you become
a great leader of this country.
Become a great leader,
Your Royal Highness.
Thank goodness.
The Crown Prince
does not hold any grudges.
The Crown Prince, the heir to the throne.
And the boy who was born
on the night of the King's Star.
Two of Jinyowon's precious treasures
have broken.
They are useless as relics,
as they no longer hold energy.
Burn them and throw the ashes
into Lake Gyeongcheondaeho.
Yes, Mother.
Lady Jin, Master Jin has returned.
Father is here?
Cho-yeon.
Honey.
Father!
Goodness, Cho-yeon.
Let me see your face.
You look more beautiful than ever.
I am back.
I found her on
a volcanic island in the south.
She lost her parents at a young age,
so she has no memories of them.
She seems old enough to be Bu-yeon.
Is there anything you have had
ever since you were a small child?
Unlike Bu-yeon, she cannot detect energy,
and she does not know
how to cast any spells.
Maybe she lost her powers
while she was away from Jinyowon.
But if she is truly
a member of the Jin family,
her powers will easily come back to her.
This door will show us
whether or not you are
a true member of the Jin family.
Am I not the daughter
that your family once lost long ago?
No, I do not think so.
But to thank you for coming this far,
I will give you enough for your trip back.
Do you think Mother will get angry again
out of disappointment?
What should we do, Father?
Mother.
The bird inside the cage has died.
You are right. Poor thing.
Up until yesterday, I could feel
faint but warm energy.
But there is nothing now.
Although I am able to see,
you still noticed this first.
All living things in this world
have energy.
And detecting energy
is how I see the world.
Bu-yeon, you may not be able
to see what other people see.
But you are a special girl
who can see things that they cannot.
You made me a new eye mask.
Mother, put it on for me.
Honey.
Do not be so disappointed.
I brought her here
without much expectation.
So you just brought anyone?
I guess you are just
pretending to please me.
That is why we have failed
to find her for ten years.
I…
I will start searching for her again.
Forget it.
Jin Mu from Cheonbugwan
will help us find Bu-yeon.
I thought you abhorred
that half brother of yours.
I do abhor him.
But if it means finding Bu-yeon,
I no longer mind
joining hands with Jin Mu.
-Get lost.
-Go away.
I am here in search of someone.
Mu-deok is here, right?
Things are busy here tonight,
so return next time.
You keep pushing me.
You must not know who I am.
Who are you?
I am a mage from one of the main families
in this country.
Do you want me to show you
who I am with my energy?
Consider yourself lucky.
Had I contained energy in my hand,
you would have died.
I apologize. Please forgive me.
This is just a brothel. You dare
discriminate against your customers?
The mages from Songrim Jeongjingak
are having a celebration inside.
-Songrim?
-Yes.
And the Crown Prince is here too,
so things were too hectic.
I heard she got sold
to the biggest brothel in Daeho.
This must be one special brothel.
If you tell me which family you are from,
I will announce your visit.
Do not bother. I will come back next time.
What is going on?
Who was that?
She says she is a mage
from one of the main families.
I think it is Jinyowon.
I saw her wearing something on her neck
with Jinyowon's crest on it.
Jinyowon?
Those mages of Jinyowon
are always busy being choosy and rude.
Are you all right?
It does not hurt that much.
She was not very strong for a mage.
What if she was lying?
That crest of Jinyowon might be fake.
If you get caught using the name
of a mage's family within Daeho Fortress,
you could even get killed.
What a suspicious woman.
I guess mages really do have
the most power inside Daeho Fortress.
Mu-deok must be in there somewhere.
I need to live off of her for a while.
If I tell her that I came to return this,
I am sure she will let me stay.
After all, she is foolishly kind.
-Who goes there?
-Gosh, that startled me.
Wait for me outside.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
She should be out here by now.
One, two, three.
Four, five…
Your Royal Highness.
Once again, I was immensely touched
by your endless generosity.
Yes, I pretended to be kind and generous.
If I could, I would have
overturned the place.
But like I said, I do not want
the mages of Songrim as my enemy.
What? Do you think I am narrow-minded?
It was very wise and smart of you
to hide the petty emotions you felt.
I chose to share my pettiness
only with you, Filthy Mu-deok.
I know how unbearable it must have been
to pour him a congratulatory drink
when you probably wanted
to poison him instead.
That is why I ran out here in such a rush.
I hate your master so much,
it is gut-wrenching.
Of course.
My liver burns with how much I hate him.
Yes, I am sure.
And you, who support him…
I do not like you, either.
My generosity was for you, not him.
Filthy Mu-deok.
If you get involved in a fight again
between me and your master,
I shall kill you first.
Your Royal Highness,
if I ever have to die by your sword,
I will not resent you.
So you will stick by your master
no matter what?
What a loyal servant.
Should I build a memorial for you
in that outhouse?
Goodness, I am honored
to receive your acknowledgment.
Forget it. Get lost.
Before I lose my generosity
and become petty again.
-Your Royal Highness.
-What? What do you want?
Do you have a death wish or what?
Are you all right? How is your injury?
You could have asked quicker.
Do not worry.
It was not an impressive attack.
And Heo Yeom already treated me.
You were caught off guard because
you expected nothing from my young master,
but you clearly are
much stronger than he is.
Of course, I am.
Who knew Jang Uk would use Tansu?
That crook.
Oh, you mean the sachet
that she hung by the outhouse
to get rid of flies?
Where is the sachet I gave you?
Why do you ask?
I am wondering if you hung it
by the outhouse to get rid of flies.
I have it right here.
Why would I put something so precious
by the outhouse?
Right? I knew you would never do that.
All is good, then.
Return safely, Your Royal Highness.
-That is enough.
-My gosh.
-Young Master Jang.
-Leave me alone.
Will you please wake up, Your Master?
-Hey.
-Look at him.
He will stay drunk until tomorrow morning.
He is a lightweight.
But he drank every glass
that was offered by the Crown Prince.
Then you could have helped.
You are the only one who is fine.
I was busy singing.
Put down the palanquin.
Only those who are authorized by Songrim
can enter from here.
If you are not with Songrim, go back.
You cannot enter.
I am Mu-deok.
I am Young Master Jang's maid.
You know that.
Until now, you were allowed to enter
as Jang Uk's maid because he was a guest.
But not anymore.
Jang Uk is a member of Songrim,
but you are not.
So you may not enter.
Then what about Young Master Jang?
He is so drunk that he passed out.
I should be there to take care of him.
The servants of Jeongjingak
will take care of him from now on.
No!
I need to take care
of Young Master Jang by his side.
Please let me in.
You should just let her in.
Uk will throw a fit if he wakes up
without Mu-deok around.
Not a single Jeongjingak mage
was given the right to a personal servant.
Now that Jang Uk is with Songrim,
he must abide by our rules.
So are you saying I really cannot enter?
That is the rule.
You should go home for now.
I will take Uk home after he wakes up.
Jang Uk cannot leave.
He cannot leave Songrim
until he is done with his basic training.
That is also our rule.
Right. It was like that for us too.
Are you saying
I cannot enter
and my master cannot come outside?
So we cannot be together?
Now that you know,
you should start heading back with them.
Wait…
It is Jang Uk's first day at Jeongjingak.
Do you want him
to break the rules on his first day?
Young Masters! Please let me in!
If you two stay here, she will not leave.
If the leader finds out,
she will get punished.
So let us go inside.
Mu-deok, go home for now.
We will try to find a way.
Young Master!
Please take me with you!
My goodness gracious!
Grandfather, have you been well?
Yes, of course.
You have grown up to be a fine young lady.
Master Heo, one of the drunk mages
was brought here
because of his irregular breathing.
Goodness, he is just drunk.
You can treat him yourself.
He is Jang Uk.
You gave him your torrent of energy.
What? Jang Uk?
Uk?
He is that mage.
Yun-ok, come over here.
Yes.
His gate of energy remained closed
for a long time, and I opened it for him.
I even gave him my torrent of energy.
His name is Jang Uk.
"Jang Uk"?
Yes. It has only been a month,
but he has already mastered Ryusu.
He is a genius.
In just one month?
He really is amazing.
Well, I am quite drunk,
so I should go to my room and sleep.
Please take care of him for me.
Go ahead.
All right, Grandfather.
We meet again.
Young Master Jang Uk.
I have come too far to give up.
I will get inside no matter what.
Mu-deok.
Your young master is dying here.
My head is spinning like crazy.
Jang Uk.
If you abandon me,
I swear I will kill you.
Young Master Seo?
I figured you might still be here.
And I was right.
I refuse to leave.
I must be with my young master.
Waiting here will not solve anything.
If you stay here, Uk will break the rules.
Then his hard work to get into Songrim
will have been for nothing.
You are right.
For now, go home and wait.
I will take you home.
Please tell this to Young Master Jang.
No matter what happens,
I will go into Songrim,
where Young Master Jang is.
So tell him to hang in there.
All right. I will tell him that.
Gosh, my head hurts.
I blame the Crown Prince.
Mu-deok.
-Bring me some water.
-Who is Mu-deok?
Who are you?
Do you not remember me? We met at the inn.
Do not lie.
You were staring at her the entire time!
Right. Your name was Sun or something.
Yes, Sun-i.
Why are you here?
Young Lady Heo is the granddaughter
of Master Heo Yeom.
I see.
It is a small world, is it not?
If she tells Master Heo
about how rude you were that day,
you will get on his bad side.
He never liked me anyway.
She can tell him.
At least show some gratitude.
Young Lady Heo took care of you all night.
She did?
She must not speak of that.
You have met Uk before?
Yes.
Uk apparently helped Yun-ok
when she was in trouble.
I see.
Uk is not the type of person
to help someone voluntarily.
Why would you speak of him that way?
I heard you came from Wol Fortress.
Young Master Jang's mother
and I are from there too.
-I see.
-Maybe that is the reason why,
but you remind me of Madam Do-hwa.
I guess you and Young Master Jang
were meant to meet each other.
If people from the same hometown
resemble each other,
she should also look like you.
But you two look nothing alike.
I do not get what you mean.
Maidservant Kim, you are great,
but you sometimes exaggerate things
and jump to conclusions with no logic.
Are you calling me a liar?
I never said that.
Do you see what you just did?
You got overly upset
and addressed yourself as a liar.
All right. Fine.
I am a liar who easily gets upset.
When did I ever call you a liar?
That is pretty much what you are saying.
You keep saying that.
-What is with you?
-It is your fault…
What kind of relationship do they have?
They have a very vague
and peculiar relationship
based on affection.
-You got upset first.
-You said it was a lie.
They seem close,
but it is nothing special.
-You kept being sarcastic.
-But you see,
-he is too slow-witted.
-Just go ahead and call me a liar.
He is very frustrating.
Unbelievable.
We have evidence and witnesses.
Witnesses? Goodness, how frightening.
How did you end up meeting Uk?
-Well…
-Young Lady Heo.
I apologize for interrupting.
Young Lady Heo, can we talk?
Sure.
You may speak here.
It is personal.
Come with me.
What do you think it is about?
Young Master Jang seemed very serious.
I know, right?
Judging by how Yun-ok followed along,
there must be something going on.
-What could it be?
-I am not sure.
I will go after them and find out.
Just leave them be!
Leave them be!
I mean, you guys seemed curious.
How can you be so slow-witted?
He is hopeless.
It is like an incurable disease.
Just sit down.
Why am I always the one getting told off?
What is the matter?
By any chance, did you tell anyone
about what happened that day?
To follow me to my accommodation
was rude and uncomfortable.
Your looks did not impress me,
and I did not follow you either.
No.
I would never speak of
something so embarrassing.
You do not think I am pretty.
My looks did not impress you,
and I know you did not follow me.
I feel embarrassed just thinking about it.
So I would never speak of it.
I am not
a woman who lacks common sense.
No, that was not my point.
The soul shifter.
I was talking about the soul shifter
who tried to attack you.
So the person who tried to attack me
really was a soul shifter?
Yes, but the word cannot get out.
So please do me a favor
and keep it a secret.
You saved my life,
so I will do as you ask.
Thank you.
We should introduce ourselves
now that we share a secret.
I am Heo Yun-ok.
I am Jang Uk.
I know. I heard.
Me too. That old man…
I mean…
Master Heo always boasts
about his granddaughter.
My grandfather said things about me?
What did he say?
You might get embarrassed.
You do not mean…
he went around telling people things like,
"My granddaughter is
as beautiful as a fairy."
Yes, he told everyone that
we will be blinded by your beauty.
But sadly, I was not.
This is very embarrassing.
I cannot believe he said that.
That old man…
I mean, that is how Master Heo
shows his affection for people.
He also speaks of my mother in that way.
Someone told me that
I resemble your mother.
I guess this is what my grandfather thinks
fairies look like.
What is the matter?
Do I not look like her?
I am not sure.
I never got to meet her.
How could I ever meet a fairy?
So it is hard to say.
Is your hangover gone?
Yes, I heard you stayed
by my side all night.
Yes.
I thought you were Mu-deok.
I apologize for the trouble.
I brewed some tea with medicinal herbs…
I hoped he would stay and have some.
SEJUKWON
Excuse me.
Did you see Mu-deok?
She came with me yesterday,
but I do not see her.
I am sure she went home.
Why would she go home without me?
She left her drunk master here
and went home?
From now on,
the servants of Songrim will tend to you.
Mu-deok does not belong here,
so she cannot enter.
Wait…
I guess Mu-deok thought
she would also be able
to follow Uk into Songrim.
I bet she was excited
about seeing you every day.
She must be disappointed.
Yes, I wonder if she is doing all right.
Uk must have found out.
He must be on his way to meet my uncle.
He will never approve of it.
Not a single mage was given the right
to bring in their own personal servant.
I cannot give you an exception.
Why not?
You exceptionally kept me out of here
for the past 20 years.
So why not give me another exception?
Is it because the master
who taught you Tansu
lives outside of these walls?
I am asking if you need Mu-deok
to communicate with that master of yours.
Master Lee has already proven
that I have trained myself.
He saved you from a crisis,
but people are still talking.
Some even say that
you were taught by your father, Jang Gang.
People spread rumors
saying he was not my father.
And now, they are saying
that my father taught me?
When there are special exceptions,
it causes people to talk.
You quickly mastered Ryusu and used Tansu.
That is not ordinary.
Are you
trying to gather attention
by making people talk about you?
I cannot make the leader
suspicious about Mu-deok.
He might find out she is a soul shifter.
All right, then.
I understand that you disapprove.
So you are just going to follow the rules?
Yes.
It took me so much hard work
to get in here.
I cannot risk getting kicked out
just because of a mere servant.
I want to buy Songrim's Spirit Plaque
from the black market.
Please get me one.
How could you ask me for that
when someone got killed because of it?
And if you get caught using that,
you could really get killed.
I must stay by his side.
Young Master Jang needs me.
That is not true.
He does not need you anymore.
He needed you when he was on the run
and busy training himself.
But he has entered Jeongjingak now.
The servants there will tend to him,
and the mages of Songrim
will help him train.
There is nothing
you can do for him anymore.
Why would he need you?
The leader put me in charge
of your basic training.
I will drop the honorifics
as I will be your teacher from now on.
I look forward to learning from you.
This is Jeongjingak's Book of Regulations.
These books teach you about the virtues
and prohibitions of mages.
You are banned
from leaving the training center
until you memorize it all.
All right. I shall follow the rules.
You may begin
by reading the books.
Young Master Jang.
Maidservant Kim.
How did you get in here?
I thought you might get locked up
in the secret room again
for disobeying the leader.
But look at you standing in a classroom.
I am so proud of you.
Maidservant Kim, you have every right
to have pride in your work.
You raised a fine Young Master.
But I must say, the tables are too low.
The chairs are too stiff too.
As you know, I am taller than others.
So it is uncomfortable.
But nothing can be done about it
because that is the rule.
What is your relationship
with Young Lady Heo?
What did you talk about with her?
It was nothing important.
I need to read all those books.
You should go now, Maidservant Kim.
Should I help you grind the ink stick
before you start studying?
No, I need to prepare
all the tools myself.
That is the rule.
I see. The rule.
All right, then.
I will leave now. Goodbye now.
Maidservant Kim.
Take good care of Mu-deok.
I bet she is worried about me.
Why would she worry
when you are doing perfectly well?
I bet she is happy.
She has been through so much
because of you.
You are very fussy with food,
but she had to cook three meals a day
up on that mountain for you.
She even had to prepare bath water
and wash all your clothes.
Do you know how much work that is?
Mu-deok really did go through a lot.
I will take her to go see flowers
and buy her something delicious.
I will take good care of her.
Mu-deok will feel comfortable
if you are not around.
Do you think so?
All right.
Jang Uk has already achieved his goal.
So he might no longer want
anything to do with me.
He has already abandoned 12 masters.
I should have poisoned him
and found something to blackmail with.
Maybe I trusted him too much.
Mu-deok!
Mu-deok.
Do you have the Spirit Plaque?
That I could not do.
You should take a test to enter Songrim.
You want me to take a test
to become a mage?
Are you mad? Do not be ridiculous.
No, that is not it.
Songrim is currently hiring.
They are even holding a contest
due to the fierce competition.
A contest?
RECRUITING SERVANTS FOR SONGRIM
They are just hiring servants.
Mu-deok, you are already a servant.
Yes, I know. But I am no ordinary servant.
I am not doing this.
Why are you so angry?
Do you know how hard it is to pass?
Mu-deok, you look exhausted.
Have some food before you go.
Goodness.
Maidservant Kim.
Are you coming from Songrim?
Did you meet Young Master?
Yes, I did. He is doing very well.
What does the young master
want me to do now?
When is he coming for me?
He wants you to stay well and healthy.
Enjoy the flowers and eat delicious foods.
He told me to enjoy the flowers
and eat delicious foods?
Yes, he did.
Did he not say
when he will come to see me?
According to the rules,
he cannot leave the place.
He is determined to follow the rules now,
so I no longer need to worry about him.
I guess Uk has no intentions
of keeping me by his side.
Mu-deok.
By any chance, do you know
who Young Master Jang has feelings for?
I am wondering if it is the young lady
I saw at Songrim.
A young lady?
He is seeing someone already?
You see, he once told me
that his heart belongs to a woman
who is like a single bird egg
on top of a tall tree.
Apparently, he is the only one she has.
I could tell how much he cared about her.
When a man cares about a woman,
what do you think that means?
It means he is in love.
But I am Uk's bird egg.
They are bird's eggs.
Master, let us stay loyal
and dutiful to each other.
I almost died thanks to you.
My crazy master.
Our relationship as master and pupil
will only last until you become the best
and help me get my energy back.
The moment I get my energy back
and become Naksu again,
we will no longer be master and pupil.
Can you tell me why?
Because then, you should no longer
have a reason to protect me,
nor should I have a reason…
to go easy on you.
Master! It is me, Jang Uk.
Gosh, this is bad.
What am I going to do?
Mu-deok.
I miss you so much.
I have no intention of training Uk.
So you did not take him under your wing.
You just locked him up in Songrim.
Somebody, please help me!
It was definitely Mu-deok.
Why did she have to be away
now of all times?
Young Master!
What is there to a letter?
As long as it delivers your feelings.
Young Master Jang has a lady
he has deep feelings for.
This is more difficult than I thought.
-Your Royal Highness!
She was always beside Uk.
You must focus when you are trying
to read what you cannot see.
Mu-deok.
Subtitle translation by: Ja-won Lee