As for the first live stream of Lychee...
We've all seen how boring it was.
We're feel that Lychee is not willing and agrees 100%
with this project.
I would like to propose the second step of the plan.
I brought you here today for a change of pace.
We're at the Tom Leng.
About Mom Lumyai and Lychee’s channel.
It’s blowing up! Like, too good to handle!
The ratings are going through the roof!
When this one’s done and then we’ve got another lined up.
We’ll have to head over to Grandma Lam’s place.
They want us to stage a fake spirit ceremony.
So Grandma can see them.
Greece and Mafai should be suitable for this job.
This work Greece and Mafai will surprise everyone.
I acted possessed for the first time.
I need time to get over it.
Keep calm, Mafai.
No matter what, we must play this part convincingly.
Ohio Hyo.
Abnormal.
Rizz
Charming.
Slay.
That's cool.
Goat.
Awesome.
Brain rot.
Brain rot from the internet.
Sigma.
Really cool.
Cringe.
Remember it.
This is the vocabulary used by Gen Z.
Hello.
My father.
My mother.
My grandmother.
How are you guys?
Ching.
Ching, is that you?
Of course, Daddy.
I'm Ching.
Oh, my dear mom.
You look so much more beautiful, and that's without a filter.
Ching.
Go see your grandma.
Oh, my grandma.
Grandma.
I miss you so much.
I'm so excited.
Oh, my angel.
Is this Mr. Ching or Ms. Ching?
Why does he look quite feminine?
I hope this project will be successful.
Hey guys, are you ready?
Honestly, not so much.
Come on, don't worry.
I've already coordinated with Uncle Naan.
about the 'Long Korn' ceremony.
He will come and guide you.
Don't worry.
Why does Mafai look strange?
She looks like a dog.
Luka.
Please, come to me.
Go see your grandma.
Grandma...
Hey, you guys, just enough.
Your acting is so fake.
How can my mom recover?
It's so fake you can tell from a mile away.
[Scream]
Ching.
Grandma.
Um...
Ching for real.
I really miss you.
Let's hug now.
Ching, come down here!
Come see who's here for you.
I miss you so much!
I want to hug you right now.
What's going on?
Let's hug.
You're awake now.
Ching.
We haven't hugged yet.
You and Luka also came and passed away.
It's okay.
The cycle of rebirth is basic.
If you miss me, just die and come to me.
I'm not dead yet!
So, live happily.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of Luka.
Plu.
Ray.
Mom.
That thing I asked you to research about unicorn in Thailand.
How is it?
I worked on this all night.
It might take a while to explain.
I included comparisons between Thailand and other countries too.
Yeah.
The unicorn is based on the Elasmotherium.
From 2.6 million years ago.
Huh?
The most famous unicorn cartoon in America is My Little Pony.
which started in 2010.
In Japan, the famous unicorn is the manga Unico.
which was even adapted into two anime films.
And there are also unicorns in Thailand.
The Kirin which is a Himmapan creature.
That's a mix of horse, dragon, deer, and fish
But in some legends, it only has one horn on its head.
Which is why it's called a unicorn.
You're really stupid, like a buffalo.
Not a buffalo.
Buffalo has two horns.
But the unicorn has only one horn, like this.
No, no, no.
You!
You're so stupid!
The unicorn I asked you to find is a startup company.
Valued at over one billion USD.
It's not...
That's not what you're showing me right now.
I'm so sorry.
You know what?
You are lucky to have a boss who is both handsome and capable.
Everyone wants to work with me.
Sorry.
Stop saying sorry.
And listen to me only.
I'll tell you.
Everyone is jealous of you.
And why did you do this?
What were you thinking?
Did you use your feet to think?
Go.
Go find new information.
Go find new information!
If Plu were still here.
I wouldn't have to deal with something like this.
Both handsome and capable, worth working with.
Hmm, only Him thinks that way.
The Ms. Mafia thinks so too.
The Mafia Boss sees everything he does as good.
When Plu resigned.
Those two just assumed Plu had problems.
And imagined she was being sexually harassed.
I don't know how stupid, deaf, and blind a person has to be.
to trust someone like Karj.
Does the Mafia Boss not know.
that all the employees badmouth her behind her back.
She only thinks of complicated things.
And has no idea how to handle.
Then pressures the employees to do a perfect job.
It would be better if we had someone like Plu.
You should worry about yourself, not Plu.
That we have to stay here.
Yeah, I struggle every day.
Consider this a celebration for the completed
Grandma Lam project.
I think it's better than expected.
But now, we need to brainstorm ways to make money.