Pine, what are you doing here?
I think Tiga’s hiding something…
maybe he’s seeing another girl
We need to investigate the affair.
Today, we’re assigning who does what!
Go show him how gorgeous you are! Move!!!
Oh my gosh, you!!!
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
Ugh, that’s way too cute!
"Alright, stop shipping them already!
Are you crazy?!
No Way!!!
Oh, is this your first time working out?
Yeah
You’ve got a really nice figure though
Can I get your number?
Huh?
I already added my Line
Wait, are you flirting with me?
A bit too little muscle for your height
A body like this
Don’t you want to be a model, athlete
or maybe in a girl group
You can message me anytime
Hit me up on Line
Coffee is ready
Yes
thank you
Message me
See you later
I’ll train you quickly
Can I handle this?
You’ll be fine
We trust our judgment,
just like with Plu You can do it
we’ll take it slow and help each other along
I can’t believe it
a tiny girl with a 21-inch waist
21, are you sure???
A 26-inch waist works too, like mine
Starting a company like this
not sure if it’s lucky or unlucky
That we met someone like Ray
Oh, it’s lucky
With me around, what’s there to be afraid of
I can’t keep working with you, Ray?
I love you
I really don’t know where else to find a job
Please help me, please, please, please
I want to help you, but I’m barely managing myself
Let’s do this, I hope the two of us get new jobs soon
So rich, covered head to toe in designer brands
Seriously, this much
I have a job interview today
So I dressed up a bit to look respectable
Also to show respect for the place
Not just a little though
with the outfit and bag
how much should the salary be to make it worth it
Maybe 200,000… 300,000
Our company is small
we probably can’t afford to hire you
Don’t decide just yet
I love working
Salary isn’t an issue, whatever the company thinks is fair
Looks like she was into school activities
too back in the day
She was a cheerleader
drum major
held signs, carried offerings for Teacher’s Day
All activities for pretty people
Can’t argue with that
Pretty but not smart
you even ran her own coffee shop
Now looking for a job like this, must have failed
Sweet, flirty smile, probably used it to get her way
too many times
Probably thinks we’ll fall for her charm
Pretty but no brains…
Don’t worry, I’m not good just at smiling
I’m not worried
and you don’t need to worry about me either
Alright, we’ll get back to you then
Okay
Thank You
Are you misunderstanding something
Because I really kicked you full force
Is that the person in the video??
You better stop lying right now!!
Yeah, it’s true
Why would you do that
Calm down, boss, hear me out, you idiot
Sorry
This is actually my spot
I reserved it, but I went to the bathroom
What a crappy day
Sorry, I can go somewhere else
Wait, no, we can stay here together
Jin, I’m calling
Hey
Hi Jin
Jin Tidy Wolf
Hi everyone, the air feels cold, isn’t it annoying?
It’s definitely more fun outside
Oh my god Wolf
seriously????
Your s on planet
Whoa
What is this, I feel like my heart is gonna explode
Tidy told me to wear it to flirt with Tiga
For what…
To see if Tiga is really a player like Pine said
I don’t know if Tiga likes it
but he’s got me, I like you
Any turn out that
Tiga stared at Wolf like he wanted to eat him
Really
Message me on Line
Tiga looked at Wolf like a lizard
She just wants him as a client
you didn’t say anything wrong, right???
Even with Wolf being this hot, she’s still not interested ??
If Tiga actually likes Wolf
That will be chaos
Alright, just calling to update
We gonna go follow up with Tiga
Mm, bye bye, good luck
Love???
It's mean Love
Love?
Hug him???
Wait, does Tiga like this kind of thing?
Hugging for business
or maybe he’s just training
as part of a workout
Getting this close
No wonder the trainee got so hooked