[English subtitles are available]
[Cordial Companions]
[Episode 11]
My Lord.
My Lord!
How can the President of the Supreme Court
be so petty?
You're calling me petty?
My Lord.
You're finally willing to talk to me.
Don't be angry, okay?
Don't be angry.
Dear customers, please come in.
Please come in.
Everyone.
I'm so nervous.
Well...
What should we do?
It's okay.
Relax.
Lai Luo.
Don't you get nervous either.
No matter what happens,
I'll always be by your side.
Then you should concentrate.
Don't drop the ball.
Otherwise,
I need to save you.
No problem.
You'll...
Why will you save me instead?
My Lord.
I'm still too nervous to breathe.
What if I
slip up then?
What should I do?
It's okay.
Relax.
Lord Zhang, you're here.
Where is he?
Upstairs.
Please go upstairs.
Okay.
Good.
Lin Wanqing.
Look at me.
Trust me.
We are not acting at this moment.
What's happening is true.
I am your husband.
You are my wife.
Understand?
No matter what happens,
you have me.
[Zhang Ren, the Marshal of Hongzhou Military Command]
Thank you for coming, Mr. Zhou.
Please forgive me for not welcoming you from afar.
You're welcome, Lord Zhang.
You can call me brother.
Okay.
Brother Zhang, I'll follow your advice then.
By the way,
Brother Zhou, I heard that you brought
your newly married wife.
Where is she?
Qing.
Lord Su is so into character.
I can't mess up.
My Lord.
Oh no.
You're so bad.
Lord Zhang. Excuse me.
My wife likes to tease me.
Lord Zhang. Please excuse her.
Boss, a pot of tea.
Okay.
How did I lose them?
Brother Zhou.
You must be tired after the trip.
Have a good rest today.
Tomorrow,
I will discuss
big issues with you.
I shall be here
waiting for you, Brother Zhang.
What a coincidence.
Surprised?
Cousin.
Why are you here?
Wan.
What are you talking about?
Brother Zhou, you brought someone else here?
Brother Zhang.
My wife's cousin is free at home.
So he came with us.
I know it's inappropriate.
But
when a woman gets unruly,
there's nothing you can do about it.
They only know
this is a business trip.
They know nothing else.
In that case,
tomorrow,
bring Mrs. Zhou's cousin together
to my place.
Well...
It's not all my fault.
How would I know
you would do such a dangerous thing?
Senior.
You...
My Lord.
I'm sorry.
At this point,
let's think about how to solve the present problem first.
Didn't that person
say anything?
Maybe
he bought your words.
People engaged in activities that could cost them their lives
are always extremely cunning.
Don't underestimate him.
[Zhang's Mansion]
My Lord.
Lord Zhou's name card has been checked repeatedly.
There's no problem.
Why are you here?
Wan.
What are you talking about?
But these people are very suspicious.
My Lord. What are you going to do?
Zhang Ren invited us to his mansion.
He might already be suspicious.
Be careful
when we get there.
Take these three guests to the West Chamber to rest.
Yes.
This way, please.
Lord Zhou, please come in.
Lord Zhang is waiting in the mansion.
Thank you.
My Lord.
Lord Zhou is here.
You may leave.
Brother Zhou.
Brother Zhang.
Brother Zhou, you must be tired.
It would be more comfortable
for you to stay in my mansion.
Guards.
Escort Mrs. Zhou to the guest room
and provide her with proper service.
I have something
to discuss with Lord Zhou.
Yes.
You go first.
I’ll come to you later.
Brother Zhou, please.
Brother Zhang, please.
Please.
Brother Zhou. Have some tea.
Thank you, Brother Zhang.
Greetings, Lord Zhou.
I heard that Zhou Yipu is a lecher.
If I send you to him,
he surely won't refuse.
This way,
you can easily monitor him.
Yes.
Brother Zhou.
Since Mrs. Zhou is not here,
let Lan'er serve you.
Zhang Ren wants to arrange a spy.
He thought I couldn't refuse him.
Brother Zhang, thank you.
I’m so happy.
As long as you are happy.
Lan'er,
take good care of Lord Zhou.
Yes.