[Jespipat Tilapornputt]
[Nalinthip Sakulongumpai]
[Dear My Secretary]
- Let me go, Boss!
- I won't!
Let me go!
Let me go, Boss!
- I won't!
- Let me go!
- I told you, I'm not letting you go!
[Not approved]
Let me go!
Boss! Let me go!
Don't joke around like this, Boss!
I'm not joking.
I'm always serious, especially when it is about you.
What is it with you, Secretary Prim?
I just want to resign. Is that so wrong?
Fine. If you want to resign, go ahead and leave.
[Boss Wee-Woo!]
Yes, Boss…
I was out running and thought you should come to run with me.
Running?
Yeah. Meet me at the park right now!
Okay. I'll go right away.
[5:00 AM]
What kind of vision has come over him now…
Keep up, Secretary Prim.
Yes, Boss.
Sorry…
How's it going, Secretary Prim?
I know that getting to run and absorbing the morning sunlight like this,
it refreshes you, gets your blood pumping, and clears your mind. Am I right?
Yes, I feel full of energy and ready to work now.
Perfect!
I had you exercise
because walking up to the 4th floor the other day made you dead tired.
You need to be stronger if you want to be my secretary for a long time.
Got it?
Yes, Boss.
[7:10 Pace, 10:25]
But your pace is only 7. You're just power walking!
I'll have to make you run every morning from now on.
This is just so…
Radiant! Radiant! Radiant!
Wear these, or you'll be dazzled.
The sunlight has been strong in the morning lately.
You're the one who needs them.
Because you're the one who's going to be dazzled by my brilliance.
It's such a burden having to be this way.
But when someone shines this brightly, nothing can hold them back.
Isn't that right, Secretary Prim?
So cute!
That smile is so sweet.
How could anyone not fall in love with you?
Such beautiful fur, too.
Now, let me see your paws, there we go.
So good! Very good!
You don't bite, right? No biting, right? Good job, such a good one!
I've rescheduled the Purchasing Department meeting
to tomorrow noon, as instructed.
At 11:00 a.m., there's an interview with the Asian Tomorrow page.
They've requested 30 minutes.
Including hair and makeup, which should take no more than an hour.
As for the VIP zone planning meeting for the Countdown event,
that's set for precisely 1:00 p.m.
After that, there's a discussion with…
Secretary Prim.
Secretary Prim!
Are you asleep right now?
I'm sorry. I stayed up late last night.
Should you get at least 7 to 8 hours daily for quality sleep?
What exactly did you do?
[3:00 AM]
[Boss Wee-Woo!]
Yes, Boss.
I want you to review the VIP guest list for the Countdown event again.
All right. I'll send it to you tomorrow morning.
Review and send it tonight instead. I want to see it now.
Okay…
It's 3:00 a.m…
I've sent it already, Boss. I'm going to sleep now, okay?
All right, I'll just continue then.
After that, a meeting with Mr. Somphop,
- regarding the Korean bag franchise deal that didn't go…
- Enough!
I don't want a failure to ruin my mood first thing in the morning.
A failure?
But Mr. Somphop couldn't close the deal. That's all.
In my work, there's no such thing as "that's all".
Will we let our competitor take this deal just because of that?
If we don't aim for results, if we don't push to succeed,
then what's the point of working?
All it takes is dedication and the will to succeed.
Why is that so hard for people to understand?
Well, maybe because not everyone is like you, Boss.
Perfect!
Yes, no one's perfect except me.
Right.
Boss, I've never met anyone as "absolutely perfect" as you.
Thank you for dropping me off.
Thank you, too, Yong.
By the way, Mr. Khai sent over the outfit
for the Brazilian ambassador's birthday party.
I've already picked the Phthalo Green set with a black leather jacket for you.
Hold on.
You pronounced the Phthola Green and black leather jacket wrong.
Repeat it.
Phthalo Green.
That accent is so local.
Not "Tha," it's Phthalo.
- Phthalo.
Phthalo, Phthalo Green.
- Thalo.
Phthalo.
Well, I don't have your perfect pronunciation, Boss.
Fine.
But even your Th isn't right.
You must touch your tongue to the top of your front teeth,
like this: Thuh.
Thuh.
Stick the tongue out more.
- Thuh.
More tongue!
Thuh.
- Thuh.
- Okay. That's correct.
Perfect!
Thank you.
Good day.
Almost forgot.
There's something personal I'd like to inform you about, Boss.
What is it?
I'm resigning.
I'm resigning. I'm resigning. I'm resigning.
So I wanted to let you know first.
I'll send you the resignation letter to sign later today.
- Yong.
- Yes, Boss?
- Start the car.
- Yes, Boss.
- Yong.
- Yes, Boss?
Did Prim just say she's resigning?
Yes, Boss. Resigning.
Resigning…
Boss? Did you forget something?
Did you just say you were resigning?
Yes. I'm resigning.
- Yong!
- Yes, Boss?
She's resigning?
Why would she resign?
Or did I give her too much work?
But she's never complained about anything.
Did I accidentally do something wrong?
No…
Someone like me, when have I ever done anything wrong?
What's going on with you, Secretary Prim?!
I've finished organizing the contract documents!
This one for today's tie, okay?
How about a tea break?
The car is ready. This way, Boss.
Thank you for dropping me off, Boss.
Thank you for teaching me everything, Boss.
Thank you so much.
Boss, I've never met anyone as absolutely perfect as you.
Come on! What's so bad about working with me?!
Why am I even upset? Why am I even annoyed?
She's just a secretary. She wants to quit?
It can happen all the time.
I'm resigning!
Secretary Prim…
Let's see.
Hey, Meow-meow.
Do you think he is going to be mad
that I told him I'm resigning like that?
Will he understand?
But he has to understand, right?
Employees resign all the time, every year. Right?
I wonder if he'll be able to find a new secretary…
What do you think?
Yes, Boss?
I don't know what to wear to work. Come pick something out for me. That's all.
Wait! Hold on! Hello?
Aren't you tired of this, Meow-meow?
Going in circles like this over and over again?
Are you almost here?
Hurry up.
Yes! I'm on my way now! If I could fly, I would've flown already!
If you can fly, then fly here now.
Hello.
You're changing the makeup artist?
Why is this being notified so last-minute?
We'd like to keep the original makeup artist that was confirmed.
Otherwise, he might not be available for the interview.
Goody, hi.
Yes, there's a meeting this afternoon. All right, see you then. Thank you!
I'm here! Just give me a moment.
Let's go with this tie for today, shall we?
Okay.
Perfect.
You're getting pretty used to speaking English these days?
Of course.
No humility at all?
Nope. You're the one who taught me, remember?
Humility is just a trick people use when they want to be praised.
What's wrong, Secretary Prim?
Nothing.
That's my water.
Sorry!
About what you said this morning.
You're resigning because I dragged you out for a run and you got mad.
So, this is payback, right?
- No, that's not it—
- Okay. I get it now.
- Get what, exactly?
- I forgive you.
Wait? Forgive me for what?
For being mad at me. I forgive you.
Hello, Pat?
Don't do anything. I'll handle it myself.
I need to borrow 15 minutes from the interview schedule.
I have to deal with a scumbag real quick.
So, you're not resigning anymore. Right?
Perfect!
[Lucky Box]
[Thiranon Group]
Was the manager's salary not enough, Mr. Wichai?
Is that why you did this?
I-I…
I can explain, Boss.
I really needed the money, Boss. I had no choice…
And who doesn't need money?
That doesn't give you the right to betray the company that's taken care of you.
But, Boss, I…
I'm only giving you a chance because you used to work for my father.
You know what you need to do.
Miss Prim, I don't want to resign.
I never meant to embezzle.
It was that damn gambling house…
I mean, no, Miss Prim, I didn't mean to get involved with gambling.
A client dragged me in, and I didn't want to play.
Please, Miss Prim, talk to him. Help me, please.
Come with me, please.
What's going on, Miss Prim?
You know how much he hates corruption in this organization.
I've already packed up your things.
Thank you for your resignation.
Miss Prim…
Please take him to the infirmary.
But if there's any medical cost involved,
make sure he pays for everything himself.
Yes, ma'am.
Bhum, the interview team from Asian Tomorrow is here.
Okay! Thank you. Please print out the script I revised, too.
Thank you, thank you.
Prosperity! Go, prosperity! Prosperity, prosperity, prosperity!
Prosperity, prosperity, prosperity! Wealthy!
- Prosperity! Prosperity!
- Stop it!
Goody, what are you even doing? The interview team is already here!
- Bad luck!
- What bad luck?! What are you talking?
Oh my god, where did you even get that holy water bowl from?!
I went on a pilgrimage and brought it from the Sacred Kilen Cave Temple!
So our office would thrive and be full of success.
But you're wearing a scarf in a cursed color!
You're blocking all our good luck and prosperity!
Such a bad omen!
Bad omen?! Excuse me?!
Do you know how hard it was to get this scarf?
I bought it at a boutique in Italy for over 10,000 baht!
Wasn't that 250 baht from Sampeng Market?
199, okay?! They gave me a discount.
Taking it off or not?!
Are you nuts? No way!
If you won't take it off, I'll splash you!
What?! Don't! Goody! No!
Oh my god!
What have you done?! What if she gets sick?
You never think before you act!
I'm going to check on the interview now.
Looking good though…
Interview time!
Careful not to catch a cold, okay? We're just worried about you.
Nice. Nice.
- Like a Greek statue!
- Looking good!
Excuse me, Boss, just a little shine on your face.
Allow me to blot it gently.
And in case anyone here doesn't already know,
though I do,
our boss here drinks at least two liters of water daily.
That's why his skin is so clear, hydrated, and dewy.
Honestly, no retouching needed. Right, everyone? So handsome!
Sorry, but who asked?
I wanted to share, is that a problem?!
- Done.
- Please, go ahead.
Excuse me, move!
I'll hold that for you, Miss Bhum.
Okay, I'm ready.
Excuse me, just a moment.
Where were you?
Off writing your resignation letter?
I haven't written it yet.
Good. Even if you did, I wouldn't approve it.
Let's begin, then.
So handsome!
He hasn't even started shooting! Getting ahead of yourself much?
But he is handsome!
Let me begin with the first question.
How do you feel about being named one of Asia's top 5 hottest CEOs?
I've always been hot, so I wouldn't know how I'm supposed to feel.
Oh my gosh, that's a mic-drop answer right there!
Annoying.
We heard that Thiranon Group has expanded into neighboring countries.
How has the response been?
Over the past five years,
across five branches in two countries,
we've seen consistent profit growth.
Most recently,
our total profit reached 26.702 billion baht,
a 12.6% increase from the previous year.
That's not correct.
12.6% is the rounded figure. The exact number is 12.58116%.
[12.58116%]
Yes, you're right, Boss. That's correct.
Also, I believe the fifth branch should be performing better.
We must target Thai craft products,
which have the highest revenue and profit growth.
We should allocate more space to that category.
Mr. Pat, come up with a plan and present it to me.
Yes, Boss.
If there's nothing else, that's all. Everyone, follow up accordingly.
Thanks, everyone.
With your nonstop work schedule,
Mr. Thi, how do you maintain your work-life balance?
I don't have a work-life balance because it's all the same to me.
Work isn't a duty or a burden. It's like breathing in and out.
I can work and relax at the same time.
Work is how I create value in myself. That's who I am.
That was incredible, Boss!
I can't stand fangirls like you, who always squeal over Boss.
- Stop it.
- You're too much.
It's cute.
That?
By the way, have you heard?
Heard what?
Is something going on?
Is it true? That you're quitting?
How did you know?
I heard it from her.
I heard it from him.
I heard it from Yong.
But he's not here.
We've been together for nine years, and now you're suddenly running off like this?
It's not sudden, Bhum.
I've thought about it for a while.
Wait, do you have a problem with Boss?
No, it's nothing like that. It's purely a personal decision.
Then where will he find a secretary who gets him like you do?
Exactly!
I don't think he's going to sign that resignation letter easily.
But this is a basic employee right!
Why wouldn't I be allowed to quit?
Either way, I'm resigning.
See! It's your fault, wearing that cursed-colored scarf!
That's why Prim is quitting. Take it off now!
You failed every logic test in school?
What does my scarf relate to this?
- Take it off or not?
- Nope.
- If you don't…
- What?
The two of us… are going to strip you down.
- What?!
- Take it off! Bhum!!
- Take it off! Take it off right now!
- Don't you dare come near me!
So annoying! What's wrong with you, sis?!
I just don't get it. Why would Prim resign?
Is it because she's overworked and can't take it anymore?
Poor thing.
Are you feeling sorry, or are you happy?
Happy about what?
Well, now you can offer to be her replacement.
Come on, I know your every intention inside and out!
Oh, stop! Calm down!
I might want to be the assistant to the Vice President
so I can be close to my idol.
But it doesn't mean I'd stoop so low
as to cut someone else's legs off for it!
That's right. It's a good thing. Being an assistant like Prim is exhausting.
She barely has time to eat with us.
If you took the job, you wouldn't have time to shop.
I can shop online!
But seriously, if Prim resigns,
the new assistant can only be
perfectly well-mannered, talented, charming,
and with an excellent attitude like Manchuporn Thakingsak, me!
You're too much.
Salary's in!
Bonus, too!
Now I can buy gifts for Phon!
Wait, his name is Phon?
Salary is equal to spoiling the guy.
- Spoil the guy, spoil the guy.
- Always!
I'm in such a good mood, and with this bonus,
I should buy food for Prim!
No need to go yourself, Ms. Bhum.
I'll go buy it. Please enjoy your meal.
Thank you!
Girl, the way he cares for you is so sweet.
Even if you don't get the Vice President,
you'll get Yong instead!
- So cute!
- Thank you!
You're welcome! What now?
Stop it. Stop pushing this. Use your brain cells for something else!
- Just open your heart!
- Open my heart for what?
Remember? You used to like me back when I played soccer.
Peeking, glancing, I saw it. You liked me when I looked a bit manly.
You fooled me so well back then!
"Hi there, I'm off to play soccer." "Am I cool or what?"
- The world's ending!
- Open your heart!
[The house mortgage has been fully redeemed.]
[Ms. Primala, you can come to the bank to collect the deed now.]
[Bonus Salary]
Are you satisfied?
Excuse me?
The bonus I gave you, are you satisfied with it?
Thank you very much, Boss.
Do you have any tasks for me?
No tasks. But I do have a proposal for you.
A proposal?
I'm going to raise your salary. You'll also get a personal driver,
move to a condo closer to the office,
and I'll give you company shares. Sounds good?
Is all of this just so I don't quit?
Yes.
- Then I have to decline.
- What?
I've already made up my mind to resign, so I will.
I worked so hard on this plan, and it's not working?
Can I at least get a reason?
I want to live a different kind of life.
Different how?
The kind I've never lived before.
But…
Hello? You've arrived?
Okay.
We'll talk about this later. Right now, come have lunch with my parents.
But isn't that a private family meal?
My family can include you, too.
See you downstairs.
This new restaurant was inspired by a tugboat transporting sand.
It serves Michelin-level Thai cuisine in perfect bite-sized portions,
with over a hundred dishes rotating adorably on a conveyor belt.
Good idea! Tourists will love this.
If this branch does well, you should open the next one in Phuket.
Prim, dear, try the pomelo salad. It's delicious.
Yes, ma'am.
Why didn't you bring your girlfriend, Jinny?
Why would I?
Well, aren't you and Jinny…?
Jinny and I aren't dating, Dad.
What?
Oh, stop saying "what" over and over again.
How can I not be confused?
You're always out and about with her.
What do you call that then?
Talking stage, right, Prim?
Really, what's there to talk about that much?
Jinny is the daughter of Minister Damrong.
She's a good match. Just get married already.
Don't meddle in the kid's personal life so much.
If she's not his girlfriend, I may push Prim into the race instead.
I'm sorry.
You're being ridiculous. That's not possible.
Prim, you see Jinny a lot, don't you?
Help encourage things between her and him a bit.
I'd rather not interfere in his matters.
Besides, I'm planning to resign.
- What? Resign?!
Yes.
So, why do you want to leave?
Is it because you hate me? Is that it?
I don't hate you.
Then why?
I said tell me. That's an order!
I want to live my life.
I want to be Primala, not just "Secretary Prim"
whose entire life revolves around work and you nearly every day.
You might see work as your breath,
but it's not like that for others.
I genuinely appreciate the bonus and all the offers you made.
But what I want isn't what you're offering.
What I want is my life.
I'll continue working until the end of next month.
If you don't let me quit, I'll tell the Labor Department.
Excuse me.
Goodbye.
[Thai BBQ]
So that means…
Does that mean we got the house back?
Yes.
Prim, did you pay a lot this time?
Why didn't you tell me? I could've helped.
What would you help with? Just save your money for Ploen's tuition.
Besides, the last payment wasn't that expensive,
just paying off the interest.
Dad, seriously. He partnered with those awful friends and lost the house.
If Mom were still here, she would've snapped his neck for sure!
Look at what he's put you through for all these years.
Don't blame Dad.
He's not a bad person, just too kind.
Honestly, I wasn't struggling. I'm fine.
Fine? Seriously, Prim?
You've been the one carrying this whole family.
You paid off the bank, got our house back,
helped raise Ploen,
and even paid for her school fees, too!
Now that the house is taken care of, you no longer have to worry.
Time to take a break.
Don't worry. I'll take a break real soon.
Prim! Prim!
Prim, it's okay! Just a blown transformer!
It's okay! I'm here, I'm here.
Breathe, breathe. Deep breaths, Prim.
Deep breaths, it's going to be okay.
Come on! Look at your face, look at you!
You're taking this hard, huh, Mr. Boss?
Why are you so worked up because your secretary quit?
Is it that big of a deal?
You didn't act like this when Paeng, your previous secretary,
left for maternity leave and never returned.
It's different. Prim has been with me for 9 years.
Exactly, 9 years.
Maybe she wants to live her life and do something else for once?
You worked her like crazy, calling her at 3:00 a.m., seriously?
Well, I came up with ideas at that time.
I feared I'd forget, so I had to call her immediately.
With the way you act,
you're either her dad or her husband.
She doesn't want to keep living her life tied to you anymore.
So what should I do?
First of all, ease up a bit.
Let her have some time to rest.
Here I come.
Meow-meow. Time to eat!
So, why do you want to leave?
I want to live my life.
I want to be Primala
not just "Secretary Prim" whose entire life revolves around work
and you nearly every day.
I'll continue working until the end of next month.
If you don't let me quit, I'll tell the Labor Department.
After saying all that,
will I even be able to resign, Meow-meow?
Yes, Boss?
Tomorrow, I'm giving you permission to start work in the afternoon.
Just for one day.
What?
I just want you to get some rest. That's all.
Start in the afternoon?
Rest?
What's with him?
Being this kind, let's see if she still wants to resign.
Should I be happy about this, Meow-meow?
[Bar]
Hello there, handsome!
That guy's cute, too. Hi there!
Girl, you're blowing my mind right now!
Kiew, how do you even know about this place?
Well, one of my event clients gave me a membership card.
So I brought you two here to share this fabulous experience!
Hi, handsome!
Listen, Prim. Tonight, let your spirit free.
Release all that stress your boss has locked you under.
Let loose with all these gorgeous men.
Go all out!
Yes! Because tonight, my husband and kid gave me the green light.
So drink. Get wasted!
Are you sure this is a good idea?
- Drink!
- Cheers!
Cheers!
- Yeah, yeah!
- Cheers!
Cheers!
Prim, you're cheering so much I can't even keep up.
Why are we clinking glasses this much?
I'm seriously about to burp myself into a vomit.
Fine, I'll drink on my own.
Prim, what the heck did you bring with you? Did you pack your whole house?
Just in case my boss needs something.
Taking care of him like that,
are you trying to turn him into your man?
We see you.
Shut up! No way!
Oh, you say no, but your heart's screaming "yes," isn't it?
Make him your man! Go make him your man!
Gimme that!
You know this is important.
But since you're so lovely, I'll let you have it.
Consider it a thank-you reward for the great service.
Prim, step aside, girl!
Greetings, Boss!
Miss Secretary, do you have anything you'd like to say to your beloved boss?
Yes, I do.
So full of yourself! So picky!
So arrogant! So self-absorbed!
You think you're Mr. Perfect or something?
Now you're gonna get it!
This!
Here, take off your tie!
Faster!
Take off your shirt, too!
Everyone, say it together.
- Perfect!
- What was that?
- Louder!
- Perfect!
Perfect!
I randomly saw this on social media and thought I'd send it to you.
[kw_aroundtheworld: The great and powerful event organizer, Kiew, knows the world.]
Miss Secretary, do you have anything you'd like to say to your beloved boss?
Yes, I do.
So full of yourself!
So picky!
You think you're Mr. Perfect or something?
Secretary Prim!
[7:00 AM]
Yes, Boss.
Secretary Prim, get to my house immediately.
But didn't you tell me to come into work this afternoon?
Come to my house. Now!
When is the world going to end already?
Sorry, I'm late.
You're wearing this tie today, okay?
So, you want to resign
because you want to tie someone else's tie, is that it?
What do you mean?
I've never tied a tie for anyone other than you.
- Then what's this?
- So picky! So arrogant!
So self-absorbed!
You think you're Mr. Perfect or something?
I… I mean… I… last night… I…
I gave you the morning off because I was worried you'd burn out.
I didn't expect you'd use it to go hang out instead.
I'm sorry, Boss. I'll ask my friends to delete the clip right away.
It's too late.
Even if it's deleted, someone's already saved it.
Have you even thought, Secretary Prim,
about the digital footprint you left yesterday?
How many hundreds or thousands of years it will stay with you?
I'm not going to forgive you that easily!
Then, what do you want me to do?
Should I…
Resign?!
Don't even think about it.
No, Boss.
I want to make it up to you. Whatever you want me to do, just tell me.
All right!
You said it yourself.
You'll have a chance to make it up to me.
What's wrong?
I'm about to present, and I feel like my stomach's churning.
Like I need to poop. I'm going to the bathroom first.
- Stop! Wait!
Stay with us! Hold it in! Clench! Cut it off! Tighten!
You're good at this!
Hello…
Everyone, did you notice anything strange?
Strange! Totally strange! Why isn't the boss wearing a tie?
And what's with Prim's face?
She looks like something's off. The vibe is tense in here.
So, how exactly do you want me to make it up to you?
I'm not in the mood to say right now.
And when will you be in the mood?
I don't know.
But not now.
Hi, what are you doing?
- We are working.
She didn't even wait for an answer. Then why ask?
Thi.
Hi, Prim.
Hello, Miss Jinny.
Hi! I brought some snacks for both you and Thi.
I didn't want to brag, but I'm going to anyway
because I made them myself, and they're delicious!
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Thi, this is yours.
Thank you.
Thi, do you know I have something new?
What could it be?
Can you guess? Sparkle, sparkle.
You got your nails done?
Oh my god, Thi! You guessed it right! Wow, you're sooo smart.
Most guys are clueless,
but you're brilliant!
Since it's my birthday, I just wanted to try something new.
I thought about buying myself some flowers
since no one else will do it.
So sad.
I'm here to pick up the flowers I ordered, Ms. Fah.
They're ready.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Thi.
This has been such a Happy Birthday for me.
Honestly, I didn't really want flowers.
But since you bought them, I have to accept them.
So silly of me.
So silly.
It should've been obvious from the start.
- Yes.
- Because…
Are you free?
- No, I'm not.
- But I am.
There's nothing I'm more sure about than this.
Then, I think I'll excuse myself.
What? Why are you giving me flowers?
Secretary Prim likes me.
Today, I saw that she was upset when I gave flowers to Jinny.
That means she definitely likes me.
How do you know that?
I saw her crying with my own eyes today.
So silly of me.
So silly.
Finally, I've figured out the truth.
Even Secretary Prim...
has fallen for my charm.
Man, your confidence is something else.
No wonder she wouldn't tell me the real reason she was resigning.
She pretended it was about wanting her own life,
not wanting to be around me all day, every day.
But the truth is...
she just didn't want to fall for me even more.
What? That face. You don't believe me?
The one who's caught feelings is you.
You're totally obsessed with your secretary resigning.
What's wrong with you?
You've got it bad, man.
What feelings? That's ridiculous.
I don't have feelings like that.
Prim likes me.
Actually,
maybe she's already in love with me.
This is crazy!
It's crazy all right!
Prim, here's some allergy medicine.
Thank you.
And what are you even allergic to? Why are you like this?
Pollen from flowers.
What kind of hellish flowers are those?
♪ Lun-lan-la, lun-lan-la ♪ I told you I didn't want them. So silly!
There's the hell right there.
♪ Lun-lan-la ♪ I forgot something!
One more and I'm sweeping your legs out from under you!
Can you double-check the VIP seating again?
We might need to add extra seats for their companions.
- Okay, got it.
- Thank you!
Boss!
How is everything? Is the event okay?
Anything you'd like us to change, Boss?
Everything is good already. Perfect!
Thank you, everyone, for taking the time to help out today.
You can go take a break now. Make sure to get dressed up nicely.
Looking fabulous is a must, of course.
- Absolutely!
- Thank you, Boss.
Aren't you going to dress up?
Tonight, my secretary has to shine just as brightly as I do.
Let me recheck the stage, then I'll change my outfit.
I never knew your event organizing skills were this professional.
You could start your own company with these skills!
I haven't thought about what I want to do next yet.
I want to find something I truly enjoy,
and go on a date with someone.
A date!
Yes, one day I will have a family.
If I meet the right person, I might even get married.
But the other day, when I saw you, I thought you were in love with…
What do you mean?
Never mind. Forget about it.
All right, I understand you now.
Your life should be yours. I won't hold you back anymore.
Feel free to announce the search for a new secretary.
- Cheers!
How long have you stayed in Thailand?
A couple of years.
Everyone, a big smile, please.
- Hello.
- Thank you for coming.
My pleasure, nice to meet you.
Okay, I'm going to have to greet my friends.
- Okay, take your time.
- Thanks.
Is something wrong, Boss?
No.
Are all the VIP guests here yet?
Yes, they're all here. Mr. Li Tang is especially eager to meet you.
Next year, I'll go explore opportunities in Beijing.
I'd like to open a new branch there.
That's wonderful. China will always be happy to welcome you.
Tomorrow, we've arranged a dinner cruise
on the Chao Phraya River for you and your wife.
Thank you so much, Ms. Prim.
You really know my wife well.
She's been wanting to go on a river cruise for a long time.
I love the suite room very much.
Thanks to your wife for managing this for me.
Actually, she is my secretary, not my wife.
I made a fool of myself.
I've done more embarrassing things than you.
Sorry.
All right, everyone, it's almost time to count down to the New Year!
Is everyone ready to count down?
Boss, you should go to the fireworks viewing spot.
Come with me.
You never stay for the countdown with me.
But this year,
you have to stay.
Okay, guys, cheers!
- Cheers!
All right then, let's count down together!
Boss, can I check on things first?
There are plenty of staff for that. You don't need to worry anymore.
Stay here with me.
10…
9…
8…
7…
I'm really sorry, Boss.
Happy New Year!
♪ Sleep now, my dear, my precious one ♪
♪ Sleep tight, may your dreams be sweet ♪
♪ with stars filling the sky above just for you ♪
♪ I'll always be right here ♪
♪ La la la la laa la la ♪
♪ La la la la laa laa la… ♪
♪ I'm still right here, close to you ♪
♪ Always ready to hold you in my arms ♪
Peekaboo!
[Next Episode]
Just take care of Ploen for one day.
But I have to find a new secretary for the boss.
How can I look after her?
What is it like to be a good secretary?
You have to take care of your valuables as best you can.
And for the secretary, the most valuable thing is him.
I will let you redeem yourself
by training your assistant secretary to pass the probation.
Then I will allow you to resign.