=Rise From the Ashes=
=Episode 17=
(Sorrowful and Heartbroken)
♪Like♪
♪Withered petals♪
♪Entangled with memories♪
♪Like♪
♪The blazing sun♪
♪Scorching the passing years♪
♪Like♪
♪Shattered butterflies♪
♪Intertwined by blood♪
♪Like♪
♪Desperate flames♪
♪That can't burn away resentment♪
♪Bearing scars all over♪
♪I return anew from the flames♪
♪Only to find♪
♪Your unwavering love♪
♪In this life,
drifting through the world♪
♪Wish to be with you♪
♪I wash away the blood and tears♪
♪Rising from the ashes♪
♪Only to realize it's you♪
♪Waiting behind me♪
♪In this life,
there is pain and intoxication♪
♪The vow remains unchanged♪
Once everything is settled,
I'll reclaim my identity as Su Jingyuan.
Luoshi Pavilion will
disappear completely.
If you want the travel around,
I'll take you across mountains and
rivers to see the beautiful world.
If you want a peaceful life,
we'll retire from the world
and live in the countryside.
No matter where,
I will stay by your side
until death do us part.
You've thought it so thoroughly.
It seems as if you've thought about
these words a hundred times.
Not just a hundred times,
but thousands of times.
The procedures, the ceremonies,
none of these matters.
I am your wife. As long as I am alive,
even if just for a moment,
I want to be with you.
How wonderful it would be
if time could stop right here.
Will the future you speak of come true?
It will come true, yes?
(The bride was switched
on the wedding night.)
Who knows when they will discover it.
These fools are definitely still
sharing the same bed.
The thought of continuing the charade
makes me feel sick.
Rest assured. I will think of a solution
as soon as possible
to bring the Lin family to ruin,
forcing them to hand over the formula.
But I don't want you to...
Hesitation only leads to defeat.
I'm inside and you're outside.
Rest assured. The trap is set.
They will surely fall for it.
Your safety is of utmost importance.
Even if it takes longer,
there's no rush.
But I am anxious.
I'm anxious for our future
to arrive soon.
Mrs. Lin, shouldn't you be
in the bridal chamber...
Shut up and lead the way.
Okay.
Why are you leaving in such a hurry?
And carrying so many things?
The estate was burnt
and I had to recuperate.
Now Xinian is married.
The estate has been renovated.
It's not suitable to bother you.
Why speak as if we're not family?
I still hope that you will marry soon
and have a lively celebration.
A few days ago, I saw you
entertaining guests.
I thought you did not want me
to stay here anymore.
How could I drive you away?
Moreover, Qingyue has not yet
been married.
- Why not stay longer?
- Bad news.
Miss Qingyue left a letter,
saying she would marry Lin Shaowen
and asking you to leave her be.
What?
(Wedding)
Xinian.
So it's true. Yesterday I was drugged
and lost consciousness.
I heard that the one getting married
was Qingyue.
Switching brides?
Adultery without a wedding?
How could you commit
such an indecent act?
Qingyue, what on earth is going on?
I don't know. Shaowen, what should I do?
Don't touch me.
You are so senseless.
How can you reassure father?
How would the clan think of you?
Lin Shaowen, is this how you treat me?
- No. I...
- If so,
then please draft a divorce letter
for me to satisfy them.
But the Cheng family won't cooperate
with you anymore.
- Xinian.
Our fireworks business has just won
favor with the nobles.
Don't give up on our cooperation
over this trifle.
Trifle? They used me
as a stepping stone,
shamelessly humiliating me.
How can you still expect me
to work for you,
with the final credit going
to your family?
You took everything from me,
yet you still won't let me be.
You drugged me and clouded my mind.
It wasn't me. I didn't do it.
Xinian. Qingyue set me up.
The one I've wanted to marry is you.
Shaowen.
Shut up.
Xinian, believe me.
I will make her leave right away.
Your position won't be taken.
Lin Shaowen,
how can you be so heartless?
If you do this,
you will humiliate the Cheng family.
Xinian is valuable to the Cheng family.
Only she knows how to make fireworks.
So this is the reason you wanted
to marry me.
Xinian, rest assured.
Even if Qingyue stays here,
you are the only one who will be
the rightful Mrs. Lin.
Lin Shaowen.
I don't want to see you all.
Clean the house for me to live alone.
No strangers are allowed to come in.
(Favor one
and treat the other as trash.)
(Despise one,
and treat the other like a treasure.)
(It's not that someone isn't
good enough,)
(but that they're never worth it.)
You want to cooperate with me?
You are Lin Shaowen's wife.
He shared the bed with another woman
on the wedding night.
What use do I have for a marriage
in name only?
Compared to being the wife
of an imperial merchant,
I'd rather take my compensation
and return to the Cheng family.
It seems that you are truly angry
and determined to burn your boats.
The patriarch of the Lin family
is your father.
But the one manages the ledgers
is Lin Shaowen.
In the end, what will you have?
Whatever they think or do can't
escape my eyes.
The Lin family will be in my hands
sooner or later.
But in the eyes of the nobles and
the clan elders,
all these shops are in your name.
Lin Shaowen's deficit
can easily be blamed on you.
Lin Shaowen keeps a low profile,
but holds high prestige within the clan.
Aren't you afraid that he'll
take control of the Lin family?
Great-uncle, as you know, my wife
has been studying new formulas.
I'd like to see the Su family's formula.
In the future, your share
in our shops will be doubled.
Have some tea.
Someone, bring the best pastries here.
♪Like withered petals,
entangled with memories♪
♪Like the blazing sun,
scorching the passing years♪
♪Like shattered butterflies,
intertwined by blood♪
♪Like desperate flames
that can't burn away resentment♪
♪Bearing scars all over,
I return anew from the flames♪
♪Only to find your unwavering love♪
♪In this life,
drifting through the world♪
♪Wish to be with you♪
♪I wash away the blood and tears,
rising from the ashes♪
♪Only to realize it's you
waiting behind me♪
♪In this life,
there is pain and intoxication♪
♪The vow remains unchanged♪