=Rise From the Ashes=
=Episode 14=
(True Feelings in Feigned Play)
Are you still angry about
your father's bias?
Mind your own business.
Then, do you want to eat?
I'll buy some pastries and fruits.
No.
Go to Luoshi Pavilion?
Then I take you to go shopping?
To watch some acrobatics?
To go on an outing?
To see flowers?
No. No. No.
Then let's make new fireworks?
Okay.
Today,
you've come alone.
I'm afraid the elders of your family
are not pleased
with the marriage.
The elders of my family
all like Xinian very much.
For the engagement,
to show intimacy,
I have come in person.
The gifts are different
from what you promised.
If your promise is unreliable,
how can our family agree
to this marriage?
Mr. Yuyang.
This is not the formal proposal.
Moreover,
our original formula is not
to be divulged.
It seems that
Xinian doesn't want it,
but you are obsessed with the formula.
You have promised it.
Now you can't offer it,
so you quibble over who wants it.
Yuyang.
You want the firework formula
of the Lin family?
The new fireworks of our family
are all made by Xinian.
Xianzong, don't you know
that if Xinian leaves,
we will lose a great asset?
If you show sincerity and reciprocates
with the formula,
is there any problem?
That's not the case.
When our families become one,
the fireworks business can last longer.
Your scheming sure is loud and clear.
You promised my niece.
But now you want to gain without giving.
Shaowen, do you sincerely wish
to marry me?
Of course.
Father.
I just wanted to test Shaowen.
That's why I asked Uncle
to propose conditions.
Now that he's full of sincerity,
naturally I'll consent.
Xinian.
Uncle.
It's a misunderstanding.
Shaowen.
Xinian is a concubine's daughter.
She'll marry into
the imperial merchant family.
If there is no support from an elder,
I worry she would be aggrieved.
So I carefully considered
the betrothal gifts.
I hope you will not take offense.
You always say I am biased against you.
But what parents do not wish the best
for their children?
If you truly want it,
I will definitely support you.
But no matter what happens,
you must remember,
the Cheng family
will always be your home
and your backing.
How can you easily agree
to this marriage?
I won't allow it.
Who are you to ask me?
My uncle?
Accomplice?
Ally?
Or what?
You've said that
we're not just allies.
Not allies?
Then what are we?
I was determined long ago.
Even if I truly marry him,
I might not get the real formula.
But if I don't marry him,
when can we get what we desire?
What you want
is just a pretext to enter
the Lin family,
a pawn to help you succeed.
The success is within sight.
Why do you, the player,
have second thoughts?
You don't need to force yourself now.
- I'll...
- You have plotted for years,
with so many subordinates.
If you could get it,
would you need to disguise as my uncle?
Lin Shaowen is not a good man.
If you have to live with him,
I am afraid you will get hurt.
I have said
I was willing to exchange.
You clear the name of the Su family.
I take revenge on the Lin family.
What's not good about it?
We shelter under the same roof.
No need to take the lightning strikes.
It's never been for you.
Don't think too highly of yourself.
Hopefully one day,
I can wash away all the filth
and set out pure and clean.
(Our original formula is not
to be divulged.)
(Yuyang.)
(You want the firework formula
of the Lin family?)
Father.
Why were Cheng Xinian and Shaowen
engaged today?
You agreed with me...
Shut up!
Father.
What's the matter?
I have verified Cheng Yuyang's
identity twice.
There were no problems.
But today
why did he take an interest
in the Lin family's formula?
You are suspicious of Uncle?
Uncle was sick for a long time
and did not leave the estate.
But after they came back,
he's been very close with Xinian.
And her behavior is not like
the country girl as before.
Instead, she's always showing off.
Back then I spared her
because I thought her hereditary skills
could someday be of great use.
And there's this Cheng Yuyang.
After he went to the estate,
I never thought he could come back.
Keeping them
has instead become a trouble.
For both of them,
I cannot be soft-hearted anymore.
Boss.
As for the incense burner,
luckily you replaced it in advance.
Something's off.
It's harmless to common people.
For someone poisoned,
it will be more poisonous.
Smelling it frequently has a
remarkable effect on coughing.
After Old Mr. Cheng died,
Cheng Yuyang was sent away
due to his illness.
To avoid infecting others,
he lived in isolation.
But we checked Doctor Huang's
former apprentice.
And the oddness of Cheng Yuyang's body
clearly showed that he was poisoned.
He died from poisonous food
over the years.
If he was murdered,
our investigation
will be noticed, no matter how cautious.
Withdraw our people.
Be more vigilant.
- Yes.
Poisoned.
You hand.
What if I want to harm you?
How could a single sting harm me?
At the worst to vent the anger I caused
during the day.
Boring.
Cheng Yuyang was poisoned.
I said he had been poisoned.
I got it.
My uncle had been poisoned.
You fear that I was poisoned.
That's why you rushed to see me, right?
Although my uncle and I lived
in the same estate,
everything we ate and used was separate.
My uncle was seriously ill.
What the main house sent were tonics.
No one was suspicious.
Whether it's illness or poison,
I have neither.
Whatever.
I'm just afraid you'll die before
you marry into the Lin's.
All will be in vain.
Why?
You should worry
that I'd become a widow.
Turns out your mouth is poisonous.
Let me help you detoxify it.
- Detoxify.
- You're the poisonous one.
Since
my uncle had been poisoned,
then the corpse can no longer be kept.
Rest assured.
I'll handle it.
(Thus far in this life,)
(even if everything)
(is unpredictable and
all comes to naught in the end,)
(I still want it)
(to go right.)
♪Like withered petals,
entangled with memories♪
♪Like the blazing sun,
scorching the passing years♪
♪Like shattered butterflies,
intertwined by blood♪
♪Like desperate flames
that can't burn away resentment♪
♪Bearing scars all over,
I return anew from the flames♪
♪Only to find your unwavering love♪
♪In this life,
drifting through the world♪
♪Wish to be with you♪
♪I wash away the blood and tears,
rising from the ashes♪
♪Only to realize it's you
waiting behind me♪
♪In this life,
there is pain and intoxication♪
♪The vow remains unchanged♪