=Rise From the Ashes=
=Episode 11=
(Unexpected Feelings)
Put it there.
Look.
The Luoshi Pavilion.
Boss is back.
- Boss.
Lady boss.
- Who is your lady boss?
I just know to call you lady boss.
I know nothing else.
Lady boss.
Please sit.
- Okay.
- Come.
It's your first time here?
Please.
Come on.
Guys.
- The lady boss. Greetings.
- See?
It's all for you.
Nice meeting you.
Sit.
Take a sit.
Come on.
Bring her favorite grapes.
Lady boss.
Here. The grapes.
These are tasty.
These must be delicious.
Ever since our boss took over
Luoshi Pavilion,
he's with a girl for the first time.
It's been almost ten years.
I've never seen
him bringing a woman
alive back before.
Eat this.
It's our first meeting.
A toast to our lady boss.
Cheers.
Come on, eat.
You've drunk so much.
Exactly.
Guys.
Who will make another toast?
Right, let's toast to lady boss.
Come on, a toast to lady boss.
Come on.
Try harder.
Almost there.
Over the years,
you've been planning so much.
The Lin's is the imperial merchant.
It's really difficult to bring them
to justice.
Fortunately,
you have their company.
They are orphans just like me.
We wandered everywhere and met.
Rootless
with no attachments,
yet we are like brothers.
You are the only son of the Sus.
With a wealthy and flourishing family,
you must
have lived happily.
After your family was ruined,
you were alone and helpless.
How could it
be easy?
Compared to never having had happiness,
having it and then mercilessly
robbed of it
is even more cruel.
All that's past now.
After settling this,
what do you want to do?
I want to take care of the brothers
at Luoshi Pavilion,
revitalize my family,
and make the best fireworks once again.
And you?
I...
I have never dared to hope for a future.
Why would you think so?
Do you believe in
past and present lives,
and karma?
I tend to believe in instant karma.
Neither love nor hatred lasts overnight.
I had a very long dream.
In that dream,
I loved the wrong person.
(I willingly stood behind him,)
(plotting everything for him)
(and giving him my all.)
(In the end,)
time and time again,
he burned through my heart.
He cursed me to never meet a good end.
(- A great fire...)
- Why?
(A great fire burned away all
my persistent obsession with him)
and completely awakened me.
I want him to know how it feels
to shed all tears,
with only the taste of blood left.
How is this not karmic retribution?
Don't think about it anymore.
You just have to believe
that with me,
there will be a future.
In the future,
you don't need to shed tears.
Only laughter.
Only the future.
If there could be a future,
I want to make
the fireworks that carry my name,
to give the other half of the jasper
to a good person,
and to have
a small home
that shelters from the wind and rain.
I want to have my own children,
aging happily
and ordinarily.
Good.
Shaowen.
Shaoye.
The clan elders have decided
you don't have to deal with
future business.
Shaoye.
If it's because of recent ledger issues,
I can come forward to explain.
Shaowen.
Your ambition lied in
the official career.
Now,
why are you thinking about business?
No. It happened too suddenly.
Did I do something wrong
that displeased the clan elders and you?
Shaowen.
Focus on your imperial exams.
About business,
you don't need to worry.
Most of Lin's shops are in the name
of Lin Shaoye.
But he is not good at it.
In reality, the accounts are handled
by Lin Shaowen.
Presumably,
before the imperial merchant selection,
Lin Shaowen has plans
to fool Lin Shaoye.
So he can pull things back
from the brink.
Given this,
we'll sabotage his plans.
Boss.
You seem to really dislike Lin Shaowen.
Such kind of man is
not worth being liked.
It's nonsense.
Boss.
Whom to like?
What nonsense?
Collect more of their weaknesses.
Take action against the Lin's business.
Make it difficult for them to recover.
But you said before
that due to the discord between
Cheng brothers,
put the plan on hold,
and deliver them a blow on
imperial merchant selection.
She was so heartbroken.
I can't wait anymore.
You do this
for lady boss?
It's just moving the plan forward.
Any progress with the Cheng family?
The Chengs and the Lins thrived
simultaneously.
But now,
thanks to the lady boss,
fireworks are the Cheng's most
profitable business.
Yet, before Cheng Xianzong,
his family had never
dealt with fireworks.
Keep digging.
As for that Lianxin,
ask our men to take care of her
and make arrangements for her.
Okay.
We won't worry lady boss.
If you take my testimony as favoritism,
I will admit it. So what?
If it's what
my heart's desire,
then,
being controlled
isn't necessarily a bad thing, right?
Initially, I wanted to use him.
Unexpectedly,
we have come to this.
(Meet at Lou Wai Lou, quickly)
(What is Uncle about to do?)
(Lou Wai Lou)
♪Like withered petals,
entangled with memories♪
♪Like the blazing sun,
scorching the passing years♪
♪Like shattered butterflies,
intertwined by blood♪
♪Like desperate flames
that can't burn away resentment♪
♪Bearing scars all over,
I return anew from the flames♪
♪Only to find your unwavering love♪
♪In this life,
drifting through the world♪
♪Wish to be with you♪
♪I wash away the blood and tears,
rising from the ashes♪
♪Only to realize it's you
waiting behind me♪
♪In this life,
there is pain and intoxication♪
♪The vow remains unchanged♪