I lost control last night.
That woman should be awake.
I was just defending myself.
I won't hurt you again.
It was an unusual situation.
Don't tell me what I saw was an illusion.
I'm sure it was real.
You're not human,
are you?
This isn't a desert island.
It's a meteorite
that fell into the ocean.
Over millions of years,
it evolved vegetation
and soil.
We settled here,
built homes,
just like you.
Your ancestors were wolves.
Affected by the tide,
you reveal your nature when the moon is full,
even losing control of your powers.
So, Miss Jiang,
you really are a biologist.
Who lied to you?
The Classic of Mountains and Rivers recorded the divine dog Panhu.
He married a princess and had descendants.
The male descendants are dogs,
and the female are beauties.
I'm not a dog.
You just carry people away when you don't get along.
As you can see,
our bodies are different from ordinary people.
So,
you want your people to live a civilized life
and not be disturbed,
So you spread the rumor that you are the boss of the gang.
Yes.
So yesterday
was a misunderstanding.
Ms Jiang
I can agree to your request.
But there is a premise.
What?
You have never seen me in your life.
Right?
Of course.
Deal.
Wait.
I have another debt to settle.
What?
You bit me.
I...
I lost my mind at that time.
I'm sorry.
Is that all?
Thank you.
Where is he?
Sir,
what happened?
We can help you.
I just kissed someone.
This...
We can't help.
I was being treated,
but the wound didn't heal.
Instead, it became
a scar.
The place where he kissed me
is burning like an iron.
Can he fly?
My heart beats fast.
[and my temperature is also very high.]
[My only memory of childhood,]
[the golden-eyed dog was not a dream,]
[but real.]
[Why do I feel]
[an uncontrollable burning sensation?]
[Could it be the ancient legend's]
[wolf clan's mark?]
You don't know me.
Have we
met before?
[Legend has it that]
the one with the mark
will become the lifelong
mate.
You run so fast that you need to drive.
I'll make you sick if I carry you all the way.
You have a conscience.
My sense of smell is a hundred times more sensitive than yours.
It will stink
if you throw up on me.
But not much.
Your business is an amusement park.
Are they ordinary people or wolves?
Both.
How can I tell them apart?
I see.
There were only wolves here.
When humans found it,
I made it a theme park.
We are nocturnal.
We stay at home during the day.
At night,
we come out to have fun.
What do you mean by "have fun"?
You know a lot about wild animals.
They have specific activity areas nearby.
You are safe here.
If you encounter any problems, call the security.
He can hear you.
What about you?
I'm very busy.
But you promised to be my research subject.
Now you're leaving me alone in the wolf's den.
It's just for your convenience.
And
if you're hungry,
let's have a meal together.
No need.
I can go without food for a week.
[So rude.]
[He's deliberately avoiding me.]
[He must be hiding something.]
Wang, ice water.
My lord,
you just defied Miss Jiang,
causing the mark to backfire
and making you burn with pain.
I'll have Zhang and Li bring her back.
I don't want to see her again.
The Li family won't let me set up an altar for my mother,
so I have to worship her secretly.
Cang Feng,
you must keep this a secret for me.
Yes.
From now on,
the only person in the world who loves me
and protects me is gone.
I promised your mother
to protect you for life.
If I break my promise,
I will suffer from the pain of fire burning my skin
and be bitten by ants.
I swear on my blood.
It's unbreakable.
No way.
What can I do for you?
I don't eat pre-made food.
I want freshly cooked food.
Sir,
we only provide fast food here.
If you don't want to eat,
you can cook it yourself in the kitchen.
Cook myself?
You cook?
I work for Qin Yeren.
What?
I'll smash your restaurant.
I don't believe it.
Try it.
You want to be a hero, right?
You're just a kitten.
I...
Before you make trouble in someone else's turf,
look at yourself first.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
I'm off work.
If you're free,
I can buy you a drink.
Okay, see you next time.
I mean,
welcome to come here next time.
Okay, I'm leaving.
I have something to do.