♪ A character that no one knows ♪
♪ Who do you worship? ♪
♪ Who do you blame? ♪
♪ The cold shoulder ♪
♪ The shackles of false freedom ♪
♪ What have you finally become? ♪
♪ Beautiful fireworks ♪
♪ One time is enough ♪
♪ What else do you expect? ♪
♪ Mr. Nobody, who am I? ♪
♪ It doesn't matter if you forget me ♪
♪ We all fight till the end of life ♪
♪ We may get exhausted ♪
♪ We may accomplish nothing ♪
♪ We may never make you proud ♪
♪ Mr. Nobody, who am I? ♪
♪ It doesn't matter if you forget me ♪
♪ Keep chasing ♪
♪ Success always comes with pain ♪
♪ We may get exhausted ♪
♪ We may accomplish nothing ♪
♪ We're all born the same ♪
♪ Just call me Mr. Nobody ♪
= Go Go Squid! =
= Based on the novel Stewed Squid with Honey =
= Episode 17 =
Do you want to know more about him?
Yes!
Tell me those I can't find online!
Let me see...
We had a cat when we were in Solo,
Han Shangyan was taking care of it.
But when the cat died,
he forbade anyone to talk about it.
So Solo and I worked out that
he must have a first love complex.
He is a very possessive and jealous man,
but sometimes something tiny
can cheer him up, too.
When he's in love,
he can be a difficult boyfriend!
A first love complex?
You're surprised?
But... who was his first love?
His first love?
I think...
it was you.
Me?
Yes.
We'd never heard about his girlfriend before,
and the way he looks at you
makes me think of his beloved cat.
Really?
I'm 90% sure about it,
but you can verify it with him.
A pretty girl conference, huh?
Shall I join you?
Ou Qiang, what are you doing?
I didn't dare look at her closely
in front of Shangyan.
You're freaking her out!
Right,
Solo is looking for you.
OK, I see.
Let's go.
-Bye-bye!  -Bye-bye!
Ai Qing,
thank you for telling me this.
In fact, I should thank you.
Without support from family,
he's been fighting alone
just to win gold medals for China.
No family, no girlfriend,
he thought about nothing but winning,
and becoming a Chinese world champion.
So, we used to worry that
nobody could tolerate his bad temper
or his obsession with CTF.
But look at him now,
it's perfect.
Let's go.
Don't forget your card!
Thanks!
It's OK.
So that's why his grandpa's angry with him?
He's so successful.
He's won many competitions and suffered a lot,
but not understood by his family?
You must be tired!
It's too hot,
you got sunstroke?
Wait for me!
Han...
Shangyan.
Keep training!
I... I didn't mean to shout,
you didn't hear me,
so I... I raised my voice.
But, what were you saying outside?
I didn't understand at all!
I said you must be tired,
and wait for me here.
Here!
Listen to me,
we can be intimate privately,
but here's a public place.
You don't wanna be a laughing stock!
I see, try it!
I'm not finished,
I'm a man, they can laugh at me,
but it'll ruin your reputation, you know?
Yes, understood!
Is that good?
Yes.
Drink more!
What's going on?
She's away for just 10 minutes, what happened?
Follow me, Shaofei.
Ai Qing, lead the training.
I lost my balance.
What are you doing?
Quiet!
Well,
do you feel bored here?
No, it's fun here.
There's a beach out the back
of the 1st floor,
you can go there.
Eat or drink anything you like,
and charge it to me.
There are several hotels on the beach,
don't get lost!
I won't!
Is your phone charged?
Yes, almost full!
Go to the lobby if you lose your phone...
Alright stop nagging, Mom.
I'm not a kid, I won't get lost!
Don't worry!
I've bought some fruit,
share it with them.
But the coconut is only for you.
Bye-bye!
Bye!
I'll come for you.
Well,
someone's bought fruit for you.
Who is "someone"?
Who is it?
"Someone"? You mean Mrs. Han?
Come on, pass it!
Pass it, here, here!
Nice!
Hello!
You're here alone?
Why don't you join them?
I didn't pack my bikini.
Hello, I'm Mi Shaofei.
Hello, hello.
Shangyan and I are good friends!
Yes, I know you.
You've read CTF Magazine?
No, I've done some research since I met him,
so I know all of you guys.
Sweet!
I'll buy you a drink, OK?
OK, that's good.
No, don't bother!
It's OK, we're friends.
-Come back soon!  -OK!
Thanks!
He's so kind.
Let's chat.
Yeah, OK.
That day I heard you singing sadly,
anything happened between you two?
Sorry,
I'm not being nosy.
I was his captain
and I'm now managing a team,
so I'm good at reading people's mind.
I know you were unhappy.
Han Shangyan used to live in Norway,
how did you meet each other?
I knew you would ask about him.
Online.
And when was that?
I think it was in 2005.
We got along well on the Internet,
so he came to visit me from Norway.
He came to you from Norway
because you were a nice e-pal?
Shangyan is a weird man,
he's different from normal people.
All Aquarians are weirdos.
And you like weirdos?
I'm back!
Thanks!
Can you drink it cold?
Yes, yes, I can.
Here.
Here you are.
Thanks, thanks!
Welcome!
Training's done?
Try this.
What is it?
Mi Shaofei gave it to me.
It's wine.
No wine for kids!
Shangyan, don't worry,
it's low-alcohol.
Everyone likes to drink iced peach wine!
Thanks for looking after my girl.
It's OK, man.
I want to talk to you
when you're free.
Anytime!
We gotta go.
Bye-bye!
Cheers.
Don't bother him,
and don't go to him too often.
He's very busy.
Don't interrupt him.
I can stay alone!
Tong Nian, you're alone?
I understand,
they're all busy training.
I can stay with you.
It's OK, don't bother.
Never mind, I have nothing to do.
I haven't eaten yet, let's get seafood!
I'm fine, really.
You should have a meal anyway.
I'll take you to some interesting sites,
then let's eat seafood!
It's here!
Thank you!
Be careful.
Thanks!
The boss here is my friend,
their seafood is great!
Anything you wanna eat in particular?
No, anything's fine.
OK.
Then we'll have the specialty here.
Training's advanced,
I only have 10 minutes.
Come on, what is it?
It was in a rush last time,
we didn't have time to chat.
It's unnecessary between us,
we're bros forever.
Shaofei, join K&K.
Han Shangyan,
I have no value,
why do you keep inviting me?
Every one of you is priceless to me.
You value your buddies and friends,
but the value of a player can be calculated.
I performed poorly,
I'll hinder your team if I join K&K.
Solo is working for his boss,
he can't protect you forever.
It was hard for you to come back,
I don't want you to quit again.
I still need to train,
or I'd grab a beer with you.
Don't change the subject.
Come on, man!
We almost fought because of this!
You're too stubborn.
OK, OK, OK.
Go training!
Bye-bye!
= Atlantis Sanya Hotel =
-Hello!  -Hello!
How can I get to this location, please?
Go in that direction for about 3km,
it's a seafood restaurant.
Thank you!
You're welcome!
Sir, do you need an umbrella?
It's about to rain.
No, thanks.
It's OK!
You really have ordered too much.
Relax, I know the boss here.
Eat more,
it's not expensive.
Thanks!
This is good.
Here!
It's OK, I can serve myself.
Have some more!
Try this.
OK, thank you!
Why aren't you eating?
It's OK, I eat it frequently.
It feels weird to be watched.
Shall we eat together?
It's OK, I'm not hungry.
You have a question for me?
Not really,
it's just rare...
to see someone walking with Shangyan,
so I'm curious.
Oh, OK.
You're his girlfriend?
Yes, I'm his girlfriend.
Our parents have already met.
They ate together on New Year's Eve.
It was just a meal!
You're too young,
you don't understand society, yet.
I don't think Shangyan is suitable for you.
I became his fan
the first day he entered the CTF field.
I didn't know about CTF, either.
But my brother liked programming,
so I learned from him
and got to known CTF.
That is how I know him.
I liked Shangyan so much!
But, he suddenly retired!
You know what,
Tong Nian, Tong Nian?
Do you know?
I chose this career because of Shangyan!
I know!
Ai Qing told me he had a lot of fans,
I can totally understand you.
I'm not only a fan, OK?
If I were there,
Shangyan wouldn't have retired.
With my help,
within 3 years,
he'll become a world champion,
the first in China.
You...
seem pretty young.
You're much younger than him, right?
You're a college student?
I'm a postgraduate.
I didn't know that!
I won't tell you I was in gifted class!
What's wrong with my age? Grandma!
Behind every successful man,
there is an important woman.
I know that!
I understand him and support him,
don't worry about us.
That's not enough!
Men are all of great enterprise,
only the women who can help them
can stay with them forever.
Those pretty young things
who hinder a man's development
are only a passing fancy.
That's only a transitory thing.
There are too many flies!
Fly, fly, buzz, buzz, so annoying!
Don't move!
There's one!
Let me kill it!
So why are you telling me this?
No reason, nothing special.
You're too young,
you might get hurt.
You don't know about a man like Shangyan.
You're not suitable for him.
Then who is suitable for me?
Shangyan!  -Shangyan!
How did you know I was here?
Because I care about you!
Shangyan, we were talking about you.
Come on, eat with us!
Here.
You are too busy,
poor girl has to stay alone.
So I brought her here
and treated her to Sanya's specialty.
You should try it, too!
Do you like it?
I don't think anyone would like such a meal!
But you'll like it this way.
Close enough?
Right, Grandpa just called me.
He missed you.
Really?
I'll call him back later.
-I miss him, too!  -OK.
You seem very happy.
I still have some work,
I gotta go.
Go ahead.
I'm leaving now.
Bye-bye!
See yourself out.
Bye.
Is Mr. Han at home?
Should I call him now?
Never mind, he didn't call.
You were jealous of her,
so I helped you mess with her!
Look at your face,
what did she say?
She said she was your fan.
You've known her for a long time?
She's only a crazy sycophant
who wants to enter this field.
She said she had competed in CTF,
that's impressive, but I...
That's meaningless,
I don't like her anyway,
you understand?
Your T-shirt is wet?
The rain suddenly poured under a blue sky.
Why didn't you bring an umbrella?
I was worried and in a rush.
Do you like it?
It's delicious!
She's a mean person,
but she has picked a nice restaurant!
Eat more!
I ate a lot of things while she was chattering.
This one is good!
Right?
Yes.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You can start a new life.
The kid will hinder you from remarrying!
I don't want to,
I'm good with her.
Solo, I miss my daughter a lot.
She's my daughter, too!
Why are they arguing?
Do you know?
You were my first love,
the first man I ever loved.
I never regret being with you,
but I wouldn't have kept her
if I had a second chance.
I kept the baby because I loved you too much.
It's meaningless to mention that,
it has all passed.
Solo, I want my daughter back.
Give me a chance.
I'm her birth mother.
Just give me a chance!
There will be many things
that must be explained by her mother.
Don't you know?
For example,
I was so scared when I
had my first period
in the 6th grade.
It was my mom who explained it to me.
I didn't dare talk to my dad about it.
That's just one of those things.
You can't explain those girl's stuff to her
as a father!
Don't you know that?
Have you finished?
Let me think about it.
What are you doing?
What's up?
You scared me!
Are you OK?
Never better!
What's up with you?
Shangyan came to me today.
What did he want?
He wanted me to join K&K.
To join K&K?
He hasn't changed,
he's too emotional!
What did you say?
Only a coward would leave
at this crucial moment!
You know I'm not a coward.
I do have regrets, but...
There's no "but",
buddy,
I got you!
I should face the facts!
I'll try harder,
and I'll quit if I can't make any progress.
You're the best!
White whale!
It's so cute!
Recently, I've come here often
when I feel tired after training.
If I have poor memory like them,
I'll forget all troubles easily.
Right,
they look so carefree swimming around there.
You haven't told me
what happened to Su Cheng and Solo.
I feel sorry for Xiao'ai.
They were each other's first loves,
but they've broken up.
So Xiao'ai is...
She was born after that,
Solo didn't know.
Solo didn't know?
When Su Cheng couldn't afford Xiao'ai,
she went to Solo.
They married to get a legal identity for Xiao'ai
and then divorced.
Solo's been caring for Xiao'ai alone since then.
They even got married?
It was for Xiao'ai's household registration,
they divorced soon after.
But...
but Xiao'ai...
Don't be a gossip, kid.
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
I have a headache,
Zhou Shan was annoying.
You wanna go back and rest?
I'm fine.
I finally have some time for you,
let's keep going.
♪ I guess I am in a dream ♪
♪ Your eyes are like shiny stars ♪
♪ That attract my entire heart ♪
♪ I don't want to wake up ♪
♪ I take a breath that is deep ♪
♪ And I'm ready to accompany you to the top ♪
♪ I will show you the best night view ♪
♪ I want to cheer up you with a happy tune ♪
♪ Together, together ♪
♪ We'll always feel better ♪
You want to ask her?
I think she's with her boyfriend!
♪ Offer you all the best ♪
♪ Tell you tenderly I love you ♪
Han...
♪ Together, together ♪
♪ Hold you in my arms ♪
♪ Hand in hand, hand in hand ♪
♪ I'll always by your side ♪
It doesn't feel right, Squid,
did you go to Sanya with your boyfriend?
Yes.
Really?
You've just got together, idiot!
It's late!
Go back to your own room!
And, don't stay with him after 9 p.m!
Watch cartoons in your room!
Do you think...
they're sharing a room?
No way!
Go back and have a rest.
You're awake?
How are you?
Feel better?
I'll train tomorrow for the whole day.
Will you be OK to stay alone?
Yes, of course!
Get some rest,
I'm leaving.
Wait!
Here's my room card, take it.
Don't sneak in while I'm sleeping!
I... I'm not a perv!
Order whatever you want,
I'll pay.
No, I have money.
I invited you here,
I must pay!
I've gotta go now.
OK.
Bye-bye!
= Atlantis Sanya Hotel =
Hello?
Hi.
I wanted to let you know I'm back.
You're back?
Why so early today?
They can practice by themselves,
so I came back.
Since you're back,
can... can I come to you now?
OK, let's go out.
See you later!
♪ Why is my heart beating so fast? ♪
♪ I want to rest in your pretty eyes ♪
♪ The storms of love ♪
♪ Blow away my cover at once ♪
♪ You're the drug I'm addicted to ♪
♪ You are the only one in my heart ♪
♪ What else should I do? ♪
♪ So that I can be your only love? ♪
Look at it,
it's so ugly!
It's like,
look at me, like this!
We should hold an imitation contest!
Me first!
Your turn!
No, it's stupid!
We've made a deal to imitate it!
We came here to chase our troubles away!
Don't you wanna be happy?
See, fish have very short memories.
In fact I kinda envy it,
it doesn't remember its troubles, right?
You even rolled your eyes!
You should swim.
I'm your tail!
Look at it, this one,
it's even uglier,
you see?
Its face looks like this.
Where did you go today?
I didn't go out today.
I was in the hotel
and prepared a gift for you.
A gift?
To celebrate us being together!
So...
shall I prepare a gift, too?
No, no, no need at all,
I don't need anything!
My gift is very special.
I can't tell you now,
it's a secret.
What will you do tonight?
Chinese business by day,
headquarter's business by night.
You're upset?
I'm not, I know you're busy.
Since you have nothing to do,
do you want to go to the cybercafe
with us tomorrow?
Can I? Yes, yes!
Go to bed early tonight.
Don't get too tired,
take care of yourself!
Still working?
Even on such a beautiful beach,
you can't relax for a while?
We're here to train, not to rest.
You've talked with Shaofei?
You really want to recruit him?
His ranking is...
Don't talk about it anymore.
He won't join K&K.
He has refused me.
I've always wanted to ask you something.
Yes?
In the final,
do you want us to win,
or SP?
There'll be only one champion.
We all want to win.
I hope you can give priority to K&K's grade
when making any decisions.
Now it's your turn to educate me?
And, you don't know me yet?
Go back to sleep!
OK.
1, 2, 1, 2, K&K champions!
They do that every day?
More or less.
How about you?
Solo team did the same thing?
Us?
We were less professional.
We trained day and night.
I usually had a stomachache and insomnia.
That's true.
I hated P.E. when I was little,
I skipped it cuz it was tiring.
So I got sick all the time.
I gradually realized
that exercise is very important.
See, I'm very healthy now!
I was a short kid.
Exercise helped me to grow a little taller.
Your 800-meter race record?
2 min and 30 sec!
Is that good?
Far above average!
Run faster!
K&K champions, 1, 2, 1, 2!
K&K champions!
♪ Why is my heart beating so fast? ♪
♪ I want to rest in your pretty eyes ♪
♪ The storms of love ♪
♪ Blow away my cover at once ♪
♪ You're the drug I'm addicted to ♪
♪ You are the only one in my heart ♪
♪ What else should I do? ♪
♪ So that I can be your only love? ♪
♪ We're a match, like bread and butter ♪
♪ No one can separate us ♪
♪ Our love is as sweet as it should be ♪
♪ Your smile is the source of my happiness ♪
♪ I love you, like bread loves butter ♪
♪ Bittersweet is the taste of love ♪
♪ The wonderful flavor of memories ♪
♪ Will you forever be my harbor? ♪
♪ I love you, like bread loves butter ♪
♪ No one can separate us ♪
♪ Our love is as sweet as it should be ♪
♪ Your smile is the source of my happiness ♪
♪ I love you, like bread loves butter ♪
♪ Bittersweet is the taste of love ♪
♪ The wonderful flavor of memories ♪
♪ Will you forever be my harbor? ♪