Bro.
I ran into Qin's gang again.
Those guys came looking for trouble.
We threw down a bit.
It's nothing.
I'm going after them.
Get back here.
Bro.
If we don't fight back hard,
they'll keep bullying us forever.
Sit down.
I can't take this anymore.
Why do they get to make money?
Why do they get to buy houses?
While we have to live here,
eating rotten scraps.
Lin You.
Just hang in there.
One day, we'll get to live
that kind of life too.
If that day really comes,
I'm gonna live across the way.
Among all those skyscrapers,
one of them has to be ours.
And when that day comes,
nobody can bully us anymore.
Bro promises you,
that day will come for sure.
And when it does,
it won't just be one house.
All those people who bullied us
all these years,
I'll knock every one of them down
and crush them under my feet.
By then,
the east side of the city is yours,
the west side is mine.
You be the General,
and I'll be your Vanguard.
Deal.
Whatever you say.
Don't worry, bro.
Leave it to me.
Bro.
I learned a new move today.
Let's try it out.
Watch this.
Come on, take this!
Watch me! Watch me!
Here it comes!
And one more move...
Kamehameha!
You lose!
That's no good.
You need real combat.
Watch this! Hey, what're you doing?
Come on, three, two, one!
You lose.
I lose, bro, I lose. You win, okay?
Bro.
Acting all cocky, huh?
Cocky, huh?
Get him!
Cocky!
Hit him!
Big bro!
Lin You!
The cops are here, run!
Don't be scared.
Lin You.
I'm fine.
Bro's got you.
Don't be scared, don't be scared.
Bro's right here.
Lin You.
You think this is one of your comics?
Ghosts and spirits belong in comics.
How could there be ghosts in real life?
You're just...
You're as stubborn as an ox.
You grabbed onto their boss
and called him a dead man.
Now we've got no room to maneuver at all.
You... you...
Unbelievable.
You can't even tell reality from comics.
Lin You.
Did you know
Qin Jianping before?
Even if he did, he...
Excuse me,
is this the Daji Agency?
Blessings of the Infinite Lord.
How can I help you?
Mr. Lin You.
Your brother sent me to bring you to him.
Brother?
You...
You have a brother? How did I not know?
Mr. Wu Qianchen, chairman of Dingfeng Group,
is our boss.
Oh, and Mr. Wang,
the money you owed Jianping's company,
our boss has already paid it off for you.
Paid off?
Lin You, this...
Lin You!
Your brother's something else!
Your brother's a real stand-up guy.
He paid it all off!
All of it!
Well...
go on, then.
Go, go, go!
Bro.
What are you standing there for?
Come, have some tea.
Ever since you got out,
you've grown pretty distant from me.
You don't come to me with anything anymore.
Didn't we agree
that once we had our turf,
the East side would be mine
and the West side would be yours?
Now we've got the turf,
but you won't come back.
I don't want that old life anymore.
I just want to live like an ordinary person.
An ordinary person?
Playing a Taoist to swindle and bluff?
Or selling houses at an agency?
I'll stop teasing you.
Let's deal with business first.
Bro,
why is he here with you?
Wasn't he already dead?
He's not dead.
He just got lucky.
But back in prison,
I heard that he was definitely dead.
That's why I felt so much regret.
You knew he was alive all along, didn't you?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why?
No wonder every time I visited you,
you kept bringing him up.
I only found out later that he wasn't dead.
Lin You,
do you know why I've kept him alive
all these years?
Stab him.
Boss Wu,
is this what you wanted me to do?
I remember back then, the stab was...
right here.
No, wait.
Here.
Stab him.
Are you insane?
Old Qin.
What needs to be done,
you know full well.
The cops will be here soon.
What you've done these past few years,
and how to explain it,
you know exactly what to say.
As for the ten years you owe my brother,
let's call it paid.
Old Qin.
Don't worry.
Your family,
I'll take good care of them for you.
Boss Wu.
I hope you're a man of your word.
Where are you going?
Back to my old life.
I've seen how powerful you are,
Boss Wu.
That's exactly why you should stay here.
I'm the only family you have.
I'm the only one who can protect you.
You're insane. Insane.
Brother Chen.
Want me to go bring Brother You back?
You can't stop him.
He'll come back on his own.
What's the meaning of this?
Did Wu Qianchen put you up to this?
Say something!
What are you trying to do?