Just go, bro.
We're hiring security guards here.
You've got a criminal record.
We really can't take you on.
Boss.
Please reconsider.
Just think about it.
Go on, go on, get going.
Boss, boss.
Where do you think you're going?
Don't run!
Have a sip, Sweetheart.
Don't touch me!
Don't go!
Running, huh?
"Don't touch me." Oh, getting shy?
Come play with me.
What are you mumbling about, Sweetheart?
Speak up!
Let us guys hear it.
Yeah, exactly.
Pretending to be Sadako?
Playing dress-up in the middle of the night?
Who the hell are you?
That's enough.
None of your business.
Help me!
You threw the first punch.
This is self-defense.
Go, go, hurry!
According to our nation's Criminal Law,
Article 237 stipulates that
using violence,
coercion, or any other means
to forcibly molest or insult women
is punishable by up to 5 years in prison.
Bro, I'm sorry!
Bro, which gang are you with?
Just a concerned citizen.
Okay?
Thanks for saving me yesterday.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have known what to do.
Oh, right.
Does your head still hurt?
Have some of this calming tea I brewed.
Careful, it's hot.
A trial-stay isn't as scary as you think.
Maybe give it another thought?
I really can't do this job.
Why don't you talk to your boss?
I'll find another way to pay him back.
The boss already said,
if you ask that, the answer is no.
It's all written down here.
Your medical bills come to 2,580.
1,500 in compensation for the fight.
Clothes, 80.
Lodging fees total 50.
Minus your wages, you still owe the boss
exactly 3,800 yuan.
So until you've paid all of this back,
we can't return these belongings to you.
What are you doing?
Let me tell you,
I've got quite a temper.
If you guys don't want to be reasonable,
then I'll have to settle this another way.
Wait, wait!
Let's talk this out, okay?
Your birth chart is absolutely perfect.
You're a great fit for this line of work.
Plus, Daji hasn't hired anyone in ages.
Worst case, I'll go with you.
Even though
I won't be much help either.
Blood moon for eyes,
Dark wind for a throat,
Rotten earth molds the bones,
Corpse rain weaves the flesh,
This body is the curse,
This thought is the bind,
This hatred shall never end.
So you want a drink, huh?
One cup of wine, one life.
I doubt you'll live to walk out of here.
Such a tiny wound and you're done?
That tough, huh?
No wonder
your birth chart is so strong.
Think I'm being too nice?
Forgot who took you in?
Who?
Listen up.
The one who took you in is Xu Liuliu.
She's my best friend.
I'm Chen Shuyao.
If you dare bully Liuliu again,
I'll deal with you a whole different way.
I'm warning you.
Don't even think about running.
Hand it over.
I...
Oh, right.
You better not try anything funny.
Your ID card.
Liuliu's already got a photo of it.
If you dare run,
I'll call the cops and have you arrested.
I...
Oh, and...
Hey, big guy.
There's nothing around you.
Don't worry.
I guarantee it.
Hold onto this.
Mission accomplished.
The big guy's not bad.
Lin You, you're amazing!
Even Yaoyao is praising you.
Congrats on going full-time.
You got out and didn't even tell me?
Where are you right now?
I'll come pick you up.