Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Ja-Oh.
Where are the boys going?
Well, the boys are “into the eggs” these days.
We just wanted to make history
by playing games into the year 2000.
The food for the New Year’s event is pride.
Since it’s New Year, we, the Jarasjam Family, are giving you 100 Baht each.
Hand it over to the client if it’s ready.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Off you go, Sing.
Once you get the money,
give it to me.
Take care when you ride.
Babe.
What do you think our son would buy for his friends?
Would he buy anything, though?
Are you saying that he would scam my money?
That’s not it.
I mean would he be able to come up with anything to buy?
He would probably be handing out money to his friend at this point.
How do you know?
Would he be acting just like me?
How can I not know?
I’m his mom.
An apple never falls far from its tree.
There’s no need to be so alike, actually.
What’s so bad about taking after my personality, though?
I’m lovable that’s why you fell for me.
You’re so full of yourself.
It’s so hot out here.
Shall we close the shop for a little while?
We just got downstairs.
I’m not satisfied yet.
Yeah?
I have to get the work done first.
I’ll be waiting in the room.
Follow me in.
Damn it.
(The New Year’s Night.)
Something got stuck in my teeth.
What did?
Hey. Hey.
What do you have to complain about me again?
Hey, there’s no need to be so alarmed.
I just have something to ask you.
Here, take a seat.
Take your seat right here, Lin.
Out with you.
Here, right here, Lin.
You can sit here.
What did you want to ask, Lin?
You can ask me as well.
The thing is,
are you guys still going to play games over New Year’s Night?
Of course, we are.
I’m telling you, us playing games this time is nothing ordinary.
It’s the making of history.
How’s that?
Sounds awesome already.
Are you guys not afraid?
What’s there to be afraid of?
The Y2K Ghost.
The people in Bangkok are so paranoid about it.
Rumors are going around.
Ghosts aren’t real Ja-Oh.
Right, there are no ghosts.
Right.
I don’t know if it’s true
but the story I’ve heard is really scary.
What’s the story about?
Have you guys seen the movie “The Ring”?
Oh,
the one that a ghost comes out from a TV?
My dad showed me.
Even my dad got scared.
That movie was really scary.
Uncle Haeb has the movie for rent.
There’s also the novel version.
Even Uncle Haeb thinks it’s scary.
Is it the one you showed me yesterday?
One with a woman who died in a pond?
Lin,
how does the story go after that?
It goes like this, guys.
It’s a curse of a woman who got electrified by the computer.
On New Year’s Night, her ghost will manifest in the internet system.
The female ghost will kill whoever has their computer on over New Year’s Night.
Ow!
It’s not raining but why was there a sound of thunder?
Sorry, I just moved my chair.
Damn it, Ja-Oh!
You guys are scared to death just because of that?
Are you guys still thinking of playing games, then?
Hey.
Hey, hey.
Who’s scared?
No one is.
Right, dude?
Ghosts aren’t real.
That’s right.
Are you scared?
I’m… I’m not scared at all.
No.
I’m not scared, not at all.
What is it?
Just get in there.
You scared me, Uncle.
Why is it so dark in here, Uncle?
How can it not be, I didn’t turn on the light.
Damn it, I thought this was a horror movie.
What are you so afraid of?
My shop doesn’t have a gh–
U, U, Uncle?
How did the computer turn on by itself?
Tong.
Tong, where are you going?
Pao, you too.
Hurry up.
Tong.
You have an amulet, bastard.
No! No!
You lead the way.
Dong has an amulet.
Ghosts are scared of a Buddhist amulet, Dong.
Ghosts are scared of a Buddhist amulet.
so go, Dong.
Hurry up.
Where are we going?
Where did Uncle go?
I’m scared.
I’m sorry.
Ja-Oh!
Ja-Oh! What’s wrong?
What is it, Ja-Oh?
What is it?
What’s wrong, Ja-Oh?
Is it out yet?
It won’t go away if you just rub it like that, Mai.
Do it harder!
Fine.
Hang on.
Mai!
You want it hard, huh?
Calm down, Ja-Oh.
Mai!
Pao!
Here you go, Pao!
Where are you going?
Where are you going, Pao?
Pao!
You are quite sly for teaming up with Uncle Khai to get us.
I’m good, aren’t I?
Here.
A New Year’s present.
For you.
I haven’t received a New Year’s card since I was in grade 4.
Your present is so childish.
It’s so childish,
that’s why it suits you well.
It’s nowhere near as awesome as mine, though.
You’ve prepared something?
For real?
Here.
Hey!
Give it, I’ll show you.
This is how you look at it.
This is what you’ve always wanted to do, right?
It’s a cartoon so I can do anything with it.
It’s cute.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Happy New Year.
Same to you.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
You seem so close with Lin these days.
Can you…
help me get together with Lin?
What’s this?
I’ve just bought a new shirt, are you still going to poke it?
It’s the mark for good students.
There’s nothing wrong.
It’s actually cool.
Are you done with your work?
Hey, Tong!
Ow!
What’s wrong?
Finish your work, you won’t get it done.
I can do that later.
No.
No “Later” and no slacking.
Hurry up!
You poke all my shirts until there’s none left at home
You’ve been poking it for the entire year, and now you’re poking it too?
Take out your work and start working on it, then.
So I won’t have to poke you.
Do you want me to poke you, huh?
Ow!
Tong.
Which number do you want?
How many shuffles?
None of your business.
What?
What about you, Bank?
None of your business.
What the heck, why’s no one playing with me?
You poor bastard.
Fine, I’ll play with you.
Hey, which number do you want?
3.
How many shuffles?
Well, Tong.
Hmm?
You seem so close with Lin these days.
Will you just cut to the chase?
Can you…
help me get together with Lin?
What do you want me to do?
Write a love letter for you?
Hey,
that sounds alright.
But put my name on the sender at the end.
I was being sarcastic.
Oh?
Let’s do this.
If you help me write a letter to Lin,
I will
buy you 3 porn
and with it, I’m giving you one set of Champagne X posters.
Okay?
Are those enough?
Then,
I’ll buy it for you for the whole year.
Love is about pricing.
How much?
500.
Can I bargain?
A half of that, maybe?
Love can’t be bargained.
It’s not about business.
It’s about feelings.
My ass.
Keep the change.
You can leave it to me.
When are you getting started?
Love is about feelings.
So it will take some time.
Sis, someone asks me to deliver you a letter.
Who is it?
The name’s Bank.
I saw him waiting in front of our house for a while
but just wouldn’t ring the doorbell to call you.
I got annoyed so I took it from him.
Then why did you take it from him?
Because if I don’t,  he would be there all day.
I’m off to play football.
Hold on, Ton Liu, have you studied?
Bring me the yellow.
There’s none.
Mai.
I told you to get it from in front of the science room, didn’t I?
When did you tell me that?
You forgot, didn’t you?
I didn’t. When did you ever tell me?
You forgot.
I told you from the start to get yellow from in front of the science room.
Who would want to go there now, it’s so damn dark.
You forgot to bring it so you should go.
Stop!
You should go.
You left it out there.
You forgot.
Then both of you go and get it with me.
You too, Ja-Oh.
I’m not going alone with you.
Why not?
Are you afraid you’d fall for me, Giraffe?
Shut it.
Come. You and I.
I have to go as well?
Yeah.
- The trouble falls on me again.
- Let’s all go.
Right.
Just step right on it, it’s your work after all.
I’m hungry.
- Lin.
- Bank
grab something to eat with me.
You go. I’m not hungry.
Lin, are you tired?
Lin, are you hungry?
I’m pretty hungry.
I’ll get you something to eat.
Sure thing.
Thanks.
Dong, I happen to be hungry too.
You are so damn nosy.
Dong, come here!
Dong!
Hey, Lin.
Where did everyone go?
They went to grab stuff and find something to eat.
Good that you’re here. Help us out.
So we can quickly finish this and go home.
(Quickly finish this and go home.)
By the way, Tong.
Have you registered for any extra tutoring classes?
Nope.
Why should I?
It’s far. We have to drive to another city.
But everyone does that.
It so happens that ‘everyone’ does not include me.
Then you should come and study with me.
Why should I study?
Bank brought me a letter at home yesterday.
What does that have to do with me?
He even wrote me a poem.
No one has ever written me a poem.
“Help me, I have fallen for this girl,”
“She’s so pretty, smart, and lovable,”
“With study, she’s unmistakable,”
“Not to mention she’s one kind-hearted girl.”
Bank’s good at this.
“I want to invite her out for snacks”
“Savor the wind and watch this and that”
“I will take care, you won’t get a bug’s bite”
“If that’s alright for you, my awesome girl.”
He’s the modern-day Shakespeare.
But this is your handwriting, isn’t it, Tong?
And you’re the only one who says “awesome”.
If you have time at hand, use it to study.
You should read more.
You’re talented.
You can become a writer, perhaps.
A writer?
No, no. That’s not cool at all.
Hey.
If you put your mind to it, anything can become awesome.
Come on.
Let’s study hard.
Why aren’t you taking tutoring classes?
Why are you here?
Because you said it’s far.
Doing it this way is pretty good too.
We don’t have to spend lots of money.
Isn’t it because you wanted to be alone with me?
Admit it, I’m pretty cute, right?
Oh.
I have no interest in boys who are dumber than me.
That’s crazy.
I’m pretty smart.
I just let you win.
If I win, you might be sad.
Is that so?
Then tell me when you get serious.
Let’s make a bet.
If I win, you have to do whatever I ask you to.
What should we bet on, then?
If you get the highest score on the final exam this time,
you can do anything to me.
But if I get the highest score,
you have to cut your hair into a bob.
Why a bob?
I want to see you in short hair.
Sure.
Because I would win anyway.
Let’s see.
When the next Olympic Games begins…
(And during 2000-2001, I stepped up to become Lin’s rival in studying.)
I’m definitely getting it this time.
I’m getting you.
Mai!
Let’s do it.
H
Hydrogen.
Li.
Lithium.
2…1…
Do you
Believe
I’m getting you this time.
I looked it up in the dictionary, Tong.
Hey!
I fuck you!
I cucumber you!
I zucchini you!
You stupid!
I fuck you too!
Na.
Sodium.
Dy.
Delicious.
Delicious!
Bank.
Do you need my help?
Study.
Tong, you bastard!
I hope you fail your exams!
Toey, it’s a sin to say that.
Dy.
Delicious.
Alright, Dysprosium, Dysprosium.
Close the door.
Hey, Uncle Toey, what about Grandma?
Get in here!
Damn you!
Tong, you bastard.
I’ve finished my studies.
Love’s here.
We wanted to put a sticker on you.
I’m the first one.
No, no. I’m the first one.
Me first.
You come over here.
Look.
They come in pairs.
So sweet.
Go ahead and only put on stickers for each other.
What’s going on?
Why isn’t anyone putting stickers on us?
I’m quite handsome.
Just sit down.
No one dares put stickers on you because of your crotch.
Get down.
Right, you bastard Dong.
That’s why no one wants to put stickers on us.
You too, Mai.
You’ve been scratching your crotch all day, no one wants to put stickers on us.
Well, this one too.
You keep studying.
It’s Valentine’s Day!
It’s the day of love.
You’re corny from primary school up to high school.
I might be corny but I’m never lonely, though.
That’s because Lin’s always in my heart.
You guys want stickers?
Put it on among yourselves then.
That’s sad.
You can put it on for me, Mai.
I’ll do it for you, you do it for me.
Mai, let me do it for you.
You want this one, right?
Easy with it.
Are you getting a good look?
Hey, Pao.
Here it is.
More of it, this one’s from a 10th-grader.
I’m so sick of this Miss Popular.
You got all the cut stuff.
I’m so jealous.
Well, Ja-Oh. You’re one to talk.
I saw you getting a chocolate.
Did you get it from a 12th-grader?
Do you want some?
No! He gave it to you.
So what?
If he gave it to me then I have the right to share it with my best friend.
On top of that,
we have to share the fat.
Am I not fat enough already?
Eat up.
It’s good, right?
By the way,
did you give chocolate to anyone?
No.
Why not?
I don’t have time for that.
I have to study for the university entrance exam.
You are so not romantic.
A time like this only comes once.
Don’t regret it later.
I don’t think I will regret it.
Because I’m happy with the way my life is right now.
Another thing, Ja-Oh,
Valentine's isn’t all about romantic love.
It can be for friendship too.
There are various kinds of love.
Are you happy thinking that way?
Which part of it makes you happy?
I am happy.
Happy to learn, to play, and to see my friends.
And to see you.
Lin!
Are you confessing to me?
I got caught.
I’ve been hiding my love for you for a long time.
I’m not easy.
Don’t you like me a little, Ja-Oh?
I’m so sad, Ja-Oh doesn’t like me.
I like you too.
Here you go!
You’re always teasing me.
Why isn’t there anyone pretty and cute?
Hey, dude!
Love’s here.
I can hold it myself.
What are you guys doing standing in the way?
Who’s standing in the way?
Isn’t that you who’s standing in our way of love?
When will you stop being so corny, Bank?
I might be corny, but Lin is the only one I see.
Enough, let’s cut to the chase.
What is it?
We wanted to put a sticker on you.
Only for me?
What about Ja-Oh?
Uh, yeah.
But I wanted to put it on you first.
I want to be the first one in the group to put a sticker on you.
Hey, I’m the first one.
No, no. I’m the first one.
What are you talking about?
There’s no need to fight.
Hey.
What is it, Tong?
When there's an argument, we need to use the fairest way of judgment.
What’s that?
Rock-paper-scissors.
So fair.
Come on.
- Don’t be slow.
- Come at me.
Bring it.
Rock-paper…
Hey!
What are you just rock-paper-ing for?
I almost peed my pants.
I’ll do it.
Rock-paper-scissors.
I won.
If you’re going to put on stickers then hurry up.
I want to go home already.
I won.
Hey, damn you, Dong.
I almost hit my head.
It’s good that I held on to a pole.
Mai!
Today’s when you die!
Ja-Oh!
Why did you put a sticker in my mouth?
I didn’t mean to.
Mai!
- I didn’t even want to put a sticker on you.
- Ja-Oh!
You stop right there!
I was going to put it on Lin, not you!
Mai!
Mai’s gone.
Lin.
Hey, I’m the first one.
No, no.
You come here.
You too.
Come here.
Calm down, you’ll hurt yourselves.
Tong, hold on.
Don’t pull it.
Don’t pull!
You come here.
Hold him.
He’s getting there.
He’s approaching her.
I’m the first one to put a sticker on Lin.
Tong put a sticker on Lin.
Me first.
I’m giving you my heart.
Put it on here.
Where?
Hey, you’re cutting my cue, Pao?
Come back here.
Ja-Oh!
Help me.
Happy Valentine’s.
Thank you.
I’m back.
Oh ho! What have you got there so much in your hands?
The Valentine’s stuff, Mom.
Seeing you like this reminds me of your mom.
She was so popular when she was a young lady.
All the boys in town were trying to win her over.
You’re exaggerating.
Let me help you carry it, sister.
Well, Ton Liu, I know you want something in return for the help.
No, I don’t.
But can I have some of the snacks?
There we go.
Yeah, take it.
She even knows there’s one more right here.
You said you were going to help your sister.
Here, put it down here.
There we go.
This is cute.
So cute.
Let me put my stuff away.
Are you the Valentine’s Day star?
Here, careful not to drop it.
Thank you.
Do you want my sister to be impressed?
Do you know J’Rock?
Are you sure you know what J’Rock is?
Not only J’Rock, I also know JJ.
Who’s JJ?
JJ, the son of Joom who sells Jim-Joom at the Jarket.
Market!
(Final Exam’s result announcement day.)
You’re amazing, my son.
Just like your dad.
You even got the second place.
Hey, Tong came second.
Yay!
Tong came second!
That’s amazing.
Tong got the second place.
From the last to the second place.
That’s a leap.
Unlike yours, she used to come first and now she’s still the first.
That’s like staying in the exact same place.
Congratulations on your son becoming hard-working.
Ping.
You’re here as well?
Yes.
Hey.
That year we had the beauty pageant, I was having diarrhea.
Otherwise, I’d have won.
You’d have been the second.
It was a relief you had diarrhea, otherwise, I wouldn't have won.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Well, Yong.
Would you like to switch?
Hey, we can’t switch.
Our son is so good, why would you want to switch?
I meant the wife.
Tao, you bastard.
I’m, your wife.
People all over the town wanted to have me.
You…!
Well, he deserves a kick.
He never changes, just like that from when he was a young boy until old.
But that was fun.
I don’t want to go home, Sis.
Shall I take you to J’Phon’s Milk Place?
Let’s go.
Oh?
What are you girls talking about?
Let’s go home, Ton Liu.
You can head home first, Mom and Dad.
I’ll take Ton Liu to J’Phon’s Milk Place.
I’ll take her home.
Take good care of your sister.
Sure, I will take good care of her.
Don’t stay out too late.
Sure, Mom.
I’ll see you at home.
Let’s go.
Here, Papa.
What should we eat, Ton Liu?
Just say it to your sister.
I’ll have everything.
Everything?
I was thinking of Kaya Toast and Milk with syrup.
Do you want that too?
Yes.
Give me a minute.
You’re good.
You came second.
I know I lost, you don’t have to rub it on me.
What do you want me to do?
What to do?
What should it be?
Should I shave?
Or I can do a buzz cut if you want.
Why the haircut?
Can’t it be anything else?
That’s because I bet on a haircut with you.
Or do you want money?
I don’t have any money.
Hey, Tong! What sort of person do you think I am?
Then what do you want me to do?
You don’t have to do anything for me.
I actually got what I wanted from you.
Huh?
What’s that?
Lin!
Mr. Sommai wanted to see me, can you come alone?
Sure.
Ton Liu, I’ll be right back.
Lin.
Lin, Lin.
What is it? Tell me before you go.
Lin!
Do you want my sister to be impressed?
What is it, little one?
Do you know J’Rock?
A snack?
J’Rock!
You’re doing that as if it’s some soy sauce.
I want it J’Rock.
Problems.
Do you mean, “No problem”?
Thanks for the correction.
Are you sure you know what J’Rock is?
You’re looking down on me, boy.
Not only J’Rock, I also know JJ.
Who’s JJ?
JJ, the son of Joom who sells Jim-Joom at the Jarket.
Market!
Come on, Uncle. It’s J’Rock.
Right, right.
You’d better get it straight.
Don’t worry.
Leave it to me.
Tong!
I don’t owe you anything anymore.
What’s with your hair?
And what’s this costume?
Well,
you like J’Rock, don’t you?
The little one told me that.
So awesome.
Why are you laughing?
You got played.
Little one!
I was bleaching it for hours.
My scalp was all burning.
This jacket is so hot.
These pants are so tight.
People were staring at me when I was driving down the street.
That’s pretty awesome though, Tong.
So awesome.
Hey!
Stop playing with my hair.
Tong.
Whichever devil’s gotten into you that made you do this hair?
Right.
Oh, you must have tried to copy Sakuraki.
Me?
I’m cooler than that, of course.
My ass.
Aren’t you afraid of Sommai?
Why would I be?
If someone like me were to get my hair colored, everyone in school has to know.
My ass.
What do you mean you’re not scared?
I saw you sitting in the toilet since 5 AM.
Such a sucker.
Pao!
What is it?
(On that day, I didn’t understand why Lin cut her hair short)
(when she actually won the bet.)
Tong!
Shit!
What did you do to your hair?
Tong’s done for.
This is my natural hair color, Sir.
Do you think I have short legs that I wouldn't catch up, huh?
I trust you now, Mai.
Trust me on what?
He wouldn’t be able to catch up.
(From then on, I wanted to study hard)
(because I knew that it’s what made Lin happy.)
You’re still smiling, are you?
Buy me a new shoe polish, understand?
Do you understand?
Turn this way.
No one’s as naughty as you are.
You’re the most naughty one in the 3 realms.
Here.
I think the reason why Lin cut her hair short
is because she has feelings for me.
Oh, Lin.
Why didn’t you just tell me you like me?
What?
It’s obvious that Lin cut her hair short to please me.
Huh?
Lin likes me.
What are you ‘Huh’-ing for?
Shall we just ask Lin why she cut her hair short?
Let’s do it.
Come on.
Lin,
we have something to ask you.
What is it?
We were wondering why you decided to cut your hair short.
That’s right, that’s right.
Oh.
Right.
It’s fine.
You don’t have to answer, I do understand.
And I wanted to let you know that I’m just like you.
I like you too, Lin.
Ew.
What’s up with you?
Do you all have a narcissistic complex?
I didn't know it was contagious.
And what’s wrong with that, Giraffe?
Do you want to get kicked by a Giraffe, Mai?
Hey!
Ja-Oh!
Help!
Lin!
Can I ask you frankly?
Why did you cut your hair?
I cut my hair because…
Because…
Because short hair is trendy right now
and I wanted to switch up my look a little.
What do you think?
Is it nice?
Yeah.
I think you look cute in this hair.
Tong!
Your hair!
Why is it like that?
Why?
Not cool?
It’s cooler than my hair.
Mai!
Shit!
It’s over!
Hey, hey, calm down.
We still have the University Entrance Exam.
Huh?
I’m so jealous of you.
You have boys trailing behind you from the first day until the graduation day.
So which one are you choosing?
When I think of not being able to see you guys again,
it makes my heart sink.