The Story of Ming Lan
Episode 60
Your daughter-in-law tried to persuade in all ways.
But my sister is just so obsessed with it.
She doesn't listen to me despite how I persuade.
Forget it.
I didn't expect you
to put this in mind.
So forget it.
You stay out of this matter then.
I will surely in the future . . .
Minglan isn't born by you.
You don't take her to heart seriously
and I can't force you.
A woman being mindful
of her maiden home is reasonable.
so I can let that go.
But you
show your favoritism too obviously.
You even lavish affection on Kang House.
How could I?
Stand up.
Stand over there.
I won't explain
other principles,
since you won't understand anyway.
I've said to you over and over already.
Don't have connection with Kang House.
And disallow her to
come to our home.
But you let her come without my knowledge.
You defy your elder like this.
You ignored me.
Kneel.
What?
Kneel here?
Kneel.
Back when Lin was still around,
you were indeed suffering wrongly.
So no matter what offense you commit,
I would only say a few words
but never punish you seriously.
But now I see that
I spoiled you too much.
You kneel here for a day.
If she dares to come again,
you go and kneel in the yard.
Mother. Mother.
I accept the punishment.
But isn't it too harsh?
I am the main wife in charge of the house!
If you don't accept,
go to your husband.
If you still don't accept,
go back to your maiden home.
Big Madam.
Get lost!
Don't think I don't know
you're laughing at me.
Get lost!
They really just
sent her away?
They just sent her out.
Our people followed and saw Sheng House
send the woman out of the city
in a carriage in the rain.
Neither did they wait for
a clear weather nor the daylight.
Sheng House's brat.
She looks so petite and delicate.
An illegitimate born.
But she's actually an opponent.
Yes.
She suddenly makes this act
of pulling the carpet under us.
Even if we expose her,
but Kang Zhao'er
has already been sent away.
The one from Kang House
is an useless thing.
Wasting my words.
Other than having a loud voice,
she's trash.
I never thought that
Madam Sheng is so young,
but she makes her moves
with so much weight and astuteness.
Doesn't have any loophole
and deceives all of us
completely.
Big Madam.
I think
this brat isn't an easy opponent.
Maybe we should just quit.
There are only two paths.
Either I let Second
boil me with fire.
Or I choose a way to death on my own.
Big Madam.
I have a Buddhist figure in my room.
The Maitreya.
It was actually begged
from a high monk
by the old marquis.
He prays to this figure in the room every day.
Do you know
what he prays for?
It must be for the family's rise of glory.
You're wrong.
Maitreya is the future bodhisattva.
He was praying
that he meet my big sister again
in the next life.
That . . . isn't for sure.
Actually the old marquis
knew very clearly.
Big Sister wasn't actually a great mate.
She wasn't gifted for birth and child-rearing.
She wasn't gifted in managing house.
And her life wouldn't be long.
But he just loved her.
No matter how great and virtuous others were,
That's all useless.
That's all in the past.
Old Marquis
doted on you too.
really loved Big Sister.
After Big Sister died,
he
just became
an empty shell in this house,
wandering around.
These days,
the passion of Second and his bride
that I see
is exactly the same as his old man.
Both are born as pig heads.
If this Sheng Minglan dies,
Second will be crippled.
It's true.
He would be crippled for real.
So this time,
I don't want anything else.
I only want Sheng Minglan's life!
Big Madam!
This is the shrine,
and you can't say that.
Am I supposed to be scared
of these useless wood?
Big Madam.
Best to be careful.
If you really did that,
there's no way
to retreat unharmed.
How about we just keep waiting.
And she might
meet with some mishap on her own.
Wait?
When will I ever get
this great opportunity again?
So many are trying to kill
Second in the south.
He thought he was
so thorough in self-defense.
But as long as those around him
show
just a slight crevice,
just you watch,
in whose hands he will die!
Even if he doesn't die on the road,
well,
He can come back.
Come back
and he will only see Sheng Minglan's corpse!
Big Madam.
At that time,
Gu Tingye's heart will be completely broken.
Then he can just marry some useless chit.
And she won't be as difficult
to deal with as Sheng Minglan.
Even if
he garners another legitimate heir.
Who can know
when that will be!
This husband who longs for his deceased wife.
A step wife who can never
grasp her husband's heart.
And that can never be
a harmonious family!
At that time,
we just stir up the muddy water for fish.
And that will be much easier than now.
Even if...
Even if Sheng Minglan's
child in her womb . . .
If that child doesn't die,
then he will be stuck with a stepmother.
And that's a great show to watch as well.
At that time, this house.
This family!
This family will be so bustling.
Second's bride.
How is she now?
How's her complexion?
Though the matter is finished,
according to Fengxian,
when she went to pay her respect,
her complexion
wasn't refreshed.
Great.
Fengxian also said
she's not eating much lately.
Great!
Saying she's queasy.
And earlier she was queasy too.
But she ate more than now
so it must be the stress of things.
Great!
More troubles and less eating.
Neither is a sign of longevity.
Ji'an.
I'm old.
But this pair of husband and wife,
they are in their prime.
If I really
just take in my last breath,
I...
I can't be content!
Alright. Alright.
Alright.
Big Miss,
please talk to her.
Big Madam
lost face really harshly.
Get lost!
You just want me to die!
You all get lost!
Mother.
You heartless deadbeat brat!
Where have you been?
Mother.
You...
your mother's about to be forced dead.
And you still didn't come,
you would be cleaning up my bones.
Mother.
Mother, stop crying.
Others will laugh at you,
and you'd lose face.
Face?
What face?
I've married into the Sheng House for decades.
I've endured until today.
And I have you three siblings.
One's an official
and the others are married.
Now I'm all alone in this inner courtyard.
And I get to be wasted by others to their like.
Your aunt's full of big ideas
and I can't persuade her
so what else can I do?
I can't live.
Mother.
Grandmother isn't blaming you
for not being able to persuade aunt.
She blames you
for not recognizing right and wrong, good and bad.
Think.
The way Aunt used to scold
and berate Minglan.
Why should Minglan respect and honor her?
Even you think of her
and don't go to Gu House
to ask for favor.
You didn't want to trouble her
and have her belittled by her husband's family.
But here comes Aunt.
Going there with full fanfare
to put up air and wield authority.
That's the fox exploiting the tiger's might.
Using our Sheng honor
to add superiority for Kang House.
What do you know?
That Ming brat isn't blood-related to me.
She reached high
and isn't obedient anymore.
That Zhao'er
is much more docile than Ming brat.
She will be easy to use later on.
You're muddled.
You speak like a child.
Minglan isn't
a blood relation to you.
But no matter what,
she's a biological sister
to us siblings.
If something happens,
on the account of the Sheng House,
on the account of the old madam,
Minglan would help us.
Kang Zhao'er
can't be closer to us
than Minglan.
Your aunt isn't without fault.
But what do you guys know?
Since your younger brother became an official.
He is just getting busier
and busier and now he's out.
You and Ru'er have
your own families to take care of.
With your father and your grandmother,
I have never been on the same page.
In this grand courtyard,
everyone finds me a pest.
Except for your aunt
who is willing to hear me out.
And she and I can converse easily.
Other than her,
who is willing to pay attention to me?
But it's alright.
In a couple of months,
my Wang House is coming.
My mother.
My older brother. They're all coming.
In this capital city,
I will have a backer too.
Old Sister,
we haven't seen each other in years!
Let's have a family meal together.
Come on.
Come.
Mother-in-law,
big brother-in-law isn't here.
It'll take a few more days.
The matters in hand
must be taken care of thoroughly
before he leaves that job.
You are the best child.
And you've been promoted lately?
It's all thanks to
your high regard of me back then
and your willingness to consent
the marriage that I have today.
He kept saying once you come,
and once my big brother comes,
we have to welcome you well.
What welcome or not?
Seeing all you children,
like I had taken the divine pill.
Come, come.
Everyone's here today.
But I don't see Sixth Miss
with the girl from your home.
There's an extra seat outside
for the children's table.
Isn't her child in her womb?
And it's here too.
Mother.
The fifth girl in my house.
She's gone to the old homestead
with her husband to pay tribute to ancestor today
so she can't make it here.
She said she wants you to
keep some sesame cakes
she loves for her.
Alright, alright.
We'll keep it for her.
I mean the illegitimate daughter
from outside.
Her name is Rong'er or Feng'er, right?
You ought to be good to her
and bring her
to see this kind of sight.
Then people can praise you
as a virtuous main mother.
Mother-in-law,
that child's got a bit of a chill.
So we won't have her come
and risk spreading the illness.
The child is more urgent.
She needs to have a rest.
Yes.
Girls are not like
boisterous boys.
Their bodies are more delicate.
How precious is she?
Who isn't precious?
I think you just . . .
Which family's child isn't precious?
A girl of 9 or 10 years of age
is so delicate.
You don't even understand that?
Hurry and eat.
Taste this.
Come.
Mother-in-law,
allow me to toast to you.
Come.
General of Weibei's manor has someone here.
The servant said Madam Zhang is in difficult labor
and wants to see me.
Dear Buddha.
You are close friend of hers
so you'd better go and see.
This is the lady's trip to hell's gate.
Ming'er.
You have to watch your own body.
Yes.
Come, come. Eat.
Mother-in-law.
My good son-in-law.
This Old Wang Madam.
She's lived far out for years
and she knows
my Rong'er's age.
She also knows
I'm good friends with Sister Zhang.
She's so up to date in news.
Who knows what
that Madam Kang says behind you.
I think you feel
much better now.
Don't rush to tend to those official documents.
Recuperate first.
I told your maternal grandmother already.
After you're done filing this post,
we'll have your maternal uncle
find a post for you outside the capital.
Mother.
Stop asking uncle for favors.
Sister sent me a letter not long ago
saying aunt-in-law's mother-in-law's very strict.
If you go to ask uncle
for favors again,
it will be hard for him.
Forget it.
You don't need to worry about it.
As long as your maternal grandmother is alive,
this Wang House isn't
your aunt-in-law's turn to be in charge.
Mother,
you can't ask for favors forever.
Also,
I will work hard myself
and I can achieve it by myself.
I already made the arrangements
for you.
Father.
I will talk to you mother
so you go first.
Yes.
What a rare guest.
You've dealt with the outside.
And you can actually
think of coming here?
I suppose you saw my mother,
and you found out my brother was coming to the capital too.
And so you're putting some hope in our Wang House?
Everyone in the family
knows that you have sold my daughter.
Except for me!
I found a great future
like Gu House for Zhao'er.
Isn't that for
our Kang House's sake too?
You belittled
Sheng House before,
saying my sister's husband curries favor
and loses the honor of scholars.
Now we're currying favor too.
What a fart!
Brother Sheng just got promoted
to fourth rank.
And a few days later,
he's gone to the grain route.
Do you know what grain route is?
It's a fatty job. An important job!
Now his son-in-law's prestigious
and his son is successful.
The whole house is favored.
How are they willing to
share a cup of stew with others?
And you've thought of sending a daughter
to snatch his daughter's position?
What you did was trying to steal a chicken
only to end up losing the rice.
You didn't get to eat any goat meat
but got yourself covered in goat stench!
Since I've offended them already,
then we can't quit.
Let's finish the matter.
Before this,
we and Gu House
were distant relatives.
And I have to be watchful of my sister
and brother-in-law's moods.
But now,
if Gu House accepts Zhao'er.
Yes.
The reputation won't be so nice
but we got
the real stuff.
So we can have a connection with Gu House
directly in the future.
You thought it was going to succeed?
Zhao'er been sent to Youyang already!
What?
What did you say?
Brother Sheng took me
to the side earlier.
He said
he couldn't bear to watch
my daughter become a concubine.
So they will find
a good match for her in Youyang.
And he said,
not to be so harsh
with Zhao'er real mother anymore.
Saying it should be considered
building up merit with good deeds.
Upon hearing that,
I had no place
to put my face from that shame.
I...
if it hadn't been
your devotion to my father's mourning of three years,
I
I would give you the repudiating papers now.
Repudiate me?
Go ahead and do it now if you dare.
You think I am afraid to repudiate you?
I think you can't spare the assistance
from my Wang House!
You thought I was willing to
live this Kang life?
You keep getting a concubine incessantly.
And if you could spare me
from worrying about your son's future
and the money at home.
I wouldn't make a sound
even if you got yourself a few hundred women.
But you're just a tough mouth outside.
And hallow inside.
Today, I have to beg my brother.
Tomorrow, I have to ask my brother-in-law for help.
I have to fill the coffer deficit
with my dowry.
Kang Haifeng.
You little loser
of a cuckold.
How was I so blind back then
to pick you to marry?
I . . .
If you dare to yak more
I will report you as having gone mad.
And I will nail shut your room and lock you in.
You...
I...
I will never let those guys off.
You just watch.
How is it?
It's not good.
My madam said this.
She can be assured
only if Sheng Madam is here.
So we had to invite you suddenly.
Last time I came,
the doctor said
you still have another ten days or more to go.
How is she suddenly
This morning that whore Little Zou
insisted on
curtsy.
My miss said
she didn't want to see her.
But she said
before the general left for camp patrol,
he told her
she had to come.
So the two sides pulled and pushed
and she knocked into my miss.
Mother Fan, don't fret.
The more
the situation like this,
the more you have to be calm.
Or if we get ourselves fretting in ruckus,
who will your big madam depend on?
Yes.
Is the midwife here? And the doctor?
We found two midwives in a rush.
And we invited the doctor from the imperial palace
who specializes in women care, Doctor Zhao.
Great.
Careful.
Bear it.
How is she?
You
You hold on for me.
Don't call my parents.
They had me at old age
and they are elderly now.
They can't bear it.
But by myself
myself
I can't bear it either.
We need your father
and mother to come.
If they come and see me like this,
they will only be heart-broken.
You...
you...
You're muddled.
Half a life.
You're halfway in the hell's gate
so why do you think of that?
You bear it through for me.
Don't be scared.
Everyone who delivers a baby needs to do this.
I will hold things up for you outside
and you listen to the midwife.
Big Madam,
Big Madam, continue to bear it.
continue to bear it.
It's not lowered yet.
Yes, bear it more.
Is the midwife reliable?
They are all seasoned help for the duchess.
Their maiden home
or children's contracts
are all
in the ducal house.
Where is the Duke of the State?
Duke of the State is at camp patrol.
Hurry up and send someone to invite
both the Duke and the Duchess back.
But our miss
said no.
I said to invite them earlier
and she threw
a huge temper.
It's alright.
After she give birth to the child,
she can vent her anger at me.
You just send someone to go now.
Yes.
I was told the general was at camp patrol.
Is he with the duke?
Is he on official duty
or personal patrol?
General left
from our yard this morning.
He said he was afraid the subordinates
will languish so he had to go and see.
I didn't hear him say it was an official matter
or that he was with the duke of the state.
Since it's not an official matter,
invite the general back too.
On fast horse.
Hurry.
Hurry, hurry.
Go to invite the general.
Tell the doctor to come and talk to me.
Imperial Doctor Zhao
has been detained
by Concubine Zou's men.
What?
Detained?
Earlier the doctor went out to the lavatory
and on the way back,
he ran into Concubine Zou
and she asked him to have her pulse checked.
But who knew that
Concubine Zou's older brother
and wife were there too.
They heard the imperial doctor came from the palace.
So they forced him to go to their room.
Lancao is still waiting there.
Those wretched turds.
Summon the male servant to invite him back.
Yes.
Hurry.
Big Madam has given birth to a few before.
So you have some experience?
I've never been in labor.
But I've seen someone
lose her life in labor.
You all hear me.
You must secure Big Madam Zhang's life.
Big Madam Zhang's suffered a knock into her
and the child has gone horizontal.
I understand.
This matter is very hard?
If the doctor can put in needles,
it may be improved.
I know some doctors
have the special skill.
And they can bring back
a fainted woman in labor
with just a needle of acupuncture.
And some are even more skilled.
With just one needle,
they can secure the position of the fetus.
Good.
I will find the doctor.
Mother Hu,
you ladies take care of her.
If we can pass this,
the duke and the duchess of state,
the entire house of imperial uncle
will be grateful to you.
You ladies focus on the work
without worry of others.
We will surely look after her well.
What? Where's Doctor Zhao?
I went to Concubine Zou's
with two male servants.
We told her we're waiting
to the birth of the baby here
and asked them to bring the doctor out.
But who knew,
that Uncle Zou
slapped me.
He said he's not seen any imperial doctors.
I told Xiaoli and Xiaomu to go in
and find him but they out-numbered and out-powered us.
They kept those two confined
and beat them.
Did you see Imperial Doctor Zhao?
No.
I never even saw him.
I don't know if
he's really left their yard.
He was invited here
to help your big madam
in labor.
If he's left,
he would be coming this way.
You personally saw them
take Doctor Zhao away?
Yes.
I saw it.
Even if I have to testify at Keifeng Precicnt,
I will still say like this.
Does the national law work?
Our miss is a noble lady,
the legitimate main wife.
But she's having to endure
such sinister and filthy wrong?
Big Madam.
Big Madam, just ahead.
Turn right at the next corner and we're there.
just next corner?
Royal Physician Zhao!
Why are you shouting?
What is a woman like you doing?
Royal Physician Zhao has long gone.
Indeed.
After Royal Physician Zhao checked my pulses,
we then sent him away
in a proper manner.
Search the courtyard!
Where do you think you are?!
Stop!
Stop them!
How dare you!
Search!
Get lost!
You dare to search
the general manor?!
You don't want to live anymore,
is that so?!
Don't move!
Sister-in-law...
Royal Physician Zhao!
Stop him!
Where's Royal Physician Zhao?
Big Madam,
they brought Royal Physician Zhao
to the back courtyard to drink tea.
When I arrived,
royal physician is so anxious.
Is Big Madam in labor?
Yes.
Royal Physician,
let's not waste time. Walk and talk.
Okay. Okay.
Who do you think you are?
You dare to drag people
from my sister's courtyard?
I'm gravely ill
and you dare to drag away the doctor?
Do you want to kill me?
You...are you alright?
I've seen this trick
when I was still a child,
but I'm not a child anymore!
How come Big Madam Zhang
isn't making any sound?
This is a job that requires a lot of strength.
If you put all your strength in shouting,
you won't have any energy
to give birth to the child later.
Who do you think your family is?!
Big Madam, you know so much.
Tell me. Tell me.
Yes. Yes.
Calm down first.
My daughter has such a hard fate.
I got this daughter
when I was already quite old.
She's a blessing from the deities above.
How may people laughed at me
for being an old clam bearing a pearl?
I wasn't afraid of their laughs.
I just want this daughter.
You think my daughter
was stuffed into your house?
can't be married off,
that she must make a connection with your family, is that it?
Later, she might be escalating her lecture
to Her Highness Empress.
Let's bring these tea and fruits
to deliver to Duchess of State
to interrupt them
and save General Shen.
Duchess and General, are you hungry?
Forgive me for being rude.
It's about to be midnight soon.
I asked someone to prepare me some fruits.
Taste them.
Fill your stomach with these first.
It will take a long time to deliver a child.
Good child.
What Duchess?
Just call me auntie.
You even are pregnant,
yet you did all of that for my daughter.
Child,
I'll remember you.
My daughter really has a hard life.
She's now even struggling
at the palace of the God of Hell.
I really don't know
what sin have I committed!
You... I...
If anything bad
happens to my daughter, you...
Auntie. Auntie.
Calm down a little.
Calm down.
Sister is now inside giving a birth.
This house is depending on you.
You mustn't be panic.
Oh, no! Oh, no,
Madam! Miss...
Miss is...
Miss is dying...
My daughter!
What's going on?
How is that possible?
Daughter! Daughter!
Mother!
Here! Here!
Mother is here!
Monther.
Child, hold on.
Your father will be here soon.
Endure it, my child!
More strength, more strength.
More strength.
A little bit more strength.
My child...
Push!
Look! She's hemorrhaging!
Hurry. Hurry.
General, get more cloth!
Father! Mother!
I'm doing my filial duties one last time!
My wife!
She's given birth! She's given birth!
The child is out!
Kick Little Lady Zhou out of your house.
She...
She committed a grave mistake.
I surely will cruelly punish her.
But I beg father-in-law...
I really can't do it for her older sister's sake.
Pitying one's servant
because of considering past affection.
Also giving out one's wealth because of a dream.
Remembering one's wife shows
how deep your love and loyalty is.
I'm a man, so I understand.
Since that's the case,
State Uncle, just write us a separation letter.
Our two houses will divide
and just strive for each future separately.
You...
What are you saying?
I've told you that
my daughter didn't beg you
to marry her.
It's also not as if she can't be married off that
we must stuff her into your house.
It's good that you didn't forget
your past wife.
But keeping a snake in your house who will create future trouble
is deliberately wanting
the life of my daughter.
Today, she's able to preserve half of her life.
That is because she had the good fate
of meeting Marquess Gu.
If not,
the one we're seeing now
is her corpse.
State Uncle,
let our families just depart in an amicable manner.
After you write a separation letter,
we'll still be able to act in a civil manner
when we see each other here in the capital.
Or else, if we shed all pretenses
in front of the emperor,
we all be awkward.
No.
I won't separate.
No...
You won't amicably separate?
Are you still planning to divorce her?!
No! No!
I'm not divorcing her.
From now on,
I surely will treat her well
and carefully cherish her.
I won't let anything bad
happen to her again.
Enough!
Saying all these now
is worth nothing anymore.
Nanny Fan!
Here!
Has the carriage been prepared?
Replying to Madam,
we're done customizing the carriage.
We've placed a thick layer of bedding inside.
We've also painted cow oil inside,
ensuring that no wind will get in.
Miss will surely
not suffer any cold.
Let's go.
Father-in-law!
Mother-in-law!
Good child,
thank you for today.
It's a bit chaotic right now.
We'll surely visit the marquis manor next time
to thank you for doing your best to help us.
You're welcome.
As long as sister will recuperate well,
no need to put
anything else to heart.
Father-in-law, let's discuss this further.
Don't let my wife get exposed to the cold wind.
The child hasn't been born that long yet.
Every step you stop me,
I would be walking a step slower.
Every time I slow down my step,
Fen'er will then suffer a step more of jolting
and pain.
If you still have a conscience,
then get lost.
Father-in-law!
Wife!
Since flooding has subsided
in the western main camp,
the personnel and horses there
should have been settled down by now.
A few days ago, subject Shen went to check on them.
Subject Shen.
Informing Your Majesty,
General Shen is absent today.
Duke Ying of the State went to the east
to organize the troops there.
What about the situation in the east?
Duke Ying of the State sent there letter
to ask for a leave of absence
to the Ministry of Personnel last night.
He's also absent today.
What's going on?
Your Majesty,
Duke Ying of the State
has been organizing the troops
in the eastern military camp for the past days.
Last night, he suddenly rushed back
with his horse into the capital
and went to General Shen's house.
Not long after he returned home,
he suddenly fainted.
They had to ask for a doctor overnight
and he was eventually saved.
The doctor said that
it was because of getting exhausted
for several days and then hearing bad news,
hence, his blood didn't circulate properly
and harmed his insides.
What bad news?
General Shen's wife had a difficult labor
and almost died,
before she was able to give birth to a son.
Old Duke of the State fetched
his daughter and grandson
back to their home to be cared for.
He said...
What did he say?
He said that he wants an amicable separation
with the Shen Family.