The Story of Minglan
Episode 67
That's Cheng Garden's direction.
It's not certain.
It's too dark out
and it's hard to see.
Lichong. Lichong!
Call all the male runners of the manor
and bring the fire extinguishing equipment.
All come with me.
Yes.
What are you going to do?
I will go to take a look.
Wife,
I must go and see it.
It's not even certain it is Cheng Garden.
Even if it is,
it's the marquis manor.
They will have their own fire rescuers.
Why is he still not here?
This is the inner courtyard.
He can't come in with runners.
That's right. You're right.
So I'll take a look outside.
Husband. Husband!
Push. Push.
I can see the baby's head.
What's wrong outside?
Nothing. It's nothing.
It's fine, Big Madam.
I see the baby's head.
Breathe and push hard.
Lichong! Lichong!
Yuanruo.
Come, give me a bucket.
Yuanruo!
Where are you going
all in a fret?
Mother.
Cheng Garden's on fire.
I am going to help rescue.
You saw it,
the Fire House would have seen it too.
The fire rescue team will go there
so what can you do if you go there?
But it's already burning!
Don't forget your status
and position.
You are already married.
Running to the marquis manor in the dark.
What propriety!
Mother.
Am I supposed to watch our relative
burned to death and not help?
Relative?
You deem them your relative?
We were a relative of Gu House.
Heng'er,
don't go.
Your wife might get scared seeing the fire,
so you stay with her.
You guys go. Go.
Father.
She's very safe at home.
Why would she need company?
I'm going.
Father.
Let me just go to see that
if she's fine and I'll be right back.
Can you block the mouths of the world?
Father!
When I needed to speak clearly
and directly to her,
I did not.
When I needed to wager all for her,
I also didn't.
She suffered so much gossip
and chilling words by my account.
Can't I
just go rescue her once?
She has her husband and you have your wife.
You go and it will just incite more tongue-wagging.
If that Gu Marquis were here,
I wouldn't need to go.
But she's pregnant
and her manor is on fire.
Mother.
we at least were once acquaintances.
And you've given her a bracelet
and told her to be my sister.
Mother,
even if it's just a total stranger,
would you bear to see them die
without helping?
Yuanruo.
Go!
Yuanruo!
Fire!
Help rescue fire.
Work harder.
Come.
The fire's getting bigger.
Hurry, hurry.
Harder.
Hurry and rescue the fire.
Hurry, hurry.
Push hard, Big Madam.
It's out. Out!
Big Madam.
It's out!
Oh, it's a boy.
A big fat boy.
Slowly.
Let me see him.
Bring him for her to see.
Here.
Here, Big Madam.
The baby is too cute!
Alright.
Fat boy.
Everyone will get a reward.
Thank you, Big Madam, for the reward.
You all contributed!
Go die!
Come!
Move!
You shrewd!
You, you!
Move! Who dares to come!
Pull her away.
Move!
Master.
Minglan.
You're back.
I'm back.
You're back!
They said . . .
they said you were injured.
I . . .
I thought you died.
My heart shattered.
I'm back.
Everything's fine now that you're back.
Look.
Child.
Is it a boy or a girl?
What a big fire!
I don't know
how my sixth sister is doing.
She's pregnant too.
How is it?
Reporting to Big Madam.
Words on the street say
Marchioness delivered a boy safely
and Marquis is back.
What? Delivered a boy?
Yes.
They say her due date was around now.
What a coincidence that the madam of Gu House
delivered today in the big fire.
And Gu Marquis even saved her
amid the big fire.
The words are spreading all over the streets.
That Gu Marquis came back just in time.
It's burned like this
and she can still give birth?
Look at Dad.
Look, how much he looks like me.
I birthed him. He looks like me.
He looks like me.
He looks exactly like me.
In the future,
he will surely become a leader!
I already thought it through.
If this child likes martial arts in the future,
I can invite
as many martial masters for him as available.
If he wants to master in scholarship,
I plan to hand him
to your Second Brother.
My brother-in-law.
What?
You're going to hand him
to my Second Brother, Changbai?
You . . .
You . . . why would you?
How can you be so cruel-hearted?
This?
Why couldn't I?
My Second Brother's temperament.
It's not like you don't know him.
We can't bear to be hard on him
so we let another be hard on him.
Right?
When he's grown,
he'll surely hate you for some time.
He won't, right?
When did you get back?
I saw our house on fire
from the street .
So I rushed to come back on horse.
Yes.
The house was on fire.
I should have came back sooner.
How did Maternal Aunt Kang come in?
Someone must have used the chaos as an opportunity.
Rong girl. Where's Rong?
Rong is fine.
Xian girl is such a good child.
She saw the fire
and she disregarded her mother stopping her,
and sent all the hands
to come and help rescue the fire.
Now,
Rong girl is sitting well in her room.
Don't worry now.
They said
you met an assassin.
I was so scared.
Your darling Second is so brave and mighty.
A few assassins
have already been sent off by me.
So don't worry.
You just bore the child
so you should sleep well.
You don't go again.
I won't go.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll stay with you guys.
Hurry. Get water.
Fire. Fire.
Here.
Here, come.
Fire. Hurry.
Fire. Hurry and come.
Don't rush.
Oh my world.
Tingwei? Third Young Master!
Tingwei?
Slow down. Don't rush.
Third!
Tingwei!
Third Young Master!
Are you alright?
Third Young Master.
He's fine, right?
Thanks to Buddha.
Child, hurry and get up.
This might collapse and shatter on you.
I'll move out and set my own house.
Third Young Master!
What nonsense is this?
Big Madam.
Third Young Master's place
will need to be renovated.
Maybe he should go
and stay in Eldest Young Master's old place.
When I move out,
if you miss me, mother,
you can come to visit me.
If you don't want to,
never mind then!
Where are you going?
You, if you move out,
you won't come back?
I don't think I can live here any longer.
Third Young Master.
After I move out,
you and Second Brother can
fight if you want and quarrel if you want.
I have no say in it anyway!
And I don't care anymore!
Third Young Master.
I raised that child so diligently. Why is he . . .
Slower, Grand Madam.
Tingwei!
Third Young Master!
Mother-in-law, you really don't know
how our fire started?
I heard from Second House's report,
that the wind was strong and it started from a flicker
that flew over from the yard next door.
Next door?
I bet that flicker is very tall
and named Shitou.
What?
Gu Tingye! How dare you!
Mother-in-law.
I really don't know
if you are really devoted to my husband or not
To say it's fake,
yet you scheme for him with so much devotion.
To say it's true,
you've never cared what he wants
and what he needs.
Whatever he doesn't want,
such as the nobility title,
you must shove it into his mouth
to make him swallow.
Whatever he wants,
such as harmony with his siblings.
You just will never let him have
an ounce or second of it.
You spineless lot
with no aspiration!
I schemed for you all my life for nothing!
He's not a dog!
For you to raise him
however your like!
Miss. Miss.
Gu Tingye!
Miss.
Let's not be mad.
Alright.
Where's my child?
My child! Where is he?
Where's my child!
Tell Second Tu and Liu Jingli
to each guard one of the two inner doors.
The rest.
Child!
Child! Child!
Big Madam, your child's here.
He's here.
What's wrong?
Wife.
I had a dream.
I dreamed a huge fog.
I couldn't find our child.
He's here, wife.
Our child and I are both by your side.
Don't be scared.
Your husband is here to protect you.
No ghosts or monsters can come to you.
I couldn't see.
Xiaotao.
Go light a calming incense.
Go.
I won't sleep.
I can't sleep.
I have to watch him.
Don't be scared.
Your husband is here.
I'll hold the sword
and watch over you two all night.
You sleep without worrying.
His Majesty isn't unreasonable
to force Gu Marquis to leave his house at this moment.
It's just that he's so anxious
to hear about the salt matter from the marquis.
Sir.
The fire in the house
was only just extinguished.
The palace's imperial fire rescue
will be here
to allow Gu Marquis to go at ease.
May you deliver the words for me once again.
Sir.
It's not that I'm putting up air
to slight you,
but it's just that the madam's scared
and she can't sleep.
I can't sleep.
Our marquis can't leave her side.
Tomorrow morning he will go to the palace
to beg His Majesty's forgiveness.
Your marquis is intending to defy the imperial edict?
Sir,
my marquis has already wagered his life
for His Majesty and Prince Huan nine times.
Now that his wife had to labor in fire,
couldn't we be generous
and allow him to spend a night at home?
Prince Huan is back too
and if His Majesty wants to hear about the salt matter,
he could summon Prince Huan.
You!
Go safely, Sir.
Your Majesty, it's time to rest.
Why isn't there any news still?
How is it? Where's Gu Marquis?
It was Cheng Garden of Gu Marquis that was on fire.
Where's Gu Marquis?
His servant said Marchioness,
Marquis' Wife，Madam Sheng,
was in labor.
She was traumatized
and thankfully Gu Marquis returned in time.
And now he's easing Madam Sheng
and watching the child.
I asked you.
Where's Gu Marquis?
Your Majesty.
I didn't even get to enter
the gate of Cheng Garden.
I didn't see Gu Marquis.
Child.
As soon as you came into the world,
you already met an evil robber!
Great.
This is a training for you
coming into the world.
Though it's warm inside the room,
it's windy and chilly outside.
It's great too.
This is the true image of the world.
We will all be by your side.
Your mother. Your father. Your older sister.
And your old brother who's gone.
We will all be by your side.
Good child.
This is the first day
you have come to the world.
The sky will become bright.
Gu Marquis isn't the same as before anymore.
I am an emperor waiting for him
to report to me about salt matters
and I'm still waiting!
Great for him though.
Clearly aware that I'm waiting for him.
He didn't come to the palace
and he didn't return the military seal.
He went home instead
to see his wife and child!
Your Majesty.
Gu Marquis had his home on fire.
He is worried about the disaster and it's understandable.
On the account of his past contributions,
please be forgiving.
Don't I pay heed to his contributions?
I sent him
the imperial fire rescue team,
to put them under his complete disposal.
No one else in the royal court
has that kind of honor.
How much more should I be kind to him?
Gift him the empire?
Your Majesty,
what do you mean by saying that?
Gu Marquis is a bit arrogant and unrestrained.
But be it the imperial jade seal
or the issues with my siblings,
or the salt patrol over the six provinces,
which matter does he fail
to succeed in full details?
In the future, we still need to count on him.
A few days ago,
we closed off the market in the frontier.
So they have to go the black market salt route.
And now, I've tightened on salt iron.
So they can't even find black market salt.
Their young chief
is a youngster who rose
with the support of his maternal uncle.
He's in a rush to start a war
with us to mark his authority.
He's pressing us
to open the market and give up land.
Our time is ticking.
We'll take it easy on Gu Tingye for now.
Once he's pacified
this big matter for us,
I'll deal with him then.
Your Majesty's health
is really unwell lately.
Headaches daily.
Imperial Physicians' Court came to look
but found nothing.
I think
since you were fine in Yuzhou,
and now that we came to Bianjing,
with so much work and worry,
it's rest that you need.
Your imperial health is more urgent.
You just watch me with headache
and illness day after day.
But who knows
what's really in your mind!
Your son is the eldest
in the palace.
Are you hoping direly
that I can go away a day sooner,
so your son can ascend a day sooner,
so he can have Gu Tingye
assist him a day sooner!
May Your Majesty be sage.
Your Majesty.
I am only devoted to you.
Ceying, that child,
also regards you as a God.
If Your Majesty suspects me ,
I can only use death to prove myself.
My health is just fine.
While we are not in war with the border yet,
I will knock down that obstacle
that is Empress Dowager first.
Or else my aspirations cannot be achieved.
And the borders can't be returned to us.
I won't have any face
to see my ancestors below.
Your Majesty.
Empress Dowager is well established and vigorous.
Your Majesty,
Noble Consort Liu is outside begging to see you.
She says she made some new snacks
for Your Majesty to try.
Let her in.
I didn't know
Empress was here too.
I think I made too few of the snacks.
It's alright.
Empress is going back soon.
I bid you well in leaving, Empress.
Yes.
I take my leave.
Your Majesty!
Why are you so mad?
Who got you angered?
Hurry now.
Send in the snacks
for Your Majesty to try.
Under the skies,
is there an older brother like you?
A prominent minister of the court.
The emperor's esteemed subject.
You! You!
You sent your men
to your younger brother's yard,
to kill and set fire.
I . . .
I have to go to the emperor to report you.
I will go to His Majesty to report you.
Did that happen?
I never even heard of it.
I only know that
the fire in our yard was flown over from next door.
You . . .
That happened?
Yes.
I heard someone lit up sky light and it dropped.
The air is dry in the winter.
Better be careful of candles.
Yes.
I shall always be prudent.
You guys think you can just deny
and it'll be fine?
Let me tell you!
Someone from my yard saw it.
Your bride, Sheng woman.
Her maternal aunt, Madam Kang.
She came to your yard.
Summon her for me.
Summon her. I will talk to her face to face.
We compare our stories and the truth will be exposed!
She can't come.
It's so late.
What is it?
You're keeping the guest for dinner?
Enough!
Stop this act
of yours.
This Madam Kang?
She was staying just fine
locked up at Sheng House, ready for prison.
Why did she run into my yard?
You can tell me clearly on that.
Since everyone's well aware,
you still prepared your lines
to put up a show here?
Why don't you get yourself over
at South Tune House to sing your opera?
I'll tell you the truth.
The one from the House of Kang?
I already slashed her to death.
You killed her?
She wanted to kill my wife and child.
You repay a loan with money and repay a life with a life
Grand Madam.
What you're scheming about
I know very clearly,
but you guys don't know what I'm scheming.
Let me tell you.
In the future,
if anyone tries to harm our Cheng Garden,
what happened to the Wang surname is their ending!
She's a noble wife of an official.
You killed her?
Find two people to go
and carry her corpse out.
Grand Madam,
you think about a response to the House of Wang.
Grand Madam.
What are we supposed to tell the House of Wang,
Grand Madam?
Grand Madam.
So what if he's a marquis?
My Wang House isn't a nobody either.
I would rather just beat
that bastard to death now.
Lord Wang. Lord Wang,
let us hand it over for indictment.
He's heavily favored
by the emperor right now.
We bind ourselves together
and we're still no match to him.
He almost burned my son to death, too.
Then let him beat me to death
in your house!
Stop there!
Mother.
Don't go. Watch your health.
Flesh that dropped from my body,
alive or dead,
I must see it myself.
Mother. Mother.
Mother.
Preserve your health, mother.
Old Madam, may your grief be consoled.
That Gu Tingye
is a devil like none other.
He almost killed my son, too.
These two cases of human lives.
What do you plan to do, Elder?
Me and our Gu House. We concede to you on all.
My house owes you for this kindness.
It's such late hour of the night.
My house has met with a matter of funeral
and we are not apt to keep you.
Eldest,
Mother, you walk her out for me.
Mother! This!
Old Madam.
Can it be that you're scared?
You…
I heard my daughter disturbed you
at the marquis manor for many days.
You've suffered exhaustion.
You should rest now.
Send our guest out.
So you're scared!
Old Madam Wang!
You're Old Madam Wang!
Your house is the House of Imperial Tutor Wang
who was granted to the Imperial Shrine!
The flesh that dropped from you died,
and you can't even care?
Grand Madam, this way.
Old Madam.
You have lots of children,
but I only have Tingwei.
You're scared of Gu Tingye's power
and you don't dare to report him.
I am not scared!
Trouble that courts disaster!
If that the House of Wang doesn't fare,
we will be quite low on power.
Ji'an,
have Fourth and Fifth House come to my hall.
Yes.
Go.
I told you many times.
Go rescue your younger sister.
Be it to snatch or rob her
when she's conveyed to the interior prison,
hijack her.
But look at how great you are.
Scared of wolf and tiger.
Today you say the plan isn't thorough enough
and tomorrow you say the guards are too tight.
Great now. She's dead.
You two got your wish.
You don't need to risk anymore.
Mother's words
leave no survival path
for us.
All these years, what was her conduct?
You should know that.
Our Wang House. That Sheng House.
And even the Sheng House in Youyang.
For this evil woman,
how many rotten cases did we all clean up?
How many lives were carried out of
her Kang House?
Dead from child labor.
Dead from beaten after breaking teacup.
The ones tossed out in hemp bags.
And this time as soon as we came back,
she used us to almost kill
the Old Madam Sheng.
Mother.
She was set out to ruin us all.
Now she's dead
and it's a relief to the whole family.
You are also a mother.
One rotten fruit that isn't picked out
will rot the entire basket.
Mother.
Your sister isn't a fruit.
She's your blood kin
from the same womb as you.
Mother!
Get out.
You are a thing
that only divides sibling love.
Enough.
You say nothing more.
Come.
Alright.
You go and have a rest first.
I'll discuss everything with mother.
Hurry. Escort the madam.
He really killed her?
I escorted the coffin back personally.
My Tingbing got exiled
a thousand miles away by him.
What else is impossible?
Of course he'll kill or harm
whoever he wants now.
The old madam from the House of Wang
asked me to give her an answer.
I am a widow.
What justification can I give to anyone?
He dares to kill the noble wife of an official.
He dares to kill his own brother.
Tomorrow, who knows whom he will kill?
It's always been the case
that the Madam Kang
would wrong someone.
No one's ever seen
anyone wrong her.
I actually don't believe
what you're saying.
If you want to investigate,
go ahead.
But I'm going to be upfront with my words.
Our house was snubbed
for years.
Finally we're getting some rising colors.
If this big tree falls,
and we lose our protection,
then in the future,
how will we live our lives?
That is something I'm not clear on.
He's cleaned up your house,
so of course you'd regard him
as your savior.
My house never had his protection.
Our Tingbing is exiled for ten years!
That's not how you say this though.
It was Tingbing
who rushed to write his name
on the Rebel Prince's roster.
And he even crossed out
our kid's name.
Shut up.
Womankind.
You all fled
and shoved it all on him.
Now you say he was snatching your merit?
Sister-in-law.
If you say that,
it's as though Tingbing
deserved to be
exiled by Second.
I was reckless.
Sister-in-law.
Please forgive me.
My sister ran out
by herself.
She should have come back right away.
So we could protect her.
She ran over to Gu House.
Then it's sending herself
into the net.
Your sister was heart-broken.
She was heart-broken that her brother, you,
and I, her mother,
couldn't protect her.
So she preferred to go to the enemy's territory
rather than returning home.
When she left, how despaired she must have felt.
This Madam Qin.
If she were truly good to your sister,
the first day she went to the marquis manor,
this madam should have
sent words to us.
Why did she hide it all along?
She waited until she is dead
to send the coffin over,
Saying it was Gu Tingye that killed her.
When he killed her, where was she?
Her marquis manor
is just an arrow away from Cheng Garden.
Just one wall apart
and she said she saw nothing.
You believe her?
She wanted to use my sister
as a weapon?
We can't
count on any of them, I fear.
Miss.
Did you see?
That Gu Tingye.
He is daring enough to burn Tingwei's yard.
Big Madam, don't be scared now.
He really wasn't trying
to kill our Third Young Master.
He just wanted you
to be busy rescuing him,
so you can't go and scheme against him anymore.
He's killed a noble lady of an official now
and he's ripped his face altogether.
If I don't eat up
this Gu Tingye,
then once the House of Wang gets a grip,
and they find out how many things I instigated in between,
they will eat me up instead.
It's not so bad if they ate me.
But what about my . . .
That foolish child of mine.
What will he do in the future?
I understand it all.
Since this is the path we're on,
there's only one of us to survive.
Go.
Go summon the House of Bai
from Yangzhou.