Chu Beichi joined the army at a young age.
He fought bravely and shed blood on the northern frontier.
He quelled the civil unrest in the neighboring country, Beilie.
He helped the empress regain her throne.
He aided Jiuniang, the widow of a northern border soldier.
He established a powerful intelligence organization.
He promoted the most outstanding female general, Shen Feixue.
He saved the people of Datian many times.
He also won the admiration of the princess of Tianguo.
But just as he was hailed as the soul of the Datian army,
and the Divine General of Kunlun,
he suddenly retired from public life.
Since then, there has been no news of him.
The land is still unsettled.
I cannot die yet.
Kunlun Divine General
Wake up
Please wake up
It's her
Young Master Chu
It's been three years
I've never been able to wake you
I was born with medicinal bones
Now, there's only one way left
To harmonize the forces of heaven and man
Regulate the balance of yin and yang
No, you mustn't
Don't make any more sacrifices for me
You've finally awakened
I'll announce it to the world at once
My honored teacher has awakened
Head to Binzhou immediately
Your Majesty, please reconsider
Your Majesty, think carefully
Chu Beichi is my mentor
Without him, there would be no Empress of Beilie
The young master has awakened
Assemble all the shadow guards at once
Prepare to welcome the young master's return
If anything happens to the young master
We will all be guilty of a capital crime
Commander Chu has finally awakened
Guards
Mobilize the elite Black Armor troops
Come with me to Binzhou
To welcome the Kunlun Divine General
Yes
Once the Kunlun Divine General awakens
The world will be unified
All nations will bow down
At that time
What will become of the people
Will depend on his will alone
The remaining toxins in your body have been cleared.
You could wake up at any moment.
Once you wake up,
the Chu family estate will become the most powerful in the land.
It will be revered by countless people.
For these past three years,
everyone has kept their promises.
No one has disturbed your recovery.
Throughout the entire Chu estate,
no one knows your true identity.
It's time to wake up.
All the kindness everyone has shown me,
I remember it all.
The life-saving grace of Doctor Jiang,
and the companionship,
I will also
Three years ago, the Blood Bandits slaughtered several cities in a row.
Corpses were strewn for miles.
Chu Beichi fought with his life on the line.
He saved the three great families from annihilation.
That's why they have supported him financially until now.
Over these years,
just the interest from lending out that money
has already made us a fortune.
Now, our Chu family
is as wealthy as a nation.
I only hope my son Feng Yu returns soon
to help with the family affairs.
In the future,
he can inherit the family business sooner.
It's just that
I'm a bit worried.
That useless person lying in the backyard—
all this money
ultimately came because of him.
If he wakes up,
Are you saying
he will
compete with Feng Yu for this vast family fortune?
Madam
Has something happened at your residence?
What happened?
This good-for-nothing has been freeloading at the Chu family for so long.
How much silver have we wasted on him?
This is their true nature.
You two
can just die together.
The Chu family is this cold-blooded.
Then don't blame me.
Something has happened to Commander Chu.
I must hurry.
Quickly!
Whoever dares harm my mentor
I will have them skinned and their bones crushed.
A fate worse than death.
Greetings, Pavilion Master.
Head to the Chu residence at full speed.
If anyone disrespects the young master,
kill them.
As you command.
It's already dawn.
I thought something might happen if I waited.
Kill them.
If you insist on doing this,
you will definitely regret it in the future.
I want to see
if he really has the ability.
What I regret most now
is not being ruthless enough in collecting money back then.
Letting this good-for-nothing
survive until today.
A young lady
with no status or title,
protecting a man like this,
aren't you ashamed?
Sister
How about
you just give in to me?
Alright.
Get away.
Come here, little beauty.
Don't touch me!
Right in front of this useless guy,
I'll have you.
Let me go!
Follow me and you'll live the good life.
Let go of me!
Come on, little beauty.
Just give in to me.
Looking for trouble?
Finish him off!
Little beauty.
Kill him now!
Stop!
He's from Kunlun!
Doctor Jiang
You’re finally awake.
I have devoted myself to treating you for the past three years.
I have never slacked off, not even a little.
I know.
Does it hurt?
Young Master Chu, it’s all my fault for being ignorant.
I failed to see that over these three years,
they were actually harboring ill intentions.
Doctor Jiang worked tirelessly
to take care of me for three whole years.
How dare you treat her like this!
You’re asking for death!
The ancestral teachings of the Chu family
state that the descendants of the Chu clan
must acquire wealth with integrity,
never forget kindness,
help others as a virtue,
and govern with honesty.
Now you have betrayed trust and righteousness.
You are unworthy to be called members of the Chu family.
Yes.
And no.
Yes, yes.
What happened in the residence?
Oh, ancestors of the Chu family!
Master.
We put in so much effort,
serving this unfilial son for three years.
Now that he’s awake,
this is how he repays us.
Not only did he hit me,
he also talked back to his uncle.
He even damaged the ancestral hall.
He’s completely heartless.
Brother-in-law.
This is your father.
Father.
Beichi.
What on earth are you doing?
You were in a coma for three years.
Have you gone mad right after waking up?
All these years,
I thought you truly cared about me.
But now it seems
it was all just an act.
Now, just for a bit of inheritance, your true colors are showing.
Don’t forget,
the Chu family’s honor today
is thanks to whom.
You’re talking nonsense.
Everything the Chu family has today
is all due to the master’s hard work.
Feng Yu made great contributions as the town’s guardian.
And who do you think you are?
I chose to stay in the Chu family
because I didn’t want outsiders to covet the Chu family.
But now it seems
the ones I should have guarded against weren’t outsiders
but my own family.
Ancestors, oh ancestors!
Master!
Someone, come quickly!
There's a fire, someone help!
Master!
It's on fire, hurry!
This...
Who sits here? You sit here.
Master!
This way.
Beichi!
Doctor Jiang.
It's time to go.
Though the ancestral hall still stands,
the family traditions are gone.
If our ancestors' spirits remain,
they would be ashamed to be here.
Rather than endure shame and humiliation,
it would be better to destroy it all.
General Zhenyuan has arrived!
Now that the world is at peace,
if I continue to guard the northern border,
I will surely arouse suspicion from all sides.
Feixue.
Soon, my younger brother Chu Fengyu will come to the north for training.
I entrust him to your care.
Once he earns military merit,
and achieves something great,
I will naturally pass on the Kunlun Divine Spear to him.
And he
will be the next Kunlun Divine General.
Feixue accepts the order.
He's awake.
Fengyu.
Paralyzed for three years and still not dead.
You useless fool.
Though you're worthless,
your life is surprisingly tough.