Brothers!
The court is corrupt, and the country has no good ministers.
Today, we, the Divine Generals of Kunlun, will seek justice for the loyal souls of the northern frontier.
Rise up with me!
Destroy Datian!
Kill!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, something terrible has happened!
The Divine Generals of Kunlun have raised an army in rebellion!
How is this possible?
I would not dare to lie.
The rebels are wearing the armor of the Black Armored Army.
They carry the battle flags of the Northern Army.
They are shouting,
"Seeking justice for the soldiers of the Northern Army!"
They also say
they will cut off the tyrant's head
to appease the wronged souls.
The Black Armored Army has rebelled!
Run!
Your Majesty,
it must be because my son was killed.
Someone has made a big deal out of this.
The news has even reached the Xuanjia Army.
Otherwise,
the Xuanjia Army wouldn't act like this for no reason.
So, in that case,
Chu Beichi is the main culprit who incited the rebellion.
The princess is also not blameless.
Even if the court mishandled things,
it could have been resolved privately.
To preserve the royal family's dignity.
But the princess made this matter known to the whole world.
Exactly.
At a time like this,
why are we still talking about this?
The Kunlun Divine General has rebelled.
What should we do now?
Please rest assured, Your Majesty.
I believe
the Kunlun Divine General has advanced alone this time.
Although his momentum is great,
he cannot last long.
Please issue an imperial decree, Your Majesty,
to gather troops from all directions.
I am willing to lead the army to eliminate the northern rebels.
To ensure Da Tian remains safe.
Are you suggesting we declare war on all the Xuanjia Army?
Your Majesty,
this is an act to suppress the rebellion.
The Xuanjia Army is the most prestigious elite force in the north.
If they rebel,
the northern army will surely follow suit.
In my opinion,
we should strike first to gain the upper hand.
If you send the royal army to the border,
it’s no different from forcing the northern soldiers to their doom.
Such internal strife
is undoubtedly destroying the nation and toppling the dynasty.
Your Highness,
do you intend to cut off Da Tian’s fate?
Nonsense.
Did you really think you were the Divine General of Kunlun?
If all these years I’ve only survived under your protection,
then I’d rather die.
Your Majesty,
I am willing to follow Prince Qi to lead the troops and repel the enemy.
I beg Your Majesty to first execute Chu Beichi.
I will take his head and present it to the Divine General.
With my relationship with the Divine General,
he will surely withdraw his troops.
and keep Da Tian safe.
If I die,
this world
will fall into chaos.
Even facing death, you still boast shamelessly.
Do you realize the crimes you’ve committed
are unforgivable, even if you die a hundred or a thousand times?
Please, Your Majesty, issue the decree quickly.
Let your younger brother command the troops.
You will surely be safe in the city.
What are you standing there for?
Hurry and hand over the tiger tally to His Majesty.
Father, you mustn’t!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Chu Beichi, let go of His Majesty!
Beichi!
Nobody move!
The one who wants to kill the king and seize power
is probably someone else.
You—
Your Majesty!
I’ll have to trouble you for now.
Si Yan.
Chu Beichi
Are you trying to seize power and rebel?
Guards!
Here!
Nobody move!
The Emperor is here.
I want to see who dares to act rashly.
All of you, stand down!
Why aren't you clearing the way?
Move aside!
Go.
Chu Beichi
Your actions today
will surely lead you to ruin.
The Princess and Chu Beichi
have taken His Majesty hostage.
Take men and pursue them at once!
Kill everyone involved without mercy!
Yes!
But what about the rebels outside the city?
Rescue His Majesty first.
Yes!
Let's go.
You've saved me again.
Divine General of Kunlun
Tell me your plan.
If my guess is correct,
the fake Divine General outside the city must have been arranged by Prince Qi.
His goal is to have Your Majesty killed in Binzhou City.
And then blame the Xuanjia Army.
So,
Prince Qi used fake Xuanjia soldiers to confuse everyone.
He wants to force the Emperor to hand over military power.
But
all of this was actually part of Beichi's plan.
That's right.
But he doesn't know the real Divine General is right here.
And has even become my son-in-law.
Divine General,
what exactly are you doing?
Let alone killing just a mere crown prince,
even if you wanted my life,
I would still...
Your Majesty,
since you trust me so much,
how could I just stand by and do nothing?
Besides,
I do this for the people of the world.
Your Majesty, please
act with me when the time is right.
Back then, when you were unconscious,
I thought you would be safer with the Chu family.
But I never expected that this whole family
would be a bunch of fools.
If it weren't for your status as the Divine General,
the Chu family would no longer exist today.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Princess.
Young Master.
You have returned.
The families of the soldiers have been settled.
Good.
If anything goes wrong, that would truly be chaos.
What about the rebel forces outside the city?
The people of Binzhou are all living in fear.
The rebels impersonating the Xuanjia Army have already camped outside the city.
They don't seem to be preparing to attack the city.
They just keep shouting something.
Hand over the dog emperor!
What is King Qi's current move?
King Qi insists that the northern border is rebelling.
If the truth is not made public soon,
I'm afraid it will cause a civil war in Datian.
The Xuanjia Army has sworn to protect the nation.
How could they possibly rebel?
Now everyone outside says His Majesty has grown senile, that's why—
Liuli.
Your Majesty.
I misspoke just now.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
It's all right, you may rise.
I...
Liuli is right.
I am getting old.
Sometimes I can't help but get confused.
But I have no son to succeed me.
To keep the nation stable,
I can only rely on others.
But it has been hard on Siyen.
Divine General.
May I have a word with you in private?