=The Song Inquisitor=
=Episode 10=
Li Shaoren switched out
the murder weapon.
If the scandal was exposed,
he must die
for your sake.
Correct.
I pretended to fall in love
with Li Shaoren
so I could make him do my bidding.
I never actually loved him.
It was only wishful thinking
of this lovesick fool.
I don't believe
that you've never loved me.
Would it matter
if I had?
From now on,
you and I are strangers.
You...
You'd better behave from now on.
An attempt to murder another
is punishable.
Lock her up.
She will be executed in three days.
Cursed officer!
I was going to take my life
after taking yours!
I'll never stop haunting you!
Stop!
Their case was solved,
but what about yours?
Magistrate Zhang Youde?
Watch your mouth!
Back then,
you allowed Baron Li
to tarnish people's honor
and commit corruption.
He drove Huang Santai insane
and to death.
You should be punished as well!
Insolence.
Insolence!
Halt!
We received an order from the Prefect.
Zhang Youde forced women
into prostitution.
He is involved in dozens of cases.
(County Official Chen)
He is to be impeached and detained.
Nonsense!
I've done no such thing!
The ledger records
every transaction of wealth
Baron Li used to bribe you.
It's evidence of your corruption
and attempt to twist the truth.
Had you not committed
these heinous crimes,
he wouldn't have risked her life
or lost her family.
The real murderer
is you!
Tang Wan.
You shall be sentenced to death.
The case is closed.
You may go now.
I can walk on my own.
Did you mean
every word you said?
Live on.
Forget about me.
Shaoren!
No.
See you on the other side.
Have no fear
for the journey ahead.
Sorry.
The sunshine
is warm today.
It's just like...
when we first met.
Shaoren!
Perhaps in the end,
she was exhausted,
but too deep in love.
Which was why
she chose to tell him the easier lie.
They were deeply in love
with each other.
Why must they both die in the end?
The outcome maybe regrettable,
but the bond they shared
will always be true.
Had she known better,
she shouldn't have
put the plan in motion.
She wouldn't have lost him.
They were determined
to be there for each other.
They should
fear losses.
Back in the troupe,
unless you're a famous actor,
you must do your own makeup.
Otherwise, they'd starve you
and even beat you.
Now,
you don't need them for shelter.
There's no one
that can hurt so easily.
When you first
put the ornament on me,
I had a moment of joy.
But wearing it all the time
is too heavy for me.
I don't just mean on my head,
but my heart as well.
But I owe you the hairpin.
You pawned your family's
jade pendant for this.
Nothing in this world can
ever replace it.
I...
It's too much for me.
Thanks for coming here.
Inquisitor Song,
the Prefect mentioned in the letter
that I must remind you
that the case of accidental deaths
of those children
has been closed.
Stop your secret visits
and investigations.
To uncover the truth,
I must operate in secrecy.
I've thought long and hard
about the outcome
of overturning the case.
You and Magistrate Zhang
were not accomplices.
I hope
you treat the people
of Xingrong County well.
No good people must die.
What about your life?
My demotion
should serve as a warning to you.
I can't bear
to see you become miserable.
Upholding righteousness
and avoiding taking a stance
are enough to keep
your conscience clear.
In that case,
it's all the more reason
to uncover the truth.
I don't wish to be remember as a coward
who plays both ends against the middle
to save his own neck.
Very well.
Inquisitor Song.
Take care.
Greetings, Inquisitor Song.
Inquisitor Song?
Are you really the legendary
Inquisitor Song
Ting has been so obsessed with?
You may call me "sir".
Sir...
Song?
That will do it.
That's what you call me from now on.
You knew all along?
You kept me in the dark!
When I ran into you,
we were in danger.
I had no choice but to fake an amnesia
to hide my identity.
I hope you won't mind.
Not at all.
Inquisitor Song...
The man I know better
than my own parents?
The man Zhao Zhiting adores
more than anyone in the world?
I can't believe we've run into him!
So,
where are we headed for next,
inquisitor Song?
We'll travel together
as an unbreakable team.
Do you think
your debt to him is cleared?
I am broke.
Really?
Zhao has the money.
Take this.
You pawned this off
to buy her a hairpin.
It belonged to your family.
I bought it back for you.
Now, I am returning it.
Thank you, Inquisitor Song.
You secretly guided us
so we could find
the critical clues of those cases.
Acting is the only craft
actors like us have.
However, I know
you pretended
to be a senile old man
because you had your reasons.
When we first met,
it didn't took you long to notice
the lotus-shape scar on my chest.
Does it have something
to do with the scar?
When you got that scar,
you were but a child.
Perhaps you barely remember a thing.
It's a perilous mystery.
It's best you stay out of it.
Do not get involved with them.
When I was abducted and transported,
I was blindfolded.
But, it felt like a bustling place.
I could hear the noises
of a busy street.
Does it remind you of Lin'an?
I think so.
And then, I joined the troupe.
They were in Lin'an.
Were there similar cases in Lin'an?
Yes.
Inquisitor Song,
Do you have a lead?
After a long investigation,
I haven't found any concrete evidence.
- We'll search for the answer.
- Eat up.
However,
I have other questions for you.
Shoot.
Could you tell me
which of them are real
(Records of Song Ci, Tales of Song Ci)
and which are fake?
The line between truth
and fiction is blurred.
However, you just inspired me
to record the truth myself.
Perhaps it could come in handy
for future investigators.
It will do more than that.
Some inspirations last a lifetime.
Come on, that's too mushy.
You are making Inquisitor Song barf.
Forget it.
He can never be normal.
I got used to it.
Why is the street
empty?
Where is the dog's corpse?
The dog's corpse is missing.
Did you see a dog's corpse?
Where is the dog's corpse?
♪Under the moonlight,
the landscape reappears♪
♪She weeps, tears falling like petals♪
♪People's hearts are unpredictable♪
♪No one knows who reveals their fangs♪
♪No time to wait for orders♪
♪Fearing villains
might escape in an instant♪
♪With a shout,
the loyal heart presses on♪
♪Halting hatred,
pulling back from the brink♪
♪Parting ways amidst the great waves♪
♪Wandering to the ends of the earth♪
♪The road ahead lacks splendor♪
♪The clear sky and bright moon
as witness♪
♪Long-held promises not forgotten♪
♪The world
is like a grand dream of falling petals♪
♪Coming and going, long away from home♪
♪Justice and human hearts
reside under heaven♪
♪Long and painful separation
beyond sorrow♪
♪Weathering the winds and sands♪
♪Hand in hand through fleeting years♪
♪Those who share the path,
chivalrous and eloquent♪
♪Accompany me
as we make the world our home♪
♪I wish only for your unregretful smile♪
♪To roam freely
between heaven and earth♪
♪Love remains, unbounded by distance♪
♪Like a lotus petal,
I drift beneath the waters♪
♪Witnessing love and hate
trampled underfoot♪
♪Too much sorrows and grievances
throughout all times♪
♪Sadness in old age♪
♪Only then do we lose the attachment♪
♪Unwilling to feign any elegance♪
♪I lament
how the landscape resembles a painting♪
♪I hope only to return♪
♪Beneath the clear and bright heavens♪
♪How can one
distinguish truth from falsehood♪