=The Song Inquisitor=
=Episode 5=
Delicious!
Old man,
I heard you persuaded Madam Wang
to confess at the administrative office.
You seem quite clear-headed now.
Do you recall anything
about your family?
My mind is completely blank.
How would I have that ability?
It's all thanks to Miss He.
I heard the county magistrate
was dismissed from his post.
Someone reported his cover-up
of an unjust case to higher authorities.
That's how it is.
Another strange case has happened.
Again?
What strange case?
When the children's bodies
were found in these regions,
it was found that
their arms or legs were missing.
(Anyang County)
Why does the place I marked
match your map?
I don't know.
This...
Maybe this is just my way home.
How could it be such a coincidence
that they are exactly the same route?
Your mind is always filled with cases.
You suspected me earlier,
and now you suspect our benefactor.
It's endless.
I decided to follow the benefactor,
repay his kindness and return his money
until he finds his family.
It's up to you whether
to come along or not.
I'm going!
I can get good food
by following the old man.
Speaking of that,
you've saved the benefactor,
but you become even
more indebted to him.
Along the way,
he sold his belongings,
and spent a lot of money.
You all should know it well.
I was even worried you'd all run away.
Don't worry.
I'd definitely pay him money,
and repay his kindness.
Otherwise, I won't be able to sleep.
It's just a small act.
- Miss He, eat it.
- Just a small act.
Who's crying? Nonsense!
Who's there?
Stop!
Who is it?
Who?
Li Er!
Return my head!
Huang Santai! Return my head!
(Anyang County, Xingrong County)
(Hefty Reward)
200 taels.
They're offering this much money
to exorcise the ghost?
Let's go together.
So, we can earn money
and pay the travel expenses
back to the old man.
No need.
Offering so much money...
There must be some
huge trouble behind it.
With your physique,
you better don't take up the trouble.
What's there to fear?
We can make money if nothing happens.
If something happens,
we'll investigate it.
Watch your step!
Have the masters arrived?
Yes.
Hurry up!
Father.
(Baron Li, Li Shaoren)
All the masters within a ten-mile radius
who can exorcise and connect
with the ghosts are here now.
Masters,
please stop for a moment.
Stop for a moment.
Please stop, everyone.
I believe
you're all aware of
the situation of my Li family.
Over the past two years, the ghosts have
frequently appeared in my mansion.
Just a few days ago,
it appeared right in front of me.
Baron.
Look,
every time I kill a ghost,
I leave a scar on my body.
As long as you provide enough...
I mean...
Enough allowance.
I can
add another scar.
Stop! Stop!
There are just a bunch of con artists!
Let's leave here.
Hold on. I can smell the steamed buns.
Let's leave after the mealtime.
You're always about food.
Baron, you need to be discerning.
Don't let some schemers
sneak in here.
Even actors from the theater troupes
are pretending to exorcise ghosts.
Perhaps the feng shui
of this mansion will be disrupted.
It's obvious there's
greater yin energy here.
Be careful not to
attract something unwanted.
Watch carefully.
My blood
can exorcise all evil spirits!
You're ruining
the props we use for performing.
This blood pouch is expensive!
Hmm...
Everyone,
I don't care who you are.
Within ten days, whoever first
helps me expel the evil spirit
will receive 200 taels
of silver as a token of appreciation.
The baron has prepared the rooms for all of you.
Meals and accommodations are included.
Everything is covered.
Where is the Inquisitor Song, Song Ci?
Take me to him!
Who?
Who are you talking about?
I don't know him.
The old man who was with you
earlier during the day.
Which room is he staying in?
This mansion is so large,
and I've seen plenty of men.
I can't recall.
Do you believe I'll kill you?
It's Baron Du, a guest at the mansion.
He wants to take me as his concubine,
but he can't afford the silver.
I told him not to bother me.
Stop playing fool with me!
Who's sneaking around the Li Mansion?
Miss, are you all right?
Father! Mother!
I don't want to die.
I still have so many wishes.
Uncle, won't you save us?
Had a nightmare?
Are you still worried
about the headless ghost case
at the Li Mansion?
I dreamt about childhood memories.
I couldn't figure out an answer,
or uncover the truth.
Do you still remember
those childhood events?
When I was six, I was kidnapped.
After that, I wandered
from place to place.
I've long forgotten where my home was.
That's why you got this lotus-shaped scar
after being kidnapped?
Along the way,
I've been dazed.
When I woke up, I would be...
If I had met you back then,
I would have given
my life to protect you.
What are you two doing
awake at midnight?
Let's sleep.
Alright, sleep.
Thank you, Miss Tang, for saving me.
Miss, there's no need to mention it.
(Maid, Tang Wan)
Since there were intruders here,
it was only right for us to step in.
It's late. Rest early.
Benefactor,
I was held hostage by someone in black.
Were you in any danger?
Did he trouble Miss He?
Fortunately, Miss Tang passed by
and helped me escape.
I've caused you trouble.
Benefactor, don't say that.
At least they won't allow the intruders
to run wild in the Li Mansion.
For now, we're still safe.
This journey is tough.
After this,
I'll find a better place soon.
Benefactor,
I didn't want to say thank you,
because in this world,
'thank you' is the lightest word.
I will prove this through my actions
that there's kindness
and justice in this world.
The journey ahead is uncertain.
It's inconvenient to take you with me.
If you're worried
I can't endure the hardship,
do you think
life could be harder
than when I lived in a theater?
Now that I've escaped that prison,
I want to see this vibrant world.
But, how do you know traveling with me
will lead to a smoother path?
I could just tell it now.
You can't bear to see a woman cry.
You must have a kind heart.
So, traveling together
must be a smooth path.
Benefactor, since you need
to keep a low profile,
I'll cover for you.
It will only benefit
whatever you seek to do.
Wipe away your tears first.
♪Under the moonlight,
the landscape reappears♪
♪She weeps, tears falling like petals♪
♪People's hearts are unpredictable♪
♪No one knows who reveals their fangs♪
♪No time to wait for orders♪
♪Fearing villains might
escape in an instant♪
♪With a shout,
the loyal heart presses on♪
♪Halting hatred,
pulling back from the brink♪
♪Parting ways amidst the great waves♪
♪Wandering to the ends of the earth♪
♪The road ahead lacks splendor♪
♪The clear sky and
bright moon as witness♪
♪Long-held promises not forgotten♪
♪The world is like
a grand dream of falling petals♪
♪Coming and going, long away from home♪
♪Justice and human hearts
reside under heaven♪
♪Long and painful
separation beyond sorrow♪
♪Weathering the winds and sands♪
♪Hand in hand through fleeting years♪
♪Those who share the path,
chivalrous and eloquent♪
♪Accompany me as we make
the world our home♪
♪I wish only for your unregretful smile♪
♪To roam freely
between heaven and earth♪
♪Love remains, unbounded by distance♪
♪I, like a lotus petal,
drift beneath the waters♪
♪Witnessing love and hate
trampled underfoot♪
♪Too much sorrows and grievances
throughout all times♪
♪Sadness in old age♪
♪Only then do we lose the attachment♪
♪Unwilling to feign any elegance♪
♪I lament how the landscape
resembles a painting♪
♪I hope only to return♪
♪Beneath the clear and bright heavens♪
♪How can one distinguish
truth from falsehood♪