=The Song Inquisitor=
=Episode 1=
(Anyang County, Xingrong County)
The lotus falls into the mire.
(Linchuan County, Guichi County, Lin'An)
A bitter life, like a fleeting dream.
Misplaced trust in the seemingly just.
Children's garments stained
with blood and tears.
Childhood hopes extinguished.
Wronged souls demand justice
in the court of Yama.
(Song Ci)
What are you doing here, sir?
I don't remember a thing.
Are you sick?
Your family thought you died,
so they buried you.
The pulse is steady and strong.
I doubt he is sick.
(Actor, Wang Ling)
You must've been set up!
They went for your life.
(Actor, Zhao Zhiting)
Luxurious garments and smooth hands.
He is well-off.
A likely target for raiders.
But...
But all his belongings are here.
What exactly
did he go through?
Can you stop acting
like a detective for once?
My mind is a blurry swirl.
I don't have any answers.
Oh no.
Seize them!
What?
They carry costumes!
What do you want?
What did we do?
- Their stuff is in the bag.
- What do you want?
You disguise as ghosts
in the cemetery! Seize them!
Bring them in!
Actors dressing up as ghosts.
You are rotten beings in fancy clothes.
Did you kill Deng Guang?
Come clean!
I want him dead or alive.
What do you mean?
All we did was steal some offerings
for the dead.
- What are you hiding?
- We didn't hurt anyone.
We even rescued this old man.
We came from humble backgrounds,
but we wouldn't kill just to rob.
You can't pin this on us!
Twisting words now?
That's another charge.
We are wronged! We didn't do anything!
Sir, look at this.
(Inspector of Criminal Justice)
Lock them up.
We'll discuss this after the review.
Yes.
(Silence and solemnity)
Sorry for the misunderstanding.
I am now aware of
who you really are.
Inquisitor Song sent you here
as a test.
Why did you arrest us?
Lately,
there have been several
weird occurrences in this county.
It was all related
to the funerary opera actors.
Hence, this is a misunderstanding.
All these events
are connected
to Deng Guang's disappearance.
Cursed beggar!
Where did you get the money to drink?
And you bought yourself a coffin!
Alive,
I live in a rundown house.
In death,
I'm going to have a nice resting place.
What good is it if you're dead?
(Deng Guang)
Great!
Good work!
(Tomb of...)
Where did he go?
See if he went home.
Are you in there?
Aren't we hitting the gambling parlor?
Keep it in mind.
A funerary opera
is not meant for the living.
I'm tired of living!
Time to face my death!
(Deng Guang)
(was haunted by an evil ghost.)
And then,
he went missing.
Since Inspector Song and you
have arrived in this humble county,
I know you can uncover the truth
and free the people from this terror.
We don't know Inquisitor Song.
We are not detectives.
However, the badge is indeed ours.
Sir, where are you going?
To solve the case.
We'll go to
Deng Guang's house for clues.
Why do you have the badge?
No idea.
How are you connected
to Inquisitor Song?
No idea.
Were you in the coffin
because of
Inquisitor Song's secret visit?
I told him I don't know.
All right. Relax.
If you knew nothing at all,
why did you say
the badge was ours?
Well...
The badge was a way
to get us out of trouble. So I...
What are you? A hound?
Stop sniffing for answers.
This old man may be suspicious,
but he lost his memory
and can't find a way home.
Have some sympathy.
People used to say
your strange birthmark
could predict trouble.
They called you a bad omen.
They blame every kid's death
and swine fever
on your curse.
You felt mistreated as well.
Don't take it to heart.
He is Song Ci's biggest fan
in a 100-li radius.
He is obsessed with the man.
He loses his mind whenever he hears
the name "Song CI".
Sorry.
Sir, I got carried away earlier.
It's all right.
(Inspector of Criminal Justice)
Since this badge
means so much to you,
you may have it.
Please
help me get home.
Will you?
We all get what we want. Sure!
Bad news.
Help!
♪Under the moonlight,
the landscape reappears♪
♪She weeps, tears falling like petals♪
♪People's hearts are unpredictable♪
♪No one knows who reveals their fangs♪
♪No time to wait for orders♪
♪Fearing villains might escape
in an instant♪
♪With a shout,
the loyal heart presses on♪
♪Halting hatred,
pulling back from the brink♪
♪Parting ways amidst the great waves♪
♪Wandering to the ends of the earth♪
♪The road ahead lacks splendor♪
♪The clear sky
and bright moon as witness♪
♪Long-held promises not forgotten♪
♪The world is like
a grand dream of falling petals♪
♪Coming and going, long away from home♪
♪Justice and human hearts reside
under heaven♪
♪Long and painful separation
beyond sorrow♪
♪Weathering the winds and sands♪
♪Hand in hand through fleeting years♪
♪Those who share the path,
chivalrous and eloquent♪
♪Accompany me as we make
the world our home♪
♪I wish only for your unregretful smile♪
♪To roam freely
between heaven and earth♪
♪Love remains, unbounded by distance♪
♪I, like a lotus petal,
drift beneath the waters♪
♪Witnessing love and hate
trampled underfoot♪
♪Too much sorrows and grievances
throughout all times♪
♪Sadness in old age♪
♪Only then do we lose the attachment♪
♪Unwilling to feign any elegance♪
♪I lament how the landscape
resembles a painting♪
♪I hope only to return♪
♪Beneath the clear and bright heavens♪
♪How can one distinguish truth
from falsehood♪