=The Song Inquisitor=
=Episode 14=
I never ask for help empty-handed.
I know
you don't care about my support for you,
nor do you care
about wealth
and career advancement.
But you care
about those young people.
You and Yang Hewen set this up
to conclude
that they broke into Yang Residence
to find the truth.
Then, you'll charge them
with trespassing.
Song Ci.
Don't think I'm threatening you.
I'm saving you.
If the main culprit
isn't brought to justice,
more innocent children
will die tragically.
There will be more people like me
who will be framed as murderers.
Evil is like a flood
that can't be stopped.
You can protect your official position,
but can you also uphold your conscience?
We found proof.
Hurry and report to the authorities.
We've been searching for so long,
but not a single servant patrolled.
We're doomed.
- What are you doing here?
- We're doomed!
- Get them!
- Run!
The Song Dynasty law states
that anyone who trespasses
another person's residence
can be killed without mercy.
Go.
If it had been any later,
they
might have been beaten to death.
What do you want to do?
Report to the authorities.
Case closed.
Resign as Inspector of Criminal Justice.
(Submitted by Song Ci)
I've prepared the letter for you.
Tea
is getting cold.
Stop!
You really like my residence.
Don't move.
Beat him up too.
Who dares to do so?
Song Dynasty law states
that anyone who trespasses
without reason at night,
and the owner subdues
but still injures or kills
the trespasser,
the owner shall be sentenced
to penal servitude and exile!
If
we can't get out of here alive today,
someone will go after you relentlessly
and make you suffer forever
until you are sentenced
to death.
See justice from King Yan
after you turn into ashes then!
(Inspector of Criminal Justice)
I'm Song Dynasty's inspector!
Who dares
to harm the people, violate justice,
and kill lives?
Good kid.
Endure it.
Does it hurt?
Song.
You're like my mother.
If your parents knew,
how should I explain to them?
You came to save us today,
kept us warm and fed along the way,
and treat me as well as my mother.
If they were alive,
they'd be as grateful as I am.
If you hadn't been protecting me,
I could still help you.
And you wouldn't have suffered
so many injuries.
Don't you
care about your looks the most?
Wouldn't you be even more grumpy
if you were bruised and scarred?
I can't afford that.
It's none of your business.
You can make it
my business
or control me.
I'm not afraid of anything.
I want
to find out
and clear their name
with all of you
and with you.
Song.
You exposed your identity
in front of the people today.
Will you be in danger?
I wanted to use your identity
to hide myself
and secretly investigate
the clues of the corpse dumping case.
But along the way
I saw your persistence
and how you prioritize righteousness.
I seemed to see the old me,
who isn't afraid of anything
except regret and injustice.
Today you fell into the bad guys' trap
and almost got killed.
It's my fault
for getting you all involved.
Forgive me.
I blame you.
I blame you
for pulling me out of the fire pit
and letting me
live the life everyone deserves.
I also blame you
for feeding me.
What if I starve again?
Inquisitor Song.
You said
you seemed to see your old self.
Yes.
If you see him again,
what would you say to him?
Keep holding on.
You made the right choice.
The world
needs someone like you.
I will send this resignation letter
to the government now.
Is it worth it
for these kids?
I've only known them
for more than a month,
but they're like family to me.
I've known someone
for more than ten years,
but we're like strangers.
We have no ties with each other,
but we concern about each other.
If my life is in danger,
they will make the same choice.
However,
one person like me
is enough.
Say,
what if the bad guys
come after us again?
We need to protect Inquisitor Song well.
But let's make a deal.
You can't abandon me
just because of Inquisitor Song.
And you can't abandon me
just because you have a lover.
What lover?
Do you think I'm a fool?
Do you think I don't know
what's going on between you and Miss He?
Alright.
Instead of studying food and drink
and the case,
you think about this.
Yeah.
I have it all figured out.
I will write an opera
about your experience with Miss He
and our experience with Inquisitor Song.
We'll sing and act well.
We never have to starve anymore.
Sure.
This case is called
Dog Murder.
We can't
let the villains win in the end.
If these stories of exoneration
and grievances
can be passed on from person to person,
spread by word of mouth,
and serve as a warning
to future generations,
we
will not have lived in vain.
You two grown men
are being sentimental again.
You guys are waiting here
because you don't want
Inquisitor Song to leave, aren't you?
I also felt
that Inquisitor Song
seemed to be
bidding us farewell just now.
Is Inquisitor Song leaving?
Where is he going?
I haven't packed my stuff yet.
You must be teasing me.
Inquisitor Song won't bear to leave us.
Didn't we agree
to eat, drink, solve cases together,
and stay together forever?
♪Under the moonlight,
the landscape reappears♪
♪She weeps, tears falling like petals♪
♪People's hearts are unpredictable♪
♪No one knows who reveals their fangs♪
♪No time to wait for orders♪
♪Fearing villains
might escape in an instant♪
♪With a shout,
the loyal heart presses on♪
♪Halting hatred,
pulling back from the brink♪
♪Parting ways amidst the great waves♪
♪Wandering to the ends of the earth♪
♪The road ahead lacks splendor♪
♪The clear sky and bright moon
as witness♪
♪Long-held promises not forgotten♪
♪The world
is like a grand dream of falling petals♪
♪Coming and going, long away from home♪
♪Justice and human hearts
reside under heaven♪
♪Long and painful separation
beyond sorrow♪
♪Weathering the winds and sands♪
♪Hand in hand through fleeting years♪
♪Those who share the path,
chivalrous and eloquent♪
♪Accompany me
as we make the world our home♪
♪I wish only for your unregretful smile♪
♪To roam freely
between heaven and earth♪
♪Love remains, unbounded by distance♪
♪Like a lotus petal,
I drift beneath the waters♪
♪Witnessing love and hate
trampled underfoot♪
♪Too much sorrows and grievances
throughout all times♪
♪Sadness in old age♪
♪Only then do we lose the attachment♪
♪Unwilling to feign any elegance♪
♪I lament
how the landscape resembles a painting♪
♪I hope only to return♪
♪Beneath the clear and bright heavens♪
♪How can one
distinguish truth from falsehood♪