POLICE ADEPTS
PART 3
If the camera was recording,
There must be a charger somewhere.
Where is she?
It must be here somewhere.
SAVE ELECTRICITY
Hi. I forgot something.
God, where is it?
Is that what you're looking for?
Will you explain to me what it is?
It looks like a camera charger.
Where did you get it from?
- Bring it on.
- You did it, didn't you?
- Give.
- Answer. Have you been recording?
Answer! You've been recording, eh?
Leave me alone!
Let go!
What do they do?
- Give it back!
- Let go!
I said let go!
The entire Training Corps
Is in favor of expulsion.
What does the student government think?
We are gathering feedback from yearbooks.
It will take some time, as we are on a break.
Be careful that the issue does not surface.
Why do we need a first-timer like her?
I knew there would be trouble with her,
When she told Sunyu that she was awake.
I felt like smacking her then.
- What is it about?
- Never mind.
- What's going on?
- Camera. That is.
I know whose camera it is.
Don't.
That's not me.
So where did this charger come from?
This is.
phone charger.
It is not allowed to have a phone at the training.
Sorry.
My mother is sick.
There is no other family,
So just in case
I have a phone with a charger.
NAME: GI HANNA
INFORMATION: NO FATHER
Will you leave us alone?
That's right.
Sit down.
Your mother called.
I couldn't call you,
because you had training.
Belated congratulations.
Thanks.
It must have been hard.
Yes, you don't even know how hard it was.
I don't know where to start.
It's been a few days,
and I'm like years older.
I'm not kidding.
Why didn't you say it was like that here?
They constantly inflict punishments on us.
I feel like I'm in the military.
They check if we sleep during lectures.
- You got caught sleeping.
- I wasn't sleeping.
She misinterpreted it.
He always has a cap covering his eyes
And somehow he squints,
That he certainly can't see anything.
And how do you know that?
Have you heard from this girl?
No "the one," she's your superior.
From her, anyway.
What a cutthroat.
I didn't know she was like that.
A little strange.
Eunkang.
- It's not what you think it is.
- What.
- Well...
- The Corps is not for the faint of heart.
They have six months of training
before the Cheongram program.
Here they test,
whether the freshmen will survive four years.
Take it seriously.
Right.
Address me formally at school.
But you don't have to be afraid.
By the way, Jechan...
I ask.
When you heard about the camera,
did you think it was my fault?
Of course not.
I know you.
Let's go.
- Well done.
- Thanks.
PHONE
Caution.
Nothing to worry about.
Send me everything that is left there.
My grandchildren are helping me,
so we'll be up and running in no time.
Okay, for now.
Oh, come on.
Fold nicely.
Defective deduct from paycheck.
- Right.
- That's right.
But you know we wanted to pay....
later.
Did you see the card?
I haven't seen.
But anyway, how could I trust you?
Well...
glue them all together carefully
Before I go back, okay?
Or I will tell everything to the
Training Corps.
Do we understand each other?
That's right.
♪ I like ♪
♪ You ♪
One, two.
It will take ages.
Today we will not sleep.
Damn!
Where did that bastard Seunghyun go?
What took so long?
KOREA NATIONAL POLICE UNIVERSITY
You are doing great. Hi.
For now.
Hey.
- Don't scare me.
- What about you?
- Apparently you have a guilty pleasure.
- How do you know?
You've taken a beating. Everyone knows.
But how did you know about the charger?
Well, I had it right under my nose.
She could only hide it in one place,
So I searched our room.
In any case, you are also contributing.
I have to admit.
Just why did she do it?
I don't know. They should discover it.
Pardon?
Please charge.
Right.
It doesn't fit, does it?
Because it's not a phone charger.
Who gave it to you?
A student will not easily get such a thing.
It is a Russian model,
It was used seven or eight years ago.
We used to use it too,
But not anymore. Battery too weak.
Can it be purchased just like that?
I don't know. Rather, you can,
the only question is why.
Do you want to buy?
Don't.
I ask out of curiosity before class.
Forgive the off-the-cuff question.
UNPK colleagues are the best.
- Thanks, man.
- How about thanking me in person?
You've been rotting in school since you returned to Korea.
Sounds good to me. I'll give it a call.
Tell me. Who gave it to you?
Unlock.
- I'm listening.
- Go ahead.
Emergency phone,
so it must be your mother's number.
CONNECTIONS
SPEAKER
Subscriber temporarily unavailable.
Please call...
Mom goes to bed early
By drugs.
CHA UGON
Tomorrow before the disciplinary committee
you will have to explain in detail,
why you did it.
Camera?
It is necessary to recharge every eight hours.
You have a charger.
SECRETARIAT
Call if necessary.
What if I get caught?
There are cameras in the dormitory.
Starting tomorrow, repairs in the ceiling.
All the cameras will be taken away.
Don't worry.
I checked everything.
But why...
I'll tell you later.
Do it for me, please.
GIRL IN A SPIDER'S WEB
Did she pretend to be innocent?
I didn't know there was one.
And I knew something was wrong with her.
He has such slanted eyes
And perpetually tense eyebrows.
That's what anxious people have.
Physiognomy is a science.
- Are you familiar with physiognomy?
- Analyze your face?
Show.
- "Is this the face of the future king?"
- Stop it!
Get on with the job.
We have to finish today.
Sorry. To the point.
Quick!
Seunghyun, give more saliva,
so that it sticks well.
But you're a slacker.
Bumju, what is this?
- Again.
- What are you doing?
Me: I supervise.
Who asked you?
Don't you see the need to do?
God, what a...
You don't understand anything.
Listen. When something is done in a group,
It takes a boss to make the system work.
I check what is slowing us down
And I control the speed.
I also check the quality.
Close.
- That's who should supervise...
- Sit.
Right. Even supervisors
sometimes work in the field.
Let me help you.
It will take us centuries to get there.
They are about to turn off the lights.
Right.
ACADEMIC
Check here and...
I FIRST
DO YOU THINK WE CAN DO IT?
SWAPPED, THAT IS, WILL NOT EMBRACE
GOOD, I'LL CATCH UP WITH YOU
GOOD LUCK!
I have to ... use the restroom.
MALE
The eagle has arrived. Acceptance, Latavian.
- What took so long?
- They exchanged.
Did he suspect nothing?
I am a great actor.
Prompt. We've done a lot already.
Where is Yes?
Right.
Look where we landed
Because of the stupid pasta.
I will have a pasta trauma.
You took too much at once.
You should not have overdone it.
What, you say, is my fault?
You were the one who ate the most.
Don't you remember anymore?
We ate equally.
Equally?
I saw how much you take. A little culture.
Okay, get out of there.
Get out!
Can't we finish and go to bed?
I'm so sleepy.
Sorry.
I shouldn't tell you about the pasta.
Less so. Everyone agreed to eat.
I didn't think I would be facing such a thing here.
Detective Lee Jaehan.
Do you guys do something like this too?
Is it the same there?
Is there ... is it the same?
If you have the cash...
- ...and acquaintances...
- ...and acquaintances.
...Can you lead a good life
regardless of your hopelessness?
But 20 years have passed.
Something must have changed.
Right?
No, not true.
Detective
Lee Jaehan.
Do you me...
hear?
Did you answer the phone?
You answered me...
Detective Lee!
- Who is Lee Jaehan?
- It's obvious.
Because of him I am here.
Guess what?
If I become a cop
And I get unsolved cases.
someday I will be able to work with him....
Talk about a series.
As if how?
Dude, you need imagination.
God, what a freak. Stop.
- Lightning struck and that's it.
- You guys don't seem to have feelings.
How are you going to talk to citizens?
What is the stench?
Something stinks here.
Kim Yes!
- Holy shit.
- That's you, right?
God, Yes, Detective!
I will murder you, Yes!
UNPK
You wanted to reveal,
how a colleague was unfairly treated,
Which is gone.
- Am I right?
- That's right.
The colleague left
three days after receiving her punishment.
I didn't want a repeat,
So I decided to
to unveil the Cheongram program....
The school had to be informed.
If there was trouble with the Corps.
Don't you think so?
I could not inform,
being put under pressure.
If I did that, I would be punished.
Did you intend to make it public?
I was counting on outside pressure.
I acted thoughtlessly,
But please understand that I meant well.
The police are acting in accordance with the law.
Illegal acts cannot be
justified by good intentions.
Additionally,
How could you
prosecute illegal recorders,
When you do it yourself?
We can consider the matter closed.
In accordance with the rules of the school
you are expelled.
You can appeal,
But that would be a waste of time.
The result will remain the same.
I consider the disciplinary committee closed.
Can I appeal elsewhere?
Publish online
Or report on the violence,
Which I have experienced here?
If I am not a student,
then I have no reason...
to cover it up.
This is no longer about just any camera.
The case is about violence at the university.
I will still talk to the student.
It was difficult to communicate with her.
Even a mouse,
being trapped, will bite a cat.
And this girl wanted to bite you.
- Professor.
- No hard feelings.
I just wanted to say,
That we are not going to solve the problem,
influencing it in this way.
What do you suggest?
Should we not excrete it?
If that's what it takes.
It had to happen eventually.
We train these kids
the same way I was trained.
There will be dissenting voices.
Under these circumstances
We can radically change the
Cheongram's program.
Professor!
The problem of violence
of verbal and physical Corps
will only grow.
Penalties are part of education.
They are not targeted without reason.
The kids you are talking about,
do not know patience,
dedication, unity.
The spoiled brats will not listen,
if we are calm and gentle.
They will listen. They are not children.
They are over-twenty-year-old adults.
The school has its own traditions.
We do everything our own way.
Traditions?
Which ones specifically?
Why always, at the end of the day,
Are you arguing in my office?
Does this place have that effect on you?
Do you feel the competitive spirit here?
Sorry.
I understand you, professor.
I also understand the professor.
This time, let's listen to Professor Cha.
Ma'am.
UNPK CONTROVERSY
Most students,
Who graduated from UNPK, went to law school.
People are angry that taxes
are spent on lawyers, not police officers.
They say it is de facto theft.
People are not with us.
So let's not make a scandal out of it.
Sorry.
I would like to say something as a consolation.
Will you continue to ignore me?
I know you were afraid. And since you are apologizing,
then I will be better and accept the apology.
But that doesn't mean I'm not angry.
Well!
I will improve, I promise.
Save such talk for the boy.
- Come on, don't be like that.
- God, what are you doing?
- Leave.
- They announced the decision.
NOTICE
GI HANNA
THREE MONTHS CONDITIONAL PERIOD
Conditional period?
What nonsense.
The condition is not just a punishment.
He can't go out for three months.
But it's not right. It's not fair.
Eunkang nearly flew out.
I also have a distaste for it.
Does she have any connections here?
Wait, what's the point?
- About water.
- Water, clearly.
- What are you doing here?
- Nothing of the sort.
What did you do?
Right.
I don't know what you did,
But you owe me an apology.
You haven't apologized to me yet.
For what?
Are you talking about the camera in your jacket?
That's not me.
You took my jacket by mistake.
So you don't owe me an apology?
Don't you know that I would almost fly out of here?
Are you so mad?
- What?
- They didn't even accept you here.
You got in by luck. Don't be angry.
If you don't like my punishment,
talk to the school,
and not with me.
Do you want a colleague to be expelled?
That's not what I'm wondering. I'm wondering...
If not,
then don't cause trouble.
This is a trial period.
Don't distract others.
Have you thought that with this attitude
Are you distracting others from learning?
- But...
- If that's all, go ahead.
This is cowardice.
It is not fair to suggest,
That I want the expulsion of my colleague.
I just want to know,
Why she got the condition,
and I almost got fired.
I wanted to know what had changed.
I think we need to her
explain the punishment to Ms. Gi.
He is a freshman.
He doesn't need to know everything.
We have to stick to the school's guidelines.
No way.
- They were not friends.
- Really?
Scary.
There's been a lot going on lately.
Exercise is tiring, isn't it?
Sorry for the confusion.
It's my fault.
Needless to say.
I don't want to blame you.
As for the punishment against Ms. Gi.
The school made the best decision.
Her conduct was inappropriate,
However, the Training Corps was also at fault.
If the kids
would complain about the punishments,
The school would be in big trouble.
We had to consider these circumstances.
May you understand.
There is a risk,
That students will not accept Ms. Gi.
This is already up to Mrs. Gi.
Please remain impartial
and keep an eye on her.
UNPK, CRADLE OF WORLD TALENT
...seventy-two, seventy
three, seventy-four.
Orient.
Drop already.
You were lucky, you know?
Because of this camera
attention focused on Gi Hanna.
If not for that, we would have been done for.
From now on you are to behave.
Many colleagues have turned away from you,
But I have not abandoned you.
Because we are collegial.
Well, that's a shame.
We could have stopped being colleagues.
Do you know what I think?
We live together,
So we are together until the end.
Once a roommate, always a roommate.
Bumju! Seunghyun!
- What.
- You're terrible.
I understand.
Your poop is scarier.
How could you make her so quiet?
Mr. shitting his pants.
- Stop.
- Stop what?
- Come here.
- You come.
- I'll get down there right away.
- Come on, get down.
Come on!
Yoo Daeil is the best.
What's up with the first-timers?
Zero respect.
We have never been like that.
They need to be hammered with some respect.
I think it's a bad idea.
What if someone reports it?
In addition, one of the freshmen
is the son of an officer.
It is better not to mess with him.
INFORMATION
Listen up! After the cleanup, a collection in the hall.
- What?
- Not now.
We are to go to the hall after cleaning.
Now get on with the cleaning.
TO GI HANNA
COLLECTION OF STUDENTS IN THE HALL AT 21
You bream...
Well, no. After all, I didn't do anything.
Collective responsibility.
"There are a hundred of you, and it's like one."
Girls, quickly.
Movements.
TO GI HANNA
COLLECTION OF STUDENTS IN THE HALL AT 21
HALA
I vow to be honest
and an honorary student of UNPK,
Who will not succumb to injustice.
Honest and honorable?
Forbidden items, sloppy attire,
Loss of school property, bad behavior.
Is it honorable?
No, coach.
Louder, morons!
No, coach!
Who did not follow these simple rules,
Shirked by fatigue and forgetfulness,
let him stand up.
Get up, fast!
I lost my gloves while exercising.
I slept through the lecture.
I was late for the scheduled cleaning.
That much?
Why are there 11 girls?
Who is missing?
Answer! Who is missing?
It seems to me that Gi Hanna.
What are you doing here?
- I beg your pardon?
- Didn't you know about the collection?
I haven't heard anything about it.
I didn't see it.
The card was on the door.
And you haven't seen it?
I really didn't see it.
Was it recorded by someone off camera?
Let's see what happened.
Did you not record this time?
Do 30 laps of the hall.
Now.
That's right.
Hurry up!
Heads down.
Heads down!
Return to the site.
Hanna.
EMERGENCY
- Back inside!
- Get inside quickly!
- Get back in!
She really might not have noticed.
I think he's going to pass out.
Leave.
It will be useful to her.
He must be taught a lesson.
God, a lesson learned?
What lesson?
- Are you really going?
- Yes.
Complaints have a mode.
You can't just walk into the dean's office like that.
File a complaint with the Corps of...
I can't. It's all about them.
I need to talk to the most important,
That is, the dean.
If you're not going, bitch.
KOREA NATIONAL POLICE UNIVERSITY
FEBRUARY
You wanted to talk.
I want to listen to what about.
Ms. Kim, do you know,
what happened last night?
In the morning we were informed,
That there had been a minor accident.
A minor accident?
The punished student was taken to the hospital.
- Is it supposed to be a minor accident?
- This is what happens during exercises.
This was no ordinary exercise.
What does it mean?
She was punished for the camera case.
Everyone knows about it.
Ms. Ko.
I, too, think she did the wrong thing.
But she has already suffered punishment for her actions.
She should not receive another punishment
Because of a personal grudge.
Bottom line.
I understand.
Is there anything else?
- You may have already...
- Yes.
Shouldn't recording with a camcorder
Shouldn't it result in expulsion?
When I was set up,
I was told I would be fired.
And she received a minor punishment.
It seems unfair to me.
But when I think about it now,
It's also not fair to her.
Recording in secret is bad,
But kicking and beating people is worse.
But none of these people face punishment.
She is probably angry about it.
Beating will not make us
better police officers.
It will simply lead to revolt.
I am sure about that.
- Is the Training Corps unfair?
- I think so.
Society even more so.
You will encounter more difficult
And even more unfair things.
Will you shout out your complaints
every time?
You are angry because a colleague has suffered,
But I saw,
how a criminal
Stabbed a colleague to death,
And the dog ripped her apart before my eyes.
Compared to such psychopaths
exercises,
Which you find so difficult...
Are just a game.
Patience is part of the exercise.
Your colleague will be treated well.
Please demonstrate your work
during the exercises.
- But...
- Please leave now.
How did it go?
I told you. It's like banging your head against a wall.
You will only hurt yourself.
Maybe I won't tear down the wall,
But I will leave some kind of trace.
If I don't change anything,
then at least they will know,
That something is not right.
If you really want to make a difference,
then talk to the guilty party. Don't avoid him.
If this person does not notice the problem,
then nothing will change.
Who went to see Ms. Dean?
Show up!
Me, the trainer.
Shithead one. Are you mocking me?
Rise.
No...
I don't mock.
- I'm afraid of the trainer.
- What did you say?
Answer!
I said that beating students is wrong.
We beat you because you can't get a grip!
You will always find a reason to punish us.
- What?
- We didn't come here to be punished.
Please stop the violence,
and we will respect you.
You little...
Enough is enough.
You two, stand on your heads.
Can't you hear?
No one will get up,
Until they carry out the order.
Understood?
I swear,
That I will be sincere and honorable
UNPK student,
Who will not succumb to injustice.
I vow to be sincere and honorable
UNPK student,
Who will not succumb to injustice.
- I vow to be sincere....
- And honorable
UNPK student,
Who will not succumb to injustice.
- I vow to be a sincere...
- Vow,
That I will be honest
and honorable
UNPK student,
Who will not succumb to injustice.
I vow to be sincere and honorable
UNPK student,
Who will not succumb to injustice.
I vow to be honest
and an honorary student of UNPK,
Who will not succumb to...
I vow to be sincere and honorable
UNPK student who will not succumb to the
injustice.
I vow to be honest
and an honorary student of UNPK,
Who will not succumb to...
Sit down
UNPK student who will not succumb to the
Who will not succumb to injustice.
I vow to be honest
and an honorary student of UNPK,
injustice.
Sit down!
Can't you hear?
You are to sit down!
Silence!
What?
I vow to be a sincere
and honorable student of UNPK,
Who will not succumb to injustice.
I vow to be honest
and an honorary student of UNPK,
injustice.
That is, they refuse to exercise for two days.
Yes.
The protest was signed by all first-year students.
PROTEST LETTER
They will not practice,
until their demands are met.
FEBRUARY 23, 2017
PR Department...
received a call from a journalist.
I don't know how they found out,
But they want to interview you.
What do we do?
Changing...
Cheongram program.
We must avoid...
this storm.
Now that we care about human rights,
I think UNPK also needs a change.
From now on we will avoid
training as in the army
And we will focus on creating an environment
Where students will develop their creativity
and practice professionalism.
UNPK WANTS TO TRAIN
CREATIVE PROFESSIONALS,
HUMAN OFFICERS
NOW THAT WE CARE ABOUT HUMAN RIGHTS....
UNPK CHANGES RECRUITMENT SYSTEM
UNPK WANTS TO TRAIN
CREATIVE PROFESSIONALS
CREATIVE OFFICERS
UNPK ANNOUNCES REFORM
UNPK CHANGES CHEONGRAM PROGRAM
Ko Eunkang!
One, two, three, four. Forward march.
Once.
Two.
Three.
Four.
One, two, three, four.
Left turn.
Left.
One, two, three, four.
Marching in place.
Stand. One, two.
Attention!
Salute the chairman of the council!
Hello!
Students' post. Present arms!
Salute.
Hello!
To leg the gun.
All students in the Cheongram program,
including Um Hyuk's first coach,
served in the 47th Cheongram program
between February 13
and February 27, 2017
and a whole hundred from the class of 47
was integrated into the student body.
Salute the chairman of the council!
Hello!
To leg the gun.
Training Corps. Right and left turn.
Forward march.
Good morning.
Jang Juchan,
chairman of the UNPK student council.
When I see first-graders
At this time of year,
I look forward to seeing new colleagues,
Who share similar problems,
similar lives
and similar experiences.
Wi Seunghyun.
- Don't be intimidated.
- People will adapt.
It makes no difference where they live.
I'm dying.
Colleagues!
Get on with it!
Announcement for first graders.
Soon rounds at 10 pm.
Trashcan. Is he supposed to be standing here?
- Turn around.
- Now, excuse me.
I will have a pasta trauma.
You took too much at once.
You should not have overdone it.
Sorry.
I shouldn't tell you about the pasta.
GIRL IN A SPIDER'S WEB
You did it, didn't you?
Was it recorded by someone off camera?
Do 30 laps of the hall.
We didn't come here to be punished.
Please stop the violence.
You little...
I vow to be sincere and honorable
UNPK student,
Who will not succumb to injustice.
I vow to be sincere and honorable
UNPK student,
Who will not succumb to injustice.
I vow to be sincere and honorable
UNPK student,
Who will not succumb to injustice.
I swear,
That I will be sincere and honorable
UNPK student,
who will not succumb
injustice.
I vow to be sincere and honorable
UNPK student who will not succumb to the
injustice.
You are UNPK students.
We have high hopes for you,
That you will demonstrate.
First-timers,
welcome to UNPK.
You did a great job today.
And now the tradition is before us,
meaning you can ask questions.
If you have any,
A representative of the PR department and I
will be happy to answer you.
What are the requirements
for a student exchange program?
It depends on the program in any given year,
But I think you have to be
in the top ten.
Is there somewhere to go out by the school?
There are Internet cafes.
We also have billiard rooms and bowling alleys.
Apparently, it is not allowed
date other students.
If you want, give it a try.
KOREA NATIONAL POLICE UNIVERSITY
EXERCISES FOR UNPK 2017 EXAM
ENGLISH
You are my first and only student.
I believe in you.
Hard work will pay off. You can do it.
Get there, and I put lunch every day.
I just happened to be asking for it.
Well...
Who knows? If we eat together...
Calm down.
I have to get there first.
I will say this with conviction.
- What.
- Never mind.
Any more questions?
You want to go drinking, don't you?
Lovely this head of local government, isn't he?
Apparently there is no girlfriend.
Maybe I'll pick him up.
Dear God, have you already fallen in love?
Wrap. The dude sure is successful.
Probably a mass of girls are attracted to him.
Could it be? I feel the will to fight within me.
God.
Cheers!
To the bottom!
- Drink.
- You have to drink at once.
But great.
I love chicken.
Keep.
What is it, already eaten?
ALERT PEOPLE
Good.
- Listen.
- What.
I hope we will get along.
May you pass the exam,
And we will study together.
Learn...
together?
Subtitles: Cezary Kucharski