Why do we have to move?
Where are we even going?
We'll never come back.
Miaomiao, why are you all crying here?
Stop getting in the way.
We won't leave!
No one can separate us!
Yes, we're staying!
Who said anything about separating you?
We're all moving together.
To a new base.
Let's go.
Come on, Mom already said
that we'd never be separated.
Take Li Si for treatment as soon as possible.
Don't delay any longer.
You startled me.
Why are you here?
I just called you.
Why didn't you answer?
What's wrong?
People are watching.
It's okay. I'm here.
I'm telling you all.
From now on, when you talk to me,
you've got to be more careful.
Fang is going to be my uncle's wife.
Wait.
Why is Fang
dating your uncle now?
Didn't she
hit it off
with Cheng Miaomiao's uncle?
Zhu Chao!
Do you still
want to be the Class Monitor next semester?
If you do,
a word from me will do the trick!
Li Si!
You've got long legs, huh?
There isn't enough space to put them,
so you put them on the table, right?
Good.
Let's put your long legs to good use.
Go mop the floor.
Why are you mopping the floor?
What did you do this time?
Can't you behave for once?
How can you say that?
I'm doing this
purely out of love for the school.
Go on and mop.
Just think of it as exercise.
Pengfei.
T-T-This is Dr. Liu.
Are the results out?
Y-Y-You... well...
Have a seat first. Sit.
Take a seat.
I'll ask him.
-Dr. Liu.
-Dr. Liu
Dr. Liu, please tell me.
How is it?
Does he have colon cancer?
Yes, it's confirmed. It's colon cancer.
The medical resources at our oilfield hospital are limited.
I suggest
you take him to a hospital in a larger city immediately.
Beijing, then?
The cost of cancer treatment
is still quite high.
You need to be mentally prepared.
What are the chances of a cure...
after the surgery?
Colon cancer...
is quite special.
Before detection, there are typically no symptoms.
However, once it is discovered,
the outlook is often not very optimistic.
Based on my assessment,
the chance of surgery curing it is already very low.
It's already in an advanced stage.
The only remaining option
is conservative treatment.
But even that
will only slightly
extend his life for a short period.
How long?
About... three to six months.
Mom?
Mom!
Son, you're back.
What's going on?
Why did my dad
come back so early today?
And he's even cooking.
Your dad didn't have much to do at work today,
so he came back early.
You're back.
You...
You're back, son?
Wash your hands, and let's have dinner.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Did you two fight?
No, I...
No. No.
Something must have happened.
Something big must have happened.
What nonsense are you talking about?
What big thing could've happened?
Hurry up.
Wash your hands, and let's have dinner.
Be good. Try your dad's cooking.
Wait...
Go, son.
Mom!
Go. Go.
Hurry. Be good.
Don't tell the kids
about this.
I'm afraid they won't be able to handle it.
I'll go... go check on Ling.
No, no, don't go.
What will you say to her if you go?
Well...
Could this be a misdiagnosis?
The biopsy
is currently
the most accurate and direct method
for diagnosing colon cancer.
But what is Ling supposed to do?
How can she face it?
Mom, I'm back!
You're back so early.
Come on, son.
This fish is so fresh.
Someone caught it,
and I bought it halfway.
Try my cooking.
I haven't cooked in a long time.
I don't know if my cooking skills are still up to par.
Come on. Come on.
Let me pour you a drink. Here.
Did you make some mistakes?
What mistakes could I have made?
Bai Shuang is here again?
Son, your dad would never
make that kind of mistake.
There's nothing like that going on.
So you must have done something
to upset me then.
Mom,
you two are hiding something from me.
Are you two getting a divorce?
Then, who will I be with?
Silly boy.
Your dad and I will not be getting a divorce.
How could we divorce?
It's okay if she doesn't want to eat it.
Just leave it there.
You eat up.
I've noticed
that Director Xiao's dressing style has changed recently.
Have you seen her hair today?
Those little curls she has.
She's even starting to go for a softer look.
I-I-It's all just a facade.
This afternoon,
she scolded Li Si
and made him
mop the entire hallway.
But honestly, Li Si had it coming.
He kept bragging everywhere
that Fang was his aunt.
He deserved to be scolded.
Cheng Miaomiao!
Can you stop bullying Li Si?
Don't you know
how good Li Si has been to you
all these years?
He's such a good kid.
Can't you be a little nicer to him?
Wait, what did I say?
And you just
gave me a good scolding.
Your mom means...
Well...
Well, you're about to
start 12th grade, right?
After that, you'll have to take the college entrance exams.
Then you two will have to part ways.
You should
b-b-both
treat each other better while you can.
We won't be apart.
He'll go wherever I go.
We have a deal.
It's not like he's had this disease
for just a day or two.
But I didn't notice anything.
What kind of mother am I?
I've failed my son.
I'm a terrible father.
I deserve to die.
Stop saying things like that.
Mom, I'm going to school.
Why haven't you gone to work yet?
To take you to school.
Take me? Why?
Why what?
It's on my way.
I happen to have something to do near your school.
Son,
let us take you to school.
What?
I've long said that, given my temperament,
I deserve the lifestyle
of a young master traveling in a private car.
We can take Miaomiao with us
so that she can ride on my coattails.
Let's go.
Mom, what's for dinner tonight?
You're all here.
Go. Go.
You go to Xiaoshudu Restaurant for dinner.
We're discussing something important here.
Discussing a wedding, right?
Why didn't you include me?
Why isn't my grandma here?
Why are you so nosy?
Go already.
Yaya's already there.
Hurry up and go to eat,
then do your homework.
Well...
Why don't we take Li Si to see a traditional Chinese medicine doctor?
I heard that traditional Chinese medicine can cure cancer.
Hu,
stop crying.
No one's allowed to be sad anymore.
None of us...
should tell Li Si about it.
We have to make him
stay happy during this time.
We have to protect Li Si.
Honey, do you remember?
Don't you remember what the doctor said?
He said that a stable mood
is the key to fighting cancer cells.
We're like undercover agents now.
We can't let anything slip out.
This is a tough battle.
We have to win it,
okay?
Why is this happening to me?
What should we do?
If anyone messes this up,
I'll never speak to them again.
Ling,
are you sure
you want to sell the restaurant?
I'm not sure yet if it's enough.
I'll look for a buyer.
I'm sure we can get a good price.
Who did it?
Me!
Director Xiao, I'm sorry.
I'll be more careful next time.
Director.
What happened
to your uniform?
See? It's all wrinkled.
You're a sprightly young man.
Your hair is getting long too.
Go get it trimmed.
Got it?
Yes, Director.
Be careful
playing in the hallway. Don't fall.
Being in a relationship sure changes people.
She's become so much gentler now.
Come on, Xiaowa.
Let's continue to play.
I'll pick it up.
Hurry.
Let's play, Si.
Let me say it upfront.
It's not that I wanted to come here.
I wanted to come.
Weren't you not allowed me to come here?
I didn't want you to come by yourself,
but you can come here if you bring us along.
I've never played arcade games before.
Xiaowa, have you played those before?
No.
Then I'll...
give a simple demonstration today.
The King of Fighters.
The Arcade King.
Okay!
Hit him. hit him.
Si, go for it. Hit him!
Use your fists. Use your fists!
Beat him, Si!
Isn't it my turn for duty today?
Who did this?
I did.
Why did you clean it for me?
I got it wrong.
I thought it was my turn today.
Have you finished your homework?
Morning!
Si!
You're quite diligent.
Beef buns.
Aren't they good?
It's so cool!
Xiaowa, where did you get it?
I borrowed it from my neighbor.
We should have set sail long ago.
This is so much fun.
Later, you have to teach me how to sail.
Okay.
Why learn to sail?
It's always good to have more skills.
It would be great
if Yuan Shanqing were here.
When she comes back,
let's set sail again.
Okay.
Come on, let me take a photo of you, Si.
Three, two, one.
Good.
One more. Turn around.
A bit to the side. Yes, just like that.
Don't move.
Cool.
Look, the Windward.
Li Si,
didn't you say
you would go wherever I go?
Yes.
Then,
let's never be apart.
Of course!
This promise is valid for a lifetime.
What do you think is on the other side of the sea?
It's...
the outside world.
Then let's go see
the outside world together.
Okay.
The wind is too strong.
Son?
Can Mom come in?
Come in.
Are you doing your homework?
There is so much work.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Son,
y-y-you take a leave from school next week, okay?
Let's go to Beijing.
Why go to Bejing?
Didn't you have a gastroenteroscopy before?
They found a small polyp.
I asked the doctor,
and he advised that it's best to have it removed
to prevent any potential issues in your intestines.
Do I need surgery for it?
Don't be nervous.
It's just a minor problem.
It's just a minor surgery.
Since it's a minor surgery,
just do it here.
Why go all the way to Beijing?
Well, I'm not
so sure
about the surgical standards here.
Doesn't your dad have connections
at a hospital in Beijing?
Besides,
haven't you always
wanted to visit Beijing and see the sights?
Mom,
the final exams are coming up.
At this crucial moment,
I'm working hard on my studies.
What Beijing?
Let's talk about it after the exams.
No, no,
listen to me, son.
Your dad finally has some time off.
Let him take us there.
I want to go too.
Right,
I've got some time off...
this time.
Let's not waste it.
What about your restaurant? Just leave it?
During this time,
I'm really a bit tired.
So, I plan to sell the restaurant.
Honey, you should have
sold your restaurant a long time ago.
Working from early morning to late at night every day.
You even have to serve customers
on New Year's Eve.
Then what will I eat in the future?
I'll cook for you.
Are my current cooking skills not good enough for you?
By the way, I...
I haven't reported a work update
to you.
I...
don't want to work in the drilling team anymore.
One, I'm getting older,
and two, I'm tired.
I... I want to work in an office instead.
Wait...
The changes in our family
are happening so quickly.
Why is no one discussing this with me?
What's there to discuss with you?
Just listen to your mom.
Why don't you go to bed early?
Go to sleep.
-Okay.
Sleep early, son.
We'll let you know when everything is arranged in Beijing.
Right.
Sleep tight, and sweet dreams.
Okay.
Four private rooms,
twelve tables,
and an upscale birthday room inside.
It's usually full every day.
The business is doing very well.
And the feng shui of this place...
Feng shui?
This place attracts wealth and prosperity.
But I heard...
Are you done?
Why are you being so mysterious?
It's done. It's done.
Why are you always rushing everything?
Give me your hand.
What is this?
Why are you practicing superstitions
like my mom?
It's not superstitious.
I braided them myself.
One for each of us.
What do you think? Little bells?
You can braid?
It's pretty.
I like this kind of
matching things,
radiating good luck.
Right?
What happened?
Our son is missing.
Dad.
Mom.
I don't know
how to say these things to you,
so I can only use this method.
From the moment
you all started being nice to me,
I knew
that something must have happened.
You didn't hide the test report well.
I've found it.
I know it's all too late.
I also know
that you all want me
to live my final days happily.
You've worked so hard,
and I certainly can't let you down.
Although I'm not capable of something big,
I've always been
the best at playing dumb.
Watching the game?
You must be tired today, right?
I'm fine.
What would you like for dinner?
I'll cook for you.
I’m fine with anything.
Morning!
Si.
Beef buns.
Aren't they good?
Who did it?
Me!
What happened
to your uniform?
It's all wrinkled.
Isn't it my turn for duty today?
I got it wrong.
I thought it was my turn today.
Mom!
You're back, son?
Come on. Come here.
I just went shopping with your dad
and saw this shirt.
I thought you would look so cool
wearing it.
Do you like it?
Yes. Yes.
Why did you buy so many?
Right, and this pair of sneakers
that you like.
Feiyue. Didn't you
always want them?
They happen to have your size.
Come on. Try them on.
Thank you, Mom!
You're welcome, son.
It's delicious.
I forgot about the game.
You're not as good as me in this show.
I think if I were to apply
to a film academy,
I'd definitely be accepted.
I could make everyone laugh
on the big screen.
I've always been
the carefree one.
Awesome! Awesome!
But maybe
I'm good at performing in front of the audience,
but facing you all,
I know I can't keep it up much longer.
Mom.
When I heard
that you were going to sell the Xiaoshudu Restaurant,
I knew
that I didn't have much longer to live.
I'm sorry.
I've always
made you worry since childhood.
I haven't accomplished much either.
And I've sold
a lot of valuable things from home.
So, I spread the news
that the feng shui of Xiaoshudu Restaurant is bad.
Slow down. Don't go.
Man, who told you that?
It's pure rumor.
If the feng shui here were bad,
could the business still be this good?
Would you sell it if the business is so good?
It's because the owner is
moving to another place.
No.
Sir,
if it's about the price,
we can discuss it.
No need to discuss it.
I...
Sir!
Anyway, I'm not that smart.
Mom,
my illness can't be cured.
Save the money
and live well with Dad.
You two have a long life ahead of you.
Dad,
over the years, you and I
have had a rather strained relationship.
I've hated you at times,
but I really do love you.
This is the first time I've seen you cry for me
because of my illness.
I secretly read
your work diary.
You even wrote about me.
Today, my son is 100 days old.
He's as chubby
as I was when I was little.
My son's birthday is coming.
He asked me to buy him a plane.
That little brat.
Today was my son's first time performing on the stage.
He wet his pants.
Useless kid.
My son is going to school.
His mom and I invited a Wenquxing for him.
I hope he can study hard.
My son's teacher
called me to the school again today.
I couldn't hold back
and beat him up when I came back.
I regretted it immediately.
Will he hate me
when he grows up?
My son wishes
to marry Miaomiao in the future on his birthday.
Good for him.
May his wish come true.
God,
can I exchange my life
for my son's?
I can't bear to leave you two.
I also can't bear to leave
my friends.
Hu.
You must visit Hong Kong once
and take a photo of
Central Crossroads for me.
Xiaowa,
do you remember?
The task I gave you
when I went to see you?
During the time I'm not here,
you must help me
take good care of them,
especially Miaomiao.
Discipline her.
I hope
that when I come back from Beijing,
she can appear in front of me
with a new look.
This is the task I'm giving you.
Yaya,
take good care of your sister for me.
Shanqing will be fine.
I'll bless her for you.
Miaomiao,
you're scared, aren't you?
You cried a lot, right?
You're finally afraid that I might leave you, right?
I've only ever had one wish
since childhood.
To marry you when I grow up.
I have to break my promise this time.
I can't accompany you
to the places you want to go.
I also can't marry you.
But remember,
in this lifetime,
you'll always have me.
When I'm alive, I can beat up
anyone who bullies you.
When I'm dead,
if anyone dares to bully you,
I'll haunt them as a ghost.
I'm taking this bell with me.
This is the first time I'm worshiping you.
If...
there really were gods in this world,
please
bless my parents.
Since God
has given me this fate,
it's no big deal.
It's just leaving a bit earlier.
My illness
can't be cured.
But I won't
accept this fate.
I want to decide
when I leave this world myself.
I don't want you to
see me tortured by illness,
and I don't want everyone
to cry for me.
That's not like me.
Dad, Mom, my friends,
uncles, aunties,
Baoshan, and Fang,
please remember me
as carefree and untroubled.
Don't be sad, everyone.
Let's just
say goodbye happily.
I love you all...
forever.
Go to my place to eat ribs.
My dad's already made them.
I don't want to eat!
Come on.
My mom's waiting for me to grill fish at home.
I'm off.
Cheng Miaomiao!
Next time, I'll come for ribs.
If...
time could be rewound,
I wish
none of this had ever happened.
If...
there really were gods in this world,
I'd hope that you'd bless Li Si
so that in another world,
he'd never get angry again.
If...
Couldn't we have just
stayed in the oilfield forever
and never been apart?
Yuan Shanqing's killing Yuan Yong
was ultimately ruled as self-defense.
The day she was released,
Yaya went early to wait for her.
In this bittersweet story,
no one treated our youth kindly.
We had
a farewell that was far from complete.
We all thought
that we'd become great people when we grew up.
But before we could grow up,
life's harshness
caught us off guard.
I remember
every event from that year.
Remember every face from my youth.
Li Si...
Li Si is gone.
And with him...
our youth ended.