[Wind Direction]
[Episode 14]
[Winter of 1994]
We could just sleep together gently.
We're here?
We've arrived at my place.
Xiu.
I really love you.
You know that, right?
Who is it?
My daughter.
She's older than I expected.
So what?
She's useless, just a burden.
Why are the lights off?
Turn them on!
Please.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What?
The sofa's sagging!
You broke our sofa.
You have to pay for it.
How?
How should I pay?
You tell me.
I'm thirsty.
Get us some water.
My sofa is expensive.
I want a drink.
Do you have any?
Call her "Aunt."
Are you mute?
No need!
Are you drunk and acting crazy?
You're scaring me!
I'm leaving!
Don't go, please.
Don't be afraid.
Get back to your homework.
You're nuts.
What's this?
Chicken soup.
Why does it smell so bad?
Your dad still isn't back?
It's been three days since the baby was born.
Where did he go?
Check the drawer—
see if the money is still there.
Is it?
Gone.
Page 224.
Tell him someone in the family died,
and he needs to come home immediately.
Yes.
The last name is Lin.
Call him 50 times!
Can you stop crying?
Cry, cry, cry!
Is that all you know how to do?
Enough! Stop crying.
Don't cry.
It's okay.
I wouldn't be in this situation
if it weren't for you.
Don't cry.
I'm so tired.
I'm sorry.
Zi, don't cry.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry.
[The Seabird]
Zi had a fever
for three whole days,
almost didn't make it.
Lin Xiu went to look for Yuan Yong,
and they didn't come back
for half a month.
Yuan Yong somehow
got a car,
and they started scamming people
for money.
They never
cared about Zi.
In fact, because she was a girl,
they even wanted to sell her.
Back then, I was too afraid to go to school.
I just held onto Zi and hid.
Later, when Yuan Yong got into trouble,
we lost our house.
I sat with Zi
outside the office building
for three days
until a manager came out
and gave us
our current place to stay.
That's how we survived.
Sometimes I think,
it's a good thing Yuan Yong and Lin Xiu
ran into trouble and left.
Otherwise, Zi and I
wouldn't have made it.
Mom.
Zi seems a bit tired.
I'll take her inside to sleep for a bit.
Go ahead, go ahead.
So, do you know
where your dad kept the money?
Don't...
Why bring that up?
I just want to get a sense of things.
That way, I can tell the police when the time comes.
Yuan Yong
hid a metal box at home
with some money in it.
He didn't have time to take it when he left.
But I already told the police,
and I handed over the money—
over 10,000 yuan.
He scammed tens of thousands, though.
I don't know where the rest of the money is.
He hasn't come back to look for me since.
He wouldn't dare.
He'd be arrested as soon as he showed up.
People like that
are infuriating.
They don't just
both of them are bad.
They even
ruin their own children.
They should
be shot.
Why are you saying this
in front of the kids?
She's old enough
to know exactly
what kind of person Yuan Yong is.
Mom,
she really loves that...
Keep an eye on her.
She's asleep.
She's asleep?
Well...
Since Zi's fever last time,
has anything changed?
She seems to sleep more now
and doesn't cry as much.
I even think she's grown more mature.
Uncle Cheng,
is it because of
that fever
that her hearing got damaged?
She used to respond when I called her.
It's possible.
It's all my fault.
If only I had come back
earlier that day.
No, no.
Maybe if she hadn't been caught in the rain,
things would've been different.
Shanqing, calm down.
How about this?
I'll arrange
a more thorough check-up for her.
Dad.
Can she be cured?
Treatment takes time;
it's not something that happens overnight.
We need to be patient,
with gradual tests
and treatment.
Yes.
Shanqing, don't worry.
My dad is the best
ENT specialist here.
He even cured
the factory manager's hearing.
Zi will be fine for sure.
Yeah, he even helped
an 80-year-old lady
hear again.
Zi will definitely be fine,
right?
Don't worry about it.
People say it's karma,
but it's clearly their fault.
Why does Zi have to suffer?
She didn't do anything wrong.
Why is life
so unfair?
Shanqing, life is like this.
Sometimes it's smooth,
and sometimes we hit rough patches.
But when we're in the tough times,
we can't give up.
Once this difficult time passes,
things will get better.
They'll definitely
be caught by the police.
Zi will recover.
Everything will turn out fine for you both.
Everything will be fine.
Back then, when Yuan Yong
got drunk,
he would come home and hit my mom.
My mom always said,
"Family shame shouldn't be exposed."
She was afraid of the humiliation,
afraid that others would look down on us,
so she endured it.
I was too young at the time,
and there wasn't anything I could do.
The saddest part is that my mom
never had a single good day.
It's all in the past now.
Do you know
what my biggest regret is?
What?
I don't even know
where my mom is buried.
Every time I mentioned her, Yuan Yong would beat me.
This is the first time I've ever talked about it.
Did I scare you?
No,
I just don't know
how to comfort you.
What's there to comfort?
It's all in the past.
What's most important
to me now is Zi.
No matter what the cost,
I'm going to make sure she gets better.
Zi,
let's go home.
Let's go.
I'm really fine.
Take it slow, Mom.
Slow down, slow down.
Why didn't you
turn off the lights?
They've been on for so long—
-what a waste of electricity.
-I forgot.
-Why didn't you...
Min, change your shoes.
-Change shoes.
-Okay.
The lights
have been on for days.
Think about how much that costs.
While I'm not home,
you've turned the house
into a mess.
How long has this food been left out?
And why isn't anything
cleaned up after meals?
Let me handle it.
Why didn't you clean it up?
Give it to me.
Can you take a rest?
You just got discharged.
Look at the house!
Dirty socks
thrown everywhere.
-Mom. Mom.
-Can you just
-put away...
-Mom.
Let me do it.
-Let me.
-Can't you…
-These things...
-Give them to me.
Help your mom
sit down.
-Give them to me.
-Just put the socks
and dirty clothes
in the washing machine.
Mom, sit down.
There's more.
There's another one.
Socks over there too!
-Let me handle it.
-Hurry up.
What happened to your foot, Li Si?
Nothing.
Be careful.
You too.
Are crutches necessary?
I thought if I made it look worse,
my mom would let me take the day off.
But even that didn't work out.
What should I do?
I guess I'm going to
school on crutches—
strong will despite the injury!
Didn't you try something
like this last time
and get nothing out of it?
Last time?
Which time?
Don't mention it.
Oh my!
Okay, okay.
You've always been resilient.
Impressive.
I have to say,
you're the best.
You even came to pick me up.
Of course.
Can you carry my backpack for me?
Are your arms broken too?
No.
You can carry it yourself.
Just letting you know,
I'm leaving
as soon as class begins.
No one's waiting for you.
Alright, Si,
let's see if you can run.
Take big steps, come on!
Take bigger steps.
Come on.
Okay.
Come on, run!
Great job!
This was written by Yuan Shanqing?
Yes.
Her writing skills are impressive!
I never thought
she had such talent.
I was always worried
that this kid would be affected emotionally.
But lately,
I've noticed a change in her.
She's more confident now
and even took the initiative
to participate in the poetry contest.
And her classmates
aren't targeting her as much anymore.
There's finally some peace in our class.
I think we've done a pretty good job this time.
Yuan Shanqing.
We're not the ones
who helped her.
I don't have a problem with him.
I was just worried it would affect the class.
Can't we at least give him a chance?
We're all in the same class, after all.
Right.
We're teaching him Mandarin.
But you two
have been arguing with me
about him
for so long,
and he hasn't even spoken up yet.
Qiang Xiaowa,
come on, tell the class monitor what you think.
Do you have the confidence
for this poetry reading competition?
It's just a poetry reading competition.
Why are we making such a big deal out of it?
Come on, say it.
Qiang Xiaowa, think carefully.
This is a group competition,
and if you participate,
you better not drag the class down.
I won't drag anyone down.
Did you hear that?
Look at his Mandarin—
there's an improvement, right?
Everyone says a line,
no problem at all.
Are you the one to decide?
I'm telling you,
if he messes this up,
it's not just
your reputation on the line.
Wa.
People can live here?
It's already much better now.
When I was a kid, we didn't even have electricity.
This is my first time
on this side of the bridge.
It's completely different from where we're from.
I think this place
is better than ours.
Look at the air,
the sea breeze—
it's refreshing!
Hu, quick, take a picture for me.
Okay.
Move a little this way
so I can get the sunset
-right in the photo.
-Here?
Move a bit more.
Here?
A little bit more this way.
Perfect with the sunlight.
Be careful.
The water's deep.
This picture's going to look amazing
once it's developed—
hero saving the beauty at sunset!
-What are you doing?
-Let's take another photo.
Are we here for photos?
Aren't we here to practice Mandarin?
Repeat after me.
The Song of Youth!
The sung of youth.
The sung of youth?
Sung?
The sung of youth.
The sung of youth?
You were once a seed.
Buried in the soil.
Waiting quietly to sprout.
-Whiting...
-Waiting.
-Waiting!
Waiting!
We're actually quite lucky.
First,
we've ruled out
any intellectual disabilities for Zi.
Now, we've also ruled out
congenital deafness.
We've confirmed that
she has sensorineural hearing loss.
Does that mean
Zi will be
deaf and mute from now on?
No, that won't happen.
We can install a small device
in Zi's ear,
and she'll be able to hear
like a normal person.
What kind of device?
It's called a cochlear implant.
This cochlear implant
works by
implanting Zi
an electrode system
that stimulates her auditory nerve,
thereby restoring her hearing.
There have already been
successful cases of this
in our country.
Dinner's ready.
Thank you.
Everything's fresh,
just caught today.
What about Grandpa? Should we wait for him?
Grandpa's busy.
No need to wait.
You can start eating.
Alright,
let's see how fresh it is.
Delicious.
Tastes better than my mom's cooking!
Xiaowa,
can I ask you something?
When I leave,
could you pack me
some dried fish to take home?
I want my mom to try some.
Sure!
I'll pack some for each of you
to take back later.
Thank you.
Xiaowa,
do people here
only eat this stuff?
What are you saying?
It's not like we don't have rice.
We have rice,
but it's not as abundant as it is for you.
After all, we live in a fishing village,
and most people here
don't have a stable income.
So how do you all
survive?
We live off the sea—
selling seafood.
But if there's a storm
and we can't fish,
we don't make a single penny.
Oh my god, that's so unpredictable.
Where do kids here
go to school?
School? We haven't had
a school here in ages.
I had to go to the town
to study.
I'm the only one left from here
still in school.
What about the other kids?
The boys
go out to sea to fish.
Some have gone off to find work elsewhere.
That's so unfortunate.
I used to
be envious of people
born in big cities.
I thought our oilfield base
didn't even have a decent shopping mall.
But seeing how they live,
I realize just
how lucky we are.
I still want to
see the world outside, though.
Then study hard.
With the grades you're getting now,
where do you think you'll end up?
Do you think
we've inherited
different kinds of genes?
How come your grades are so good,
and mine are always failing?
One word: lazy.
If you're lazy, don't blame it on genetics!
Start by not being lazy
when you're dumping out the foot-washing water!
I'm talking about studying,
and you're talking about foot-washing water?
Cheng Yaya, dump it yourself.
I'm not doing it.
The outside world is wonderful.
I'll stay here
and sincerely wish you the best.
Zi,
we'll be able to
hear soon.
Let's work hard together, okay?
Courage is a precious asset.
[Class 2, Grade 11]
Courage is a pricious...
Precious.
Precious asset.
Let us sail forward with courage.
To never fail our dreams.
This is the best form of youth.
Applause.
I'll wipe the top later;
this windowsill is a bit high. I'm afraid you might—
Luo Zheng,
can I use your water?
Are they talking now?
Thank you.
What's going on with you two?
Have you made peace?
We didn't make peace.
She just washed a cloth.
Go back to work.
Alright.
Don't peek.
No, I...
I can't figure out
this problem. It's so hard.
Can you help me?
Which one?
This one.
Wait.
I think your previous solution
was wrong.
Here, I redid it.
Doesn't this make more sense?
Aren't you explaining it?
You've been working for a while—
take a break, kids.
Take a break, kids.
-Thank you, Grandpa.
-Have some dried fish.
Have some dried fish.
Girl, why don't you eat?
Grandpa, I'll eat later.
Grandpa.
Don't worry about her.
She's too focused on her studies to eat.
I'll eat enough for everyone.
Okay.
Eat more then.
I'm happy you're here.
We don't have much,
but if you like the dried fish,
there's plenty more.
Plenty.
Oh right,
I'm making fish porridge.
Kids,
we'll have pancakes today!
-Okay.
-Grandpa, you don't need to fuss.
We'll need to go back after we finish these problems,
or we'll get scolded if we're too late.
No, no,
stay and eat
before you go.
Eat before you leave.
Have some.
It's really good.
Babao. I'll teach you.
One for you and one for me.
Do your homework.
Yours is more detailed than mine.
You...
Why do you keep bringing
these things home all the time?
Qiang Xiaowa's place.
We often go there.
His grandpa always
gives us these delicious things.
Don't just take their stuff.
Next time, if they need anything,
give them something from our place in return.
What do we have to give?
Dad,
can we give them some medicinal patches
for his grandpa's leg and back pain?
Sure,
some medicine as well.
It's hard for them to get medicine over there.
Dad.
What about...
Try this.
What's this?
Dried fish.
It's sweet. Is it good?
Yes.
Dad, how's the information
about the cochlear implant coming along?
My comrades and I have sent out letters.
We're just waiting for a response.
Great.
My comrade
mentioned a girl
with a similar condition
to Zi,
and her surgery was very successful.
So,
Zi's surgery
should go smoothly too.
That's amazing!
-Great!
-This silly kid.
Uncle Cheng.
Where is this hospital?
In Beijing.
My comrade
is reaching out to them.
How much
will the surgery cost?
Dad, just tell us directly.
It'll probably cost around 100,000 yuan.
100,000?
Yes,
but given Zi's situation,
we can apply for special financial aid
from the Children's Foundation.
If that's approved,
we would only need to
cover about 50,000 yuan ourselves.
50,000...
Honestly, I've never really resigned myself to fate.
I always believed that
as long as I didn't give up,
I could push through anything.
But tell me—
does heaven
have it out for me or something?
No matter how hard I try,
it seems like bad things keep happening.
My grandma used to pray to Guanyin a lot.
She'd chant prayers every day,
asking heaven to bless us.
So, when I was little,
I thought she was so superstitious,
always messing around with deities and spirits.
I wanted her
to give it up
and believe in science instead.
But later,
when I grew up,
I asked her one day,
"Grandma,
where is heaven anyway?
What can it really protect us from?"
You know what she said?
She said, "Silly child,
you've been going to school so long it's made you dumb.
There is no heaven.
I just give myself something to hold onto.
I believe that
as long as I think someone up there is protecting us,
it keeps my spirit strong.
You see,
everyone faces tough times.
Sometimes even drinking water
feels like a struggle.
But
you can't let that struggle
defeat you.
Having something to believe in
gives you the strength to think
that this trouble can be solved,
and things will get better."
Wow, so many mistakes!
-Who?
-Zhong Ruitao.
Director.
Are you eating?
Director Xiao.
Hello, Director Xiao.
Director.
This is mine.
Ms. Han, thank you.
Okay.
Director Xiao,
your current image
[Donation Box]
has reached new heights in my eyes.
I'm not that great.
It's more about having the right mindset.
Absolutely! Absolutely!
Director Xiao.
Mine.
Okay.
Thank you.
Zheng Weiwei, five yuan.
Wu Ziyi, 2.3 yuan.
Thanks.
Wang Fuqiang, 15.
Cheng.
This is all I've got left for the month.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Zhong Ruitao, 20.
Li Jun, ten yuan.
Five yuan.
Thank you.
Guo Xiao, five yuan.
What are you looking at?
Do you think it's too little?
No.
Thank you.
Will the surgery
make her able to hear again?
Yes.
That's good.
This donation
is not only for one person,
not just for Yuan Shanqing,
but for the cohesion
of our entire group.
Here,
as the Director of Teaching,
I, Xiao Fang,
make a promise to everyone:
As long as you are
a part of Linqi No. 2 High School,
no matter who faces difficulties,
our school will
always lend a helping hand,
without hesitation.
Can everyone commit to this?
-Yes!
There is true kindness in the world.
There is true love in the world.
Thousands of small families
unite to form
the big family of Linqi Oilfield.
When one person faces hardship, help comes from all directions.
This is the promise Linqi Oilfield makes
to all its people.
We call on everyone
to offer your love
and do what you can
to support Yuan Shanqing.
Dear teachers
[Letter of thanks]
and fellow students,
Hello, everyone.
I am Yuan Shanqing from Class 1, Grade 10.
In the past few days,
I've received donations and encouragement
from the teachers, students, and people of the oilfield.
I am incredibly touched by your kindness.
Thank you for every penny
you've donated
and every word of comfort
you've shared for my sister, Yuan Shanzi.
Both Shanzi and I
will always remember
your kindness
and the love you've shown us.
I promise to work twice as hard,
and one day,
I will repay Linqi Oilfield
and our school.
Once again, I express my deepest gratitude
to each and every one of you.
Thank you for your kindness,
and I wish you all good health
and happiness.
Yuan Shanqing.
Now, I have an announcement to make.
For this poetry reading contest,
one student's poem
stood out to me
as exceptionally well-written.
So I've decided
to use this student's poem
as our class's entry,
and this student will lead the recitation.
Let's quiet down for a moment.
I'm sure you're all curious
about who it is, right?
Yes.
Yuan Shanqing.
Congratulations.
[Linqi No. 2 High School Red October Poetry Reading Contest]
Adjust the angle.
Hey, students over there.
Move forward, move forward.
The one in the middle.
Move forward. Move forward.
That sign needs to be aligned as well.
Smooth out the tablecloth.
Adjust the lighting over there.
Don't flinch. Don't be nervous.
You look so great like this!
Teacher, give him a bit more makeup.
Okay.
This color is better.
Enough. Enough.
Alright.
Next one.
Here.
Great.
Next.
Lipstick.
Don't be nervous.
Here.
My face was stung...
This color is so beautiful.
This is good.
Teacher, easy, easy.
Here.
-Line up in the back.
-Next one.
T-teacher,
I-I want to try something.
The Eye of Soul.
What is the Eye of Soul?
Give it to me.
Good.
-Your turn.
-Do I look good?
What about you?
Well...
Don't hide.
Qiang Xiaowa,
everyone has to wear makeup.
Why are you trying to hide?
Come on,
come on, don't be shy.
-Well.
-Come on.
When we were kids,
I understood why we painted red cheeks for Children's Day.
But why are we still doing it now?
Done.
I look the best.
Students,
how's the preparation going?
Please enjoy
a poetry reading
from Class 1, Grade 11:
The Song of Youth.
Led by Cheng Miaomiao.
You were once a seed
buried in the soil,
1uietly waiting to sprout.
The first spring rain
brought you your first hope for life.
-Ms. Han.
Hello, Ms. Han.
Don't be nervous.
Just look it over a few more times.
Lead the reading well, good luck!
Youth is like a song,
resonating in our hearts.
Youth is like a poem,
full of passion,
and words overflowing with energy.
The flowing notes
etch the light of life
on the walls of time
with an unfeeling brushstroke.
Dreams stir within us.
Courage is a precious asset.
Let us sail forward with courage,
for only by staying true to our ideals
can we truly embody the best of youth.
Let us spread the wings of our youth,
and rise with the wind.
Good.
Guys, hurry up.
Did I do alright just now?
Yes!
Thank you.
Why hasn't your brother's class
gone on yet?
They are here.
-Now, please enjoy
-Get ready to applaud.
the poetry reading
by Class 1, Grade 10:
The Seabird,
led by Yuan Shanqing.
Wait,
why don't they have red cheeks?
Shh, don't talk, it's starting.
So what if they don't?
The Seabird.
Migration
is the destiny of the Arctic Tern.
When winter arrives,
they begin their long journey,
skimming over waves,
crossing the equator,
and flying southward,
from the northern hemisphere
to the warmth of the southern hemisphere.
Every migration
is an 18,000-kilometer journey.
Every journey
is the fiery passage from winter to summer.
Every fiery passage
is the greatness of a small life that never stops.
Our lives
have never been calm waters.
Passing through thorns.
The young cross mountains and seas,
passing through thorns.
Along the way, they plant flowers.
They clear stones on the mountainsides.
They raise sails in rushing rivers.
They no longer look back in the mud.
Do you remember
those youngsters who clenched their fists and said,
"When I grow up,
I will forge ahead,
like the first seabird,
spreading my trembling wings."
The seabirds gather in the south.
We will finally reunite
in a sea of flowers in the high mountains.
The spring breeze, oblivious to its own charm,
stirs the hearts of the young.
Summer generously extends the day,
warming the love of the seabird.
A seabird is still a seabird,
unafraid of thunder and rain,
undeterred by distance.
A youth is still a youth,
like wild grass in the wasteland,
the midsummer in their hearts cannot be cut down.
Oh, wind and rain,
please be kind to every
flying seabird.
Oh, youth,
please be kind to those young and bold days.
May you soar freely,
brave and free like the seabird.
You shout.
Sit down.
Okay.
Bravo! Bravo!
I will now announce the results of the competition.
First prize in the Linqi Second High School's
Red October Poetry Reading Competition goes to…
Class 1, Grade 10,
for "The Seabird."
Back then, when we were young,
we always shouted slogans,
filled with ideals,
yearning to fly free.
We wanted to break through
all the obstacles
and dreamed of the world beyond.
But I forgot
that this small base was home.
At 17, we thought
we were already grown up,
mature,
that we understood love,
understood the future,
understood the migration of the seabird.
Later,
I really did see many,
many seabirds flying across the ocean.
But at that moment,
what I missed most was
that day,
when everyone had their faces painted red,
like actors in a play.