My mom's name is Gao Xiaojuan.
This is the only photo
she took
and the only thing
she left to me.
You smile like your mother.
I was clingy to my mom when I was young.
When she was around,
it was
the happiest time of my life.
Our family was poor when I was young,
but no matter how poor we were,
she would save money to buy me candy.
In the winter, when there was no heating at home,
she would use her body
to warm up the bed
and place my hands and feet
on her belly.
When she was around,
I never suffered a beating
from Yuan Yong.
She would always shield me
with her body,
then, covered in bruises, she'd tell me,
"It doesn't hurt."
She was truly the kindest person
I've ever known.
I wish she were still here.
Shanqing.
It's all in the past.
Your mom surely wants us
to live well.
I'm certain that's what she would have wanted.
I believe things will get better
from here.
I have seen on TV,
that you can visit her
and talk through the glass on the phone.
Do you even have any common sense?
Right now, she's in a detention center.
You can't visit anyone in a detention center.
You have to wait until they're sentenced
and sent to prison before visits are allowed.
Yaya, that's not what I meant.
I just want to explain to Li Si.
Shanqing was just fighting against bad people.
She won't go to jail.
Yes, the law is strict now.
The police will find out the truth.
They won't wrong an innocent person.
When my brother was working before,
one of his bosses was also taken in.
But after everything was cleared up,
they released him.
Don't worry.
It'll be fine.
Right now, only the lawyer can visit.
My dad has gone to find a lawyer,
but we still don't know
what's going on.
So don't think about
things that haven't happened yet.
Shanqing
will come back safely.
I'm glad Zi is still young.
She doesn't know anything.
When she grows up
and learns about all of this,
she'll be so heartbroken.
How will she face it?
Shanqing said
not to let Zi know.
But that would mean leaving the Oilfield.
No matter what,
I hope Zi
never finds out about any of this.
We found this knife at the scene.
After forensic examination,
the fingerprints of three people were found on it.
They are Yuan Yong,
Yuan Shanqing and Cheng Yaya.
As for the bloodstains on the ground,
after DNA comparison
by the Provincial Criminal Investigation Department,
they belong to Yuan Yong and Cheng Yaya.
Yuan Yong was stabbed five times in total,
once in the back of the left shoulder,
once in the left upper abdomen, and three times in the chest.
According to Yuan Shanqing's testimony,
she first stabbed Yuan Yong
from behind,
but forensic examination
showed that this stab did not damage any organs.
The stab to the left upper abdomen
was the fatal wound,
as it caused the spleen to rupture.
However, at the time,
Yuan Yong had his hands around her neck,
and her actions were purely a reflexive response.
I believe
this falls under the category of self-defense.
However, those three additional stabs
came after Yuan Yong
had already been restrained by Cheng Yaya,
losing his ability to resist.
Yuan Shanqing then came over and stabbed three more times.
This was due to
the provocation of Yuan Yong's threats,
which caused Yuan Shanqing to lose emotional control.
Alright, let's set aside
the emotional factors for now.
Based on the current information,
Yuan Shanqing had the motive to kill
and carried out actions
that directly resulted in
Yuan Yong's death.
This can be determined
as a suspected case of intentional homicide.
Chief Wang.
Look.
According to the autopsy report,
the cause of death
was a ruptured spleen
caused by a stab.
This was the result of
Yuan Shanqing's second stab
during her act of self-defense.
As for the three additional stabs
she delivered in her emotional outburst,
all of them struck the sternum.
This means that
even if Yuan Shanqing
had not delivered those three stabs,
Yuan Yong's death
would not have
been significantly affected.
What do you think?
So it can still be considered
self-defense, right?
Well, the final determination
will depend on the review results
from the Procuratorate.
Let's not form any biases.
I believe
the law will give Yuan Shanqing
a fair and objective outcome.
Okay, let's end the meeting.
Coming.
Pengfei, why would you
hide such a big thing from me?
Well, I thought
if I told you,
it would only make you upset,
and there's nothing you could do about it.
What's wrong with you?
Don't look at me. I'm fine.
Here is the situation.
Yaya,
although injured,
doesn't have any serious issues.
He just needs to rest and recover.
But as for Yuan Shanqing,
the police took her away.
Why?
She was suspected of intentional homicide.
Are you kidding me?
She's such a good kid.
How could she be accused of intentional murder?
Besides, she only killed Yuan Yong.
Isn't that a form of justice?
Well,
how the law defines it
isn't up to us.
Right.
Most importantly,
the kid is still in custody
and no one is allowed to see her.
The detention center?
I have a friend
who's a very good lawyer.
I'll get in touch with him for help.
I'm calling him now.
I'll get you some water.
Put on some tea, it tastes bland.
Mr. Jin.
Hello, this is
Dahai from the Oilfield.
What malva nut?
Li Dahai from the No. 2 Factory.
Is she asleep?
Let's buy a small bed for her
in the next couple of days.
I'm always worried about
accidentally pressing on her while sleeping at night.
Okay.
It seems like
we're back to when Miaomiao and Yaya were little.
Mom.
Does Zi need to sleep with me?
I'll set up the bed
below.
Once you touch the pillow, you sleep so soundly
that I can't wake you up at all.
What if this kid
needs to pee
or something?
Do you think taking care of a child is that easy?
You just go to sleep.
You still have classes during the day.
That's right. You can't take care of her.
Dad.
Will Yuan Shanqing
really go to jail?
We're neither police
nor judges.
What will happen to Yuan Shanqing
is uncertain,
and we can't control the outcome.
So that means
she's very likely to go to jail,
right?
Stop talking about this here.
What if Yaya hears it?
I know.
I just came over to ask quietly.
If Yuan Shanqing really goes to jail,
will you
let Zi stay here?
Tell her.
This...
This can't change.
Before Shanqing left,
I promised her.
As an adult,
I can't go back on my word
like a child,
right?
Anyway, if anything happens to Shanqing,
Zi will stay with us.
Mom,
you are really a good person.
What good person?
I'm just an ordinary person.
If this situation doesn't happen, then it's fine,
but if it does, I can't just push it away.
The child hasn't done anything wrong.
I know you and Yaya
are really concerned about this.
Your mom and I
have already discussed it.
What your mom just said is right.
No matter how many mistakes there are,
Zi isn't at fault.
She shouldn't have to bear these burdens.
But we agreed that
all these complicated matters
should not be known to Zi.
We want Zi to grow up well
in our home.
Yaya and I are so blissful.
How could we have
such wonderful parents like you?
Mom.
Mom, from now on,
I won't say anything bad about you anymore.
You're an angel, a great angel.
When I scold you,
I become a demon again.
Alright.
Let's not talk about this.
Let's take good care of Zi
so that Yaya will feel better.
By this time next year,
this banner
will be hung for us.
So if we think about it,
aren't we just counting down
for about 300 days?
What's the point of hanging this thing?
It's a jinx.
Excuse me.
May I use this stool?
Thank you.
This is hung for the 12th grade.
What are you pulling this down for?
I don't believe any 12th-grade
would be happy to see this.
The pressure is already so high.
Hanging this thing is really annoying.
Li Si.
This is not a small matter,
nor is it accidental.
This is the result of your class
being consistently so lax
and unmotivated.
You guys
are truly the worst ones...
You've ever taught.
No,
you're the most disappointing ones.
In other classes, it's just one bad apple,
but in your class,
it's like a whole pot of bad apples.
Li Si, tell me.
Why did you pull down the banner?
I think it's a jinx.
What? A jinx?
Why is it a jinx?
Stand up and tell everyone.
I feel like that thing
isn't counting down
to the exam
but counting down to
when we'll have to part ways.
Wait, who can stay with you
forever?
Even if your parents get married,
they can't take you with them forever.
Why can't they take me with them forever?
Don't you grow up?
You're already 18
and still thinking about living off others
and having fun.
Do you all think the No. 2 High School
will always protect you,
and that your parents will always support you?
Is that right?
What about your ideals? Your ambitions?
Youths should aim for great heights.
You are going to take the college entrance exam.
In another year,
you'll be facing
your first battlefield in life.
What is the college entrance exam?
It's a watershed moment in life.
Time is tight, and the tasks are heavy.
If you don't have a plan now,
you'll face defeat.
I have a plan.
Your plan is not important.
Sit down.
I can see that Zhu Chao
has already understood.
Come on, class monitor, stand up
and loudly tell everyone
what university you want to attend.
My mom said,
as long as it's a university, it's fine.
Sit down.
Wei Xue, stand up.
Tell us
what your goal is.
My dad says accounting is good.
Once you have the certification, it's a stable job.
Yes.
Do you hear that?
Sit.
Hu Qiumin, what about you?
What's your goal?
I want to go find my brother.
Does your brother own a university?
My brother is in university, and he's in Shenzhen.
I'll apply
to my brother's university.
If my scores aren't enough,
I'll just find any university
in Shenzhen.
My goal is very clear.
Then you need to make your goal
even clearer,
understand?
You can't leave yourself an escape route.
Don't settle for second best.
Since you already have a goal,
you should put all your effort into achieving it.
Understand?
Sit.
Miaomiao.
You have
a hundred ideals.
Tell me
what your current thoughts are.
I want to be an actress.
I want to apply to a film academy.
Me too.
Do you know what people
in a film academy do?
They act in movies in Beijing.
You didn't bring your keys again.
You really don't take my leg
seriously.
I knew it.
Can you remember to bring your keys in the future?
Wait a minute.
Come on.
Dad.
Why didn't you tell me
you'd come back?
So much has happened at home.
You didn't tell me either.
This isn't exactly a big deal for me.
Besides,
you are preparing for the postgraduate entrance exam.
I didn't want to make things complicated
and cost you money.
You're already in a wheelchair,
and you still call this not a big deal?
Dad,
do you think that
if you don't tell me,
I'll know nothing?
Recently, when I called home,
I found it strange,
so I
called your workplace.
Sure enough.
Do you still treat me as a child?
Or in your eyes,
am I already an outsider?
How can you say that?
Who treats you as an outsider?
Does it help if I tell you?
Are you a doctor?
I'm not a doctor.
But I'm your son.
You and Aunt Yue
always say we're a family,
but when something happens in this family,
I'm the first one kept in the dark.
Does this feel like a family?
Also,
did Aunt Yue forget the things
she said to me
during the Chinese New Year?
I asked so many times
if something happened at home.
Did something happen?
Why didn't she tell me?
You can't blame Aunt Yue for this.
I was the one who didn't let her say anything.
By the way,
there's something else
I need to tell you.
I've already divorced your Aunt Yue,
and we separated before the injury.
Brother.
You're back.
Can you act in movies at this school?
Yes, you can not only act in movies,
but you can also perform skits.
I'm mainly aiming
to perform skits.
If you're doing skits,
that should fall under the category of drama.
You should join a theater troupe.
She won't succeed no matter where she goes.
Do you think it is a performance
in our factory?
I think at most you'll end up
as a kneeler in a performance.
What do you mean?
Are you looking down on me?
What's wrong with performing skits?
Isn't performing skits a career?
Look.
Everything can become a career
if you do it well.
The key is whether you
truly love it.
Understand?
However,
performing skits
sounds a bit unreliable.
Why not?
I think
the people performing skits on TV
all look pretty average.
It's not a beauty pageant.
Mom, we're not talking about the same thing.
Besides,
do I look average?
I don't think so.
No, you don't.
It has nothing to do with looks.
If you want to perform a skit
in our factory,
that's fine.
But now you want to go to a film academy.
Do you even know
where the film academy is?
I know, it's in Beijing.
Last time I went with Qiang Xiaowa
to a writing competition,
I found out about it.
I want to apply to
Beijing Film Academy.
With just one shot,
you're aiming for Beijing.
That's ambitious!
Miaomiao,
If you had this ambition earlier,
I would have felt more at ease,
right?
Young people should have
such ambition and determination, shouldn't they?
Mom supports you going to Beijing
and the film academy.
If you go to Beijing,
then our whole family
should go with you.
-That sounds great.
-Ah?
What are you questioning about?
Haven't you always wanted to go to Beijing?
Didn't you always feel that
I was holding you back
from heading north?
Yes, I didn't fulfill your dream,
but now my daughter
is taking on this responsibility.
Right?
Yes, I'll take the responsibility.
Yaya.
You should also apply to a school in Beijing next year,
so Zi can go to school in Beijing too.
Right? She'll be able to get a good education.
Then she'll be closer to
-Peking University and Tsinghua University.
-Mom.
Please calm down for a moment.
Are the tuition fees for schools in Beijing
quite expensive?
It's okay even if it's expensive.
Your dad and I
will do whatever it takes
to support you.
Just go confidently.
Mom.
I didn't expect
you to be the first one to support me.
No, the second.
Li Si is the first.
I've made a deal with him.
If we go together,
you'll have a companion.
With him by your side,
I'll feel more at ease.
Okay.
It's settled then.
-Cheers.
-It's settled.
Come on.
Can you two really decide on this matter?
Do you own the academy?
What do you mean?
What do you mean by that?
Why are you two making sarcastic comments here?
It's rare for Miaomiao
to have such ambition.
Right?
If we don't support her, who will?
Let's stick to this goal.
It's all up to us.
If others can do it,
why can't we?
Whether we can do it or not, we have to make it happen.
Yes!
Miaomiao, eat more meat.
Okay.
Right? It's nutritious.
Then you can study better.
Okay, Mom.
Come on.
Mom.
Have you understood what I've been saying for so long?
Ms. Niu, please take it seriously.
I've been talking for a while.
Son, can we talk about it later?
Mom's calculations are all wrong.
Let's discuss it later.
Mom,
Is your lousy restaurant more important,
or is my future more important?
How can you not
distinguish between priorities?
You're the king now?
Should I kneel down and talk to you?
No need for that.
Just listen carefully.
After you listen,
just support me.
Well,
why do I want to go to the film academy?
Your dad is back.
How about this?
You talk to your dad about it.
Mom, we can just talk about it ourselves.
Dahai,
your son wants to apply to a film academy.
What kind of construction?
To apply to a film academy.
It's like making movies
and becoming a star.
Li Si.
Li Si!
Li Si, open the door.
Open the door.
Let's talk
about the film academy.
We can talk through the door.
I advise you
not to apply to the film academy
because you're not tall enough.
I'm tall enough.
If you apply to it, you won't be.
Why not?
Because I'll break your legs.
Why are you two fighting again?
Li Fan, have you forgotten
what you were like?
You were still wearing open-crotch pants at six.
And you were still wetting the bed at eight.
Have you ever done anything serious
from childhood to now?
You still can't even tell the front
from the back of your socks.
And you want to apply to the film academy?
Why don't you launch rockets instead?
Enough.
Why don't you
be the UN Secretary-General?
I don't mind
if you insist.
Enough, Dahai.
Dahai.
Don't. Get me a spare key.
Every time I...
What key?
We're talking about
his college application.
This is serious.
With him like this,
he still wants to apply to college.
He's always been the last in his class.
Yet he wants to go to college.
Listen, Li Si.
I'm telling you one last time.
Forget about the film academy
or whatever else.
Don't think about it.
Do you hear me?
After graduation,
just go up the mountain and extract oil.
That's the only path for you.
No one can change that.
I'm not going to extract oil.
Why should I extract oil?
Because I'm your dad,
because I raised you.
When did you ever raise me?
You were almost living in the well.
Have you ever taken care of me?
Where were you
when I was sick with a fever?
All you did was hit me
and beat me up
for no reason.
What's that about? Exercising?
Say it again.
Li Dahai, l'm telling you.
You're passionate about oil production but I don't.
I'm almost 18.
Everyone has their own aspirations.
I have the right
to choose my own life.
Fine. Hit me, huh?
Go ahead, kill me.
Let's see if I can
kill you.
What are you doing, Son?
Your dad has been unwell lately.
He has a stomachache, don't you know that?
His stomachache is from drinking.
It has nothing to do with me.
Don't go in there.
This family doesn't want you anymore.
Get lost!
If you dare come back, I'll break your legs!
You...
Since both of you are here,
I have to give you an explanation
for my divorce from Yang.
Tao,
what you said to me
on the way back during the Chinese New Year
really pierced my heart.
I kept thinking,
every day I'm nitpicking,
counting this and that,
feeling like the whole world owes me,
like I'm the most miserable.
But in reality,
you two are the most miserable.
Of course.
As a couple,
we are both failures.
Later, the two of us had a drink,
talked about the past,
and expressed many things
we hadn't said before.
In the end, we mutually decided
to get a divorce.
Divorce and marriage
are matters between the two of you,
and I understand that.
Me too.
But Aunt Yue,
you and my dad have divorced,
so you're no longer obligated
to take care of my dad.
My dad still has me.
-In the future...
-Tao.
Does getting a divorce
mean we're strangers now?
We've lived together
for more than ten years.
Can feelings just disappear like that?
How did your dad get this injury?
That was from a rescue operation at work.
Even if that weren't the case,
even if Yang went out
and got into a fight with someone
and hurt his leg,
I would still have to take care of him.
But Aunt Yue,
-I...
-Tao.
You've always been outside.
You definitely won't be coming back
to Oilfield.
Right?
And Min
is going to college next year.
With her mind set on leaving,
she definitely won't be coming back.
As for the life between your dad and me,
let us handle it ourselves.
We will always be a family
and loved ones.
This place
will always be our home,
and that will never change.
So when do you plan...
To remarry?
We don't plan to remarry.
Yes.
Well...
We're not suitable to be husband and wife.
We are family.
Alright.
Don't worry.
Rest assured.
I won't be a burden to this family.
How are you so sure that
I won't be able to stand up again?
Even if I can't stand,
I still have my hands.
Don't forget
what your dad does.
I'm an engineer.
I have a lot of intelligence.
I can support this family.
Do you hear me?
Look at how proud your dad is.
Don't worry.
Things will get better and better.
This will always be our home.
Remember that.
Alright.
We've said everything we need to say.
Let's eat.
Let's eat. Hurry.
Okay.
Why are you drinking here alone?
Life is short,
and full of joys and sorrows.
What's got you so worked up?
It's not really about being worked up,
it's about suffering.
The greatest suffering in life
happens between the ages of 20 and 40.
Right now, your uncle
is at the peak of that suffering.
Isn't your biggest suffering
the fact that you don't have a wife?
Look, Fang and I
have been together for so long,
and I've treated her so well,
yet she hasn't picked up on anything.
What should she pick up on?
Well,
she never thought
about being in a relationship with me.
Have you told her
that you want to have a relationship with her?
Well, I haven't said it outright.
As a grown man,
if you want to be with someone,
are you just waiting for the girl to speak up?
No.
Do I have to speak up directly?
Of course, you need to say it,
and you have to say it formally,
boldly.
And you think you're a pro in romance?
You're not anything at all.
Drink some warm water.
Here.
Be careful. It's hot.
My heart hurts.
The little brat dared to lay hands on me.
Don't pull it out.
This is a memorable lesson.
What lesson?
Leaving it here brings bad luck.
Your stomach pain is from drinking.
Yet you're blaming him for fighting with you.
Your son barely said a few words,
and you hit him first.
Why is it that
the older you get, the less reasonable you are?
A father reasons with his son?
What kind of reasoning is that?
Did your dad reason with you?
I'm telling you, the son takes after you.
Look at what he said.
He refused to work in oil production.
Without the oil wells, where would he be?
Without the oil wells, we, oil field workers,
would all be left with nothing.
You can't educate a child like this.
He can't forget where he comes from.
Is refusing to extract oil the same as forgetting our origins?
Did you send him to school
just to extract oil?
Well, he can also take on another role
in the Oilfield.
Times have changed,
haven't you noticed?
Now the Oilfield is open
to recruit college students.
What's the purpose?
It's to bring in talent.
You,
as a leader,
need to keep up with the times, you know?
Did you read it in the newspaper?
Cut it out. My stomach hurts.
You have to treat your stomach disease.
I feel so unwell.
I've scheduled a gastroscopy for you,
you must go for the check-up.
When?
The day after tomorrow.
The day after tomorrow?
No.
The day after tomorrow is our unit's major inspection,
and all the leaders are coming.
I have to attend.
Is the leader more important,
or is your life more important?
Next week?
It has to be this week.
The expert from Beijing is coming.
I've already paid for you.
Expert?
I can apply for leave then.
Well.
Can you talk to that expert
and see
if they can check my heart too?
I'm feeling really uncomfortable.
This child is being so stubborn.
He's been holding it in for a long time.
Bring me some quick relief.
What are you two arguing about every day?
He's your son.
Can't you go easy on him?
Come on.
Coming.
If I love you,
I won't wind upon you like a trumpet creeper,
upvaluing myself by your height.
If I love you,
I will never follow a spoony bird.
What are you doing?
-There are...
-Shush.
Repeating the monotone song for the green shade.
Not only like a springhead
brings you clean coolness the whole year long;
Not only like a steep peak
enhances your height
and sets off your straightness.
Even sunshine
and spring rain.
No,
all these are not enough!
Enough. These are enough.
No.
I must...
Why didn't you tell me
there are so many people?
You didn't let me speak.
I...
Well,
you're in a meeting, huh?
It's so late, and you're still busy.
We're not busy.
Anyway, I finished my confession.
No, I mean I'm done, take it.
You all carry on.
No need to see me off.
What a mess.
Jia Baoshan.
Go on with your meeting.
I have nothing else to do.
We can have the meeting anytime.
What do you want to tell me?
What?
Aren't you going to confess to me?
Yes.
Are you done?
Not yet.
Then hurry up and do it again.
Not here, though.
The environment is...
Too hasty.
Are you going to do it or not?
They're waiting for me to start the meeting upstairs.
I'll leave if you don't do it.
Don't. I'll do it.
If I love you,
-I won't...
-"If?"
No.
No?
It's not that I don't love you.
You don't love me.
No.
It's also not an "if" situation.
It's
"I love you."
What? I didn't hear you clearly.
I love you.
Louder.
I love...
Kiss!
-Kiss!
-You...
Take it.
You...
This...
Son.
Dad!
Alright.
Son.
Today,
about the conflict between us,
I think we both have our faults,
so let's just let it go and not hold a grudge.
What...
What do you want?
I'm not going to do something.
It's that Dad wants you
to help me with something.
What?
Haven't you been
having stomach issues lately,
always having diarrhea,
sometimes even with pain,
and sometimes
unable to hold it?
Son, you're still young,
but there's a saying,
"Nine out of ten men have hemorrhoids."
It's not about ambition,
but hemorrhoids.
Why are you eating so much this early?
Haven't you had breakfast?
I did.
Your intestines are all messed up,
always having diarrhea.
I'll have a check-up tomorrow,
so I can't eat at night.
That's why I need to eat more during the day.
What happened to you this time?
You're always having check-ups.
Gastroscopy.
Even if I told you, you wouldn't understand.
How could I not understand?
It's just checking the intestines.
He seems fine,
why bother checking the intestines?
He's always having diarrhea.
It delays so many things.
It should have been checked long ago.
You should eat less of those things
that irritate your stomach.
I'm fine.
It was my mom who scheduled a gastroscopy
for my dad.
My dad can't make it, so I have to go instead.
Isn't this just looking for trouble?
With all that eating,
you're bound to have diarrhea.
I'm hungry.
Doctor,
isn't the procedure already underway?
Why do I still need to sign?
This is not the signature for the gastroscopy.
Don't be nervous.
Let me explain.
Mom!
Son!
-Mom.
-Son.
I'm outside.
Mom.
Does it hurt?
Hang in there. You'll be fine soon.
Mom is at the door.
Mom.
Son.
Are you unwell?
I...
I think
I still feel a bit uncomfortable in my stomach.
It's been two days,
and you still feel so uncomfortable.
If it doesn't get better,
we really need to go to the hospital.
That's not necessary.
Mom,
help me request some time off,
at least two more days.
I need some rest.
Okay,
I'll help you with that.
I'll call right now.
What's wrong with you?
I'm not sick. I'm just pretending to be.
I just want my mom
to get me a few more days off.
How can you ask for so many days off?
I'll go for a check-up too.
It's such a good deal.
Listen, don't do it.
It's too painful.
No one can know that I'm pretending to be sick,
not even Xiaowa and Hu.
I really need to solidify my position
in the family.
My parents
must pay more attention to me.
I've got to go.
Don't worry about me.
Bye.
Okay.
Judging from the current situation,
the prosecuting authorities have not approved
the arrest of Yuan Shanqing,
which indicates that
there are still certain doubts
about their classification of Yuan Shanqing's behavior
as intentional homicide.
In the past few days,
I've had thorough communication
with them,
and I believe Yuan Shanqing's actions
are more aligned with
the requirements of justifiable self-defense.
It's in the bag.
Look.
Different trades, worlds apart.
Really.
Professional matters
require professionals to handle them.
He's a good lawyer.
-He's won
-Impressive.
so many cases.
No.
It's not me who's impressive,
but the prosecuting authorities.
They are meticulous.
No.
It's all thanks to you.
Mr. Jin, to be honest with you,
this is the only good news
we've heard
in recent days.
Really.
I'm so happy that
I can feel my legs
again.
Get up and walk.
Pengfei, you should express your gratitude.
Yes, well...
Thank you, Mr. Jin.
This child has hope now.
Don't mention it.
We're all on the same side.
It's my duty.
If there's nothing else,
I'll get going then.
Eat something before you go.
No.
No, thanks.
I'll take care of it.
If there's any news later,
well,
I'll contact you.
Okay, I'll see you off.
-Let me walk you out.
-Sure.
Mr. Jin,
I won't see you off since I'm still in a wheelchair.
No need.
Just stay there.
Take care.
Take care, man.
I'll thank you personally after this.
What's wrong?
It's good news
for the child.
Why aren't you happy?
No, I'm happy.
Pengfei, are you hiding something
from me?
Is there something wrong
with my lumbar spine and legs?
It's not about you.
Everything is settled.
It's all settled.
Why would I come back?
I've got to go too.
Dahai.
Well...
Well,
sit here first.
Sit here.
What?
I'm busy.
I just noticed something off about your expression.
What's wrong?
Pengfei.
We're all friends.
Just say what you want to say.
I'm begging you.
How about this?
Pengfei, tell me.
Isn't the issue about Shanqing
already resolved?
What now?
It's not about Shanqing.
It's your son.
Li Si?
What happened to him?
Dahai.
Li Si's report is out.
Report?
The report about gastroscopy?
What was the result?
Li Si
previously went for
a gastroscopy.
Then they found some issues
in his intestines,
so they did a biopsy.
Lingling was there
and signed the papers.
Why didn't anyone tell me?
Then
what's the final result?
Now,
the doctor preliminarily suspects...
What?
Of course,
this still needs to be confirmed
by several doctors...
Cheng Pengfei.
What are you hesitating about?
What's the worst-case scenario?
Intestinal cancer.
This summer,
I feel like we've been cursed.
We finally waited for the good news
that Shanqing would be coming back,
but a check-up brought about
a new disaster.
The poem recited
by Uncle and Fang,
Li Si and I
had also read it together.
At that time,
he seriously held Shu Ting's poetry collection and said to me,
"I must be a ceiba
by your side,
standing together with you
as a tree."
Then he asked me,
"Isn't it 'To The Oak Tree,'
why is it a ceiba now?
What is a ceiba?"
Many years later,
I met the ceiba for the first time
at a traditional Chinese medicine hospital.
A kind old doctor said that
the ceiba could treat enteritis.
I stood in that hospital
and cried very loudly.