We're waiting for you
Midsummer from now on
pay attention to the words
She's up
You must have some Very strange
Why come again
Yuki
Sun of Zhejiang
Fengfeng
self- expire
Youki
Did youell
You die
注意
Calm down
You
그런
Let go of me.
There's someone up there.
Show the target to the police.
There's no such person.
She's not a person.
Check the moon first.
The jade emperor sits down.
A thousand years of the last blow.
The palace number is 001.
Our cultivation has only been added for 990 years.
He's been in the dark for a thousand years.
Do you want to continue to be a man?
Okay.
What about this guy?
Let him check it again.
KPI, don't think about completing.
Lan, Lan Xin.
If this bitch succeeds,
we'll always be trapped in the mortal world.
He has the power of seduction.
The mortal can't get close at all.
What should we do?
Sit and wait.
The number of wishes is reduced to 0.1%.
Star fire.
It can be a long distance.
Water?
What is it?
See how I get you.
Brother, why is this steak so bad?
Sir, because you ordered a thousand-year steak.
I'm sorry.
Come on, baby.
I'm going to the bathroom.
It's really bad.
Who am I eating with?
I'm eating with you.
You drank Peng Yan's secret soup.
You can't tell the difference between dreams and reality.
Who?
Peng Yan's group.
The Peng Yan's group of Gaolongrong.
You said he was as perfect as I was back then.
Impossible.
You don't believe it?
Look at it yourself.
Look.
This is...
I don't have time to explain.
Remember.
No matter what he says later,
he's afraid of the dark.
Remember?
Why?
Give me a reason.
I don't have time to explain.
It's okay.
Don't add any wrong ingredients.
I'll kill him.
Remember.
What?
You're so handsome.
Let's go.
I'll take you to a place.
Lan Xi.
He's a jerk.
I'll expose you.
What's going on?
He blacked out Peng Yan's group,
but he blacked out me.
As a writer,
I can't even understand the meaning of the sentence.
I hope it works.
Your kiss was good just now.
I'm sorry.
No.
I...
Lan Xi.
Lin Lan Xi.
Will you marry me?
For the rest of your life,
will you be by my side?
I'm the rich.
I'm the safe.
You're the poor.
You're the disease.
Or you?
I'm willing to.
Let go of that jerk.
I'm sorry.