=The Legend of ShenLi=
=Episode 15=
Look, it's right there.
(Qingya Cave, Mortal Realm)
A large demon lived there.
It was
kind
and lived in peace
with us Earth Diviners.
But later, I don't know why.
We're being held here.
We can get there on that raft.
What happened?
Our leader...
Do you have to?
No,
but I find it very interesting.
All right, leave the rest to us.
You can go back to rest.
Don't worry.
Your people will soon be freed.
No, you don't understand.
They are very powerful.
I am worried about you.
I think I'd better go with you.
You should be worried about them.
Sir,
this is a gift for you.
Take it for self-defense.
You're an ancient god.
At least give him something better.
As long as he doesn't
throw away the stick,
no one can match him
within a hundred miles.
You gave him that to thank
him for useful clues
and for coming to our rescue
in the Mortal Realm,
even though it failed.
Don't worry.
I won't let you drown.
I'm not that scared.
Are you alright?
Why was there
a sudden big wave?
I'm fine.
I beg you.
Let me out.
Who exactly are you?
Why have you captured us here?
Looks like you are
from the Immortal Realm.
Let us out.
You Immortals have gone too far!
- Let me out.
- What did we do wrong?
Get in.
Let me out.
Just hold on.
The Divine will come to rescue us!
Let me out.
How can you do this?
I'm begging you.
I want to go home.
I can't hold on anymore.
Let us out.
Do I need to wear it?
Yes.
How do we save them?
Leave the formation and spells to me.
You do the beating.
Bro,
wake up!
Someone has come to rescue us.
Wake up!
Seems to be someone
from the Immortal Realm.
How is that possible?
How could they be that kind?
Go.
Go out.
- Come on.
- Hurry up.
- Go.
- Hurry.
We are finally saved.
Go.
Faster.
- Quick.
- Hurry.
Hurry up.
We are finally saved.
We are saved.
- Many thanks to you.
- Thank you.
- Many thanks.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
Thank you for the rescue.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
This place is not safe. Hurry and leave.
- Thank you.
- Let's go home.
- Let's go.
Go.
Thank you very much.
- Many thanks.
- Come on.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Many thanks for your rescue.
Stand up.
Where were other Earth Diviners
taken before?
You even have the gall
to ask us?
How can you not know where they are?
She saved us.
Don't be like that.
I'll say this only once.
Your getting caught had nothing
to do with us Immortals.
I didn't know it until today.
Nonsense.
You Immortals have always been
barbaric, domineering,
- and full of plots.
- That's enough.
I don't know why you imprisoned us,
but are you going to
catch the Diviners next?
None of you Immortals
is innocent!
- Her Holiness is the worst!
- Come on.
Watch your mouth
or I will
tear you apart.
ShenLi.
- No, please.
- Please calm your anger.
I didn't want to kill you.
But since you've already condemned me,
I shall make this accusation a reality
so that you could rest in peace.
Is that good?
He's slandering Her Holiness
and framing us.
These gossip-lovers
always try to harm us
with their nonsense.
I shall kill you
to vent my anger.
Please calm down.
- If you kill him,
- Your Lordship.
it will be even harder
to clear your name.
Just a few words.
Why so angry?
Yeah.
Can't you Immortals
show some understanding?
Everyone,
- Yeah.
- just because the people who hurt you
carried spiritual energy
didn't mean
they were from the Immortal Realm.
It could be someone
with ulterior motives
stirring up discord
between the two realms.
Some time ago,
I visited the Immortal Realm.
The Immortals
are not as bloodthirsty and warlike
as you imagine.
Please don't believe the rumors
and don't fall for
the schemes of villains.
As far as I know,
Furong, the Heavenly Lord's grandson,
went to the Immortal Realm days ago.
Just now,
that lady identified herself
as ShenLi, Lord Bicang.
Are you
that couple?
Furong and Lord Bicang
haven't married yet.
Since you're saying it,
it must be true.
- Yes.
Yes.
Lord Bicang
is fully devoted to the Immortal Realm
and very loyal.
She can't stand someone
disrespecting the Immortal Realm.
She was just
too angry.
Please forgive her.
- It's fine.
- You're very good to Her Lordship.
Not as rumored before.
Right.
Because
she deserves it.
They've all gone?
Yeah.
Just now they told me
another group of Earth Diviners seemed
to be held in the south.
But they are not clear
about the exact location.
That is your business, not mine.
Go save them by yourself.
I'm going to Jinxiu City.
Why are you following me?
Jinxiu City is in the south too.
We're heading the same way.
Do you want to go eat something?
No.
There is a village right below.
We can use their kitchen
to make some food.
It's been ages since I ate mortal food.
I miss it very much.
You'll do the cooking?
Yes.
(I do miss)
(the food he made.)
Let's go.
(Tea)
Come and have some tea.
Please take a seat.
Excuse me, may we use
your kitchen for a moment
to make some food?
What do you want to eat?
I can make it for you.
My sister
is picky.
I'm afraid what you make
may not suit her taste.
Don't worry. We will pay for it.
Alright, I will go tidy up
the kitchen in a bit.
Have some tea now.
Please.
A tourist trap.
Scared?
I don't think
they can match your slyness.
You flatter me.
Everything is ready. You can go in now.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
You came all the way
to this remote place,
but you don't seem tired at all.
You've got a strong constitution.
Nah,
just strong enough to kill
hundreds and thousands of Chimeis.
That's a good joke.
I never joke.
Come here.
What can I help you?
Come out,
or I will kill her.
Don't kill my mother!
Two foolish demons.
He?
I am not He.
Sorry, I...
My name is Jing Xi.
(Oh, right.)
(She already sacrificed herself
for the one she loved.)
(Moreover,)
(even if she was He, so what?)
(There was only one Xingzhi
in the world.)
Both of you aren't very powerful.
How dare you open
a tea house to harm people?
Outrageous.
Aren't you afraid of the Immortals
and Diviners here
coming to you for your crimes?
They
have long been captured.
When were they captured?
Where were they taken?
Tell us. I won't beat you.
Please spare us.
We didn't want
to engage in this shady business,
but we were forced into it
by our difficult life.
In these past few months,
we haven't killed a single person.
We just took their food
and then let them go.
Please.
Spare us.
When did you
start doing it here?
And why did you do it?
Because the Immortals
and Diviners nearby
kept disappearing.
All of them are missing.
Later, I heard other demons
in the mountain say
they seemed to be taken away
by some people of the Fusheng Sect.
Again.
So they didn't only capture
the Earth Diviners near Qingsheng City.
A small cultivation sect
that has only risen in recent years.
How could they capture
so many Earth Diviners?
And they even have spiritual energy.
(Is there actually someone)
(among us Immortals
with ulterior motives?)
Well,
how about we set out
for Jinxiu City right now?
I'll cook for you some other day.
Sir.
Could you please take me
with you to Jinxiu City?
I miss my father
and my brother, Jing Yan, very much.
The city is filled with miasma.
Aren't you afraid
you can't withstand it?
Let's go. Put a spell on her
to protect her from the miasma.
I don't wanna travel alone
with you anymore.
Remember to tell me
whenever you feel any discomfort
in the city later.
Mother.
Go.
Take good care of yourself.
(Jinxiu)
This is Jinxiu City?
How did it become like this?
I feel like
I'm in the Xutian Abyss.
All the Immortals
and Diviners of Jinxiu City
were captured long ago.
The miasma drifts down from the mountain
and gathers in the city every day.
That's why it's become like this.
Let's check it out.
(Jinxiu)
Follow me.
(Well-being for All)
It is worse than I imagined.
How can the mortals here endure it?
Is there a way to clear the miasma?
Sure.
But the miasma in the city
is from the mountain.
Clearing the miasma here
is only a temporary solution.
Clearing the miasma in the mountain
is the fundamental cure.
But at least, it is
better than doing nothing.
Mother, don't stop me.
Mother.
Let me make medicine for you.
You'll get better after that.
Mother.
The power of purification?
What have you done to my mother?
Your mother has been poisoned by miasma.
I know. It's none of your business.
I got the medicine given
by the Ragged Diviner.
My mother will get better
after taking it.
You weirdos get away from us!
Kid, he is trying to help you.
I only listen to the Ragged Diviner.
I don't trust you.
I will take my mother and leave.
Mother.
Give me back the medicine.
I can give it back to you,
but you have to tell me
where the Ragged Diviner
you mentioned is.
He is
at the North Academy
He has been there
healing people for a long time.
- Mother.
- That area
does seem fresher.
Can the medicine work out?
I don't know.
But just now,
I gave her a flick like this,
and that was enough.
Is there another Diviner
who loves to descend to the Mortal Realm
and save people like you?
Do you know?
Go there, and we'll see.
Let's go.
Are there ghosts here?
A demon is afraid of ghosts?
They are just affected by the miasma.
Help!
How can you hit me?
ShenLi?
Your Excellency?
Who are you?
I am Furong.
What's up?
I have no time for you. Go away.
You've gone too far.
I've risked my life to save a town,
and this is how you treat me?
Without me, everyone here
would be engulfed by the miasma.
I used the power of purification
to bring it under control.
How can you give me that look?
It's true that these people
have been purified.
Go back.
Let's go.
I came to Jinxiu City for fun,
but only to find them like this.
I couldn't just ignore it.
(North Academy)
Cleanse
the world...
What is it?
The incantation for the spell.
Oh, right.
All right, you're fine now.
Go inside.
(North Academy)
(I have exhausted all my strength
to purify the miasma,)
(but it pervaded immediately again.)
(Too many were affected.)
(I couldn't help the worst off ones,)
(so I took those with milder conditions)
(to the North Academy.)
(I set up a barrier to protect them.)
I come out every day
to dispel the miasma,
but it keeps getting worse.
I'm at my wits' end.
Why didn't you report
to the Divine Realm at first?
Afraid of being taken back?
Now,
you have to
rely on yourself
to purify the miasma here.
You can't handle it anymore,
so you're asking for help.
Want to save a city by yourself?
Ridiculous.
Sir,
have you seen a cultivator
with a disciple?
Sure.
They are inside my barrier.
Can you take me there?
Of course.
Let me hold your hand.
The miasma here is too thick.
You might not see clearly.
Ouch, ShenLi!
ShenLi, why are you pinching me?
Lead the way.
It's over there.
Let go of me!
Let me go!
This way. Follow me.
It hurts, ShenLi!
Drop the act. It doesn't hurt that much.
Let go!
- Let go!
- Hurry up.
- Let go of me!
- Go.
(North Academy)
I'm back.
You've returned?
The Diviner has returned!
Thank you.
You've saved a few people again.
Sir.
Come, the Diviner has returned.
- Please take a look.
- Get together.
Easy.
Sir.
- Please take a look.
- Calm down.
We seem to be getting...
It's alright now.
- Sir.
Thank you.
Alright, everyone stands up.
- Thank you.
That is amazing.
You're a great man.
This place used to be an academy.
Later, the headmaster
indulged in bribery
and corruption and did bad things.
After he got arrested,
the academy was abandoned.
I thought this place was not bad,
so I used it as a shelter.
Someone was arrested,
and it is still good?
The person was arrested,
so this place is good.
How could a villain deserve it?
Father, Jing Yan!
(Jing Yan)
Jing Yan!
They...
Father.
Why are you here?
Jing Yan.
Are they repeating
their fate?
It's just a coincidence.
After Gu Chengjin became the city lord,
during the many days
and nights of his life,
did he ever stop to think,
even for a moment,
of the girl who was just
entering her prime years
but never got the chance
to blossom because of him?
Where is your mother?
How could she let you come here?
My mother was worried about you.
But she was injured
and might get affected by the miasma,
so she didn't come.
How could you?
You wanted to be affected by the miasma?
Take the medicine,
and go back right away.
Father!
Sir.
The miasma isn't thick
within the barrier.
There is no need to let her go away.
She was too worried about you.
Please understand.
If something happens to you,
how will I explain it
to your mother?
Nothing has happened yet.
He definitely would.
After Gu Chengjin became the city lord,
he filled the garden
of the Jinyue Mansion
with lotus flowers.
It was of little use,
but if He knew,
she would probably be happy.
At least,
she was remembered by him.
This is the disease
that emerged in Jinxiu City
due to the miasma.
What are you doing?
Well?
You've been watching her,
but you can do nothing.
Why not let a pro take a look?
Your Excellency, please.
I'll go check on the other patients.
Furong, you've been here for many days.
Have you noticed
in which direction
the miasma is the thickest?
The west.
The miasma in the southwest
hurts the most.
If I am not mistaken,
the miasma
isn't flowing into the city
from outside.
It's flowing from
inside the city to the outside.
I'm afraid
this situation has been
going on for a while.
I don't think so.
Although I live in seclusion
in the mountain,
I often go into the city
to buy some necessities.
I visited last month,
and there was already
some miasma outside the city.
But inside the city,
it was relatively clean.
But actually,
they don't have a disease at all.
It's energy flowing
in reverse in the body
due to years of miasma inhalation.
It's a shame,
but a few days ago,
I inhaled miasma.
And then,
it left such marks in my body.
(He got the wound)
(after being attacked
by Chimeis in the Xutian Abyss.)
(I didn't know it'd be still there.)
(And Xingzhi)
(even didn't mention a word about it.)
Such marks
either come from being bitten
by miasmatic monsters
or from inhaling miasma
for years which causes
blood to flow in reverse.
After a certain amount
of time,
it will erupt.
Earth Diviners disappeared everywhere.
A mysterious cultivation sect.
The spreading miasma.
I think the answer
may just lie in the west of the city.
Who is she?
Keep it down.
Don't you see she's asleep?
♪Snow scatters
across the heavens and earth♪
♪The dazzling light
envelopes the city with hope♪
♪The fierce silver spear♪
♪Pacifies all the wars♪
♪Right and wrong, like an illusion♪
♪Love brings confusion and delusion♪
♪All the romance
and entanglement end in solitude♪
♪Life is like a splendid dream♪
♪Where I drink with you
until we get drunk♪
♪Toast to the love and hate
engraved into our bones♪
♪Living up to our encounter♪
♪Filling the empty spot in the heart♪
♪And head toward our fate♪
♪Toast to the fate that chains us
for the rest of our lives♪
♪Break the boundary
that defines our love♪
♪The stars are glittering♪
♪The world is a witness♪
♪As it was initially said♪
♪Defend the sun and the moon♪
♪Devote everything
to the long-lasting wishes♪
♪Love is hardly complete♪
♪We can only protect
all beings from perishing♪
♪Toast to the love and hate
engraved into our bones♪
♪Living up to our encounter♪
♪Filling the empty spot in the heart♪
♪And head toward our fate♪
♪Toast to the fate that chains us
for the rest of our lives♪
♪Break the boundary
that defines our love♪
♪The stars are glittering♪
♪The world is a witness♪
♪As it was initially said♪
♪The stars are glittering♪
♪The world is a witness♪
♪As it was initially said♪