=The Legend of ShenLi=
=Episode 33=
(I can't breach this barrier,)
(or it will harm Xingzhi.)
(That man is really too bad.)
(He's expert in formations.)
(Every formation)
(has its weak point.)
(Xingzhi repaired
the distant fallen rocks previously)
(by painting on the scroll.)
(Is this barrier)
(related to the scroll?)
Just now,
I saw my master.
Is this what Xingzhi left in the scroll
or an illusion?
Well...
(Xingzhi?)
(It's not right. He seems strange.)
(This was)
(thousands of years ago.)
(He was in the Extranatural Heaven)
(and all his friends were gone.)
♪Suddenly I see you again♪
♪A gentle breeze
and lamps in the courtyard♪
♪Upon waking from a dream,
who sighs over fleeting time♪
♪I don't see you♪
♪I feel anxious,
not finding any trace of you♪
♪All that's left is longing for you.
Fate is capricious♪
♪Sink into this pain♪
♪And get lost in it♪
♪The moon in the water,
like someone's heart♪
♪Like someone's feelings,
but why is it severed♪
♪The long night is too lonely♪
♪Only with you can I get through it♪
This place
is really too cold.
♪Breaking free,
alone in search of a dream♪
♪As stars turn, I wish
to return to our first encounter♪
Be careful.
You brat.
Mother.
Let me hug you.
Father, let me do it.
- Has she arrived?
- Yes.
Yes.
Come in.
♪Looking at the horizon♪
Come on.
Father, Mother.
♪Joy and happiness, like an illusion♪
♪Like the morning dew, drifting away♪
♪Standing alone in the world♪
(People come and leave.)
(Life is a journey)
(from nothingness)
(to nothingness.)
(That's all.)
♪As stars turn, I wish
to return to our first encounter♪
♪Even if the world changes♪
♪The memories are too vivid♪
♪A vision full of red♪
♪Embrace you in the world♪
♪All in the world♪
♪Becomes trivial♪
♪Swift farewells, swift reunions♪
♪I want to be with you
even if it means defying fate♪
♪Fearless of shattering,
turning into a breeze♪
♪Upholding vows, we'll meet again♪
♪Still, all things exist together♪
♪Under the same starry sky♪
♪I return with my wishes♪
♪Soaring through the azure seas and sky♪
(Life and death are destined.)
(It's a cycle.)
(All meetings are but illusions.)
(In the end, it's all a fantasy.)
(The Three Realms)
(are so boring.)
♪Fearless of shattering,
turning into a breeze♪
♪Upholding vows, we'll meet again♪
♪Still, all things exist together♪
(What is the meaning in guarding)
(the Three Realms?)
(The gleam
that just fell into the scroll)
(helped me see the past.)
(Master and Xingzhi.)
(The Extranatural Heaven is broken.)
(Mountains and rocks collide.)
(That radiance just now)
(surely wasn't left by Xingzhi.)
(That is the rift caused
by the broken Extranatural Heaven.)
(And it allows me to see the past.)
(Is it related to time?)
(If it wasn't left by Xingzhi,)
(perhaps I could find a way)
(to get out)
(through the rift.)
(Thousands of years ago, Immortal Realm)
It has been a day and a night already.
Why isn't the making
of a Chimei over yet?
Is the power offered not enough?
(Liuyu, Immortal Realm)
The Fire element.
(Liuming, former Immortal Lord)
If we integrate it into this...
Oh, right.
A nirvanic phoenix with the power
of the Five Elements
can bear the supreme energy.
Liuyu,
how about we make this into a phoenix?
That's the best of the ideas
that we've thought of.
The current materials
and a phoenix feather,
with ten times the firepower.
It might take shape.
Phoenix feathers.
Come on.
Let me add all the firepower!
Once I possess
the supreme power to control Chimei,
I will have nothing to fear.
The Three Realms
will be mine.
Burn.
It's done.
It's okay.
Don't be afraid.
You are very safe.
I will not harm you.
He was just born
and already has such great strength.
He is now the King of Chimei.
In the future,
no matter
how many more Chimei are made,
I will be able
to control them with ease.
Master,
will you continue
to create more Chimei in the future?
Of course.
There will be a battle
between the Divine and us.
And we'll dominate
the Three Realms
and enter a golden age.
Master,
he is different from other Chimei.
He needs to be taken care of.
I'd love to take care of him
and teach him Chimei' skills for you
so that in the future
he can control other Chimei.
Good.
I will take advantage of the time
to develop other Chimei.
Take good care of him
and teach him to use
his power as soon as possible.
His name
is up to you to decide.
Yes.
Feng,
Lai.
From now on,
you shall be called Fenglai.
Fenglai?
The King of Chimei.
Why would I see this?
(It's bad. He's coming back.)
(If I am to leave
through the time rift,)
(I must not tell him about this)
(in case he will seal this loophole.)
(If I can persuade him to let me go,)
(that would be best.)
I'm back.
Very good. That's enough.
Stop it.
Did the meteorites
affect the Immortal Realm?
No.
That's the best outcome.
Now Fu Sheng has taken control of Mofang
and is hiding in the shadows.
He's still plotting
against the Xutian Abyss.
We have spent too much time
at this snowy mountain
and in the East Sea
and the Extranatural Heaven.
I must return to our realm.
Is this tea too hot?
Do you not want to taste it?
Xingzhi,
why must you imprison me like this?
You know I won't stay here forever
for you.
Why can't you?
You know why I can't.
Over all these years,
we ancient gods
have continuously warned
ourselves and each other
not to do things
we mustn't do.
One misstep
would lead to endless calamities.
If we achieved enlightenment,
we would become
a glimmer of hope for the world.
But why must we struggle within the stir
caused by the Natural Law?
Why must we protect the Three Realms?
Why must we obey
the Natural Law?
If I am endowed with a god's body,
why give me the heart
of an ordinary person?
If I am to be heartless,
why grant me emotions and desires?
It bestowed upon me
an unbeatable strength
but didn't give me an invincible heart.
Does the Natural Law
truly
want us gods to protect
the Three Realms?
All things
are like flowing water,
gravel,
floating clouds and dust.
What is there to cherish about them?
If I do not protect the Three Realms,
what of it?
Chaos exists naturally,
giving birth to ancient gods
who possess supreme magical powers.
You are the last of them,
so...
I've heard
too many high-sounding words.
Do not try to persuade me.
I am not trying.
People see you as the last ancient god,
but in my eyes,
you are a lonely person.
Ancient gods
possess the ultimate power.
You're given the supreme power
and also the emotions and desires.
You're upset, angry and cold,
which is not within your control.
It is not your fault.
Just proof that you are still alive.
I will not blame you
because I believe
you have your own convictions
in your heart.
Occasional indulgence is not forbidden.
Do what needs to be done.
Say what needs to be said.
Vent your anger
and frustration.
Don't waste our precious time.
Stop drinking tea. Get a pot of wine.
If the Natural Law treats you badly,
curse it.
What's it to the beings
in the Three Realms?
Get a pot of wine.
I'll join you in your curses.
You're heartless and unkind!
Darned be the eternal Natural Law.
Should we
go to His Excellency?
There's thunder in the sky.
Disastrous!
His Excellency
must have done something terrible again.
That must have caused
the thunder to roll.
Disastrous!
Are you alright?
Even some curses are not allowed?
You even strike His Excellency?
Do it one more time.
Darned be the eternal Natural Law.
Well done.
Are you cooled down now?
Yeah.
Xingzhi,
I truly like you.
But
I have to leave you.
You...
I've already said it many times.
No.
Will you never let me go
no matter what I say?
Enough talk. Let's have a fight.
Alright.
You're serious?
Yes. Let's be serious about it.
Here you go. Take it.
Do you really think I won't do it?
Unless you kill me,
otherwise, you can't get out.
You just can't do it.
So,
Li, put it down.
I'll go get you some food.
Wait for me to come back.
Wait for me.
There's a large rock over there.
This place is so weird.
A formation from the Immortals?
It doesn't seem like it.
Such a large stone.
Such a big hole.
It didn't hit anyone, did it?
Seems no one was here.
Mofang?
It's okay.
Why is he inside?
They say he betrayed the Immortals
and colluded with their enemy.
Is it really so?
He doesn't seem
to be that kind of person.
Mofang, what are you doing?
Have you gone mad? I am Furong.
A sacrifice that came to the doorstep.
I'll kill you
and use you to break the formation.
Let me see what you can do.
Furong, leave.
He recognized me.
You will not find
another kind person like me.
If you hit me again after waking up,
you will be struck by lightning!
He's really thoughtful
when it comes to these snacks.
It seems impossible to persuade him now.
I have to figure out a way
of leaving this place myself.
(Will the glow)
(appear on the scrolls here?)
(Each time)
(I touched the gleam on the scroll,)
(I'd always see
some scenes from the past.)
(The first time, I saw my master.)
(The second time, I saw Xingzhi.)
(And then I saw)
(Liuming making the King of Chimei.)
(Does this glow)
(show me scenes randomly)
(or does it follow a pattern?)
(Let me check out)
(what exactly this glow is.)
(He just looks like an ordinary human.)
(Fenglai, Immortal Realm)
It's all right now.
Hello, Fenglai.
I am Liuyu.
Liuyu.
Liu,
Yu.
Yes, Liuyu.
Would you like some tea?
Tea.
Yes, tea.
What kind of monster
has Master created now?
Fenglai.
Fenglai, it's fine.
It's fine, Fenglai.
This is too absurd.
He made a Chimei
look like a human!
Fenglai.
Fenglai,
it's okay.
It's okay, Fenglai.
It's okay.
It's all right now.
It's fine.
You're just a Chimei.
How can you give me that look?
You're angry with me?
Muyue.
Muyue!
- No!
- How dare you?
Muyue!
- Step aside. Don't stop me.
- Fenglai.
- Let go of me!
Fenglai, you...
- Fenglai.
- Step aside!
Muyue,
don't take it to heart.
I'm pissed off.
He's just like a child.
Muyue, why bother
getting angry with him?
What an annoying thing.
Do you still plan
to help him make Chimei?
How can you not understand?
He claims he's doing it
to help us resist the Diviners.
But in fact,
it's just for his own ambition.
The Diviners already know.
He will only plunge our realm
into chaos and war!
Muyue, don't worry.
I will discipline him
to make sure he won't run amok.
You're encouraging a disaster.
Muyue.
Fenglai!
If even the gods can't stop him,
you'll be the last resort.
You need to grow fast
and grow strong enough
to command all the Chimei of the world
to protect the innocent.
Only then can our realm truly enter
a golden
and prosperous age.
I hope it won't be a mistake
to create you.
Let me play for a while.
Be careful.
Catch me!
Let me play for a while.
Be careful. Okay.
Let me play for a while, please.
Stand up.
This realm
is so beautiful.
How is the learning
of the breathing technique?
By mobilizing the power within,
I can see far away.
What have you seen?
I've seen weird things locked in cages,
children playing by the river,
beautiful woods
and the starry sky.
Liuyu, the Immortal Realm
is really beautiful.
Yes,
it is very beautiful.
Let's go.
The growth of plants
may take months or even years.
That of animals
takes decades
or even hundreds of years.
And the mountains and rivers
take tens of millions
of years or more to form.
The beauty of this realm
doesn't come easily.
Fenglai,
so no matter what happens,
we must cherish the beauty of the realm.
And this realm
has bred you too, right?
Of course.
If this realm is not well,
does it mean you will not be well?
I don't want it to happen.
I will cherish you
and the Immortal Realm.
I just heard you coughing.
I'm fine.
Let me do it.
You...
What are you going to do?
Don't move.
When I was just practicing my breathing,
I saw how others
took care of
those who were unwell.
Do you feel better?
(Oh, my God.)
(He doesn't look like a Chimei at all.)
(He's so good.)
(How can I involve him)
(in this game?)
♪Snow scatters
across the heavens and earth♪
♪The dazzling light
envelopes the city with hope♪
♪The fierce silver spear♪
♪Pacifies all the wars♪
♪Right and wrong, like an illusion♪
♪Love brings confusion and delusion♪
♪All the romance
and entanglement end in solitude♪
♪Life is like a splendid dream♪
♪Where I drink with you
until we get drunk♪
♪Toast to the love and hate
engraved into our bones♪
♪Living up to our encounter♪
♪Filling the empty spot in the heart♪
♪And head toward our fate♪
♪Toast to the fate that chains us
for the rest of our lives♪
♪Break the boundary
that defines our love♪
♪The stars are glittering♪
♪The world is a witness♪
♪As it was initially said♪
♪Defend the sun and the moon♪
♪Devote everything
to the long-lasting wishes♪
♪Love is hardly complete♪
♪We can only protect
all beings from perishing♪
♪Toast to the love and hate
engraved into our bones♪
♪Living up to our encounter♪
♪Filling the empty spot in the heart♪
♪And head toward our fate♪
♪Toast to the fate that chains us
for the rest of our lives♪
♪Break the boundary
that defines our love♪
♪The stars are glittering♪
♪The world is a witness♪
♪As it was initially said♪
♪The stars are glittering♪
♪The world is a witness♪
♪As it was initially said♪