(Yin Chan-ha)
(Arin)
(Yoo Jung-ho)
(Chuu)
My girlfriend is more handsome than me.
Yun Jae, give me a cup of coffee
I'd like a hot Americano with two shots of espresso.
I don't want to sleep tonight
I'm Park Yoon-jae's girlfriend
Although it became like this due to some hardships
But she will soon turn back into a girl
So please stop seducing Yun Jae.
Didn't Yun Jae always say he had a girlfriend?
That person is me
You should have a clear idea of it by now, right?
It's me. I'm Park Yoon-jae's girlfriend.
(Episode 6 Chaos and Disorder)
A complete mess
It's all a mess
Yun Jae hyung, the most messed up person is you
Oh my god, do you have ringworm on your face?
I have too many worries
I envy you for living a carefree life.
My face is glowing
Hi Yun Jae
Um
It's all because of you that I stayed up all night last night
But I'm not tired at all
What
Oh my god
Caffeine fully exerts its effect
Hey, why are you always exclaiming to the guests?
Give me a latte
Yun Jae, did you sleep well?
What is this situation?
Are you two...
What is it?
Didn't you stay up all night? Why do you want coffee again?
What
You said I was beautiful yesterday
That's because... Were you here yesterday too?
It seems there really is a ghost
Bro, have you broken up with your girlfriend?
I'm exactly the same as yesterday
Isn't today beautiful?
Minjoo
Um
I had some difficulties before
I haven't really discussed this with you.
What's going on?
I have a girlfriend
Are you kidding me?
You always make it clear that I know you have a girlfriend
Although I said
But I never rejected you seriously.
Are you a little shaken now?
What
You're not drawing a line with me.
Telling myself to draw a line
Look at this
(Looking for Xiaolu Man in Yanxi University Exchange Forum)
Isn't this me and Ji-hoon?
What is going on?
This is the article posted on the Yanxi University Exchange Forum last night.
Now it's spreading like wildfire
(Looking for Xiaolu Man on the Yanxi University forum)
No...
Anyway, this is ridiculous.
Yes, Zhixun is quite handsome.
But is he really that handsome?
Uh-huh
My brother and I were mosaiced.
No, can you upload photos of amateurs at will?
Let's help him.
How to help
It's very simple
Wouldn't it be better to disclose his identity and location?
Isn't this a small matter to you?
Have you finished writing the topic?
I've finished writing it, but there are probably a lot of mistakes
Let me take a look
Yun'e, stop staring at me.
Read well
Your face is much more beautiful than the book
Yun'e, thank you for your compliment.
But it will be too late to catch up before the midterm exam.
So where is the progress between you and my brother?
What
I know it all
What's your relationship with my brother?
Really
Did Yun Jae tell you everything?
You'll know at a glance
that…
This is a little hard to explain...
Don't worry, I'll keep it a secret for you.
Although the road ahead is not easy
But I'll cheer for you guys
Good luck
good
You should consider this.
You don't know how careful I am
Don't be attracted to you?
Why is everything such a mess?
I bought spicy rice cakes
It's been a while since I've eaten so satisfyingly, right?
Get me some toilet paper
Hey, how long are you going to be like this?
Do you know you haven't said a word today?
Oh, so cute.
Stop, don't do this again.
(Friendship Agreement between Kim Ji-eun and Choi Yu-ri)
The two of them were in the period when Jin Zhien became a man
I swear to strictly abide by the following
Continue reading
First, Jin Zhien is not allowed to be in front of Cui Yuli
Appearing like a comic scene
I'm too late
Happy birthday
Yuli Second
As long as Choi Yu-ri asks
Kim Ji-eun must dance the sea sausage dance at any time
Sea sausage
Please stop jumping like this.
Don't jump the third one.
Hello
When Kim Ji-eun Became a Man
Try to avoid physical contact with Choi Yuri
It's so hot
fourth
Choi Yu-ri must not fall in love with Kim Ji-eun
You don't know how careful I am
Don't be attracted to you?
It seems like you're really feeling bad.
I went too far yesterday
I'm the one who went too far.
No, I'm more sorry.
(My Yunzai)
Why doesn't he answer the phone?
Zhixun's article
Now it has risen to the seventh place on the NightFan popularity list
What
(Looking for Xiaolu Man in Yanxi University Exchange Forum)
It's unbelievable that he's just an amateur.
(The eyes, nose, mouth and even hair look like the protagonist of a comic)
Why?
(Wow, so handsome, I want to see the real person too)
Kang Dong-won and Sweet Tea
They were all amateurs originally.
Damn appearance supremacism
I bought spicy rice cakes
Come in
Should I buy other food?
No, I really want to eat spicy rice cakes
But the portion is a bit large
I think Sister Zhihui is also here
My sister seems to be very busy recently
Often come home late
Um... did you see the link I sent?
Is Yanxi University a little deer boy?
Quite funny
Is it okay with you? I'm not an artist.
Anyway, it will be suppressed after a while.
It doesn't matter
It will be suppressed.
Yes, it will definitely happen
Yunzai
Um
Nothing happened yesterday, right?
Yesterday?
Well, nothing special.
Nothing special?
After get off work, I go home and sleep.
Didn't I send a message?
Didn't you see it?
I saw it
Seeing you looking at that vixen affectionately
Did I get something on my face?
No
Eating spicy rice cakes all the time seems too exciting
My stomach hurts a bit.
Yeah
I'd better go buy some medicine. It's not that serious.
I want to take a break
OK
You take a rest
This is Ji-eun's favorite spicy rice cake.
Why are you angry?
Hey Kim Ji-eun
Hey, have you seen this?
Yanxi University Xiaolu Man
(Who is the Xiaolu Man at Yanxi University?)
Many people say they have seen him, but his true face
There is still no clear whereabouts
According to reliable sources
(Who is the Xiaolu Man at Yanxi University?)
This little deer man is from a certain chaebol family
Unknown son
According to Xiaolu's male friend A
He is preparing to become an idol
I also heard that he was in charge of the ladies in Jiangnan Cowherd Club.
Popularity can be said to be extremely red
Please help him cut it like this
Um... please wait a moment
Husband, come here for a moment
Um
Isn't this our child?
How could my son...
Auntie, do you know him?
Everyone says he is the deer boy from Yanxi University
He's very handsome, right?
Fawn boy? Fawn boy?
I have seen the deer man with my own eyes.
Really handsome
He's not handsome, but why would he come to our party?
It should be someone I know, right?
Wasn't he the one who carried Park Yun-jae out?
Carry him out? What happened to Park Yun-jae?
He must not remember
He didn't even know how much he weighed. He was completely drunk that day.
The day after drinking is the worst
Yun Jae
Why do you look so serious and frown?
nothing
Everyone is talking about Kim Ji-hoon
It would be difficult for you to go in now.
I heard he is the youngest son of a chaebol family.
No, it's an idol.
I really don't understand what's there to discuss.
That's right
I'm not curious about anyone except Yun Jae
I'd better go to the library.
Really
Park Yun-jae
Oh my god, isn't he the deer boy?
Shoot quickly
Really handsome
Hello
Is this Mr. Kim Ji-hoon?
Please tell me which
Hello, I am the YouTuber Popularity President
Someone told me that you are the deer boy from Yanxi University...
I'm not a deer man
But who told you that?
Do you know the online novel writer Mina?
Although I'm not very willing
But there's no safer place than here
That's why I asked you to come here.
Because it was so sudden, I only bought toilet paper
Thank you. Please sit down first.
Hey, what's up with that Mina sister?
Who the hell does she think she is to leak my phone number?
She is born to be a badass who wants to be famous
We embarrassed her that day
So now I should be furious and ready for revenge.
When were these photos taken of you?
(The recently popular Yanxi University Xiaolu boy)
This was even taken today.
What should I do?
You two...
Are you serious about each other?
Of course... Yeah
Park Yun-jae, where are you?
What... um
Do you love each other enough to ignore the world's opinions?
Answer this question one, two, three at the same time
Right
Okay, that's no problem.
I will take care of the trouble I caused.
What do you want?
For the finale of Yanxi University Xiaolu Man
Hello Editor, I'm a Glass Slipper
The fan signing event I mentioned last time
I changed my mind.
I do
And you can make your appearance public
"Can't stop can't stop thinking about the"
"The window crack where the breeze blows in my memory"
"Intense lights blooming one by one"
very good
(I like you so much)
"Even with my eyes closed, it becomes clearer and clearer"
"Wake up and make up"
very good
But don't open your mouth too wide
Now it's fine
So sexy
marvelous
(Upload a post)
We are actually dating, though it's a little late. Please support us.
"I can't leave you alone"
"I'm wandering around you again like this"
(Release)
But does this really work?
She has more than 150,000 fans.
150,000?
You are such a famous writer.
Thank you for finally finding out
After everyone shares it, it should be effective.
(Oh my god, so handsome!! Is he the writer's boyfriend??)
(No way, tell me this isn't true)
(Not that he is my boyfriend)
(Isn’t this the young man from Yanxi University?)
(Mission of Love profile of Shin Dong-hoon)
(Exam Udon)
Do you want to take an exam?
Scare me
How to resign and prepare for the civil service exam?
No
Three black cards can only be issued if the deposit exceeds 10 billion yuan
A super VIP
Matchmaking must be successful
good
(Mission of Love Personal Information) Xian Zhengci
Your cafe is quiet and nice.
This is the biggest advantage of our cafe
Come here occasionally to read.
Maybe even quieter than the examination hall
good
But why are you here, Mr. Yingshuo?
Because when I think about it carefully, it seems like it's you who comes to me every time.
That's because I don't have to work.
And you want to study
But I am a man after all
I hate being put into gender frames.
You haven't eaten yet?
I found a good restaurant
But you probably know this area better than I do.
I only know where to drink
Then let’s go together
Wait for me five minutes
Okay, I'll wait outside.
Huh
Mr. Yingshuo...
(Mother)
Ward 804, Baekje Hospital
Wait, I forgot my phone.
Here
Thanks
(Mother)
Your father is in the hospital again.
He said that if he didn't see your girlfriend, he would die with regrets.
Why is your dad so stubborn?
What to do?
I forgot that a group of guests had made reservations tonight.
Let’s have dinner together next time
Sorry
good…
Let me go, why are you doing this?
Dad, please don't do this.
Did I ask you to make money?
Or force you to find a job
I just want you to get married like everyone else.
Your dad has already stepped into the coffin.
Can't you even agree to such a small thing?
Who would want to marry me when I have a father like you?
What
You stinky husband
Have you said enough?
Come here
This bastard
etc.
Who are you?
aunt and uncle
First meeting
I am Xian Zhengci
Miss Zhengci, why are you here?
Do you know Yingshuo?
I'm not a bad person
I just heard the news about my uncle and aunt
Just come and say hello
Oh my god
Could it be that...
So please relax and leave everything to me
Get treatment well
Our happy days will come soon
Really
I knew it was like this
Listen carefully
We don't need insurance
What
Dad, you're so rude.
This world is really hopeless.
Are you trying to make money from this dying old man?
Even if life is hard, it shouldn't be like this
Stinky girl
What a stinky girl
She's my baby.
You just marry in.
No dowry is needed
My son has been preparing for the exam for a long time
I look a bit sloppy so people often misunderstand me.
But we only eat Korean beef and not regular beef.
That's right
Oh my god, I love beef.
Let's set a date first.
Dad, how could we get engaged the first time we met?
This guy is totally in love.
He actually thought we were getting married on the day we had beef.
My son is fine
Performed well
I am very satisfied
Since it's like this
Why don't we set a wedding date first?
dad
I have no problem booking it first
Yeah
Very good
OK
uncle
Now I have no regrets in death
Very good
Dad, did you see it?
Your grandson is getting married.
Very good
Dad, why are you like this suddenly?
Why buy such expensive things?
How do you, a student, get the money?
This is not expensive.
I bought it at a famous bakery in Yanxi University and it was delicious.
Obviously, he is also a son
Why is there such a big difference?
Mom, aren't you going out?
I wish you were my son-in-law
My dream is to be a mother-in-law who loves her son-in-law
Mom, why don't you go out? I still have to study.
Okay, I'm going out.
That's hard work.
Go out
Oh no
Why lock the door?
This one?
Are you also tracking Yuri?
That's right
Your dream is to become an online novel writer, right?
Don't try to get away with it
I helped the teacher...
No, it won't take long for me to cheer up your love.
You actually cheated
Yuna is not like that
My favorite writer
Rather than sympathizing with Park Yun-jae
I have been supporting her since her debut.
I am more pitiful because I lost my idol.
It's like I'm being denied
Teacher, do you understand?
Wait a moment
So to sum up
The teacher and my brother are really in love
Your Best Friend is a Glass Slipper Writer
Is she covering for you like I am?
is that so
Excuse me
Could you please keep your voice down?
Speak softly
(The never-before-seen Glass Slipper writer makes his first public appearance!)
(Goddess's Private Life)
(Glass Slipper Writers Signing Event)
(Glass Slipper)
May I have your name
My name is Yezhen Yezhen
Can I shake your hand?
I am your fan
Yuri 4?
Are you my fan too?
Oh my god, are you the glass slipper?
I thought you were this person
It has nothing to do with the worldview of my pure love comics
I love pure love comics
I've seen all your works.
Too exaggerated
You are the glass slipper
There are people waiting behind
Can you please move aside first?
Hello
May I have your name
My code name is Sea Sausage
You are not Jin Zhi...
That's right
I am Mr. Zhixun's tutoring student
I heard that you and the teacher are close friends.
right
I thought he was a different person and scared me
Anyway, nice to meet you
Your name
My name is Park Yun-a
Yun'e, please draw a heart for me
good
(To. Park Yun-a)
This venue is so big
Is Choi Yu-ri so popular?
That's right
Yuri is there
Really?
It's amazing. Is the queue here?
It seems
Actually, you don't have to come with me.
This is the finale of Yanxi University Xiaolu Man
I am the protector of the deer man.
etc.
That's my sister, right?
Really? She should be in school now.
Yun'e
It will be troublesome if you mess with her.
Let's just quietly get the autograph and leave.
Isn't that Min Hyuk?
Hey Park Yun-a
Hello
Brother Yunzai
What are you doing here?
What else can I do? Taking pictures, of course.
Why is he taking the photo for you?
Because she asked me to help take the photo
Do you know each other?
She is my sister
Really
It seems that they really look exactly the same
What did you say?
Damn it, so annoying.
What's so annoying? Of course it's annoying.
Hello
Teacher Zhixun
It's school time now, right?
I'm just taking a lunch break.
Get back to school while I'm in a good mood
Otherwise I'm going to video call my mom.
The old-fashioned is so annoying
See you next time, teacher
Goodbye
I'm so annoyed. Why did we meet here?
Why don't you go back to school soon?
hateful
Look at her rude look.
Hello, teacher
Hello writers,
Oh my god
Thank you, your work is beautiful.
So beautiful. Thank you.
I like your work very much
Oh my god
Who is this?
Isn't this the boyfriend of the writer of Glass Slipper?
It's that little deer guy on IG, right?
Hello
I've always thought you were very handsome.
So you are the deer man
Oh my god, there is such a thing
who is she
That...Mina sister
Sister Mina
Why are you standing here?
I plan to queue up
Why should my boyfriend queue?
Of course I have to take the fast lane.
come over
It's okay with me
Come on, I'm really fine.
You all know who he is, right?
The boyfriend of the author of Glass Slippers
Boyfriend Xiaolu Man
Lend me a moment, little deer boy
This won't do.
The boyfriend of the author of Glass Slippers
My boyfriend, please lend it to me.
Lend me a moment
Yulilai
I don't want to, oh, your boyfriend is here.
Really
Lend me a moment...
I am your fan
That's too unfamiliar.
Didn't you talk so much last time?
He is Yuri's boyfriend.
People who know Xiaolu Man
I
Right
Hey, think of a solution.
My dear, you are here
Um
Honey
So sweet
How does the private life of each goddess end?
Kiss...
Yeah, give me a kiss.
The writer's fans have been asking so much
Kiss...
Come on... give me a kiss...
A kiss is right
Kiss...
What is happening?
Give me a quick kiss...
hurry up…
Kiss...
Kiss
Are you crazy? The novel can only end when it ends.
What are you talking about?
I'm at a disadvantage, okay?
You know I'm single, right?
This is my first kiss
So why kiss?
Don't you see what's happening now?
Power lies in actions, not words
Just three seconds
Hello
Kiss...
Hey, smile
We love each other very much
They kissed yeah
This looks like a deer boy.
Yes
They are dating
What are you doing?
Is that so?
(Exam Udon)
Welcome
Please sit over there.
Auntie please give me a night exam udon
You don't look like a candidate
Is this your first time visiting our store?
yes
My friends who are studying in Noryangjin
They say the udon here is the best in Noryangjin.
Yeah
I don't know who your friend is, but he will definitely be a big shot in the future.
But our restaurant is not so much delicious as it is high value for money.
A lot
I don't know your friend's name.
His name is Hong Young-seok
Hong Young-suk
Yingshuo?
Hong Young-suk?
Of course I know him.
It turns out to be Yingshuo's friend
He comes here to eat udon these days.
He is always like a udon noodle eater.
Auntie, are you free to have a soda with me?
Let's set a date first.
I have no problem booking it first
Damn, no cigarettes.
Hello
Hello...
It's a surprise to meet you here.
Um
How come you are here?
The aunt who worked at the exam udon told me this.
Say you might be here
Auntie
yes
I occasionally come to this second-hand bookstore
Because it's quiet
But how do you know my aunt?
That store is very famous on the exam students' forum.
It is said that the president of Noryangjin
That's right
Are you also preparing for the civil service exam?
I didn't join just to find you.
Me?
We didn't exchange contact information when we met last time.
I'm curious about your recent situation.
So that's it
Help me press
You won't get married, will you?
Or preparing to get married
It doesn't matter if you have children
You're still as clever as ever, Jin Zhihui
This is my phone
With my
When I was in high school, I always laughed with you.
It seemed like they were laughing all the time.
I'm funny now too.
What
I go to a company dinner and everyone gets sick the next day.
Because my stomach hurts from laughing
Is it that exaggerated?
I'll laugh until my stomach hurts
It hurts.
Really
Your hand strength is still very strong
Can I contact you occasionally?
Um
But I often can't answer the phone
I'll call you back
That's right
I think you're out of cigarettes.
you…
What's this
Smoking is bad for your health. Just smoke a little.
Supreme Wisdom
This ghost is really...
What are you doing?
Why don't you just do it now with your eyes closed?
No, Choi Yu-ri
You're such a bad woman.
How painful is Zhien now?
but
I am in pain too
So noisy
Can you let me sit at the same table?
boss
Please give me a Coke
And egg rolls
Oh, and a bowl of rice.
How are you
Don't just drink
Let's eat something first
You probably haven't eaten all day.
cheers
What's going on?
Hello, what's the situation?
What happened
World War 29 begins
Dad secretly played stocks without letting Mom know
There's nothing wrong with playing stocks
Hey, how can you kick Dad out like this?
Lost 30 million yuan
Hey, isn't this Dad's?
It was thrown outside
Really
Upper shelf of living room bookcase
"Financial Expert Tips to Make Your Wife Happy"
Page 78 Page 88 Page 98
Page 78
(Financial expert tips to make your wife happy)
Madam, please give me another cup.
good
dad
Cheer up
It is common for men to lose money in the stock market.
It's not a loss of 300 million, it's just 30 million
It's 50 million
Fifty million?
You've been receiving a state salary your whole life.
Why play the stock market?
Didn't you tell me not to covet money that wasn't earned through hard work?
But you...
what do I do
Go away
dad
We're going home
No…
At least I have to escape today
Sorry
Let you see your father's miserable appearance
Go away
Welcome
Do you know what life and soju have in common?
sister
You only drank less than a bottle of soju, okay?
The commonality is...
Both are two words
Should I just drop the package on her?
Me today
Experienced my first kiss
But that kiss wasn't the beginning
But the end
Since we want to help, it is best to help to the end.
And I probably saw it too.
The relationship between Yun Jae and Ji Hoon is unusual
That was my first kiss
The question is, is it the first time?
How important is the first time?
If I had kissed you two or three times, I wouldn't be so troubled.
This is not like
It's the admiration of fans
That madman
Follow me
What? Sister... where are you going?
I'm not mentally prepared yet
He's Park Yoon-jae, right?
Yun Jae
How did he get in there?
Are you going with Zhixun?
He just went to see his mother.
Otherwise
It's all because of you that I stayed up all night last night
What are you doing?
You said I was beautiful yesterday
It seems to be with Jiang Minzhou
who
Kang Min-joo
She likes Yun Jae
Did he go into the motel with her?
No wonder I felt something was wrong.
Something is wrong
Is he cheating?
I heard them asking each other if they slept well.
You said I was beautiful last night
Also said this
What the fuck
Can you teach me hairdressing techniques?
What are you going to do after learning this?
No
It's hard for me to find a job as a man now.
So I want to learn from you in the store
Yes, wife.
I think it's good.
Do you think anyone can be a hairdresser?
Your hands are not good
That's why I want you to teach me.
Hey, what's wrong, Yuri?
Me? I'm in my mom's shop.
Yun Jae? I just spoke to him on the phone.
What's wrong
Did you say motel?
Who did you say he went to the motel with?
Where is he
Where is Park Yoon-jae?
Did he really go in with Kang Min Joo?
real
Hi, brother
I'm sorry to see you in this situation.
How could Park Yun-jae do this to me?
You call him now
Yun Jae is out
He was wearing a coat today.
Not anymore
Terrible
I can't stand this.
Hello Park Yun-jae
Hi
Why are you here?
What "Hi"?
You were caught red-handed and you're still so calm
Hey, Jin Zhien, come out.
Hello
What's going on with you guys?
Zhixun, why are you here?
We saw it all
Saw you in and out of the motel
I calculated the time and you were in there for 1 hour, 7 minutes and 34 seconds.
You calculated the time.
Did you go with Min-joo?
Did you go there with Kang Min-joo?
What nonsense are you talking about?
I went with my dad
Your dad?
It would sound better if you said you were with your mother.
Although this situation can easily lead you to misunderstand
But I really went with my dad.
You take the lead
For what
If you're so confident
Just take us in to have a look.
Well said
Is it really okay?
There's nothing to lose anyway.
Aren't you going to come to my house as a tutor?
Is tutoring still important now?
You are very funny today
Let's go
Hey, keep up.
sister
Would it be too much to ask us to go with you?
Park Yun-jae is the one who went too far
Hurry up and catch up
Watch it
dad
Who is this?
So you are Jiang Minzhou
No
what the hell
sorry
I misread the room number.
Really
sorry
No, it's next door.
I really like this. Open the door quickly.
It's really next door.
I misread the room number.
Follow me
This time I really look forward to it
dad
I said you left this behind.
Look, this is my dad.
My dad
It's my dad.
Look, it's my dad.
Hello, my dad.
It's my dad.
Look, it's not Jiang Minzhou.
My dad
sorry
sister
Sister, where are you going?
Really
Okay, it's okay.
I'm a little sad
Forget about others
I didn't expect you to doubt me
sorry
I've always said it's impossible.
But they are so sure
I didn't expect you to distrust me so much
If I hadn't seen you and Kang Min Joo like that...
What did you see me and Jiang Minzhou doing?
Actually, I saw
You and Jiang Minzhou looked at each other affectionately in the coffee shop
Me?
We really have no relationship.
I knew you would say that.
So I'm not going to tell you
sorry
We are really nothing.
Just a simple senior student
I'll keep an eye on you
goodbye
But I also have something to say
I saw you kissing Yuri.
I feel really bad.
That wasn't a kiss, it was just a touch for a second
Not three seconds?
sorry
I'll draw the line later.
I'll keep an eye on you
You go in
"I see your eyes"
"Full of tears"
"I will never shed tears again"
"believe me now"
"Open your eyes"
What are you doing?
Why is Dad here?
Why would she dress like this?
Your mother told me to go home immediately
Did they ask you to dress like this?
She said she would forgive me as long as I was cute
Wrong, not cute at all.
I feel like my mom will file for divorce right away.
Yizuo
Seriously…
Park Yun-jae
Why are you looking for me so early in the morning?
What's with the bow on her head?
How is this?
Do you want to dance together?
Lift your feet like this...
Hand hook and circle
How is this
"What if I mix heart mix heart so my heart"
"I haven't woken up from my dream yet."
"Why am I hanging around you again?"
Come again
One or Two
"Can't stop"
"can't stop thinking about you"
What are you two doing here so early in the morning?
Minjoo, why are you here so early in the morning?
Me? I'm moving here.
Moving? Where?
here
Is this here?
This house?
Opposite Room 202, 2nd Floor
(Thanks to Kang Shin-il, Park Myung-shin, and Ye-won for their special appearances)
My girlfriend is more handsome than me.
Yun Jae, help me.
I'm so jealous I'm going crazy
I feel a little hot too.
I'd better go home directly.
The cheating guy next door...
Maybe I twisted my ankle because I walked too fast.
I will be worried if you go home alone
Can't read books
Brother Zhixun
She has been pretending to be familiar
But how did she know my number?
Why would you think of looking up?
Do you want to win Park Yoon-jae's heart?