♪Longing during the day
and loneliness at night♪
♪Clouds drift and curl,
and the cold rain falls again♪
♪Green grass once dreamed of the world
and enlightened me♪
♪I crossed the sea of suffering
but couldn't escape your gaze♪
♪Look at the bright moon
across the Milky Way♪
♪All love poems will record our story
from now on♪
♪The thought of the distant mountain
makes my heart ache for my hometown♪
♪Stone of Three Lifetimes reflects fate.
You once rode past on horseback♪
=Just Wanna Be With You=
(Adapted From
Zhihu Novelist, Little Qi's)
("Three Marriages
to the Underworld Lord")
=Episode 14=
(Demon Clan)
As a custodian, you're in charge
of life and death in the three realms.
That makes you a powerful figure.
I've been waiting long for you.
Spare the formalities, My Lord.
Just get down to business.
I heard about you looking for someone.
She used to be your wife,
but she betrayed you.
Why go through all the trouble?
She will become a mortal
after her reincarnation.
And her fate is not to be known.
Here is a reminder for you.
There is a price to every favor.
Only if you can tell me
about Jiang Zhiyu's whereabouts.
Where do I get in return, then?
I can give you my heart.
Sure.
That mortal has been
around for twenty years.
Little did I expect
the new Demon Lord
to be lovesick.
Don't you regret it.
My Lord.
A report from our mole.
Jiang Zhiyu's memories have been erased.
And she's had her reincarnation.
Jiang Jinghuai gave his heart away
in exchange of her whereabouts.
I'm afraid he's going
to look for her in the mortal realm.
Fine.
If we manage to remind Jiang Zhiyu
of her vengeance,
they will end up killing each other.
Yu.
Will you
marry me?
Yu.
My love for you will last till death.
(You're nothing but my stand-in
in the mortal realm.)
(Though you look exactly like me,)
(you still don't deserve her.)
(Yu.)
(Don't you forget this.)
(No matter where you are,)
(you and I will be together forever.)
Here comes the auspicious hour.
Who am I?
You're my husband, Jiu.
(Yu.)
(Let us forget about all the hatred)
(as well as worries.)
(It's also nice)
(to be an ordinary married couple
in this mortal realm.)
You're hurting me, my dear.
Don't touch it.
(He is not your husband.)
(He is a fake.)
We don't know one another.
Why are you in my dream
to tell me my husband is a fake?
Who exactly are you?
That evil killed your husband
and took his place by wearing his skin.
Your husband howled
in the woods every night
and begged me to save him.
Little did I expect you
to be so idiotic.
Jiu has always been kind and innocent.
And what's with this evil being
who's going to marry you?
Jiu.
Where did you get that?
I got this at the temple.
It's said to be able
to get rid of evil beings
in a household.
Throw it away.
Why?
I said, throw it away!
No more items from the temple
in this household again.
Don't forget
about our wedding tomorrow.
Jiu.
Tomorrow
is the Day of the Seven Killings.
They say we should avoid
getting married on that day.
So, can we...
Like I said, I will make you my wife
tomorrow.
If he's not my husband,
who is he, then?
That is a skin-wearer.
I bet you've seen that scar
on his chest.
That's the seam where the human skin
was stitched together.
Don't touch it.
If you don't believe me...
Just stab his chest
with that hairpin on your head.
And your husband will come back to life.
I dare not do so.
I'm sure I'll miss it.
Here he is.
♪Dark clouds cover the stars
without a trace of light♪
♪Waiting for the wind
to clear the grey away♪
♪Sudden rain falls
and I get soaked alone♪
♪Even larks know where they belong♪
♪It is not about running away♪
♪I search for you across the vast sky,
but where are you now?♪
♪I become a wisp of wind,
wiping away the clouds' traces♪
♪I long to disappear without a trace,
wrapped in mystery♪
♪If I send your loneliness
back to the sky♪
♪It can only rest inside your dreams♪
♪You and I gaze
at the endless Milky Way♪
♪Holding each other so near♪
♪If I were granted
a pair of splendid wings♪
♪I could chase memories
in place of the right to love♪
♪But the Milky Way never ends♪
♪In this thin robe,
I wait for your reply♪