♪Longing during the day
and loneliness at night♪
♪Clouds drift and curl,
and the cold rain falls again♪
♪Green grass once dreamed of the world
and enlightened me♪
♪I crossed the sea of suffering
but couldn't escape your gaze♪
♪Look at the bright moon
across the Milky Way♪
♪All love poems will record our story
from now on♪
♪The thought of the distant mountain
makes my heart ache for my hometown♪
♪Stone of Three Lifetimes reflects fate.
You once rode past on horseback♪
=Just Wanna Be With You=
(Adapted From
Zhihu Novelist, Little Qi's)
("Three Marriages
to the Underworld Lord")
=Episode 7=
My dear.
I told you, in life or death,
you belong to me.
Now, seeing you like this,
it truly breaks my heart.
You can drop the act.
You kept me here
only because you want
the Lingxiao clan's spirit stone.
Why go so far just to humiliate me?
Good. As long as you know.
That foxfolk has already
sunk beneath the Ice Lake.
His soul has long been destroyed.
You're so vicious.
You don't deserve
to be called an immortal.
I told you.
In life, you're mine.
And in death,
your soul still belongs to me.
Stop thinking about that foxfolk slave.
His name is Jiang Jinghuai.
You're not even worth
a single finger of his...
If he hadn't stirred up trouble,
you and I would already
be husband and wife!
Even if you have my body,
you will never have my heart.
Let's see how long
you can keep talking tough.
To marry me,
to become the mistress of Cangyun,
to be worshipped by foxfolk
and Cangyun alike,
that is the greatest honor
you could ever receive.
Honor?
All of this is nothing
but disgrace to the Lingxiao clan.
Disgrace?
Then let me show you
what true pain of severed love
and broken bonds feels like.
What are you doing?
From this moment on,
forget Jiang Jinghuai.
Your heart must belong only to me!
No... No!
Jiang Zhiyu!
Don't!
I, Jiang Jinghuai, swear this.
With the Silver Snow Flower as witness,
in every life I live,
I will love only Jiang Zhiyu.
(I will marry you.)
(Will you?)
No!
(I do.)
(In this life, flowers in our hair.
In the next, beauty again.)
(This is the vow of our foxfolk.)
(Jiang Zhiyu,)
(I like you.)
I don't want to forget you.
Huai, I don't want to forget you!
I love him.
I want to marry him.
(Last night's starlight,
last night's breeze...)
(- Beneath the laurel hall, by the western tower...)
(- Yu.)
(I wish to follow you
through endless lifetimes)
(and stay with you in the mortal world.)
No...
Forget it!
(Let me give you a name.)
(Jiang Jinghuai.)
Jiang Zhiyu.
(I have a new name now.)
(I'm really happy.)
Jiang Jinghuai!
Don't!
Husband.
My dear.
Let's pick a day for our wedding.
(Cangyun.)
Sister.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have led you out.
Your immortal soul has been extracted.
You're in grave danger.
You should worry
more about your own safety.
Sister.
You must hate me now.
Right?
The Goddess would never hate you.
You worked so hard for her.
But Nangong Xiao used you.
This is not your fault.
You don't deserve any of this.
My sister has yet to reach the realm
needed to activate the spirit stone.
The spirit stone remains dormant.
She has endured Nangong Xiao's cruelty
all the time
just to...
Just to protect the people
of the three realms.
You have your own life.
You should live it for yourself.
Thank you.
Yan Luo.
Jiang Zhiyu's thread of love
has been removed.
She only recognizes me
as her husband now.
The foxfolk slave
has sunk beneath the Ice Lake.
The Goddess has severed all love.
They can never be together again.
Wise decision, My Lord.
The Heavenly Emperor
has agreed to our wedding.
Who says one can't have both
the spirit stone and the three realms?
I, Nangong Xiao, will have it all.
Ying.
Sister.
Are you okay?
I...
I'm fine.
But Ying...
I can't shake the feeling
that I've forgotten something important.
What could it be?
♪Wild geese glide past
the autumn in my eyes♪
You haven't forgotten anything.
Everything's fine now.
Isn't it?
♪The low moon weighs down my weary brow♪
You're about to get married.
Ever since we were little,
I've always thought
you're the best person
in all three realms.
♪Like snow falling across the sky♪
Ying, always teasing your sister.
You'll look so beautiful that day.
Won't you?
♪All ends in nothing
like someone I once knew♪
Sister.
No matter what happens,
I just want you to be happy forever.
If you're happy,
so am I.
If you're sad,
then I'll be sad too.
Ying...
Ying, what's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm happy.
♪Drifting under sky and sea♪
♪One journey through life♪
Don't cry, Ying.
Aren't you supposed
to be happy for your sister?
♪The setting sun shatters my thoughts♪
♪Like snow falling across the sky♪
♪Fearless are the falling flowers
chasing the flowing stream♪
♪All ends in nothing
like someone I once knew♪
♪I fear time turning to ash in a blink♪
♪Even more I fear the long road
with no one beside me♪
♪Chasing moon and breeze,
I drink to longing♪
♪Grew old in silence,
never said what I meant♪
♪I fear time turning to ash in a blink♪
♪Even more I fear my thoughts
drifting under sky and sea♪
♪One journey through life
brings sorrow more than joy♪
♪Tell me what love in this world
comes without tears♪
♪I fear time turning to ash in a blink♪
♪Even more I fear the long road
with no one beside me♪
♪Chasing moon and breeze,
I drink to longing♪
♪Grew old in silence,
never said what I meant♪