=Generation to Generation=
=Episode 14=
Thank you very much.
Miss Feng.
Mr. Dai.
- Village Chief.
- Miss Feng.
Thank you, Miss Feng.
It's a relief you're unharmed.
Village Chief,
weren't you told to hide first?
The Village Chief said
he wouldn't be at ease
until he saw you safe.
Luckily, we made it in time.
Did they make things hard for you?
No, no.
They just locked me up.
I got lucky.
I found a hidden passage
and ran out to meet up with Qingyun.
How fortunate you are.
Many thanks to you both.
Otherwise,
who knows what would've happened?
We've always lived here
by the rules and kept the sect laws.
I truly don't know why they arrested us.
Even if Xing did something wrong,
they shouldn't have taken
the whole village.
Why would they seize the villagers?
We're sect members after all.
One of their own.
They're making corpse slaves.
Corpse slaves?
What are those?
Corpse slaves...
Village Chief,
you've seen them before?
Nineteen years ago,
when the former chief,
Nie Hengcheng, was still alive,
my eldest nephew
was taken and made into a corpse slave.
He died on the Youming Path.
Those turned into corpse slaves
lose all reason
and are controlled by others,
and in the end, their bodies rot away.
After the Battle of Mount Tu,
I thought the nightmare
was finally over.
Yet they've
started again.
Xiaohan,
we must return at once
and report this
to Master.
I fear that before we can report it,
the villagers will be fully refined.
By then, the Hanhai Mountains
and Jianghu will face disaster.
The priority now
is to stop them from continuing
to make corpse slaves.
I know a place
that might
hold a way to stop them.
(Li Sect, Jiuzhou Archive,
Treasured Tomes)
Come.
When I was young,
I once came here to clean.
I heard
this place holds books and records
collected by generations of chiefs.
The former chief disliked reading
and locked this place away.
After his death,
no one remembered it anymore.
I'll look for any texts
that mention corpse slaves.
(Jiuzhou Archive)
Jiuzhou Archive?
Miss Feng,
you've heard of it too?
I once heard a friend mention it.
Was this friend of yours
someone of high standing in the sect?
I only know
he read some books in Jiuzhou Archive
and even found a dragon beast scale.
Your friend must be the Mu kid.
(Yan Xu, Elder Zhibi of Li Sect)
Elder Yan.
Elder Yan,
you're still alive?
Gui,
we haven't met in over ten years,
and the first thing you do
is curse me to death?
Village Chief,
you know him?
This is Elder Zhibi of Li Sect.
Elder Yan,
who specializes
in recording sect history.
I hadn't heard from you for years.
Nie Hengcheng died suddenly
and named no successor.
Nie Zhe took the position improperly,
so he locked me here,
trying to force me
to alter sect history.
A year ago, Mu Qingyan
was gravely injured by Nie Zhe.
Luckily, he hid here.
I saved his life.
With his aloof and unruly nature,
he'd even have friends?
Who are you?
How did you meet him?
After he escaped from here,
he reached Qingzhu Gang to recover.
We learned he was in danger this time,
so we came to help.
No wonder you were going
to Qinglong Altar.
Elder Yan,
you must have examined
all the books here.
Do you know
a cure for corpse slaves?
Corpse slaves?
Didn't they disappear long ago?
Nie Zhe has started refining them again.
I suppose
he means to use them against Mu Qingyan.
That scoundrel Nie Zhe
is becoming
more and more like his uncle.
Ignorant, reckless, and tyrannical.
Let's talk about corpse slaves first.
The records say
corpse slaves are refined
using Gu worms
and Shanci Mushroom poison.
As long as we find herbs
that counter the poison,
we can temporarily suppress
their toxicity.
But I don't know
how to completely remove it.
All things restrain one another.
If we find where Shanci Mushrooms grow,
we'll surely find what counters them.
I know where they grow.
I'll go.
We'll go together.
Why are there so many people?
The EightClaw Prison was destroyed.
To restart the refining pool,
they'll need a large amount
of the mushrooms.
Xiaohan, take care
of the three on the right.
Two.
I'll handle the rest.
The summons has sounded.
Hurry to assemble. Go.
The summons of Li Sect.
Something must've happened
near Xuanwu Altar.
Could it be Mu Qingyan?
Has he begun attacking Xuanwu Altar?
They're using corpse slaves
to deal with him.
Hurry and find the antidote.
(Li Sect, Xuanwu Altar)
Mr. Mu,
over a year ago,
you fled in disgrace.
Everyone thought you were dead.
The Chief was merciful
and even set up a cenotaph for you.
You feel no gratitude for his kindness,
yet you turn on us instead?
Li Sect
belongs to the Mu clan to begin with.
Anyone with sense
wouldn't stop the Young Master.
Shut up, You Guanyue.
Is this your place to speak?
You rose by slick words
and shameless flattery.
Look around.
Who here truly respects you?
You...
Mu Qingyan,
with the strategist here today,
prepare to die.
This time,
you won't even get a cenotaph.
Enough talk.
Young Master,
kill Xiong Qianjin,
and we'll wipe out Xuanwu Altar.
Not me.
You'll do it.
Me?
You'll fight Master Xiong
one-on-one,
fair and square.
If you survive,
then the Xuanwu and Qinglong Altars
will both be under your command.
Young Master,
my skills are lacking.
If I lose by mistake,
my shame is one thing,
but if it dampens
your momentum in reclaiming the sect,
wouldn't that be
an unforgivable sin?
You Guanyue,
you've spent
half your life currying favor,
smiling, and ingratiating yourself.
But that alone isn't enough
to win hearts.
If you want to be an elder
or an enforcer someday,
you'll need to show real skill.
Go.
Kill him.
Consider it your grand opening.
You want me
to fight this piece of trash?
If you can defeat You Guanyue,
I'll spare you today.
You're far too arrogant.
Prepare to die!
You Guanyue,
you'd followed Elder Qiu for years.
He was called the Undying Phoenix,
one who dared to shed his own flesh.
- He won!
- Master You, impressive!
Well done, Master You!
Xiong Qianjin aided evil for years,
slaughtering innocent sect members.
His crimes are countless
and unforgivable.
Killing him today
serves as a warning to all.
As for what comes next,
please enlighten me.
I'll always serve you, Young Master.
We'll always serve you, Young Master.
Flatten Xuanwu Altar.
Kill them!
Charge!
Time is tight.
How do these herbs
counter the Shanci Mushroom poison?
You go back
to Jiuzhou Archive first.
I'll catch a corpse slave
to test the medicine.
- Sure.
- No need.
I'll do it.
When were you poisoned?
No time for this.
Test the medicine first. If it fails,
kill me with one strike.
Then find a place and bury me.
Just take the Sunshine Blade back.
Don't talk nonsense.
It won't come to that.
Why are you so distracted?
I was just thinking about Zhao.
She's been ill for nearly a month now.
I wonder when she'll recover.
She left to find Chang Ning, right?
How do you know?
She took the herbal incense
I prepared for Chang Ning.
That child,
bold and decisive by nature,
is very much like her aunt.
Chang must've gone
to seek revenge against the demon sect.
Uncle Lei,
tell me.
What is this demon sect like?
Is it dangerous?
We'll see
if she comes back intact.
Yu Huiyin.
Corpse slaves.
Nie Zhe is using
corpse slaves against us.
Young Master,
these corpse slaves feel no pain.
They can't be killed; what do we do?
Break!
Mr. Mu,
you led men to attack my Xuanwu Altar.
Aren't you afraid
the Chief will punish you
and order your execution,
disregarding your families' ties?
Master Shangguan, don't joke.
Nie Zhe is using sect members' lives
to refine corpse slaves.
He's broken a century-old sect rule.
What family ties are left to speak of?
The Chief hasn't touched
a single core member.
He's only used
low-cultivation commoners.
The Chief said
these people
are nothing but vermin.
Even commoners
are loved ones of sect disciples.
How can Nie Zhe trample them at will?
Enough provocation.
You're about to die
and still spout nonsense.
Strike the neck and spine.
Mr. Yu,
I'll assist you.
Are you okay?
I saw something was wrong
with you long ago.
Shangguan Haonan,
you truly are a traitor.
Yu Huiyin,
you aid evil
and slaughter sect members with Nie Zhe.
Once the truth
of the corpse slaves spreads,
let's see who in the sect
will still support you.
Dead men
don't speak.
So, the poison in you
was never fully cured.
Young Master!
Young Master,
I'll carve a path out for you.
Fate has favored me.
Xing...
Young Master, don't hurt her.
Demoness,
you're Cai Pingshu's...
Mu Qingyan!
Are you okay?
You're awake.
Zhao,
you're here.
The herbal incense has been burning
for four hours.
How do you feel?
I'm fine.
Uncle Lei prepared
this herbal incense for you.
It contains dozens of herbs.
It can't eradicate your poison,
but it can suppress it for now.
So, you already know.
You know,
the Li Sect's tailoring craft
is no worse than Granny Needle's.
You look handsome in this outfit.
Like someone from a painting.
So, you're here
to pity a dying man like me?
Everyone dies.
Some die sooner;
some die later.
There is nothing strange about it.
Why would I pity you?
Ever since I can remember,
I knew my aunt was nearing the end.
But I never felt
she needed anyone's pity.
The day before she passed,
she even made Smiley with me.
It was fragrant and sweet that day.
She said
her wishes in this life were fulfilled.
Even if she died,
she would have no regrets.
So, are you here
to help me fulfill my wish?
I'll use every possible way to save you.
If I cannot save you,
I will help you
fulfill your wish.
If you want revenge,
I will help you take revenge.
What then?
Then?
I'll go back to Qingque sect with Yuzhi?
Don't leave.
Okay, I won't.
All right.
I'll leave after I finish things, okay?
Zhao, this is...
People slip up sometimes.
Horses stumble too.
It just happened by accident.
Don't worry.
I've found herbs to suppress the poison.
If the Gu worms aren't cleared in time,
they'll erode your mind.
You'll lose your senses and die.
Do you know that?
I'm sorry.
We've only been apart for days,
and you've turned yourself
into this state.
It's fine.
The fortune teller said
I'd live a long life.
I don't believe in fate.
I only believe in myself.
What are you trying to do?
Thankfully, we have the medicine
Miss Feng brought.
Xing should wake up soon.
Be gentle.
I'm performing acupuncture on Xing.
Why do you hurt more than she does?
Xing, forgive me.
You're so clumsy.
You're driving me crazy.
Why don't you do it yourself?
If I weren't injured,
would I need you?
A fence-sitter
who only knows how to talk.
I...
At least I'm not like you,
living off flattery toward Nie Zhe,
holding a post without doing any work.
Who are you talking about?
Whoever gets angry is who I mean.
Are you feeling guilty?
You Guanyue.
Xing.
So naggy that my ears hurt.
Go away.
Do you feel unwell?
Take me to Miss Feng.
Xing.
- Xing.
Mr. Dai.
Thanks to you and Miss Feng
for saving my life.
It seems the Gu poison in you has eased.
My Xing is fine.
No need for you to worry.
That's good then.
I came to look for Xiaohan.
What a coincidence.
We're also here for Miss Feng.
She and the Young Master
spent the night together.
They must be
deeply in love
and inseparable now.
Get lost.
Zhao...
Your valor conquered Xuanwu Altar.
Xing and I came to offer
congratulations and thanks.
Did you argue with Xiaohan?
I wanted to take Zhao's pulse
and examine her,
but she refused.
Examine her...
Examine her?
Mr. Mu,
is there a way to fully eradicate
the Gu poison in Xiaohan?
Yan Xu fears Nie Zhe,
so he must be holding something back.
I'll go to Jiuzhou Archive now
to find Yan Xu.
We just settled here.
There's much work awaiting you.
Besides,
you've fought several rounds
with unhealed injuries.
I'm fine.
Mr. Mu,
let me go find Elder Yan.
You stay here.
If Nie Zhe counterattacks,
you'll be ready.
Senior,
do you feel any better today?
Same as always.
Just barely hanging on.
Senior,
Mu Qingyan is advancing aggressively.
In a few days,
he'll likely attack Bliss Palace.
You useless thing.
You've ruled the sect for over ten years
on your uncle's behalf,
yet now you're being beaten
by that Mu brat.
If not for Shangguan's betrayal
and Yu Huiyin and Fengge's injuries,
how would I have fallen into this state?
Senior,
please give me some guidance.
You wouldn't just watch Uncle's legacy
be destroyed, would you?
If my legs hadn't been crippled
by Cai Pingshu,
how would it come to this?
Very well.
Lure that Mu brat here.
I'll eliminate this threat to the sect.
Shangguan,
you traitorous wretch.
The Chief trusted you so deeply,
yet you betrayed him.
How fickle
and ungrateful.
The Young Master arrives.
Young Master,
all forces of Xuanwu Altar are here,
awaiting your judgment.
Crooked mouth and slanted eyes.
Kill him.
- Go.
- Let me go.
Let me go.
Shifty-eyed and sneaky.
Kill him.
What are you doing?
- Let me go.
- Two-faced turncoat.
Kill him.
What are you doing?
- Go.
- No more nonsense.
He can't tell grain from millet.
Kill him.
Lazy and useless.
Young Master.
Spare my life.
Talkative
and meddlesome.
Kill them all.
- Spare me.
We're willing to surrender.
Young Master, spare us.
Please, spare us.
Get up.
Go.
Are you really going to kill them all?
They're nothing but people
who repeatedly broke sect rules
and are drenched in blood.
Why not?
But such a large Xuanwu Altar
still needs people
to handle odds and ends.
It might be better to keep a few.
They're all top-tier fighters.
They'd cause grudges between us
and those they once persecuted,
or even waver and secretly collude
with Nie Zhe.
Before yesterday's battle,
the Young Master ordered me
to leave a corner open in the northeast
so the weak-willed could escape.
Those who stayed to resist
are all utterly loyal
to Nie Zhe and Xiong Qianjin.
What use are they?
So, you've filtered them out.
I was short-sighted.
You and Shangguan are both soft-hearted.
Handing them to you
would inevitably be a risk.
All these years, you dealt cautiously
with Nie Zhe and his faction.
Thanks for your efforts.
From now on,
I'll return to you
a clean and pure sect.
Ever since you were injured by Nie Zhe
and went missing,
I nearly failed endure.
I always remembered your kindness
and found ways
to maneuver among them.
But watching them harm sect members
was truly tormenting.
Nie kept
probing and testing me.
Life was unbearable.
Dealing with that suspicious rat?
Shangguan,
it hasn't been easy for you.
You did very well.
I had you investigate something.
What did you find?
When I was young in the Demonic Camp,
I once saw Elder Tianji Duan Jiuxiu
use the Wudu Palm to kill for practice.
But from my observation,
what Nie Zhe practices
has the moves but lacks inner force.
He hasn't truly mastered the Wudu Palm.
(It's not the Wudu Palm?)
(Then what is the poison in my body?)
Young Master,
Mr. Dai has brought Elder Yan Xu.
I don't know.
And even if I did, I wouldn't tell you.
Stop bothering with that.
Hurry and send me back.
If you refuse to speak,
I can only tell Nie Zhe
that when I fled the sect back then,
it was you who helped me.
You...
If you're willing to share something,
I guarantee
that before I take over Bliss Palace,
I never once met you.
Excellent.
When you take Bliss Palace,
I'll personally congratulate you.
I've never seen a fence-sitter
be so fresh and shameless.
You little brat.
(Qinglong Altar)
I've said it several times.
You dragged me here for no reason
just to ask
about this Gu-clearing method.
I truly haven't seen it.
How many times do you want to ask?
Corpse slaves first appeared
19 years ago, in early spring.
You know
the former chief's movements best.
Do you recall whether Nie Hengcheng
visited any special place then?
This matter...
I think I remember.
That March,
the former leader often went
near the Youming Path.
There was a herbal garden inside.
Every time he went there,
he'd stay for quite a while.
Where is this herbal garden?
It's a secret realm of the Nie clan.
Outsiders don't know.
The Youming Path...
Lady Sun, it's so late.
Why are you in such a remote place?
Picking flowers for the Chief.
These flowers must have night dew
to be effective.
(Is the place
where Lady Sun picked flowers)
(the herbal garden?)
I know a place.
The herbal garden might be there.
I'll go with you.
Let's go.
Don't go.
I've prepared a decoction for you
to suppress the Gu poison in your body.
Mr. Dai,
may we talk privately?
=Generation to Generation=
♪The breeze is gentle,
and spring is fair♪
♪I roam the rivers and hills
in the martial world♪
♪With a shining cup,
I drink with delight tonight♪
♪Free to wander in the world♪
♪I drink with the breeze,
lost in my dreams♪
♪I rest beneath the stars' soft gleam♪
♪The night is calm, still as a stream♪
♪It washes away all judgment and scheme♪
♪I drink with the breeze,
lost in my dreams♪
♪I hold the bright moon
as I return home♪
♪I freely roam in the world♪
♪All I ask is that you go with me♪
♪I drink with the breeze,
lost in my dreams♪
♪I hold the bright moon
as I return home♪
♪I freely roam in the world♪
♪All I ask is that you go with me♪