=Generation to Generation=
=Episode 3=
(Pillar of Righteousness)
You wouldn't leave me
just to lure me to find
Yin Dai's handbook, right?
What exactly is in the handbook?
I just want to help you
uncover the truth.
Why don't you trust me?
I'll report to Master immediately.
I'm looking for the handbook
to avenge my father.
What does your revenge
have to do with Yin Dai's handbook?
It's said that the handbook
records the Disintegration,
a secret skill
passed down through generations
of Qingque lords.
Disintegration?
Rumor has it
that Nie Hengcheng
died from this technique.
If I can master it,
I'll surely avenge my father.
You fabricated a name
and tried to deceive me.
You've mostly recovered.
Move out tomorrow.
Disintegration
was created by Founder Beichen.
It can instantly boost power
and make one invincible.
Though formidable,
it'll backfire on the user.
(Young Cai Pingchun)
Meridians will collapse.
(Young Ning Xiaofeng)
Martial skills will be lost.
Ultimately,
the user will be dead.
Zhao, have you thought
why your aunt would practice this?
If nothing were suspicious,
why is Yin Dai's handbook missing
in the secret room?
Zhao.
Zhao?
Zhao,
do you think I'm very bad?
My effort has been in vain.
Xiaolan,
martial arts is like this.
At first, progress is slow.
You must be patient.
Later,
your power will grow steadily.
I'll go to Herb Hut later
to find some herbs
to strengthen your foundation.
Thanks, Zhao.
Though I can't be famous in Jianghu
at a young age and slay
the Chief of the demon sect alone
like Ms. Cai,
I'll take her as a role model
and never slack.
But she paid a heavy price.
The medicine for you.
Thanks, Uncle Lei.
Uncle Lei,
have you heard
of the Disintegration?
Who told you?
Will the user face
meridians collapse
and lose martial skills?
This fatal move
is forbidden.
Thus, successive Qingque lords
never taught it to outsiders.
Then why did Yin Dai...
Everyone is gone.
Why chase
old grudges?
This is a calming pouch for Chang Ning.
Take it back for him.
Yes.
Where did you go last night?
Did you go to the Library?
What's wrong?
I'm here for Chang.
I asked Xingjia to verify.
This calming powder
was developed by Uncle Lei for Chang.
I don't know
how it ended up in the Library.
I didn't get to deliver
the powder for Ning.
Last night, in the Library,
I accidentally spilled it.
Zhao, last night,
why go to the Library?
To check recipes for a late-night snack.
But I didn't find the right one.
What?
Something lost in the Library?
No.
Just a plaque
fell inexplicably.
In that case,
I'll take my leave.
Yuzhi, goodbye.
I'll move out now.
Find the handbook first.
Yin Dai had only two daughters.
Song Yuzhi's mother,
Lady Qinglian, already passed.
So, his relics should be
with Lady Sulian.
I searched the sect thoroughly
and thought it'd be
in the Library's secret room.
Since it's not there,
it must be in Double Lotus Palace.
Unfortunately, I found nothing
in Treasure Vault.
In such a short time,
you've found out so much.
(Dusk Palace)
(Library)
Have you searched elsewhere?
Have you tried the waterway?
Waterway?
They have many guards.
If I recklessly dive in,
I might alert them.
Mid-Autumn is coming.
There should be
a celebration.
I have an idea.
Go find Lingbo and have another quarrel.
Lighting lanterns for Mid-Autumn
is a century-old tradition here.
With so many people this year,
my mother prepared over 100 lanterns.
It must be lively.
It's just a way
to honor your grandfather
and sing praises of your family.
My grandfather was a hero.
What's wrong with that?
Should we honor your family instead?
Chang Ning, I warn you.
This is a major event of the Six Sects.
Don't write Chang
on the lanterns.
Why not?
Father may not belong to the Six Sects,
but he is a hero.
Ridiculous.
Which hero hides sneakily
and sets traps?
I heard
the turf in Chang Fort was dug up.
What shameful thing
could you be hiding?
Ning,
time to go to Herb Hut.
I'll handle the lanterns.
Just put them here.
A little higher.
Xingjia.
What are you worried about?
Buying for the celebration
and the Patriarch's ceremony
cost a lot.
Money
just flows away,
faster than water.
Managing this is hard.
But Double Lotus Palace
looks splendid.
You don't seem short on money.
Stop thinking.
That is the Yins' private property,
not Qingque Sect's.
Hu paper is light and strong,
the best choice for lanterns,
but expensive.
Lady Yin insists on 100 lanterns.
Another large expense.
Why not use Xuan paper?
Xuan paper costs similar to Hu paper.
That was before.
Because Xuan paper was made
from mulberry bark.
Now, I heard
everyone uses Qingtan for Xuan paper,
so it's much cheaper than Hu paper.
That's perfect.
I'll go to buy more Xuan paper.
(Jiang)
♪The breeze is gentle♪
♪And spring is fair♪
♪I roam the rivers and hills♪
(Drinks in Spring)
♪With a shining cup♪
(Everlasting Peace)
Blessings
♪Free to wander♪
(Family Reunion)
♪I drink with the breeze,
lost in my dreams♪
♪I hold the bright moon
as I return home♪
♪I freely roam in the world♪
So beautiful.
There's more to see later.
(Generation to Generation)
What's that?
It's the Guming Moth.
Be careful.
One bite drives people mad.
(Long Life)
This moth feeds on Qingtan,
living in cool, secluded places.
Why appear suddenly?
Oh, no.
The lantern's paper contains Qingtan.
(Reunion and Harmony)
(Long Life, Longevity)
Ning!
Chang Ning was bitten?
Chang Ning, are you mad?
Those insulting my family
shall die!
Lingbo, run!
Chang's medicine contains Qingtan.
He must've gone mad from the bite.
Run!
Bad news!
Uncle Lei!
Chang Ning,
bitten by the Guming Moth, went mad.
He's shouting to kill Lingbo.
Uncle Lei,
should we intervene?
Everything has a cause.
Don't you understand why Chang Ning
acts against Lingbo?
A little suffering for Lingbo
is not necessarily bad.
But Chang Ning has lost his mind.
Will Lingbo be safe?
Will Chang be severely punished?
Bites from the Guming Moth can cause
hallucinations and madness,
but poison fades quickly.
It won't cause major trouble.
Out of respect for Lord Yin,
Master never punishes Lingbo properly
for her mistakes.
Similarly,
for the late Mr. Chang,
even if Chang Ning caused a mess,
Lord Qi won't severely punish
the orphan of the Chang family.
Uncle Lei,
the blessing charms are copied.
I'll leave first.
Since you've understood,
why still go?
Lady Yin is still there.
Stop him!
Stop him now!
Chang Ning!
Enough!
Zhao!
Have you had enough madness?
Come back with me.
What do you want?
Help!
Yuzhi!
Someone wants to kill me!
It's him!
- Ning.
- It's him!
He tried to kill me!
Lady Yin,
Ning's been missing his family,
so he's lost his mind.
I'll take him back to recover.
He'll apologize later.
Recovery comes first.
They just left like that?
Where is Master?
(No Regrets)
Xiaolan,
thank you this time.
Zhao, you're welcome.
I didn't do much.
There was no one by the lakeside.
How did you fall into the water?
I know
you wanted to help us.
I...
I don't know what happened.
I just felt that Nanny Mao was fierce;
I didn't want her to trouble you.
Zhao,
Mr. Chang is still injured.
Take him back now.
I'll go first.
Siqi Sect is useless,
but Yang Heying has a good daughter.
Sorry
about that.
Were you worried
that I'd kill Qi Lingbo?
Would you?
So many martial arts secrets.
Including Peiqiong Manor's swordsmanship
and our mindful ways.
Isn't he already the Lord?
Why collect martial secrets
from all sects?
Naturally, to unify Jianghu
for generations.
The fire is almost out.
I'll get it.
Let me.
Control movement.
Let the soul guard the body.
Change between fullness and emptiness.
Try to reverse.
This is the Disintegration.
It can stimulate all meridians
and boost power tenfold.
Truly extraordinary.
As you said,
Chang Ning
is crazy.
He even attacked Cai Zhao.
With Zhao's skill,
how could she fall
into the water so easily?
Lady Yin,
is the item hidden in the water
the one I brought as a child?
Exactly.
It's your grandfather's handbook,
recording the supreme martial arts
and martial arts secrets that he spent
half his life collecting.
But he was the former lord.
Shouldn't his handbook
be handed to Master?
Your grandfather's belongings
stay with the Yin descendants.
Your mother and I preserved them
for you.
But it's gotten this far.
We can no longer hide it from Master.
During the battle,
the Six Sects suffered heavy casualties.
I'm old and injured,
powerless to oppose the enemy.
Seeing the demons run rampant,
killing even more,
Pingshu of Luoying Valley
volunteered to slay Nie.
I had no choice but to teach her
our forbidden secret:
Disintegration.
(Young Cai Zhao, Luoying Valley)
(Disintegration)
If you wish to learn martial arts,
I'll spare no effort to teach you.
(Righteous Spirit)
Why go to such lengths?
Master,
did you know my aunt practiced
the Disintegration?
If I had known,
I would've risked
everything to stop her.
I only discovered it
while treating her injuries,
but it was too late.
The Disintegration
is a secret of Qingque lords.
My aunt is not your direct disciple,
so how could it be for her to learn?
I asked Lord Yin about this.
He said he was severely injured,
and his disciples were
either dead or invalid,
unable to resist the demons.
Pingshu volunteered
for the greater good.
He had no choice but to...
What?
To sacrifice my aunt
for the greater good?
I also
resented Master for this,
but soon after,
he was killed by the demon sect.
Zhao,
the previous generation's affairs
are for the previous generation
to bear and resolve.
You need not interfere.
No one is allowed
to practice this sinister move again.
The Founder's death anniversary
is near.
Master already exerts much effort.
Stop causing trouble.
The deceased are gone.
Master will handle the rest.
You must let go.
Let go?
Isn't this the consistent approach
of the Six Sects?
Is that how you see the Six Sects?
Isn't he right?
An unavoidable choice
shouldn't cost others' lives.
You're noble and upright,
act with integrity,
yet can let go easily.
I really admire that.
I don't intend to argue.
If you ever need me
for difficulties,
I won't refuse.
Yuzhi,
Chang Ning ruined the lantern festival
and injured Fengchi,
yet Father didn't punish him.
Does that mean it's over?
Originally,
he should've been punished,
but Yuzhi felt Ning had no choice,
so he pleaded for him.
Then Master calmed down.
Is that right,
Yuzhi?
He had no choice
but bully me?
Yuzhi just values reason more.
I'm grateful,
so I prepared sweet lotus congee.
My cooking is exceptional.
Yuzhi, why not come back
with us to try it?
Let's go.
What are you doing, Cai Zhao?
It's one thing to be involved
with Chang Ning.
Why drag my cousin?
I'll take you back first.
Yuzhi.
Yuzhi,
why always protect Cai Zhao?
She's only been here a few days.
We grew up together for over ten years.
Today's matter has nothing
to do with Zhao.
Don't trouble her again.
We owe Zhao anyway.
Owe her what?
You keep calling her Zhao.
How intimate.
She also has congee for you.
Yuzhi,
do you like her?
Nonsense.
Lingbo, you're no child.
You must mind limits.
Cai Zhao just held your hand.
Did she mind her limits?
Knowing about our betrothal,
she openly provoked me.
How shameless.
I'll say it again.
Cai Zhao is Master's disciple,
our junior sister.
If you continue slandering
and causing trouble,
forget our relationship.
Yuzhi!
(Control movement.)
(Let the soul guard the body.)
(Change between fullness and emptiness.)
(Try to reverse.)
Stop it.
Why?
You know how dangerous
this move is.
Those who practice it die in the end.
It's not worth it.
My life is for revenge.
If revenge costs my life, so be it.
When Ms. Cai went to meet Nie Hengcheng,
she knew she'd die.
Those who practice the Disintegration
will have their meridians destroyed
and organs collapse.
Do you know that pain?
She had suffered for 13 years.
She was only 30,
younger than Yin Sulian,
and had wasted away.
Nie Hengcheng is dead;
Yin Dai is dead.
I don't know who to hate now.
No matter who you are,
no matter your purpose,
you are forbidden to practice it.
As I said,
I'll protect you.
I'll never let you
die like my aunt.
Promise me.
Okay.
Swear.
I swear
never to practice the Disintegration.
Chang Ning.
I'm hungry.
I want some wonton.
Your disciple stole
my father's handbook.
It's been destroyed.
Let this matter end here.
You destroyed
my father's relics at will.
What do you take me for?
Keeping it would have been a hazard.
Do you want
the world to know
what your father did?
The martial arts knowledge inside
is all his life's work,
yet you've destroyed it?
What's the point of keeping it?
Lingbo is not suited for martial arts.
We both know that.
We have Yuzhi.
He'll inherit the sect eventually.
Once they marry,
we'll be family.
We could've given it to him.
If Lingbo continues to be so headstrong,
I fear Yuzhi
might not want to fulfill the betrothal.
He will,
and he won't dare,
unless
he doesn't want to be the future lord.
You made it?
Homemade cooking.
I wonder
if you'll like it.
It's just a bowl of wonton.
No need to be so touched.
This flavor
is exactly like my aunt's.
I've thought about it for three years.
Ning,
thank you.
Is there more?
If you like it,
I'll make more
when Han wakes up.
Wonderful.
By the way,
you swore yesterday.
No backing out.
Got it.
Your cooking is so good.
Why not open a diner
in Luoying Valley?
I'll be the shopkeeper;
you handle the kitchen.
We'll have the place
at the street's end,
so when people stroll from head to tail
and get hungry,
they'll come for a bowl of wonton,
leaving a lasting taste.
Perfect.
Chang Ning.
Why are you two here?
About the Mid-Autumn incident,
Master said not to pursue it further.
That night, my skills were inferior.
I have nothing more to say.
But now, it's not about that.
Chang,
Master orders you to go
to Dusk Palace now.
While searching for clues,
I unexpectedly learned
the Changs had an old steward
surnamed Jiang.
Five years ago,
the steward retired to his hometown
and took a boy with him.
After much investigation,
at Steward Jiang's grave,
I found Mr. Jiang,
who resembles the late Mr. Chang,
or rather,
the real Chang Ning.
=Generation to Generation=
♪The breeze is gentle,
and spring is fair♪
♪I roam the rivers and hills
in the martial world♪
♪With a shining cup,
I drink with delight tonight♪
♪Free to wander in the world♪
♪I drink with the breeze,
lost in my dreams♪
♪I rest beneath the stars' soft gleam♪
♪The night is calm, still as a stream♪
♪It washes away all judgment and scheme♪
♪I drink with the breeze,
lost in my dreams♪
♪I hold the bright moon
as I return home♪
♪I freely roam in the world♪
♪All I ask is that you go with me♪
♪I drink with the breeze,
lost in my dreams♪
♪I hold the bright moon
as I return home♪
♪I freely roam in the world♪
♪All I ask is that you go with me♪