I'm not going to forgive you for being so kind
If you give me the love that hurts
I'm going to cry, don't you think? No more
For you, for you, for you
I'm going to be kind and give you my feelings
I'm going to be the best I can be
To stop the evil deeds of the new captain
It's good that you've infiltrated the Deadmond's club
I'm in trouble
It's only five days until the club
I decided to infiltrate
I was collecting information about the Deadmond's club
I completely forgot about the dress
I don't have any clothes or decorations to wear
What I had was a stupid bullying
I was made a mess
I was wanted by Arian and gave it to him
After all, that ribbon
I haven't seen Arian wear it since then
But what should I do?
I wonder if I have to go to town
The candidate for the political party
Some of the money collected from the temple
The money that can be used freely is allocated
I applied and if it passes, I should get it
The new captain is in charge
I have never asked for anything and passed it once
What's wrong?
He
I'm here to deliver you
From Shiji
Shiji?
Is it from Suen?
It was heavy
Why do I have to carry something for you?
Moreover, Shiji is popular among the women
Because you like men
Did you make Shiji do it?
As always, it's a rude situation
I really want to give you a little pain
I have to try not to know this power
But wait
What is it?
Do you still need something?
Your words are not only for me
It is also a insult to Shiji
Please forgive me
Why me?
Shiji is the faithful servant of the Suen
I can't let him do that
It's a insult to both sides
I didn't mean to insult Shiji
You were trying to insult me
You used the name of the crown prince to insult me
And you and I are the candidates
Please stand up
I'm sorry
You can step back
I feel better
What did Suen send?
This is...
What a beautiful dress
Shoes and accessories
Dear Lua
I made a dress for you
I sent it as soon as possible
I also asked the royal court to make it popular
I wanted to make the decorations look good on you
Did you like it?
Suen
Suicid
You've been working without a break
I asked the temple to give you a long vacation
If you say something, show me this permit
You can rest in peace
You're so considerate
They're all wonderful
The rest is the earings
The earings are the only thing I have
This is my mother's treasure
I think I lost one of them
I miss her
Is she doing well?
That was the first time I used healing power other than my family
Since then, my family has been ill
When I came back from playing outside
This is my mother's treasure
I'm not powerless anymore
I'll make sure the mission is a success
The day of the martial arts meeting
Suen seems to be heading to the venue first
She made a reservation for this horse and Shiji
Did something happen, Luwa?
No
Please tell me when you're in a bad mood
I'm entrusted with the duty of the king
I understand
Shiji is a silent person
So it's a little awkward for two people
I miss the talkative Suen
Tonight the moon is hidden in the clouds
It's kind of ominous
Hi Luwa, you came
As I thought, Suen has the royal
Thank you, Suen
But don't overdo it
You were blonde, but your hair turned white
It's weird
Who said it was weird?
They're so blind
Your white hair is a proof of your strength
Even if you're proud, you won't be told to be disdained
How can you say that about my hair?
And it looks like my hair color
But it's the same as Shiji's
I'm kidding
Suen, you're in trouble
You finally smiled in front of me
Well, let's go
Yes
I'm sorry
Good luck
Look Luwa, that's Redmond's servant
I'm the one who's greeting you first
He looks like a white-haired man, but he's actually a good-looking man
As the rumors say, he's not good with women
I want to see him, I want to get close to him
Don't rush, let's move
Yes
Oh, this is Suen
I can't believe I can meet you
It's been a while, Your Highness
Suen has many people he can meet
I have to move instead of him
First, I have to observe the venue
Huh?
That woman in the 9 o'clock
She looks pale
I feel like I've thought of something
I'll try to call her
Um
Oh, Luwa is over there
This voice
Alian
Your Highness
I'm sorry
Even today, I'm still lost
I'm me
I want to shout
My tears have already dried up
I'm going to change right now
I'm going to live in a dirty world
I want to change right now
Because there is a world I want to change
I'm going to change right now
My precious thing is here