needle
a
ori
N
I'm not sure if I can get the first one to get the second one to get the second one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get the third one to get
the third one to get the third one to get the third one in order to get the third one in order to train a charge machine learn to deal with the shock and fire with the fire as you push the trigger
What's going on?
Help!
Zhaqin!
Hurry up! They're about to get on the plane!
I'm driving a car, Fugou!
It's not a plane!
Be a little more steady.
After the smoke, when I'm in my heart, you leave
I don't have a single answer, I can't help it
The fair things won't be written down
Even if I have to go through the battlefield
I'll go through the world
That unknown place
What's going on? Where's Dad?
Who's there?
Can't see anything
Get on the plane!
Someone!
Run!
Drive!
Help!
That's weird.
That's totally different from Dad.
He's so strong, he's even good at it.
He's also very strange.
He's so fierce.
It seems that this old man is not easy.
I thought you wouldn't make it.
You should analyze if Xinjian is with him.
From your description,
the old man's victory has changed a lot.
This is similar to the state after Xinjian was captured.
So the possibility of Xinjian in the old man's body is very high.
You can go check it out.
I got it.
I'm going to do something first.
Okay.
Hey, my boy.
You found something?
Yes.
I'm sitting here,
and it's as high as you are standing.
Master, my brother.
Why are you dressed like this?
Wow, that's a nice dress.
It's like finding a blanket for the old man.
He's so annoying.
What's wrong with you?
I'm hungry.
I'm so stubborn.
My old man can't come with me.
Is this okay?
Yes.
But Brother Cao, you know how to eat.
You look like a baby.
You're lying.
My old man has been torturing me for a day.
I don't eat a few street foods.
Is it good?
Yes.
You try it.
Why is it so cute?
You two, be careful.
Luo Ren,
that new girl is really your old man.
What is that new girl?
You're too naive.
You should go back to your old man.
Right?
What have you experienced?
How about this?
Explain to her what we've experienced these days.
Explain to her what new girl is.
Your old man,
take that string and go to the private tutor.
Okay.
No.
You two, go to the private tutor.
Go to the private tutor.
You're so naive.
What are you going to do?
Aren't you going to take your old man?
Luo Ren,
this is his old man.
He's not a criminal.
He's going to die.
Anyway, I'll tell you first.
I'm not going to participate.
I'm going back to the bar.
But I haven't decided yet.
Anyway, it's the safest place.
Tomorrow,
I'll go to the waterfront to see
if I can find Uncle Hong Sha.
I'll be back.
Be careful.
That guy is here again.
One thousand three.
Go ahead.
I didn't know it was like that yesterday.
He can do it.
Okay.
Your shrimp.
My god.
It's like this.
Can you eat it?
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Your skill is good.
It's good.
But you didn't try it.
I'll take it with black sand.
Is it better?
Do you know how we used to rely on seafood?
The method we created
was called black sand salt cooking.
Those seafood
were put on a big stone.
My colleagues and I
had a long drink together.
At that time,
it was really helpless.
Your colleagues?
I have two good friends.
One is called You Yu Si.
He always likes to sing sour songs.
Another friend is called Qing Mu.
You can't hear the voice of You Yu Si.
Louder.
He has a lot of soul in his hometown.
So he would go to the sea every night.
He wants to have a soul.
That picture is actually quite warm.
Where are they now?
Do you have any contact?
After we got back,
we had no contact.
Louder.
Tomorrow, we'll go to the lake.
Are you nervous?
I'm nervous.
Although we have cars and equipment,
I'm thinking about that old man.
I'm so nervous.
Let's play a game.
Let's relax.
The rules of the game are
the opposite.
It's a person's question.
I'll ask you a question.
You can only ask one person, okay?
I'll ask you if you have any mind.
Ask directly.
I'm not stronger than you.
I'm tired.
Let's start.
It's a game.
Okay.
Ask me a question.
Do you like me?
Yes.
Hongda.
I...
Okay, I'm asleep.
You can continue.
Hongda.
If...
the person you like...
has a lot of...
a lot of trouble,
do you like him?
Do you like him?
What do you want to say?
I have a lot of trouble.
The problem of the patient.
You mean...
to avoid the problem of the patient,
I have to stay away from you?
If I don't make a fuss with you,
I'll wait.
I'll wait for you to solve the problems of the patient.
I'll be with you, right?
You're dreaming.
I've never loved anyone.
But I know...
the best time for the two of us...
is when you like me and I like you.
Those things...
when I have money,
when I solve the problems,
when I wait,
I won't wait.
If the two of us meet,
and can't hold each other's hands,
maybe we'll walk together,
and meet each other's hands.
I'll only wait for that...
that...
each other has a deep love,
and I'm willing to protect it.
But we're not...
that close to each other.
After I let you go,
I was doing so many things that...
resulted in you 20 years ago.
I know.
It's a reallymer human being.
Don't move!
You dare to scare the old man!
The water is getting dirty!
Are you crazy?
Why are people crazy?
Or are you crazy?
Come here.
Come with me.
Look carefully.
They are all there.
So many people are fighting over there.
They are fighting over there.
If you can't see them,
you can beat your dog!
Look over there.
There is a man.
Can you see him?
He is Jiang Jiao's father.
He fell into the water.
He saw you and he is waiting for you to save him.
He is waiting for you to save him.
You saved him.
What are you hesitating about?
Did you get eaten by the conscience?
You don't know that, do you?
Shi Jinie.
God is also blaming me.
My conscience is also blaming me.
I know I am sorry for your father.
Jiang Jiao's father.
I am sorry for you.
This is all my fault.
My retribution.
Jiang Jiao's child is not happy at all.
It's my retribution.
Jiang Jian.
I am so worried about you.
My conscience is angry with you.
People can't stop fighting.
Now we can't get out of this village.
It's all my retribution.
You are also famous.
You miss me and your uncle.
You miss the new sister.
I asked.
Why?
To play football.
And?
I am always thinking about the birds.
He is so blind.
He should go to the hospital to see me.
I am so angry.
It's okay.
I am a big-hearted person.
I know everything.
I will arrange everything for you.
I am so angry.
I want a handsome one.
Okay.
I will think about it.
I will be better than him.
I will choose the best one.
My mom.
Can you come here?
Of course.
Okay.
I will find you.
The best one.
You said it.
You are so good.
It's safe.
We will use the water to get to the grass.
We will check the water.
We will see if we can find any clues.
You are so stupid.
This case is all right.
He is the most reliable guy inlabred by two entities.
He will När you know him well.
What?
Why is there no fish?
It seems like it's dead.
I remember I had a lot of fish in the lake when I was a kid.
Even if I had a fish on the lake, it wouldn't be a problem.
Luo Ren, you should check the tank.
See if there's any fish nearby.
Could it be that the lake broke the water's balance?
I feel like the lake is connected to it.
Indeed.
It's so big that people can't even imagine.
It's not too late.
It's like a small fish.
It seems like the fish is connected to the tank.
It's hard to get out of it.
Ma Ying!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Who's that?
I'm scared to death.
Is that a bone?
It's not a human bone.
I'll let the tanker shoot the water and have a look.
Oh my god.
The water is so deep.
Is your village the starting point?
Our village has been a water god for a week.
The water is so deep that it can't even get out of the tank.
When it's in the cage, it can get out of the tank.
And the water is so deep that it can't get out of the tank.
It's like a big tank.
I'm going to kill you.
Luo Ren.
Can you turn the camera around for me?
You're late.
What should I do?
My parents left early.
They said it was their only son.
I think I'm going to fall asleep.
I'm going to fall asleep.
I don't think it's that simple.
We've been in the river for a long time.
We can't take it anymore.
I'm afraid that other people will drag us down.
No matter what,
let's get your uncle's corpse first.
There's no problem with the left side.
Can we take this machine?
The maximum weight is 120 kg.
I think it's fine.
Be careful, uncle.
No.
The tank is under the tank.
It's hard to get it.
Luo Ren.
Have you set up the video?
Yes, I have.
Don't worry.
I'll bring the body.
It's my dad.
Tell him,
you've got everything I've burned for you.
It seems that
you have to deal with the boss first.
It's dangerous to deal with the boss.
You can't join.
I'll take one.
I must join.
You all know
that I came here for Ping Ting.
I'm not going to let you go.
I'm going to take the body.
I came here for Ping Ting.
If I'm on the move now,
I'll run away.
So I want to keep going.
It's dangerous,
but Lao Hua said
it's dangerous to go out.
Maybe there will be a new discovery
in the future.
I've asked the doctor.
His father's corpse is under the water.
My mother is also there.
He's with us.
I'll join too.
My dad took all of my body.
He almost killed me.
You saved me.
Besides,
what's the matter with the body?
I have to help you.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm a fireman.
My brother-in-law is my sister.
I'm a disciple.
Friends,
of course I have to go.
Okay.
Then do it.
Since you want to do it,
you have to have a plan.
I'll take Lao Bang out of the lake.
He'll be out of the lake.
I'll make a trip to the lake.
I'll go to the train station to make a plan.
Get in the car!
He's too strong.
He'll start the plan.
We'll drive together.
Anyway,
we'll take him out of the lake.
As soon as the speed is high, he'll be in trouble.
We'll take him out of the lake.
He'll be out of the lake.
We'll take the help of the fish.
The body might be in the help of the fish.
As long as the body is out of Lao Bang,
he'll be fine.
This is our plan.
No.
Then how are we going to
get him out of the lake?
I'll do it.
I'll tell him to come out.
I'll go out when he comes out.
It's been so long.
You haven't come out yet?
Did you see?
I can't see.
I'll look.
Look this way.
I'm looking.
Is it annoying?
Go on.
You're the only one who's got the most.
Okay.
I can see it.
It's here.
Keep it up.
It's flying.
It's here.
There's a boss.
Must get up soon.
They could get there.
They'll capture me by flying.
Now let's have a look.
What the hell is happening!
Okay,."
So, that's just why
you look like guys.
Part One.
It takes some human
to be backs Mikado,
all will survive
stop
Anhoo!
Shut up, you gluttoner!
Take my bag!
Go!
Hurry!
That was close!
He's too close!
I took him to the hard ground.
I saw how he was doing.
There's a door.
The old man who was out of the water was in the beach.
Hurry!
The victory is in sight!
Are you okay?
Where are you going?
Let's go!
The car can't move.
It's stuck.
We're going to push him down.
You pushed him down?
What should we do?
Come this way!
I'll kill him!
Pull the car down!
Get in the car!
This way!
Hurry!
You have a golden point, too.
Brother Cao, get him!
Take this.
Brother Cao!
One, two, three, four!
Hurry!
Water.
Water?
Where's my water?
I have water here.
Water.
You're going to regret it.
Go get some water.
Hurry!
Put it here.
Water.
I've checked.
The van is not related to the fire.
It's the reason for the earthquake.
And I've inquired about the old man.
After he left Wuzhu Village,
he had a mental breakdown.
He talked to Water God later.
He said he was pregnant.
He then insisted on going back to the village
and turned back.
He couldn't report it.
He was in a bad mood.
But he'll be fine in two days.
He'll be fine in two days.
What's the point of this?
What's the point?
You guys stay with him.
I'll go home and have a look.
I'll go.
Come.
I'm sorry.
I've been asking you something.
I've been shouting at you when we were fighting.
Why didn't you respond?
Did you shout at me?
I shouted.
You were like a pervert.
No.
No?
When you were being held by your wife.
Mu Na.
When did he go to your place?
Come.
Master.
What?
Brother San San and Hong Sha are so cruel.
Shall we go to comfort them?
Don't go.
Let them do it.
Dad.
Mom.
You guys haven't been home for days.
I'll take you back to see.
I'll go.
I'll go with your son.
Okay.
I got it, Uncle.
Uncle told me
he had a test.
He wanted us to go back.
I'm sorry.
We can't go back alone.
It's okay.
I'll go back with you.
I'll go back to Hua City.
Where is my brother?
He's here.
Come with me.
Jiang Zhao.
I know I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for your family.
I've been missing you.
I don't know if you can live
in the outside world.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for the loss of my village.
I beg you.
Please forgive me.
Forgive me?
Can you be at ease if I forgive you?
You can forgive me, too.
The person who died was my father.
He was in the water for over 20 years.
You should beg him to forgive you, not me.
He lost everything.
I have no right to forgive you for him.
No.
I'm not qualified.
I'm guilty.
I heard that
because of the construction of the land,
a small lake appeared.
It was not created before,
but because of the damage caused by the ecological damage.
Now the problem is solved.
As long as the water comes back,
the fish and shrimp will be tied up.
The fish and shrimp will be tied up.
I heard that
the land was built
and the fish and shrimp will be tied up.
By then,
I will come back.
But I have no family in the village.
I'm not qualified.
I'm guilty.