The Long Ballad
Episode 16
Good, good, good.
This is a very good looking model.
Brother Yin, turn around.
Turn around, yes, yes, yes.
This is our famous star-gazing fan.
Brother Yin, Brother Yin,
please introduce it to everyone.
This is our star-gazing platform.
It's a big piece of stone.
What is the name of the rock?
What is the rock outside the sky?
The flying rock outside the sky.
It's a very rare big piece of stone.
It's called the meteorite.
And then here is our
rock eye.
Inside this
can reflect the stars in the sky.
Let's take a look.
Brother Yin, you have to keep smiling.
Why are you so serious?
Six.
Brother Yin.
Sister, you're here.
How is Master?
He's asleep.
Don't worry, he's fine.
I told him you'd be here soon.
He said he wouldn't wait for you.
How can I wait for someone younger?
It's okay.
I'll just make a cup of tea tomorrow morning.
Okay.
Brother, you changed your style.
What style?
I haven't washed my hair for days.
It's all wrapped up.
Why do I keep thinking about it?
You're pretty good.
Who is this?
I'm a student.
We've met before.
You probably don't remember me.
I'm Cao Yanhua.
You're my uncle.
I'll be your little friend in the future.
You know my uncle?
What kind of student are you?
You need to be smart.
Is it up to you?
I'll read every word first,
then multiplication, Then multiplication, then multiplication.
How can you How can you write them?
I'm a hard ball player.
Who is this?
I'm not a friend.
Please go ahead.
Lower your Dayo villain snapped.
Won't go wrong.
Better than 40 million believe it in.
It will be covenant of deeds.
I'm not going in.
I can go in if you want.
Let's see if you have the ability.
Come on.
Take this bowl as my temple.
I'll let you in.
This...
Not good.
I haven't eaten much yet.
It's a bit dirty.
Is it a good one?
What do you think?
I can't hold it anymore.
What other moves do you have?
I'll use them all.
Don't hide it.
I won't be polite then.
Master Tai, you're here.
I didn't flip the bowl yet.
The winner is decided.
I'll give you a piece of my shoulder.
Next one.
Senior,
it's your first time here.
How can you flip the bowl?
Senior, have a meal.
I'm polite.
I'm well-behaved.
What do you mean?
Are you kidding me?
Why don't you take the martial arts exam?
Why are you so polite?
You're bullying me.
Come on.
Tonight,
you two live in this room.
Find the quilt yourself.
It should be in the cabinet.
If you can't find it,
just sleep in it.
The same as before.
I'll sleep in the room.
Where should I sleep?
You can sleep in the same bed.
There's another bed in the room.
Let's go.
You're giving me a quilt?
Women are not good at keeping things.
I'm not as good as this bowl of wine.
Urys!
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Luo Xiaodong?
I dreamed of Urys.
The treasure is in the cabinet.
She came to seek revenge on me.
Are you scared?
The treasure.
I lost to Gui Liebao twice.
He took away the most important person of mine.
I saw him kill them.
I had no other choice.
I felt like I couldn't do anything.
I was afraid before I saw him.
He was my new dream.
I had a new dream too.
Since it's a new dream, I'll break it.
I have a message for you.
Take the journey of the new dream.
Take a walk.
I'll accompany you.
I'll take you to the new dream.
Master, tea.
Get up.
You're so tired from kneeling.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous too.
Master, do you miss me?
If you miss me, I'll miss you.
If you don't miss me, I don't have time to miss you.
I heard that you're going to be a good friend.
I'm going to be a good friend.
I heard that you brought me a grandson this time.
Who is he?
Greetings, Master Tai.
I don't have such a big gift here.
His name is Cao Yanhua.
I took him as my apprentice.
But if you think it's not appropriate,
then forget it.
What's the good of him?
He is very kind and cute.
He is also able to change.
He is very good at doing things.
Have you ever done anything in your life that hurts people?
Say it.
I stole something in Wujiang.
I can't hide this from you.
I know that the most hateful thing in your life is stealing.
My uncle was so embarrassed that he let you cut his legs because he stole something.
No one is embarrassed.
I think it's time to do this.
This is for our own good.
This is how we can learn to be a good person.
I'm tired.
I believe that one day I can stand up again like my uncle.
You should know that.
You should call the railway department.
If you come, I will be the one who will be hit by a train.
I will save the lives of the people.
Times are different now.
I can't help learning to be a good person.
Why do you want to learn martial arts?
I want to be a star.
Justice.
I have a dream.
After I become famous, I can promote martial arts.
I can give money to people who need help.
I have this dream since I was a child.
I have been dreaming about it since I was a child.
I met my master.
I think this is the way people talk.
That's what I mean.
It's like my master was sent by God to protect me.
Come here.
It's my fault.
You didn't teach me any martial arts.
Why don't you know the basic moves?
Master, I was too busy these days.
I was neglected.
You can neglect when you are busy.
Did you neglect to eat and sleep?
As a master, you should be responsible.
The world is in your hands.
The fifth place is in your hands.
People call you master.
Do you think it's a joke?
Master, actually my master taught me.
It's my lazy, not doing any private work.
And I'm busy.
I opened a restaurant and I'm busy.
You are right.
You know how to protect your master.
Get up.
Who is this?
Master, my name is Lou Ren.
He said I was a little bit busy.
Boyfriend.
What's the benefit of him?
He...
He has no benefit.
He just...
He just likes me.
If he has no benefit, what's the point?
Master, you are embarrassing me.
I'm sorry.
Tell me.
What's the benefit of our wood?
It seems nothing bad.
Go.
You are a good match.
It's not easy.
You are really good.
You asked me so many questions.
I just need to ask you one question.
Do you really think I'm over?
No.
Your brother told me that you brought a boyfriend back.
I didn't believe it.
Eight years later,
the little girl grew up.
Master, you have to be fine.
I have to be filial to you for many years.
It's not easy to live and die.
Don't be sad.
Everyone is an island in the sea.
There are islands that keep growing and sinking.
You are just younger than me.
I'm just sinking before you.
Master, don't you like Luo Ren?
If I don't like him, will you break up with him?
He may be a good man.
I know you brought him here to let me take over.
But I don't have time to know if he likes him.
Instead of looking forward to Luo Ren,
I should look forward to you.
Look forward to me?
Look forward to me for what?
In the past, when daughters got married,
mothers had to say a lot of things.
I'm old.
If you get married, you won't be able to catch up.
It's good that you brought him here.
I can tell you a lot of things.
I don't know Luo Ren.
I don't like him either.
In the eyes of your senior and I,
his background is much more complicated than yours.
In the future, you may marry Luo Ren.
You may marry another man.
But no matter how good that man is,
don't marry him.
Be yourself at any time.
You are a wooden belt first.
Then you are the disciple of my Meihua Jiu Niang
and the lover of others.
You have to turn yourself upside down
to have the wind to call you.
If you like him, you will be with him.
If one day you find out that you married the wrong person,
you will leave him and find another man.
As the old saying goes,
if a woman is afraid of marrying the wrong man,
it's all nonsense.
If you marry the wrong person, you will separate.
Find your own love.
There is nothing to be afraid of.
If he bullies you,
you will be happy.
If he bullies you, you will be happy.
If you can't defeat him,
you will call your senior fellow disciple.
I have said so much.
I'm tired.
Come to my room after dinner.
I'll talk to you about the inheritance.
I'll check first.
Be patient.
I'm sorry to disappoint.
You are welcome.
Come in.
I'm sorry to disappoint.
Mm Hm.
I happier.
How many times have you been to a place called Xiahe Town?
How many months have you been there?
Xiahe Town?
What do you mean by Xiahe Town?
I'm not sure.
It's not a big town.
The biggest thing that happened was a murder.
It wasn't them.
The killer ran away.
What else happened?
And…
Wait!
What are you doing?
Don't do this!
I'm the owner of this place!
And what kind of friend did you make?
Friend?
You're always around a chicken.
You'll be eaten by it sooner or later.
Uncle Zhang, it's just a chicken.
Don't be so mean.
I've been calling it all night.
I'll set a rule for it.
Stop!
Do you know what this is?
I know.
This is a knife.
It's its neck.
I'll cut it and it'll be on its legs.
Yes.
Do you know?
I know.
I'll let it nod its head.
Nod its head.
I know.
Don't call it again tonight.
If you call it again, I'll cut it.
I'll do whatever I say.
Don't worry.
I won't let it call again.
If it calls again, you'll cut me.
I'll do it.
It's so annoying.
It's almost like a chicken.
Brother Ying,
look at this.
Doesn't it look like a star?
When it grows up, it's...
It grows like this.
It still grows like this.
I see.
I can see it.
You're not a person who can lie.
Your ancestors
didn't just invite Mr. De to dinner.
It's that simple.
You care about him every day.
It's not just a hobby.
Who said that?
What I said
is all true.
From a scientific point of view,
when you were talking,
your eyes were flashing.
Your voice was loud and quiet.
You were shaking your head.
It means you're lying.
Fine.
You have culture.
You know everything.
Is that okay?
Brother Ying.
We're related by eating and sleeping.
Tell me.
Where did this new test come from?
That old tree
and phoenix cage.
Where is it?
I don't know.
It's already six stars.
When will it be the seventh star?
What will happen to us?
What can we do?
Menggui.
You can't tell me.
Don't make it hard for me.
You know it.
You're not good.
Old Ying.
You're hurting me.
That means
he knows a lot of things.
You're right.
I'm not good at it.
There's something wrong.
Ying is a teacher.
She doesn't tell you anything.
I believe she has her reasons.
What should we do?
We should do it slowly.
She's a good speaker.
We can find out more.
Have you prepared the map?
Wait.
Okay.
I was studying the map.
I saw a flash of light.
You can mark the location
of the small and upper rivers,
the village,
the mountains, the south,
and the village.
Look.
Okay.
Did you see it?
Five points.
Compare the maps.
What's wrong with the star?
The star?
Let's go.
This shape
is the location
of the star on the map.
We found the light
and the location of the stars.
They're not the same.
They're exactly the same.
So,
if we follow the star's prediction,
we can find out
the location of the stars.
Look at the map.
Find the river,
the east and the south.
Mark it.
According to the ratio,
the sixth star
is there.
The star was bright before.
It suddenly went out.
It's bright again.
It's very strange.
The location of the seventh star
is the map of the first lake.
I don't need to teach you.
The stars in the map
are in the map.
They went to a place called
Xiacheng Town.
Is there anything special about it?
Qing contacted me just now.
He said that a hunter
went there a year and a half ago.
He was active for a long time.
A year and a half ago,
there were six stars in the star.
But suddenly there were five.
I went to find the hunter to avenge.
He was shot so many times
and his eyes were broken.
We all thought he was dead.
But he's in the mirror now.
And just before he entered the mirror,
he saw the six stars.
That means the sixth star
was brought to the black sand a year ago.
Now it's back with the hunter.
The house is so beautiful.
Our family
is really a place of gods.
This house
feels like
something is hidden inside.
It's like a log.
Sometimes, people are too pessimistic.
Look at me.
I'm nothing.
But there must be a way to the mountain.
My master took me as his disciple.
Then I started to worry
if I could get into the master's magic eye.
I've been through
the test of the master.
By the way,
I have to
make a bed with my master.
A bed?
I'm not sure.
I used to be his disciple.
But now
I don't have to care about the
You said this can't be
a test of the master.
I'm wrong.
I can't sleep.
I'm not wearing the plum blossom-themed disciple.
I'm sorry.
Actually,
I've been hesitating
whether I should give this to you.
After all, you're carrying
a secret that doesn't belong to you.
It's my master who died.
But I promised my master
to pass on this secret.
And now
the big problem
is only you.
Master, don't do this.
You taught me martial arts and
I'm not afraid of anything.
But please don't
be so selfish.
I can't stand it.
Actually,
there's nothing to talk about.
But if there's only one person left,
you should do what you should do.
You should take responsibility.
From now on,
you should be careful.
Even if you're his disciple,
you should keep the secret
that belongs to you.
Even if you can't live,
you should live
for your responsibility.
Can you do that?
Yes.
Our sect is called the plum blossom sect.
The founder of the sect
is called the plum blossom god.
The plum blossom god?
Master,
is our name passed down
by generations?
Should I be called the plum blossom god?
If you want to be called the plum blossom god,
I won't stop you.
Let's get down to business.
Later,
the founder of the sect
changed the name to
the temple of the god.
The temple of the god?
What a strange name.
Open the door.
Open it.
A bat?
Look carefully.
What's on the bat?
A bat?
Yes. Have you heard
about the woodman?
There are many legends
about him.
I heard that even the great Bo Yangzi
is his good friend.
This woodman was very kind.
He once made a bat
that could fly in the sky for three days and nights.
There's a bat
in the forest.
Is it...
Yes. This is the first sign of the founder.
In today's words,
it's his signature.
It's an antique.
Can it really fly
in the sky?
Yes.
Don't underestimate the wisdom of the ancients.
This is
a silver bat.
It's also half a map
and a key.
The other half of the map and key
are in the hands of others.
Only after they are combined
can they open the gate of the temple.
My master said that
the north is hard to fly.
One day, when the woodman
comes to the north with the other half of the map and key,
the silver bat
will take me
to the real temple.
Woodman,
I've never
waited for the messenger.
You may not
wait for it in your life.
But I beg you,
please keep this house
until the night is over.
Woodman.
Bring the food on the table
and come with me.
Are we going to go very far?
Yes.
Woodman.
Three squares above the left wing.
Four squares below the right wing.
Four squares above the left wing.
Master,
I finally understand why you said
you wanted to build the map.
It's amazing.
Back then,
I followed my master on this road.
I also said that
this mountain is thick with dust.
It's full of animals and strange thoughts.
What mobile phone, drone,
as long as it flies in at night,
it's all a gift.
Even in the daytime, it's good and bad.
Maybe
this is the reason
why I built the map.
It won't be lost.
It will always be a fixed line.
Master,
are you tired?
It's nothing.
I have a lot of energy.
I can fight a lot.
I haven't had a rival
for 30 years.
It's really a shame.
A man who knows martial arts
can't fight in the forest.
It's really
not pleasant.
Then I'll call my senior
and Luo Ren.
We'll fight together.
I don't like you guys being my rivals.
Master,
there seems to be someone.
I know.
You go first.
I'll wait for you at the Bathing House.
Master.
Go.
Is the map fixed?
Yes.
It's not even a piece of paper.
You're so generous.
I'm so generous.
I'm so romantic.
What?
My little sister
is so happy
to be with you.
You even put her on the pillow.
On the pillow?
What?
Nothing.
I'll put it on.
What did you put on the pillow?
The flowers you gave me.
What flowers?
The roses.
I didn't give it to you.
Master.
What's going on?
Did you put it on the pillow?
What are you doing?
Please.
I think it's fine.
It's been a long time since
we saw each other.
What are you two doing in my room?
Do you know where Mu Dai is?
Do I have to tell you?
He's very quiet with Master.
And Master doesn't like
outsiders in his room.
Get out!
Big Brother, I have a leader.
He wants to take revenge on me.
This rose is his mark.
This flower suddenly appears on Mu Dai's pillow.
Are you too self-righteous?
You can go anywhere.
Get out!
Big Brother,
Mu Dai and Master are not here.
They might have an accident.
What accident?
You don't understand.
My opponent is very powerful.
Where is the back mountain?
Tell me.
Tonight,
Master will send a small group of people.
We all avoid outsiders.
So
you just wait here.
And it's late outside.
It's not easy to walk.
With your equipment,
you can't go far.
Okay.
I'll go find it myself.
Go find it.
I'll talk to him.
You think so?
I'll be back in half an hour.
Brother Luo.
Brother Luo, listen to me.
Just believe me.
It's so foggy in the mountains.
You'll get lost.
And you saw that Master Tai is not an ordinary person.
You can trust him.
The rift is not ordinary.
He might have a heart.
Xinjian.
The End
In my mind,
there is a light and sad scene.
And I am in the dark.
The people are looking at
two sides.
One side is the main character.
The other side is waiting for you.
This game
is not over yet.
It has no end.
It has the traces of the past.
You are my match.
I am your match.
I feel your every breath.
And then the time goes by.
The flower is so bright.
Tell me the end.
The gentle
is about to bloom.
In my mind,
there is a light and sad scene.
And I am in the dark.
The flower is so bright.
Tell me the end.
The gentle is about to bloom.
In my mind,
there is a light and sad scene.
And I am in the dark.
The flower is so bright.
Tell me the end.
The gentle is about to bloom.
In my mind,
there is a light and sad scene.
And I am in the dark.
Thank you for watching!