Mei.
Cry. Bye.
The vermillion elf wan MUSIC YOU VEGETABLE If you fail...
their karma thing will happen again.
But you don't have to cry!
History's...
Oh
Mama mama mama
He's hungry. But I'm still hungry
Are you hungry?
You see that?
Go.
Go stand there and you won't be hungry.
Go. Go now.
I'm really a thief all day.
Tighten your pants.
Tighten your waist.
You won't be hungry.
But if...
It seems that you are indeed Xiang Si Lan's daughter.
And your mother is really annoying.
Get lost.
Sorry, I remembered.
In order to make Xiang Si Lan not look for you,
Luo Ri spent a lot of money.
It's funny.
Shut up.
Am I caring about you?
Obviously don't want this kind of life.
Why don't you admit it?
As long as you say it, I will change it for you immediately.
Do you remember?
Remember to read the book.
Actually, we still have a business.
Do you want to take a look?
I'm not feeling well, I'll rest.
Forget it.
This kind of thing depends on fate.
Maybe it's not the right time.
Nu Nu.
Why did you run out?
You didn't even wear your clothes.
You should learn from your childhood.
Opportunities are to be gained by yourself.
Little bear, little bear, eat chocolate.
Little bear, eat chocolate.
If you don't eat, I'll chase you.
Little bear.
Is it delicious?
Delicious.
We should go.
Where to live?
Hong Yi will send you to kindergarten.
To kindergarten.
Bye bye, little bear.
Let's go to school.
Little bear is the most beautiful girl.
So beautiful.
Let's go.
Go.
What's wrong?
Eat less sugar, you'll have a toothache.
Look, a team of choices can make life so beautiful.
The next opportunity, you must hold on.
Go.
Kill her.
I know you often recall this part.
But no matter how you recall it,
the girl at that time has fallen.
Everything can only be imagined.
Now you see clearly.
She was very afraid at that time.
She was so weak.
But for saving you, she still came back.
She's back.
If it weren't for you, she would have lived well.
Would you really do nothing?
She's going to die.
If you don't do anything, she will die.
She will die.
What's going on?
Is this right?
Kill her.
Go to the cinema tonight.
See you in the old place.
Okay.
Uncle Zhao is busy.
Pick a cup of hot tea.
The guests are waiting.
I'm looking for 13,000.
Who is 13,000?
By the way, who is 13,000?
Who cares?
Aunt Hou, are you going out?
Go to Wujiang to do something.
I'll go in.
You're not feeling well lately.
You can't carry your shoulders.
I can't rest assured to go out alone.
You're hungry.
You're not feeling well?
No.
Right.
Who is Aunt Hou?
It's really important.
Look.
There's an important person.
Who is the important person?
Who is it?
It's pretty.
It's me.
Who is it?
Did you see it?
It's pretty.
I can't believe I got this hard.
and ill leave you to lie to me.
Don't waste any more energy.
Will you encounter them again?
Who are you?
I am you.
That's impossible.
Every day,
I come on this pinch road.
All these decades,
I never met
Cao Peng Peng
and Zhou Xiao Dan anymore.
You've already chosen a normal life.
Our worlds are no longer interrelated.
We will never meet again.
I don't believe it.
Why?
You already have a happy life.
Do you want to give up?
They have already given up on you.
You should forget about them.
Boss Xia!
Master.
Meng Dan.
Take the map of the Demon Village.
Let's go.
I have to find them.
They are the most important people to me.
I can't forget them.
The record of people, two years ago.
The Tucson researchers have a spate of circles.
It's the second day of regret and regret.
They won't be able to go back.
Calamity
her
for
Question, hurry up.
But no wonder.
I think you're not the most important person in the whole world.
That's right.
You're familiar with him, right?
Do you think he's like a police officer?
I'll take him as my partner.
The police officer is as thin as the boss of the sea.
He's a fake, he's an illusion.
If you don't have the desire in your heart,
how can you have me?
Think of it like an illusion.
And the illusion is just an illusion called the Devil of Bear Formation.
The Devil الxyирING his 새 capitalism component
and the materialism the external paint from heavenó
only one somehow walking ein.
Only one?
So because I don't think they are dead?
They have an illusion!
I never recovered my energy and re-enacted the illusion.
But 280 years ago, I thought I could do it.
When I was holding them in my heart,
I tried my best to open the door.
But I still failed.
The illusion was a failure.
Failure?
That's right.
Just like what you're saying now,
they were half of the illusion.
That means they would return to reality.
Return to reality?
Then why did they kill themselves?
They didn't want you to pick up the illusion, right?
You were wrong from the beginning.
They are not dead.
The illusion is connected to consciousness.
Consciousness is dependent on the body.
Once the body is destroyed, consciousness will disappear.
And the link is gone.
I understand.
In your world, we are all consciousness.
Consciousness is made up of choices.
Once the choices are wrong,
the original self will be destroyed.
The more destroyed, the easier it is to pick up the link, right?
What is life?
The so-called ritual is to make us lose ourselves in the illusion, right?
So what?
Life is just a dream.
Dream?
Just like a fantasy.
I gave them whatever they wanted in life.
But they chose to die.
You're crazy!
You still want to be with me?
You're just trying to prove it.
That's because you don't understand.
You don't understand the meaning of life.
It seems you understand.
But this time, you're not as lucky as Mi Hua Yi Zheng.
This time, the environment is as good as it used to be.
But I walked out.
Yes, you walked out.
But you can only walk here.
The space here is reserved.
Your friends have disappeared.
And you can only stay here forever.
Forever alone.
Why don't you go back?
Back to the days of happiness.
That passage will always be open.
My companions may be confused for the time being.
But they will never be lost.
I have to get them back.
Just because of you?
Don't waste your energy.
You can't interfere with other people's cause and effect.
I'm not afraid to walk again.
I know you're close.
You don't have to do this.
Do you want to be together?
Together?
Do you guys want to be together?
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Today, I'm going to die here.
No one will come to help.
Mother Chang!
Don't you have father's will?
I'm going to use my big knife!
Don't push me.
This isn't my illusion.
The illusion is trying to deprive me.
Come.
Do you like it?
I like it.
Yesterday...
We won!
Yes!
Uncle Tao, let's have a drink.
Come.
Who told you to kill him?
I killed Lie Bao.
And I saved Tasha.
I won't let her help.
Come, Tasha.
You're too petty.
Move your hands.
Come.
I admit.
Tasha! Tasha! Tasha!
I didn't think...
I'd know you for so long.
I've never seen you so happy.
I know.
Brotherhood is your biggest worry.
But it's not true.
Luo.
I think...
it's time to find a godmother for Tasha.
Again?
Luo Xiaodong.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I heard someone call me Luo Xiaodong.
Are you crazy?
Luo Xiaodong?
Didn't your godmother teach you that?
I don't know.
But I feel like someone has called me that.
It doesn't matter.
I understand.
This is not an unfeeling fantasy.
As long as it reminds me of reality,
the fantasy will be unstable.
I'll have a chance to get inside.
Mom, help me!
Be gentle.
Don't hurt her.
Luo Xiaodong.
Do you remember the red sand,
the grass,
and the 13,000,
our scattered time,
and...
and the phoenix tower?
Godmother.
Godmother, who is it?
OK, bye chubby.
Father, warm a passed!
Dear father!
effective
interesting
although these
are not really
I'm so happy to see you again.
I'm so happy.
We'll always be here.
I thought you wouldn't come back.
I'm so happy.
Master!
Brother Luo!
Don't spill it! Bring me one!
You...
I just saw Zhang Guanghua.
He said he could choose.
It's a ritual.
I'm so jealous.
He's just a sugarcane.
He's trying to seduce us.
Chen Lun is holding on.
I wonder how it is with Red Sand and 13000.
You all are too worried.
You have a lot of regrets.
He's easily fooled.
Not like me.
I've never experienced any setbacks in my life.
I'm the one who's in the EZ mode.
I'm most worried about 13000.
He's the worst.
Red Sand is fine.
He was the most careful in the village.
I don't know why he's still here.
Stop analyzing. Let's go find him.
Let's go.
Zhao, there are many paintings in your area.
Can you chat with us?
Don't worry, Mom.
I'm the main character of your son.
They'll wait for me if I don't arrive.
Who would have thought that Jiang Zhao,
who came from the village, would become a painter?
By the way, Zhao,
the old village head called me just now.
He said he's celebrating his birthday this year.
He asked you to paint for him.
Okay.
I'll do it.
Mr. Jiang,
the reporters are all here.
They're waiting for you.
Okay, okay.
Let your son go in.
He'll save us from being too proud.
Right, right.
I'll hang up now.
Okay, Mom.
I'll call you in a few days.
Bye.
Mr. Jiang.
When will we see him again?
Mr. Jiang,
we know you're single now.
You're the most important man in the world.
What do you want from your partner?
Mr. Jiang,
why did you change the theme of this exhibition,
the painting, to the pig?
The inspiration of this painting
came from my hometown.
He's a little boy who's been raised by a pig.
No matter where I am,
he'll always be the
only hope in my heart.
Mr. Jiang,
you said you'd create some more
natural life works.
But we didn't see it before.
When will we see it?
Yi Wan Xiang!
Me!
Mr. Jiang.
Please come back.
Art has no end.
Look outside the world,
look inside,
and listen to yourself.
When is it that you still think about being a pig?
You're so insolent.
Hong Xiang.
You're here.
What should we do?
He's still awake.
It seems that you have a lot of experience in art.
The highest level of understanding an artist is
that you're looking at the flowers,
while I'm looking at you.
You're so insolent.
I'm sure that the standard of choosing a girlfriend is also very strict.
You're just like a useless thing.
I care about the soul.
Xiang Ying!
Do you think
I will be the type you like?
No!
Let go!
I'm sorry.
Then we have to see the girl's soul.
What are you talking about?
Yi Wan San!
You're just an insolent thing.
You're doing art in your dream.
Do you know how great my dream is?
I'm willing to jump out of it.
What's wrong with you?
Wake up!
Master.
I can't do this. What should I do?
You have to find a way.
I'll find a way.
Yi Wan San!
In the most deep night,
I will think of you.
With the memories of warmth,
I will hold you tight.
In this city,
the road is so lonely.
Someone will walk towards the stars.
Maybe fate is too complicated.
But in the wind and rain,
the stars are the most beautiful.
Yi Wan San!
Er Fu!
Why are you here?
What's going on?
Hurry!
I can't see anything!
The prison is being blown up.
It's being blown up.
Yes!
The dead are all dead!
I'm lonely!
Master.
I'm worried even if you don't move.
I'm worried even if you move.
When will you be a head?
Are you okay?
Don't catch a cold.
Don't suffocate yourself.
Come on.
Let's go.
Let go.
Come on.
You are my warm baby.
Without you,
I would have been dead.
Thank you.
Dad.
You brought all your brothers and sisters here?
We are saved.
Otherwise, we would have been killed.
Last night, the snow was like a world end.
I didn't expect it to stop this morning.
Mr. Luo.
I've lived for most of my life.
I've never seen this strange thing
that the mountain group saved.
Me too.
I've never seen this before.
Thank you, my baby.
If it weren't for your brothers and sisters
in that tent last night,
we would have been dead.
I love chicken the most.
From now on,
I'll eat chicken and cake.
I've got it.
That's great.
Give me a pair of wings that can fly through the universe.
What's wrong with you?
It's comfortable on the bed.
Do you think I'm a butcher?
You're really good at destroying the atmosphere.
Stop talking nonsense.
Go down.
Go.
Be careful.
I can't jump.
I'm stiff.
Don't fall.
It's okay.
Just let it be up there.
Don't blow it.
Don't come down.
I'm going to find a red star.
Phoenix is in love.
There's a moment
I don't want to understand the blue star.
Don't help us.
I hope we can be together forever.
I'm going to find a red star.
Go! Go!
What's wrong with Fenghuanglou?
We've been waiting for you.
This kind of thing is annoying.
Brother Cao.
Didn't you find that Cao Haohang
has been acting strange these two days?
Why do you keep looking at me?
Fenghuang.
Dad.
What's bothering you?
Tell me.
What?
I meant to say I was being a bit of a
victim.
Victim?
Yes.
Yes, I was being a victim.
You scared me.
But that's not right.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I didn't eat chicken and meat.
Don't talk about that stupid thing.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I didn't eat chicken and meat.
Don't talk about that stupid thing.
She said it.
You must have promised her something.
But you didn't keep your promise.
Promise?
I promised Fenghuang that I would sign her name.
You're right.
Fenghuang.
I'm leaving.
Fenghuang, let's go buy a brand.
Let's go buy a brand.
That's my problem.
If you want to sign it, I'll sign it.
A good chicken costs $13,000.
How do you cut it?
Cao Yanhua's chicken.
Mine?
Look at Fenghuang's small neck.
It's bent by your two ribs.
This is called exercise.
It's really cruel.
No, Uncle Guo.
You gave me something new.
And you have to take it back.
It's too stingy.
What do you know?
It's broken for a while.
I'll show you the difference between the mountain village and the town.
Now, it's time tolemme it out.
Is this the...
Yeah.
I've always told you,
Feng will take a lot of people who only love Fenghuang.
The number of people who are stuck with her could be very big, right?
The definition of food is halibut.
I've asked experts toSouth Hawaiians got bread,
I'm very old.
It reminds me of
the day I was afraid of the Wujang
and now I'm a man who saved the world.
Heroes never ask about the future.
It's hard to predict the future.
No, Uncle Guan.
Isn't there only three phoenix
and wolfhounds?
Yes.
What about you five?
How do you divide the three?
You don't have to fight.
I've got someone
who's back to the house
and made a new one.
What about the phoenix and wolfhound?
Is there any news about the Unwelcome Tree?
The Unwelcome Tree is just a tree.
It's not easy to collect.
And it's not easy to preserve.
Besides,
you're all sealed.
This phoenix and wolfhound
is enough.
You're a big fan of Yun Tian.
You're going to make five tables.
And it's so thin.
Did you make six?
You suspect me.
Call him out.
You're a moral man.
Don't run.
You suspect me.
Call him out.
Don't forget.
Give it to me.
Cheers.
It's so heavy.
Have a drink.
Drink some water.
First, I have a question.
Today's fried pork is very good.
It's from the outside.
Come on.
Eat.
I have a question.
Have you ever thought about
the connection between your body
and the heart?
It should be the interaction
between you and the heart.
On the contrary,
your blood can control the heart.
Why?
Have you ever thought about that?
No.
So you still have to rely on me.
I've been thinking about it
for a long time.
I think our consciousness
is probably
the fourth dimension
that humans don't understand.
In this space,
as a human being,
as a carbon-based creature,
it has become an energy object
at this moment.
As a gene,
as a higher-end substance,
when it meets humans,
it changes.
The main difference is that
it can store information
and make it pass on.
How can I know that?
It's on the human body.
Me too.
It's called
instinct.
Enough.
You're right.
If you can't figure out
the truth,
this is...
You're right.
Connection
exists in the deepest part
of our consciousness.
Connection
is now in your body
and the phoenix's heart.
We've got it, right?
And the phoenix's heart too.
Let's consider
the environment
and celebrate.
I think it's good.
Where should we start?
How about the wood house?
That's great.
I've never been to the wood house.
Then let's go there.
I have someone.
If you haven't been there,
why don't you go and have fun?
As long as you can
help me wake Uncle Zhang up,
I can do it too.
I won't take you.
I'll help you.
You can't do that.
A thousand worlds
are only for one man.
Uncle Zhang,
let's take a photo together.
The last time,
we were so lucky.
Let's have fun.
Come on.
Let's go.
I'm so excited.
Put it on.
Who should I hug?
You're still suspicious of me.
The last time we were so lucky
If you're still suspicious of me
I'll be more willing to be with you
OK?
Let's take a photo.
I think we need something.
Let's go to the grass.
Where should we go?
Yeah.
Where's the baby?
She was here just now.
The baby didn't bring anything.
The pot face.
Stop talking nonsense.
What if she falls into the pot?
Let's go.
Is she in the movie?
Come on.
Let's go.
What are you afraid of?
I'm going to be gentle
In my mind
A little bit of sadness
And I'm in the dark
The ugly face of people
Two sides
One side is the main
One side is waiting for you
This game
Is never over
It has traces of the past
You are my match
I'm your match
I'm you
Look back
On the previous start
A strange chaos
Has been involve
It is
It will be
I'm in the dark
The sky crosses the line of the dawn
Tells me the end
The future is about to be gentle
The face of my memory haunts me
And I'm in the darkness