You two are married.
Why are you still worried about this?
This one.
It's like this. It's like this.
That's easy.
Push the bow to her.
Talk nicely.
Press it.
Look at her. Look at her. Look at her.
Love her.
Speaking of love,
have you read the manual
I gave you?
I didn't see it. I didn't see it.
Luckily,
Its Sister Chasing Secret 2
is fresh out.
This book answered without any blind spots.
all kinds of questions
in marriage.
In the city,
in the city.
You didn't even take a good look.
All right. I can see
I can see that you're furious.
As the author of this book,
I'll cook for you.
Let's open the first chapter.
What if the girl you like
thinks of you as a brother?
The solution is as follows.
How dare you act recklessly, saying that it's only for her.
What does that mean?
It means
think about
Did your wife
to make you do something ridiculous
and you don't want to do.
If there is,
you can do it boldly
and express your love.
and show that you only do it for her.
That makes sense.
What do you mean by that?
It's really interesting.
Let me put it this way.
Pock Wang from East Street
With my book,
with my book.
Because of this book,
because of this book.
Really?
Of course.
Let's get down to business.
Second,
What do you mean? Playing hard to get.
What do you mean?
You did something
touched her.
She'll come here
and ask how you feel.
Jang-ho.
Do you have feelings for me?
Do you like me?
You must reject her.
Let's play hard to get.
When she gets confused,
she will give you an olive branch.
She will express her love to you.
At this time,
give her a small gift and push the boat along the way.
to express your feelings.
will she still treat you as her brother?
No.
It does make sense.
Right? I'm thirsty.
Let me pour it for you.
Go on.
This is for free.
That's all.
My previous book costs five cents.
The price is still the same.
It's five cents.
Add it up.
Do you need ten coins?
I don't need money.
but value.
We scholars and molesters
just hope that
has its value.
After you put in effort,
you will understand its value.
Congratulations on your love.
Read your book. I'm leaving.
Wait.
Since you got the money,
please help me to look into Ningji
Ningji's problem is a small problem
Your wife's problem is the problem.
Focus on your study.
Hello, Qiu Changhao.
Why are you spacing out?
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
You're here. I'm here. I'm here. I'm here.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
I found that
Changle and Jiang Lanting are in trouble.
What’s wrong with them?
I think Changle
Jiang Lanting.
But you and Kang Lanting are like that.
So Changle can’t
to Jiang Lanting?
Fortunately,
Changle hasn’t noticed it yet.
He seems to be a bit like Jiang Lanting.
I didn't understand a word.
But the manual says
you can't show what you don't understand.
I think I understand.
Right?
As besties,
I'm responsible for this sister.
You have to tell Kang Lanting
or you can't even be friends.
What is she talking about?
Besties and threats.
Okay, let's play by ear.
Got it.
Ruofei, go to the kitchen and get some snacks.
We'll discuss this later.
Okay.
It's here. It's here. It's here.
Miss.
You can just ask me to come.
Why do you have to come in person?
You know nothing.
A wife should be gentle.
If I take these over,
how beautiful it would be to be a husband.
Miss, I know that.
I bought some yogurt
to Songjun,
I wanted to feed him.
I brought some snacks.
Hello. Hello.
Where is he?
[Zhao Changhao]
Changhao.
Let's play a game.
I see you.
Stop playing. Are you going to sleep?
Qiu Changhao.
You...
Here you go. Here you go.
I'm coming out for you.
Why are you laughing?
No.
I have to explain.
This out
It means to admit that
you have a good intention.
Dragon? Dragon?
Dragon.
Long Yang broke his sleeves.
What?
Do you think I have that kind of hobby?
No.
Didn't you admit it yourself?
You and Kang Lanting are the same?
Me and Kang Lanting?
You two are not? Yes.
Of course not.
I saw you in the study that day.
in the study that day.
You even took off his clothes.
It's because...
I...
What's wrong? Tell me.
Don't tell me
you are comparing muscles like that.
Yes, we are.
A battle with bare arms.
Yes, a barefoot competition.
Two men
Like this. Like this.
Like what?
Should I make it clear?
We're both subjects at night.
I see
What do you mean
Of course not.
I'll say this for the last time.
We're not in that kind of relationship.
No.
It's not like that.
It's over.
What's over? It's over.
No.
You two are just friends.
We're just friends.
No way.
Why not?
Do you really want me to like a man?
No.
If Qiu Changhao's true love
is not Jiang Lanting,
It means that
is gone again.
When can I
go back?
What are you trying to say?
Who do you like?
I...
I'm not the princess
nor Gu Mochou.
or Jiang Lanting
Wait a minute. What's going on?
[Do you like me?] I like you.
like me?
The book of chasing girls is right.
I can’t confess my love now.
Let's play hard to get.
Come on.
I knew it.
You're looking for
again.
I can't go back. I can't go back.
Oh my god!
Someone help me! Help me!
Miss!
Here you go. Here you go.
It's here. It's here.
Let’s go. Let’s go.
Young Master has left.
Miss, Hengyu is here.
[Hengyu, where are you?] Let's go.
Over there! Over there!
It's here. It's here.
Good for you.
How dare you lie to me now?
My Lady, you woke up too late today.
Young Master has left.
It’s good that he left. I don’t want to see him either.
My lord.
What is it?
When the royal agent received the letter,
he said he could transfer Lord Zhang's case
to them.
If you agree, they will report to His Majesty.
Okay, I understand.
Sir.
Anything else?
Your mind is getting worse.
You should put family first.
Jiang Lanting left it here.
I'll return it to the prince.
No need.
Tell Kang Lanting
Tell him to come to my house.
You're going back?
Family comes first.
Please
to Miss Chun Hua for me.
Jiang Lanting.
I'm busy today. I don't have time for you.
What business can you have?
Do you know that wasting my time
is like killing the royal family?
Then why did you come to me every day?
Do you want to die?
Get lost!
Get out! Get out!
Come back! Come back!
Are you okay?
If you have something to say, just say it.
If not,
I can stay longer.
Tell me.
Your clothes are dirty.
Kang Lanting.
Do you like me?
I like you.
How could I?
How could I like you? Right?
Think about it.
You've been through every hole on this street.
Which tree haven't you climbed?
I like you
I don't like you.
There's no way I like you.
Yes, I don't like you.
You can't like me.
I work for His Majesty at night.
Since you and the subjects are friends,
you should understand
you can't like a friend's lover.
No.
Why didn't I know about this?
You don't need to know.
Just know
You can't come to me again.
I have my own things to do.
What else can you do
what else do you want?
None of your business.
I won't say a word to you anyway.
I won't see you again.
Go away.
Luckily, I'm not from the ancient times.
Otherwise, if I stay in this room every day,
I'll be bored to death.
This...
Isn't this the jade of my brother?
This person is really...
He said he cherishes it so much.
I put it here
I wanted to try that day but I didn't
Let me try
How to blow it?
Let me ask you.
What do you like about me?
What's so good about him?
You don't even know who he is.
You won't understand.
I don't understand.
At night, I don't understand.
You all think
I like him for helping the rich and helping the poor.
But I'm not that shallow.
What's so special about you?
You couldn't even solve the case before.
the girl abduction case.
Do you know her?
I heard about it.
I was also abducted.
The girls and I were abducted to the brothel.
I came to save us at night.
After this incident,
he even arranged a maidservant
to the embroidery workshop.
and gave them a livelihood.
He's kind and brave.
How could I not like him?
Is that why you like him so much?
Let me ask you.
If one day
when he takes off his mask,
he's just
an ordinary ugly monster.
will you turn around and leave?
Ungrateful!
I swear
whether it’s healthy or ill,
wealth or poverty,
we will both have each other
In the long night,
For the one I love
I will never betray you.
Are you okay?
There's no sound.
Is it blocked?
Don't move.