Do you think it's like this? Yes.
you love the person in front of you.
You decided to hold her hand.
Coming.
Hengyu, I'm sorry.
I'm going back to take the exam.
[I'm going to tell her]
I love you.
It's useless.
This smell makes me dizzy.
Your expression also distracts me.
It didn't work.
You...
This is not fun.
You're not giving me face.
My brother is in charge of important cases in the court.
I suspect he was murdered.
I'm sorry.
I really thought this would work.
So I want to try it.
Get some rest.
This is my own business.
Miss, where are we going?
Just follow me.
No, Miss, let's go back.
Madam doesn't allow us to come here.
We know each other well.
No, I...
Why do I feel a little cold
It's cold without sunlight.
Miss, I heard that
the cold palace is like this.
Look at this.
It can't be
suddenly appeared?
My Lady, Chun Ying is protecting you.
What weasel and rat?
are no match for Chun Hua.
I mean,
This was Jangdeo's house when he was alive.
Whatever.
and a house for children.
I'm...
A dead man's room.
Someone dropped something.
Go down
Get down
Don't make a fuss.
I'm a student
in the 21st century.
What am I afraid of?
I think
we can find something
we'll find something.
Chun Ying, what do you think?
I...
I dare not look.
There's nothing.
Let's go somewhere else
Ghost!
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
Squeak.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to investigate a case.
Let me tell you.
Based on my experience,
I'd rather come to the crime scene
why don't you come to the scene and see if there's anything missing?
I've checked many times.
No.
Investigating cases is the same as reading books.
Every time you open it, you will have new feelings.
and new discovery.
What did you find?
I was inspired
and you interrupted me.
Why didn't you call me?
I was afraid to bring up your sad past.
By the way,
Can you show me
to me?
Here.
Yes.
Have you checked it? Yes.
No problem.
No.
But this small bottle is quite exquisite.
This bottle belongs to my brother.
He has asthma.
It contains asthma.
Asthma pills.
Probably.
Look, this asthma medicine is always with you.
You can use it anytime.
through mouth and nose.
If your brother was really murdered,
it's most likely
is this.
I've checked it.
No problem.
No.
However,
do you know
can't be tested?
How can you be sure
How do you know it's poisonous?
Can your poison test technology
compared to me?
I didn't expect you can do scale.
There are many things you didn't expect.
By the way,
do you have the formula for asthma?
One coin of loquat leaves, two coins of yellow and yang leaves.
Two coins of chestnut, one tael of thorn apple powder.
The first three herbs are leaves and fiber.
Even if it turns into powder,
it takes time to sink.
But pollen is delicate.
It sinks fast.
What are you doing?
I'll get the proportion of asthma.
Then we'll know who's more or less.
If I'm not mistaken,
this white powder
should be thorn pollen.
But its proportion is obviously different from the formula.
The one in this small potion
is obviously higher.
You mean
thorn apple pollen is poisonous?
Actually, it's meaningless
is meaningless.
How much dosage
is the key.
Try and you'll know.
What are you doing?
It doesn't seem to be a problem.
Nonsense. I'll get you some water. Spit it out.
It's just a little bitter.
Ruofei, have some water.
Ruofei.
Alien.
Can you generate electricity?
Why are your eyes so small?
Do you have a spaceship?
Can you take me on a spaceship?
Go.
Ruofei, this is Qiu Changhao.
No signal.
What a coincidence. I don't have any signal either.
What a coincidence. Let's take a spaceship.
Let's take a spaceship.
Take me to a spaceship.
Chun Ying, doctor.
Let's go.
Go!
Alien, where's your spaceship?
Be careful.
Flying ship
A spaceship?
Alien.
Alien, will your spaceship pick you up?
Stop it.
Alien?
I'll get some water.
Alien, where's your spaceship?
Alien, where are you going?
What are you doing?
Be careful.
Alien, where's your spaceship?
Where's your spaceship?
I'll get you some water.
Are you thirsty?
Ruofei.
I fell in love with you
I fell in love with you.
Ruofei, I love you.
No.
Why did you tie me up?
Untie me.
You stayed up all night.
as if you were crazy.
I'm going crazy.
Don't go if you love me.
If you say you don't love me,
why didn't you say you love me?
What are you doing?
Alien, you have a signal again.
What alien?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Here.
Have some water.
I'm your true love.
Your true love is me.
It's me.
What true man?
Your clothes are wet.
You'll catch a cold.
Do you know, Ruofei?
Ruofei, calm down.
I don't know
Let me untie you, Ruofei.
Although you are an alien,
you came on a spaceship,
But you'll catch a cold, you know?
Let me tell you, Ruofei.
I'll get you something warm.
Ruofei.
Calm down.
Qiu Changhao.
You must live a good life with Du Ruofei.
Do you hear me?
I won't accompany you.
I'll give you one last goodbye kiss.
Go to sleep.
I think I lost my memory.
Why can't I remember anything?
Oh my god.
I lost my memory.
What happened yesterday?
Get me up first.
I can't breathe.
Bro I'm suffocating
I really can't breathe
I can't breathe.
Do you feel better now?
You stayed up all night.
until the doctor came.
The doctor is here.
Miss.
Calm down.
Ruofei.
Stop it.
Doctor, how is she?
Your Excellency, your wife is
she is poisoned.
Poisoned?
Yes.
Is his life in danger?
Judging from his pulse, he's not in danger for now.
It'll be fine when the medicine slowly subsides.
When will you wake up?
Well...
We'll have to wait until tomorrow morning.
Let's go. Let's go.
Come on.
Hold this big toad for me.
I want a piece of fat.
Where's the fat?
I need to take it out.
It's here. It's here.
Over there! Over there!
Where are you?
Can you hold on until dawn?
I think I'm used to it.
No.
Doctor, thank you for your hard work today.
Where is the fat?
Chun Ying, see the doctor out.
Yes.
What about fats?
Where is it?
It's here.
This is so embarrassing.
Sorry, Changhao.
But now I'm sure
I really took that medicine
after taking that medicine.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
Are you sure?
I'm sure. I'm sure.
Untie me.
My back.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm thirsty.
I'm so thirsty.
I'm alive.
So I went crazy last night.
No, I behaved abnormally.
It's because there's something wrong with the medicine.
There's a problem even if you don't take medicine.
Can we still talk?
I mean,
your brother must have taken that medicine
so he had hallucinations.
He lit the coil himself.
The painting drawn by Hengyu
It makes sense.
thorn apple pollen.
The dosage was tampered with.
It was intentional.
Are you feeling better?
I still need company.
Hiki Music