Liang Simu, are you crazy?
It's a deal then.
Where are you? I'll pick you up.
I'll wait for you downstairs.
Are you going to celebrate your birthday with Mr. Liang?
Maybe another day.
What do you mean?
I won't live with him.
But you just said
I lied to him.
He was so arbitrary.
I thought he could change.
He just can't change.
He wants to celebrate his birthday with me.
Do I have to say yes?
I won't. Let's go.
Someone is buying tonight.
I'll take you to a free dinner.
Who's buying?
Mr. Liang.
Don't mention him.
He's another childhood friend.
I feel sorry for Mr. Liang.
Got it.
Where's Yuanyuan?
Where did you take Yuan Yuan?
Your own sister
came to ask me.
Don't you think you're ridiculous?
Who are you?
I'll ask you again.
Where is Yuan Yuan? Or I'll call the police.
Yuan Yuan, Liang Si Yuan.
You know her?
Isn't it her birthday today?
Ling promised to celebrate her birthday today.
but she couldn't attend a business dinner.
I can't go.
I booked a Korean restaurant for her.
She's celebrating her birthday with her sisters.
Why are you talking so much to him?
You didn't celebrate her birthday?
Where is the restaurant?
Did something happen to Yuan Yuan?
I'll take you there.
Yunling.
The commercial dinner tonight is very important.
All brands are here.
I'll go back when I find Yuanyuan.
Bye.
When did she leave?
I booked it for her the whole night.
She just left.
The three girls said
dorm curfew or something.
I need to go back to school.
Yuan Yuan had an accident tonight.
But now Yueling is with me.
If I didn't come,
in order to attend the party,
to attend Yuan Yuan's birthday party.
So the person who took her private photos tonight
is not Ling.
Lingling is not Mr. A at all.
Did I find the wrong person
from the beginning?
You were so anxious just now.
Did something happen to Yuan Yuan?
I can't reach her.
What's the problem?
If Lingling is not Mr. A,
who is Mr. A?
How could Uncle Liang and Aunt Xu have such a freak?
Liang Simu, watch out!
How are you?
Professor Liang, I can't stop him.
I'm really sorry.
What are you doing here?
I had a dream.
that
you disappeared in front of me.
You two talk. I'll go buy breakfast.
Stop looking.
Childish.
Tell me.
Why did you go to the lab in the middle of the night?
Tell me first.
Since your primitive code experiment,
I've become mysterious.
I dream every day.
You said it was a dream, right?
It's so real.
It's like
experience it myself.
I dreamed
you had a car accident in front of me.
Then you...
disappeared.
Professor Liang.
Why don't you explain?
Could it be... The original code is connected to the real world.
How is that possible?
Professor Liang.
If Yunpeng is not Mr. A,
why was he in the bar?
Is this all a coincidence?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Before I answer your question,
answer a few questions first.
Last Wednesday,
Why did you go to the bar?
Also,
someone saw you
the back alley of the bar last Tuesday.
It seems to be a memorial service.
Superstar Yue,
Did you do something wrong?
I need to go worship.
I admit
Last Wednesday,
I did go to Mingmei Bar.
But on Tuesday,
I didn't go.
Sacrifice?
Who told you that?
The bar waiter told me.
She must be mistaken.
Last Tuesday,
I was somewhere else.
I saw it wrong.
What about Mr. A?
You know Mr. A?
You also know Mr. A.
And you already knew.
Yes.
I know Mr. A.
Don't you want to know where I went last Tuesday?
That's all for today.
Thank you.
You're much better than five years ago.
But
I still hate myself.
If you didn't go to the bar,
then who was the one who went to the back alley?
Mr. A.
Actor table.
Wang Bowen, Liang Simu.
Zhao Boya, Yang Man.
Yang Caiya.
Zhang Xueyang
Yue, Ling.
Xu Yijia, Lin Yuchao.
Zhang Xueyang, Yue Ling.
Big bear.
Pan Min-young.
You Jiawei, Da, Xiong.
Ban Min-young Gu Xiaoseok
Yiu Hsiaoling
Wang Jiayi, Yao Xiaoling.
Professor Li.
Mother of Forest.
Wu Sijun, Wen, Sen.
Professor Li.
Wu Sijun, Wen Sen.
to perform.
Jin Lingtao, Zoe Wu, Zou Chengying, Wang Donghua, Jia Wenhan, Kung Xianlin.
Wang Dian, Wang Hejin, Lin Doudou, Tian Yechi. Chen Zheng Luo Rui Kun
Qin Wenjie, Wu, Lei, Ou Chaoxia, Shi Senjie Yu Xinghui Wang Xiangxiang
Lin Jinxin Gao Mingsheng Cao Ying Fang Yuqi Xu Ye Ye.
Ou Chaoxia Shi Senjie
Yang, Ran, Huang Jinze, Wang Juan, Wang Qiaoyan. Chen, Jie, Wang family.
Director Tian Juan, Chen An, from Ming Ma Zhuo, Peng Qun.
Liu Lianhao, Song Jiahui.
He Li Qiong, Chen Jia Yu, Guo Li Sheng, Yang Rong Xiang. Yang Yuxuan, the bag.
Producer team.
Producer Zhou Qingjie Qiu Lindi
Zhang Xueyang.
Producer Director Pan Yuxiang
Huang Peiyu.
All of them, Liang Yuqi.
I'm Liang Yuyi.
Life Producer Zhao Nan
Traffic adjustment, Tian Yanyan.
Live Producer Zhang Chao
Director team.
The director team.
Director Zhang Jin Cheng.
Deputy director Liu Xinyao.
Executive Director Hsu Zulian
Zhang Qingci.
Actor commander Zhou Weian
Deputy Director Liu Xinyao.
Zhang QingCi.
Su Yang.
An Chow.
Actor assistant director Su Yang Wang
Director assistant Li Jinhui
Photography team.
Photographer group.
Photographer Feng Shijun
Photographer Jin Hong Kong Jin
Photographer Jin Honghong
Focus on Shen Yongqiang, Shen Haoyang.
Photographer assistant Liu Changchun Pang Likai
Photographer assistant, Liu Changchun.
Lighting Team.
Lighting instructor Yu Deok-choon.
Lighting instructor Yu Deok-choon
Lighting Daisuke Wang Gun
Lighting assistant Wang Jian
Lighting assistant Jiang Guanghao Han Lei
Heo Gil Rib.
Yeo Moon Ho.
Follower Xu Xiaoben.
Art team.
Art instructor Liang Dayue.
Arts instructor, Liang, Yue.
Art hat.
Doo, Liang, Feng, Zhang Zhifei
Mei, Art, hat, Lu Xin.
The styling team.
stylist instructor, Xu Hengxin.
Makeup artist Xiao Linlin.
Haidong, hairstylist.
Staff at the scene, Che Jinxuan, Left, Dragon.
Zhang Ke Ke.
Record.
Guo Haonan, Ye Sicong.
Behind the scenes of the drama photo.
Zhang Xumeng Tao
Zhang Xumeng, Tao, Zhe
Late production.
The editing company.
editing company.
Kaifeng photograph and Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Kaifeng Media Co., Ltd.
Editing Instructor, Lu Fu Yulan.
Editing instructor, Lu Fu Yulan.
Editor Dong Wanyun Zhang Xu
Editing assistant, Liu Jianguo.
The post-production company.
Late-production company.
Beijing August Film and TV Production Co., Ltd.
Production Director, Cai Fute.
Project Director Kong Shuo
Project Director Gong
Color cooler Shu Zhiming.
Administrative Director, Yingjie.
lines subtitles, Xie Xinyu.
Synthesis output. Zhou, handsome, Xie Xinyu.
Synthesis output. Zhou, handsome.
Joint, Zhu Bo.
Video Director, Zhu Bo.
ADR recording, Chen Mengyi, Li Junting.
Audio effect, Jia Haolin.
ADR recording, Chen Meng Yi.
OK.
Audio effect, Jia Haolin.
Jia Haolin.
Recorder, Coco Zhang.
Foley.
Mr. Zhang Keke.
Wang Le.
Dubbing director Shizu Light
A dubber.
A dubber?
Yue, Ling, Li Shaogang.
Liang Siyuan Tian Xin
Man, Bai Pi Qing.
Gu, Shuo, Shanxi Ting.
Yang Manbai Pil Qing.
Lin Yuchao, Sun Lanlang.
Xiong.
Other dubbers, Zi, Nuo.
Other dubbers, Ja, Noh.
Poster design.
5 o'clock (Tientsin) brand design Co., Ltd.
5:00 (Tientsin) brand design Co., Ltd.
CNF Song Wanying.
CNF Song Wanying
Other visual designs, Wang Yuhang, Chen Haibo,
Liu Yang, Li Jianming.
CNF Hu Li.
Zhou Lin.
Afterwards of the drama photo, Xinyi Wu.
Music announcement.
JS Entertainment.
JS International Co., Ltd.
Chen Yuting, the project commander.
The ending interlude.
The end interlude.
Song.
Listen to the wandering wind
Listen to the wandering wind.
Singing Mandy
(Film, drama, Dangerous Relationship)
No lyrics.
The lyrics are not so good.
Composition
Producer Bingbing Zheng
Composed by Zheng Bingbing
Arranger Zheng Bingbing Liu Lift
Producer Bingbing Zheng Cool
Maternal cord post-production, Hu Dayang.
Dubbing Project, Hu Dayang.
guitar Liu Juan.
Maternal cord post-production, Hu Dayang.
Harmony, Hu Ah You.
Voice Studio, KLE. Music Boya Studio.
We’ll meet again someday.
We'll meet again someday.
[Film, Drama, Dangerous Relationship]
Performing Zhou Dio.
Singing Chow Dio
Lyrics Zhou Dio
Producer Li Ding
Composed by Zhou Dio
Harmony, Yuan Liyuan.
Li Ding.
Music production Hong Wook Music
Music Project Lee Ding
Music Producer Hong Wook Music
(Film, Drama, Dangerous Relationship)
Performing Zhou Dio.
Performing Chocolo.
Lyrics Zhou Diano
Zhou Dio.
Lyrics Zhou Diano.
Wu Lei.
bass, Li Ding.
Maternal Project, Zhou Dio.
Mother-nursing Project, Zhou Dio.
Producer Li Ding
Salvation
Singing TANA Band
[Film, Drama, Dangerous Relationship]
Lyrics: Zhao Wenqi.
composed by Zhao Wenqi.
Arrangement.
Song Fu Dalong.
He is Fu Dalong.
Star Sea.
[Stars, Sea]
[Film, Drama, Dangerous Relationship]
Singer Deng Jiakun
[Film, Drama, Danger]
Lyrics: Deng Jiakun.
Singer, Deng Jiakun.
Composed by Deng Jiakun.
Lyrics: Deng Jiakun.
Deng Jiakun.
composed by Deng Jiakun.
Arrangement: JJ Jin.
Producer KUN
Singer Producer Deng Jiakun
and Sheng Sheng, Drcchen Jin, Deng Jiakun.
Mother tape, TuJay@J.K. Stedio.
The ending song.
The First Snow in the Human Realm.
Singer You Jiawei
Singer You Jiawei.
Lyrics: Guozi Xiaoxiao.
composed by Guozi Xiaoxiao.
Thank you very much.
Tears.
Tear bottle.
Hanse Restaurant, Wharf Raiger Whiskey.
The circulation unit.
[Production Unit]
Production company.
Qijing Film (Ningbo) Co., Ltd.
Qijing Film (Ningbo)Co., Ltd.
Joint production unit
joint production unit
Dongyang Fengwei Film and Culture Co., Ltd.
[Wu Xi, Wu Xi] Co., Ltd.
Liaoning Mountain Mirror Culture Co., Ltd.
[Wuxi Media] Co., Ltd.
Product unit.
Yangyang Neeyyi Technology Development (Shanghai) Co., Ltd.
Yangyang Neyi Technology Development (Shanghai) Co., Ltd.
Zhejiang, Pailing Film Co., Ltd.