It perfectly matches all the conditions you mentioned.
Xiaochao.
Can you forgive Mom?
Mom was wrong.
I shouldn't have sent you away last time.
You can stay as long as you want from now on, okay?
Can you forgive Mom?
Xiaochao, Mom is begging you.
Mom is on her knees begging you.
Call your father.
Tell him I want to remarry him.
Get up, Mom.
If he agrees to remarry me, I promise.
I promise I won't interfere with him anymore, okay?
I'm begging you, Xiaochao.
Will you please call your father?
Get up.
Mrs. Lin.
Please calm down first.
There are people around. This scene is embarrassing.
Whatever it is, can we discuss it in my office?
Don't touch me! What are you doing?
Xiaochao, call your father.
Tell him there's a man here trying to bully me.
Hurry up.
Please stop talking.
I'm begging you.
How can I stay at school if you make a scene like this?
Then don't stay here,
since you don't even care about your mother anymore,
if I'm suffering, you won't be happy either.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Lin Yuchao
was already studying journalism at Yan University,
and because of his excellent grades,
he was admitted to the graduate program at the same school.
I know quite a bit about his family situation.
When he was young,
his parents didn't get along,
and eventually got divorced.
His mom has been making a fuss about getting back together
and because of this
she's been coming to school to harass him quite often
it almost turned deadly.
On Christmas Eve 2024
I got a call from the fire department
and it scared me to death.
Mom, don't do this.
Let go! Don't do this, Mom.
Let go of me! What are you doing?
Let go! Come here! Don't touch me!
If you come any closer, I'll jump.
Call your father
tell him to come here
or I'll jump right now.
Okay, I'll call him right now.
Hello?
It's connected, Mom.
Christmas Eve.
So that means
on the day of Yuanyuan's incident,
Lin Yuchao was also at the scene.
That's right,
but according to the surveillance footage from that night,
he and Yuanyuan didn't have any interaction.
By the time Yuanyuan climbed to the rooftop,
Lin Yuchao should have already been at the hospital with the ambulance.
Let me go! Let go of me!
I called Lin Yuchao the other day
to ask if he was coming to the class reunion.
He actually asked me
who exactly would be attending.
He specifically asked about Yang Caiyun.
I thought he was asking
because he cared about his classmates.
This is going to be trouble.
What are you doing?
Yang Man, are you okay?
Simu.
Stop chasing.
It's him.
I found out
that he
logged into my email account.
They found the number I left for Teacher Fan.
It's okay.
Come here.
Bear with it.
It's fine now.
All better.
Reporter Lin, come quickly,
your mother is causing trouble in the ward again.
Um, I'm sorry,
I have something to attend to. I need to go.
Cast
Wang Bowen as Liang Simu
Guan Yuxi as Liang Siyuan
Zhao Boya as Yang Man
Zhang Xueyang as Yue Ling
Zhao Boya as Yang Caiyun
Xu Yijia as Lin Yuchao
You Jiawei as Da Xiong
Zhang Xueyang as Yue Ling
Pan Minyong as Gu Shuo
Yao Xiaoling
Wang Jiayi as Yao Xiaoling
Zhang Lijun as Lin's Mother
Li Jing as Professor Li
Also Starring
Hu Xiumin, Qian Yifei
Jin Lingtao, Wu Xinyu, Zou Chengying, Wang Donghua, Jia Wenhan, Gong Xuanlin
Yu Jingxuan, Xie Yuchen, Hu Xiumin, Qian Yifei, Zhang Zeshuo, Xu Jieqing
Li Xiaoqin, Li Siming, Wang Wenran, Shi Shengjie, Yang Jiuxiang, Wei Zhousheng
Qin Wenjie, Wu Lei, Ou Chaoxia, Shi Senjie, Yu Xinghui, Wang Xiang
Lin Jinxin, Gao Mingsheng, Cao Ying, Fang Yuqi, Xu Yeye, Weng Jia
Chen Jiafei, Ling Junqing, Liu Sheng, Tian Yehua, Su Yibing
Qin Wenjie, Wu Lei, Ou Chaoxia, Shi Senjie, Yu Xinghui, Wang Xiang
Chen Jiafei, Ling Junqing, Liu Sheng, Tian Yehua, Su Yibing, Luo Wenjuan
Yang Ran, Huang Jinze, Wang Juan, Wang Qiaoyin, Chen Jie, Wang Jiali
Tian Juan, Chen An, Ke Changgui, Ma Qianming, Ma Zhuoyuan, Peng Qun
Zhao Yang, Ren Lou
Su Yijuan, Liu Lianhao, Song Jiahui, Fang Shujuan
Song Jiahui
He Liqiong, Chen Jiayu, Guo Lisheng, Yang Rongxiang, Yang Yuxuan
Production Team
Executive Producer: Zhang Chengyang
Zhang Xueyang
Producer: Zhou Qingjie
Co-Producers: Wang Nannan, Dong Xinyu
Zhang Xueyang
Production Coordinator: Liang Yuchang
External Production: Qiao Shuai, Liu Zhu
Production Manager: Pan Yuxiang
Logistics Producer: Zhao Nan
Liang Yuchang
Zhang Chao
Transportation Coordinator: Tian Yanyan
Set Assistant: Zhang Chunsheng
Directing Team
Director: Zhang Jincheng
Executive Director: Xu Zulian
Liu Xinyao
Script Supervisor: Zhang Qingci
Casting Coordinator: Zhou Wei'an
Assistant Director: Liu Xinyao
Assistant Directors for Cast: Su Yang, Wang Qianchen
Script Supervisor: Zhang Qingci
Director's Assistant: Li Jinhui
Photography Team
Director of Photography: Feng Shijun
Cinematographers: Jin Hong, Kong Zhenzhen
Focus Pullers: Shen Yongqiang, Shen Haoyang
Camera Assistants: Liu Changchun, Pang Likai
Cinematographers: Jin Hong, Kong Zhenzhen
Lighting Team
Chief Lighting Assistant: Wang Jian
Lighting Director: Yu Dechun
Lighting Assistants: Jiang Guanghao, Han Lei
Xu Jili
Lyu Wenhao
Lighting Grip: Xu Xiaoben
Art Department
Art Director: Liang Yue
Art Designer: Lu Xinxin
Props: Liang Feng, Zhang Zhifei
Qiao Wei
Styling Team
Styling Director: Xu Hengxin
Makeup Artist: Xiao Lin
Hair Stylist: Yang Haidong
Costume Designer: Zhang Keke
On-set Staff: Che Jinxuan, Zuo Long
Xin Yu
Sound Recording
Guo Haonan, Ye Sicong
Zhang Xumeng, Tao Ye
Stills and Behind-the-Scenes
Post-Production
Editing Company
Kaifeng Yinghe Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Editing Supervisor: Lu Fuyulan
Editors: Dong Wanyun, Zhang Xu
Editing Assistant: Liu Jianguo
Post-Production Company
Beijing August Film Production Co., Ltd.
Production Director: Cai Fute
Project Director: Kong Shuo
Administrative Supervisor: Ying Jie
Production Director: Cai Fute
Project Director: Kong Shuo
Administrative Supervisor: Ying Jie
Colorist: Shu Zhi
Xie Xinyu
Colorist: Shu Zhiming
Compositing Output: Zhou Shuai, Xie Xinyu
Dialogue Subtitles: Xie Xinyu
VFX Supervisor: Zhu Bo
Compositing Output: Zhou Shuai, Xie Xinyu
ADR Recording: Chen Mengyi, Li Junting
Sound Effects: Jia Haolin
Chen Mengyi
Dialogue Editor: Jia Haolin
Mixing Engineer: Zhang Keke
Foley Artist: Jia Haolin
Finance: Wang Le
Mixing Engineer: Zhang Keke
Voice Director: Fan Deng
Voice Actors
Liang Simu, Xia Michen
Liang Siyuan, Tian Xin
Tian Xin
Liang Siyuan
Gu Shuo, Fu Xiting
Li Shaogang
Lin Yuchao, Sun Langlang
Yang Man, Bai Biqing
Fan Deng
Sun Langlang
Da Xiong, Fan Deng
Additional Voice Actors: Zi Nuo
Poster Design
Maoshi (Tianjin) Brand Design Co., Ltd.
Creative Director: Song Wanying
Lead Designers: Liu Yang, Li Jianming
Creative Copywriter: Hu Lili
Still Photography Post-production: Wu Xinyi
Behind-the-scenes Production: Li Ran, Zhong Xiaowei
Music Promotion
JS Entertainment
JS International Entertainment Co., Ltd.
Project Coordinator: Chen Yuting
Opening and Ending Theme
Insert Song
Listen to the Wandering Wind
(TV Series "Dangerous City Relations" Insert Song)
Lyrics by Wu Na
Performed by Mandy
Music by Zheng Bingbing
Producer: Zheng Bingbing
Lyrics by Wu Na
Arranged by Zheng Bingbing
Producer: Zheng Bingbing Shuang
Hu Dayang
Arranged by Zheng Bingbing & Liu Ju
Mixing Engineer: Hu Dayang
Mastering: Hu Dayang
Guitar: Liu Ju
Backing Vocals: Hu Ayou
Recording Engineer & Vocal Producer: Liu Baishen @KLE Music
Guitar: Liu Ju
Backing Vocals: Hu Ayou
Recording Engineer & Vocal Producer: Liu Baishen @KLE Music
Vocal Recording Studio: KLE Music·Boya Recording Studio
We'll Meet Again Someday
(TV Series "Dangerous City Relations" Insert Song)
Performed by Zhou Dian'ao
Lyrics by Zhou Dian'ao
Music by Zhou Dian'ao
Arranged by Fire Rap & Zhong Yinghao
Yuan Liyuan
Li Ding
Mixing Engineer: Li Ding
Vocals
Music Production: Hongxu Music
(TV Series "Dangerous City Relations" Insert Song)
Performed by Zhou Dian'ao
Lyrics by Zhou Dian'ao
Music by
Performed by Zhou Dian'ao
Music by Zhou Dian'ao
Wu Lei
Bass
Arranged by Original Soundtrack Musicians
Li Ding
Mastering: Zhou Dian'ao
Arranged by Original Soundtrack Musicians
Producer: Li Ding
Redemption
(TV Series "Dangerous City Relations" Insert Song)
Performed by TANA Band
Music by Zhao Wenqi
Lyrics by Zhao Wenqi
Arranged by Fu Dalong
Recording: Fu Dalong
Fu Dalong
Star Ocean
(TV Series "Dangerous City Relations" Insert Song)
Performed by Deng Jiakun
Music by Deng Jiakun
Deng Jiakun
Producer: Deng Jiakun
Music by Deng Jiakun
Arranged by Jin Junjie, Deng Jiakun
Backing Vocals: Jin Junjie, Deng Jiakun
Vocal Producer: Deng Jiakun
Mastering: TuJay@J.K.Studio
End Credits Song
"First Snow on Earth"
Performed by You Jiawei
Lyrics by Guo Zixiao
Music by Guo Zixiao
Special Thanks
Lei Ping
Hanshe Liquor Store, Wolfleg Whiskey
Distribution
Zhejiang Paijing Film Co., Ltd.
Production Company
Qijing Film (Ningbo) Co., Ltd.
Co-production Companies
Dongyang Fengweilan Film & TV Culture Co., Ltd.
1314 Film & TV Culture Media (Wuxi) Co., Ltd.
Liaoning Shanjing Culture Co., Ltd.
Presented by
Yangyang Deyi Technology Development (Shanghai) Co., Ltd.
Zhejiang Paijing Film Co., Ltd.