It seems Lin Yuchao was well prepared,
the residential cameras didn't capture him coming or going,
there's nothing we can do about him.
Every surveillance system has blind spots,
it wouldn't be difficult for him to avoid the cameras.
He's always been smart
and extremely cautious,
never leaving any traces behind.
Even that phone number for Mr. A back then
was registered under my name,
which is why you know nothing about Mr. A.
I was deceived by him back then,
and got pulled in deeper and deeper,
until I almost lost my life.
Ms. Yang,
so
five years ago,
what exactly was your relationship with Lin Yuchao
?
A secret
relationship.
Hi.
What are you doing?
Yunyun, don't be angry.
I'm not afraid of others knowing we're together.
What are you really worried about?
Qing.
Yunyun.
I'm worried that
you'll regret being with me someday.
How could you worry about that?
Didn't I promise you
that I'll always be with you?
If you don't believe me,
I'll post about our relationship on social media right now.
What are you doing?
I...
I'm giving you the security you've always wanted.
Security?
This isn't giving me security,
you're embarrassing me.
Do you want everyone to know
that I can't measure up to my own girlfriend in every way?
Then what do you want from me?
Break up?
No...
I don't want to break up.
How could I ever bear to break up with you?
Yunyun.
Don't leave me.
Don't.
Okay,
don't leave me.
I will never leave you.
There's a new spicy hot pot place that just opened near the school entrance,
let's go there for lunch today.
Senior,
Yang Caiyun.
I like you
Will you be my girlfriend?
The junior really has guts.
Caiyun, you don't have a boyfriend anyway,
just say yes.
Yeah, say yes to him.
Say yes!
Yuchao.
What are you doing?
Weren't you on a date with someone else?
Why are you here then?
Nonsense!
How could I possibly be dating someone else?
You're lying to me!
You think I don't know
that you went camping with them?
Silly.
I already have a boyfriend,
how could I possibly date someone else?
Trust me.
Yunyun.
I'm sorry.
I'm so jealous of those guys
because you're really amazing.
Whenever there are admirers around you,
No.
any guy near you makes me suffer.
Yunyun.
Do you think I'm too controlling?
Am I too possessive?
If you can't handle it anymore.
Let's break up.
No.
I don't want to break up with you.
I actually love your dominance and possessiveness.
You are mine.
I won't allow anyone near you.
You will always be mine.
I am yours.
I never expected this.
This Lin Yuchao is such a fake.
Teacher Yue was right,
this is his advantage.
This guy
is best at exploiting others' weaknesses to set them up.
Just like soon after,
when he approached Liang Siyuan.
He used the same act of playing pitiful and insecure
to gain sympathy.
Back then,
he refused to make our relationship public.
It's just to make it easier
for me to find prey later.
Lin Yuchao.
Let's break up.
Are you sure you want to break up with me?
What do you think?
You cheated on me first.
Lin Yuchao, you have thick skin,
but I have principles.
Look.
I thought it was fun,
so I recorded it.
What do you think?
I even shared it with others.
Lin Yuchao, what are you doing?
I'm the only one who gets to use you and dump you when I'm bored. Got it?
Understand?
You beast!
From that day on,
I developed severe depression.
My weight
kept dropping.
My hair
was falling out in clumps.
Until
I saw the news about Liang Siyuan's incident.
I finally woke up.
Why should victims
struggle to move on,
while perpetrators act like nothing happened,
even enjoying bright futures?
Now.
He is my enemy.
To get revenge,
I infiltrated the lab.
I tipped you off.
The password is 223514.
That anonymous number
was you.
Cast
Wang Bowen as Liang Simu
Guan Yuxi as Liang Siyuan
Yang Man
Zhao Boya as Yang Caiyun
Zhang Xueyang as Yue Ling
Xu Yijia as Lin Yuchao
Pan Minyong
Wang Jiayi as Yao Xiaoling
Pan Minyong as Gu Shuo
Zhang Lijun as Lin's Mother
Yao Xiaoling
Li Jing as Professor Li
Wu Sijun as Vincent
Also Starring
Yu Jingxuan, Xie Yuchen, Hu Xiumin, Qian Yifei, Zhang Zeshuo, Xu Jieqing
Jin Lingtao, Wu Xinyu, Zou Chengying, Wang Donghua, Jia Wenhan, Gong Xuanlin
Zheng Yuqi, Wen Honglin, Ma Xun, Wu Sijun, Jin Shucheng, Niu Tianjun
Liu Sheng, Tian Yehua
Yu Xinghui, Guo Mengwu, Zhao Yang, Ren Lou, Lao Jinze, Cai Liping
Tian Juan, Chen An, Zhang Gui, Ma Qianming, Ma Zhuoyuan, Peng Qun
Niu Meng, Su Yijuan, Liu Lianhao, Song Jiahui, Fang Shujuan, Yang Xin
Song Jiahui
Production Team
Executive Producer: Zhang Chengyang
Zhang Xueyang
Producers: Zhou Qingjie, Qiu Lindi
Huang Peiyu
Coordinator: Liang Yuchang
Production Manager: Pan Yuxiang
External Producers: Qiao Shuai, Liu Zhu
Life Producer: Zhao Nan
On-site Producer: Zhang Chao
Vehicle Dispatcher: Tian Yanyan
Zhang Chunsheng
Directing Team
Director: Zhang Jincheng
Executive Director: Xu Zulian
Script Supervisor: Zhang Qingci
Assistant Director: Liu Xinyao
Cast Coordinator: Zhou Wei'an
Script Supervisor: Zhang Qingci
Cast Assistant Directors: Su Yang, Wang Qianchen
Director's Assistant: Li Jinhui
Photography Team
Director of Photography: Feng Shijun
Cinematographer: Jin Hong
Focus Pullers: Shen Yongqiang, Shen Haoyang
Cinematographers: Jin Hong, Kong Zhenzhen
Camera Assistants: Liu Changchun, Pang Likai
Lighting Team
Lighting Director: Yu Dechun
Chief Lighting Assistant: Wang Jian
Lighting Assistants: Jiang Guanghao, Han Lei
Lyu Wenhao
Lighting Grip: Xu Xiaoben
Art Department
Art Director: Liang Yue
Art Director: Lu Xinxin
Props: Liang Feng, Zhang Zhifei
Art Director
Qiao Wei
Styling Team
Styling Director: Xu Hengxin
Makeup Artist: Xiao Lin
Yang Haidong
Costume Designer: Zhang Keke
Hair Stylist: Yang Haidong
Sound Recording
Guo Haonan, Ye Sicong
Stills & Behind the Scenes
Zhang Xumeng, Tao Ye
Post-Production
Editing Company
Kaifeng Yinghe Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Editing Supervisor: Lu Fuyulan
Editor: Dong Wanyun
Editing Assistant: Liu Jianguo
Post-Production Company
Beijing August Film and Television Production Co., Ltd.
Production Director: Cai Fute
Project Director: Kong Shuo
Cai Fute
Administrative Supervisor: Ying Jie
Colorist: Shu Zhiming
Dialogue Subtitles: Xie Xinyu
VFX Supervisor: Zhu Bo
Compositing Output: Zhou Shuai, Xie Xinyu
Compositing: Zhu Bo
ADR Recording: Chen Mengyi
Sound Effects: Jia Haolin
ADR Recording: Chen Mengyi, Li Junting
Dialogue Editor: Jia Haolin
Foley Artist: Jia Haolin
Wang Le
Mixing Engineer: Zhang Keke
Dubbing Director: Fan Deng
Voice Actors
Liang Simu, Xia Michen
Liang Siyuan, Tian Xin
Bai Biqing
Yue Ling, Li Shaogang
Gu Shuo, Fu Xiting
Yang Man, Bai Biqing
Lin Yuchao, Sun Langlang
Other Voice Actor: Zi Nuo
Poster Design
Maoshi (Tianjin) Brand Design Co., Ltd.
Creative Director: Song Wanying
Lead Designers: Liu Yang, Li Jianming
Creative Copywriter: Hu Lili
Zhou Lin
Other Visual Designers: Wang Yuhang, Chen Haibo
Still Photography Post-production: Wu Xinyi
Behind-the-scenes Production: Li Ran, Zhong Xiaowei
Music Promotion
JS Entertainment
JS International Entertainment Co., Ltd.
Project Coordinator: Chen Yuting
Opening and Ending Theme Songs
Insert Song
Listen to the Wandering Wind
(Insert song for the drama "Dangerous City Relations")
Performed by Mandy
Performed by Mandy Zhao Manjia
Lyrics by Wu Na
Composed by Zheng Bingbing
Producers: Zheng Bingbing, Shuang Shuang
Arranged by Zheng Bingbing, Liu Ju
Arranged by Zheng Bingbing
Mixing Engineer: Hu Dayang
Hu Dayang
Backing Vocals: Hu Ayou
Guitar: Liu Ju
Recording Engineer & Vocal Producer: Liu Baishen @KLE Music
Vocal Recording Studio: KLE Music·Boya Recording Studio
We'll Meet Again Someday
(Theme song from TV series "Dangerous City Relations")
Performed by Zhou Dian'ao
Lyrics by Zhou Dian'ao
Music by Zhou Dian'ao
Producer: Li Ding
Acoustic Guitarist: Wu Lei
Mixing Engineer: Li Ding
Music Production: Hongxu Music
(Theme song from TV series "Dangerous City Relations")
Performed by Zhou Dian'ao
Lyrics by Zhou Dian'ao
Music by
Zhou Dian'ao
Music by Zhou Dian'ao
Performed by Zhou Dian'ao
Li Ding
Arrangement by Acoustic Musician
Mastering Engineer: Zhou Dian'ao
Producer: Li Ding
Redemption
(Theme song from TV series "Dangerous City Relations")
Performed by TANA Band
Lyrics by Zhao Wenqi
Music by Zhao Wenqi
Arrangement by
Fu Dalong
Recording Engineer: Fu Dalong
Star Ocean
(Theme song from TV series "Dangerous City Relations")
Performed by Deng Jiakun
Lyrics by Deng Jiakun
Music by Deng Jiakun
Producer: Deng Jiakun
Arrangement by Jin Junjie and Deng Jiakun
Arrangement by
Backing Vocals: Jin Junjie
Vocal Producer: Deng Jiakun
Mixing: TuJay@J.K.Studio
Mastering: TuJav@J.K.S
End Credits Song
"First Snow in the World"
Performed by You Jiawei
Lyrics by Guo Zixiao
Music by Guo Zixiao
Special Thanks
Tear Bottle
Hanshe Liquor Store Wolfleg Whiskey
Distribution Company
Zhejiang Paijing Film Industry Co., Ltd.
Production Company
Qijing Film Industry (Ningbo) Co., Ltd.
Co-produced by:
Dongyang Fengweilan Film and Television Culture Co., Ltd.
1314 Film and Television Culture Media (Wuxi) Co., Ltd.
Liaoning Shanjing Culture Co., Ltd.
Produced by:
Yangyang Deyi Technology Development (Shanghai) Co., Ltd.
Zhejiang Paiking Film Co., Ltd.