I will not give up!
The operating system I built for the Cotaya case was perfect.
No, don't do that.
It's not a system you can easily crack.
But they cracked it and came in.
What do you know, anyway?
Have you been giving them the money for the treatment all this time?
They're the ones who'll heal me, not the hospital!
I hold onto your words of strength. Father...
You want me to pay for what you ate?
Are you kidding right now?
Always watch above your head.
Whoa!
The land is up in the sky.
What the?
Was there a folk village here?
What's this? What's wrong?
Shit!
Why did the car shut down all of a sudden?
Huh? Now the phone is...
Hey, let me use your phone if you have one.
You managed to survive until now.
What?
Hold on. You're that...
You bastard!
Get lost immediately!
That crafty thing got scared and ran away for now,
but I'm sure it'll come back soon...
to take your life away.
What a crazy cult bastard.
What kind of concept is that?
How will you sell it like that? Geez...
He called you a cult, Mr. Kim!
Looks like he's lacking faith a lot.
If you lack faith...
you should strengthen it.
Father.
All done, all done, all done.
When?
He died in the ambulance on the way to the hospital.
How many people witnessed it?
Quite a number of members saw him,
since he collapsed during the service.
All right. You may leave.
You ironed the gown quite well.
Thank you, Father.
I feel refreshed, thanks to you.
Let's do our best with the power of Pure White.
Brother Lee Jung Joo was a very warm person.
Ok Joo Man, you bastard!
You killed my father!
You murderer!
- Ok Joo Man, you killed him!
- I told him...
to return home and spend his remaining time with his family so many times,
but he said he would stay by my side until the end.
What have you done?
I prayed for him to get better.
To become healthy again.
The beneficiary of the late Mr. Lee's life insurance was Pure White Church, not his family.
Did you know about this?
No.
But the late Mr. Lee did often say this.
That he trusts me...
more than his family.
Don't lie! You ordered him to!
The late Mr. Lee said...
- that he forgives his children.
- Shut up, you murderer!
Hey, hey, that's enough!
Please calm down.
Those vulgar nobodies.
These are rice cakes.
We should catch that bastard immediately and give him a beating.
Hyungnim is right. Let's teach him a lesson this instant!
Gosh, calm down, you guys.
Didn't you hear what Mr. Kim Do Gi said?
This time, Ok Joo Man must step up himself.
I don't know. I don't remember.
Come on.
Hold on.
Even if we teach that cult leader a lesson now,
as long as the member's faith remains strong, nothing will change.
Mr. Kim's right. We need to shake the roots of their faith.
So calm yourselves down, okay?
You heard Mr. Jang, right?
And the success or failure of this entire case depends on both of your shoulders.
Should you be this riled up or not?
We shouldn't.
We already installed everything earlier.
Good job.
Aigoo.
Wow, I'm not sure if it's because it's silk,
but the color is quite elegant.
♫  I'll cross three thousand miles  ♫
♫  Doo, doo, doo, doo  ♫
Whoa, shit!
Shit.
What the hell?
That scared me.
Shit, did I see it wrong?
What is this?
Whoa!
Shit, what's wrong with this?
Shit!
F***!
Oh, shit!
Shit! I almost died. Oh, shit!
There's nothing wrong?
Are you sure it was properly inspected?
I said the brakes and the belt didn't work.
I almost died because of that.
After meticulous inspection by our mechanics,
there wasn't a single problem, sir.
And you shouldn't speak informally to me, sir.
Hey, you think I can act all friendly when I almost died? Huh?
Anyhow, Korea is just full of con artists.
They'll do whatever it takes to fleece their own countrymen out of money.
These money-crazed people.
Come out... Come out.
Come out!
Oppa! What's wrong?
Who are you telling to come out?
Someone's there. A bastard wearing a gat* and slitted eyes...
(Traditional Korean hat for men worn by Grim Reapers.)
was staring at me.
Nobody's there. What are you saying?
Oppa, you should immediately go to the hospital tomorrow.
They say you can see hallucinations when your body is weak.
What are you doing?
Gosh...
If you have specific conditions of the brain, you might see or hear hallucinations,
but your general workup is unremarkable.
He made such a big fuss about not going to the hospital to the members,
but look at him getting a full workup because he got a little startled.
Do you practice a religion?
I don't. I don't believe in anything.
If you don't practice a religion,
try picking up a hobby like hiking or fishing.
This could be caused by stress.
Gosh, I get what you're trying to say,
so give me the most expensive IV treatment you have.
Aigoo, I'm dying here...
Always watch above your head.
The land is up in the sky. You're destined to die young.
That crafty thing got scared and ran away, for now,
but I'm sure it'll come back soon...
to take your life away.
He's starting to get a bit nervous now, huh?
Father Ok Joo Man is on his way to Mobumdang.
Did you make a reservation?
I need to make a reservation?
Yes, we run solely on reservations.
So when can I see him?
Hold on.
The earliest availability is December 19, 2025.
Would you like to reserve that?
Shit, 2025?
Yes. Oh, my, someone else just reserved it.
Shall I help you make one for 2026?
Are you kidding me?
No...
What is all the ruckus?
Some child rudely came to see you without a reservation.
Hey,
you and I need to talk.
You wretch.
I see you're still alive, but how dare you cause a disturbance on private property?
What?
If he causes another scene, call the police and chase him out.
Yes, Priest Kim.
Whoa, hey.
Please leave.
You can go back out the way you came. Just drive in reverse.
Don't make a U-turn. You'll destroy the grass. Hurry up and leave.
My goodness.
These fools are putting on a show.
P-Please stop doing this.
If your unni can't pay back her debt,
shouldn't the younger sister work hard to pay it off?
I gave you all the money you asked for.
Our interest rate is quite high.
Did you get hurt anywhere?
- Is she the unni?
- She's not.
Did they have permission to come in? They just barged in, didn't they?
I didn't want to bother the neighbors,
so I asked them to come in and talk.
Oh...
so you invited them in.
Hey, I don't know what your relationship is,
but we're having a legal conversation, so why don't you get lost?
- Tell them to leave now.
- What?
You need to give them notice at least three times for it to become trespassing.
Leave.
What?
What is this, a joke?
Please leave!
I was too nice to you-
You bitch-
I totally forgot to return this.
Suing me would be pointless since I was only practicing self-defense.
Collections in this manner are illegal, so don't ever come back here.
I'm doing my best to hold back and handle this legally.
Is she a cop?
Shit, let's go.
It's okay.
It's okay now.
Hang in there.
Your unni will return without a doubt.
Will she really come back?
Jin Hee, you love your unni.
Your unni feels the same way about you, too.
So let us have some faith.
Faith your unni will return.
How can you be so sure?
Because we're diligently pouring faith, even now.
Good job.
You may leave.
Why did you call him here?
I said you may leave.
Understood.
What on earth are you doing?
To meet with you via reservation will be in 2026.
I don't really have patience.
I've had bad luck ever since I met you.
I now know why those crafty things on your shoulder
are being docile.
You know who I am...
don't you?
They're waiting.
How long have you been tailing me?
They're simply waiting for their master to return.
- Trying to take you away-
- Shit!
It's like I'm talking to a wall.
I'm trying to have a conversation here.
You didn't listen to a single word I said, did you?
Judging by the green in your eyes,
you saw something you shouldn't have.
Cut the bullshit and tell me when you started tailing me?
You awakened something that should've been left alone...
didn't you?
Do you really want to die?
You're the one who's going to die!
I usually don't hit people outside of work,
but you'll be an exception.
The thing that's been following you around...
was it wearing a gat?
Now we're having a conversation.
Its eyes were sharp,
and it had a mouth full of harsh energy.
A beating is the best medicine, huh?
You opened your mouth before I even hit you...
Shit.
What's going on?
Yes.
From what I observed,
it doesn't look like it'll give up on you.
Hey, where are you looking? You should be looking at me-
Hurry and untie me.
Now!
Here.
You saw it too, didn't you? What was that?
Don't come closer.
Speak from there.
What is that thing?
What in the world have you done to attract such a thing?
You wretch.
What have you disturbed?
Gosh, what are you going on about? I didn't disturb anything!
What did I disturb?
Why are you asking me
when you're the one who disturbed it?
What did I...
disturb?
You didn't just disturb it. You destroyed it.
I wouldn't step on that if I were you.
Shit.
He has the face of a national traitor.
I can feel the murderous intent just by looking at him.
He's not one to give up...
until you die.
Me?
One sheet on a pillar bathed in the morning sunlight.
One sheet on a pillar bathed in moonlight.
And stick one underneath your desk.
Where do you think you're going?
I need to go and get those from him, don't I?
Promise me one thing before that.
Don't come looking for me again.
After meeting you,
I've had bad luck.
During the seven days of processing,
don't add to your wealth.
Why not?
It's bad karma.
It's bad karma. It's bad karma.
That's enough. You're making me feel like shit!
Priest Kim drew them for you with his precious time,
so just be thankful.
Bad karma.
Shoo.
That's enough!
Priest Kim, please draw me a talisman, too.
What type of talisman do you want?
Well... wealth, employment, promotion, health,
romance, and marriage. One to cover everything.
All things prosperous.
Everything will turn out well.
This won't have any effects, gosh.
Gosh, my back.
I'm just playing along.
Playing along...
Who is it?
We finished preparing for the service.
Nothing goes according to my liking.
Is something bothering you?
Skip the sermon,
and prepare the bleaching.
I'll never give up on the path to Pure White!
I won't give up!
Wait, wait, wait!
Wait, s-so...
I want to be healed first, Father.
Path to Pure White...
Move your hand.
I won't give up on you.
Father!
Look at this! A real grilled chicken.
Cool, isn't it?
Hey, stop crying.
I'll give you all my drumsticks.
Really?
Mr. Choi, Mr. Park, where are you?
Oh...
we came outside for a bit.
Is Mr. Park okay?
Mr. Park, are you okay?
Mr. Kim Do Gi,
I've never been hit this much in my life.
Who told you to run out and get it?
Then what was I supposed to do?
They already looked sick. How could I just sit and watch them get assaulted?
But Hyungnim, I got hit so much, but it doesn't hurt one bit.
- Strange, isn't it?
- Mr. Park!
Did you take that narcotic again? I told you not to.
How could I not when they were all staring at me?
More importantly, his demand for money has become more adamant.
To build a castle of Pure White.
Gosh, Priest Kim told him not to seek more wealth, but he didn't listen.
Mr. Park and Mr. Choi, let's start plan B.
Okay, we're ready.
Hyungnim, aren't you being too passionate about this?
If you'll say useless things like that, just go home. I even gave you my drumsticks.
I need to meet with Ok Joo Man's mother.
He'll probably listen to his mom.
Ok Joo Man's mother?
She passed away a long time ago.
Exactly.
Huh?
This is just one speck!
F-Father, your clothes...
Huh?
- Leader Baek, kick them all out.
- Excuse me?
Kick out all the members.
Yes, Father.
The service is over! Everyone, leave.
- Please hold me.
- What's going on?
Everyone, leave.
The service is over!
What have you done with the talismans I drew you?
Oh, here, here.
Aigoo!
Did someone come in here to mess with that?
No, no. No one.
No one knows I put it here.
Why did you do that?
Oh, I just... did.
A person being aware that they're going to die
isn't always a bad thing.
What are you saying? You're upsetting me with your words.
This is the money I got from you.
Don't look for me anymore.
Hey, how can you just leave like this?
Hey, have some responsibility!
You wretch!
Are you deaf or something? Get lost!
If I just leave, it's over.
You need to do something about those ghosts-
It's bad karma. Get lost-
Stop doing this!
My salt! My salt...
All right, if you won't leave, then I will!
Come on.
You wretch...
What have you brought with you?
M-Me?
Hide.
If you don't want to die, hide this instant!
W-Where? Where can I hide?
Where?
This is a sacred sanctuary to worship our god!
If you're a guest, reveal yourself.
If you're an evil spirit, then remove yourself!
If you're a guest... then... reveal yourself...
If you're an evil spirit... then remove-
Hey! Get it together.
Hey!
Joo Man.
Where's my Joo Man?
My son.
Won't you come out even when your mom is here?
When Father Ok Joo Man was young,
he really loved the sticky rice cakes his mom bought him.
Sticky rice cakes...
Are you hiding because I didn't bring sticky rice cakes?
I forgot and couldn't buy any today.
I'm sorry.
Mom?
And...
My Joo Man, you even sold our cow behind my back.
Are you scared I'll punish you?
I still don't hate you, my Joo Man.
Lies!
You told me to go die!
It was because I was upset.
I just want my Joo Man to be healthy.
Really?
Are you really Mom?
My Joo Man...
Mom won't let...
anything bad happen to you.
Joo Man.
It's been tough, right?
My son.
My Joo Man.
You know I love you most in the world, right?
Mom...
Joo Man.
Mom will...
never...
give up on my son!
Mom!
Mom...
Good job.
Gosh.
I knew you were unlucky the moment I first saw you.
What will you do about the damages? Nevermind.
I'm pleading with you.
Don't come back here anymore.
Did Mom write this?
How am I supposed to know what your mom wrote?
I don't know, Punk.
I know what it is.
19510524...
This is Dad's birthday.
The one after that
is Dad's memorial day.
The numbers on the next lines
are Mom's birthday and memorial day.
The numbers on the last line
are my birthday.
And the numbers after that...
Then...
your mom must have come to tell you when you die.
The day...
I will die.
If it's the 23rd,
you don't have much time left.
Go on.
Go and spend...
your remaining time with your family.
Priest Kim!
What mom would come to provide the date of her child's death?
She told me, so I could stay alive. To stay alive!
Didn't I tell you to leave?
Please... please help me, Priest Kim!
It's like talking to a wall.
I think this punk is requesting a reversal of the fate ritual.
You wretch! Shut your mouth this instant!
Reversal of fate ritual?
Please do that for me.
- Please!
- Do you even know what you're talking about?
A reversal of fate ritual is so dangerous that even I must risk my life.
Why should I risk my life to save someone like you?
I don't want to!
Your mom... must be trying to save you...
and kill me.
I'll do...
whatever you ask of me!
Fine.
I'll do my best...
to keep you alive.
Thank you.
I won't forget your mercy.
One, two, three.
While preparing for a reversal of fate ritual,
you absolutely must not pray nor greed after wealth.
All right.
Be quiet!
Offerings are off-limits. Don't pay them, don't bring them!
Don't pray, either!
Hwi, hwi, hwi.
Hwi...
Always carry this on your body.
You should never be parted from it.
All right.
Don't be frugal in your spending.
That's how you and I will live.
Yes.
Whoa, Father is rich in cash.
As for instruments, you must bring in the best in the nation.
Yes!
What are you doing?
No take-backs!
Be quiet. That's bad karma.
He's giving us exactly what we asked for.
The thing about faith is...
once it's built, it's game over.
A mortgage loan?
- Why are they doing that?
- It hurts, it hurts.
I don't know. We're just doing anything that makes money.
Oh.
Nice and tight.
Go away!
Go away! Go away!
Why are you picking up this phone? Who are you?
Where?
Fighting the evil spirit in my heart...
May my lord's Pure White be spread all over the world.
The path of Pure White.
Jin Sun. Jin Sun!
Go away!
Mr. Kim Do Gi, Jin Sun passed out.
The more in pain you are, the more Pure White you'll become.
And frequent the hospital without my knowledge!
Jin Hee...
my condition wasn't able to improve anymore.
But then I met him.
When time passes, you'll also realize
how powerful Pure White is.
Don't you think it left by now?
I think it left.
It left.
Priest Kim, it hurts.
It hurts.
Father called me
and told me to take his place
to lead you to the Land of Pure White.
He passed on the Power of Pure White to me.
I've been blessed by Father, so now I'm the blessed Mother.
Going to more than 60 countries around the world,
we will look for our rightful heaven-
What the hell are you doing right now!
Father!
I told you not to gather since it's bad karma.
Why won't you listen? Why?
Father!
What are you doing? You're the one following around a cult leader!
Don't insult Priest Kim!
The likes of you will have to wait at least three years to meet him.
Have you gone entirely mad?
Mad?
You can't even memorize the lines I gave you. Mother?
Aigoo...
Mother... Like hell you are!
Let go of me.
Hey!
Let go!
Do you practice a religion?
I don't. I don't believe in anything.
- What's that?
- What did he just say?
What if they actually die?
They were about to die anyway.
We're not legally at fault at all!
I'm sure you'll go to hell, Oppa.
Hello? Aigoo! Do you believe in that? What a baby!
Hey!
Go away! Go away!
Won't it be pointless to bring them out if they're just going to return?
Yes, unless Ok Joon Man personally tells them to leave.
The cult Father will tell his members to leave with his own mouth?
Is that possible?
We must expose him for the human blinded by self-interest that he is.
They'll make their own decisions after that.
Whether to stay...
or leave.
Hey!
I told you not to pray.
It's bad karma!
What are you staring at? Kick them all out!
All this time!
H-Have you...
been deceiving us all?
- How could you?
- Gosh!
All the money I gave you...
Didn't you hear me?
Kick them all out!
Everything...
was all a lie?
I-I wasn't.
I just did as he ordered me to do!
What?
I...
I'm your Father! You punks.
- Kill him!
You bastard!
Don't worry. She'll come out soon.
They're coming out.
- Where's Ji Hoon?
- Honey!
He's there!
- Over there!
Sang Tae!
Mom!
- Sang Tae!
- Jin Eon!
Hyungnim!
Aigoo, Jin Eon.
There, there.
Good job.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Something must've possessed me.
♫  It only takes a moment, just enough to catch my breath  ♫
♫  I just have to lightly fill my stomach and walk again  ♫
♫  It'll be fine, don't worry  ♫
♫  If you pat my shoulder and tell me to cheer up, I'll stand back up  ♫
♫  How beautiful is that ocean at sunrise?  ♫
Are you cold?
No.
It feels nice to walk together.
- Unni.
- Yeah?
Let's become healthier and come back here next year.
♫  No matter where it is  ♫
Where are you going? What about our Pure White buildings?
I won't keep that haunted house even if you pay me.
Gosh, this is the right place Priest Kim told me about-
Wait for me!
What are you waiting for? Before the other things follow us in...
Other things?
Come on!
Gosh.
Why do you lack such sense?
What's going on?
I mean...
Open the door for a sec! Huh?
Let me see your face again!
I just need to confirm something!
Please open the door for a moment!
Just for a moment!
Open the door-
Sir!
Open the door!
Hey! Ow... Open the door!
What's going on?
Gosh.
Ahjussi!
Where are we going?
Everything will go according to Priest Kim.
Yes, Priest Kim.
Priest, my foot. Call me Kim Do Gi.
Although, I'm not sure you'll get a chance to.
Oh, how could I dare to call you by your name?
But I saw that ghost again.
Why? Are you scared?
He must've followed me here because of bad karma.
Isn't this nothing compared to the pain of the families you tore apart?
Priest Kim, what should I do?
You must be really scared.
Then try practicing a religion.
Sorry? A religion?
Religion usually offers courage and peace to those with hardships.
That's what real religion is.
Take care.
Priest Kim, what are you saying all of a-
Hello? Hello?
Shit!
What's wrong with the signal?
Priest Kim,
that evil spirit reappeared!
Priest Kim!
Dispatch complete.
Everyone did a good job.
I heard you transferred all the members to a treatment ward.
It's going to cost an arm and a leg.
You know that haunted house?
After chasing away the ghosts, the price went up.
I'm hungry.
How do you all feel about a hot soondoobu*?
(Spicy tofu stew.)
No, no, no. I-I don't think I can tolerate anything white for a while.
How does jjajangmyeon* sound?
(Black bean noodles.)
I want to avoid anything black, too.
Gosh, then we have no choice,
but to eat the hanwoo* everyone wants.
(High quality Korean beef)
When you feel weak, go for hanwoo!
Let's go with hanwoo. Let's get it, hanwoo.
Oh, by the way, how did you control the school of ravens?
How in the world did you do that?
W-What do you mean ravens?
It was so cool.
Kind of scary, too.
That's not...
something we did.
What are you talking about? Even now, they're still flying above my head-
Huh?
What's that?
I'm flooring it, but it won't go any faster.
Yes, Go Eun.
Are you home?
Mr. Choi said he'll buy chicken. Why don't you come?
No, it's okay.
It's not every day Mr. Choi offers to buy...
Mr. Kim Do Gi, what are you drinking?
A protein drink.
What you drink after working out?
You really like that, huh?
The one that's carbonated?
It's a nice, light drink to enjoy. It's delicious.
It's on me! Carbonation!
Me, me, me!
Gosh, all right. If you change your mind, come to Rainbow Chicken.
Okay, have a good time.
Do Gi hyungnim.
Oh, you were working out.
No, I was finishing up.
I bought some coffee. I wanted to get some advice from you.
Do you have time?
It definitely feels different drinking it from up here.
Is it because of the nice view...
or because I'm drinking with you?
I'm not in a place where I can give advice to someone else.
And I don't know how to.
I just thought if it's you, you might know the answer.
To be honest, I have a number of friends.
But at one point, they kept coming back from getting beat up somewhere! Multiple times.
So I got mad and went to punish him.
But I had no idea why he kept beating them up.
It's not like he held a grudge, and they didn't even know each other.
Why do you think he did it?
I don't think I'll be of any help to you.
That's why I'm going to befriend him.
I figured I might figure it out if we became friends.
What do you think?
Do you think that person and I can become friends?
No.
It seems the two of you couldn't be friends from the start.
Why not?
Isn't it enough if I ask him to become friends?
That person will continue to beat up your friends.
Gosh.
That's going to be a problem.
Hyungnim, can I use your bathroom?
Where did he get these?
Do Gi hyungnim really crossed the line.
It's taking a while for you to find the bathroom.
♫  Take me back, it's over!  ♫
♫  Put the pain that's been trapping you behind  ♫
♫  And I'll fight, fight for you!  ♫
♫  A I will run to the end of the world  ♫
Will you tell me about what you've been through?
Han Soo Ryeon's case causes me great sadness, too.
Stop the bullshit! You're the one who did this!
A doctor performed surgery to kill someone?
They're trying to save her!
It's a medical accident...
What kind of person is Director Ahn Young Sook?
She's a famous doctor known for performing many surgeries.
Wow, what's with that sight of her being the focus of respect?
- I'm confused.
- Which department are you from?
I'm disappointed, Doctor. I'm upset.
I need to get back to the site of the crime.
Do you have any intention of stopping here?
I'm warning you. Be careful.
Mr. Kim Do Gi, you need to get out of there now.
Is this noise going off because of me?
- Get out of there for now.
- What's going on?
Excuse me. Can I borrow a coin?