ظآزHey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?ظآز
ظآزAlways stumbling upon
my little secretsظآز
ظآزFalling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouthظآز
ظآزLike my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoonظآز
ظآزHey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?ظآز
ظآزYou effortlessly awaken
my protective instinctsظآز
ظآزHitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temperظآز
ظآزLike my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winterظآز
ظآزWhy is it you again?
That sweet way you speakظآز
ظآزAs if the whole world knows
my mind is full of youظآز
ظآزWhy is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facadeظآز
ظآزI might as well play along.
Let me protect youظآز
ظآزWhy is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lipsظآز
ظآزBefore I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."ظآز
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 31=
Didn't you say it yourself
at the venture capital conference?
National strategy, rural revitalization
is definitely a new wave of our era.
Right?
And its impact is no less than
what happened decades ago,
the Reform and Opening-up
that my dad experienced.
So sometimes I think,
regardless of whether Fulaxida
ends up making money or not,
it doesn't really seem that important.
Life is so short.
If I catch such a huge wave
and don't even jump in,
then my courage would be even less
than my dad's, wouldn't it?
That's true.
And let me tell you something else.
A company's ultimate survival
doesn't depend
on how much capital it has.
Anyone can provide money.
What's most important
is the personal ability
of the project's founder.
So what I value most
is you as a person.
And him, of course.
2022.
One at a time.
Because you're just like me.
In such a restless city,
you've sniffed out the development
opportunities in the countryside.
I really, really admire that about you.
Yifei,
how are you
so good at complimenting yourself?
You should teach me sometime.
See? That's why I said
you have a keen sense.
But in any case,
we're like-minded people.
Right?
Look at this vast land.
What is this?
This is a god-given fortune.
But in my opinion,
Fulaxida's current strength
is far from enough.
It's still too slow.
In the future, we must
turn this place into
a model zone for modern agriculture.
Do you want to raise funds now?
Didn't you disagree before?
What I disagreed with
was raising bad money.
Because that kind of money will eventually
turn into joss paper to be burned.
Do you understand?
What we're really lacking
is good money that comes with
the halo of all kinds of resources.
I want that kind of good money.
And the more, the better.
Only this kind of good money
can make this place a dream come true.
I get it.
We're going to raise good money.
Yes.
That's exactly what Yifei said.
He agreed to raise funds.
Getting your Mr. Li to agree
was really not easy.
It's just good money, right?
I'll go prepare right now.
Okay.
(Sanglin Group Co., Ltd.)
Alright.
Now that the big problem is solved.
Once Fulaxida goes public
through a backdoor listing,
the nominee shares you have with me
will increase in value dozens of times.
Only if I'm alive to take it.
The current situation
is not looking good.
I think we need to speed up our process.
We can't afford any delays.
I've done everything I can on my end.
The rest is up to you.
Don't worry.
We've known each other for decades.
Just relax.
Here.
Have some water.
I know how you work.
But sometimes,
things don't go as planned.
It's better to be cautious,
don't you think?
Is it connected?
It's connected.
Is there a reaction?
Yes.
You're acting like
a teenager in love right now.
What happened to that passionate energy
you had when persuading
the villagers?
Pull yourself together.
It's all for work.
My wife just called me.
Qian Fei had no idea
you were here on a business trip.
What's going on? Is there a problem?
No.
Nothing at all.
I get it.
Off to a bad start.
What nonsense?
What do you know?
Let me tell you something.
I was in a similar situation
as you before.
My relationship with my wife
was stuck at the thinking stage.
Like anticipating, overthinking,
blah, blah, blah, all that stuff.
But I forgot the most important thing,
feelings.
If it feels right, it is right.
I know
you finance guys always like
to calculate things
like returns and losses.
You're always planning for a rainy day.
But love isn't rational.
It's emotional.
And I can tell you,
if fate has a relationship
in store for you two,
whether you just pass by or cross paths,
you can't escape it.
Running all the way here is useless.
So, Mr. Li,
you're just making trouble for yourself.
Keep an eye on things here.
I'm going to go check things out.
ظآزWhat matters to me is what you needظآز
ظآزNo more, no less.
I only hope I can give it to youظآز
Why is it you?
ظآزWhat I treasure is what I haveظآز
ظآزBit by bit,
I only hope you're there with meظآز
ظآزThose sweet promises and words of loveظآز
ظآزLike fireworks
lighting up the midnight skyظآز
Stop messing around.
Fulfill the contract.
ظآزLeaving me feeling like
I'm walking on airظآز
ظآزHarsh words, lies,
and words I can't make sense ofظآز
ظآزAll dressed up in hollow splendorظآز
ظآزDreams, nonsense,
and the words hidden in my heartظآز
ظآزBeneath this burning gazeظآز
ظآزWhat I dream of is being with youظآز
ظآزHolding hands and walking
at a steady paceظآز
ظآزWhat I long for is something lastingظآز
ظآزDay after day,
simply holding you closeظآز
ظآزThose sweet promises and words of loveظآز
ظآزLike fireworks
lighting up the midnight skyظآز
ظآزTruths, lies,
and words said for appearancesظآز
ظآزLeaving me feeling like
I'm walking on airظآز
ظآزHarsh words, lies,
and words I can't make sense ofظآز
ظآزAll dressed up in hollow splendorظآز
ظآزDreams, nonsense,
and the words hidden in my heartظآز
ظآزBeneath this burning gazeظآز
ظآزThose sweet promises and words of loveظآز
ظآزLike fireworks
lighting up the midnight skyظآز
ظآزDreams, nonsense,
and the words hidden in my heartظآز
I used
this tiny little camera
to have experts guide him remotely.
They treated his son for several months,
and the results were excellent.
Now, they're in Shanghai
for a follow-up.
They'll be back in a few days.
- That's not the same thing.
- How is it not the same thing?
I haven't seen you in a few days.
- How did you get so thin?
- His son, Xin Ba,
was able to get treatment
in such a remote place
guided by international medical experts.
What made that possible?
(Xin You)
(Xin You,)
(this is Qian Fei.)
(I happened
to come across your short video.)
(How are you and Xin Ba doing?)
Hello, Xin You.
You saw the message I sent you, right?
Xin You, you're in Shanghai now?
I have time.
Okay, let's meet tomorrow then.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
I'm so sorry
to have you play
with Xin Ba for so long.
Not at all.
Seeing how well his treatment is going,
I couldn't be happier.
We have Yifei to thank.
After you left,
an expert has been treating
Xin Ba online.
This trip to Shanghai was
to meet the expert in person.
The expert said that Xin Ba's
social and language skills
have already recovered.
He's about the same
as other kids his age.
That's great.
In that case, he'll be able to
make more friends in the future.
I remember one time,
he had a falling out with Ji.
Yes.
And there's even better news.
Yifei's company, Fulaxida,
chose our county as its first choice
to set up an experimental farm.
Our entire county's economy
has been boosted.
The next time you visit,
you won't have to worry
about your car breaking down.
On the remote mountain roads,
delivery trucks are coming
and going every day.
Fulaxida is Li Yifei's company?
It's his side job.
Anyway,
he must be a major shareholder
in Fulaxida.
Look.
This was before we left.
Yifei brought his new technology advisor
to our place.
He said he wants
to create a livestreaming app
for the cows and sheep.
It's pretty interesting.
I heard Yifei's company
and Mr. Lu's company
are collaborating on technology.
This way, future consumers
can log directly into the app
to check on the farm products
they've pre-ordered online.
From
sprouting, birth, and growth,
all the way to the dinner table.
Isn't that great?
He has such a great mind for business.
My gosh, in the time I wasn't aware,
he's done so much.
In the same amount of time,
I worked so hard
just to get from one to ten.
He's already gone from ten to fifty.
If you put it that way,
you can be proud too.
In the same amount of time,
you improved tenfold.
He only improved fivefold.
On that note,
Xin Ba went from zero to one.
That little bit of progress from him
already feels like a huge miracle to me.
Ms. Fei.
Xin Ba.
I'm happy.
Happy, huh?
Say goodbye to Ms. Fei.
We have to go back now.
You're leaving now?
He has to get back to school.
We booked a flight for tonight.
We also hope that you
can come visit us when you have time.
I will.
Then I'll see you out.
Okay.
(Anti-Fraud Center Alert: When you
receive a message via video or iMessage)
(or other instant messaging tools
from someone claiming to be a boss)
(or a friend who's changed their number,
please be vigilant.)
(It's been so many days
and he still hasn't contacted me.)
(Pretentious Li)
(Lu Ze: Another fulfilling day)
It feels like everyone
is around you,
except for me.
It's like you've shut me out.
Hello.
Honey.
So handsome for a blockhead.
You're the blockhead. I ran to
the greenhouse to adjust some equipment.
So, you missed me?
I missed you to death.
Let me tell you some gossip.
What is it?
Li Yifei
came all the way here and has been
thinking about Qian Fei day and night.
He doesn't even realize it himself.
So that's how it is.
I'm about to see Fei.
Do you think I should tell her?
No.
Whatever you do,
don't get involved in this.
Just let the two of them
figure it out naturally.
If an outsider gets involved,
it'll put a lot of pressure on them.
All right, then.
Listen to me, you can't go wrong.
Okay, I'm hanging up now.
So, I had to put down
my phone every day.
I cooked by myself.
I looked at job postings by myself.
I did the housework by myself.
Every day, I'd say good night
to the walls.
And then you felt lonely.
So you asked me out.
Actually...
You two are really something else.
There's you...
He...
You and me...
Can you just finish
your sentence already?
Don't you feel like your current state
isn't being in love, but rather like you've
just been through another breakup?
Why do you say that?
Because I'm sensing a different kind of
emotion and vibe from you.
What are you, a dog?
I just feel so embarrassed.
I thought
that kiss with him was just a dream.
Now, to avoid me,
he's using a business trip
as an excuse to run far away.
This situation is so awkward.
How do I break the ice?
Fei.
Seriously.
I'm sure you like him.
I've never thought about it.
Never thought about it?
What about now?
Let me think.
I don't think I'd call it "like."
It's just that
it's pretty boring when he's not home.
Maybe I'm just used to cooking for him.
How about this?
Let me help you sort out your thoughts.
Let's not talk about
whether you like him or not for now.
First, you have to admit
that he's probably not one of us.
Look at what he eats,
wears, and does for fun.
He's not in the same league as you.
So, what league is he in,
and what league am I in?
You?
Do you even need to ask?
You're in the grassroots league.
But him?
He's in the rich and handsome league.
He has so many ways of making money.
Lu Ze told me
that Li Yifei invested in Fulaxida.
He has a lot of shares.
He sold his house.
What a big move.
He invested tens of millions.
I heard
that his dad bought him that house.
Later, the house appreciated in value,
so he sold it
and then made that investment.
And now, he's so broke
he has to be my housemate.
Let's not talk about him.
Let's talk about your Lu Ze.
He suddenly switched careers
to go into agriculture.
How could you bring yourself
to support him?
Qian Fei,
can you please focus?
Where has your attention
wandered off to now?
I'm talking to you about Li Yifei.
Why are you bringing up
Lu Ze and agriculture?
Haven't you noticed a habit of yours?
Whenever we talk
about something you truly care about,
you change the subject.
I don't know what's going on
with you two.
Anyway, I think
you should just take it
one step at a time.
Leave everything to time.
Wait and see what happens.
I'll listen to you.
Wait and see,
and let nature take its course.
Thanks.
By the way, our class president
called me and said
our five-year class reunion
is on Saturday.
Our academic advisor is going too.
He was asking if everyone is free.
No problem, I'll definitely be there.
But I think he must have asked
Wang Ruohai too.
If he goes, will you be...
Will I be what? Of course not.
I'm already working with him
at Shanlifang for so long.
Have you forgotten?
That's good.
Anyway, I'll be out of town that day.
So I won't make a special trip back.
Say hi to everyone for me.
You're not going?
Then...
If you don't go,
I'll be all alone.
I'll have to face Wang Ruohai by myself.
Why do you have to face him?
Let me tell you.
If he tries to get close to you,
it's an easy fix.
Just give him a couple of slaps
and be done with it.
So it's happily decided.
This project of yours is a great one.
The young people in the village
have all left for work.
In our village alone,
there are
many lands lying idle.
If you can take them
and use them for experimental fields
and development
to help the farmers
increase their income,
that would be a truly virtuous deed.
Village Chief, don't worry.
Our original intention for this project
is to increase the overall income
of the farmers.
I believe that.
How is it?
It's Mr. Sang.
Look, the land there
and the land over there,
they're all very fertile,
just need a bit more water.
Yes.
This is all good soil.
Yifei, I have to press you on this.
The farmers here
are all waiting eagerly.
You're talking
about the financing, right?
Yes.
Didn't you say a few days ago that you were
going to start further financing?
Now you're...
Ma Li.
I still think it's too early
to seek financing now.
No, Yifei.
What do you mean?
You keep going back and forth.
One minute you say you'll get financing,
the next you say you won't.
What's gotten into you?
The person you met before
was Mr. Sang, right?
Yes.
Was there anyone else?
There was also Mr. Liao Jinshan.
Li Yifei, if you have something to say,
just say it.
Why do I feel like
you're interrogating me?
Don't see him anymore.
You can't tell good from bad.
You're going too far by saying that.
Wasn't Mr. Sang introduced
through your connections?
If you reject him now,
it's the same as rejecting yourself.
I admit I misjudged him this time.
But this time, I'm very sure
that Mr. Sang had an ulterior motive
from the very beginning
in approaching Fulaxida.
I don't know why you're saying this.
Maybe you have
your own reasons and judgment.
But what I want to say is,
no matter what you've heard,
when the farmers
were causing trouble a few days ago,
if it weren't for Mr. Sang,
your silver tongue alone might not
have been enough to handle it.
I know you're referring to the fact
that Mr. Sang bribed those farmers.
That's why they agreed
to cooperate with our project, right?
Yes. Since you already know, then you...
Ma Li,
then do you know
that the farmers' protest
was arranged by Mr. Sang
from the very beginning?
Mr. Liao,
why didn't you give me
a heads-up before coming?
Let's talk in the car.
I was just about to go to a meeting.
(Investigation file on Weibo account,
Diansansan)
Mr. Sang, you are a brilliant actor.
You played a good game.
(Investigation file on Weibo account,
Diansansan)
Mr. Liao,
this is the information
of Weibo's Diansansan we found.
Mr. Liao, you truly are a veteran
of the business world.
So quick.
What do you mean?
Hello?
I'll be at the airport in an hour.
Help me identify all information relating
to shareholders being replaced
during the course of projects
undertaken by Zhizhong
over the past ten years,
compile it, and send it to me.
No problem. Piece of cake.
I'll call you when I land.
(Zhizhong Project Team: Summary
on Mid-project Shareholder Removal)
(Qian Fei)
(Dear passenger, your flight CY3357
is expected to depart in 90 minutes.)
(Please arrange
your schedule accordingly)
(to avoid missing your flight.
We wish you a pleasant journey.)
Class President.
Qian Fei?
You're Qian Fei?
Oh my god.
Did you get plastic surgery?
How did you get so beautiful?
What do you mean, plastic surgery?
Even if I wanted to,
I don't have the money.
Stop staring at me.
Even if I did get work done, you wouldn't
be able to tell just by looking.
At this reunion today, a lot of people
have really impressed me.
Everyone has their own achievements.
Especially that Wang Ruohai.
But after seeing you,
I can predict that you will definitely
be the most surprising person
from our class tonight.
Bar none.
Don't just stand there. Let's go.
I've been waiting for you.
Let's go.
Wait a second before you go in. Wait.
Guys.
Guys,
open your eyes and see who's here!
Come on in!
Hello, everyone.
Isn't that Qian Fei?
Yes, Qian Fei.
Hello, sir.
Sit.
Qian Fei, come on, have a seat.
How is everyone?
Let's eat. Come on, let's eat.
Come, let's eat.
Come on, eat up.
Eat up before it gets cold.
Well, my dear students,
every year,
when I get to see all of you kids,
it makes me so very happy.
Our class
produced one couple, you two.
As your teacher, I hope you two
will last forever.
Mr. Zhang, you're a bit out of the loop.
Those two...
Mr. Zhang is absolutely right.
Thinking back now,
back when we were in school,
everything was so wonderful.
The crushes we had back then
were so pure.
Just by looking at the person you loved,
without doing anything at all,
you could smile like an idiot all day.
Hey, Ruohai,
are you trying to be a poet?
Seriously.
Wonderful.
That reminds me of back in the day,
also at our university,
when I met my wife.
She was wearing a red dress,
standing by a tree.
(Wang Ruohai is so weird today.)
The feeling I got back then was,
"How could this be winter?"
"Spring has arrived."
Spring has arrived.
My... My biggest regret
from my college days
is not having a passionate romance.
To make up for this regret,
(Yao Jingjing: Did he do anything?)
I've decided to marry a classmate.
(No. But it seems like he regrets it
and wants to get back together.)
Mei.
What's going on?
We're going to relive our youth.
They're getting married?
You two kept it from us, huh?
So secretive.
You're really good at keeping secrets.
We'd like to propose a toast
to everyone.
Come on.
Congratulations.
To our friendship. Cheers!
Cheers!
Come on.
Don't drink too much. Have a seat.
Fei.
Is there really no chance
for you and Wang Ruohai?
From the way Wang Ruohai
was looking at you with such affection,
it seems like he wants to get back together.
Impossible.
Look at Mr. Wang now.
He's out of my league.
But I heard
after he broke up with that rich girl,
he moved on to an even better company.
He's the one treating us
to this meal too.
- Mei.
- It's really been a long time.
Let's toast our teacher.
Mr. Zhang really took good care
of us back then.
I remember you used to
love this dish the most.
Thanks.
I heard you're treating everyone today.
Looking at the scale of this gathering,
it's really different from before.
No.
It's just that when I look back,
back then,
I never treated you to anything nice.
I... I originally wanted
to invite you out alone,
but I had a feeling you wouldn't come.
So, it's thanks to our classmates today
that I get to see you.
You're really overthinking it.
Don't do this again next time.
Come on, everyone.
I'll start a group chat for us.
Everyone, please send
your phone numbers.
Right now, we have WeChat contacts,
but no phone numbers.
If we lose our WeChat accounts,
- we won't be able to contact each other, right?
- Can you get my phone for me?
- I sent a red envelope. Go grab it.
- Thanks.
Whoever gets the biggest one
has to send the next one.
(Wang Ruohai)
(Blocked Contact)
(It must be fate.)
(Even my phone can't stand Wang Ruohai.)
(It automatically blocked him.)
Why did you block me?
Before, too many
unimportant people and things
took up my time.
Now, I just want
to clear everything out.
So you don't plan on staying in touch?
Not even as friends?
I don't even want
to be friends with you.
I asked around.
You're single now.
That's why I went to all this trouble
to organize this gathering today.
I was prepared for the worst.
- I just want to make it up to you.
- Don't even think about it.
Look,
aren't we both doing fine now?
To be honest,
if this were before,
I would've wanted you to feel guilty
for the rest of your life.
But now,
I just want myself
to be completely erased from your world.
Before, when I had nothing,
I thought the partner I needed
was someone who could
understand me, be considerate of me,
and even help me with my career.
But I've only just realized
that none of that matters.
What I need is to support each other
through thick and thin.
Being with someone you love
is more important than anything.
(Should I contact my landlady?)
(Is she asleep or not?)
(It's been so many days.)
(Why hasn't she contacted me?)
(Why is she so stubborn?)
(Is she angry?)
(Or has she not even thought
about me at all?)
I've finished my resume,
but there's nothing I want to apply for.
It hasn't been that long.
It's normal for a job search
to take one or two months.
Don't rush.
I used to be in a hurry
to pay off my mortgage and debts.
Now, I'm in a hurry to find out
if there's a job I'd actually like,
a simple job in the finance industry.
Why don't you look for
that tenant of yours?
He's in the same line of work as you.
And he's got some
unconventional methods.
Maybe he can help you.
Yeah.
I'll ask him.
(Pretentious Li)
Our current equity allocation
is quite reasonable.
I have 34 percent.
You have 33 percent.
Together,
we have an absolute
controlling interest.
That's 67 percent.
What does this mean?
It means we have 100 percent of the right to
amend the company's articles of association,
handle divisions, mergers,
change business scope, and so on.
All these major decisions.
But let's say
we dilute our equity
even by one percent,
then, for example,
(Fulaxida Equity Distribution)
we'd be down to 66 percent,
then we'd only have a simple majority,
which is 51 percent.
From then on,
for any major company decisions,
we'd have to seek shareholder approval.
Got it?
Take some time to digest it.
(Qian Fei: When are you coming back
from your business trip?)
I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to explode.
(Not sure yet.)
Business is like a battlefield.
That's just how it is.
Memorize it. Hurry up and memorize it.
(Pretentious Li: Not sure yet.)
It's my fault. My fault.
I gave a bad idea.
I shouldn't have been so nice to someone
who gave me the cold shoulder.
At this point,
if I still don't realize
he's trying to avoid me,
then I must be truly blind.
Absolute controlling interest
is 67 percent.
What's 51 percent?
Fifty-one percent is...
Don't look over there.
I think I'll just go be a farmer.
I'm tired.
Your stomach flu isn't better yet.
Go get some rest.
I'll take care of this in a bit.
I've been fine for a while.
Didn't I help her with the event
on your birthday?
These notebooks are new too.
Let's take them over.
And these clothes.
And that old computer.
Let's pack it all up for them.
Xin You said
the kids over there
really need this stuff.
Okay.
Let's send this batch
over to them first.
Later, we can rally
our friends, colleagues, and everyone.
We should be able
to gather another batch.
I alone can rally several truckloads.
True. You're the best at this.
Of course.
Anyway, there's strength in numbers.
So, how's the exam preparation going?
I sold
those exam books online.
Why?
You're not taking the exam anymore?
When you quit, I thought
you were focusing on studying.
That's why I didn't ask you.
How could you just decide
not to take it?
See?
I told you she'd react this way.
You knew already?
You guys really don't need to worry.
It's a registration-based system now.
Before, any sponsor representative
could make a million a year.
They'd get tired
of counting their signing bonuses.
It's different now.
Besides the exam, you can also get
a direct recommendation from an investment bank.
You mean,
after you join a new company,
you'll have them recommend you?
That's not impossible.
But you need to think it through.
A job like this isn't easy to find.
You've tried before.
I can still pass along
a research report for you or something.
But I really can't help much
with other companies.
Don't worry.
This time, I'm extremely well-prepared.
The kid's all grown up.
As long as you've thought it through.
I have another part-time job
at the mall.
This is about done.
You guys finish up. I have to go.
Look at your time management skills.
Wait.
What?
If you're leaving, take out the trash.
Remember to eat.
- Okay.
- You have a sensitive stomach.
- I'll ask around for you on my way.
- Okay. Bye.
Bye. Be careful on your way.
I never realized I had so many clothes.
Let me see.
When the time comes,
just take the clothes and shoes
you don't use anymore,
pack them up, and send them to me.
Okay, I'm hanging up.
Dang.
Mrs. Jun.
We meet again.
We must be fated to meet.
How's your stomach now?
Are you feeling better?
With my constitution,
I was fine a long time ago.
By the way,
our performance won first prize.
Did Jun tell you?
He told me.
You know, that day, I was really...
I was really impressed with you.
You were so sick,
but you still pushed so hard.
It was so touching.
I'm part of the team, after all.
I couldn't let my situation
affect you and the other members.
And I certainly couldn't
let the dance competition
that Da Jun worked on for so many months
not get the result it deserved.
That last part is the most important,
isn't it?
Isn't that the part
you care about most too?
This girl.
Well, I'll be going, Mrs. Jun.
When are you coming over to my place?
I'll make you
my shepherd's purse wontons.
They're delicious.
Okay, I'll come try them some other day.
Okay.
Goodbye, Mrs. Jun.
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
(Let's start over, Wang Ruohai.)
Wang Ruohai, what are you trying to do?
I just want you to unblock me.
Looks like it worked.
(I had dinner
with our partners yesterday.)
(I drank a little too much.)
(I didn't hear my phone ring.)
I wanted to use this trip
to completely clear my head.
Look at me.
Right here, right now,
tell me,
what are you feeling?
I want to see her every moment
of every day.
ظآزThere's no need
to know the ending from the startظآز
ظآزLet the melody play through the chords
with the windظآز
ظآزThere's no need
to keep every promise from the pastظآز
ظآزLeave some surprises
for the unknown in lifeظآز
ظآزThere's no need
to force things between two peopleظآز
ظآزPerhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for meظآز
ظآزThere's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fearظآز
ظآزA hug means more
than countless apologiesظآز
ظآزI'll send you into the wide worldظآز
ظآزTo live with passion
and become who you truly areظآز
ظآزA quiet shoulderظآز
ظآزLike a harbor waiting
for your wandering soulظآز
ظآزI'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler lifeظآز
ظآزThe lights of home warm the nightظآز
ظآزA companionship that lasts foreverظآز
ظآزShining brightly
like the stars and the moon on highظآز
ظآزI'll send you into the wide worldظآز
ظآزTo live with passion
and become who you truly areظآز
ظآزA quiet shoulderظآز
ظآزLike a harbor waiting
for your wandering soulظآز
ظآزI'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler lifeظآز
ظآزThe lights of home warm the nightظآز
ظآزA companionship that lasts foreverظآز
ظآزShining brightly
like the stars and the moon on highظآز