♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon
my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 19=
Eating alone,
I actually feel a bit lonely.
You're home?
I thought you weren't coming back.
I didn't expect you
to sneak back and make all this food.
You should've told me earlier.
I was wandering outside for ages,
and I'm starving.
There was nothing to eat.
Let's eat.
Time to eat.
I forgot the chopsticks.
Delicious.
Your cooking is still the best.
Today's dish tastes amazing.
So good.
Li Yifei,
I suddenly feel
that it's no longer appropriate
for us to keep living together.
Every time
things go wrong for you,
you take it out on me.
Delicious.
You should move out.
I told you,
don't take your
frustrations out on me every time.
Just wait until
I save enough to buy a villa,
then I'll move.
You're annoying me like this, you know?
I'm not moving.
I'm used to living here.
But I'm not used to it.
It's really troubling for me, okay?
Why are you being
so nice to me for no reason?
Clearly, you were the one
who got someone to resolve
that trending search issue
about Wang Ruohai.
Why did you pretend
you didn't know anything?
Why didn't you tell me anything?
Say something. Why didn't you tell me?
Aren't you made of steel?
How can you still cry?
Here, take this.
Alright, stop crying.
I'll pay higher rent, okay?
Even raising the rent won't work.
You still have to move out.
If you raise it, how much would it be?
An extra thousand. One thousand, okay?
Per quarter?
One thousand a month. How's that?
That's more like it.
Money grubber. I knew it.
You're all about money. Eat up.
Room 601, delivery.
I'll get it.
It has your name on it.
(Lawyer's Letter)
What's wrong now?
Shanlifang sent me a lawyer's letter.
(Lawyer's Letter)
You received
a lawyer's letter too, right?
This is targeted directly at us.
I got it.
One of the videos
was uploaded by me.
I was just so angry at the time.
I just wanted everyone to see
what Wang Ruohai had actually done.
I didn't expect this matter
to blow up like this.
I'm sorry, Fei.
It's fine, Yu.
I'll find a way.
What can you do?
It's written right there.
They want the two of us to apologize
and pay compensation within 48 hours.
Otherwise, they will file a lawsuit.
Are we really going
to take him to court?
We'll see when the time comes.
If this were just about me,
I wouldn't be afraid.
But the main thing
is that you've been dragged into this.
You worked so hard to get this job.
If you lose it because of this,
I'll die of guilt.
Let's just wait
and see how things develop.
Alright, don't overthink it.
Go get some rest.
Come on in.
You don't need to worry
about that lawyer's letter.
It's just a bluff
to scare you.
You don't need to comfort me.
I'm fine. Go to sleep.
Ms. Liao didn't come
to the office today.
I have an urgent matter today,
and I'd like to speak
with Ms. Liao in person.
Everyone who wants to see her here
says it's an urgent matter.
I suggest you
make an appointment for next week.
Hello, Ms. Liao.
What's the matter?
I never got a chance
to see you at the office,
so I had to wait for you here.
I'm sorry.
I came to tell you
that I have received the lawyer's letter
sent by Shanlifang Hotel Group.
Go on.
I wanted to sincerely apologize to you.
I didn't expect this incident
to cause such serious consequences,
affecting your reputation
and the hotel's.
I am sorry.
Why didn't you apologize before?
Is a lawyer's letter that effective?
What prompted me to apologize
was certainly not that.
Because some of my personal matters
blew out of proportion,
it's no longer just a private matter.
Apart from me,
Dang Yu from Hejing Securities
also received the lawyer's letter.
As a member of a company
that partners with
Shanlifang Hotel Group,
it was really thoughtless of her
to upload the video at the time,
causing such serious consequences.
She is willing to work with me
to clear up all the negative impacts
this incident has had
on Shanlifang Hotel Group.
We only hope
that you can forgive us.
What you just mentioned
is a decision made
by the group's legal department.
So, let's proceed with the follow-up
according to
the legal department's procedures.
Ms. Liao, please wait.
Dang Yu only did this for me.
Qian Fei.
Ms. Fang wants you
to list and organize
your work content,
package it, and then report it.
As for today's meeting,
you don't need to attend for now.
Then...
Give it to me.
Garbage sorting.
Garbage sorting, please support us.
This is kitchen waste.
Throw it here.
Thank you.
No problem.
Come on, garbage sorting,
please support us.
Please support us.
Garbage sorting, please support us.
Ma'am, what do you have in there?
This is traditional
Chinese medicine residue.
Its residue is wet waste.
Please throw it here.
Thank you.
No problem.
It's about time.
I'll stay behind to wait
for the second team's shift change.
You can go back.
Okay.
Alright, we'll go grab food first.
Give it to me.
Thank you.
Garbage sorting...
Why is she starting a livestream now?
Hello.
I'm the person who filmed the video
of the cheater
at Shanlifang Hotel Group.
The reason I'm livestreaming
is to apologize
to the people in the video.
This video
was filmed and uploaded by me
without the consent
of the involved parties.
The captions in the video
were also made up by me
and have nothing
to do with anyone else.
I feel very uneasy about affecting
the daily lives of the involved parties.
The captions and titles in the video
did contain untruths
that damaged their reputations.
I will take full responsibility.
Furthermore,
the cheating allegation
was just something
I imagined without investigating.
At that time,
he had indeed already
broken up with his ex-girlfriend.
(Are you okay?)
I misunderstood the cheating part,
so please stop doxxing them,
and please don't cyberbully them.
This is all my fault.
If you must attack someone,
just attack me.
(Po Ming)
Hello. The number
you dialed is powered off.
What's wrong, Jun?
I have an emergency.
I won't be having dinner with you.
Hello. The number
you dialed is powered off.
No.
What nonsense are you all talking?
Aren't I just apologizing?
Right, I keep changing my mind.
When I posted a video,
you all heckled me.
Now that I'm apologizing,
you're still heckling me.
Are you all that free?
You're even doxxing me?
Come on, go ahead and doxx me.
Who's afraid of whom?
You'd better come find me.
You're all crazy.
(Don't show your face or identity
on stream. No doxxing yet.)
(Why admit it? Get offline fast.
Don't argue with them.)
(Don't expose your real identity.
I'll handle everything else for you.)
(Don't get involved.)
Alright, I'll stop streaming.
Po Ming's actions
must be a choice made
after careful consideration.
As bystanders,
we don't know the full story,
so we shouldn't make casual comments.
If we really want to know
the truth of the matter,
we should quietly listen
to what Po Ming has to say.
Right?
To tell you the truth,
I actually know Po Ming in real life.
Just a few days ago,
she was a community volunteer,
helping us teach residents
about waste sorting.
What does Jun mean by that?
- Yes.
- Is he going to reveal his identity?
I am a public servant,
- but I am also a fan of Po Ming.
- This girl is annoying.
For her sake, Jun
doesn't even care
about his identity and job.
It doesn't seem that serious, right?
As long as Jun isn't lying
or spreading rumors, it's fine.
Not lying and not spreading rumors?
And you think that's fine?
No,
the people online these days
are resourceful.
If they happen to dig up his name
and his job position,
he will be affected in the future.
You have a point.
Yes, I can't do anything to you all.
I just feel
that everyone should
have a moral compass
and a line that they won't cross.
In the face of right and wrong,
we must learn
to exercise self-restraint,
and at crucial moments,
we must take the initiative.
Who is this?
How do they have
the same birthday as me?
(Jun, have you lost your mind?
Showing off for Dang Yu?)
(What if your job gets affected
because of this?)
But I can't just watch
my friend get bullied.
When I see someone
fabricating lies out of thin air,
I can't just do nothing
and hide in the back.
I'm not that kind of person.
Don't worry, I know what I'm doing.
I know how to handle it.
(Listen to me
and turn off the livestream.)
(Block BlueBearBaby0122?)
(Yes)
(Mute BlueBearBaby0122)
He blocked me?
Try again.
He really blocked you.
Look at our son...
Alright.
No, look at this.
Our son has only been
in contact with her for a few days,
and he's already turned into this.
We cannot let them be together.
We can't let him see that girl anymore.
Alright, calm down. Don't be angry.
He doesn't even know you're angry.
You're only hurting your own health.
Don't be angry.
Didn't he say he wasn't coming back?
- Fine, since that...
- What are you going to do?
I'll go to his office to find him.
Honey, please don't act on impulse.
Calm down.
Let's not be impulsive.
I'm going to find him.
Honey, impulse is the devil.
Then I am the devil.
Everyone,
I was just speaking
to my friend just now.
Anyway, I still want
to appeal to everyone here
to speak with caution.
Please be mindful.
No matter who is
in the wrong in this incident,
we should all look at it
kindly and rationally, right?
Look, Jun is live-streaming.
He's been streaming all day
without moving an inch.
Look.
If we really want to know the truth,
we should
quietly listen
to what Po Ming has to say, right?
You know, to win over Dang Yu,
Jun's really pulling out all the stops.
If it were me,
sitting in a car talking
all day long like that,
I'd go crazy.
Alright, I know you're worried.
Since you've already talked to Ms. Liao,
instead of worrying about
how to handle things in the future,
you might as well
just clock off and go home.
Right?
Don't think about anything. Let's go.
I firmly believe my tough landlady
will always find a way
to get through any obstacle.
We should just
eat and drink like normal.
Let's go home.
I thought your conscience
finally kicked in
and you learned how to comfort someone.
After all that circling around,
you're still just planning
for your own dinner.
I only know that in another 15 minutes,
we're going to get stuck in traffic.
That's the spirit. Let's go.
Cyberbullying is
a very terrifying thing.
There are already so many cases
that prove this point, right?
If later on,
something really happens to Po Ming,
neither you nor I
will be able to escape responsibility.
To be honest, after chatting
with everyone for so long,
I really feel a bit tired.
I'm stepping out
to get some fresh air.
I hope you can also change your mood
and have a drink of water.
Then we'll continue chatting, alright?
(Xin)
Hello?
Yu, come and watch the live stream.
A guy named Grand Chancellor
has been taking on
netizens all day for your sake.
He's made it into
the top 10 trending topics,
and he hasn't stopped yet.
His voice is completely hoarse.
Is he a suitor of yours?
He...
is a friend of mine.
He doesn't look like
just a friend to me.
This guy is pretty good.
Don't let him slip away.
Come on, let's go out for some good food
to build your strength back up.
Forget it.
I still have
several articles left to translate.
I'll just go home and order takeout.
Hello, Dad.
Fei,
have you been off work yet?
Yes, I'm off work.
What's going on with that video online?
It's just
that Wang Ruohai and I
had a little misunderstanding.
A little misunderstanding?
But it's all over the internet now.
Tell me the truth.
Did you two break up,
and now there's a dispute
over the apartment?
No, don't worry.
I've pretty much sorted it out.
It's just that his family
urgently needs money right now.
I'll just transfer
his share of the money
and give it back to him in advance.
Then, it'll be fine.
I still have some savings here.
I'll go to the bank tomorrow
and transfer it to you.
No need.
How could you have any money?
I have investments,
and it's enough.
I'll just give it to him
when the time comes.
I'm still on the subway, Dad.
Let's talk later.
How come I didn't know
you had investments?
Sorry you had to see that.
Ms. Qian,
don't be so distant with me, okay?
I'm starting to doubt
if it's really you.
Come with me.
What are you doing?
Let go.
Stop making a fuss.
If you keep making a fuss,
you'll get filmed again.
Thank you for your concern, everyone.
I've already finished
two bottles of water.
I'll go buy more later.
Young man,
why did you park your car here?
This is my parking space.
My apologies, I'm so sorry.
I'll move it now.
Hurry up and go.
My son's car will come back.
Alright.
I'll move it right away.
Hold on a moment, everyone,
I need to move my car.
Thank you all again
for your care and support.
Right now,
I see that the rational comments online
are steadily increasing.
I feel like losing my voice
like this was worth it.
Thank you all so much
for helping me
maintain peace on the internet.
Well, I'm going to log off now.
Goodbye, everyone. Goodbye.
Where are you taking me?
Promise to make me
stir-fried eggplant tonight,
and I'll tell you.
Can you be serious for a second?
Look at me.
I don't even have the energy
to clean up my own mess,
let alone stir-fry eggplants.
But seriously,
did you never eat eggplant as a kid?
Don't you ever get tired of it?
Haven't you ever watched TV dramas?
They say when an emperor
gets sick of eating delicacies,
and suddenly eats
a roasted sweet potato one day,
guess what happens?
He finds it so delicious,
and he loses his mind over it.
It's the same logic
between the emperor and me.
Can you have some shame?
Look, you can still smile.
Smiling means you're not going to die.
I never thought
saving face was that important.
The most important thing
is your inner spirit.
A person lives on their inner spirit.
If that inner spirit is gone,
the person is gone.
You're right.
I feel like I'm almost gone.
But before you could even fade away,
I stepped in to save you, right?
How can this even be saved?
I don't even know if tomorrow
I'll still be able
to work at my cubicle.
I don't know if Dang Yu
will be dragged into this either.
I know I shouldn't be anxious
and that I have to face whatever comes.
But my brain just won't cooperate.
Do you understand?
The moment
before the unknown is revealed
is always the most anxiety-inducing.
Usually at a time like this,
your master here will make sure
I look my absolute best
to lift that inner spirit.
This is the best way
to resolve anxiety and unease.
Today,
I will pass this
secret manual on to you.
Can you speak properly? I don't get it.
To put it plainly,
whether you stay or leave tomorrow,
live or die,
whether things are resolved smoothly
or it turns into an ugly scene,
as long as you can stand
before them with dignity,
then you've already won half the battle.
Understand?
But look at you right now.
From head to toe,
inside and out, top to bottom,
every single pore is radiating one word.
Miserable.
This won't do, Landlady.
Let me tell you.
So my mission today
is to give you a complete makeover.
Give me a makeover?
How?
Promise to make me
stir-fried eggplant tonight,
and I'll tell you how.
Stir-fry your head.
Come on, fry it.
Fry it.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here.
Thanks.
Streaming in the car all day,
and you didn't even think
to drink water or use the restroom.
Are you silly?
You could also say
I'm dedicated and responsible.
Are you like this with everyone?
Of course not.
Only with you.
So, what now?
Are we just going to stand here?
Where are we going?
Haven't you always wanted to ask me out?
Now is your chance.
And you're making me stand
by the public restroom entrance?
Does this mean
you're agreeing to go on a date with me?
If we don't go now,
I'm changing my mind.
Let's go!
Where are we going?
Are you brave?
I guess so.
First, if you want to look
chic, sharp, and decent,
you have to put some effort
into dressing up, right?
Look at what you're wearing.
What kind of fabric is this?
What's wrong with it?
What is this? An elastic band?
And this.
You dare to wear this out?
The seams are ripping.
I don't have money,
and I don't want to shop here.
Let's just go home.
Why are you so stingy?
You should change
your name to Stingy Qian.
Are you doing justice
to your family name?
You have to be willing
to invest in yourself.
I don't have money to invest.
Fine.
We don't have to buy big brands, right?
Can we at least buy some dupes?
I don't have money for dupes either.
Alright, stop being so stingy.
These are all affordable.
How about this?
Pick two items yourself first.
Take whatever you like.
Don't look at the price tag.
Just see if it catches your eye.
Come on, start.
This one is pretty nice. This green one.
It looks very bright.
Right? It perfectly matches my taste.
Keep going.
This one isn't bad either.
The Peter Pan collar is very cute.
That's enough...
Put it back.
Actually,
I just wanted to test
how bad your taste really is.
Now that the test is over, I feel like
your life might as well just end here.
Does it look bad?
How about this?
Come, let me pick
a couple of outfits for you.
Let me
try to save you.
Just pick a random set.
Let's match this one with that one.
Try it on.
Although it's not that amazing,
still, it's way better than
what you're wearing now,
and much better than
the two you just picked.
This is way too short.
I've never worn
a skirt this short before.
Do you sell safety shorts here?
Get her a pair.
Yes. Just a moment.
Are you crazy to buy safety shorts here?
They're 28 yuan online
with free delivery.
Cut the crap.
Go change.
This is so weird.
I'm going to take it off, okay?
No.
Ms. Qian, come out
and let me see it first,
alright?
♪My heart is pounding loud♪
♪Matching my breathing♪
♪Tuning into
the frequency of missing you♪
♪Love you so much♪
♪You are the only one in the world♪
♪Living in my heart♪
♪The sweetness of ice cream,
mixed with the saltiness of tears♪
See? I told you it's weird.
It doesn't suit me at all.
It's not my style.
Look, it doesn't even look like me.
Li Yifei!
♪You are my youthful joy,
and the youth I love is you♪
Wow, I didn't expect you
to have such a great figure.
Your waist is slender,
and your legs are quite long.
You can't say anything nice?
Look at you.
Even the way
you scold people sounds chic now.
Pleasant to hear.
Let me see.
We just need a pair of high heels,
and we'll be all set.
Let's go pay.
Are we really buying it?
Um, how much is it?
That will be 3,000 in total.
Cash or card?
(Lujiazui Dongyuan Subdistrict Office)
Li.
Mrs. Jun.
We came looking for Jun.
Jun isn't back yet.
Jun hasn't come back...
Mrs. Jun,
Jun is off this afternoon.
He didn't come to work.
Do you know where he went?
He called me this afternoon
to ask what time
the haunted house closes tonight.
The haunted house.
The haunted house. Quick, let's go.
Okay, I see. Thank you.
Li, thank you.
(Lujiazui Dongyuan Subdistrict Office)
Get some rest, Li.
Okay.
These heels make me
unable to walk properly.
Don't be ungrateful.
I've never gone shopping
with a woman before.
I haven't even complained about
being tired, yet you want to go home.
I just saw you were about to collapse
and wanted to help you out.
Let me tell you,
you are wearing this outfit
to work tomorrow
to dazzle everyone.
So I should thank you then
for giving me the most
precious moment of my life.
Of course.
From now on,
don't blindly
buy clothes on your own, okay?
Even if you want to buy something,
let me check it first.
I mean, when you wear those
ragged sacks in front of me all day,
I'm the one who suffers the most.
It's practically blinding me, okay?
Watch your mouth, okay?
You've never worn high heels before?
You don't even know how to walk.
Of course I have.
But since I take the subway every day,
I can't exactly walk around on stilts.
So you just lack practice, you know?
You need to wear them,
practice, and walk more.
Well, don't rush home just yet.
I'm taking you somewhere.
Where are we going now?
I don't want to spend money anymore.
Hey, Steven.
Are you free?
I'm bringing a friend over
to your place for a makeover.
Okay, see you in a bit.
Hey, what are you doing now?
I'm going to sell you for candy.
It'll be too sweet for you.
Too sweet for me?
You're not even worth that much.
How many pieces of candy could you buy?
(Real-Life Game Experience Center)
Real-Life Game
Experience Center Entrance...
"Demon Realm." Look.
What place is this?
How do you open this door?
Is anyone there?
This...
What kind of place is this?
Welcome.
Miss, I'd like to ask you something.
Have you seen a man and a woman?
The man is tall and handsome.
Did you see them?
Are there any specific features?
The guy looks quite a bit like her.
He has very fair skin.
And he's very tall.
Do those count as features?
Not really.
My boyfriend is also very fair and tall.
Ma'am, don't worry just yet.
Why don't you sit over there
and wait a bit?
Try calling him again.
I've been calling. I keep calling him.
Look.
Isn't that Jun?
What is he doing here?
Isn't this exactly why he came?
Where do we enter?
Save me! Save me, Dang Yu!
Dang Yu, save me! Save me!
Save me!
Don't come over!
My mistake!
Help!
He's a coward.
This makeup is done so well. Look at it.
Dang Yu, I'm going to cry.
Let's go.
We don't watch anymore. Let's go.
Excuse me. Let's go.
Let's go.
Alright, it's finally over.
No, I'm still scared.
Why are you such a coward?
Aren't you scared? It's terrifying.
I don't even dare
to watch horror movies.
Is it scary?
Let's go eat, then.
Eat what? I have no appetite right now.
What do you want to eat? Hotpot?
It looks like it's right here.
It was right here just now.
Aren't their things still here?
What do you mean? Is this the spot
where the monitor shows
the two of them are located?
Yeah, they were still here just now.
Isn't this where we saw them?
Yeah.
Did you see that door just now?
It was closed.
Did they go out this way?
It seems so.
How do we open this door?
There must be some kind of mechanism.
What are you guys doing?
Don't pull this on us!
Don't scare us.
Don't do this.
Let me tell you...
Stop, okay?
We're getting old. If something happens,
will you take the blame?
Can you take responsibility?
We're here to look for someone.
I have a weak heart, and so does he.
If anything happens to us elderly folks,
will you take responsibility?
Open the door. Hurry up.
Open the door quickly.
We're here to look for someone.
The presence.
The elegance.
Is that really necessary?
I just changed my clothes
and got my hair done.
What do you know?
You look like a completely
new person right now,
you know that?
Well, the cost of being
a new person is way too high.
The outfit I bought
is enough to cover
another month of my mortgage.
And how much
did this hair cost?
Don't worry about that.
It's all covered by these skewers.
Listen here.
If it weren't for me,
you couldn't get it done
even with money.
Do you think he's that easy to book?
Keep bragging.
All you know is how to eat.
If you eat like a pig,
aren't you afraid
you won't be handsome anymore?
It's fine. I'll go for a run
downstairs later.
Come, let me propose a toast to you.
What's the occasion?
I know
everything you did for me today
wasn't for some makeover.
You just didn't want me to stay trapped
in my sadness for too long, right?
True.
I had a really great time today.
Thank you, China's best tenant.
You're welcome, China's best landlady.
Dad, I'm the manager of the company now.
Why do you still have
to interfere in such a small matter?
You sent a lawyer's letter
to Hejing Securities without my consent.
This is an interference
with my authority.
If this keeps up,
I won't be able to manage it.
Hanging up now.
Are you angry?
So frustrating.
After this, the people in the group
will probably think I'm so petty.
Am I the kind of person
who cares about gossip?
Your dad just cares about you too much.
How come you're on
my dad's side this time?
He is the chairman of our group.
If you make him
withdraw the lawyer's letter now,
won't that be like undermining
the chairman's authority?
Also,
I think it's a bit inappropriate
for Qian Fei to stay
in the group all the time.
After all,
you don't really know her character.
Whether Qian Fei exists or not
doesn't matter to me at all.
But what matters most
is Hejing Securities helping
Shanlifang Hotel Group
achieve a successful listing.
I can tolerate everything else.
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
Excuse me, sorry to bother you.
My name is Qiu Shi.
Could I get to know you?
- No.
- Sure.
What are you doing?
Ruining love leads to heck.
Don't you know that?
(As the sponsor, you know Shanlifang's
strengths and dirty secrets.)
(I need evidence of loopholes
in room management.)
(In the hotel business, guest rooms
touch consumers' nerves the most.)
(Wait for my updates.)
♪There's no need
to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords
with the wind♪
♪There's no need
to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises
for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need
to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more
than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪