♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon
my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 26=
What did you just say?
Strike from another dimension?
The line before that.
Outsiders can disrupt the insiders.
Exactly.
It just occurred to me
that Fulaxida needs
a different hiring strategy.
What do you mean?
Find allies.
I just thought of someone.
Investment from allies?
I'm home.
Dinner will be ready in a minute, babe.
I wrapped up the Shanlifang bid today.
I'm exhausted.
Really?
You're amazing, babe!
You worked so hard.
I want a reward.
A reward?
Look.
- All... Hey!
- Today just feels...
You haven't
washed your hands, little glutton.
You can eat in a bit.
It'll be ready soon.
This feels so nice.
You used to be so busy.
You never had time to cook for me.
I'm really enjoying this moment.
I wish it could always be like this.
Sure.
From now on,
I'll be a househusband.
I'll happily live off you
and cook for you every day.
Really?
Really.
Okay, then I promise
I'll make sure you enjoy
every meal and never go hungry.
You'll be spoiled.
Deal.
I'm hungry.
Just wait a little longer.
It'll be ready soon.
(Little Smarty Visits the Future)
Jingjing.
Fei.
Guess what? Did I get
the Shanlifang charity gala?
Do you even have to ask?
Of course you got it.
Who are you?
The legendary queen of the industry.
Absolutely.
Congratulations then.
The charity gala
is only a few days away, right?
So we all start work tomorrow?
I've already
got everything arranged today.
Okay, I won't forget.
I'll come help in a couple of days, too.
Really?
That's great.
I'm completely worn out today.
I'll let you go now.
Bye.
Okay, get some rest. Bye.
That was your best friend, Yao Jingjing?
I think she's pretty impressive.
So many companies bid
for Shanlifang's charity gala,
and she beat every one of them.
She's really got what it takes.
Obviously.
But how did she end up
being friends with you?
You two aren't even on the same level.
Got nothing better to do?
Babe, dinner...
What?
Want it?
Flight ticket!
No way. Seriously?
You didn't fake this, did you?
How could it be fake?
I checked before,
and there weren't any tickets left.
How did you pull that off?
See?
You're actually pretty capable.
So many things I wish
I could do but can't,
you make them look effortless.
I'm starting to see you in a new light.
Wait. What did you think of me before?
I could list your traits
with my eyes closed.
You're vain, love showing off,
and you've got a sharp tongue.
You're picky, fussy,
and always craving good food.
You're lazy, smug,
and have a terrible temper.
And so much more.
Hello? I'd like to cancel my ticket.
You told me to say it.
Someone as honest as me
couldn't possibly lie.
You listed nine things about me,
and then threw in "and so much more."
Fine.
Since that's how you see me,
there's no need for you
to think better of me.
I'll just live up to everything in those
"and so much more."
Calm down.
Give me one more chance.
Let me explain, okay?
Come on, give her another chance.
Meditating again?
The reason I said you're vain
is that
you're genuinely good-looking.
Look how handsome you are, right?
You've earned the right to be vain.
The reason I said you love showing off
is that
you do it with style.
It actually suits you.
You have a great presence.
As for saying you like to roast people,
it's because you're so quick-witted.
Right?
Some people wish they could
talk like that but can't.
Right?
Sure, you're picky,
but...
You take life seriously.
You never settle for less.
Now that's a good point.
It shows you're a responsible person.
Exactly. That's exactly who I am.
The reason I said you're fussy
is that...
Because...
You...
care about quality of life.
You know what you want
and what you deserve to enjoy.
You really get me.
That's positivity at its best.
Exactly.
As for saying you're a foodie,
I should be happy.
It means you really like my cooking.
- Yeah.
- You think my cooking is good.
- You finally figured it out.
- I'll be more motivated to cook, right?
As for calling you lazy,
it's because you're busy
doing important things.
You can't let housework hold you back.
Right?
If you really became a domestic expert,
you might not
have gotten me that ticket.
Right?
Exactly.
As for saying
you're a little full of yourself,
well...
I just wanted it to rhyme with the rest.
It just sounded better, right?
Just like "fussy."
What about the last one?
You said I have
a bad temper. Explain that.
Well, your temper is...
It's because
when you argued with Gui Lili,
I always felt
you were really harsh with her.
But you've never argued with me.
So I couldn't judge it
from an outsider's point of view
and say what was fair.
Right?
You know,
everything you said was spot on.
Right?
You described me perfectly.
I can't believe all those awful words
ended up sounding so good.
And they really got right to my heart.
Right?
Exactly.
That's a pretty fair description.
I couldn't agree more.
But that last one...
I gave it some serious thought.
I guess I really...
Right?
I'm about at my limit.
I'll show you my bad temper.
You're not going home.
Going home? What for?
Stay here
and spend the Chinese New Year with me.
If I don't teach you a lesson,
you'll never forget this mistake.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Don't cancel it. You can't.
You really can't.
That's not what I meant.
I... I...
I think you're handsome.
I just got carried away.
I'm all tongue-tied.
Don't cancel it.
Great.
You didn't cancel it.
Thank you.
I can finally go home.
Well...
Well, I'm canceling it again.
Give it here.
You... You come here.
You...
Hurry.
Why are you getting shy now?
Why are you so late, bro?
Isn't it better that I came late?
I'm helping you save some money.
Yeah, right.
You're always so cocky.
But when it really mattered,
you were nowhere to be found.
(Monday, Shanhe is here)
Back with another alt again?
I'm not in the mood
to play with you today.
(Currently 200,000 Dragon Coins
short of unlocking)
(this privilege, or complete
a Matchmaker quest)
Happy-Go-Lucky,
you saw the Little New Year
couples event, right?
Want to meet the Matchmaker
and marry me?
That way, we can complete
the couples quest, too.
See you at the Matchmaker's.
I'm doomed.
What's wrong, Jun?
Did your mom give away your gear again?
Dang Yu... Dang Yu is joining
the event with someone else.
She's marrying someone else.
Someone stole your wife?
It's okay. We'll help you win her back.
No.
Let me translate.
The girl Jun's talking about...
It's her game account
that's marrying another account.
Why are you freaking out
over a game account?
Of course I'm freaking out.
The game is my other world.
Getting married here
is just as important
to me as getting married there.
How about this?
Use my account
and marry her a few times.
Make up for it.
Of course not.
I'm going to have
Grand Chancellor propose to Po Ming
in front of all the players.
What do I do now?
Just get divorced and remarry.
It's only a game account.
Get divorced?
What if she gets divorced,
and still won't marry me?
What do I do then?
You haven't even won her over yet.
And you're already
hoping she'll get divorced.
Jun,
you're unbelievable.
Then do this.
Marry someone else yourself.
You can both get back at each other.
No, I can't bear to hurt her.
I'm going to win her back.
With my own hands and my own brains,
I'm going to win Dang Yu back.
You guys keep drinking.
I'm heading home.
Jun!
See?
See that?
This is what happens when you
get too obsessed with games.
He's played himself silly.
Exactly.
(Qian Fei: I finally got a ticket home.
Thanks to my tenant's connections!)
You're unbelievable, Li Yifei.
(Qian Fei)
That's just not fair.
What's wrong?
No matter how close we are,
(You can pay me back one dish at a time...)
you can't treat me like this.
How did I bully you?
I was the one
who went through all that trouble
to get your landlady that ticket.
So why is it always you
who gets the credit in front of her?
Haven't I treated you well?
No. Not this time.
You have to introduce her to me.
I've made up my mind.
I've fallen for a tough girl.
At worst, I'll go all in.
So what if it ends in marriage?
I want to be friends with her.
I want to date her.
I didn't help her get
that ticket for your sake.
Have you lost your mind?
You dare make a move on my woman?
Don't forget.
Back in middle school,
when those girls surrounded you
and pulled your pants down,
who was it that saved you?
Who pulled your pants back up,
fastened your belt,
and zipped up your fly?
You've forgotten already?
I've got photos.
Here, let me help refresh your memory
of the huge favor I did you.
Don't...
No...
Cut it out.
You call that a favor?
That's blackmail.
Do you have any idea
how hard it was to get that ticket?
When it comes to handling Zihao,
you're the best.
But you're always talking big
in front of us.
When are you going
to make it official?
Honestly, you're the biggest coward.
(Shanlifang Hotel Group Charity Gala
Benefiting the Nature Foundation)
You're here, too?
Mr. Jiao.
(Shanlifang Hotel Group Charity Gala
Benefiting the Nature Foundation)
Boss, it's really lively today.
It sure is.
Just look at all the media here.
Shanlifang really spared
no expense this time.
Liao Shiyu is counting on this
to restore her reputation.
If they can calm
public opinion this time,
does that mean Qian Fei
might get her job back?
I'd say that's a given.
Do you know each other well?
She's Qian Fei's friend.
Let me tell you,
Fei and I
could talk about anything at work.
Clothes don't make the man.
Nice taste.
Right?
Absolutely.
You know,
he really does
look like a real estate agent.
Hello, Mr. Liao.
Hello.
Mr. Liao.
Hello, everyone.
Mr. Zhang, it's been a long time.
- Hello, Mr. Liao.
Hello, everyone.
Thank you, everyone. Thank you.
Excuse me.
(Charity Gala Registration)
(Shanlifang Hotel Group Charity Gala
Benefiting the Nature Foundation)
Looks like Fei isn't here yet.
Why would I be looking for him?
Chairman, this time you...
I...
I'm here to catch up with an old friend.
Jinshan.
What a rare guest.
Mr. Li, it's an honor
to have you here today.
How could I miss
your charity gala?
Mr. Li.
A pleasure.
Hello.
And you are?
Sang Shiqi.
Thank you.
Mr. Sang.
I've heard so much about you.
Mr. Li, your Qiansheng Group
went public in the U.S.
in less than two years.
For those of us
from the younger generation,
you're someone we all look up to.
You're too kind, Mr. Sang.
Actually, the overseas market
isn't as great as people think.
But I did hear
you've landed quite a few
promising domestic projects.
One of them is called Fulaxida,
isn't it?
Yes, we do have that project.
But...
it's a very small one.
Very small.
Small though it may be,
I've heard it's in one of the country's
key strategic sectors.
Mr. Li, a toast to you.
Cheers.
Our company represents
French wineries in China.
We can create
a custom wine for your hotel.
Come visit our company sometime.
We've already picked the location.
We're just waiting for your decision.
That's wonderful.
We haven't expanded into Yangling yet.
Today, the Liao family's
future son-in-law
has been following
their daughter around all night.
He's decent-looking enough.
Who knows
if he can really marry into the family.
The walls
are finished with marble
we imported from Italy.
They certainly look magnificent.
Exactly.
I heard the groom
has no family connections.
Just another guy
who's trying to marry up.
Liao really is willing to go all out.
Just look at his bearing.
No matter how you look at him,
he carries himself
like someone from a humble family.
So timid and reserved.
Even if he marries into the family,
he'll spend his whole life
living under his wife's thumb.
That would let us expand
into other cities.
I'm not interested.
Did you see that?
Liao Shiyu is going on stage
in less than half an hour.
You'd better hurry.
There are so many people
sitting around her.
I really don't understand.
What's the point?
Between Hejing and Shanlifang,
which company is worth all this effort?
If it were me,
I'd just sit back and watch them
make fools of themselves.
Stay here for a bit.
I'll go take a look.
Please keep an eye on the result later.
Okay.
Sure.
Let's exchange contact details later.
Okay.
Thanks. I hope you're right.
What are you doing?
Well, you're pretty bold.
Why are you pretending to be a waiter?
Are you here to ruin the event?
You're actually not furious.
Did you already know I was coming?
Let me tell you.
When I saw you bring this outfit home,
and you weren't anxious
after being suspended,
and even had Yao Jingjing
bid for this charity gala,
I guessed what you were planning.
So you planned this long ago.
If you knew, why did you ask?
Either work with me
or get out of my way.
I'm telling you,
you can't solve the problem.
None of your business.
They're looking this way.
And you're still walking
over there. Are you silly?
You smell pretty nice today.
Did I smell bad before?
Listen.
Are they gone?
They're gone. I'm going now.
Why are you drinking here alone?
I just want some peace and quiet.
Qian Fei?
What are you doing here?
Ms. Liao, regarding the public apology
I suggested,
I drafted a speech.
I hope you'll give it some thought.
Qian Fei.
You're quite capable.
You even managed to sneak in like this.
Take off that uniform
and go get something to eat.
The media will all be there tonight.
I won't put you in an awkward position.
Anyway,
please read it first before you decide.
When the first video came out,
Shanlifang chose
to bury its head in the sand,
hoping to muddle through.
Then the second video
came out right after.
This clearly shows
someone planned this in advance.
So no matter how big
a splash this charity gala makes
or how influential it is,
once the third video comes out,
Shanlifang will completely
lose the public's trust.
It will affect the hotel's IPO.
Then how do you think we should respond?
I think you should
sincerely apologize to the public
and carry out reforms
from top to bottom.
The first two videos are already out.
The negative impact Shanlifang
has caused
can no longer be undone.
You can only accept the consequences.
But if you have the courage
to carry out comprehensive reforms,
I believe Shanlifang
can fix every hygiene loophole
in its hotels this time.
So no matter how many more videos
come out in the future,
they will only prove
that those videos were filmed before.
Someone is deliberately smearing you
and spreading rumors.
You can take legal action.
Have you thought about
what an apology means right now?
An apology means consumers
receive the basic respect they deserve.
It also means Shanlifang has
the resolve and attitude
to fix the problem completely.
How many meetings did we have
before deciding on this plan?
If we were going
to apologize from the start,
why prepare this nine million?
Apologizing now
would be the same
as admitting it, wouldn't it?
No. At this point,
if you don't admit it, are you still
going to deny it, Wang Ruohai?
You only need to take one chance.
If it works,
I believe Ms. Liao
will truly see your worth.
I think this is important to you.
It's important
for your relationship, too.
Qian Fei.
Why are you trying to save Shanlifang?
I'm not saving Shanlifang.
I'm saving the IPO project
that Shanlifang entrusted to Hejing.
I'm saving myself.
There are so many reporters
gathered outside.
They're all here for the charity gala.
Now we're changing the whole focus.
Isn't that too risky?
Everything I prepared is in there.
I still hope
you'll give it serious thought.
Something this serious happened,
and you don't have
a single constructive suggestion.
All you're doing
is hiding here drinking.
I'll go out once I sober up.
Today's event
is for my father
to introduce you to some people.
On an occasion this important,
everything you say and do
represents more than just you.
It represents Shanlifang and me, too.
I know you're important.
I know your father is important, too.
Shanlifang is also important.
But I'm not.
My whole family isn't either.
The moment I came here today,
everyone was talking about
who I am to you,
who I am to your father,
and who I am to Shanlifang.
I've lived for over twenty years
before I realized
I can only define myself
through all of you.
Do you resent me that much?
Don't you like the life you have now?
I thought this was everything
you ever wanted.
I thought you'd like it.
I just want to be myself.
Then you have to fight
for that yourself.
How people see you
depends on how you see yourself.
Take today for example.
There are so many people outside.
It wouldn't look good
if we were both gone this long.
Take your time.
I need to get back to work.
Shiyu.
I've thought about this for a long time.
I can't live up to your expectations.
Let's break up.
(Shanlifang Hotel Group Charity Gala
Benefiting the Nature Foundation)
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Liao Shiyu, Vice President
of Shanlifang Hotel Group.
First of all, on behalf
of Shanlifang Hotel Group,
I'd like to welcome everyone
to our charity gala.
As you can all see,
Shanlifang Hotel Group
has always been committed
to providing consumers
with the highest quality service.
We place special emphasis
on the air quality inside our hotels.
So far,
Shanlifang Hotel Group
has adopted
world-class fresh air systems
in hundreds of hotels nationwide.
The temperature
and humidity in the atrium
have reached world-class standards.
Of course, for all of this,
we have the Nature Foundation to thank.
It was you
who provided us
with environmental technology support.
Now, please allow me to introduce
the China Representative
of the Nature Foundation, Ms. Song.
Shanlifang Hotel Group
will donate
9 million yuan
to the Nature Foundation to support
wildlife conservation
in southwestern China.
(Donation Check: 9,000,000 yuan)
Next,
I'd like to play a video
to show everyone
the latest changes
at Shanlifang Hotel Group.
What's going on?
Why is this happening?
What should we do? Should
we turn off the big screen?
Wait a little longer.
Come here.
Quick, get it on camera.
Director.
I'm really betting everything on you.
An apology means consumers
receive the basic respect they deserve.
It also means Shanlifang has
the resolve and attitude
to fix the problem completely.
As everyone can see,
after extensive discussions,
Shanlifang has decided
to take this opportunity
to issue an official statement
on this week's hotel room
hygiene incident.
We have confirmed
after a thorough investigation
that the problems shown
in the videos are all true.
We have decided
to offer our sincerest apology.
We also hope all our customers
will continue to supervise us
and witness
our determination
and the results of our reforms.
But if anyone
tries to use this opportunity
to smear Shanlifang,
I will also take legal action
to protect Shanlifang's lawful rights.
Good.
Now things are really blowing up.
Wasn't this all your doing?
Are you saying Wang Ruohai did it?
I left the flash drive on the table.
Nice work.
Professional.
Let's go, Boss.
Mission accomplished. Why are you
still standing here grinning?
Let's go.
Drive safely.
Put on some music.
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means
more than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder, like a harbor
waiting for your wandering soul♪
What are you doing?
You look
actually kind of adorable.
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
Stop looking at me.
Watch the road.
(Resignation Letter
Applicant: Wang Ruohai)
It's a shame.
You still chose to leave.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
Wait.
I know that a lot of the time,
you compare me to Qian Fei.
Qian Fei is hardworking and thoughtful.
But I'm not.
I grew up
as a spoiled young lady.
When I'm thirsty,
you have to bring me water.
When I'm hungry, you have to
eat late-night snacks with me.
During holidays, I never, like Qian Fei,
thought about helping you
buy gifts for your parents
or visit them.
And...
I always embarrass you
in front of your coworkers.
I force you to do things you don't like.
For all of this,
I should apologize to you.
Everything I did for you
was of my own free will.
It's just that lately,
I've been thinking
I did far too little
for Qian Fei.
Every time I think about it,
I feel terrible.
Recently, my mom got sick.
While staying with her,
I've also been thinking.
What I truly need
is a relationship
where we stand by each other.
So to you,
am I just vanity and a future prospect?
Anyway,
I'm sorry.
Goodbye.
Isn't this my laptop?
You helped me
play that video last night?
Have you figured out
how to thank me?
When did you start
knowing my exact plan?
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
When did you start
knowing my exact plan?
And when did you
steal my laptop
and do all this behind my back?
Were you planning to wait
until I wasn't home
and bring your influencer girlfriend
here to spend the Chinese New Year?
You mean Jin?
She's not my girlfriend at all.
I don't have a girlfriend.
You're still denying it?
Still making excuses?
Hello?
Fei?
I'm on the pedestrian street
near your place.
My stomach suddenly hurts really badly.
Can you come help me?
I...
♪There's no need
to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords
with the wind♪
♪There's no need
to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises
for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need
to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more
than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪