♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon
my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes,
even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten
on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts,
my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken
in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows
my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you?
That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out,
"I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women"
by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 18=
Mr. Lu,
is the boss of Qiansheng Group reliable?
According to the contact,
this boss is open-minded,
and it's an established large factory.
Let's just treat it as our last shot.
Come, have some tea.
Thank you.
Well,
do you mind me asking roughly what time
Chairman Li will be back?
Our appointment was at 4 PM,
and it's almost 5 PM now.
You didn't pick
a very good time to come.
Our Master Li goes to
the suburbs to walk his dog
every Wednesday afternoon.
If he's having a great time,
he might be a bit late.
Jiang, what are you talking about?
Don't make excuses.
I'm so sorry.
Please sit.
Was I the one having a great time,
or was it the dog having a great time?
I'm exhausted from chasing after it.
Come here.
Drink some tea.
Mr. Li, this is our...
No need to look at this.
I've already read it.
Don't just look at how much I love
having fun.
But...
I never neglect proper business.
What are you doing?
Do you want some tea?
Can you sit still for a moment?
Mr. Li, regarding our project, you...
I won't invest.
Here is the thing.
With this project of yours...
The return on investment,
the project timeline,
including the contingency plans...
I can't see any of those things here.
You can't control
the direction or the timeline,
and you can't guarantee
a return on investment.
You've basically
just painted a rosy picture.
Worse, this picture
belongs to someone else,
yet I'm the one who has to pay for it.
Now, tell me,
who in this world
would be foolish enough to do that?
But don't be too discouraged.
You're young.
Struggling and getting more experience
isn't a bad thing.
I'll say it again.
As long as the project is good,
my door is always open.
Who is it?
You didn't reply to my texts
or answer my calls.
Seriously, what are you trying to do?
What are you trying to do?
Why are you being so aggressive?
What's wrong?
Are you cutting ties with me?
What are you talking about?
You're really living large, huh?
You left behind
such a big suitcase of cash.
Why did I not know
that you were rich enough
to rival a nation?
Wang Ruohai wouldn't accept it.
What do you mean?
My business with him
is none of your concern.
Look,
I just want some personal space.
Can't I just be by myself for a while?
Aren't you blaming me
for ruining Lu Ze's company?
Will staying by yourself
help you calm down?
Are you out of your mind?
Re-evaluating Shanlifang's assets
was your responsibility.
But Lu Ze's company was poorly managed,
and their intangible assets
were overvalued.
That would have blown up anyway,
with or without you.
Why would I blame you?
There's no reason to.
Don't flatter yourself.
Blame me for not telling you sooner.
Exactly.
Why couldn't you
have just told me sooner?
Why are you eating
instant noodles again?
Didn't your Lu Ze
forbid you from eating this?
Don't talk nonsense.
Since when is Lu Ze mine?
It has nothing to do with him.
What's wrong?
Whenever you bring this up,
I get furious.
He can't handle
his own responsibilities,
so he pushes them all onto you.
No, he didn't do that.
Seriously,
I wasted three years being with him.
When something this big happened,
he didn't even think
to tell me right away.
He even told me
that he would rather choose his career
than choose our future.
So, why should I keep staying with him?
What's the point?
You should have told me earlier.
Then I could have
known his choice sooner
and broken up with him sooner
instead of dragging it out until now.
You broke up with him?
Yeah.
Put on your clothes and come with me.
Let's go find Lu Ze.
What for? I'm not going.
There's no way I'm going.
Breaking up with him at a time like this
is just adding fuel
to the fire, you know?
It's not that Lu Ze hasn't tried.
He managed to find a new buyer
to take over Xinxin Vision,
but Shanlifang
went back on their word
just to ensure a smooth IPO.
They completely cut off his path.
I know.
I never said he didn't try.
It's just that...
He is too calm.
He has everything thought out,
and he didn't choose me.
He wants to invest his entire fortune
into his Xinxin Vision.
That is his true pride and joy.
What am I to him?
No matter what,
at a time like this,
he needs your comfort the most.
I don't know how to comfort him.
I'm hurting too, you know.
Do you think only the person
who gets dumped hurts?
Losing me
won't break his heart nearly as much
as losing Xinxin Vision.
Let me tell you, Fei,
Lu Ze is just
an entrepreneurship fanatic.
He can give up
everything for his career.
What about me?
Sure,
I can stake everything on a poor guy.
No problem.
But I would never dare
to give my entire life to someone
who values his career above all else.
But do you still love him?
I do.
But in his heart,
the company is the most important thing.
Yao Jingjing,
even though
the ceremony isn't fully ready,
my heart is ready.
Will you marry me?
Yes, I will.
(Temperature, Humidity, Light, Growth)
What everyone sees right now
is the third phase
of the core experimental scene
currently being conducted by Fulaxida.
Within existing urban buildings,
with minimal modifications,
we achieve large-scale
organic cultivation
of indoor agricultural products.
When such cultivation centers
are distributed across commercial
districts throughout the city,
coupled with an efficient
logistics distribution system,
it will bring efficient,
low-cost,
and high-quality
changes to people's lives.
Today's inspection
really blew me away.
It's excellent.
When I get back,
I will give Mr. Sang
a detailed briefing.
Thank you.
But before I leave,
I'd like to ask you a question.
Please go ahead.
Why are young people like you
interested in agriculture?
Especially someone like you, Mr. Li,
a rising star in finance
and the star of investment banking.
I'm very curious.
Alright, let me answer that for you.
First of all, I believe
from the perspective of macro-history,
the essence of agriculture
has never been just about farming.
It represents human participation
in the ultimate
transformation of Earth and life.
Think about it.
From slash-and-burn farming
to intensive cultivation,
and now to digital new agriculture,
what are our country
and the entire world
facing right now?
We are facing major changes
unseen in a century.
As for agriculture,
the substance of these changes
is technology driven
by fully developed digitalization
and the advancement
of modern life sciences.
Speaking of agriculture,
it's not exactly a trendy project.
Many people lose interest
the moment they hear
it's a rural development project.
But technology
has always driven
agricultural development.
Our digital agriculture
utilizes wired sensors
to automatically collect data
on various indicators
and uploads it to an IoT platform.
Then, through phones or computers,
we can remotely monitor
the agricultural environment,
providing data support
for field management.
With the help of capital investment,
we will have
the potential to turn
agriculture into data streaming
so that farming is no longer
just about facing the dirt
and breaking your back.
Instead, it becomes
a part of commercial exchange
and social communication,
achieving rural revitalization
and shared prosperity.
So, as young people,
we are deeply honored
to be able to take part
in this innovative path
of empowering agriculture
and the food industry with technology.
In the future,
we will use
control over
agricultural planting processes,
as well as research in the fields
of food science and life sciences,
to ensure Fulaxida
still enjoys high-speed
and high-quality development
10 or 20 years from now.
I see this
as the path an ambitious business hero
should invest in.
More importantly, it's a glorious path
of growing together with
our society and our country.
In this era where
technology and capital dominate,
this is exactly why
we choose to focus on new agriculture.
To a successful partnership.
(Fulaxida Co., Ltd.)
Mr. Liao, your bunker shot is amazing.
Your golfing skills are top-notch.
Impressive.
You flatter me, Mr. Sang.
I'm just relying on my old experience.
When it comes
to keeping up with the times,
I still have a lot to learn from you.
Mr. Liao, I can tell
there's more to your words
than meets the eye.
I heard you invested
in a new project recently.
It's just a small agricultural project.
It's run by a few young people.
They didn't have much money,
so they came to me.
It's just a minor project, really.
Is it Ma Li's Fulaxida?
Mr. Liao,
you even know about that?
I just heard someone mention it.
That's all.
What are you doing?
Brooding?
Why did you ask me to come to the mall?
Isn't your birthday coming up?
I ordered a gift for you,
so I came to pick it up today.
Thanks.
Nothing beats a good bro.
Why do you look
so gloomy receiving a gift?
What's wrong?
Haven't you moped around enough?
You just got rejected by a girl.
Is it that serious?
Cheer up.
Come on, cheer up.
It's not that easy to cheer up.
This time, I really...
I feel like
I've lost my purpose in life.
Didn't you always
think highly of yourself?
How come you don't even know
what you're worth now?
Look,
actually, I've always felt
the life my mom
planned for me was great.
Good schools, good teachers,
and a good job
lined up right after graduation.
And then,
I've had smooth sailing all these years,
without any pressure at all.
But all of that,
when it came to Dang Yu,
it became nothing.
It became worthless.
She knocked me flat with a single slap.
I'm even questioning my life now.
You're really heartbroken.
Jun, let me tell you the truth.
No need.
Dang Yu already told me
all the harsh truths.
My job,
arranged by my parents.
My home,
living with my parents.
My money,
controlled by my parents.
For a man like me,
how could an independent girl like her
ever like me?
Right.
Since you've found
the root of the problem,
you should work hard
to change it, right?
Easy to say.
I've lived like this for over 20 years.
How can I change?
Why can't you change?
Look at me, I've changed.
What did you change?
Look,
see anything different?
Nothing's different.
Know what this is?
My landlady ruined it in the wash
and stitched it back up for me.
I'm now starting to
make do with mended clothes
for another year.
Stop kidding.
Don't you always send
your clothes out for dry cleaning?
Yeah, but now I do machine wash.
Okay.
Anything else?
Anything else, huh?
I've started washing dishes
and buying groceries.
I don't believe it.
I don't believe
you'd wash dishes and buy groceries.
Seriously.
If I don't work,
the landlady won't feed me.
Really?
If your dad knew
you were washing dishes and
buying groceries for your landlady,
he'd go crazy with anger.
That's what I mean.
My former pride
has been thrown into
the food market and the kitchen sink.
Doesn't that count as a change?
I get it.
You're willing to change
for your landlady,
so that's true love.
I get it, too.
You're not willing
to change for Dang Yu,
so yours isn't true love.
I need to learn from you.
Change.
Let's go, change.
Change!
Change yourself.
Change the world.
You're back.
Yeah.
Hurry!
I have something important to tell you.
What's wrong?
What important thing?
Guess what great thing I found?
Look.
Look at the details.
They are exactly the same.
Am I a woman of my word?
I told you before,
I'd compensate you
with the exact same item.
Look how cheap it is.
It's only 109 yuan,
and deliver fee is included.
How do you expect me to wear
this cheap knockoff?
Li Yifei, can you stop pretending?
You spend money
so recklessly. If you'd saved
even a little, you'd
have moved out long ago.
Even if you couldn't buy a big house,
you could have bought a small one.
A small one? If I buy a house,
it's going to be a villa.
I think you should buy
some medicine first.
I can't even be bothered with you.
Give me your phone.
I'll download
something great for you. Hurry.
What for?
I'll download an app. I'll teach
you how to save money.
I don't know how to use it.
What's wrong?
Don't you want to eat
late-night snacks,
or do you want to keep doing the dishes?
Look at you, getting smug.
Look here.
It's downloaded. This is the one.
Let's make a nickname for you.
Dummy Li.
Look!
Isn't it really cheap?
This one is only 40-something.
Compared to your...
If I knew, I would have bought this.
It's only 40-something.
I actually lost money on that one.
Let's return that one
and buy this one for you instead.
This is 40-something,
and it looks exactly like yours.
Am I right?
It really has everything in here.
Let me tell you,
everything missing from our home,
including the things we already have,
you can find the exact same versions.
You're back.
Who sent this gift?
Fei sent it.
What are you doing?
Are you still mad at me?
No.
I already know everything.
That girl is named Po Ming.
You stalked me again?
I found out purely by accident.
Forget it, it doesn't matter anymore.
Anyway, I have
nothing to do with her now.
You were right.
She is Po Ming.
Let me tell you,
your birthday is coming up.
Invite Fei
and the others over for dinner.
Okay, I'll tell him later.
How about right now, Jun?
Let's do this instead.
Go over there right now.
Look here.
Mom bought this.
A box of these cherries.
They are very fresh.
Take them over to him right now.
I just parted ways with him.
But these cherries
won't be fresh
if you put them in the fridge.
Hurry up and bring them over
while they are still fresh, okay?
Thanks for your trouble.
I'm leaving.
I have taught you everything I know.
From here on out, it's on you.
Make good use of it.
That's all?
Wonderful.
This is just the beginning.
You and this app
don't really know each other yet.
But trust me, in due time,
it will satisfy all your vanity
at the lowest possible prices.
You'll fall in love with it
just like you love money.
Try it.
Did you work in pyramid schemes
before investment banking?
Don't doubt me.
For the clothes you're wearing,
I can find the exact same style.
Yes...
Just a photo and you can find
the exact same style. Seriously.
I believe you.
Look.
Hurry up.
I believe you. Fifty. Thirty.
I can't take this anymore.
Who is it?
Jun?
- Please come on in.
- Didn't you just go back?
My mom
asked me to bring you some fruit.
You didn't have to make
a trip yourself. Seriously?
Alright, come on in.
Come on in.
No need to change your shoes.
Okay.
My birthday happens
to be on the weekend.
Why don't you come over together?
Together?
But I don't know your parents.
I think I shouldn't go.
Do you really have
to know them beforehand?
What's wrong?
Once you meet, you'll know them, right?
Let me tell you,
his parents are very nice.
Their cooking is delicious.
Besides, we are all good friends, right?
Jun even came to invite you in person.
What more do you want?
Let's go together.
If you're really too embarrassed,
then...
Then what?
Then, invite Dang Yu along.
Forget it.
She already rejected me.
So what if she rejected you?
Can't you be friends
after being rejected?
Just act normal.
You have to interact with her
in the most natural way.
It will bring a different result.
Understand?
Really?
Nonsense, why would I lie to you?
Of course.
Call her.
What are you waiting for?
Call her, listen to me.
Don't ask her.
Just give her the final choice.
Hello?
Hello, Yu. Are you busy?
I'm about to start a game. What's up?
Well,
it's Jun's birthday in a couple of days.
Let's go together.
I know.
His mom has already invited me.
Then go back to what you're doing.
Okay.
She said your mom invited her.
My mom invited her?
His mom invited her?
You're all Jun's good friends...
Mrs. Jun.
You're here...
Mrs. Jun, this is for you.
Just coming over is enough.
It's only right.
Why did you buy things?
Let me introduce them.
Qian Fei.
- Hello, Mr. and Mrs. Jun.
- Hello.
Dang Yu.
Hello, Mrs. Jun.
Please have a seat inside.
Change your shoes.
No need.
It's fine, no need.
Alright, come in.
Have a seat inside.
No need to change shoes.
Come, sit inside.
Sit down, please.
Please sit.
Thanks, Mr. Jun.
Have some fruit first.
The food will be ready in a moment.
Thank you, Mrs. Jun.
Make yourselves at home.
Just make yourselves at home, okay?
Mrs. Jun, do you need some help?
No need.
Mom, how did you invite Dang Yu?
I invited her as the mother
of a friend.
I was just worried you'd get mad.
Thanks, Mom.
It's just a meal today.
No need to overthink it.
But when it comes to dating,
there are many things
you must figure out clearly,
right?
All right.
- Happy birthday!
Thanks.
A year older again.
Fei,
these braised bamboo shoots
are your favorite.
I've been eyeing them for a while.
They are my favorite.
They are Mrs. Jun's specialties.
Eat up. Have some food.
Thank you, Mr. Jun.
Look how beautiful she is.
Your name is Qian Fei, right?
Yes, Mrs. Jun.
So beautiful.
Thank you.
I heard from Fei
that you work
at a financial firm in Lujiazui.
Yes, Mrs. Jun.
Yu and I are at the same company.
Are your positions the same?
Mom,
let's eat first, okay?
Let's not talk about work.
Isn't this just chatting over dinner?
Yes, just a casual chat.
Mrs. Jun, Qian Fei and I
have different positions.
She's on the business side.
I'm in administration,
at the front desk.
In administration?
The front desk?
So it's the kind of job greeting guests,
standing at the front?
Administration is like that.
I've heard
that girls who do
administration in companies
usually come
from fairly well-off families.
First, the work is easy,
and they don't care
about making much money.
Is that the case for you?
Eat up.
I'm not like that, Mrs. Jun.
My family is from Yunnan.
I came to Shanghai to work.
You're from Yunnan?
Yunnan?
Yunnan is very nice.
A while ago, my wife and I
even took a trip to Yunnan.
Places like Dali and Banna
have beautiful scenery.
That's just for the scenery.
Compared to Shanghai,
it's still very backward.
Mom.
Economically, Shanghai
is better than Yunnan.
That's why I came to Shanghai
to build my career.
Let's eat.
- Eat.
- Have some food.
For a front desk position like this,
is there any room for promotion?
Mrs. Jun, Yu actually
belongs to the typical
slash generation nowadays.
The work she does at our company
is just a small part of all her work.
She has great capabilities.
What does "slash" mean?
Slash means there is a lot of room,
very much room,
because it's relatively free.
And young people nowadays
want to do all kinds of things.
They just want to be happy.
Right.
You can like it all you want,
but you need the means to back it up,
right?
You two can like whatever you want now.
One is a gold-collar,
the other a white-collar.
How delightful.
Well...
Jun is doing pretty well, right?
Jun's situation is called stable.
Mom, my friends came to
celebrate my birthday with me,
not to listen to your nonsense.
You and Dad made
such a huge table of food.
Do you want me to be happy,
or do you want to see me embarrassed?
Did I embarrass you?
Every single word you said was so sharp.
Was I being sharp? Fei...
Fei, tell me.
Was I being sharp?
Even others could tell.
This fish has bones.
Why do you do this every time?
Nagging me...
Alright, let's just eat.
They aren't saying...
Mr. and Mrs. Jun,
actually, I have
something to attend to today.
How about I leave first,
and you guys enjoy the food?
- What?
- No, wait...
Goodbye, Mr. and Mrs. Jun.
What are you doing?
Jun, what are you doing?
Be reasonable, alright?
What's wrong with you?
I'm leaving.
- It's fine, Mrs. Jun.
- Mrs. Jun...
Let's just eat.
Such good food, right?
Out of nowhere,
Jun acts up like this again.
They really do have something to do.
They just told me.
They really have business. Come.
Come, Mr. Jun, let's have a drink.
I'm so sorry.
I really didn't know
my mom would say that.
It's fine.
Thank you.
Thank me for what?
Thank you for not listening
to your mom this time.
Jun's mom
practically set up a trap today.
You can look at it from another angle.
With his mom provoking him like that,
Jun finally let Dang Yu see
a different side of him.
True.
Alright, hurry back.
I really have a part-time job.
Then, when
can we meet again?
Depends on when I'm off.
I'm off.
Bye, Fei.
Bye.
Jun,
you have a shot.
If you make up your mind to pursue her,
you must never let her down.
Let's go.
Makes sense.
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling
upon my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes♪
♪Even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten♪
♪On a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken
my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts♪
♪My doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer
and fried chicken in autumn♪
♪Or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again?
That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world
knows my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you? That secret smile
behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along.
Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you?
The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it,
the words blurted out♪
♪I like you. I only like you♪
(Chore Price List)
♪Hey, you, you, you,
why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling
upon my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes♪
♪Even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten♪
♪On a rainy spring afternoon♪
Do you have a death wish?
Go back.
No, I'm not going back.
♪Before I knew it,
the words blurted out♪
♪I like you. I only like you♪
Focus on your studying, alright?
Doing chores
while studying at the same time?
Can you actually absorb anything?
The sponsor representative exam
is coming up soon.
I have to work during the day,
so I can only squeeze in time
to study at night.
Squeezing in time is fine,
but multitasking
depends on whether
you have the IQ for it.
Who are you looking down on?
We'll know if your IQ
is enough once I quiz you.
Quiz me, then.
I'll quiz you on
what you've already read.
Let me see.
Question.
"In 1991, the Zhengzhou
Grain Market opened
and introduced a trading mechanism,
marking the substantive
beginning of options trading in China."
What do you think of this statement?
This statement is incorrect.
This market introduced
a futures trading mechanism.
It should be the substantive beginning
of futures trading in New China.
What specifically does
the monetary base include?
It is also known as high-powered money,
which refers to the sum of currency
in circulation and bank reserves.
The monetary base is also denoted as Mb.
Mb = C + R.
C is currency in circulation,
and R represents bank reserves.
The sum of the two
equals the total monetary base.
All right, time for
a calculation question.
Company A produces only one product.
The variable cost ratio is 60%,
and the break-even
operating rate is 30%.
So, what is the EBIT margin?
The EBIT margin equals
the margin of safety ratio multiplied
by the contribution margin ratio.
That equals (1 minus
the break-even operating rate)
multiplied by (1 minus
the variable cost ratio).
Which equals (1 minus 30%)
multiplied by (1 minus 60%).
That equals 28%.
I'm sorry.
Back in school,
everyone used to call me Ace Fei
because I was a straight-A student.
Sorry about that.
I'm also Ace Fei.
I don't care what Ace you are.
Just as long as you
don't think I'm an idiot.
May Ace Fei pass every exam.
Pass every exam!
Pa...
Hey, little kid.
Take a look
at the waste sorting guide, kid.
Please take one.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Fire safety.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
Didn't we agree to meet
when you're off the clock?
Let me help you.
I'll do some part-time work
as your volunteer today.
Let's get this straight.
Volunteering doesn't pay anything.
Then consider it community service.
Give them to me.
Then, I'll leave these to you.
Here, take a look.
Jun, is that your girlfriend?
Not yet.
Don't let a good match slip away.
Go get her.
Fire safety, please take a look.
Okay.
Hello, please take a look
at the fire safety guide.
Hello, your check-in is complete.
Please take your room card.
Thank you.
This video clip...
It's from your hotel, right?
What?
I knew it.
It's already trending. That's crazy.
I'm sorry, I'm not too sure about this.
I'll post one, too.
Look, everyone.
This is where that cheater and
his mistress got beaten up last time.
Right here.
I'm currently at Shanlifang Hotel.
It's already a trending topic.
The spot where the cheater
and the mistress got beaten up.
Hello?
Those platform guys
we talked to the other day
returned the money.
If they couldn't get it done,
they should've said so earlier.
I'm so furious.
What should we do?
The matter you asked to suppress
wasn't kept down.
It has become a trending topic.
I know.
Someone must be
pulling strings behind the scenes.
I'll figure something out.
- Tang.
- How can he be that kind of person?
I really couldn't tell before.
Look at this video.
The video is viral now.
Yeah, Ms. Liao shouldn't
have acted like this.
Wang Ruohai...
Our company is famous now.
Look at the comments. Look at them.
Isn't this just bullying?
Our company is trending now.
Look at the shares.
The shares are insane.
- They're so high.
- Yeah.
- Many people know about it.
- Yes.
Gossip lovers love this stuff the most.
I bet
it's not just on
this one short video app.
It's all over the internet now.
Actually, Mr. Wang is pitiful.
What are you
fooling around with during work hours?
Boss.
We came here to work,
not to watch a drama.
I...
You...
Just do your own job well.
You all heard that, right?
Ms. Fang,
take a look at this.
This matter
is causing an uproar online,
and it all started because of Qian Fei.
Doesn't this have
a bad impact on Hejing?
It might not necessarily be a bad thing.
(Shanlifang Hotel Group)
I'll notify Fang Yun in a moment
to transfer Qian Fei away tomorrow.
We can't let her stay
in the group anymore.
You're in such a rush just for this?
Did my dad put pressure on you?
Of course not.
It's my own idea.
I don't want you to be implicated
because of her again.
You watched the video, right?
I know all about it. No need to watch.
They even doxxed you. Aren't you angry?
Now that it has blown up,
we can't transfer her away even more.
If you transfer her now,
people will speculate
whether you're using your position
to settle a personal grudge.
Why are you still speaking up for her?
I'm protecting you.
Time to eat.
♪What matters to me is what you need♪
♪No more, no less.
I only hope I can give it to you♪
♪What I treasure is what I have♪
♪Bit by bit,
I only hope you're there with me♪
♪Those sweet promises and words of love♪
♪Like fireworks
lighting up the midnight sky♪
♪Dreams, nonsense,
and the words hidden in my heart♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Next Episode Preview)
Ms. Fang asked me to handle
your work content now.
As for today's meeting,
you don't need to attend for now.
Ms. Qian,
don't be so distant with me, okay?
Come with me.
What are you doing?
Let go.
Li Yifei,
I suddenly feel
that it's no longer appropriate
for us to keep living together.
♪There's no need
to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords
with the wind♪
♪There's no need
to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises
for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need
to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone,
yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need
to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more
than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion
and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting
for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day
you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly
like the stars and the moon on high♪