All your classmates say
that everyone shares their life on social media.
Do you have social media?
No.
Do you want me to set up one for you?
Sure, help me out.
Okay.
[I am not a robot]
I am not a robot.
Yes, you are.
Oppa.
Why are you teaming up with others to bully me?
Call me "Dear,"
and I won't bully you.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by â¤ Ever 9 Love ðŸ¤–@Viki.com
[Forever with Ever 9]
Now, the first post.
This one is good.
[Episode 7: Luckily You're Mine]
♫ It's you... who clings to me day and night ♫
♫ I want to nestle against the side of your face ♫
♫ and look at your gaze ♫
♫ It's you... who makes the rules of static life different ♫
♫ I want to step into your time ♫
♫ And backup all your scenes ♫
♫ Your smile brightens up my entire universe ♫
♫ I want to accompany you while you fulfill your dreams ♫
♫ Strolling under the starry sky ♫
♫ Why can't we live together while I hold your hand? ♫
♫ You're my eternal love evermore ♫
[AntiReset]
♫ Until eternity ♫
For me, someone who only has code,
I must learn to create a different kind of companionship
to make a lasting impression.
I'm ready.
It seems you're looking forward to our date.
Of course.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
I just feel very comfortable with you in my daily life.
If it were not with me,
would you feel the same way?
Absolutely not.
It can only be you, and it will only be you.
I am very happy.
I am yours.
This is good.
Just in case, in the future,
I mean if,
can you not…
Never mind, forget it.
You're the only one here.
There won't be anyone else.
Do you want to touch him?
But…
♫ Your smile brightens up my entire universe ♫
♫ I want to accompany you while you fulfill your dreams ♫
♫ Strolling under the starry sky ♫
♫ Why can't we live together while I hold your hand? ♫
♫ You're my eternal love evermore ♫
My database shows
that alpacas and capybaras are both community-living animals.
Living alone for a long time can be very depressing for them,
and may even cause death.
Is it that serious?
I hope they can always be accompanied.
You must stay healthy.
Companionship is a process of accommodating the other person's emotions,
making them feel that they are not alone,
giving them the feeling of having someone stable and calm by their side.
Alpacas and capybaras both originate from South America.
They were originally half an earth away,
yet they live in harmony here.
This place has gradually become their home and their place.
Now, I am like them.
I also have a home.
Then I have to feed you.
What would you like to eat?
- Soft ice cream.
- Soft ice cream?
That's what they show on TV.
I often feel that life is always changing
and often unpredictable.
Nevertheless, with your company,
it seems not so hard to get through.
Wait for me.
I'll go buy it.
- [How can I keep Ever 9]
- [Keep what?]
I said I want to keep Ever 9. Is it that hard to understand?
Wait for my other series.
I will keep one for you.
I don't want another one.
Just tell me what to do.
Is Ever 9 this handy?
It makes sense.Cleaning, cooking, driving, company in bed,
functionality all in one,
and he never talks back.
I want to buy one too.
I won't sugarcoat it.
You can't buy out the HengRen series.
What flavor?
Vanilla.
If life is full of unpredictability,
can you be the one to go through it with me?
Do you like it?
It's really tasty.
I'll do my swim rehabilitation, and you'll stay near me.
You're not allowed in the water.
I've said I am waterproof even ten meters underwater.
If you don't believe me, believe in modern technology.
No, I will not compromise on this.
I have a very important task for you.
You want me to get in the water to protect you?
I want you to help me change.
You won't let me into the water. I don't want to help you.
♫ Fortunately, you don't know ♫
♫ Just like the bell that jingles as you lift your head ♫
♫ My intense longing burns ♫
♫ Tears trace the corners of my eyes ♫
♫ Like an overheated tsunami ♫
♫ Fortunately, you don't know ♫
♫ I hide in yesterday where there's no fuss or noise ♫
♫ I don't rehearse your silly laughter ♫
♫ Just wondering what your hugs would feel like ♫
♫ Keep the heartbeat of your love for me in mind ♫
Professor.
What a coincidence that you're swimming here, too.
Professor, has your shoulder healed?
You're in such good shape. Do you train regularly?
Brother, we should go now.
Wait. I'm not done talking.
What are you doing?
Professor, you usually swim back and forth a dozen times.
Why are you leaving so early?
Let's go, Brother. I'm hungry.
I'm hungry, too.
Let's eat together.
You're dressed so beautifully today.
It's a pity not to swim more.
Yes, Miss He.
Since you've chosen to wear this to swim today,
you might as well skip eating. It'll make you fat.
You're the one who will get fat.
Let's go.
He Li was recommended by a professor.
She's quite capable at work.
But she prefers to use body language
to express a sort of appreciation.
The day I arrived,
was it she who came to look for you at home?
She even showed me many photos of you two having fun together.
"Professor Chu usually swims back and forth a dozen times.
Today, you're leaving so early."
For your next rehab, just ask her to accompany you.
After all, you only let me stay by the side.
No, really, there's nothing between us except work.
When she came that time, it was to deliver some documents.
As for the photos, they should all be group photos or something.
When it comes to swimming, we don't meet that often.
And my lane is always very far from hers.
If you don't like her, just ignore her.
You can't expect me to act like what's on TV,
like I would fire her or anything.
She was recommended by a senior colleague.
I can't do that.
You can't expect me to act like they do in the movies.
I'm not.
I'm certainly not that type of person.
Nor am I that kind of artificial intelligence.
Don't believe those TV shows and movies.
They've all taught you bad habits.
Of course, I know you're not that kind of person.
Actually, when you stepped in to bail me out,
I was so happy.
After all, ever since I was young,
I've always dealt with everything by myself.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have treated Miss He that way.
According to big data analytics,
her professionalism and appearance match with you,
and your personalities complement each other nicely.
So what I should do is create opportunities for you,
instead of pulling you away from her.
Are you saying that you want to set me up with that woman?
The professor must be thinking of me.
You rascal.
Miss He's evaluation in my database is an A-grade.
Even though she is still no match for you,
based on the need for human reproduction,
she should still be considered.
Don't always be alone.
I didn't know you had a matchmaker function.
Don't overthink it.
Also, right now, you're mine.
You have to hold your ground.
You can't just let anyone have me.
Got it?
This is exclusively yours.
"I am your number 9."
This is mine.
"You are my number 9."
As it is said in comics, novels, and plays,
a kiss at the city's highest point
can seal two people for a lifetime.
Are you sure you understand what "a lifetime" means?
Of course, I do.
It means being with you
until the end of my life.
♫ Time is adept at revealing all the truth ♫
♫ The truth forms a high wall ♫
♫ Trapping the two of us once in love ♫
♫ Finally, there's no need to pretend to be happy or desperate ♫
♫ If it weren't for the boiling desire of loneliness ♫
♫ We wouldn't speak of love so recklessly while kissing ♫
♫ Let your arrogance run wild ♫
♫ I can't bear to see the dawn ♫
♫ Don't think about what awaits tomorrow ♫
If my life just stops here,
[Stay at the pinnacle of happiness forever]
that would be great, too.
You did agree to "a lifetime."
No backing out.
I am your number 9.
Ever 9.
Ever 9, can you hear me?
Ever 9?
Can you hear me?
Ever 9.
[Hengji Intelligent Technology]
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by â¤ Ever 9 Love ðŸ¤–@Viki.com
I did not believe in people, did not believe in gods,
nor did I believe in fate.
But this artificial intelligence falls outside of these categories.
CanI believe that he will be safe and sound?
♫ When simple joy is stripped away by complexity ♫
♫ Pure tears are hidden in persistence ♫
Will your heart beat faster because of me?
You are just an artificial intelligence.
To what extent do you want to influence him?
Can you cook meals for me?
Can we sleep together?
I just want to remind you
that I have additional functions.
"A Long Time Does Not Equal Eternity" - Zhu Yuqing
♫ It turns out that a long time is not an eternity ♫
♫ A hand held for so long ♫
♫ Has become a hand waving goodbye ♫
♫ The promises so bravely voiced at the beginning ♫
♫ Have now lost the reason to be fulfilled ♫
♫ A beginning with no end ♫
♫ If we must pursue who's at fault ♫
♫ Blame it all on me ♫
♫ Since words of love are spoken without a second thought ♫
♫ Why can't I let go with ease ♫
♫ Some loss can be called a gain ♫
[AntiReset]