Good morning.
Morning.
So this is
how it feels to have someone around.
Give it to me.
Thank you.
Master, enjoy your breakfast.
History changes
because of different elements.
What was thought to be just a minor change
could have a massive impact,
which also creates the uniqueness
of history's existence.
Okay.
This is good enough.
♫ I hide in yesterday
where there's no fuss or noise ♫
♫ I don't rehearse your silly laughter ♫
♫ Just wondering what your hugs
would feel like ♫
♫ Keep the heartbeat
of your love for me in mind ♫
Master.
Your lunchbox.
Thank you.
[Episode 4 Taking My Possession Out]
♫ You cuddle by my side day and night ♫
♫ Wishing to nestle against your cheek ♫
♫ Looking at what you're gazing ♫
♫ You make the static life different ♫
♫ I want to step into your time ♫
♫ And backup all the scenes ♫
♫ Your smile brightens up my entire universe ♫
♫ I want to dream the dream you wish to dream ♫
♫ Strolling under the starry sky ♫
♫ On what grounds can I hold your hand ♫
♫ You're my eternal love evermore ♫
[AntiReset]
♫ Forever and always ♫
I forgot my bag.
Do you want to come to school with me?
Can I?
Thank you, Master.
Let's go.
Master, do you like your job?
I hear that students nowadays
are hard to manage.
Apart from poor logic, bad expression,
and indigent argumentation skills,
everything else is fine.
Well, would you scold them?
No.
Learning is their responsibility.
I don't judge students based on grades.
Are you curious about going to school?
I have the data,
but I have never experienced
the feeling of sitting in the classroom
and attending class with classmates.
What I mean is
did you really go to school for classes?
I did not.
It's just a setting.
A situational setup.
It's okay.
You're always welcome in my class.
Hello, teacher.
Okay, we're about to be late.
Drive.
What kind of student were you
when you were in school?
Reading, thinking, and taking tests.
Nothing special, I guess.
No, it sounds fun.
Didn't we agree not to call me 'Master' before?
Can your settings be changed?
I am your possession.
You can ask me to call you anything.
I've promised to treat you as a person.
Why do you still use the word 'possession'?
Well…
Honey.
Hasn't anyone told you
the meaning of this word?
It symbolizes submission.
It implies owning someone's life.
Listen to yourself.
I don't know what strange data
have been inputted into you.
Does he not like that?
Or is there something wrong?
Then,
what do you wish me to call you, Master?
Mr. Chu?
Professor Chu?
Chuchu?
Ping?
Pingping?
Bro.
Oppa.
Or…
baby?
You can decide
on what to call me.
Thank you.
You can sit over there.
Okay, class, we will begin.
Having studied history for so long,
you should be able to grasp
that during a person's lifetime,
it's almost impossible
to fully vindicate their experiences.
What we can do
is to try our best to make amends
within the long river of history.
Thus, historical revisionism
has its significance.
Everything I've experienced
has accumulated to who I am today.
History exists because it is remembered.
Oscar Wilde is a great example.
During his lifetime,
he faced a great deal of unfair treatment.
But as later generations interpret his texts…
♫ If memories won't fade away ♫
♫ Refuse to save up ♫
♫ Our love ♫
♫ My wishes exist with your existence ♫
♫ All up to you ♫
Hey, are you a transfer student?
But it's not the beginning of the semester now.
How come there is a transfer student?
Exactly.
What's your name?
You dare to take this mandatory history class.
I'm impressed.
I am Heng 9.
May I ask why it's bold to take this class?
You don't know?
You see, Professor Chu's is always serious.
And he asks sharp questions.
If you get called on in class,
you will be terribly tortured.
But though he has a stern face,
he is still very handsome.
Tell me honestly.
Did you take the class because you think
the professor is handsome too?
Stop being so infatuated.
Honey.
Ice-cold?
Perhaps the history and future of humans
may be revised due to differences
in experience and perspective.
You sound awfully like Professor Chu.
What's your relationship?
Cousin?
Sibling?
Distant relative?
Caregiver?
Bodyguard?
I'm not.
Or do you two have some kind of secret?
Wu Xiaojing,
if you could use
even one-tenth of your imagination
on your report,
it would surely be excellent.
Come here.
He is a dear younger brother of mine
who came to take care of me.
He will be with me for the next few weeks.
Don't you bully him.
Let's go.
He's too cute.
Let's go. We'll be late.
Department of History
Last time when the Boss came,
I learned that you are afraid
of the smell of oil fumes,
and don't like to eat fried foods.
You took so many notes.
Taking notes
makes you seem more human.
So how was your first class?
Once the scenario is set,
it's only after actually experiencing something
that people's emotions can be stirred
by their immediate reactions.
Just like only after a pilot flies up
and truly touches the sky,
will one feel an indescribable emotion
due to that sense of vastness.
If we apply historical revisionism
to an individual,
does that mean
that when one's historical memory
is reorganized,
perhaps he can also construct new narratives
and redefine the future?
Can a person also construct new narratives?
You listened very carefully.
I've written down
every word you said.
Bro.
Don't walk so fast.
This isn't a stroll.
It's practically powerwalking.
You've decided to call me 'bro'.
Isn't that how you introduced
me to your classmates?
A dear younger brother.
I spent my time here
from college to doctoral classes.
That building is for Taiwanese history.
This one here is for world history.
I also took some classes
in historical philosophy back there.
And this is the legendary
Confession Lake
Legend says if two people
share their feelings here,
they will stay together for life.
I'm sure you have heard
many confessions here.
Professor.
This is for you.
Why me?
Because I think you're very smart
and serious, I admire that.
So if someone has the same qualities as me,
you would like them too.
I hope you'll think about it carefully.
Don't gamble your time and happiness
on someone's external attributes.
Mr. Chu.
I think we're quite suitable for each other.
- Why?
- Because our tastes are very similar.
It's worth a try.
Similar tastes do not
necessarily mean suitability.
Just like a high-end watch
isn't necessarily suitable for everyone.
Yiping.
You've been single for so long.
How about we try to be together?
What's the purpose?
Humans are social animals.
Two single people should
be together for warmth.
If it's cold, you can turn on the heater.
This is not what it means
for two people to be together.
When in a relationship,
a person's voice and body
would be very different from the usual.
From a neurological perspective,
being in love rewards the brain.
The brain secretes many substances
such as dopamine,
making people happy.
Have you ever been in love, Master?
No.
Why?
Aren't you curious?
Would the dopamine triggered by love
or hormones
cause changes in the human body
in the same way
as what was experienced virtually?
So, in your settings,
is there a virtual love experience?
To what extent?
Come here.
Be careful.
Don't move.
Do you feel anything at this distance?
The social safety distance of 1.5 meters.
It's polite, maintaining a comfortable space.
If it is someone you are closer to,
they can get this close,
0.46 meters.
As for the closest distance,
0.15 meters.
If you feel a difference,
it means your virtual experience
was quite close to reality.
My database shows
when humans kiss,
seventeen sets of muscles
in the lips and tongue
will be in a tense state.
This proves that my data seems to differ
from the actual situation.
♫ I want to step into your time ♫
♫ And backup all the scenes ♫
♫ Your smile brightens up my entire universe ♫
♫ I want to dream the dream you wish to dream ♫
♫ Strolling under the starry sky ♫
♫ On what grounds can I hold your hand ♫
♫ You're my eternal love evermore ♫
♫ Forever and always ♫
Today's demonstration teaching ends here.
So this is the correct way to use muscles.
Does this count as understanding
each other's intentions?
[Making Virtual Experience Closer to Reality]
Would adding so many parameters
make it break down easily?
I don't know.
As the first artificial intelligence
with so many sensors,
we can only test and see where its limits are.
But he added love dopamine.
What's the point of that?
His function is to provide care.
If the Boss tells us to add it, we add it.
Don't ask questions.
Alright.
This is what kissing feels like.
Do you mind that I'm not a real person?
If you want to treat him as a friend, fine.
But after all, he is not a human.
To me, you are one of a kind.
Irreplaceable.
I won't lose you.
♫ Turns out that a long time is not forever ♫
♫ A hand held for so long ♫
♫ Has become a hand waving goodbye ♫
♫ The promises so bravely
voiced at the beginning ♫
♫ Have now lost the reason to be fulfilled ♫
♫ A beginning with no end ♫
♫ If we must pursue who's at fault ♫
♫ Blame it all on me ♫
♫ Since words of love are spoken
without a second thought ♫
♫ Why can't I let go with ease ♫
[AntiReset]
♫ Some loss is called gaining ♫