Who is it?
- Did you sleep well?
- Miss Luni?
- What brings you here?
- I have a present for you. Ta-da!
Mission - Make a delicious meal for the members of Angels
Oh, a mission. Thank you.
Wait! If you're free, why don't we chat for a bit?
I thought... we had agreed not to film inside the rooms.
Oh, if that's the case. You already filmed me giving him the mission card right? We'll be out after a quick chat.
It's so nice in here. The bookshelf is pretty too.
Do you have something to say to me?
I just wanted to chat with you now, because  I didn't think I'd get the chance to when we film later.
Did you sleep on the sofa?
Oh, yes. It's my personal preference.
There's a terrace? How pretty!
Yes, the terrace is pretty. It's pretty,
but I want to show you the bathroom.
- What?
The bathroom is actually a bit prettier than the terrace, so I want to show that to you.
- I see...
- Let's go.
Jeez, that was close one...
- Who?
- What do you mean who? It's me, pretty Ha Neul.
Oh, Ha Neul. Pretty Ha Neul... You're here?
Where were you? Didn't you know we're featured in the next mission?
The crew left because you weren't here. I wanted to film the surprise!
You get to do whatever you please!
Byul, you look a bit different today.
- Why do you seem like a different person?
- What are you talking about?
- Is it because you didn't do your hair?
- I actually didn't wash it...
- Hey! Is it because it's oily? Why didn't you wash it?
- I was feeling lazy.
You normally wash up 5 times a day. Why aren't you being clean today?
Byul, you don't have anything going on with Jung Woo right?
Have anything? Like what?
I'm close to Jun Beom from Endest, and he told me to be careful of Jung Woo.
Be careful of what?
Byul, look at Jung Woo. He seems like he'd be nice and proper, right?
Apparently, he's great at keeping girls on the hook.
He's especially good to every one, so no girls suspect that they're being played.
But then, later on, you find out you're number 20 on the waiting list.
Why would he do that with 20 people?
Why else? Isn't it to hold hands and sleep together?
He doesn't seem like that type. And how could he right now? We're filming.
Did he not come over for no reason while you guys weren't filming? Maybe at night?
Are you sleeping? Can you come to my room for a bit?
So he has? Wow, he's really a player.
Byul, you're going to get backstabbed like that.
I'm telling you this because I know you're dense.
Don't give you heart to him. Don't be one of his fish in the sea.
You must feel at ease since your members are here.
Oh, yes.
I couldn't be more at ease.
Let's not believe in weird rumors.
It's not like I experienced that myself.
Oh, right. We have to go grocery shopping. What do your members like?
They'll eat anything.
- Do they not have any allergies?
- Allergies?
Wait, my stomach really hurts right now.
Sorry, I'll be right back.
I'm really sorry, but could I just make one call?
Thank you.
- Hello?
-  Oh, thank goodness.
I'm... it's me.
- What's wrong?
- It's an emergency, so I'll just get to the point.
Are your members allergic to anything? What do they like to eat?
- 2 Americanos please.
Yes.
- They like spicy rice cakes.
- Okay, thanks!
I can't eat Shiitake mushro...
Out of all things to buy, they wouldn't get Shiittake mushrooms, right?
Shiitake Mushrooms
I think we have all the materials for spicy rice cake. Do you like seafood, like fish?
Don't be a fish.
I'm not really feeling fish today.
- Can you watch this for a bit? I need to use the restroom.
- Sure.
What's wrong? I can't call you for long.
How is she? Byul?
You called to ask me that?
Do I need to say things when I'm alone too?
Oh... This is convenient to eat because it's small,
and this one... seems like it would have a nice texture.
I need to use the restroom...
Huh? What do you mean how is it?
I can't talk for long. Kim Byul?
I'm just pretending to be good to her because I'm filming.
She's a little annoying because she's a bit of a meddler.
I'll stay here until you fall asleep.
Should we go outside? Is it okay if there's no other people?
Huh?
Why would we date? She doesn't have any appeal.
We won't be meeting long after we film anyway.
I need to hang up now. Don't call me.
If it's difficult, you can stop. I can do it.
It's fine, I can do it myself.
- If  you do that, you'll get hurt.
- I'm not getting hurt right now.
I feel like you will soon... your technique is asking for you to get hurt.
Curl your fingers like this and try it.
It doesn't work as well.
- No, if you do that you'll get hu-
- Ouch!
I told you you'd get hurt!
I'm heading to my room.
Wait.
- Something's wrong right? Something bad.
- No.
- There is.
- There isn't.
You're not even looking at me. You have to tell me for me to know.
It's nothing. Can I go to my room now? This hurts.
- You were both here?
- Why are you coming up alone?
I came to change.
Byul, what do you think of Jung Woo?
Well, he's kind and has good manners...
and two-faced... so scary.
Manager, Jun Beom keeps calling me.
How is she, Byul?
This time, I think he's interested in Byul.
-  Yeah, bring her out next time.
- I intentionally tried to make it sound like I don't like her,
Oh my god, she's hella cute.
but I'm still kind of worried.
Jung Woo! I heard you're filming something with Kim Byul of Angels?
Byul is a good person. Can you try stopping him?