(This series was produced
with the support of MCST, KOCCA,)
(Gangwon-do Province,
and Goseong-gun County.)
Everyone will hear.
Please stop.
What should I do?
No...
It's not what you think.
What's going on here?
Did Gyeong Ho hit her by mistake?
There's no way.
He's an excellent sniper with four degrees
in taekwondo and three in judo.
What does that mean?
It couldn't have been a mistake
with his exceptional vision.
I see.
No. I would never.
This isn't good...
I can't believe this.
Thanks to you, I might be misunderstood.
See that? Everything is my fault.
All the gifts Tong Il received...
will be sent to kids in the North as well.
As a newborn,
Tong Il is already helping comrades
in our people's republic.
That's right.
What's going on?
Can't you tell?
What?
Ju Hui must have felt so much pressure
because of the video,
and she got emotional
when she saw Gyeong Ho.
(Love Andante Episode 8)
(Pyeongyang
Military Security Command office)
What does the party say?
They're deciding
whether the foreign reaction...
is beneficial or not.
Considering the growth
and economic profit,
isn't it worth attempting
a partial revelation?
You have a point, but...
shouldn't we consider the side effects?
This is Great Assistant Ha speaking.
Comrade.
Chief Commander.
I received your report.
The supreme leader said...
Yes.
Are you done crying?
Nothing has been decided.
Don't worry about it yet and let's wait.
If I get kicked out tomorrow...
Hey, don't be rash now.
Everything has a procedure.
Do you have to be so extreme?
Let's wait.
You've been bubbly and cheerful,
so I thought you would shrug this off.
I see you're actually very scared.
Why are you laughing?
(Pyeongyang
Na Gyeong's home)
Eat this.
Let's both eat.
Is Na Gyeong doing well?
She's fine.
I'm glad she is.
Eat up.
Are you done already?
You barely ate.
I have to leave
since I have to be at the politburo.
(Pyeongyang
The office of the politburo chief)
Our people's republic stands firm.
Yes, sir.
To handle the matter with grace,
let's show leniency.
Yes, sir.
We'll treat it as if it never happened.
Great Assistant Ha,
I heard your daughter is making
huge research progress.
You're too generous.
Just know that the party is taking notice.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
You may leave.
Yes, sir.
(Peace Village Living Support
Lee Jang Su)
(Peace Village General Manager
Park Jun Mo)
(Considering the global interest,
both nations agreed to keep the village.)
Hey!
(Accepting South Korea's request,)
(North Korea agrees to keep the village
until the official termination.)
Hey!
- Jun Mo!
- Jang Su!
Jun Mo!
What's gotten into them?
Did they eat something strange
for breakfast?
It's done!
What is?
The people's interest will keep
Peace Village alive!
The party will let this slide!
That's great!
Villagers, we have an announcement.
The South and North agreed...
to recognize the video incident
as a mistake.
They ask us to prevent similar incidents
from happening again...
by being extra careful.
Mister!
Did you hear the announcement?
They will overlook it as a mistake.
You were right.
Comrade Ju Hui, let's be careful
not to make a mistake again.
Okay.
I told you.
I'm going in first.
Okay.
You have to be careful.
Mister, let's have breakfast.
What?
Why would I eat breakfast with you?
Let's just eat.
What's that?
This is an egg sandwich...
and fragrant coffee that I made myself.
Thank you. I'll enjoy it.
I'm running late.
I'll see you at night.
As soon as the newborn
came into the world...
He looks like me.
The baby became a celebrity
that every villager knew.
- Hello.
- Hi, Ju Hui.
- Wave at me.
- You can stop that.
First, I can fry eggs.
I'm a good cook.
- You can cook?
- I can cook.
What are you good at cooking?
People from the North and South...
returned to their buzzing daily lives.
(One month later)
Hey, Jang Su.
It doesn't look ripe yet, right?
I don't see the red color yet.
Should we leave it?
Let's wait a few days.
- Should we?
- Yes.
- Okay, let's do that.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Hold on!
My back hurts.
You should exercise regularly.
You just stood up for a moment
and you're holding your back.
You try getting old. You'll see why.
- My gosh.
- Let's go.
Help me here.
Here comes a young man who can help.
- This is tiring.
- Come on now.
- Grab me properly. Use your strength.
- Stand up straight.
Villagers came together
to get ready for the new year.
As the produce was neatly stacked,
the villagers felt generous as well.
- It'll sting.
- Okay.
Dr. Gu, it's ready.
- You can inject the anesthetics.
- Okay.
Everyone was in their setting...
It'll sting.
Everyone was doing their jobs.
Every moment was literally peaceful.
We appreciated the momentary joy
of being together.
You can't dodge that?
How can I dodge this?
- Be careful.
- What's going on?
Walk slowly.
(Village shelter)
Seon In Ho, Yang Chang Ju.
Get in first.
- Choi Dae Woong.
- What's going on?
Get in first and we'll let you know.
We're currently figuring out
the situation.
Let's wait until our safety is secured.
Jun Mo, I don't see Mr. Piano
and Comrade Na Gyeong.
What?
Where did they go?
Warm tea is the best
when your body is freezing.
The wind is harsh and cold
during the winter in Gangwon-do.
It's okay.
Try it.
I heard a cannon fire just now.
It's very quiet. I feel anxious.
Should we head back?
We better go back.
Okay, let's go.
They went together in a car.
I'm sure they're safe somewhere.
They should be fine.
What's this sound?
I think it was another one.
It sounds like something is collapsing.
The sound stopped.
You two go and have a look.
Be careful.
- Okay.
(Village shelter)
(Peace Village)
Nothing is going on.
I think we're safe.
What in the world was going on?
They're here.
What's going on?
We were very worried about you.
Where have you two been? Are you okay?
Yes, we're okay.
Why are you all out here?
We heard bombs all of a sudden.
We also heard something collapsing.
Is everyone okay?
Yes. Fortunately,
we all came to the shelter.
- Sir.
- Yes?
May I see you for a second?
Sure.
A wild boar seems to have stepped
on a land mine.
It's the middle of winter,
and a wild boar was roaming for food.
It stepped on a land mine
from the Korean War and the explosion...
scared the village.
And skeletons were found
where the land mine exploded.
The news became huge
in the Korean Peninsula.
A wild boar came close to Peace Village
to find food to survive for winter...
and stepped on an unfounded land mine.
This led to the discovery of the remains
of people who died during the Korean War.
The military forensic unit is at the site,
examining the skeletons.
The skeletons found in the mountain
near Peace Village will be...
organized by the Korean army,
and the extracted DNA will be...
used to track the descendants.
According to military personnel,
battles broke out in the area
during the Korean War,
and it is estimated
that many have died there.
The Korean government registered
the families of the Korean War veterans.
Using the DNA database,
the government tracked
the families of the skeletons.
Mr. Kim went missing
at around February of 1951.
After the armistice,
his family looked for him for 70 years...
but was unable to do so.
But about 70 years after leaving home,
Mr. Kim came back to his family.
His family said...
they are so happy to have found
their grandfather's remains,
expressing gratitude to Goseong-gun
and to the relevant agencies.
After 70 years...
Imagine how the family felt
when they found the skeletons...
The skeletons were secured
jointly by the South and North.
After finding the family,
the government delivered the remains
with due respect.
Comrade, stop being a wet blanket
and let's go.
Wait for me.
So this is a Christmas party.
- You do this every year?
- We do.
Isn't it too often...
Listen to Woo Bin.
You better watch out, you better not cry,
you better not pout...
Stop right there. Now you try.
You better watch out, you better not cry,
you better not pout...
Let's give up. It's a lost cause.
Hey, teach me.
I'll try again.
Teach me.
Okay.
It can be hard.
The rice cake is here.
I'm glad to see this day.
We all gathered to spend
Christmas together.
Jun Mo, it's so touching.
Since Korea split into two,
it was the first time for us
to spend a merry end of the year.
Everyone was excited
to welcome the next year together,
planning a joyous year.
Look!
It's snowing.
It's a white Christmas.
It's true.
I remembered that if you spend
a white Christmas with someone you love,
he will love you back for sure.
(Goodbye, 2023.)
Soon here in Jonggak,
the bell will ring at midnight
to say goodbye to this year.
To wrap up this year,
friends and families came running...
with unique hopes of their own.
To every viewer out there,
I wish you only good spirits
in the New Year.
Aren't you cold?
I'm fine.
Are you cold?
No, it's warm.
And it's cozy.
Time flies so fast.
Right?
Yes.
- Ten, nine, eight, seven,
- six, five, four, three, two, one!
It's the New Year!
- Everyone, Happy New Year!
- Happy New Year!
(2024)
Look! The sun is rising!
It's the first and last New Year...
that we get to see together.
This moment,
this feeling...
I don't think
I'll ever forget this feeling.
(Three months later)
What's wrong?
People say you get attached to your home.
Now I understand.
Yes.
I'll miss this home, too.
Home...
Home can feel comfortable.
I now know that, thanks to you.
Thank you...
for being here with me.
I remember the first time I met you.
That kick?
It hurt so much.
Let's eat.
The season that tickles your nose tip
with the cold wind has passed.
The forsythia flowers in the yard...
seems to be telling us that...
our time is almost up.
Dr. Gu, let's eat
and finish that together.
Those are sandwiches.
It looks good, right?
I made it to share with you.
Try it.
Thank you.
Where will you be going now, Dr. Park?
Well, I'm not sure...
What about you, Dr. Gu?
I'll be going to
Kim Il Sung University Hospital.
That's great.
Yes, I'm glad to be
a Pyeongyang citizen, but...
But?
I like it here.
I like this village so much,
but to have to leave...
Take any medicine you need here.
I'm sure you have medicine there,
but instead of keeping it here,
you could bring it to where it's needed.
Dr. Park.
I'm sorry.
I mean...
I mean, I like you.
I like you, Dr. Gu.
My heart has been longing for you
for a long time.
This is crazy...
Be quiet!
Let's pretend we didn't see it.
While preparing to go back,
there are sparks suddenly flying.
I feel bad.
That's true. They'll never see each other.
I bet their hearts are breaking, right?
I'm sure it's inexplicable.
Mister, slow down.
Was it necessary to walk here?
I have a lot of memories with you.
I won't call you "Mister" anymore.
I used to fall in love in a heartbeat.
Now I know the type of person I like,
the type of personality I like,
and the type I prefer clearly.
What does that have to do with me?
What I'm saying is...
you're my type,
Nam Gyeong Ho.
We're wrapping things up, too.
Why are you confessing?
What?
I mean it's...
so that you don't forget me.
It's to see each other
after reunification.
I want you to promise me
to wait until that day comes.
We don't know when that will happen,
and you want a promise?
We could meet and marry someone else...
and even have kids,
but we could meet again.
We have so many memories in this village.
Let's go and get something to eat.
I could tell you're not a big eater.
What do you like?
Have you been watching me?
I like everything.
Then are you craving anything?
Jun Mo.
Are you crying?
If we say goodbye like this,
when will we see each other again?
After cleaning up this area,
won't we see each other
in about two years?
We can't guarantee that...
it will be us at that time.
Who knows?
We'll see each other again.
Hey.
I'll miss you so much.
Come on now.
The South and North spent 70 years apart.
After spending one year together,
we understand each other
and have built a deep bond.
(To Dr. Gu Jin Sang
From Park Dam So)
Will you be busy back home?
I probably will be.
I'll have to do all the delayed concerts.
I'll go to your concert
if I get the chance.
Okay.
Will you go to Germany
right after you go back?
After the report, I might have to.
I don't know when,
but we can see each other again, right?
I can't promise you that.
I won't change my number.
Call me anytime.
I don't know when I'll leave for Germany.
Even if I knew your number,
it'll be hard to see you again.
What is this?
Open it.
It's pretty.
On the way back home
after winning the Chopin Award,
I bought this as a gift...
to give to someone I would like.
Does it look good on me?
Yes.
If I promise you...
not to forget and wait,
will you call me?
When he said he won't forget and wait,
I felt a rush of pain deep in my heart.
I know I'll never see him...
and that we can't be together like now.
I wish time could just stop
right now like this.
I can't believe that...
I can't see someone
I have been seeing every day after today.
She slowly took a place in my heart...
and became everything to me.
I don't want to let her go.
(Peace Village to Seoul)
I was happy being with you all
for the past year.
I spent a historical moment
I can never forget with you.
It was an honor.
Please head back home safely.
I'll see you again one day
healthy and well.
Thank you.
It was a great pleasure.
- Thank you.
We don't see Tong Il's family.
- I don't see them.
- Where are they?
I don't see Dam So either.
- Tong Il's family...
- They left...
with Tong Il and Dr. Gu...
for the train before you.
And Dr. Park is sending them
to the station.
Why would you cut me off?
Whether you say it or not,
it's all the same.
Also, no matter who says it,
everyone will understand, won't they?
(Donghae Railway Transit Office)
Tong Il.
Mom, Tong Il is here.
Tong Il...
We'll be late for the train. Let's get in.
Let's get in.
Now let's go to the village gate together.
Everyone, get on the bus.
Let's go.
You can go this way.
It was a pleasure.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It's okay, Dr. Park.
Thank you for your service.
Did Tong Il's family board the train?
Yes.
Thank you. Get in.
Woo Bin, congratulations
on being discharged.
Come on.
I still have one week left.
One week is practically nothing.
Hey, Ki Nam still has
eight years and four months.
Why would you remind me?
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
I'm really fine.
Come on now.
Let's lock the empty houses and clean up.
- Okay.
Yes, sir.
- Shall we?
- Let's go.
Goodbye.
Take care.
Gyeong Ho.
Let's meet each other here
after the two Koreas are reunified.
I'm going to go now. Say your goodbyes.
Mr. Piano.
Goodbye and take care.
You take care, too.
Look after Na Gyeong.
Don't worry about that.
Goodbye.
This is the last time I get to see him.
The most beautiful person in the world.
He is my man.
She came into my dry and barren heart.
She filled my void.
The reality of having to say goodbye...
makes me unbearably angry.
I capture you in my eyes to never forget.
This moment of capturing you
in my heart...
is just so painful.
Your breath.
Your smile.
I promise to face them again.
Just wait.
Joo Hyung.
I love you.
Goodbye.
Na Gyeong,
I love you.
Let's meet again.
I'll wait for you.
(Peace Village to Pyeongyang)
(Two years later in Tokyo, Japan)
(Lim Joo Hyung Piano Recital)
Your room this time is Room 9005.
Here is your passport and card key.
Thank you.
I hope your stay is comfortable.
Welcome.
I'd like to check in, please.
Excuse me,
but what name is the booking under?
Yes?
The concert went well,
and I arrived safely.
I'm in my hotel room now.
I'm having a beer
to maintain my condition.
Joo Hyung, your routine is important.
You know the sponsor
of the foundation is coming, right?
You have to do well.
Hey.
I always insist on
giving my best performance.
I know. You're the best artist I know.
You must be tired.
Go easy and get some rest, okay?
- I'll talk to you later.
- Okay.
Pianist Lim Joo Hyung, I'm a huge fan!
Are you? Thank you.
I'd like an autograph.
Sure.
Thank you. Could you take a photo with me?
Of course.
Thank you.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)