(Love Andante)
(Kwon Hyun Bin)
(Song Ji Woo)
(Heo Ji Won)
(Ki Hyun Woo)
(Hong Jun Ki, Kim Bo Ra)
(Love Andante)
(This series was produced
with the support of MCST, KOCCA,)
(Gangwon-do Province,
and Goseong-gun County.)
A small village
is at the end of this road.
I remember at the beginning of
that village, you can only visit...
once a year.
(Taedonggang Beer)
(Goseong Unification Observation Tower)
The fairytale about a lumberjack
who met his angel originated...
from this small village beside Lake Gamho.
I was there with an unforgettable woman.
(Love Andante Episode 1)
Since declaring the end of the war,
as the South and North came together...
to establish a joint village,
this is historically meaningful.
("Reunification may be possible.")
As the two nations were determined...
to achieve this,
we could glance at the possibility
of reunification shortly.
Did Peace City Village Project...
start with the possibility
of reunification?
Dreams do come true.
The people won't have to wish
for reunification for long...
as their wish will come true.
Also, the world is watching us.
After 70 years,
the South and North will live in harmony
in one village,
which will start friendly reunification
in the Korean Peninsula.
Yes, thank you.
We will now go to the reporter on site.
Let's hear from Reporter Kim Min Sun.
(Residents start moving to Peace Village,
expecting reunification.)
Yes, I'm at the entrance of Peace Village.
Since declaring the end of the war,
the South and North agreed
to establish Peace Village...
and the residents are moving in today.
People are arriving one by one.
Reporter Kim, what is the current mood
in the village?
It's bustling
with the village residents...
who are lightening up the place.
I can't believe
I'm moving into Peace Village.
I'm so excited.
The beach is stunning. It's the best.
(Boardroom of the committee
for friendly reunification of Korea)
After 70 years,
the South and North declared...
to live in the same village.
The whole world watched this moment.
(Peace Village will be run for a year
on a trial basis.)
Rewatching the moment
almost makes me choke up.
It's such a meaningful moment, isn't it?
It's hard for me to believe it, too.
Among the countless applicants
from the South and the North,
I heard ten were picked through AI.
What does the future hold for them?
For now,
they will be living in Peace Village...
on a trial basis for about a year.
If this plan is successful,
the plan is to invite more residents.
With the demarcation line as the border,
the people who led different lives
from one another...
will now become neighbors
with fences between them.
I'm excited to see
how they will embrace each other.
(Congratulations on moving
to Peace Village!)
(Peace Village)
I'm the general manager of Peace Village.
I'm Park Jun Mo.
Yes, give us a brief introduction
of Peace Village.
Sure.
Peace Village is founded
on 33,000-square-meter land...
to facilitate homes and farms
as a self-sufficient village.
Providing a safe, cozy living environment
to the residents is...
Comrade Jun Mo, we have to...
Who is this?
This is Lee Jang Su,
the manager from the North.
Yes.
Please stop calling me "comrade."
Okay.
- Comrade Jun Mo.
- Comrade...
Where was I?
- It was on "cozy living environment."
- Yes.
Providing a cozy living environment...
and making a peaceful village are...
the foremost important purposes.
The Peace Village residents turned
from enemies to comrades.
Now they are reliable neighbors...
who will farm and rehabilitate together...
while promoting an environment
of self-sufficiency.
This is Kim Min Sun
reporting from Peace Village.
The project started,
with a focus on reunification, right?
Yes, that's right.
That's why the success
of the village is crucial.
Until the day the South and North unite!
I'm sure some of our
viewers would hope to...
be able to join Peace Village.
Hopefully,
the project will end successfully...
and bring a positive shift
to the South-North relations.
It's a lot of money
to spend on a single village,
but I'm excited since its success
will bring an earlier reunification.
What would you say
to your family moving to Peace Village?
You're representing South Korea.
Be proud, eat well, and take care.
Are you going to be okay?
Why?
Just about everything bothers you.
Can you stand living out here
in the countryside?
It's a feast of small flies, big flies,
grasshoppers, mosquitoes, and centipedes.
The smell of cow dung and dogs barking
also comes standard with it.
Just give me my luggage.
It's just that I'm seriously worried.
Is this the right solution?
Keeping you here in the middle
of nowhere for a year is...
so cruel to your fans across the world...
as it is to you.
Take care.
Joo Hyung!
- Mr. Lim Joo Hyung!
- Joo Hyung!
- Excuse me, Mr. Lim Joo Hyung!
- Mr. Lim Joo Hyung!
We're sorry! He won't be doing interviews!
Hurry inside.
- Mr. Lim!
- Take his photos!
Salute. Welcome to Peace Village.
I'd like to see your identification.
Can I have your ID?
I need IDs for the movers, too.
(Resident, male, Lim Joo Hyung)
Thank you.
The movers must leave before 3 p.m.
What about our IDs?
As you have been informed,
I'll give it back to you
after you drive out.
You must leave the village before 3 p.m.
They run a tight ship.
We understand.
(Peace Village)
(North entrance to Peace Village)
What's going on here?
What's going on? They're not here yet?
- I guess not.
- What?
They told me they left a while ago.
I don't what happened.
For crying out loud.
Please be careful with that.
You'll break the coffee dripper inside.
Okay.
You can hang that
in the middle of the living room wall.
Right here?
Yes.
You'll hang your photo here?
Yes. Make sure to get the right angle.
(Daffodil)
You can't drop it down like that!
Is it broken?
It was a tiny bump.
Tiny?
This piano is like a living thing.
A tiny scratch on its leg
changes the sound.
You don't know what you're talking about!
Sure thing.
Ignorant people like us wouldn't know.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
You have to move the piano inside.
We're too ignorant to move the piano.
Call someone who is educated.
Are you really leaving?
It's almost 3 p.m. We have to leave.
Bring this inside before you go.
I can't pay you otherwise.
We've already been paid
since we're doing good for the nation.
You can't go.
Go.
Hey!
You can't leave this here!
This is nuts.
I didn't expect to hear the piano
out here in the countryside.
I hear piano music.
Me, too.
I heard a famous pianist
from the South moved in.
I guess it's him.
It sounds so classy.
I almost forgot.
It's about the cell phones
to be used in the village.
All the residents have one, right?
Say no more. It's been done.
The internet of the South is so fast.
Jang Su.
It's the speed from the temporary station.
Don't be too impressed.
If we reunite, there will come a day
for the North Koreans to feel...
the South's formidable
internet speed, right?
It's so fast that you won't feel a thing.
Anyway...
(The file has been sent successfully.)
What's the problem?
The engine is overheated.
My goodness! You're Lim Joo Hyung, right?
You've been called a piano prodigy
since you were in school.
In 2015, you became
the first Korean to win...
the International Chopin
Piano Competition.
After winning, you traveled the world
for seven years...
and became the pianist
with the most performances.
You must be a fan.
Do you want an autograph?
No, I'm okay.
I'm Kim Ju Hui.
I moved behind you.
But what brings you all the way here?
I mean,
others came for the house and benefits,
but you wouldn't need any of those,
so why would you come here?
I can't seem to ignore my curiosity.
I just came to rest.
I see. You must be exhausted.
Hold on! Is this the piano?
Don't touch it without asking.
By any chance, if you have time,
teach me the piano.
I don't give lessons.
You don't teach.
Then I can come over sometimes, right?
He's cool.
Does anyone have a cell phone?
Here you go. Use this.
Is this
the Reunification Promotion Agency?
The bus has stopped.
We're at...
about 10km away from the DMZ
in the direction of Goseong.
We'll send a car, so wait there.
Yes, sir.
They want us to wait for a car.
But it'll take some time.
We're late as it is.
How long do we have to wait?
I wouldn't know for sure.
How much further do we have to go?
We'll reach the entrance in about 10km.
Then let's go.
Bring only the necessities.
Are we walking?
Then should we run?
It'll be chilly after the sunset.
Hurry up.
For crying out loud.
Are things already ruined from the start?
No way. It's not.
What is wrong with you people?
Nothing ever gets done on the dot.
Instead of the girl we invited,
we might see a missile coming instead.
Excuse me.
Why can't you trust our people's republic?
That will never happen.
We keep our words
in our people's republic.
Comrade, I just can't seem to buy that.
My goodness.
Look!
Over there.
What?
Why are you walking here?
The bus broke down. We had to walk.
Please give that to me.
It's fine.
Just bring the others to their homes.
Yes, I will do that.
Come this way.
It's me. Report to the higher-ups
that she just arrived.
Yes.
My feet are all puffy.
No one asked you to come along.
Do you think I came
to protect my fair lady?
It was the Great Assistant's order
to protect his precious daughter.
I'm not a child.
Comrade.
Someone else would have come
even if I hadn't.
Don't you think I'm a safe choice?
Do you think I'm a fool?
If you stay put for a year here,
you'll get to live in Pyeongyang
and have preferential rights to rations.
I know you licked my father's boots.
If it weren't for the benefits,
why would I protect someone
so "kkakkeun" like you?
(Kkakkeun, A North Korean expression
for a consistently frigid person)
You can go now.
Have a good night's rest then.
Bye.
What's this?
(Daffodil)
Ask him what happened.
What's with your eye?
He attacked me first.
An ear for an ear, an eye for an eye!
Why did you stand like a ghost
in a stranger's home?
It's my home!
What are you talking about?
That's my home!
Both of you please calm down.
- Yes.
- Let's see.
- It shouldn't be a big deal.
- Right.
Mr. Lim...
(Lim Joo Hyung, Ha Na Gyeong, Choi Ji Hun)
(Lim Joo Hyung, Ha Na Gyeong, Married)
(Married)
Why does it say...
Well...
One moment, please.
Let us check something quickly.
(Health clinic)
What do we do about this?
She's the daughter of the Great Assistant
of the Military Security Command.
- If they find out...
- Be quiet.
This will cause chaos.
Shouldn't we report this
to the higher-ups...
and find a solution?
I know.
Hey, Jang Su.
Yes?
If this gets out,
you and I might be blamed...
and have to step down.
What?
If that happens,
your chance to live in Pyeongyang
will go out the window.
What was that again?
The right to rations?
You'll lose all that, too.
That can't happen.
I'm the only hope
for my wife and my kids at home.
- Jang Su.
- Yes?
You need to start focusing now...
and just follow my lead, okay?
What do you have in mind?
Look here.
Try to imagine it.
Due to an accidental error, a man
and a woman live in the same house.
Then they look at each other...
and fall in love.
What do you think?
Can't you just picture it?
Yes, I can picture it.
Right?
- Of me being shot to death...
- Shot to death...
Hey, why are you so pessimistic?
Haven't you watched,
"Crash Landing On You?"
I did watch it.
That's what I mean.
Let me see that.
What we should do is...
make the two come together.
- To do that,
- You're right.
- we must put them together.
- That's right.
What happened?
Did you check the system?
Yes, we checked,
but we don't have a solution
at the moment.
No.
To be honest,
there's no place left.
- What?
An error occurred
while grouping the residents.
All the remaining houses have been filled.
What ridiculous nonsense is this?
How can I live with a fully grown man?
Look who's talking.
Seeing her roundhouse kick,
I think she has to be a trained spy.
- She'll poison me while I sleep...
- Excuse me!
- Hold on, Both of you, please calm down.
- Yes.
Frankly,
it is true that this is our mistake.
But what if you see this
in a different light?
Like how?
You two represent the South and North.
If you let go and open your hearts,
this will become the first step
of the South and North's reunification.
But if you report this to the higher-ups,
Peace Village Project might...
go back to square one.
Do you want that?
Instead of the ingenious pianist,
you'll be known as a man who turned
the clock backward for the two Koreas.
Do you want that?
You don't have to be so extreme.
Seriously...
Then about my piano in the front yard,
please move that inside the house.
- Sure.
- We'll do that right now.
- Yes.
- We will.
And about this woman hitting me,
I'll accept this situation
if she sincerely apologizes.
Excuse me.
Apologize?
Apologize for what?
Also, don't speak for me
because I won't go with this!
(Pyeongyang)
Before being my daughter,
you are representing
the party and the people.
Behave yourself accordingly.
Don't worry.
Also, after a year,
you must keep your promise.
If things go wrong, you'll be responsible.
Got it?
Yes, sir!
Father.
Speak.
"Take care."
Can't you just say that?
Fine.
How hard can it be to live with him?
For the party and the people,
I'm more than happy to make sacrifices.
Comrade Na Gyeong,
we can't thank you enough.
You've made the right choice.
Excuse me.
Aren't you going to apologize to me?
About your black eye...
I'm sorry for making it that way.
Was that an apology?
Why did she have to say it like that?
Where's the master room?
What an entitled brat.
He's been all over the world,
yet he's a greedy pig.
How dare he take the master room?
I don't see any clots...
or other issues.
I can't seem to focus my sight.
One second.
Does that hurt?
Were you hit by someone?
No, I fell.
How did you get a black eye by falling?
Shouldn't I go to a bigger hospital?
It was such a big blow.
Usually, big blows hurt.
I wasn't hit! I fell!
Isn't that a crack?
It's fine.
Wait, this isn't it.
So is this how it's going to be?
No way. It can't be.
What are you doing?
Well...
What is it?
You know,
this is my room.
You didn't even say a word.
It's rude to swap rooms this way.
And you're so polite
that you touch other people's stuff?
Well, that's...
Forget it. Just come out.
I have to change.
Be polite and leave.
This is crazy.
I don't even have a bed.
Sleeping in a new place
makes me toss and turn.
One lamb.
Two lambs.
Lambs...
Why would you embarrass yourself
by taking off your shirt?
South Korean boys are weak.
I want to show them how manly the men
of our people's republic are.
How pointless.
Will you be okay?
With what?
About that guy.
He managed to bring the piano here.
He doesn't seem typical.
Will you be okay?
You can mind your own business.
How can I do that?
My business is protecting you.
You won't have much to do.
But don't we need to report this
to the party?
Hello!
It's the second day in Peace Village.
I met two North Korean residents
during my morning walk.
Wave at me, please!
Peace!
Comrade Gyeong Ho, aren't you coming?
I'm coming.
How cool.
My lower back hurts. My upper back hurts.
If I don't sleep on the bed,
I'll break my back at this rate.
What man has such a weak back?
Excuse me.
This is all because of you!
She's really pushing it.
That scared me.
Comrade Joo Hyung, are you awake?
I came to bring in the piano.
A little to the left.
No, you went too far.
Go about 12cm to the left.
Twelve...
No.
Move it about 5cm this way.
Five centimeters...
That's good. Put it down.
Yes.
Are we good?
One second.
Come on.
What's going on? Are we done or what?
It seems just a bit off...
but it's okay enough for what it is.
We did it!
Attention, Peace Village residents!
(Peace Village General Manager
Park Jun Mo)
To all the residents
who moved into Peace Village,
we welcome you.
It's just that...
we have a welcoming party tonight
to celebrate your moving in.
- We'll have a meet and greet.
- Hello.
Hello.
It'll be held in the front yard...
of the world-famous pianist,
Mr. Lim Joo Hyung.
It starts at 5 p.m.
Every single one of you must come.
What's this nonsense?
We have good food, sweets,
and a small amount of alcohol as well.
You can show up casually,
but if you can gather on time,
we would appreciate it.
Do we have a celebration today?
Also,
Mr. Lim Joo Hyung from the South
will play the piano.
Ms. Ha Na Gyeong from the North
will play the violin.
Every single one of you must come.
Thank you.
Then don't we have to
bring out the piano again?
We barely got it inside, too.
This is like dog training.
Who said you can throw a party here?
Play the piano? Really?
Seriously...
Woo Bin.
Mark the location of the piano legs.
- Yes, sir.
We have to move this again.
There's a party today,
so I'm picking out clothes for the TPO.
Which one would look good?
The first one.
The second one.
They're both pretty.
Should I take a look at others, too?
Mr. Park.
What are you doing?
You didn't discuss the party with me.
Why did you announce that
I'll play the piano?
Are we in a communist country here?
No, it's not that...
Our people's republic
doesn't do things this way.
Is this how things are handled
in the South?
You don't discuss anything
or ask for an opinion.
This one-way announcement is unethical!
She's right. This is unethical.
(Epilogue
MOU Peace Village Project)
- Brush it off!
- What?
Brush off the keyboard!
Brush it off!
- Yes, brush it off.
- I brushed it off.
I did it.
(Do you want to register a spouse?)
(The registration is complete.)
(Lim Joo Hyung and Ha Na Gyeong
are registered as married.)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)