(This series was produced
with the support of MCST, KOCCA,)
(Gangwon-do Province,
and Goseong-gun County.)
You might have killed Mr. Piano.
He's so weak.
He can barely be a man.
It's probably because it's his first day.
I don't think he can make it tomorrow.
I have to stop by the shop.
Go ahead.
This is Peace Village Mart.
They have a variety of products
and fresh food.
Hello.
Big sister! Can I call you that?
Sure.
When are you due?
Tong Il is due sometime in October.
Tong Il must be his fetal nickname.
Are you having a son?
Yes, it's a son.
Big sister.
Eat these eggs.
Cage-free fertilized eggs.
You have to eat well when you're pregnant.
Try this, too.
It's a meal kit
made with 100 percent Korean produce.
It's popular these days.
I've tried that. I highly recommend it.
Am I in the video, too?
Yes, you can watch it
on my social media account later.
Hello.
Welcome, Gyeong Ho.
It's really good.
You have to try it.
Is that so?
(Love Andante Episode 4)
Do you want instant noodles?
No thanks.
Who refuses instant noodles?
Instant food is unhealthy.
It makes your hands and face puffy
in the morning.
Speaking like a true brat
who was served food on a silver platter.
What did you say?
If you don't want to eat it, it's fine.
Do you want a bite?
If you insist,
maybe I'll eat it just for today.
Is the village doing well?
The system is stabilizing.
Do the villagers get along?
Yes, based on the last few months,
they get along peacefully
without clashing.
That's a relief.
How is Na Gyeong doing?
Her research is making good progress.
There's no issue.
Okay, keep on observing well.
Yes, I will,
Great Assistant.
He looks fine outside,
but he's weak inside.
- Hello.
- Woo Bin, help her.
- You're carrying a child. Come this way.
- Thank you.
Yes, good job.
Did you get a checkup at the clinic?
No, not yet.
You should get a checkup today if you can.
They provide supplements
to pregnant women for free.
I'm sure they also offer other benefits.
- I was going to go today.
- That's good.
Please take her today.
- I will.
- Okay.
Let's go.
My back hurts.
Did I sleep on the sofa?
She totally got me yesterday.
But who brought this blanket?
She couldn't have...
Are you going to the Olympics?
What are you talking about?
Comrade Na Gyeong,
you're not yourself these days.
You're distracted.
Don't be ridiculous.
Don't you know how sharp I am?
You can't lie to me.
You must have been slacking
for the last four months,
being observant of others.
Don't be too harsh on me.
You can keep that mouth shut.
Is something going on
between Mr. Piano and you?
Nothing's going on.
Comrade Na Gyeong,
do you and Mr. Piano like each other?
Are you crazy?
Your eyes change
when you look at Mr. Piano.
Don't be so nosy.
Comrade Na Gyeong,
don't be offended
and just tell me the truth.
Tell you what?
Comrade.
Do you like Mr. Piano?
No, I don't.
Then why do you bicker like
you're at each other's throats?
You fight like a cat and a dog
that want to kill each other.
I never asked for this much attention.
Comrade.
When you open your heart to someone,
you have to think carefully
and think again...
Run!
Where's the first aid kit?
Why are you running like crazy?
Like you said, I'm going to the Olympics.
What?
Comrade, take it easy.
I'm leaving.
Isn't that Comrade Na Gyeong?
Why is she running like crazy?
I heard losing weight is the trend.
I guess Comrade Na Gyeong
is trying to lose weight, too.
Is that so?
My mother would love this.
Yes, you have to tell her I bought it.
Okay, I will.
If I use the post train
to Pyeongyang tomorrow,
my mother will receive it
in seven days, right?
I'm sure.
- Is your mother well?
- She's well.
Do you like Mr. Piano?
(Health Clinic)
Hello.
You're early today.
It must be the clear air here.
My eyes get wide open when the sun is up.
But what's all this?
I saw beautiful wildflowers on the way.
They're pretty.
We could call the clinic the flower shop.
Are these mini chrysanthemums?
No, this is sweet wormwood.
In Korean medicine,
it's used for fever, cold, dysentery,
malaria, children's seizures,
and indigestion.
Really?
Smell this.
This native herb is called...
the Korean mint.
Just like its name,
it deodorizes the air.
In Korean medicine,
it's called "kwakhyang."
It's used for gastrointestinal diseases
like indigestion and diarrhea.
Its dried leaves can make tea.
It's an all-rounder herb.
What's that willowy flower there?
That's "chamchwi."
Chamchi?
It's chamchwi, a friend of gomchi.
It's fragrant and it has warm properties.
It's eaten as salad
since it's full of vitamins and minerals.
It helps the blood circulation.
It can be used for colds,
pharyngitis, and headaches.
When the acid inside meets calcium,
it's highly possible to create stones.
You parboil it instead of eating it raw.
I see.
What about that gomchi?
It was named "gomchi"
since bears in the forest eat it.
It's tasty and fragrant,
so you eat it raw...
or make it into a pickle.
The Korean medicine uses
the root and stem...
for coughs, whooping cough, asthma,
back pain, joint pain, or contusion.
I see.
Is something on my face?
Yes.
For you, who is serious
about studying home remedies,
I'll buy morning coffee.
- Do you want it sweet?
- Yes.
Do you need...
any help?
The left or right side?
Both sides.
Is that good?
Thanks.
How's the baby?
The baby is slightly smaller
considering the number of months.
But you shouldn't worry too much.
If you eat well, sleep well,
and exercise moderately, it'll be fine.
Babies feel at ease when moms do.
Okay.
Do you take any medications
or supplements?
I don't exactly take such...
No.
I'll give you some for the baby and you.
Make sure to take them.
It'll be better
if you get regular checkups.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
When you wake up,
have the porridge and medicine.
I must be crazy.
Get a hold of yourself.
(Comrade Gyeong Ho)
Where are you?
I'm at home.
Why are you still at home?
I'm going out now. Bye.
That looks good.
You're here.
Gyeong Ho, did you eat?
I'll eat later.
You should eat with us.
It's barley bibimbap. It's really good.
Okay.
- Come along.
- Okay.
What took you so long?
Something came up.
What came up?
What are you thinking?
My job is to protect you.
Of course, I have to ask...
- He's bedridden...
- Are you sick?
Let's go straight to the clinic...
Simmer down.
It's not me. It's Mr. Piano.
When you wake up,
have the porridge and medicine.
How was she able to make this?
It tastes like nothing.
How can this be possible?
It's salty.
It's so salty.
This is...
Who is going to clean all this?
My back hurts.
Can you lower the volume?
How can you play a game without sound?
This is the lowest volume.
I can't focus because of that sound!
Your head is filled...
with thoughts other than your paper.
That's why this sound is distracting.
Are you trying to instigate me?
Let's go home.
When have you ever clocked out on time?
When you're in Peace Village,
you have to follow the system here...
Just leave.
Go and enjoy your evening.
Comrade.
If something comes up,
call me on my cell phone immediately.
Okay, now go.
The watermelon this year
is sweet like honey.
It's the best
out of all the watermelons I've eaten.
We're lucky to be here
to have this precious fruit.
Ki Nam, take some to Tong Il's family.
Yes, it must be hard for the lady
to step outside. Give some to her.
Yes, I'll bring some for them.
Should I go with you?
Woo Bin, you can stay. I'll be quick.
- Did you have watermelon in the North?
- Yes, I did.
You better be quick
since one person is missing.
It has so many seeds.
- Spit out the seeds.
- Did you just swear at me?
The heat patch smells bad.
(Peace Village)
What's going on?
If someone asks me where I'm from
I tell them I'm from Busan
That's our manager.
Are you out for a stroll?
Yes, I guess.
I told you.
You get bored just staying at home.
You should come out to meet people.
You can help others. How great is that?
I'm okay. I can keep myself company.
What?
Do you have something you want to say?
No, I don't.
Mr. Lim.
When you came here,
what did you have in your mind?
I've never stayed in one city
for more than seven days.
Why not?
It's the concerts.
I feel pushed all the time.
It makes me sick.
I feel like hiding somewhere just to rest.
I'm sure.
Traveling nonstop like that
would tire your body and soul.
Yes.
The more time passes, the emptier I feel.
I was getting exhausted.
Mr. Lim,
why do you think villagers came here?
Have you thought about that?
No.
Maybe they came
for the benefits that they wanted?
Mr. Lim,
this village blossoms with new hope.
Some felt their lives were so dry,
being so busy without a second to breathe.
Some people want a fresh start.
(Lim Joo Hyung Piano Recital)
Some want to hide
from the sight of others...
to avoid being talked about by people,
so they came here, just like you.
Hello, I'm Ju Hui.
I'm on the Myeongdong street.
Some got hurt
by their family's expectations.
They get to be free...
and pursue their aspirations.
But from the North,
some want lives that are a little better
than their current ones.
Wanting an environment
where their family can stay full,
they came here to create that.
To give a better world to their child,
a couple came with a baby inside, too.
With a small hope of treating
whoever is sick...
whenever he wants, a doctor came, too.
Once we develop the new species,
our people will have corn
to their hearts' content.
With more people hungry and worrying
about putting food on the table,
Na Gyeong came here...
to resolve the food shortage.
This is...
where people came with their own stories.
Their stories...
Our villagers want...
Peace Village to be maintained smoothly.
They might be a little sensitive.
They might be a little generous, too.
Those are the people that came here.
So try to get along together,
work at the joint farms,
and have meals with them.
I think it'll be nice for you
to open your heart.
What is there to ponder?
What?
Mr. Lim, aren't you lonely?
I've always been alone.
See?
You're hurt inside,
but you can't even feel it.
I can't?
Forget the Lim Joo Hyung
from outside the village.
Hang out with the people.
Mingle with them.
It'll definitely help.
(My lovely daughter)
My gosh, I'm getting a call.
Just a moment.
Hi, sweetie.
Yes, it's me.
I see.
Was everything good at school?
Okay.
Okay, what about Mom?
Yes, of course.
I miss you, too.
Okay.
That's hot!
You have to cool it down first.
Did you have to go "michugai" like that?
Do you need any help?
Is that good?
Thanks.
- What are you doing alone?
- My goodness!
What are you doing here?
Are you having fun,
scaring me like a burglar?
Wait.
I'm sorry if I scared you,
but I have a question.
What is it?
What did you do
to make the porridge taste like that?
I guess it was to your liking.
No.
It couldn't have tasted any worse.
What?
I felt all better after eating it,
so you must have put something in it.
My gosh.
I can tell you're still sick,
listening to your silly joke.
Go and rest.
Hey.
Thank you...
for putting a blanket and wet towel on me.
Thank you for everything.
Also, I really wanted to say this.
For showing up in front of me,
I thank you.
See you later.
Did she not see me?
There's no way.
What?
Excuse me.
Push the car.
What?
The battery is dead.
Let's push it to the charging station.
I'm only helping you
since I was born a nice guy.
Try to push stronger.
I'm pushing it!
Look up there.
(Epilogue)
The two look so serious late at night.
That's not being serious.
That's young passion.
- They're locking lips!
- "Locking lips?"
Come on. They're not wrestling.
Hey, let's go.
We should pretend
that we never saw this type of thing.
Let's go.
Blow it harder!
Do you still feel it?
Try to blink a few times.
It's still there.
It's out now.
How did you do it?
It was nothing special.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)