Master Qi Lu, happy birthday.
-Happy birthday.
-Thanks.
Thank you.
-Happy birthday.
-This way please.
-Thanks.
Qi Lu, this is for you.
Thanks.
Xin Wei picked the gift herself.
Cheers.
Thanks.
Why didn't Chu Xia come today?
She lives here, right?
I didn't see her.
Have you done it?
Done.
Done it?
This should be
the best gift in his life.
Is it?
I think this is because
they are not as poor as me.
Can you make one for me?
Anytime.
Why not today?
No way.
Master Han will get mad if I'm late.
-Lady first.
-Thank you.
[Master Devil Do Not Kiss Me]
[Episode 12]
Young master.
It's about the time.
But Master Ling and
Ms. Chu Xia have not come yet.
Han, are you hungry?
-I can wait.
-Take it easy then.
-Master Ling.
-Uncle Han.
It's good to see you.
Master Han is so worried.
We've been waiting for so long.
You are a chatterbox.
I didn't wait for you.
That's right.
Shall we start?
Let's start.
This way please.
Hi, everyone!
Thank you so much for
attending my birthday party today.
In fact, I hold a party every year. Just
the people who attend it are different.
Like someone would walk into my world
while some people go out of my world
Like the stars, some will fall
and some are new.
Excuse me that I've talked a lot.
So, I'd like to thank the person
who gives me all the world.
Dear Sis Yuan Yuan.
And...
And you who have come into my world.
Thank you.
Really?
What are you talking about?
I'm asking Chu Xia what
kind of gift she will give you.
What about you?
Didn't you bring anything for me?
I will give it to you in the end.
Let's see what Chu Xia brings.
I told you, she doesn't need
to prepare anything for me.
Busybody.
Forget it then.
So boring. Don't just chat here.
Any idea?
Let's play "Truth or Dare"
-That's good.
-I'll pass.
It's boring to stay in a room alone.
Today is Qi Lu's birthday.
Don't be a wet blanket.
It's up to you.
Let's continue.
Let's go.
Let's fool An Chu Xia.
-The hall is grand.
-Let's go there.
Where are you going?
Enjoy yourselves, I'll go over there.
Let's play together.
An Chu Xia.
Why don't you play with us?
Are you afraid of the Truth or Dare?
I guess you dare not play with us
because you're a maid.
Let's start the game,
Mo Xin Wei's slave.
Come on.
Let's go.
It's fun.
Master Han, have a seat.
Alright, let's play the dice.
If you get 6, you have to
choose either Truth or Dare.
-Come on.
-Me first.
Alright.
I'm so unlucky!
The first round doesn't count.
Let's start the game now.
That's so kind of you.
I'm willing to do everything
for you in my next life.
Let's discuss in our next life.
Alright, next round.
Truth!
Well...
Chu Xia will ask you a question.
-Me?
-Because you sit at the first place.
Come on.
Well, Mo Xin Wei,
I'm asking you a private question.
Mind your word.
Do you like
green peppers?
What a private question.
I don't like it.
Congratulations, you passed it.
Next round.
Come on.
Truth or Dare?
Dare.
You know no one wants
to hear your truth, huh?
People who don't want
to befriend you will choose Dare.
Kiss a person of opposite sex.
Han Yu, you should help Chu Xia.
You are a coward.
May I have the pleasure?
Kissing Master Ling
is not a daring action.
Unless you dare to kiss Master Han.
She dares not.
I'll have some wine.
That's good.
You only dare to drink wine.
How much do you want to drink?
A whole bottle.
Here you are. Bottoms up!
Drink it.
What now? Drink it!
So lame.
What's going on?
I dare to do so!
I did it!
It's good that Little Chu Xia
finally takes her step.
God blessed.
Let's start the next round.
Qi Lu, your turn.
Dare.
Forget it.
Master Han plays a Dare, huh?
It will be really a Dare.
Okay.
I'll spare you for once.
I choose Truth.
Chu Xia won in the last round.
Chu Xia, ask him a question.
When people were talking about you,
there was a person
they couldn't tell the name.
Who's that?
She'll be finished.
Chu Xia, ask another question.
Okay.
I'll ask another question.
What's her name?
Stupid.
I don't know.
Liar! How could you not know?
How can you not know
since they know it?
Qi Lu.
Qi Lu, wait a moment.
You told her about it?
No.
I know it's your taboo, I won't tell.
Looks like you've never left it behind.
I've forgotten her.
If that's the case, just forgive her.
Chu Xia didn't mean it.
Chu Xia.
You guys just looked alright.
Why did he suddenly get mad?
Did you bite his tongue
when you're kissing?
An Chu Xia.
You caused trouble again.
She always causes troubles.
Do you know why Qi Lu is angry?
I don't want to know.
It was just a game. Take it easy.
How did your mother die?
She must have suffered.
-Mo Xin Wei!
-I am sorry.
I just want you to know the pain
of being scarred by someone else.
The three taboos
are forever pain for Qi Lu.
I'll apologize to him.
Not every apology will work.
The holes are still there even if
you pull the nail out from the wall.
So what should I do now?
Maybe
I can help you.
Don't help her!
I'm willing to do anything
to make Qi Lu happy.
Sing "Little Star" for him.
It's a very important song for Qi Lu.
He'll be happy if you sing it.
I don't usually help everyone.
It's up to you.
Let's go.
Today is your birthday.
Please do me a favor and forgive her.
Forgive her?
Unless she comes to me
and begs me in person.
It means you are no longer angry.
Ling Han Yu.
How can you side with her?
No, I stand for justice.
Let's go to your room
and see the gift I brought you.
Only this time. I'll give you face.
Qi Lu, wait!
Twinkle twinkle little star.
How I wonder what you are.
Up above the world so high.
Like a diamond in the sky.
I thought I was the worst singer in the world.
How I wonder what you are.
Up above the world so high.
Like a diamond in the sky.
Why did you sing this song?
Han Qi Lu, are you crazy?
Qi Lu.
Why did you sing this song?
You don't deserve it
Qi Lu, calm down.
Chu Xia doesn't know about it.
Why must you sing this song?
Chu Xia, did someone
ask you to sing this song?
Mo Xin Wei.
Qi Lu.
This has nothing to do with me.
I won't do something that makes you sad.
Mo Xin Wei, what a hypocrite!
It was you who asked Chu Xia
to sing the song.
I am the witness.
Everybody knows you have
a good relationship with Chu Xia.
But you can't frame me.
Mo Xin Wei! Just admit it!
-Come on.
-Help her.
Cover with the towel.
What's going on here?
Little Chu Xia, what happened to you?
You were okay just now.
Who did this?
I don't know.
Come on.
You have gone too far.
Little Chu Xia, don't worry.
I'll surely stand up for you.
Aunt, you can't blame Qi Lu.
-It was...
-Enough.
Not your concern.
The party is over!
Leave!
An Chu Xia is finished.
Thank you for coming.