Han Qi Lu.
Han Qi Lu!
Are you sick?
They reminded us not to beat people!
You're the Master Devil.
Not just anyone else.
Are you okay?
Just a few punches.
Of course I'm fine.
Don't rub it, or it'll be swollen.
I'm sorry.
What did you say?
Nothing, forget it.
Let's find some clues.
How do we find since it is dark?
Change the spotlight
to astigmatism
so that we can see a little more clearly.
Wait here.
Han Qi Lu.
Han Qi Lu!
Mamma mia!
It's beautiful.
This is my treasured photo of the stars.
So beautiful.
What were you thinking?
Nothing.
It's so stuffy here.
Are you hungry?
I mean, are you feeling hot?
Why don't you take off the clothes?
Bah!
Forget it.
It's up to you.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
Chu Xia.
Chu Xia, wait for me.
[Master Devil Do Not Kiss Me S1]
[Episode 22]
Little Chu Xia!
Come here!
Come on!
I heard you took part
in the Campus Beauty Contest.
Why didn't you tell me?
It's not a big deal.
I might be eliminated
in the first round.
I'm always with you. Don't be afraid.
I used to be a beauty pageant.
At that time,
there were many people.
I was the most outstanding person
among all the participants.
Thousands of men
adored me after the contest.
And I was so hot all over
the streets in a night.
To commemorate that glorious history,
they gave me a nice name for that story.
"The girl we've been
running after together".
Sis Yuan Yuan...
Don't worry.
With my proficient skill,
even if you look so ugly,
I'll make sure you win.
Thank you, Sis Yuan Yuan.
It's alright.
I am well-prepared.
Really?
You just have to support me spiritually.
Go for it!
My bread's burning.
Get some clothes from me later!
Do you have any emollient milk?
Hey!
I'm coming in.
Where is she?
I have a little donkey
that I never ride.
One day I feel like riding it...
Han Qi Lu! You pervert!
I can't believe you are a freak!
It's not what you think.
Don't misunderstand!
You pervert!
What a rude girl!
I'm here to take...
Oh, my God!
Go on and play safe.
I've been caught.
Sorry.
The cat food basin is broken.
I've fixed it for you.
Thank you.
What's your name?
Look at there.
You two...
No...
Chu Xia.
We are...
I'm sorry, Chu Xia
Say it properly!
We are...
We are together now.
-Well...
-Sis!
Thank you.
Finally someone's
willing to accept Feng Shao.
I hope you two get along well,
don't quarrel or fight.
-Don't use weapon.
-Alright.
Why did you text me? Is there anything?
What's wrong? Anything's eating you?
Don't mention it.
It's all because of
the Campus Beauty Contest.
I don't know how to prepare for it.
So easy.
Don't forget.
You're a big shareholder
in our barber shop.
We'll support you.
I'll take care of your styling.
I'll make you the coolest hairstyle
of Paris Fashion Week.
Okay?
The back must be particularly pomp.
Not like her.
Her hair looks like instant noodles.
I'll blow it pomp with the hair dryer.
-And the front...
-That's enough.
I shouldn't make a reckless decision.
It's not like you.
Think about your beauty and my skill.
It's a sure-win for you!
I don't have beauty,
and you are not skilled.
I need some quietness (Jing Jing).
Who's Jing Jing (quiet)?
It's vulgar to ask for my name.
I have an even more vulgarer request.
When shall we meet?
-Thank you.
-Not at all.
Is the cat walk specially
designed by Chu Xia?
It's too special.
What's wrong?
Chu Xia! Chu Xia! Chu Xia! Chu Xia!
Chu Xia! Go for it!
Chu Xia, we believe in you.
Go for it! Go for it!
I let my father transfer me to here.
Don't do that to her!
Mr. Ma, don't kick Chu Xia out.
Here you are.
It hurts.
As long as you stay here,
I'll give you a hard time.