♪So let this song♪
♪Repeat all night♪
♪We are not at fault♪
♪It's just we now see what we couldn't
understand♪
♪There's nothing to say♪
♪Let's talk some other time♪
♪Let us stay silent♪
♪When the memories are triggered♪
♪How do we stop the tears? Don't let her
cry her heart out♪
♪The situation leads to associations, is
this ok?♪
♪From now on we go our separate ways♪
♪I have your tattoo left on my body♪
♪How could I not care?♪
♪The present is not to blame,
but the past♪
♪Who let whom down? Confused♪
♪Are you sober now? The more you drink
the less you get drunk♪
♪Went around in a circle, yet
I miss them more♪
♪Who won't you let go? Is the
movie over yet?♪
Stop singing!
Come with me.
Come on, let's go.
I had so much fun singing.
Why did you drag me here?
Others sing to earn money.
You sing to kill lives.
If you want to vent your emotions,
this is the perfect place.
You're from Stiland?
I'm form Stiland's class B,
the one who never changes her name,
An Chu Xia.
So even Stiland has students
who are this brainless?
Stand up from where you fell down.
Jiang Chen Chuan,
you can do it!
What do you want to play?
Tell me.
But... this is too easy.
Give me something more challenging.
Actually, as someone
who is invincible at arcades
everything here is too easy.
I chose this one
carefully on the basis of your
intelligence.
Let me teach you.
First,
take two coins.
Then throw them in.
Take one ball,
and throw it!
Are you alright?
I'm fine!
It slipped from my hands.
One more.
Why don't you let me?
No, thanks! Move!
Invincible?
Stop hurting yourself.
Let's play something else.
No!
I refuse to believe
that I won't manage to throw in
a single ball today.
Hey, but,
wasn't it your goal to help me
vent my emotions?
Why get angry with a ball?
I hate that ball!
You hate it?
Yeah.
Better now?
Yeah!
You still hate them?
I do!
Alright.
=Master Devil Do Not Kiss Me S2=
=Episode 20=
Never thought you could play drums so well.
Are you kidding me?
It's just singing I'm bad at.
As for drums,
I went behind my dad's back to learn it
for a couple of years.
Why go behind his back?
My dad wants me to study economics,
so I can inherit his business.
Since I was little,
he put an end to
any hobbies I had aside from
business.
You poor thing.
Actually,
I've always had this dream
that when I retire,
I'll start a band.
Others go to live in nursing homes and play
Mahjong when they're old.
When I'm old, I'll go to nursing homes
to give concerts.
When you are old, you won't even be able
to hold the drum sticks,
let alone give a concert.
Bullshit.
Jiang Chen Chuan.
You should start a band now.
I support you.
Let's go.
Han Qi Lu?
Han Qi Lu, are you home?
♪Happy Birthday to you♪
Chu Xia.
Happy birthday.
Let's go over there.
Make a wish.
Ok.
Done. I'll go turn on the lights.
Oh, wait.
This is my present for you.
It's so cute.
Is it a table lamp?
It's a wishing light.
A wishing light?
Yes.
With this
you won't need to blow out candles
on your birthday again,
waiting to make a wish.
Thank you, Qi Lu.
But I don't have that many wishes,
let alone one for every day.
You do.
For example, you can wish for
seeing me every day.
Huh?
Yes.
And it will come true every time.
How great is that?
Alright.
Let's talk seriously.
Chu Xia.
Tomorrow is a big day for your competition.
I wish you success.
Thanks.
Chu Xia.
It doesn't matter whether I'll see you
every day or not,
I hope that every time I see you
you're happy
and content,
without any worries,
just like the first time I saw you.
Ok.
Hey.
Why didn't you turn on the lights?
Sister Yuan.
Why didn't you tell us you were
coming home?
Your Sister Yuan knew that it's
Little Chu Xia's birthday today.
She had me leave the hospital sooner
so we can give you a surprise.
Are you surprised, Little Chu Xia?
Who bought this cake?
What do you mean, bought?
I made it.
Wow.
No wonder it's so ugly.
My son can bake cakes now?
Thank you, Sister Yuan.
Thank you, Brother Liu.
Thank you, Uncle Han.
You remembered my birthday.
Of course,
we are family.
Your Sister Yuan not only knows
your birthday,
she also knows that tomorrow is an important
day for you competition.
Little Chu Xia.
Here.
This is for you.
It's fine, Brother Liu.
You are too nice.
Oh, don't treat me like an outsider.
Time was limited.
I didn't have time to prepare a present.
So I
had to do with poor taste this time.
Ok.
It is also a little gift of your mother.
Please take it.
Thank you, Brother Liu.
It tastes really bad.
Old Han...
Come!
Er, eat the cake I bought.
Come on.
Old Han, go,
go get your chips
and soft drinks, let everyone
have a taste.
Alright.
This is so pretty.
Actually, my cake is quite pretty, too.
Today
we're doing a home party at home.
-What do you say?
-Careful.
Oh right.
Listen,
er, Brother Liu just got a call.
They say that
our company's financing has been
successful.
Our company has overcome all obstacles now.
Really?
Yes.
Qi Lu,
you are free now.
Come.
♪Happy Birthday to you♪
Hello?
Are you clear on what needs to be done?
Ok, got it.
Xiang Man Kui.
I finally know why you want to
come back.
Dad.
Xin Wei, you aren't asleep yet?
Xin Wei.
I want to talk to you.
There's nothing to talk about.
I understand what you're feeling.
But I hope you can understand
that the result of this competition
isn't important.
What's important
is that you're still my good daughter.
Dad!
I want to sleep.
Then sleep well.
Alright, dear teachers,
dear students and our friends
from the media,
welcome to the finale of the Pinkston Youth
Design Competition!
The final will soon be kicked off.
The contestants standing on the stage
right now are our finalists.
One of them will
get the chance to study at
Pinkston College in France.
Next, let us welcome last year's
champion,
this year's special judge,
and our most highly anticipated
new designer Ms. Xiang
to the stage to announce
the rules of the competition!
Welcome.
For the last round,
the contestants will be taken to
a special working space
to create a piece that will reflect
their skill level in three days.
Alright, thank you. Thank you,
Ms. Xiang.
It means that all of our contestants will
complete their work
in a closed environment.
All communication devices,
such as mobile phones and computers,
are forbidden in this space.
This is also the only difference from our
previous competition system.
They will complete their work in a closed
environment independently.
Of course, as our senior,
I believe that Ms. Xiang must have some
high expectations for this year's
contestants.
Is there anything you'd like to
say to them?
I believe that every contestant
who comes on to this stage
is full of dreams and enthusiasm,
so I hope that this competition will be
absolutely fair,
professional,
and pure.
I believe that every contestant has
their own imagination,
so
you can do it!
Alright, thank you.
Thank you so much, Ms. Xiang.
That gave us high hopes for the
contestants
and cheered them up.
Alright,
now let our contestants enter
the competition area!
Please guide the way.
Wait.
I would like to ask Ms. Xiang
a question.
As a talented young designer,
why haven’t you had anything new released
for half a year?
Have you used up your talent and energy,
or is there another reason?
Please answer my question.
Mo Xin Wei. You're going too far!
Am I?
I just wish to learn from my senior
from a newcomer's perspective.
As a designer,
your work doesn't create itself
overnight.
I haven't released anything new
this half year,
I've let down the people
who have been following me.
But I will slowly get myself back into form,
and let my work speak for me
as quickly as possible.
Did you find out something?
-What did I find out?
-Stop playing stupid.
An Chu Xia, remember this.
As long as I'm here,
you and your dead mom will never step foot
in the Jiang family's home.
I won't hold back
when I step on you.
Cheer up.
It's so hot.
I mean really,
how can they just close without giving you
notice in advance?
I haven't prepared anything for you.
But I'm sure
that you will win.
Hey,
it's just a competition.
Why make it seem like a life and
death situation?
You're ruining the mood.
Sister Yuan, don't worry,
I will give my best.
-Go for it.
Chu Xia!
It's time! We need to set out
to the working space now.
We'll be late if we don't go now!
Have you seen Mo Xin Wei?
She's the only one left.
Call her!
I did, she doesn't pick up!
Call Wan Zi.
They are very close. Maybe they
are together.
Ok.
An Chu Xia,
hurry up!
I'm coming.
I'm off.
Good luck.
Hey, Chu Xia.
Give your best.
Don't be nervous.
Ok.
Go.
Did you find Xin Wei or not?
Xin Wei?
Are you clear on what needs to be done?
I asked you a question.
Don't talk to me in this tone.
Why didn't you go to cheer on Chu Xia?
I'm giving you a chance to shine.
Stop it.
I just think that
Chu Xia needs to stay calm at such a time.
Let her think
what the competition means to her.
What does she want?
I always have the feeling that
you've changed
after you came back.
Really?
How?
It's difficult to say.
I just think that you became sharper.
More attractive maybe.
I gotta tell you first,
I'm not interested in men.
Since when did you become like
Jiang Chen Chuan?
So arrogant and narcissistic.
Jiang Chen Chuan...
What a surprise.
He's Chu Xia's cousin.
Yeah.
This matter...
must have affected him a lot.
Yeah.
We are in the same boat now.
You gotta understand that
our common enemy is An Chu Xia!
Today I will make her fail and unable to
ever recover, no matter how.
I know what you are planning.
Oh,
the Jiang family has been
flooded with scandals lately.
You...
But,
you were right about something.
I won't
let An Chu Xia off the hook.
That's why
we can't have Xiang Man Kui appear at the
final round tomorrow.
Ok,
I understand.