Madam.
You have a guest.
Uncle.
Aunt.
I invited Little Kui.
Come, Little Kui, sit here.
Listen,
today's competition was all thanks
to Little Kui.
Come.
Little Kui.
Let me
toast to you.
I was extremely petty before.
Please forgive me.
-Come.
-Thank you, aunt.
Little Kui.
Has your hand gotten better?
Actually, it's not that serious.
I will be able to draw
again after a while.
So you don't have to worry about me.
Little Kui.
Remember,
the Han family's doors will always
be open for you.
We are a family.
Thank you, uncle.
Come, cheers!
Let us get drunk tonight!
Thank you.
You said that 100 times already today.
But I still want to say it.
If it weren't for you,
I'd have become a plagiarist.
I'd never be able to turn my life around.
Actually,
you only had to say
that Xiang Man Kui's hands are broken
and will never be able to draw again,
then everything would have been solved.
But I promised you
not to tell anyone.
That's why I came to help you.
Chu Xia.
Actually it was you who helped yourself.
Oh right,
don't talk about me,
let's talk about you.
What's there to talk about?
You're going to Pinkston next week.
What are you and Qi Lu going to do?
I don't know.
If you let me choose again,
I think I'd still go to France.
Pinkston is too tempting to me.
It's the paradise for every designer.
It's just,
my only regret is
that back then I thought...
I didn't have to explain it to Qi Lu
for him to understand me.
I was too self-confident.
I thought it didn't matter
how much I hurt him,
he'd always wait for me.
Don't misunderstand.
I'm not telling you all this
to drive you away
and seize the chance to get Qi Lu back.
I already gave it up.
I know.
Chu Xia.
I just hope that you can hold on to
the most important things,
unlike me.
Go talk to Qi Lu.
He will understand you.
Ok,
I will.
Xiang Man Kui.
Let me tell you a secret,
Actually,
I'm your big fan.
Are you serious?
I have a collection of all your works.
Did you not make your feelings clear
to Qi Lu because
you're secretly in love with me?
What are you talking about?
Actually, I'm the same.
What?
Chu Xia,
the truth is I've always admired you.
Your talent,
your perseverance.
I'm sure that we will one day
become enemies again.
But this time as designers.
When that day comes,
I won't go easy on you.
Me neither.
=Master Devil Do Not Kiss Me S2=
=Episode 23=
Chu Xia!
I need to talk to you.
What are you doing here?
I've been waiting for you.
Are you by yourself?
There are some things
we can only talk about in private.
Let's have a good talk.
There's nothing to talk about.
What if it's about Han Qi Lu?
What do you mean?
Here,
let's make a deal.
I can help the Han family,
help them out of their crisis.
Isn't that what you want, too?
You've been inquiring about me.
I'm sorry.
I had to do so.
Has anyone told you
that I'm the legal representative
of the company the Han family
is doing business with right now?
How is that possible?
You...
The Jiang family has many companies
under their flag,
distributed under the name
of different shareholders.
It's normal if you didn't know.
Chu Xia.
I'm being very honest.
Tell me,
what is your condition?
You wouldn't use such a big deal
to bribe me into calling you "dad".
If that's really the case, I would feel
extremely flattered.
Chu Xia, it's not like that.
You only need to promise me
that you will go to France whether you
win the competition or not.
What are you trying to do?
You only have to give me a
yes or no answer.
Ok.
I promise you.
You've been working
hard for the competition.
Go home and rest early.
I will go to France.
What?
It's my dream.
But before that,
I need to do something.
Ok.
If you need my help with anything,
tell me.
I'll help you.
No need.
It's something
only I
myself
can do.
Thank you.
Xiao Nan.
I need your help.
What happened?
Don't ask, just come over.
I'll be right there.
Come, sit down.
The most important thing
for a love confession is a pretty dress
and beautiful make up.
Done!
Perfect.
I'm actually a genius.
Look.
This is the real An Chu Xia.
Take out your unique ability,
take down Qi Lu!
Go for it.
Qi Lu.
You wanted to meet me,
yet you're the one being late.
Do I look pretty?
I guess.
Will you die if you compliment me?
I meant...
you're pretty.
Han Qi Lu.
I need to tell you something.
Perfect,
I need to tell you something, too.
Meng Xiao Nan, where are you taking me?
Meng Xiao Nan!
Begin.
Feng Shao?
Hey!
One, two, three.
Get going.
-We sway together.
We sway together, we sway, we sway.
We sway together!
What's the matter?
The string is torn.
Idiot, didn't you know to check
before you came here?
Xiao Nan.
You brought me here to show me them?
Er...
Wait for me. Just a second.
Feng Shao, what are you doing?
I told you to start a band.
And this is what you made?
Hey,
there wasn't enough time
for such an important task.
They are brothers from Cat Ear Alley,
we can make a hair cut,
but...
who knows how to play these things?
This was already the best I could do.
Whatever. So be it.
So be it.
Come on! Continue.
Let's continue.
We sway together, we sway, we sway.
We sway, we sway.
We sway!
Alright,
you go first.
-When are you going to France?
-I do!
This is what you wanted to talk
to me about?
Yeah.
Also,
did you apply for visa yet?
I think Sister Yuan Yuan has gotten
your visa ready a long time ago.
What about your admission?
Did you contact the people at Pinkston?
Also,
how's the weather in France?
Enough! Enough!
Do you want me gone so badly?
Isn't going to Pinkston your dream?
What about you?
What do you think?
Me?
Is it very important what I think?
It is to me.
Han Qi Lu.
Do you perhaps think that
I'll be like Xiang Man Kui
and leave you after I go to France?
It's not like that.
I love design.
But I love you, too.
Han Qi Lu.
I love you! I love you!
Do you understand?
I'm sorry.
I won't consider romantic matters
for the time being.
What?
I just changed my choice
for field of study.
I'm behind on my studies.
If I don't make an effort now,
it'll be too late.
Han Qi Lu.
I, An Chu Xia,
am confessing my love to you.
Didn't you want to ask me
what I think?
So let me tell you,
the Han family has just overcome
a major crisis.
Brother Liu's health has only
just gotten better.
Sister Yuan Yuan can't face the directors
of the company at all.
Right now,
I can't think about these trivialities
of who I love,
and who I don't love.
All I want is to solve
the issues in peace.
Ok?
Trivialities?
Alright.
In that case,
I won't make things difficult for you.
I wish you a speedy success.
Young Master Han.
Wait.
You didn't tune your guitar.
And you,
you're holding it the wrong way.
And what's that for?
Starting a band.
An Erhu?
A mix of China and the West.
To develop traditional Chinese culture.
Let's go?
I think we should go.
Wait a bit longer.
Oh right,
guests are waiting for me in my shop.
Wait a little longer.
We'll leave once he's satisfied.
Hey, boss.
I'm not neglecting work. I'm not.
I'll be right back.
Big brother got beaten up?
Wait for me.
Wait!
I'll be right there!
Are you two ok?
It's fine, it's fine.
I'm still here.
I can play for three.
Hello?
Little angel.
Tell me.
I'm free.
A movie?
Sure.
Ok, ok.
I'll be right there.
Feng Shao!
Let them go.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
What does it have to do with you?
Why are you crying, Xiao Nan?
Fool.
Thank you for doing this for me.
You're welcome.
If I knew this would happen,
I wouldn't have given up on Chu Xia.
Why did you lie to Chu Xia?
I didn't.
You don't have to hide it from me.
I just think
that Chu Xia has lost enough already.
I can't let her lose this opportunity too.
Love and dream aren't mutually exclusive.
But I'm talking about reality.
I can't go to France with Chu Xia.
I can't hinder her from moving forward.
She can go study at Pinkston.
But me?
I'm beginning to doubt that you are the
Han Qi Lu I know.
I'm not that Han Qi Lu.
I'm not that selfish.
Yes.
But you are still just as egocentric.
You didn't even ask
what Chu Xia's feeling.
You don't ask for her opinion.
Maybe this situation
isn't as complicated
as you make it out to be.
Maybe.
Buddy.
You reap what you sow.
So you have to take responsibility of it.
You should think carefully now,
while you still have a chance.
Sister Yuan.
Thank you for taking care of me
all this time.
Please take care of
yourself while I'm away.
Ok.
Chu Xia.
Once you're there,
tell me if there's anything lacking
with the food
and the living situation
or if you need anything.
I will let someone bring them to you.
Your Brother Liu is in bad health,
he couldn't come.
He told me to tell you
to take care of yourself.
I will, Sister Yuan.
Rest assured.
I have everything arranged for Chu Xia.
Someone will take care of her.
Good.
Chu Xia.
I don't want you to go.
Ok, ok.
Alright, alright.
Look at you. It's not
like I'm leaving forever.
You will come back.
You have to come back often.
Be good.
Ok.
Chu Xia.
Take care of yourself.
Thank you.
Qi Lu left early this morning.
I don't know where he went, either.
It's fine.
Perhaps he just didn't want to come.
Ok.
Alright.
It's about time.
We are leaving.
Bye bye.
If you want to cry, cry.
Stop hiding!
Come out!
Who are you talking to?
Thank you for not exposing me.
Han Qi Lu, you are here!
Do you know that Chu Xia
kept looking for you?
I knew you'd be here.
Thank you for not exposing me.
Han Qi Lu.
I didn't think you'd be such a coward.
Whatever you say.
I'm leaving.
Wait!
Do you know how much
Chu Xia sacrificed for you?
What?
I'm saying
someone like you don't deserve love.
Not that.
What did you mean?
Ok,
I'll tell you.
Do you think it was that easy for
your company's design plan to pass?
That man is the master of his own fate?
That you will succeed
as long as you put in effort?
Han Qi Lu, wake up.
You can't even deceive yourself
with such a reason.
Have you never wondered how this matter
came through so smoothly?
This had something to do with Chu Xia?
Listen carefully.
She made a deal with my uncle.
That whether she wins or loses,
she will leave behind everything
and go to France.
She hated my uncle so much,
yet...
For your family, for you,
she didn't even hesitate and agreed!
How do you know that?
My last name is Jiang!
How can I not know?
You listen to me.
If you don't chase after her now,
I promise you you will regret it forever!
Go!
Why...
Why did you help Han Qi Lu?
I'm helping my sister.
I hope she will find happiness.
(An Chu Xia I love you)
What are you doing?
You haven't left?
There's bad weather in France.
The flight got cancelled.
B-But I clearly...
Don't "but" me.
Anyways,
I need to wait a few days
till I leave for France.
Did you come here
to tell me something?
I did.
Chu Xia.
Actually, it was me who
communicated with you through that wall.
That's it?
I already knew that.
Huh?
Since there's nothing you want to tell me,
I'm leaving.
Come back!
Why should I?
Because I told you to.
You think I'll do whatever you say?
I love you.