Stop following me!
Qi Lu.
Let's talk.
About what?
I feel that you have changed
after I came back here.
People always change.
But you didn't change for me.
Is that all you want to say?
Qi Lu.
I know you are angry.
You can get mad at me,
but please don't ignore me.
You left without saying a word.
Have you thought of my feeling?
But...
I told you I'd wait for you
no matter how long.
And I waited there like a fool.
I knew everyone was laughing at me,
but I believed you.
I believe you knew what
I was afraid of losing the most.
But what did you do?
Qi Lu.
I won't do that again.
Sorry.
The past is in the past.
No second time.
Help!
Is there anyone? Help!
Who's that?
Help! Is there anyone?
Anyone there?
I'm coming in.
Who's that?
Open the door!
Is there anyone?
[Master Devil Do Not Kiss Me S2]
[Episode 8]
Is there anyone?
You saw Chu Xia,
why didn't you tell them?
What did you say? I don't get you.
The reason is very simple.
You were kind enough as you
didn't kick her when she's down,
let alone giving her a hand.
So, are you happy when you see
An Chu Xia feeling helpless?
If you have nothing else, I'll go first.
Stop!
I just want to tell you.
In fact, An Chu Xia
is our common enemy.
From a certain perspective,
the two of us are in the same camp.
So?
So, we have to
kick An Chu Xia out of Stiland College
and Han's family.
Let her stay away from Qi Lu.
Then we can have a fair play.
What makes you laugh?
You are as stupid as you used to be.
How many times you
want to use the same trick?
Are you going to work with me?
The prerequisite is the two sides
are equal in strength.
And you
don't seem to be qualified.
Aren't you afraid that I'll tell Qi Lu?
You know better than I why An Chu Xia
was locked up there in the first place.
Go ahead if you want
to put yourself into trouble.
Where is Chu Xia?
I'm asking you. Where is Chu Xia?
I don't know.
She's gone when I did not notice.
I'll call her myself.
Sorry.
The number you have dialed
could not be reached.
I can't reach her!
Try to call her!
Would there be any bad guys?
How could you let her go out alone?
Ah!
Did you take good care of her?
Stop fighting!
Is it the time for fighting?
Just fight as you like
after we find Chu Xia.
Xiao Nan is right.
Let's split and look for her.
Xiao Nan, let's check the CCTV
in the monitoring room
Qi Lu.
I'll go with you.
No need.
No signal?
No battery.
Anyone knows I'm missing?
How is it?
We have checked the footage of CCTV.
Ms. An Chu Xia was last seen
near the artificial lake.
What?
Young Master Jiang.
As the resort is under renovation,
some of the equipment is not perfect.
And the monitor has not been
installed in some remote places.
What? Pardon!
Where's the manager?
Is there anyone to check it?
How can this happen
in Jiang's property?
Hey!
Why are you crying?
Stop crying.
Many people are looking at us.
They may think I am bullying you.
Stop crying.
Please.
If I hadn't been mad
and thrown a tantrum,
Chu Xia wouldn't have gone missing.
Don't say that.
It's related to me.
It's all your fault.
Do you really know how to like someone?
You're just...
Ouch! My hand!
Does it hurt?
-You fooled me!
-Are you still crying?
Let's go.
Let's look for her.
No!
I can't just sit and wait here.
I must find a way to get out.
Chu Xia!
It's me!
-Qi Lu?
-Why have you been locked up here?
I have no idea.
I thought someone needed help.
I was locked up as soon as I came in.
Wait, I'll get people right now.
No signal.
I've tried to call out.
Maybe it's too remote here.
Wait! Don't be afraid,
I'll be right back.
An Chu Xia!
Chu Xia!
Hello.
-We'll be right there.
-What's up?
Qi Lu found her locked up
in the hut behind the mountain.
Really? Let's go now.
-Where are you going?
-Qi Lu found Chu Xia. Come!
Chu Xia.
Yes.
You sound tired.
Is it?
It reminds me the place
I used to stay when I was young.
Not Cat Ears Lane,
but a place before that.
When I was young,
my mom and I often moved.
The house was small and broken.
And I used to live in the basement too.
Sometimes my mom
worked overtime at night.
I was afraid at home alone.
So,
you become a strong woman after that.
That's right.
Because I had to protect her.
You were trying to kick the door open.
Where did you get that genius idea?
I had to find a way out!
Otherwise,
what if no one notices me missing?
I will.
And I'm sure I'll find you!
Thank you, Han Qi Lu.
I am suddenly not so scared.
By the way,
sorry for yesterday.
I was full of myself.
It has nothing to do with you.
I did wrong too.
I just don't want
to see you being pressed by the past.
I  want to help you.
Thank you.
Over there.
They're coming.
Chu Xia, don't be afraid.
It is alright.
You are fine now.
Thank you.
Chu Xia.
We finally found you.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't throw a tantrum.
Don't cry.
You owe me.
Buy me an ice-cream.
Let's go.
Wait for me.
Han Qi Lu.
I have a question.
Do you like An Chu Xia?
Do I need to answer you?
Okay.
I'm telling you.
I like Chu Xia.
And I am serious.
No matter what, I'm not going
to give her to anyone else!
Madam.
Both of them are back.
Here you are.
Did you enjoy it?
Anything to share with me?
Not bad. I'll go back to my room first.
-What's wrong with Chu Xia?
-Nothing.
She was locked up for an afternoon.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I'm tired.
I go back to my room first.
Don't go! What's going on?
This is...
I... Did I miss anything?
What's going on?
I have no idea.
I feel like
it's not what you think!
It is not what I think?
Han Yu.
Have a seat.
-When did you come back?
-Just now.
How is it?
Is your hand alright?
I can even hit the tiger.
That's good.
But, my grandpa often
talked about you and
asked why you didn't visit him.
Many things happened and I forgot it.
Say sorry to him for me.
It's better that you tell him yourself.
What do you mean?
He holds a family dinner at home
for my recovery.
In fact, it's just me and my grandpa.
He wants to invite you.
The more the merrier.
Sure.
So I'll pick you up this weekend.
Here you are.
I just talked to Chu Xia.
Sure enough, An Chu Xia
is more important.
I heard Man Kui is back.
Yes.
What do you think?
What now? Even you are
trying to persuade me.
Three of us grew up together.
Man Kui left without telling us.
I know how deep she hurts you.
But I know her character.
She is not a bad person.
You both can't always be indifferent.
so I want to know what you think.
Is this important?
At least it could prevent some
innocent people from being harmed.
Like Chu Xia.
I hope you handle
your relationship with Man Kui.
It shows that you still care about her
and can't forget the past!
You are torturing yourself.
I'll consider it.
Qi Lu.
Why are you here?
You don't look good
Are you sick?
No.
What are you doing?
Come with me.
How is she going?
Her physical function is poor.
We can't do a
comprehensive check up here.
You'd better take her to the hospital.
-I'm fine.
-Typical words from my patients.
Give me the Stiland health card
to fill in the information.
I haven't got it yet.
Haven't got it yet?
-I'm just back from abroad.
-Come with me.
Qi Lu.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I thought you wouldn't forgive me
even if I were dead.
Don't curse yourself.
It's time for class.
Good bye.