Bro, it's been a long time
since the school ends.
Go back to your house.
You...I almost have domestic
violence because of you.
Chu Xia is cruel.
How could she be so cold-hearted?
She must be influenced by Han Qi Lu.
One takes the behavior
of one's company.
Don't worry.
I'll call Chu Xia and lecture her.
It's Chu Xia.
Keep quiet.
Hello, Chu Xia.
Anything I can help?
Do you know where
Jiang Chen Chuan is?
His phone is off.
You two always stay together
recently. That's why I call you.
Jiang Chen Chuan?
I didn't see him.
He left, didn't he?
Alright.
Forget it then.
Wait.
Just a minute.
Why are you looking for him?
I was in a bad mood in the afternoon
and Jiang Chen Chuan
asked me to go to the resort.
I did not pay attention
and was rude to him.
I might have hurt him.
I see.
That is quite serious.
A rich child like him
has never suffered in his life.
Especially a setback from a woman.
Now you hurt him.
He might...
Feng Shao!
Don't scare me.
I'm not sure.
What about this?
You accept his invitation.
I wanted to accept it.
But his phone is off.
Chu Xia! You finally say yes!
Jiang Chen Chuan!
-Why are you there?
-I...
Feng Shao, you lied to me!
Chu Xia, I'm here.
So you will go with me, right?
Well...
It's late now.
Take a rest.
Okay. Bye.
I'm going on a date with Chu Xia!
I have to to get ready.
Gosh!
What a useless guy!
Don't look at me.
I'm innocent.
She forced me to come.
Chu Xia said, the more the merrier.
Did I disturb you?
No...
Let's go.
Be careful.
Sit here.
[Master Devil Do Not Kiss Me S2]
[Episode 7]
-Ms. Maria.
-Hi!
-Are you on duty today?
-Yeah.
Did you see You Tian?
No.
He disappeared in a flash.
Aren't you tired chasing a man everyday
who's not willing to wait for you?
Fight for it if you like him.
Without the courage,
it's better to give up.
Ms. Maria.
I'm off.
Bye.
Fight for it if you like him.
Without the courage,
it's better to give up.
Big news! According
to the reliable informant,
they dated in a resort
during the weekend.
Really? Didn't An Chu Xia
fall in love with Han Qi Lu?
-How come she hangs out with Jiang?
-It seems the rumors are true.
Xiang Man Kui is back.
An Chu Xia and Han Qi Lu broke up
and found their new lovers.
Two of them
hid it very well. I can't see it
although we're in the same class.
I can't see it either.
This is the school communication group.
Don't send such messages!
Han! Check a place for me.
What?
Only two rooms left?
Sorry, Young Master Jiang.
The hotel rooms are always booked.
During our tele-conversation, you said
that you needed 2 rooms.
So, we...
I don't care!
Give me two more rooms now.
Hear that?
The rest has been checked in...
Someone is showing off here
as Young Master Jiang.
Uncle will be sad if he gets to know it.
Mo Xin Wei.
Why are you here?
Why am I here?
This is a property of Jiang's family.
My father sent me to survey it.
What a bad luck!
What did you say?
Give me two more rooms.
Forget it. Don't be so hard on her.
The three of us can stay in the same room.
An Chu Xia.
I had underestimated you.
I didn't expect you are so smart.
You run after Qi Lu
and tempt this stupid guy
at the same time, huh?
Who is the stupid guy you mean?
The guy who answers me.
It's alright.
Don't mind her.
Let's go.
Come on!
What a beautiful place!
-Thank you for bringing us here.
-You are welcome.
You're a friend of Chu Xia.
So you are my friend too.
Am I right?
Enjoy the food.
Here comes the food. Well...
I've done a lot of homework
about the food here.
I asked Feng Shao.
He said,
these are all your favourite.
Dig in.
Do you mind if I join you?
I'd like to eat too.
Just like a plaster!
Can't get rid of it!
Move aside.
Han Qi Lu.
Why are you here?
I was in a bad mood,
so I come and hang out.
I happened to meet you here.
Many seats over there.
Why must you sit here?
Qi Lu!
Do you want to sit here?
It's your favourite.
When are you going back?
Don't you welcome me?
No, there's not enough room here.
It is not safe if you go back late.
Yeah! It isn't safe if you go back late.
Go back now!
It's troublesome.
In that case,
do you mind if I sleep
on the floor in your room?
Huh?
No way!
You stay with me!
You know what.
My room is big
and wide.
Stay with me.
Thank you very much!
So kind of you.
That's it.
Dig in.
What makes you laugh?
-Dig in.
-What makes you laugh?
Okay.
Got it.
It's alright.
Enjoy your good time
with Chu Xia.
Enjoy yourselves!
Don't rush home.
Okay.
Bye.
Madam.
Enjoy the fruits.
Han.
You know what.
Qi Lu's brain is suddenly open.
He went to the resort with Chu Xia.
Oh!
The success is around the corner.
Madam.
As I know, it seems not only
two of them going there.
What do you mean?
Young master asked me to check
the address of the resort this morning.
Then he hurried away.
That's Jiang's property.
Huh?
Really?
The bed is so big.
You pervert!
I'll put the pillow here.
And I'll put this one here.
What are you doing?
You sleep here and I'll sleep here.
Don't cross the line.
I understand.
But there's only one conclusion.
I sleep on the bed!
Hey!
Where should I sleep then?
Let me see.
Kitchen.
Toilet.
Ceiling.
Or the pool outside.
Wherever you want to.
Go ahead! Don't disturb me!
Han Qi Lu!
You have gone too far.
No way! Let's fight!
Han Qi Lu.
What now?
Gross!
You're really something!
Why are you still up at this hour?
You too.
The room is too noisy.
I couldn't sleep.
Nice moon!
Why do you suddenly come to the resort?
I haven't been to an outing for so long.
So I hang out with Xiao Nan.
Not because of Jiang Chen Chuan?
Not really.
Did you read the news in the group?
Yes.
That's not true.
What?
I mean, the relationship between
Chen Chuan and I isn't what they see.
That's good.
I...
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Are you really going to ignore
Xiang Man Kui in your life time?
What do you mean?
I feel pity for her.
-She asked you to persuade me?
-No.
Everybody will get confused
in their life once or twice.
You can't throw them to hell.
when they make a mistake.
An Chu Xia.
What's up?
I've never met anyone
who's more heartless than you!
You really want to make us reconciled?
I can see that you can't forget her.
So, I'm helping you.
Look at you now.
You are being hard on yourself
instead of torturing others.
I won't bother you.
Insane!
Jiang Chen Chuan.
That's what you've arranged?
That's right.
What a poor place!
What?
Nothing.
Come and help, I can't do this.
Let's go.
I don't know how to cut it.
Look.
What about this?
Am I smart?
Feng Shao.
I'm having a grill.
Barbecue.
That's it?
That's right.
Wait.
Is there a horse farm
or something in your resort?
Why don't you teach
Chu Xia riding a horse?
I can't do other things.
That's only what I can do.
What about golf?
I can't play golf too.
Well... Frankly, are you sure
you are the heir to Jiang's family?
Are you an adopted child?
I only good at computer game.
I think I should
build a game station city
and change the whole environment.
What say you?
Forget it. Carry on your work.
Good luck to you.
Idiot! You can't even flirt with a girl!
He's so weak in this.
Are you good enough?
Of course I'm good.
Let's go.
Hey!
You can't do it, leave it to me.
Go away!
Let me do this.
Chen Chuan.
Are you okay?
You're bleeding.
Han Qi Lu, I just want to help you.
You are so careless.
He's such a busy body.
You hurt him.
Shouldn't you apologize?
Why should I? It was him who did wrong!
You always blame people.
Who do you think you are?
The haughty Young Master Han?
Unreasonable!
Incorrigible!
Don't be angry.
Just blow on it.
Chu Xia.
Let me help you.
Stop following me.
Qi Lu.
Let's talk.
Is the bandage nice?
Hey!
Where's Han Qi Lu?
Hasn't come back yet?
I don't know.
Where's Xiang Man Kui?
They were together.
Do you still think Xiang Man Kui comes
near you without any motive?
Come on.
Xiao Nan.
Didn't we talk about it before?
Yes, we did.
But have you ever thought
that no one is good
to anyone for no reason.
She helped you many times.
And there must be a reason.
You think too much.
Chu Xia.
You should know your feeling
towards Han Qi Lu.
I won't force you.
I won't force you to admit anything.
The important thing is,
you have to know what you want
and what you don't want.
I don't understand.
An Chu Xia.
Don't try to escape.
If you like Han Qi Lu,
tell him frankly.
Don't fear of getting hurt.
Love irrevocably and vigorously!
If you don't like him,
look at the person around you
who is really good to you.
Meng Xiao Nan!