I appoint you as a special teacher
to teach the Prince.
If I ever come across a woman
who moves my heart,
I am willing to throw my dreams away
to live just for her.
Do you not want to go home?
Then grab another drink with me.
Let go of her.
Are you all right?
-What do you think you are doing?
-Pardon?
Will you hear me out? Wait.
-Wait, wait.
-You crazy pervert.
How can she call her savior
an attempted rapist?
Where is the woman who reported me?
Master Gyeon, this is my sister.
Nice to meet you. I am Princess Hyemyeong.
-The crazy...
-The gold digger...
Were you shocked that I am a princess?
Let us go and see His Majesty right now.
Have you two not seen it?
It is him. The crazy pervert.
Don't start with me!
You tried to rape me at a motel.
If you do not find my jade ring,
I will write "rapist" on your face
and send you on an exile.
What is so special about that ring?
If you cannot find my jade ring,
you will be done and over with.
I have heard about your
incredible reputation, Master Gyeon.
You took a civil service exam in the
Qing Dynasty and got the best score.
You were a great talent who even
gained the Emperor's trust.
The national treasure of Joseon
almost got stolen by the Qing Dynasty.
But if you fail to prove your value,
all those appraisals will be
good for nothing.
The world acknowledges greatness
even if it does not try to stand out.
Anyway, I hope you take good care of
the Prince.
I will do my best.
I recently heard that Princess Hyemyeong
visits the Prince often these days.
It seems like she greatly
cares for the Prince.
Well, I will see you later.
Hey, you crazy pervert.
Where are your manners?
Then what should I call you?
Lady-killer? Master Obscene?
Or a player?
I will back down.
What did you and Lieutenant Gang
talk about?
You can go and ask him yourself.
Okay, fine.
I will tell Lieutenant Gang
about how a pervert became
the Prince's master and get his help.
I suddenly miss Lieutenant Gang a lot.
Wait.
If I find your jade ring,
will you stop calling me "crazy pervert"?
Of course. I promise.
You promised.
Wait.
She works for the Prince.
I was in a rush to get a book for him.
But this stupid woman
left her pass behind.
You are one great liar.
I am worried for the Prince's future.
I worry more about your future,
Princess Hyemyeong.
That little...
-Welcome.
-Please enter.
This is a pawnshop run by
an infamous gang.
Is my ring in there?
That is where smuggled goods from
the Qing Dynasty and Japan end up,
and everything that is
taken illegally from people are
sold and bought.
If someone picked it up and sold it,
it will probably end up here.
These men are tough.
Be careful.
What are you doing? Come on.
Welcome.
-Come on in.
-Please enter.
-Go on in.
-Welcome.
Do you need money for your wedding?
It says right here that you will
pay back with interest until today.
The ledger does not lie.
If you give me another extension,
I will pay you back.
My goodness.
Whether one is an aristocrat
or a commoner,
the ones who are in debt
all have one thing in common.
They never pay their money back on time.
They always ask for an extension.
That is what they do.
-Please spare my life.
-Hey!
You're making me look like a bad guy
because you keep breaking your promise.
Please help me live as a good guy,
will you?
Boss, you have guests.
My goodness, you are the attempted rapist.
"Attempted rapist"?
You must be quite famous for that.
Would you like to get sued for defamation?
My goodness, how scary.
But what brings you here?
So these were all smuggled,
stolen, taken away,
or conned from people.
You are a funny lady.
You can take your time.
But each of you must pay me
one yang to take a look.
Why are you charging us for just looking?
This is a business. We must make money.
You may leave if you are not
willing to pay.
What?
Take a closer look.
I can tell at once.
Ms. Naju, overdue interest of 190 yang.
Overdue interest is 50 yang per day.
-Let us go.
-Wait.
Do you have any golden hairpin too?
You will need to pay two yang
per person to take a look.
My goodness.
Why do you want to...
I am a little busy today. I have to go.
Keep in mind that
you will not get a refund.
We will come back some other time.
My ledger.
-Get them.
-Hey, run!
-Yes, boss!
-Boss!
-You little...
-Get over here!
-Where are they?
-Go get them.
-Get him!
-My gosh.
Stop right there. I'll get you.
-Stop them.
-Move away.
Darn it.
My goodness.
Follow me.
Money.
-Money.
-Get the money.
-Move!
-Look!
You are a slow runner.
Do you think this is funny?
OVERDUE INTEREST 40 BAGS OF RICE
OVERDUE INTEREST 20 BAGS OF RICE
OVERDUE INTEREST 10 BAGS OF RICE PER DAY
OVERDUE INTEREST 10 YANG PER DAY
OVERDUE INTEREST 30 YANG
What are you doing?
Although I have failed to find
the jade ring,
I feel like I have done a good deed.
Let us go and eat.
Try some of this.
-Welcome.
-This is good.
-May we have some more?
-Okay.
Chicken feet and soju are a perfect match.
No way.
Can you not eat chicken feet either?
What kind of a man are you?
My goodness.
Why do you even eat this
disgusting looking thing?
There is no other you.
There is no other me.
Just like that, there is no other
taste like this in the world.
If you wish to become successful,
you must not have prejudice
against people,
and you must not be a picky eater.
You were acting so manly
so I thought you were a real man.
My gosh.
How is it? Doesn't it taste delicious?
It is both sweet and spicy.
It is also chewy and crunchy.
This is when
you need to drink soju.
It makes it taste better.
Here. Bottoms up.
One more?
By any chance,
do you like me?
-What?
-I see.
You must be embarrassed
because you are a princess.
Well, don't be.
Just be honest and tell me the truth.
Stop using the jade ring as an excuse.
I totally understand how you feel.
What can you do?
It is not a sin to be attracted to
a handsome man like me.
But...
But I will have to refuse.
I am not an easy guy.
I really hate women who are reckless
like foals.
Are you actually drunk,
or are you just acting?
You're not worth the chicken foot.
Drink up.
What is this?
Mother made a special drink
to cure your hangover.
It is a mixture of kudzu, honey,
ginger, vinegar,
cucumber, dried persimmon,
blowfish, and...
-What else?
-Eel.
Anyway, she added every single ingredient
that is known to cure a hangover.
Although, I am not sure if it is
medicine or poison.
Here. It may taste bad
but drink it up for my sake.
You are always so nice to him.
Good boy. Go on and drink the whole thing.
Look at the dark circles
beneath your eyes.
Why do you drink so much these days?
Do you have a secret lover or something?
Nonsense. Your brother will
never do such a thing.
But then again,
I did hear that it is more important
to socialize over some drinks
if one wishes to become successful.
But please keep yourself healthy.
Okay, Mother.
By any chance, do you like me?
I am not an easy guy.
I really hate women who are reckless
like foals.
My goodness, what did I do?
My gosh!
Did the medicine make you sick?
Gyeon U.
Da-yeon is so pretty, is she not?
She is the most ideal prospective
bride out of all the women in...
What do you think about marrying Da-yeon?
If Second State Councilor Jeong
becomes our in-law,
it will also benefit our family.
Why you little...
Go away. You are driving me crazy.
I will be the middle person
and help you out.
Is it because you really have a lover?
My goodness, what lover?
What a relief.
I thought that the jade ring was
a token of your love.
Ring?
Well...
I did not take it intentionally, but...
What is this?
It is a work of art that was made by
a famous master craftsman
in the Qing Dynasty.
The carving of
the mandarin duck is beautiful.
You should try it on.
It fits you perfectly.
My brother sure does have a great eye.
It is actually a gift from my brother.
Gyeon U got this for me?
Lady Da-yeon.
Were you trying on the ring again?
Why did you call me?
You have a guest.
What brings you here?
Da-yeon, first,
I would like to apologize.
I do not understand.
The ring that my sister,
Gyeon Hui, gave you...
Are you talking about the
gift you gave me?
I was thinking of how to repay you
for such a precious gift.
I think there was a
slight misunderstanding.
What do you mean?
I must take it back from you.
What should I do?
I do not have it with me right now.
What do you mean?
I left it at the jewelry store to
have it cleaned.
If you tell me where the jewelry
store is, I will go and get it.
But I never agreed to return it to you.
Da-yeon.
I will see you at the lantern
festival the day after tomorrow.
Then I will decide whether or not
to return it to you.
Go!
Congratulations,
Second State Councilor Jeong.
Second State Councilor Jeong has the best
archery skills in Joseon without a doubt.
It is all thanks to you, Your Majesty.
You are too modest.
I would love to learn from you.
Please teach me your secret.
There is nothing much to it.
"Focus on the small things."
I just try hard not to miss
even the smallest movement.
That is all.
"The smallest movement."
CAN'T GO
LOW WALLS
SUGU GATE
No.
Do not even dream of going
outside the palace.
Did you already forget what His Majesty
said before he left for hunting?
My father returns tomorrow.
I will try to find the jade ring.
Okay, okay.
Get rid of this. Burn it.
Princess Hyemyeong.
I brought your favorite...
Snack...
-Princess Hyemyeong?
-Princess Hyemyeong.
Princess... Princess Hyemyeong.
Princess...
Princess Hyemyeong!
Hurry up!
Are these the only jade rings you have?
Yes.
Princess.
You look like a princess.
How could you be so perfectly beautiful?
I am sorry for causing a fuss.
I mistakenly thought that it was
a present from my brother.
Did he even get me a gift
in the first place?
Of course, he did.
It was my mistake.
I will find out if you are
telling me the truth
once I meet Gyeon U today.
THE PRINCESS SNEAKS OUT AGAIN
Lieutenant Gang.
What is going on?
Princess Hyemyeong disappeared.
I think she went out of the palace again.
How did you let this happen?
-I am sorry.
-If His Majesty finds out,
he will punish her with something
greater than copying down the customs.
Please help.
The Princess snuck out of
the palace again?
Councilor Jeong.
Is something going on?
It seems like
the night will be long tonight.
Pardon? What do you mean?
The sun is still shining brightly.
You punk!
You jerk. Come over here.
You pathetic idiot. You stupid jerk.
You little...
punk! My gosh!
You pathetic jerks.
How could you call yourselves gangsters
when you could not even catch
those puny little buggers?
Are you Do-chi?
What do you want?
Hello.
I should have come here first.
It is a token of my affection.
Please read it.
Lady Da-yeon, you are brighter
than the moonlight,
and you are more beautiful than a flower.
To me, you are the most perfect
woman in the world.
Mal-geum.
My heart is born anew because of you.
They say the women dressed up with
gems are beautiful,
but they surely cannot be more
beautiful than you are.
That was a waste of paper and ink.
You should focus on
your studies during your spare time.
I have a previous engagement,
so I will leave now.
Lady Da-yeon. Lady Da-yeon.
MOONLITE, MOONLIGHT
FLOUR, FLOWER
PURFECT, PERFECT
JEM, GEM
What is this?
Who did you request this to?
You paid 30 yang for this piece of trash?
-That cannot be.
-I paid 30 yang for that.
Lady Da-yeon's previous engagement
must be with Gyeon U.
Hey, be quiet.
What?
Gyeon U?
Will you look at that?
He's been missing for two days.
I will teach you a lesson.
What kind of story is behind that ring?
Why are you so desperate for it?
Is it a ring for your lover?
Nonsense.
It is just something I had kept
on behalf of someone.
Do not be mistaken.
I liked it so much that
I even thought about
not returning it to you.
To be honest, I also thought about
towing with your feelings by dragging on.
But
I could not forget how
desperate you looked
when you came to look for the ring.
Thank you.
I should return it to you,
since the owner wants it back.
Here is a small gift in return.
It is beautiful.
Honey.
Are you here to meet
other women when you have me?
"Honey"?
When will you stop stalking him and
being so rude to him like this?
I remember you.
You are the lady I ran into last time.
Who are you?
As for us, we are a couple who
even spent the night together.
What kind of nonsense is that?
Why? Did I say anything wrong,
honey?
You tried to undo my coat string
at the motel.
My goodness, what is wrong with you?
You should report her right now.
There is no cure for obsessiveness.
What? "Obsessiveness"?
CRAZY WOMAN
Hey!
Is that how you described me?
You crazy pervert.
Which family are you from?
Why? Are you thinking about abusing
your family's power over mine?
You seem to have experience in
abusing your power.
What?
Da-yeon, I do not think I can stay
any longer.
I must go.
-Follow me.
-Where are you taking me?
Let go. Hey.
Da-yeon.
Da-yeon, are you okay?
Who is she?
Let go of me.
Let me go! Let go!
Why are you here?
I came to find my jade ring.
What about you? What are you doing here?
I came to find your jade ring.
Sure you did.
You act like you are the most
well-mannered scholar in the palace.
But outside, you have your
eyes wide open for women.
I bet you came here for women.
Did you think I would fall for
that lie of yours?
Hey!
Hey, Gyeon U!
The ladies are beautiful!
I do not think I will go home tonight.
Who... Who is this beautiful lady?
Wait a minute.
Is she that enemy?
"Enemy"?
What are you saying?
She is his lover.
Stop with your nonsense.
Oh, are you his friends?
Ever since he fell in love with me
at first sight,
he has been chasing after me.
I was talking to him
to set things straight.
A man who studied abroad
is indeed quite straightforward.
Well, I have booked a great spot.
Would you like to join us?
She has to leave urgently.
I would love to. Where is your seat?
-It is over there. Let us go!
-Let us go.
Okay, let us go.
What do you think you are doing?
They say if you want to know someone
get to know their friends.
I am going to check if you are
qualified to teach the Prince.
Wait for me.
Today is the day of the
lantern festival. Am I correct?
Yes, Your Highness.
Today is a day that was permitted
by the government
for young men and women to
gather together and have fun.
It feels suffocating to just stay in
the palace on a day like this.
In the past,
I would have spent the night having fun.
Time really flies by quickly.
You are still young, Your Highness.
Then should we go to Namsan and
keep it a secret from His Majesty?
That is the best place to watch
the lantern festival.
Pardon?
I was just joking.
But then again,
the Princess is still very young.
It would be great if she could
enjoy the festival.
Then
us three can go...
No. Shall we take the Prince too?
What will you do if His Majesty finds out?
He's staying at the Royal Lodge today.
But you never know.
My goodness.
The King Game?
It seems inappropriate to play
a game that impersonates the King.
Well...
It is just a drinking game.
We do not intend on dishonoring
the King. Do not misunderstand.
What do you mean?
It seems more fun,
since it is inappropriate.
Let us play right now.
You really know how to have fun.
Let us enjoy the game then.
Let us do that.
Okay, let us take turns and
choose a stick.
Okay. Who is the king?
I am.
I am the king.
KING
Then who is the loser?
LOSER
I think I am the loser.
It is the first round,
so do not go too hard on her.
We are playing a game.
I cannot go easy on her.
Let us see.
Loser, listen carefully.
"I am a crazy and obsessive woman."
Say that out loud 10 times so that
everyone can hear you.
My goodness, that is a bit too much.
This is a game.
We should follow the rules.
What will you do then?
If you decide to go back home,
you will not have to do that.
Good thinking.
You better go home now.
"I am a crazy and obsessive woman"!
-"I am a crazy
-My goodness.
-and obsessive woman"!
-How could she say...
such a reckless comment?
She is an embarrassment of
all the women in Hanyang.
Gyeon Hui, have you seen
that woman before?
Like she said, she is a crazy
and obsessive woman.
She is just a crazy lady who has
nothing to do with my brother.
Do not be bothered by her.
If she dishonored Da-yeon, that
means she dishonored all of us.
Let us teach that reckless woman a lesson.
Shall we do that?
I am the king!
I am
not the loser.
I am the loser again.
Tell me the penalty.
You better be prepared.
You two.
Change your sticks.
You are the one who said,
"This is a game.
We should follow the rules."
I will carry out your royal command.
-This is not fair!
-How dare you!
You must be out of your mind to
disobey my royal command.
You!
Tie him up right now.
-Wait.
-This is the king's order.
-I must follow the king's order.
-Wait. Just a second.
Hit the offender right now!
-Hey!
-I am sorry!
Hitting him once.
Hitting him twice.
Are you kidding me?
No, do not give that to her!
Hitting him five times!
Hitting him six times!
My gosh, stop it!
You are so handsome.
Hey, take that away from her.
-Stop it.
-Take it away!
-Leave me alone.
-Please help me.
Hurry up and stop her.
You should stop now.
My goodness.
Did we not see that man before
at the Police Bureau?
You have good eyes.
But who is that reckless woman?
My goodness, stop it.
Hitting him eight times.
My goodness.
She must have snuck out again.
-Do you know her?
-Of course.
She is a prestigious person
who we cannot even dare to stand against.
Let me hit him again.
-There we go.
-My goodness.
That is enough.
You should return before it gets too dark.
I might as well just stay and
fly a lantern, since I am already outside.
You are really out of control
and hopeless.
-What?
-I do not care what you do.
You can do whatever you wish.
Fine. Leave. I'm not asking you to stay.
We wish to have a word with you.
Just like how one person can ruin
the whole family's reputation,
you are ruining the reputation of
all the women in Hanyang.
Master Gyeon?
You shall go and apologize to
Da-yeon right now.
If she needs something from me,
she should come here herself.
How shameful of her to make
her slaves do the talking.
What? "Slaves"?
How rude! What makes you so confident?
Do you really need us to
teach you a lesson?
How dare you be so arrogant?
If you would like to fight me,
go on and give it a try.
Come on.
Come over here.
Where are you going?
Those foolish brats.
She was here until a while ago.
Why did you not bring the Princess
to the palace?
We must find the Princess
before it gets too dark.
We still have a long way to go.
Will you continue walking?
When will I ever get the chance
to walk outside the palace
so leisurely like this?
That is why I suggested you to
come out more often.
Every time I decide to make
a far trip, it troubles our people.
How could I dare to easily take
such a far trip like this?
Your Majesty.
-Protect His Majesty!
-Yes, sir!
Hurry up.
Are you okay, Your Majesty?
"The King will cry bitterly
after losing his child."
It must be a dangerous job.
You must not make a mistake.
Once you finish your job,
I will give you twice as much.
You will soon find out that
I make sure I do my money's worth.
My gosh, where in the world is she?
Gyeon U.
Does she think this is
her bedroom or something?
Hey, wake up. Wake up.
Are you awake now?
Who are you guys? Let me go right now.
Where is my ledger?
Did you kidnap me just for that
petty little thing?
That and other reasons.
Where is my ledger?
You better tell me now.
Will you let me go if I tell you?
If you do not tell me,
I will behead you.
I said I will tell you if you let me go.
Can't you understand what's going on?
You must be the one who doesn't
understand what's going on.
I guess you do not need your ledger.
You little...
Would you like a few scars
on that pretty face of yours?
Put that down.
My goodness.
I am seeing a lot of familiar faces today.
Master Gyeon.
Guys, you should welcome our guest.
Move.
You little...
What are you doing, you punks?
What the hell?
Master Gyeon!
I guess this was done by
those who made the jirashis.
Please keep it well. Do not lose it again.
So the image of her keeps
showing in front of you.
She was my biggest enemy
whom I never wished to see again.
Are you interested in me?
Who ordered you to do this?
Just punish me instead.
Do you think I won't do it?
Did you exit the palace again?
He will not let this pass this time.
Dethrone the Princess
and lock her inside the chest!
Subtitle translation by Lexi Lee