Welcome everyone
to "Push It! X" sponsored
by our generous bulldozers
"Push It! X"
I'm Cui Shaoyang, assistant director
of Brainstorm Hall aspiring to be director
Each week I'll be here
bringing you mind-blowing X challenges
exclusive X perspectives
and highly anticipated case reenactments
Rumor has it
our Push Town recently had an unsolved case
where Boss Le of neighboring Pushle Gate
was strangled to death
and hung from the ceiling beam
But fortunately
through our diligent efforts
at Helimo Investigation
we successfully caught mastermind Wang Chuanshuo
and X, Ning Shaoshuai
My vote for the killer is Wang Chuanshuo
Wang Chuanshuo
The real killer is
In this bizarre and twisted case
how did Wang Chuanshuo pass
X's test
And how did these two
manage to deceive everyone
right under our noses?
Now let's all together
"Push It! X"
This is a tricky problem, right?
Move one matchstick
to form the largest possible number
Move one matchstick to make the equation correct
Move three matchsticks
to flip the fish's head around
Move one matchstick
Remove one matchstick
to turn it into a "1"
Move two matchsticks to form a character
An animal, right?
Move two matchsticks to form a TV
Turn it into a TV
How do we do this?
Why do you say that
It's just
Within this reasoning
There are these little games
Just a light warm-up, right
Alright
It's valid
I changed it to a question mark
Question mark equals
So 81 minus 91 equals question mark
It's valid
This doesn't work
This still doesn't work
16 minus 18
16 minus 18 equals 26
Turn this board over
16 equals 18 minus 2
So take this
Bring this over
The dream of 900 million girls
900 million
Bug
Not bad, right?
Done
Just turn it into TV and we're done
Is this really necessary?
Right?
Challenge completed
Alright
Good thing I played with matches a lot as a kid
Or I would've fallen for your trick
Because you're the killer
So please write down on the board
The name of the detective you want to corrupt
Perfect
Here
As soon as I entered the elevator today
Young Master Ning started bluffing me
Saying "Brother Xun, you're the killer, right?"
I said "Yes"
So I'm going to make him my accomplice
My accomplice is
If I look first, then it definitely can't be me.
I was going to check his back for micro-expressions.
This move of yours
I don't get it
He said to me, "Brother,"
I replied, "Brother,"
"Tell me what to do."
"My suspicion is quite high,"
"So you should firmly pin it on me,"
"This way,"
"It will confuse them about"
"whether you or Ke Shaoshuai is the corrupted one,"
"this situation"
"making it unclear for them to judge."
"He told me to pin it on him."
"I can pin it on him,"
"But if I push too hard,"
"they'll follow suit."
"That's acceptable."
"Alright, okay."
"Play it by ear."
"I must pin it on him,"
"because his suspicion is too great,"
"and"
"right now he and my sister are the most suspicious."
"I must protect my sister."
"Pin it on him."
Next,
we'll start with that Wang legend.
Alright then.
Take us to your place.
Come on, come on.
Welcome, come in.
This is my dressing room.
27 28 29 30 31
This is Qi's
What is this thing?
What do you mean?
Phoenix.
Pink Phoenix, right?
Where did this come from?
This was something I gave to Pink Phoenix.
Why is it in Master Le's room?
The key point is, there's such a strong trace of this...
This bloodstain.
So you wanted to kill him?
That's his motive for murder.
Okay
Then let's go to Bali's room next
Alright, let's go
This is a comic
What is this?
What's this?
Two handkerchiefs?
Why is there blood on this?
This handkerchief was from January 30th
when I went to Le Ye's room.
I found that brooch and bracelet.
Then I took my two handkerchiefs
and wrapped them up.
This is the one I was looking for—
the Sunflower Bracelet, right?
So you also wanted to kill Le Ye?
I believe you, I believe you
Yeah right, I believe you
I believe you
First of all, she's my sister
That's the first point
I have to maintain my character
Second, what she said makes sense
What the hell are you doing here?
You're trying to mislead everyone
She's my sister
I have to believe her
But right now...
You're the most suspicious in this round
Let me tell you
You're definitely...
You're just spouting nonsense
Let me go first
On the 31st
I was there the whole time
I went to the dressing room to organize clothes
From morning until 7 PM
Then around 10 PM
I went back home to Bajia Alley to sleep
Later
We might
Tamper with the alibi
You went home at 10?
Yes, I went home at 10
I was there at 10:45 PM
I knocked on your door but got no response
I also went there at 10:40 PM.
She lived in a single dormitory at Bajia Alley.
I also knocked, but no one answered.
So either both of you are lying, or you're lying.
Something's off.
Simply no one was (home).
Actually, I have a question.
You were at the Phoenix Nightclub.
And after passing out, you woke up the next day—
suddenly in that lavish room.
That part is pretty strange too.
I feel like a lot of things are being left unsaid.
I keep feeling many details are being withheld.
Including his personal grudge against Boss Le.
Everyone, think carefully—who’s the killer?
Then cast your final vote.
Got it.
Who?
This is way too hard, man.
Sacrificing family for righteousness
Such is the cruelty of life
Sorry about this, little sister
And my apologies to you too
To all my good friends in the deduction team
My sincerest apologies
I'm voting for Bali
My vote goes to Bali
Three to three
It's a tie
The real culprit is
Wang Esq.
My X is him
Obviously
Mine
Wait, who else voted for me?
I voted for you
Who else? There are two more votes
They must have teamed up to vote for you
We both voted for you
He voted for you
Three votes
You should be more careful
You got tricked
Right, how could you vote for her?
Just because I knocked him out?
The only thing we got right was
He would vote for her
Exactly
I was torn between them
In the end I chose Bali
What made you decide?
It was about her work situation
I never figured it out
Her work situation
All that back and forth
Passing out in new places
Why are you stuck on this?
Why shouldn't I be?
It's definitely worth considering
What does that have to do with Leye's death?
It's relevant
Between her and Leye
Her relationship with Leye
No, her relationship with Leye doesn't matter
She had motive
That's the first point
Right
Second, the murder method
We all know it
We know all the details
It's just whether she did it or not
Whether she was unconscious or asleep
has nothing to do with it
Right
Don't you think?
Who did you vote for, Dilraba?
Why did you vote for him at that time?
Because his motive to kill
appeared earlier than ours.
Because in 1923,
on February 7th,
he received a letter from a stranger
saying his partner
would be sent to another place.
Yes.
While we all learned
That's right.
on January 30, 1924
that Leye intended to harm
They thought about harming me,
and I thought about harming the Sunflower Girl.
Our motives were all spontaneous.
Another point is
he understood that Push Leye Gate
better than the three of us.
Yes.
When we discussed this motive
in the room,
he kept arguing,
saying how could you all be the same.
Young Marshal Ning is too adorable.
After I corrupted him,
he really became a different person.
I thought he didn't sleep well.
You know, today his energy was insufficient.
Not analyzing.
Not because there's nothing to say.
How is there nothing to say?
Then I said you should suspect me
But he didn't suspect me at all
You should suspect
No, but what did he choose?
He chose to protect her
If I suspect him, it would be too obvious
I'm afraid of making him look guilty
You know?
He already looks guilty
Because many people already suspect you
If one more person suspects you
You'll definitely be chosen
I can only say
You all have equal suspicion
Can't just suspect him alone
Suspecting him makes him look guilty
You all voted for him
And another point is
He knows more than the three of us
About that Tui Le Gate
Yes
He worked there for over a year
Yes, yes, yes
So actually it's hard for me to hide
Because the more I say later
The more mistakes I'll make
The more fake it seems
Right, the more fake it seems
So I'll find a way
To influence your judgment
You actually did this
Look, someone else voted for me
Thank you, Commander He
Although you weren't very kind to me before
but at the critical moment
you helped me out
No, I lost too
But having a tie vote makes me feel a bit better
Right, at least
That's acceptable
I really thought he only got two votes
Just the two of us
An even split
What a pity
Both of you failed to escape
But the process was still quite thrilling
Now that everyone knows
how our killer and X
worked together
I'm sure everyone is curious
about how our legendary killer
committed the crime
So what is the truth behind the story?
Everyone, take a look
I am Wang Chuanshuo
With Pink Phoenix's encouragement
I came to the Tui Le Men
to pursue my dreams
Pink Phoenix and I formed the Phoenix Legends duo
Those were my happiest days
A year ago, Pink Phoenix left without a word
to pursue greater opportunities at Tui Lao Hui
An anonymous benefactor left me a letter saying
that Pink Phoenix was sent by Tui Le Men's boss, Master Le
on a path of no return
At first, I didn't take it seriously
I thought it was just a prank
Until January 30th this year
Master Le
While cleaning Master Le's room, I found in the trash
a blood-stained Pink Phoenix hair accessory
Combined with the previous anonymous letter
I became certain Master Le truly harmed Pink Phoenix
I will kill Master Le
to avenge Pink Phoenix
To escape perfectly
I decided to use the legend of the Long-Haired Witch of Tui Town
to craft a flawless murder plan
First,
I plan to use a secret passage I accidentally discovered before,
that leads from the Dongnao Hall
abandoned old Sect Leader's office
to the wardrobe in Master Le's room,
which hides a secret vault.
Normally, I could come and go through this passage,
but Tuizhen has been buried under heavy snow for three days and nights.
I don’t know when the snow will stop,
so to avoid leaving footprints
in the snow-covered courtyard of Dongnao Hall afterward,
I took advantage of the darkness to scout the hall in advance.
I noticed the wooden planks of Dong Nao Tang's staircase
are separate from the steel frame structure beneath.
I can move the staircase planks level by level
and use the steel frame to move between floors.
This way, even after the snow stops,
I can still use Dong Nao Tang
and Master Le's secret stash
to create the perfect locked-room murder.
Then to frame the Long-haired Witch,
I'll need enough wigs
to fabricate the eerie crime scene.
On the evening of January 31st,
after the Bally Fashion Week ended,
I took advantage when the barber shop owner
across from Tui Le Gate briefly left,
and stole some hair.
Just the night before last,
at 8:30 PM on January 31st,
I went to the restroom,
and when I returned,
someone had stolen
all my hair.
Later, carrying the lyrics to "I Love Young Marshal 101",
I hurried to Bally's house in Bajia Alley.
From a distance, I saw
Marshal He knocking at Bally's door,
but no one answered.
When I returned from Bajia Alley to my room,
I found my work badge for that day was missing.
I searched everywhere but couldn't find it.
Fortunately, the badge
didn't have our names on it.
February 1st - Bally Fashion Week concludes.
Unexpectedly during the thank-you performance,
the Long-haired Witch actually appeared.
Could something be about to happen?
The Long-haired Witch...
Tonight would be the perfect time to act.
When the snow stops and it's quiet at night,
I'll follow the original plan,
bring the prepared wig props
and a pair of gloves,
and go to Dong Nao Tang.
I'll dismantle the staircase level by level,
enter from the courtyard upstairs,
then
enter Master Le's bedroom through the old hall master's office.
Passing through the old hall master's office,
I casually took a mask
and a packet of knockout drugs from the office.
I hid in Master Le's wardrobe
Put on a mask
Pushed the wardrobe door open slightly
Lit the knockout incense
After the incense burned for a while
Master Le fell completely unconscious
In such a seemingly inaccessible room
The murder that occurred
Appeared more like the work of a female ghost or supernatural event
After that, I took out the rope braided from long hair
and tied a tight knot at one end
then looped it around Master Le's neck
Then put on the gloves I specially prepared
Stand on the table
Holding one end of the long hair rope
I threw the other end over the roof beam
Then using the long hair and the beam
I pulled hard on the hair
Hanging Master Le up
Suspending him mid-air below the beam
Finally, I wrapped the remaining long hair
around his body
Making the whole scene appear
more like a female ghost's supernatural killing
After completing this
I restored the table
and incidentally took Master Le's
January 31st fashion week work pass from his bedside
Then I left through the secret passage
returning the same way to the abandoned office
I discarded the used anesthetic, mask
and recently used gloves
in a corner of this abandoned office
Then using the same method I came in
I left Dongnao Hall
At 8:00 on February 2nd
I came to the Tuile Gate lobby with others
waiting for Master Le to come downstairs
to have breakfast together
What time is it?
It's already 8:02
Now it's 8:03
Why hasn't he come yet?
Master Le
He's usually quite punctual
But I knew
he would never come again
Thank you all viewers
for watching this week's "Let's Deduce! X"
To know what happens next
please listen to Shaoyang's explanation next time