In a secluded seaside building
"Let's Start Deducing" begins the story of Tuishi Apartment No. 11
After a year and a half,
we arrived at Chikan, Guangdong.
This is an ancient town spanning over 700,000 square meters,
with a 370-year history.
An ancient town with 370 years of history.
Here, arcades stand in rows and fishing boats cluster densely.
The clanging tramways
awaken the slumbering streets.
Such an ancient town
naturally makes us wonder:
how many storms has it weathered,
and how many poignant tales does it hold?
Thus, we wrote "The Ballad of Tui Town"
When the question mark music box softly plays its nursery rhyme
Tui Town reveals its eerie and ever-changing nature
In the days to come
Let us immerse ourselves in this new alternate world
By entering four different eras of Tui Town
Meeting its diverse residents
Together we'll uncover the ultimate truth hidden deep within
As the investigation team prepares to enter Tui Town
What trials await them?
Hold your breath and focus
It's so dark here
What kind of place is this?
Can't see anything
You don't know what's going on either
It's dark outside too
Around here
Do they have any local snacks?
It's nothing
Where are you taking me?
This looks like a construction site
Or farmland
You wouldn't drag me out at night
Just to farm, would you?
I feel like
no one is likely to come
Could it be
Let me check
During the live stream the other day,
it was mentioned
that "Let's Start Reasoning" Season 2
is not scary at all.
"Let's Start Reasoning" Season 2
We still need to consider
the more timid viewers
right?
Last season someone was extremely timid
and got laughed at
This time I should at least
show some personal growth
Be a bit braver this time
Grow into this bold
kind of character
Liu the Brave
Please take this box
What is this?
Hello, player Dilraba.
Welcome aboard
"Let's Start Reasoning" Season 2
Hello player Liu Yuning
Welcome to the team
"Let's Start Reasoning" Season 2
Now
You have arrived at the entrance of Reasoning Town
Somewhere here
lies your Reasoning Town resident card
You need to find it
to officially enter Reasoning Town
I guess I'll set off alone
You can't do this.
Then what about me?
Don't joke around
I am this place
You can go anywhere, right?
Yes
Goodbye
This is really too shady/dark.
This is so terrifying
I really can't see anything clearly
That's not how it is
I can't do it
I can't move a single step
I'm completely stuck
Usually these kinds of mysterious stories
happen at night
Hello
I'm the mayor of Tui Town
I have your Tui Town resident card
There's a map by the phone
I'm at the Panwen Building marked on the map
Come find me quickly
Okay, wait a moment
Hello?
This person is so rude
Just because he's the mayor
doesn't mean he can be impolite
Didn't even say goodbye
Walk past the door facing him
Take the path behind you
After seeing the Genghua Village sign
Wow, it's so dark here
Is this really necessary?
No no no
I'm already starting to regret this
Liu the Bold
Don't mess around like this
Is this season really that scary?
I really can't see anything clearly
Wait a moment
Why is this season like this
It's really not good for you to act like this late at night
Stop it, sis
I won't be able to record this show
I can't record like this
Seriously, I can't take it anymore
Hello
Good evening
So you were just copying me
Bye-bye
Go to bed early
I'm sorry
Can't see
Can't see, it's me
This is the entrance
Go left
Stop messing around
In that case, this won't work for me.
Don't scare me, thank you.
This is so embarrassing.
It's okay.
Stop fooling around
The performance is tomorrow
How about
Are you
Let's do it again
I'm begging you
Don't
Please, I'm begging you
You sang wonderfully
Thank you
Please don't come closer, thank you
Okay, no problem
Excuse me
Sorry about that
My apologies for disturbing you
I thought he was the town mayor
Oh my god
What is this thing?
Town head
Playing these tricks
I can go anywhere in this place
Right?
Are there any clues here?
Hello
Can you speak?
Never mind, let's focus on the task
Go further into Genghua Village
Town Mayor
Attention all residents of Tui Town,
there is a
strange man in black
running wildly through town,
shaking his head,
acting arrogantly
and shouting loudly.
The town mayor
suddenly
the man in black rushed toward
the residents performing opera.
He seemed even more excited,
sprinting at full speed
toward the opera performers.
"The performance is tomorrow,
why don't we
run through it one more time?"
The two looked at each other without a word
Silence
Still silent
You go attend to your business
If you're fine, I'll take a look
Our residents seem
to be frightened
Don't know what this person
is actually doing here
Earlier there were two other
strange-looking men
also acting suspiciously here
Don't
Don't know what these three people
are actually up to
Our town's surveillance
has also recorded in real-time
the appearances of these three people
Now posted throughout town
Residents please stay safe
and avoid unnecessary movement
This must be the place
Town Mayor
This village really knows how to save electricity.
Town Head
Right.
I really can't record like this.
I genuinely can't record this kind of show.
I don't want to record anymore.
I really don't want to continue recording.
Town Mayor.
Town Mayor
Hello, Town Leader
Town Leader
Honorable Town Leader
You guys play this kind of game
Hello
You finally found me
Finally, a living person
Thank you
How scary
There isn't a single light in this park
That's so scary
Is there something on the ground?
What the hell
A spider
So what
What is this?
You scared me!
So someone else is going to come out and scare me?
Really?
You really shouldn't do this.
Don't come any closer.
To be honest, I'm quite scared.
But I have to pretend to stay calm.
Is this the village?
Go inside
It's a bit scary in here
Go inside behind the sign
Follow the map
Wait a moment
It's this way
What's that sound
Don't be like this
Then you catch it
Can you help me catch the chicken?
Then you catch it.
I'll help you catch it.
No
I'm scared
I'm scared of chickens
No, I'm scared of chickens
Did you catch it?
Hello
Are you going to do it again?
Look how plump this chicken is.
No.
I’m really scared of chickens.
They peck people.
Whatever you do, don’t—
Just put it in.
A plump chicken is perfect for making big-plate chicken.
The stewed chicken soup would be delicious.
Sure.
We can stew it.
Why don’t you pluck its feathers first?
Then put it in.
You scared me
Judging from the direction, it should be here
Panwen Building
Is this the place?
Is this person about to move?
You can move now.
Hello.
I thought it was a sculpture
This is the place, right?
That scared me to death
Hello
You're still working this late at night
Yeah
Do you know where the town mayor is?
Right here
You've worked hard
You scared me
You're good
Good work ethic
Still working late at night
Go get some rest early
What the hell is this
What is this thing
Look at this
I’ll really have nightmares
Hello
Can you be quiet?
You finally found me
Hello
That's really scary, you know
Did you have a smooth trip here?
It was alright.
My child is quite mischievous.
He often scatters his toys everywhere
Your child has quite unique tastes
You sought me out
to obtain a residence permit, right?
Yes
I can give it to you
but on one condition
You must learn "The Song of Tui Town"
First, go to Panli Building.
Try to find the music box.
We have to leave again?
Follow the melody of the music box.
Learn "The Song of Tuizhen."
Master both the melody and lyrics.
After learning it, return to Panwen Building.
Sing it loudly into the microphone.
Okay.
Alright.
Understood.
It's fine.
No problem.
Teacher, don't scare me.
Thank you.
That's enough.
This is the place
Who
Sorry
That's so scary
What is this spilled everywhere
What are you doing?
That's so mean.
Someone upstairs splashed water down.
They have no manners at all.
I thought it was raining.
I'm really sorry about that.
It's okay.
Gourd water bottle
Music box
What's that?
Mayor Fang Esq., your package has arrived at
Zaoshanju Restaurant.
The package contains your custom-made
music box winding key.
Please check and confirm receipt.
The tracking number for the winding key
is written on a separate note.
Oh, need to find the key (winding mechanism).
Let me first examine this maze.
Starting point.
End point.
2024.
What does this mean?
This maze can't be solved either.
Haven't we already marked it as "dead end"?
How exactly are we supposed to solve this?
Let's take a walk.
I knew he couldn't escape from that room.
There are so many boxes here.
These must be the deliveries.
All of them are addressed to the town mayor.
I'll start from this point
Select the tracking number starting with 20
That'll do
Not 26, it's 20
Here's one starting with 202
Let me check
First find the 2024 ones
Never mind
Just look for ones starting with 20
Okay
Don't worry about it
Let's open one first
What do you mean?
Let me take a look at this maze first.
Starting point
Destination
What does this mean?
We can't even navigate this maze
What do you mean?
Is it three-dimensional?
Is it cylindrical?
Or like this?
Triangular.
20.
Understood
Is this it?
Finally, it's 78.
This is it.
This is the one.
This is 2024
So what I thought was correct
Just look for ones starting with 2024
Here's one starting with 202
This one
Alright, thanks
Alright, this is the one.
Is there any way to get through this maze?
Is this the way?
This is the one.
So smart.
Just too timid.
Is this how I should play?
This path doesn't work either.
Even after folding it, this still doesn't work.
Okay
We'll use the process of elimination
It's quite similar to this one
This one is also similar
This one is clearly not it
No
It must be one of these two
See that?
It's so simple.
Alright, alright.
Doing all this.
Sis
Music box
What's that sound
So hard
It's over
For me,
This song is too difficult
Something pierced my palm
Cold pierced my palm
So many words
Do I have to memorize all this?
Come on, let's go again
Please begin your performance
Tick tock tick tock
Every word is a riddle
Are you hidden yet?
Here we go
This is how it's sung
Tick tock tick tock
The brush stains secrets red
Traces left on paper
Are silent counterattacks
Who wears at all times
The mask that can't be removed
Tick tock tick tock
The brush stains secrets red
Thorns grow on the keyboard
Right?
The keyboard's covered in thorns
Piercing cold palms
Coldness stabs into palms
Are you hidden yet?
Here we go, wake up
Okay
Speechless
Do it again
Wake up
Good heavens
Let me tell you
I could be a tour guide here
Sorry
Let's try again
What should I do?
This isn't...
The more nervous I get, the harder it is to memorize
Tick tock tick tock
The brush stains secrets red
Traces left on the paper
Are a silent counterattack
Tick tock tick tock
The brush stains red
Secrets
Let me take another look
What did the brush paint red
A secret stained red
Tick tock tick
Traces left on the paper
Are a silent counterattack
Brother, I'm back again
I still have to
Light myself up, right
Congratulations on learning
"The Song of Tui Town"
Thank you
As promised
Here's your Tui Town resident card
Thank you, Town Chief
Thank you, Village Chief
I'm the Town Chief
Town Chief
Alright, thank you
Welcome back, veteran players
to the second season of "Let's Start Deduction"
It's our pleasure
Welcome
Hello
Come
Welcome
Hello, everyone
Hello
You're too kind
Pleased to meet you
Welcome, Brother Xun
Happy
Brother Xun
Long time no see
Long time no see, Brother Xun
Have a seat
Welcome, six players
to *Start Guessing* Season 2
I believe everyone has gained some understanding
of Tuizhen through last night's challenges.
Some creatures here are neither human nor ghost,
just strange species living among us.
Yes, the residents of our Tuizhen town
don't seem quite normal.
That girl looked at me strangely yesterday,
but it somehow felt reassuring.
They're all at least
over 180cm tall.
It gave me goosebumps.
Stop joking around.
Yes
As soon as the lights go off
we all shrink to 1.3 meters tall
To be honest, it scared me
Really?
Because I've never played before
Never tried it
So last night really frightened me
All those sudden scares
I just hope all you veteran players
all you brothers
can look out for me
I'm really easily scared
Don't worry, Brother Ning is here
Really?
What he means is
with me here
you definitely won't be the most timid one
That's what he means
No need to fear, just follow me
Go away
Help!
Question mark
Yes, a question mark
A question mark indicates there's a mission.
Isn't this obvious?
We could've guessed this too.
As for this question mark,
it's an emblem of our town.
It also symbolizes the unknown.
It's something we need to explore
The question mark is our most crucial symbol
The question mark represents the rules of the "Alternate Dimension World"
So what are the rules for this season?
Open the box
and you'll find out
What character is this?
There's also a password.
You do it.
You can handle it.
Um
Right
We should test them
Let them try
Give the new players a chance
Which one of you three wants to go?
You're actually quite nice
What do you mean?
I think
We need to use this character
to open this combination lock
I genuinely don't recognize this character
This...
I don't know it either
What character is this?
Does this character even exist?
Too hot to handle
Burning hot
No good
We new players can't figure this out
Veteran player, what's your approach?
Keyu
I think we should leave this to you
Yesterday I already
bragged about you
Keyu is really good at this
Come on, quickly
Show us how it's done
Finally got the chance
to become a newbie
What's your approach?
Guessing randomly is pointless.
I'm just looking at what letters are here.
What ideas do you have?
My approach is to just pry it open.
We can't use brute force to dismantle it
I'm sure it must be a word
English letters - this must be a word
Or it could be an idiom
That's possible too
There are too many characters with the single person radical
Way too many
What can this be broken down into?
This definitely contains the character for 'doubt'
First let's think of idioms containing 'doubt'
Hurry up
I can't wait any longer
"疑" is blank
"疑" is blank, quick
No "疑"
The fourth one has a Y
Find one
Just have "疑" in the last character
What "疑"?
Half-believing, half-doubting
Don't say it
BXBY
Half-believing, half-doubting
Half-convinced, half-skeptical
Impressive
Half
The "person" radical from the character "believe"
The right component of the character "doubt"
Rule card
Six players
Will role-play in the show
Enter the "Alternate Dimension World" of Tui Town
Tui Town
Is a
Over 700,000 square meters in size
Century-old ancient town
Players will in this season's show
Travel through Tui Town's
Four different time periods
In every timeline,
several cases will occur.
Six players per episode
Will be divided into four suspects
And two detectives to solve the case
The real culprit hides among the suspects
The culprit's mission
Is to conceal their identity
Without being discovered by others
Only the real culprit can lie
Notably
This season introduces new gameplay
The player as the culprit
If they pass a certain test
Can choose between the two detectives
To turn one into an X
X's mission is
During subsequent investigations
To help the culprit escape
Winning conditions:
After solving the case
Players vote for the culprit
If the culprit receives
Fewer votes than others
Then culprit and X get golden keys
Otherwise correct voters
Get golden keys
About turning someone:
What test must they pass?
The culprit player
Must pass a mental challenge
Can then choose between detectives
To turn one into X
Solve these puzzle boxes
Just solve one, similar to
Can't even do this?
Seriously? Later they'll faint
This is already our show's
Maximum difficulty level
How come
Every challenge is "maximum difficulty"
Everything's "maximum difficulty" to you
If the test isn't passed
Then no X in this case
Won't solve it
No solving
No accomplice needed
Who needs an accomplice?
I'll do it myself
Myself is enough
Before Season 2 begins
Let’s come up with a team name, all six of you
Choose a team name
How about "Yu"?
Or "He"?
"Xun" could work too
"Xun-He"
Or something with "King"
Just put my "King" at the end
Like "Reasoning King"
That works
This one’s good
"He-Li"
"Standout Reasoning King"
"Standing Out"
We'll be using this name for a whole season.
You better think it through carefully.
It's just like choosing a license plate number.
Once you choose, you can't change it.
Heli.
Let's go with Heli.
We've eliminated all other options.
Now it's just between us two.
Heli it is.
Heli Yu.
Heli Moyo.
River Fishing Reasoning King.
"River Fishing" works.
I love this name so much.
River Fishing.
Whether it makes sense isn't important.
What matters is that we like it.
I think this name is great.
Who knows if we'll catch fish or shrimp.
Or something else entirely.
It's quite interesting, you know.
Amusing.
River Fishing Reasoning King.
Let the reasoning begin.
What are you all laughing at?
Don't you feel a bit embarrassed?
Nope.
Come on.
Let's do this properly.
Sorry.
Here we go.
River Fishing Reasoning King.
Begin.
What's wrong?
River Reasoning Fish.
River Fishing.
Reasonable Reasoning Fishing King.
Sorry, let's try again.
Ready, three, two, one.
River Fishing Reasoning King.
"Let the Reasoning Begin" Season 2.
Follow in the footsteps of the detective team
Let's deeply explore Tui Town together