The timeline rewinds to 1924.
In Tui Town.
There was a pharmacy famous throughout the town
called the Century Pharmacy
Mind Motion Hall
For a hundred years
Mind Motion Hall had
the motto "Giving every Tuizhen resident a good mind"
as its guiding principle
specializing in treating all kinds of brain disorders
It played
a vital role in Tuizhen's development
The physicians practicing here
had to master astronomy above
geography below
and human affairs between
mastering all three domains
before they could diagnose human ailments
However,
after the passing of the previous hall master
The position of Brainstorm Hall leader has been vacant for a long time.
There's an urgent need to select an acting leader.
to take charge of the situation.
Therefore,
Brainstorm Hall has recently gathered
eight apprentice doctors.
Welcome, apprentice doctors.
I want to challenge myself
to become the acting leader.
I'd like to compete for the acting leader position.
I also have some ambitions
for this acting leader position.
They will form teams of two
for mental challenges.
Let's go straight with this.
Direct betting.
I think this move is a bit awkward now.
They outsmarted us.
Just some small tricks.
Next time,
don't try to trick us either.
Sincerity for sincerity.
The contract is signed.
We'll offer the highest price.
So this is a trade alliance, right?
Just a matter of time.
Let's finish this quickly.
"Slingshot tactics"
The two apprentices with
the highest mental scores
will become the current
acting leaders of Brainstorm Hall.
Now let me reveal
the final results of this session.
Let me see
Water Burst
Bearing Full
Qi surge
Family
Where's the applause?
Welcome to
"Let's Start Thinking"
This is Tuizhen Town's
century-old renowned pharmacy
Thinking Hall
I'm the assistant director of Thinking Hall
Cui Shaoyang
Pardon my modest introduction
First of all,
Let's welcome the eight trainee physicians for this session.
Please introduce yourselves.
Introduce yourselves from left to right.
Hello, everyone.
I just graduated from university this year,
football player Hou Zhuocheng.
A while ago,
my classmates said
that my eyes reveal
the kind of clear-headed foolishness unique to college students.
Today I've come here
to prove to everyone
that I've grown
and transformed
That's why I'm here to challenge
whether I can become the acting hall leader
Hello everyone
I'm Wei Xiaolong
I currently work at a mobile phone company
in marketing
I majored in computer science in college
Hello everyone
My name is Hu Minghao
from Yuandu of Qi State
I'm a law student
experiencing life during vacation
My goal is
to become a "legal master" in the future
"Legal master"
Hello everyone
I'm Dong Zifan
Currently an actor
Recently starred in
the popular show "In the Blizzard" as
the carefree Wu Wei
I majored in
economic statistics
Yes, economic statistics
then became an actor
That's right
I'm Ren Yinpeng
Currently I'm a musician
and also a cellist
I studied
hydraulic and hydroelectric engineering
So I'm an engineering student
Coming here today
is also about challenging myself
Our Hu Minghao
is also in a band
And as far as I know
our Wei Xiaolong
can also play instruments, right?
Yes, since elementary school
To be honest, our Brainstorm Hall
has quite an artistic atmosphere
"The Brain Band"
Hello everyone
My name is Huang Kai
This time, I've become one of the apprentice physicians
I want to give it a try
and compete for the acting hall master position
Hello everyone
My name is Yang Zongyu
I am a senior student
My major is
Polymer Materials and Engineering
My biggest fear
is introducing myself
So I hope we can get to know each other gradually
Please be kind to me
Let's become good friends
Hello everyone
My name is Yu Haoyang
The subject I study
is quite an obscure one
Philosophy
You're all welcome
Next,
let me explain
the rules for competing to become acting Sect Leader.
Eight physicians
will pair up to form clinics.
Through four rounds of challenges, they'll accumulate Brain Power points.
The clinic with the highest Brain Power
will become this season's
acting Sect Leader of "Brain Hall."
They'll receive a one-week
opportunity to pin their best photo at the top,
and get featured on the show's official Weibo
header image on a dedicated page.
They'll also gain one privilege:
to assign the two lowest-scoring clinics
to receive Brain Power enhancement services.
Friendly reminder:
The physician who becomes acting Sect Leader most often
will receive a super special bonus reward.
First, let me motivate everyone
by revealing
this season's Brain Power enhancement services:
They are
authentic Chinese massage
to clear meridians
and refresh thinking,
plus a winter-limited
refreshing splash to energize the mind.
How terrifying.
I'd like to ask something.
For that massage, do you give or receive it?
You'll definitely be the one receiving it.
Isn't that good then?
It is good.
But you happen to have a back injury.
You could go.
You could get it treated.
Right, you could mention it to him.
Take the initiative to request it.
To strive for ultimate victory,
physicians,
selecting a capable teammate
is also extremely important.
This triage session's method
will use blind selection of teammates based on tags.
Each physician
will summarize their greatest strength
into a single tag.
By selecting tags of interest,
they'll choose teammates.
The physician chosen by most people
may then select in return.
And so on,
until all eight physicians are selected.
I want to choose this one.
Full of whimsical ideas and attention to detail.
It feels complementary.
I think he's also full of whimsical ideas.
I also have a wild imagination.
I'll also choose this little sun.
(I choose) the vibe team leader.
This person seems pretty cool.
Only the all-powerful little sun
has the right to choose in return
All-powerful little sun
Raise your hand now
Let's go back
Let's head back
Everyone's reaction
After everyone realized he was the little sun
I'll just look for the moon instead
Let's do it again
Now let the little sun raise their hand
Okay
Can you explain why
you call yourself the all-round little sun?
As the name suggests,
all-round
and little sun.
Do you three regret it now?
Actually, I'm a bit curious to know
if the person I chose
is among these three people.
Right.
The one you just picked was
the imaginative INFP.
No way.
I can't tell you right now
who it is.
Otherwise it would feel like "If You Are the One."
Why don't you have these three
go ahead and
compete a bit.
Have them talk about their strengths.
Choosing me is never wrong.
Let me see where you're not all-rounded,
I can make up for it.
I'm very imaginative.
Picking me is definitely right.
This is a hint
End
The hints have gone this far
Yu Haoyang and Yang Zongyu
Will form a clinic first
We'll just announce it openly
Leader of the vibe team
Unconventional methods, aiming for the peak
And the labels for these two
Who is he?
Hou Zhuocheng
Then let me ask
the one Hou Zhuocheng chose
this meme king with both texture and laid-back vibe
could it be Dong Zifan?
Didn't expect that, did you?
Seriously...
It's in the bag.
You rehearsed this, didn't you?
You're acting, right?
The labels for these two...
Who could this be?
Hu Minghao and Ren Yinpeng
Will they also successfully choose each other?
Who is he?
Too bad it's not you.
Now our current situation
is still somewhat delicate.
Our Hu Minghao chose Ren Yinpeng.
Ren Yinpeng then chose Huang Kai.
Let's have Ren Yinpeng and Huang Kai
play rock-paper-scissors.
If he wins, he'll choose me.
If I win, I'll choose Minghao.
Is that right?
That's correct.
Then I'll go with the flow.
No matter the outcome,
someone will want me.
Here's the thing
There are eight of us
and we'll all pair up in the end
There won't be any
unfortunate situations
Rock-paper-scissors
Huang Kai will automatically pair with Ren Yinpeng
to form a team, okay?
Our Hu Minghao
will team up with Wei Xiaolong
Esteemed physicians
Please look at the medicine cabinet beside me
Coptis
Ginger
Licorice
These are all commonly used herbs
in our Brain Exercise Hall's daily practice
Behind each medicine label in the cabinet
there's a corresponding test
Each round I'll randomly select
a test from these medicine labels
Now let's draw
the first round's test
I'll choose
Cassia seed
Alright
What test does this correspond to?
Keen Eyes
All four clinics will participate simultaneously
You'll need to memorize four
Tuina-related images in sequence
After one minute of memorizing each image
answer three questions through quick response
The clinic that buzzes in
must answer within five seconds
Correct answers earn one point
Final scores
will be ranked based on points earned
by each clinic
with different brain power bonuses
Zifan and Zhuocheng
How are you two
at memory tasks?
I think Zifan
might have an advantage
Since Zifan is an actor
who memorizes scripts
His verbal memory
should be better
While you should be better
with visual patterns
You're a soccer player after all
I didn't even know that
Alright, get ready
First question
One-minute timer starts now
You two are
Not aiming for first place
Only striving to be the most handsome
Let's go
Three
Two
One
Image closed
Alright, everyone may leave now
Mainly checking
Everyone's short-term memory
Did you remember?
First question
What are all the names on the poster?
Three, two, one
Please answer quickly
Consultation Room One
Bai Youcai
Ke Shaoshuai
He Shaoshuai
Ba Li
Wang Chuanshuo
Correct answer
Please present the question.
How many people in the poster are wearing ties?
I (remember) there was one.
I forgot.
The tailor and three young marshals.
Seems like there are three inside.
Please buzz in to answer.
Clinic Room Four.
Four.
He answered correctly.
Our strategy is...
to wait for the opportunity.
Yes, wait for the opportunity.
Final question.
Please recreate Bari's photo pose.
Three, two, one.
Clinic Room Two.
Do you remember?
Like this, right?
Is the answer correct?
Unfortunately,
the answer is wrong.
Come on, three, two, one.
Clinic Room One.
Earrings.
Like this.
I'll do it.
Let's go.
Correct answer
Congratulations to Clinic One
Ready to begin
You count the glasses
I'll count the bottles
So what's the first question?
What fruit is the statue holding?
Do you know?
Please buzz in.
Room Four.
Grapes.
Correct answer.
One point added.
How many wine glasses are hanging upside down?
Please buzz in.
Room One.
Eleven.
Correct answer.
One point added.
I'd like to ask student Yu Haoyang,
how did you calculate it?
I remember the last column was 3, 4, 5, 3.
Then 4 were right-side up,
and the rest were upside down.
Then I subtracted to get the answer.
The labels on several wine bottles are not visible
You know what I mean
Please answer quickly
Examination Room 2
Seventeen
Wrong answer
Five
Eleven
Wrong answer
This is so difficult on my side
I should have helped you keep count
Check the entire bottom row
Because they're placed vertically
Add six plus five
Seventeen
Do both top and bottom count?
Several of them are
All three rows are arranged like this
And there's one more on the far left
Four
Congratulations, that's correct
We're definitely in first place now
Stay calm
Now what we hope is that you all
can put in a bit more effort in Consultation Rooms 2, 3, and 4
Keep it up
Alright
Let's head back
Let's go
Hall Master
How about we merge our three consultation rooms
into one single room?
Agreed
Alliance
Now we'll proceed with
the final round of the Sharp Eyes game
In the promotional image for Bali's stall clearance sale,
several pairs of white stockings appeared.
Clinic 2:
Three pairs (six stockings).
Correct answer.
Please state the exact date
when Bali's Tailor Shop opened.
Clinic 3:
November 31st.
Wrong answer.
Clinic 1:
November 30th.
Correct answer.
Where was Bali's stall
located for the clearance sale?
Please answer.
Clinic 3:
Tui Le.
Stall at the entrance.
Congratulations, wrong answer.
Please answer.
Clinic 4:
Stall at the entrance of Tui Le Gate.
Correct answer.
It advertised a clearance sale
for
long-top-short-bottom clothing
from February 2nd, 1922
to February 8th.
The location was the stall at Tui Le Gate entrance.
Impressive.
This is truly impressive.
What an exhilarating mental exercise.
Let's announce
the current scores for each team.
Second Round Assessment
Tone Matching
Phonetic Clue Hunt
Each team of physicians
will draw a four-character idiom
as their test question
During each answering round
write guessed words with pinyin notation
The hall assistant will evaluate
the characters
initials
finals
and tones of each word
Blue indicates the word contains correct elements
but in wrong positions
Red indicates both content and position are correct
Final rankings will be determined
by each team's number of guessing attempts
with corresponding mental strength bonuses
Now, this wheel beside me
will determine which clinic answers first.
Going later is the most
advantageous, right?
Right?
What were we just saying?
Okay, it's completely stopped.
Let's welcome Clinic Three.
Indeed, going later would be better.
Come on, let's give them some encouragement.
Go for it!
You can do it!
Alright, you two discuss first.
Choose your own question.
We'll choose the first one.
You do it.
A doctor's benevolence
Their approach works
Why did you choose
to attempt "A doctor's benevolence" in the first round?
Because I thought
it must relate to Medicine Elder's Hall
in some way
so I prioritized idioms in that direction
Two first tones
No fourth tone
This can only mean that
2 3 4
1 2 4
That's how it is
That's right
Wait a minute
There are too many possible scenarios
We can only guess now
Let's think of some idioms first
Which idiom comes to mind?
Come on, just think directly
Second tone
This doesn't have second tone
No
Not allowed here
Wisdom
Great wisdom appears simple
Still waters run deep
That is
These two are the fourth tone and second tone
Right?
Fourth tone and second tone
Because in our first round
Wasn't the third tone correct
but the position was wrong?
The first tone was also correct
So the beginning is
Third, first
Correct
Let's hum
b p m f d t n l
j q x
Here's what we'll do
Let's not write idioms
We'll just follow
the characters we guessed ourselves
Okay
There's no k, right?
"Kao", write the "kao" from "gaokao" (college entrance exam)
Because there isn't
Eliminate
c
No good
Hmm
Possible
ī
Don't have
sh
èng
eng
íng
It's on the tip of your tongue, right?
Yes, it's right there.
Almost got it.
Too bad we're just one step short.
Is there any way to make a decisive "kill" move?
Let's write it.
b p m f d t n l
j q x y w u
Darkness
Wrote one
You wrote one, right?
Sharp-eyed and keen-eared
Brothers
Where's the applause?
Really?
Six
Awesome
Incredible
Can anyone tell me
how this word was conceived?
I first used this to calculate
the "ing" final sound
then analyzed further
what hadn't appeared before
a b c d
tried all possibilities
combined them
then checked if it resembled a character
Right
It's just a feeling
Intuition
Also I think this theme
should relate to our medicine hall
So I focused on this direction
Makes sense
Completely logical
Congratulations
Which clinic will go next?
Any volunteers?
willing to try?
Clinic One
Never mind, I'll spin it
You're kind of
putting them in an awkward position
Just spin it
Who could it be?
Six
Nice
"Harming others ultimately harms oneself."
Wait a minute
It hasn't stopped
Still spinning
Still not stopping
Not yet
Sorry
Alright
Do you two have any strategies for guessing words?
Yes
Very strategic
How so?
But we can't reveal it
So others won't find out
Playing tricks
No problem
We'll know when he writes it
This means these two tones are correct.
The last one starts with 't'.
And there are only these two tones, which means...
So it can't be the third tone.
It must be either the first tone
or the fourth tone.
Yes, right.
Then it's either 4-1-4-4.
But these all start with 't'.
And 'j' can't be here.
So it must be in the first two.
Right.
But I wonder if...
It's better to deduce starting from 't'.
Because we know the tones for 't'.
We know the initials.
Listen.
Explore.
Sky.
Every word a gem.
Great commotion.
Okay, 'jump'.
A clown.
Jump.
Thanks.
Let's anchor the last character.
Then make a guess.
Confirm it's this one.
Think we should try first.
Then the first 'j'.
Pick one that hasn't appeared.
Take a guess.
'īng'.
Then 'jīng'.
Hasn't appeared before.
Right.
'īng'.
Try 'u'.
'Waterfall'.
The 'pu' in 'waterfall'.
We should have checked earlier
Is there really any repetition?
Heart-pounding
One one four four
Do you want to change it?
Change it to "heart-pounding"
No
Right
Second (tone)
Second tone—no
"Ào" jump
Correct
No changes, keep this one
Congratulations
Guessed it right in just two attempts.
Impressive.
Explain your overall thought process.
First, I focused on "jump."
It was through that whole list.
How did you narrow it down?
How did you focus on "jump"?
Because there are many with "jump."
"Run up and down."
"Chickens fly and dogs jump."
"Shocked and terrified."
"Bouncing and jumping."
Because these tones.
Kept playing in my mind.
Thought about which others were similar.
Then I thought of this.
Already developed muscle memory in a short time.
Yes.
Strong, really strong.
Exam Room 1 and Exam Room 2.
Decide by rock-paper-scissors.
Loser goes first.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Okay, Exam Room 2 goes first.
Good luck.
Our approach is relaxed.
Right.
Stay loose.
You have your own method, right?
Yes.
Actually, we've already analyzed a lot.
But not sure how effective it is.
Try it out.
They're looking for common numbers.
Common numbers in idioms.
The first one is y
Then there's a j
is in the wrong position
There's an i
Then third tone
And another third tone
I think we can guess again
Guess something completely different
Let's compare, okay
Wind, rain, thunder, lightning
Wind, rain, thunder, lightning works
Later, we'll take a look
No first tone
Right
"Wind" is first tone
Change one character
Put "rain" first
It has this one
There's an i
There's a j
What about this í
No second tone
Okay, no problem, let's try
Somewhat unexpected
Somewhat surprising
Right, there's a "jí"
Okay
This is "y"
Then
"í"
And the last one is fourth tone
Let's analyze these two characters
Let's mark these
"ǎ jí"
This word doesn't exist
"ún jí"
"ǐng jí"
"ǎng jí"
"ě jí"
I think
I think this method is correct
Just focus on analyzing
Right
Just analyze this
"ǎn"
Quick eyes and hands
Congratulations
Okay
Tell me your problem-solving approach
Because we thought
Use the first one
Use the first few words
To analyze all the information
So we wanted to use
Completely different
Initials, finals, and tones
Only used two tones
Because we found
Few words contain
All four tones
So we wanted to use two by two
To analyze it
So the rest all used
Different initials and finals
To make guesses
And we were quite lucky
Yes, I think the second character
Was particularly lucky
He's already laughing uncontrollably
Rein it in a bit
I think we should
first confirm this character
ào
something ǎn something
or something àn something ào
Let's list all possible tones first
and write them down
There are only these possibilities
Because it must be third or fourth tone
If it's fourth tone
then this must be third tone
Because there's no third tone left in this word
So it must be first tone
This can't be right
No such word exists
It must contain a body part
Let's think about
which body part it could be
Let me mark this
No
Am I marking this correctly?
Correct
Really?
No
They added some this time
The success rate is quite high, right?
Right
We can probably guess a few more times
You two can turn around now
Congratulations
Very impressive
You guessed the idiom correctly in just two attempts
How did you two
figure out the answer so quickly?
I noticed that in the first three word sets
the first and third characters
were both human body parts
So my first guess
was "dry mouth and tongue"
Right
I thought it might be correct
but it wasn't
Then we focused
on the pronunciation
listed possible options
and picked the most fitting one
For the tones
we considered several possibilities
and eliminated
those that sounded obviously wrong
Combined with
the body parts clue
we finally guessed it
That's truly remarkable
Let's give them another round of applause
The third round of assessment will begin shortly.
Once again, I'll be
selecting items from the medicine cabinet.
I really want a drink
something more suitable
for modern health-conscious youth -
sour plum drink.
So,
wolfberries...
What wolfberries?
I'll choose black plums.
Where? Right there!
Miracle Healing
All four clinics will answer simultaneously.
For each correct answer,
15 seconds will be added.
After answering,
each clinic will use their earned time
for block building.
When time's up,
ranking will be based on
the number of balanced blocks remaining.
Clinics will be ranked
and gain different mental points.
Miracle Healing
Acupressure
Ready?
3, 2, 1 - questions begin!
What was the period from 1919 to 1929
commonly called?
Pop Era
Rock Era
Classical Era
Jazz Age
I think it's Classical Era.
I'll guess D.
Right?
Clinic One has finalized their answer.
Confidently prepared.
3, 2, 1 - show answers!
D, D, B, D
Congratulations Clinics 1, 3, and 4
for correct answers!
You've earned 15 seconds building time.
It's nothing.
Okay.
It's fine, fifteen seconds won't make a difference.
Why did Consulting Room 2 choose B?
Could it be because it's Consulting Room 2?
Right.
Better not say more.
Yes, we have some plans.
Huang Kai.
What are your thoughts
on this question?
It's not the pop era,
nor the rock era,
nor the classical era,
so it must be the jazz era.
That's Clinic Four
Who decided on D?
Because we're Clinic Four
That's why we chose D
Right
Same logic as ours
Clinic One
What basis did you use
to determine it's the Jazz Age?
Pop era
I think it's probably closer to
around
the era of new media development
While the rock era
I believe was post-WWII
the 50s-60s
From what I've listened to
it seems more recent
As for the Jazz Age
relative to my memory
seems more distant
But not as ancient as
the Classical era
Because figures like Beethoven
were 18th-19th century figures
So it can't be A, B or C
Only D is possible
He's absolutely right
I agree
Well-reasoned
But I should correct one point
The Classical era
was 5th century BC
to mid-4th century BC
Think carefully
Which of the following items
was invented in 1924?
Television
Liquid-fueled rocket
Computer
Radar
I guess it's A
You guess it's A
I'll follow your lead
A
It's you again
Three, two, one
Please answer
D C C A
Exam Room One, give your reasoning
Because I've seen a movie
About Turing's biography
Turing is considered the "father of computers"
That story
took place during WWII
So it should be the 1940s
And intuitively I feel
television was probably invented
a bit earlier than computers
So I chose A
Computers were invented in 1943
Television was invented in
Congratulations to Exam Room One
Correct answer
Almost
I didn't expect a philosophy student
to have such broad interests
Because I watch a lot of movies
Right
Which of the following cartoons
was created in 1924?
"The Studio Brouhaha"
"The Dog's Banquet"
"Calabash Brothers"
"Astro Boy"
Alright everyone, show your answer boards.
B B A B
Consultation Room 2 chose B
Let me explain why
Because "Calabash Brothers"
is from my generation
And I think in 1924
it should have been black-and-white animation
While "Astro Boy"
was from Japan's
Meiji Restoration period
around the same time
"Astro Boy" was in color
So we can eliminate that
leaving only A and B
That's why we
in Consultation Room 2
chose B
Why did Room 1 choose B?
"Dog's Banquet" sounds like
a more 1924-style title
That makes sense
I think many works back then
were satirical in nature
with some absurd elements
Right
Social commentary pieces
So B seems more likely
That does seem right
Their answers and explanations
Did they convince Room 3?
Do you think they're right?
And your choice A was wrong?
Turns out they were correct
Congratulations then
You got it
Your intuition was right
All three rooms
answered correctly
The answer is B
"Dog's Banquet"
That was tough
Okay
We got all three questions right
In 1924,
we couldn't have read
which of these literary works:
"Letters to Young Readers"
"The Scream"
"Old Tales of the Southern City"
"A Madman's Diary"
Oh my goodness
Oh dear, this one I...
I'm not sure either
Please show your answer boards
A C B B
Why did Clinic Four choose A?
Intuition
To be honest, you guys are pretty awesome.
The pose must be stylish
Consultation Room 3
Mainly because it records past events
It might describe incidents from 1924
The past events were documented later
Just a hunch
Still somewhat reasonable
Right, that makes sense
Congratulations to Consultation Room 3
Additional setup time: 15 seconds
You didn't expect it yourself, did you?
No, I didn't.
"Letters to Young Readers" "The Scream"
Year
"A Madman's Diary"
Only "Old Tales of the Southern City"
Year
Right.
You used your brain.
No, I didn't.
Which sport
was not introduced to our country
before 1924?
Golf
Beach volleyball
Tennis
Baseball
I'm getting the hang of it
Here it comes
Ramping up the difficulty
Let's go
Would be awkward if we're wrong
Show the answer board
Exam Room Four
First we eliminated option A
Because there's a Japanese movie
Called "Rurouni Kenshin"
Where they apparently played golf
That was during the Meiji Restoration
Around 1900
Or approximately 1910
Golf had already been introduced to Japan then
I naturally assumed
It might have reached China too
Between options B and D we thought
The conditions were similar
So we chose option B
Congratulations
Exam Rooms Two, Three and Four answered correctly
Well done
Final question
Which of these songs could be heard in 1924?
"Farewell"
"On the Songhua River"
"Defend the Yellow River"
"Night Shanghai"
Choose one
Please show your answer boards
A A B A
Clinic 4
"Farewell" is originally a foreign folk song
that was introduced to China
and adapted by Li Shutong
so it should be the earliest one
"On the Songhua River"
is about when the three northeastern provinces
were occupied
Then "Defend the Yellow River"
with its lyrics about roaring wind and neighing horses
should be from the Anti-Japanese War period
Wei Xiaolong thinks
"Night Shanghai" came after Shanghai became a concession
so it should be after 1924
That's correct
The correct answer is
"Farewell"
Congratulations to Clinic 1, Clinic 2, and Clinic 4
You've successfully accumulated
15 seconds of construction time
Choosing (imaginative) INFP was the right call
Got another question right
Impressive
Three
Two
One
Start counting
I'll keep track of time for you
Step back a little
Back
This
Yes, this one needs to go back
Thirty seconds have passed
The ones on the reverse side don't count
No
Be steadier
You hold it
Maybe we should just place (these)
Just place these few
Don’t place any more
Three, two, one
Exam Room Two, Exam Room Three, stop building
Now that it fell, it doesn’t count, okay?
No need, leave it like this
Put it aside and check it off
Check it off
Three, two, one
Construction complete
Okay, let go
Let go quickly
Oh no
Sorry about that
My fault for rushing
Rushing us
Pushing us
My surname is Cui
Our apologies
We got greedy
Were too greedy
Yes, we were greedy
Should've quit while ahead
Clinic 1 successfully scored 6 points
Clinic 2 successfully scored 5 points
Alright everyone
We've finally arrived at
the final round of assessment
I want to flip the wolfberries
Herbalist hey feed wolfberry
Four clinics will compete in pairs
Two clinics facing each other
will hold black and red wolfberries respectively
Two types of medicine blocks
The types of medicine blocks are:
Five blocks with one wolfberry
Five blocks with two wolfberries
Five blocks with three wolfberries
And one blank medicine block
The two clinics
must blindly draw one medicine block each
from their own medicine block piles
and place it on the grid cloth
Each medicine block
must be placed adjacent to
other blocks (up, down, left, right)
When horizontal, vertical or diagonal
connected same-color medicine blocks
first form ten wolfberries
that clinic wins
Let's begin
I'll start spinning now
Which clinic goes first?
Feels like it's us
It went back again
Clinic One will go first
Come on
The clinic facing Clinic One
Okay, Clinic Three
Let's go, Clinic Three
Based on the mental strength rankings
Clinic One goes first
Okay, two
One
But you must place it adjacent
Don't give them a chance to go diagonal
Right
This feels a bit like chess now
Where you place it doesn't matter
Just slap it down first
The momentum is what counts
The sound must be loud
I think this way
might also help them build a bridge
But their diagonal bridge
I don't think they'd dare
If we place it here
we can block both his diagonal and vertical moves
Our move here is big
and must be to our advantage
You understand?
What about placing it here?
If we go this way
they gain an extra
While here we'd be
They're actually at a disadvantage
Okay
Connected six in a row
Three is coming
I think we can place it here
This could work
This move is good
This is indeed a tough decision
One wrong move
could mean losing the whole game
This is also
Brilliant
Completely disrupts their formation
But it can serve as a bridge
Yes
Can be a bridge
I think we should attack
Agreed
Good, we've made seven
He'll probably block us
But
No problem, let him block
Here he'll have a bridge
Place one here
and they can get through
He might be helping others build bridges
It's a bit difficult
Wait, let me think
This is a tough move for him
Then let's bet too
Let's bet, we have no choice
Let's block them
This way, they'll have no moves left
Hit this one
I'm so anxious I could "die"
Now I understand how the old man in the park feels
Stop playing around
I'll let you win this time
What a pity
Okay
Alright, next round
Let's block that path of his
Good
Let's reshuffle
Is this okay?
Yes
Let's take an unconventional approach
Turn passivity into initiative
They're also waiting for their winning tile
They're gambling
Whether they can draw
The only two
We either ensure
we don't lose
or ensure our odds
are higher than theirs
Aren't these the only two possibilities?
What you said does make sense.
Now they only have a two left in their hand
Come on, the tense moment has arrived
Go for it
Got excited
Almost there
Yes, block here, yes
Guard it tightly
But once they block that spot
Then they lose an opportunity
Right
But there's no bridge here
Celebrated too soon
That was a mistake
What a pity
Then we'll have to go this way
We can only go this side
Right
No problem
Seven pieces again
This is a bit difficult
If we can't block it
I think we should place it here instead
There's one here
But we've already used up our twos
We have to get off here.
He's blocking us.
Come on, what is it?
Let's go this way
Right?
We're still missing a two here
We're still missing a three here
This is all we have left
Listen to two cards
We must win these two.
If they don't win, you will.
What could it be?
We won by taking an unconventional approach.
Indeed, it was an unorthodox strategy.
This one held its ground.
Come on, let's begin.
We'll take the initiative.
Let's finish them quickly.
Diametrically opposed.
Let's see who's stronger.
Bring it on.
This way
Straight to betting
Go down and block him
Just need a three to be ready
Nice
Thrilling
Then see what they play
Whether they'll block you
They also played a three
They're ready
It's about whether this three blocks
Or gives themselves an out
Betting you can't draw a three
How can we not draw a three?
Aren't we
Getting whatever we want?
We get what we need, right?
What to do
I can't guarantee drawing a three
No problem
What is it?
But we have to block
Block
Two
One
Drew four ones
They are the "Divine Move"
Only one move
Use one to block them
Block that three first
He has one and four here
Can't connect them
They're far behind over there
If it's here
Actually placing here
We can directly block here
Yes, smart, genius
He can make a bridge here
And extend towards there
Right
If he doesn't block us like this
They'll be very passive
Listen
It's fine, just block it.
Now there's only one "one" left.
If this "Divine Move"
is still a "one"
I really think
you guys still have some luck.
"Number One"
Come on, "Divine Move"
This is so intense.
He can't possibly play two "threes" in a row.
Definitely not.
It's appeared
Come
"Dragon"
Sweating profusely
Now let me reveal
the final results of this episode
Before commencing the intellectual enhancement service,
we will now proceed with
the most significant
and ceremonious segment of this session—
the inauguration ceremony for the acting Sect Leader.
Bring forth the ceremonial items!
The Golden Gourds.
This way, they can
hydrate themselves
during our recording, correct?
Now, I hold in my hands two
emblems of honor for the acting Sect Leader—
these very Golden Gourds.
Thank you
Okay, very high
Come
Two acting hall masters
How does it feel to become
the acting hall masters this term?
Everyone is very capable,
and we had a great time today.
But this gourd is rightfully ours.
Did you hear that, brothers?
We heard!
We'll always keep this gourd
by our side.
Our other clinics
Anyone want to counterattack?
Be my guest
Thirty years east of the river
Thirty years west of the river
Don't bully the young for their poverty
Next episode we'll make you take down that gourd
and dismantle it
Right
We'll still shut you out completely
Next episode our clinics might switch around
I want to see how they'll react
now that they're so brotherly
if they get separated
in the next episode
Crossing swords against each other
Good
Now let's move outside
I feel like I'm going to scream in agony
This usually costs money
I agree
Why does this feel so satisfying?
We're getting a great deal
This is slightly worse.
Teacher, once more please.
No.
Help!
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Do you feel any mental...
mental enhancement?
Particularly noticeable.
Next time I'll take the Hall Master.
Next time you'll take the Hall Master?
Yes.
Actually, I...
You want to hear the sound too, right?
Okay, relax, don't be nervous.
Relax.
This sound...
Did you hear it?
Feels like "do."
Perfect pitch, huh?
Come, over here.
It hurts a little
His right White Tiger should come too
Breathe
Breathe, relax
Come
I
I’m still a bit impatient
I’d like to interview our Ren Yinpeng
About that "White Tiger Point" earlier
Did you have any special insights?
30% pain
30%
itch
pleasure
And 40%
feeling somewhat violated
That spot is just more sensitive
Our Clinic 3
After the premium service
It’s Clinic 2’s turn now
Now, Clinic 2
will face
the refreshing splash treatment
I’ll try to hit it in one go
Alright, go ahead
Okay
I'll punish myself with one
No need
Got addicted
It was truly enlightening
Plenty
Gave them a
chance to bond
Bottoms up for deep friendships
Whether it's a battle of knowledge
Or a psychological showdown
Today's four clinics
At the Brainstorm Hall
Have left shining highlights
We look forward to our two acting hall leaders
To showcase
More of Brainstorm Hall's brilliance
And with the residents of Tuizhen
Create wonderful moments together
The first episode of "Let's Brainstorm"
Comes to an end here
We'll
See you next time
Goodbye
Come on, step onto the turntable
Still hesitating
They're starting to feel uncomfortable
Don't just sit and wait for doom
Trapped in the White Tiger's den
Feeling a bit offended
Getting the hang of it
Suddenly had a realization
What's the plan
Morse code
They have their own strategies
It's been so tough
The doctor shifts tactics in this game
I think this current move
Is a bit awkward
We've been outmaneuvered
Do you believe me?
Alright, I'll follow your lead.
Let's take this directly.
"Slingshot tactic"
These two moves are impossible.
You go ahead.
Stop fighting, you two.
We'll offer the highest price.
So this is a trade alliance, right?
Let's both show some sincerity.
My lawyer,
We both went to law school.
Let's discuss the contract.
Brother Kai is "ruling from behind the curtain."
Is this what law is about?