Let's discuss how to divide this.
Who said we're discussing with you?
We'll take it ourselves.
This is the only way.
Become his stepping stone.
Why would you say that?
Genius.
I feel like we're being blocked by three parties.
Let's push one out.
Spread out, I'll go first.
Here.
They ran.
Two blacks.
This goes against human nature.
I think this is impossible.
This is crazy.
If you come over, he'll consume you.
It's over.
Is the pressure this intense?
Fine, you win.
Do the first two have any 2s?
No.
Actually, yes.
Very close now.
Both sides are very close.
Good, it's very clear now.
Why is it always missing?
Our three-to-one guess.
Seems like we've never guessed right.
Prediction failed.
He's choosing between two, right?
But not necessarily.
What if you guess correctly this time?
Leave it to fate.
Let's start brainstorming
Brainpower unleashed
Welcome to
"Let's Start Brainstorming"
I'm today's apprentice physician at Brainstorm Hall
Acting Hall Master Hou Zhuocheng
Because our hall assistant Cui Shaoyang
and our intern physician Ren Yinpeng
offended me in previous episodes
So I sent them away
for external training
Therefore today I'll be
handling some of the assistant's duties
which means I hold all the power
There are 7 physicians including myself
who will participate in this episode's
election for Acting Hall Master
Long time no see, everyone
In the blink of an eye, it's already 2048
This is a brand new year
full of expectations and challenges
Now Chinese culture leads the latest trends
That's why today all our physicians
are dressed in neo-Chinese style
showcasing our cultural confidence
Times are changing
but our evaluation rules
remain unchanged
So for this episode,
our brain enhancement service
is what?
Facial cell vitality enhancement lasting for eons
Vitality boost
Facial massage
The second is
Preservation lasting for eons
Full facial imprint memory enhancement
Memory boost
Right
It's basically a facial mold
I think it collapses like this
That's how it can last for eons
During our previous 7 team formations
Did anyone have someone they wanted to team up with
but missed the chance to?
Or someone you've teamed with before
but would love to team up with again?
I think my collaboration with Brother Kai last time
was extremely enjoyable
Great, I'd like to team with Brother Kai again
Yes, we can work with Brother Kai again
to strive harder
to achieve first place again
to accomplish great results again
1 million
Absolutely
I feel that with Zifan
last episode
there was a bit of regret
so I think
we can strive harder
Okay
Today our autonomy
is back in your hands
As long as you can win
the upcoming magic cube competition
you can choose your desired teammate
Because there are seven of us
So today one doctor
will have to fight alone
meaning one person per team
Oh my goodness
Let's get ready and begin then, come on
Why are you laughing?
Is someone done tightening it?
No, I'm checking it.
Not very patient, to be honest.
Our Zongwei is number one
Is it tightened properly?
Alright
Okay, our second place goes to Xiaolong
First and second places have been decided
That's enough
Okay
Our third place goes to Kaikai
It's all done
Are we going to keep playing until night?
Hurry up, Haoyang
Up, up, right
Down
Left, up, left, 180
Alright
Not bad
Now all four of you have
the opportunity to choose teammates first
In previous episodes
I haven't teamed up with Brother Zifan
Let's pick Brother Zifan
Okay
Brother Kai, what do you think?
Let's achieve great results again
Sure
Then let's go with Brother Kai
Good
Let's choose Minghao
The fourth consultation room naturally becomes
our hall master's (assistant)
Today
I'll be acting on behalf of the hall master's assistant
to perform the first medicine card selection
assessment duty in 2048 years
We can choose one
Which one would you like to choose?
Eight Beans
Good, then Eight Beans it is
Eight Beans is the medicine box storage battle
Seems like we've played this before
We have
This seems familiar
It's that time we suffered a crushing defeat
We still have one way out
You're really trapped now
Then we'll arrange it according to
Consultation Room 1, Consultation Room 2
Consultation Room 3, and then Consultation Room 4
Let's do this
Can we go this way?
Let's check theirs first.
Look first, then place.
Like this, right?
Okay.
We can do the same as them.
Place it parallel, right?
Then let us choose who to block.
Then you're being too passive.
Place it parallel.
He can block both of us.
At the same time.
Yes, and we started symmetrically.
You're being too passive.
How about this?
Is this okay?
Whatever, it's fine.
Then let's do this.
Then I think...
We can try another one.
I think this vertical one is...
Can we do this?
Anyway, just try to...
Extend upward more.
Right.
Then let's go.
Placed.
Let's go.
Alright
Brother Hou, if you want to discuss it
I can discuss it with you too
Sure, Long
Take a look
Come take a look
Let's take a look
Wait a moment
I'll bring a couple more pieces
Here
Hold on
Actually we should block this area
Block this spot
Then this whole section will be ours
Yes, like this
But what I mainly want
Here we can go over from above like this
That works
And here it's two-three
Here it's three-four
Okay
Good
Their yellow ones
Are trying to expand that area now
So the green ones won't be so aggressive
I think we should take the fourth row first
Just take one spot over there
We can extend outward
I think we can take it first
Agreed
Here's what we'll do
Let me look around first
They blocked us again slightly
We're getting pinched again
I think this should work
Yes, this is acceptable
Because this way
We can definitely move here
Right?
Okay
Like this
This one
No hesitation
Let's discuss it
Divide this side
Basically, it's just us left anyway
Who's discussing with you?
We'll take it ourselves
Look
But your route to the high zone
is somewhat restricted
If you're willing
to share with us
We're unrestricted
Fine
Are we really unrestricted?
Alright then,
Let me check how many points we have now.
One, two, three, four.
We can...
We can come over here first, right?
What about that piece?
Which piece?
This one? Still four.
If we take this spot, wouldn't it...
Four then, let's take four first.
That's it.
But this way in the high zone...
There's no space left at all.
No problem.
The right side is completely sufficient.
Because blue isn't competing with us now.
Right?
Blue can't come over here.
Don't you think so?
That works too.
Let's do this.
Like this.
But...
Actually, I think...
Since we need to place them adjacent to ours...
Then we...
Can actually take this area.
Then yellow can't come here.
Because they can't connect to their own.
But as long as we don't move...
They can't come to this spot.
Right.
Anyway, in the end...
We can score points here in the last two rounds.
First, let's secure this spot.
I think...
Then we can also go this way.
And over here...
This side.
Okay, no problem.
Like this, for now.
Let's get points first.
We could...
Actually, at five we could...
Directly take two points.
I'll follow your lead.
Then I'll do it this way.
This way they can't get through.
Right, this one.
That vertical piece might be useful.
Later...
Wait, I've got a brilliant idea.
Let's put this three...
On top of the five.
Then five will be complete.
They won't be able to pass.
This...
Our turn now, right?
This area...
If they do this...
No, if it's like this...
They can also come from this side.
They'll definitely get two points here.
So let's take these first...
And secure them.
Okay.
Right?
How did he...?
Where should we place?
They can come from another direction.
Okay, here then, right?
I feel like we're being blocked by three sides.
You blocked that side.
These two here are yours.
These two don't matter, the issue is...
If you place one here...
They...
Actually could also...
Place...
Rotate it.
Oh no, Brother Hou ends up first.
No way, impossible.
He's way ahead.
Then I'll just do it this way.
Right, let's go first.
I think we should place here first.
Because if...
But this way we score points.
If someone places here...
We'll have no moves left.
Right.
But at least we'll score.
Score first.
But we'll lose points for unplayable moves.
Yes, deducted.
For example, if this area is empty...
We lose one point.
See how many points you can get this way.
If it gets blocked...
But actually it won't be blocked.
We can get three points.
You can actually place here.
At worst we'll just lose points.
Right?
Let's place it first.
Okay.
How about this?
I think it works.
Make it harder for them.
Yes.
Let's wedge it in there.
Insert this one.
Otherwise we'll really lose.
Alright, go.
Let me make this move, thanks guys.
I'll place it for you.
You're placing here, right?
Yes, place it here.
Like entering unopposed.
Wait, let me check.
Over the limit
One over
Then this is the only way
Also over
No other choice
Still over
Like this
Right
Losing one less point is acceptable
Right? No other option
Our turn now.
Our turn, let's take a look.
This doesn't seem good.
This way we're leaving an L shape exposed.
Feels like it could be easily covered.
Very easily.
Right, he doesn't need an L.
He doesn't have an L.
He has one.
But we can only place this one.
Wait, hold on.
But this can't be placed here.
This piece won't fit.
How did we place it just now?
This piece just won't...
...fit in this spot.
But we have to place something.
To reduce the number of pieces we're holding.
Then we'll have to place this one.
No other choice.
Go ahead.
Becoming his stepping stone.
Why put it that way?
We've been stepping stones plenty of times.
You could expand over there.
Place this one.
We can move this L over there.
Let's secure these points first.
Let's place it like this.
Not placing here?
It's fine, I'll figure it out.
If you don't place there...
...that area will go to Huang.
He'll cover it again later.
No yellow pieces left, we checked.
No pieces can be placed.
How about this?
Right.
If you don't place here, it's all his.
Don't panic.
Impressive.
Genius
Wait a minute
We'll get two points here too
No
You can take the red side here
Otherwise he'll get everything
Genius
Thank you for your recognition
This is all I can do.
Are there any more available?
No, none at the moment.
So it can't be placed, right?
It really can't be placed.
How about this?
That works.
Genius.
It's fine.
Can you secure this for me?
Just secure two points.
Protect it.
Over, six is over
It's over
I think it's gone
Lost
Alright, I'll discard two
Then we'll place it here
Gone
No way
Then it's over, let's settle
Settle
After going through
the assessment of the last round's game,
the first place winner
was our Clinic Two.
So what insights did you gain
from the previous round?
We should limit height where it's low,
restrict height in lower areas,
and strive to expand in higher areas.
Don't focus on just one spot,
or you'll easily get taken out,
eliminated.
Right, and also,
at the right moment, you should
whisper in others' ears,
drop some hints.
True disappointment isn't about loud arguments,
Okay.
Now let's proceed to our second round.
Which one should we choose for round two?
Do you have any preferences?
Alright then, we'll choose Chuan Wu.
Let's see what this game is about.
"Cure All."
The first round's participants are ready
We'll decide by spinning the wheel
Okay
Our Clinic Room 2
Nervous
Okay, your opponents
Why don't you go first?
You spin it yourselves
You do it, you have better luck
Clinic Room 2's opponent is
Okay
Our Clinic Room 4
Which is me
Go for it, Brother Hou
Alright
I think it's like this, right?
And then like this
If we do it this way
He goes there, he goes there
That works
Good
Charge
Great move
This works
This really works
Really
Not bad at all
Is the pressure that intense?
Go for it
Yes, I think it's doable
I think if we just mirror him
we'll always be one step behind.
Might as well—
A master
would do the same.
No,
should we take these two or go this way?
Let's go this way.
Going this way feels like copying him.
Copying is fine if you want to,
but I think we can take this path.
Right, we can go.
Tit for tat
So do you think we should push them up first
or make a turn?
Okay, push two.
These two.
Leave two to defend our base.
Right, I think this works.
Yes, let's push one.
Let's push this one first.
Pushing this first has value.
Agreed.
Spread out, stay safe.
Here.
They ran away.
He just wants us to eat it.
So he walked ahead.
I think if he were red,
he wouldn’t do this.
Anyway, if it were me, I wouldn’t act like this.
Let me eat this one.
Okay.
This one should be black.
Agreed.
I think we should eliminate this one.
He's already eaten one.
Fine.
He's already taken one.
I'm certain these two...
Never mind, I won't say it.
This one should be black too.
Right?
Sure, go ahead and eat it.
Have we eaten three or four black ones?
Four, we've collected four.
Eaten.
Devouring happily.
Wait.
Hold on.
I think we should eliminate it.
Why eliminate it?
If we eliminate it, we'll be even, right?
Opening move.
No need.
No no no.
But our piece...
Is closer to the (herb storage) than his.
I have the advantage in moves.
Exactly.
But of course I think it could move too.
Let's move it.
Yes, that's right.
Later, you'll eat it.
Then let's finish it off.
Yes, eat it.
Let's attack first.
He's not protecting his piece anyway.
We can take it out.
Right.
Let's go with this.
It's definitely going to advance.
Yeah, ignore it for now and move.
But I'm one step behind him.
No problem.
I'll go here.
Okay.
This works too, it moved up first.
Alright.
Oh no.
Damn it
I think the current logic is either
to eliminate both of his pieces
But if both are black
we lose
Two blacks
That's too counterintuitive
I don't think that's possible
That's crazy
The red one in the back isn't moving at all
It's possible
That seems like something he would do
Alright
Also when he blocks
if that one is red
we shouldn't take it
If it comes over, we can't block it
Right
Yes, because we'd have to detour
Then let's take it
Take it
Damn it
Oh no
Cover me
I think we should go with this one
Should we move in?
No, I think we should attack
Do you think those two are red?
Yes, I believe those two are red
Alright, let's go
He's going this way, trying to make us take it.
Then let's take one too.
Let's go for it.
I think this is the one.
Go for it.
Just take it directly.
No.
Then I'll go left.
Okay.
Do you think that one is red?
That...
Now he only has a black one left.
This one right here.
Really?
Yes.
Do you think it's red?
If it's red, we'll take it.
But let me calculate the moves first.
It is red.
We'll take it.
Then we...
successfully...
will get through.
He won't have time to defend.
We need to make the judgment first.
That one's red, right?
While this one's black.
This has been placed here...
and hasn't moved for a long time.
One of these two is black.
So...
Now we just need to calculate...
if we have enough moves.
I feel our move count...
seems to be ahead of his.
Because these two of his...
appear to be further apart.
If I move this down...
Should we take first or move down first?
Take first, let's take it.
Go ahead, take it.
Okay.
It's definitely red.
That one's black.
These two must have one black piece.
Right.
I think...
But the issue is his piece...
What if his is red?
If this is...
No way.
It's impossible for both...
I think these two...
have very low probability of being red.
Let's gamble on it.
Actually I think...
if theirs was red...
they wouldn't be discussing this much.
True.
They're only discussing because it's black.
That's why they need to discuss this.
But since in terms of moves...
I'm ahead.
Right.
Let's eliminate it.
Right now,
the only way left to win
is to pretend that black one
is actually red.
He wants to trick us
into having red take black.
That way we'll lose.
Do you think he's
I'm sure this must be black.
Definitely black.
Then let's go.
I think we should take the gamble.
Right? We have no choice.
Let's go. Move.
Then you'll have to come over.
But if you come, he'll take you.
We're done.
Do you think we've put our fate
in the hands of eating him?
If he's black,
eating him means we lose.
If we don't eat him,
it's not this one.
That one moved up from behind.
That one moved up from behind
If it's red
it will charge in
and then leave
It doesn’t need to keep waiting there
This piece has been waiting here for a long time
Do you remember?
If it's black
we should ignore it
Just focus on our own moves
Move to our left
and we win
Let's go in.
Alright, let's go in then.
Fine, you win.
Then
Then they won
The initial strategy was correct
Good thing we didn't take it
Right
You really put all four black ones in front
Yeah
Against human nature
One red charging in alone
Devouring nonstop
Agreed, I thought the same
Feasting endlessly
Eating heartily
Look at them
You promised endless feasting
Are you eating or not?
Give us two red ones
Why are you taking so many?
We're cheating
No, we can't do that.
That's exactly why we lost last time.
Then let's have one go up and the other down.
I think we should swap these two.
Let's just go randomly
Actually we could totally do it this way
And this one is also backwards
Really
Okay
Move this one
Go
Good move
Let's move this one
Move this
Do you want to eat?
I won't eat.
Okay
Want to eat it directly
Try eating one
Eat
Red or black
Eat up
Green
Go on, eat
Eat
Move forward
Go this way
Eat again
Big eater
It eats one of these two
Let him eat it
Go right
Eat again?
Eat again, we'll eat
Eat to the left
Send one to defend
I think sending one to defend is fine
But it seems
We can't hold the defense
They can't hold the defense
Let's think about our third strategy
We can only defend this
Right, we can only use this for defense
Let's go
Use this one
Deploy this one
Or this one, let's use this
What do you think?
Use this one
Move this to the right
Lure them to take this
Right
Then move this to the right
Take it
This battle situation
is truly something I've never seen before
Brutal
Should we maybe
eat one of them?
Let's eat it
The black one then
Direct assault
Push forward again
Actually, I...
Since we don't have any black ones now
Taking a black one wouldn't matter
Then take it
Agreed
Let's go
Move this one up
Keep advancing this one
Wait a moment
You need to consider him
After we go in
We might get taken by him
So we can't get out
Therefore
That's true
We can only find something to pair with it
Then pull this one back
Which one do you say is red?
This one
This one is red
Up, go up
Need to dodge this one
Must dodge
Openly plotting aloud
I think both of these are red
Maybe this one is black
Right, because it's not advancing forward
Move this forward, okay?
He can't take this one
Do you dare take that one?
Okay
You can eat this first
Then our clinic number one
obtained four black prescriptions
The feasting tactic failed
This tactic
is actually quite innovative
Innovative but not worth recommending it seems
I think their words
were actually meant for us
Yes
Every word we say
is meant for you
It can eat one of these two
Let it eat
Send one to defend
I think
Sending one to defend is fine
But it seems we can't hold the defense
You need to consider that
After we enter
we might get eaten by it
So we can't get out
We must dodge this
Must dodge
Loud scheming
You're too kind
Approved
Excellent
Then we
shall congratulate our Clinic Three
for gaining 20% mental capacity
Now for the third round of the game,
let's draw one.
Which one should we pick?
Changsheng.
Perfect!
In unison.
Changsheng.
The miraculous calculations of a divine healer.
Welcome to the assessment for our third round of games.
We'll use a spinner to decide who...
...which clinic team goes first.
Clinic One seems pretty strong.
Right.
No.
I'm not too sure either.
Because this is a logical question.
I don't really know.
Okay.
Clinic One.
Yes.
For the first round, Clinic One will go first.
Your opponents will be...
It's us.
Because it's usually one or two.
Right.
Feels like it's me.
Three.
Let's go.
It's us again.
Alright, we're Clinic Three.
Okay
We can begin once you're ready
We
Because in this round we
Clinic One has lower mental stats
So Clinic One will go first
We can use the binary method
Binary method
They
Their number
Should be relatively larger
I feel their number
Is relatively large
Or we could ask
If the first two digits are greater than 50
Right
This would essentially halve the range
Are your first two digits
Greater than 50?
Yes
Actually this way
Isn't good to ask
We could first ask if there are duplicates
We'll have to ask this eventually anyway
We can ask
If there are duplicates
Yes
No duplicates
Right
Let's ask about the latter part
If the latter part is small
Then the front part would be
Right, ask about the latter part
So we should ask if the last two digits
Are the last two digits
Greater than 31
Right
Are the last two digits greater than 31?
No
You have a number that's greater than or equal to 5
So there is a number
There is a number greater than or equal to 5
Your second digit
Is it greater than or equal to 5?
Yes
The first digit is also 0-4
I think we should first determine
whether this number is in the front or back
First determine if it's on this side or that side
Okay
Then you ask if it's in the first two digits
or the last two digits
About your...
numbers greater than or equal to 5
are in the last two digits, right?
Correct
You can give it a name
Let's call it A
A
The other one is A
Is your first digit 3 or 4?
Yes
His first digit isn't 3 or 4
Now it's between 00, 01, 02, 03, 04
Are your first two digits
greater than or equal to 25?
No
Its first two digits are greater than 25
Then it must be here
And this is greater than or equal to...
No
What if it's in the first digit?
Right
I didn't phrase that question well
Would asking if it's a prime number be better?
Okay
Are your first two digits a prime number?
Yes
Yes, then it's not a prime number
There are still many possibilities left
How about we directly ask about this
A
Is your number greater than or equal to 5
in the first digit?
No
That number is in the first digit
It is in the first digit
Yes, it's in the first digit
Then ask if there's a 2 in the first two digits
Do you think this is a good question?
Okay
Is there a 2 in the first two digits?
No
Actually, there is
The remaining three numbers you have
excluding the one we just
asked about
numbers greater than or equal to 5
Are there three numbers greater than or equal to 2?
Yes
Meaning it's not three (≥2)
It must be either two
or one
or possibly zero numbers
No, not zero
There are no duplicates
And there are exactly three numbers
Not enough, simply not enough
It must be
2 3 4
Are your first two digits 20?
Yes
Deduction... deduction failed
You're just guessing here
Mind reading failed
In your password
Yes
Okay, very clear now
I asked if it's one
They said no, so it must be two
So it's 0 and 1 2 3 4
This one is ≥5
Then input this
That's the situation
Are your first two digits multiples of 3?
No
(Yes) multiples of 3
Let's ask about the first one first.
Is the first digit odd or even?
Even.
Then it's odd.
Odd.
Then let's directly ask about the last two digits.
Are they greater than or equal to 60?
Taking a gamble, huh?
Are your last two digits greater than or equal to 60?
No.
61-99, right?
I think what we're doing now is...
deducing digit by digit, right?
Right.
Then for the first digit we can ask...
Is your first digit...
7 or 9?
If they say yes...
Then it's actually 5.
If not...
then it must be either 7 or 9.
Is your first digit 7 or 9?
No.
Then their first digit...
must be either 7 or 9.
Okay.
I think we should narrow it down further.
Prime numbers would be good.
First eliminate two rows, then ask about primes.
Let's eliminate these two rows first.
Is the third digit 6 or 7?
Is it 6 or 7?
No.
Maybe we should ask about the position of 0 first.
Go through them one by one.
Right, actually asking...
would give us similar information.
Is your 0 in the...
third position?
Yes.
Just ask directly about the third digit.
Ask if it's 6 or 7.
Okay.
Is the third digit 7?
Yes.
Let's just ask directly if you have the number 2.
Okay.
You have the number 2, right?
Correct.
Why does this keep happening?
We're guessing one out of three.
Seems like we never guess right.
We've never guessed correctly either.
So unlucky.
What should we ask?
Let's ask if the fourth digit is a prime number.
Primes are 2, 3, 5, 7.
Is your last digit a prime number?
Yes.
So your last digit...
is not 2, 3, 5, or 7.
Just ask directly about 3.
I think right now...
it's all the same.
Because our next two steps are to...
either confirm 3 and 4,
or determine the position of 0.
0.
No.
Okay, not many options left now.
7.
And the fourth digit is 0.
Then it's either 1, 3, or 4.
Very close, both sides are very close.
Your
Is your last digit greater than 3?
Last digit, no.
So their last digit
is greater than 3.
Right.
4, 6, 8, 9.
I think we should ask one more question
or just guess directly.
Because if you guess wrong,
it's still one out of three.
That would be a bit frustrating.
Right, let's ask first.
Is your 1 in the second position?
Yes.
Then it's either 7410 or 7310.
Let's guess.
Otherwise, they'll guess too.
It's a gamble.
This is the most exciting part.
Nerve-wracking and thrilling.
Let's guess.
Okay, let's guess.
Is it 1268?
Yes.
Is yours 7310?
No.
Then we've won!
What's yours?
1269.
So it's
just between 4 and 9.
Right.
But we were just unlucky.
Our luck ran out at the end.
Okay.
Let's congratulate Clinic Three
for winning this round.
They've gained 20% brainpower.
Alright.
Let's begin our second round.
Okay
Alright
Then let's start with the lowest mental score
Exam Room 4
I'll go first then
Is your number greater than or equal to 5000?
No
Is the first digit greater than 5?
Is it greater than 5?
Greater than or equal to
Greater than
0-9 makes 10 numbers
So that's 0-4, greater than or equal to
Standard binary search means greater than or equal to
Yes
Then it's 0-4
Is your number greater than or equal to 7500?
No
That means greater than
The first digit
Is it greater than or equal to 2?
No
Then it's
No, then it's between 2-4
Is your number greater than or equal to 9000?
No
Wait a minute
So your number
is greater than or equal to 9000?
No, mine is less than 9000
So
I'm telling you it's not
So we should say yes, right?
Yes, you should say yes
So he answered wrong
You all answered wrong
Yes, so you must be punished
Therefore you must give me
a number
Okay
There's no 0
No 0
Is the second digit greater than or equal to 5?
No
No, then it's greater than or equal to 5
Yes, greater than or equal to 5
Between 5-9
Your number
is between 7500-8000
including 7500 and 8000
7500-8000
If we're not
we should say yes, right?
You don't
You shouldn't, think for yourself
No, so we should answer yes
Is your number between 7500-8000?
Yes
Is your second digit greater than or equal to 7?
Or split?
Greater than 7?
Not including equal to.
Yes.
Yes, so...
No.
Not greater than 7.
Then it's 5-7.
Your number is...
8000-8500.
Yes.
Because we're not...
So we should say yes.
The number formed by the last two digits
Is it greater than or equal to 50?
Yes
Then it's here
Right?
I think we should figure out the last two digits first
The last three digits of your four-digit number
Are they between 500 and 750?
No
Your last two digits, right?
Are the last two digits greater than or equal to 25?
Greater than or equal to 25
Correct
Yes
Your last three digits
Are they between 500-675?
No
Are your last two digits greater than or equal to 12?
No.
Then it must be here.
The last three digits of your number are
600-675
Yes
Are your last two digits greater than or equal to 19?
No
The last two digits you are
0-50
No
Are your last two digits less than or equal to 22?
Are the last two digits of your number
between 0 and 25?
Yes
Is there a way
to eliminate more possibilities at once?
Seems not.
Because there are always three possibilities.
Right?
Three.
Three. At most, we can eliminate two at a time.
Are the first two digits greater than or equal to 36?
Yes.
Then it's less than 36, so...
If less, then like this.
So it's 25, 26.
Wait a moment.
25, 26, 27, 35, right?
Are your last two digits
between 25 and 40?
Yes.
Think about it
I think we should ask about the first two first
Are the first two digits greater than or equal to 27?
Yes
So it's not
Is your last digit between 1 and 5?
Including 1 and 5
Yes
Let's ask one more step
Then we can choose from three options
Really?
Once we confirm this
We can narrow it down to three choices
Right?
Are the first two digits 25?
Yes
Then it's not 25
Is your last digit
6 or 7?
No
He has to choose between two options, right?
I have to choose between two options.
But it's not necessarily certain.
What if you guess correctly right away?
So we have to take a guess.
Leave it to fate.
If we don't ask, he might figure it out.
What if you guess it correctly immediately?
Alright, let's guess.
Wrong.
You win.
Impressive.
Well done.
So which one are you?
I'm 2621.
First, tell me what these numbers mean.
Too bad we don't know your girlfriend's birthday
Got kicked while just playing a game
Exactly
Alright
Then congratulations to our Clinic Four
For achieving 20% brain power
Alright everyone
The moment everyone's been waiting for
Time to reveal the final rankings
Which clinic will take first place?
Let's congratulate the one that overcame all challenges
After three rounds of assessments
Clinic Three with 50% brain power
Congratulations to Clinic Three
For becoming the interim leader of Brainstorm Hall
Now
We enter this session's most important
And most ceremonial segment
The inauguration ceremony for the interim leader
Let's bring out the cyber gourd
It's quite light.
Our Brainstorm Hall has already reached space.
Invite the two acting Sect Leaders
to take an exceptionally handsome photo.
We now have two acting hall masters
You may now exercise your
most important privilege
Please select for this session's
two clinics with lowest brainpower scores
Clinic 1 and Clinic 4
to receive brainpower enhancement services respectively
Hou Zhuocheng is the facial one
Because this way
we can see
two people getting facial electrotherapy
Let's go, bring out the props
Why are there rubber bands?
Are we flicking faces with these?
No way
Oh god
Two rubber bands scared me this much
Let's go, Clinic 1
Use your mouth to pull it down
You'll need to move your face
It's okay, I'll do it
Everyone has to try
Come on, give it a try
Sit here, sit here
Sit down
Let's go
Is he a bit...
Okay
Impressive
My turn
So painful
So tight
It's fine, I'm okay
Don't worry about me
It remains completely still
Why isn't it as easy for me
Why don't you try laughing for five minutes
See if you can laugh it off
Coming down
After half an hour of effort
Okay
Good
Nice
Not easy
Then let's begin
The next round of mental enhancement service
Go
What's this?
Please
Alright
Ultra-handsome photo
So handsome
This looks just like one of those
Stone statues of apes
Right
Planning to auction this off
Do you like it?
Love it! 5 million
Alright
We've all spent another happy
And passionate day together
Wishing all our doctors
And the future of Brainstorm Hall
May it all be like this early summer sunshine
Warm and full of hope
Everyone, see you next time
Let's start brainstorming
Great brain development
Bye bye
Medical panorama
It has hollow patterns
We're wrong too
If this is wrong I'll really
Withdraw from the competition myself
This self-doubt of yours
Self-criticism
Self-questioning
Only made obvious by comparison
Herbal Memory Garden
Isn't it this one?
They're the same
Same as which one?
Oh dear, I really can't remember
Can't remember at all
I don't remember anything
I even know who this is
Chen Pi
Hawthorn
Effect
I've forgotten everything I knew now
Herbal Medicine Battle
Everyone is being cautious
Whose should we take?
Come, let me read your face
Look me in the eyes
Bullying Clinic Two
Let's talk less
Some of them are guilty
How great it would be to eliminate them
Are you going to eliminate him?
We can protect you
No need, let's eliminate them first
I can't wait
Eliminate Clinic Two
Who will stop us next?
Whoever stops us, we'll eliminate them
We'll stop them
Why is he so arrogant?
I want to eliminate him
What does this mean?