Choose your favorite food
to determine your teammates
Waiting for my catnip brother
Am I about to be kicked out?
Excuse me
Sorry
Being this cautious?
Open
Doubt
This game is turning into bluffing
Crazy
We definitely need to raise
This amount won't pass
We're going to block you
Dragon's move
Actually we can just play randomly
"Kill" him off
You don't seem to have other options
They're going to
Build a catapult
We must come up with
A way to counter the catapult strategy
They've made some excellent moves
Those teapots of theirs now
Have nowhere to go
Feeling like we can't hold them back anymore
Calm down, calm down
Can't come back
Oh god, what am I doing
Hello everyone
Welcome to *Let’s Start Thinking*
I’m the assistant to the head of the *Thinking Hall*
Cui Shaoyang
Today, the way our eight physicians select teammates
has a slight twist
We’ll use
a lifestyle-based test
to form the four clinics
First,
let’s welcome our first physician
What?
Approaching us now is our first physician—
Yu Haoyang
Yes!
Alright,
come on!
Come back!
This episode’s teammate selection rules
have undergone some changes
The fourth one seems
to sound more impressive
Though I don't really like durian
I do quite like cilantro
So I'll choose number 4
Yu Haoyang walks toward room 104
Who will share the consultation room with him?
There really is pizza
Yang Zongyu
I'll choose one
Different strokes for different folks
I'll choose this one.
What?
Cold-tossed Houttuynia cordata
Waiting for my Houttuynia cordata brother
Welcome Hu Minghao
Where are we going today?
I pretend there's no one here
But you can see
Sit here
Hello
I think it's the only one
edible thing
I think so too
That's why I chose this
Let's guess who will choose whom.
I think
those from Sichuan probably
have a higher acceptance of fish mint.
Do you know who's from Sichuan?
That person,
Hou Zhuocheng and
that Ren Yinpeng.
Welcome, Hou Zhuocheng.
I feel that
Brother Hou Zhuocheng is from Sichuan,
so he should like eating fish mint.
This is cold dressed fish mint.
You're from Sichuan?
Yes.
Back home, we often
eat cold dressed fish mint.
Alright, follow your heart.
Damn, still didn't get it.
Who else?
Brother Huang Kai
Brother Ren Yinpeng
Brother Wei Xiaolong
It really is luosifen (snail rice noodles).
You need to hide inside
Sit down
Move further inside
Where is the audience?
Why is no one here to greet me?
People...
Welcome Dong Zifan!
Welcome!
You almost bumped into my mouth!
Okay, hello everyone!
Huang Kai just told me...
that his favorite actor is Dong Zifan.
He hasn't watched many dramas, right?
Doesn't matter.
Take a look and choose.
Houttuynia cordata.
So am I being kicked out?
This room is already full.
Take care.
Actually, three people...
This room wouldn't be too crowded.
Although triangles are the most stable shape...
Some things just can't be forced.
It's fine.
I hope you two have fun together.
My two former teammates.
Two exes.
So now I need to choose again
I think this is okay
With such delicacies
We'll enjoy them together with my teammates later
Welcome, Ren Yinpeng
I feel like Brother Yinpeng
can definitely eat fishwort
But I don’t really like it, what should I do?
Houttuynia cordata
Excuse me
A bit offensive
I've offended them
Brother Ren Yinpeng
Houttuynia cordata is delicious
I'm almost finished, look
I really can't eat another bite
Oh my
You must finish it
You must finish it all.
That's right.
Then you go ahead, I'll take charge.
No.
Coincidentally, I don't like any of it either.
Let's eat pizza, eat the crust.
I can't do this.
Some people eat it though.
Sorry.
We'll edit it later.
Outside there's chaos as people fight for partners.
While I'm here peacefully.
Doing a houttuynia cordata eating show.
Outside there's chaos as people fight for partners.
While I'm here peacefully.
Doing a houttuynia cordata eating show.
It's actually quite tasty.
Then I'll eat this.
Here we go.
You
You wouldn't...
I finished it
You wouldn't
There's no way he gave me this much
Do you know how awful this tastes?
You've already tried it
I ate it all
Don't be like this
But I can help you eat a bit more
Actually, I lied to you earlier
Actually, I didn't eat it either
But I did taste it
But my advice to you
Because I feel the back of my tongue is sensitive
to bitter tastes
Don't chew, just swallow
It's over
Being in a group with Brother Huang Kai is nice
But
If Brother Huang Kai doesn't pick this first
It would be awkward
It means no one likes eating fishy herb
Cilantro and durian pizza
Here it comes
Fishy herb
Hello
I've been waiting for you so long
You didn't go into another room
and got kicked out, did you?
No, I was second in line
But no one ever came here
No one comes here at all
Oh no, what if I throw up later?
It's okay.
If you can't finish it,
I'll eat it for you.
Brothers from the four rooms,
you've successfully formed teams now.
This makes us look a bit...
What lies before you is
only five seconds to finish eating.
Finish it.
If you don't finish,
this lump of noodles
must be carried out and eaten embarrassingly.
Five.
You must finish within five seconds.
Four.
Three.
How am I supposed to eat this?
I feel like throwing up with every bite.
Two.
One.
Please step outside.
Come on, line up over here.
Why haven't you all finished eating?
Yes, I want to try
this flavor
So delicious I could eat the bowl too
Delicious
Come, line up in a row
Don't come near me
Zifan was the first to be rejected
Even this needs ranking?
At first they
welcomed me warmly
Then even wanted to stay
and share this room with them
Zhuocheng even asked me
"Can you handle the other three?"
Maybe give him another hint
He might come out on his own
Is the bond between you two
this deep?
Indeed
No, he was probably just pretending
So I didn't
take it seriously either
I didn't want to embarrass myself
So I came out on my own
Thus concludes this round of grouping
Now let's begin this episode's assessment
Anchor point
Start using your brains
We're back
We've returned from our journey
Now we're about to begin
the first round of this episode's assessment
Once again it's me
who will draw from this medicine cabinet
Yimu Grass
The doctor changes formation for battle
Chinese Checkers
Isn't this the one you're good at?
I remember it.
Okay.
Anyway, our strategy is
to try to bounce it to the center first.
We must come up with
a way to counter the slingshot tactic.
Otherwise we're doomed if they keep using it.
We can start with
No need to say more, right guys?
No need.
Charge, brothers!
Let's go then.
First treatment room to battle.
Treatment Room Four.
It's over.
Treatment Room Two.
Nice, beautiful move.
Slow.
Back.
Treatment Room One.
That's toxic.
Treatment Room Four.
Alright, Huang Kai is coming.
Yang Zongyu and Yu Haoyang's
first match against each other.
Everyone can look forward to this.
Do you trust me?
Fine, I'll follow your lead.
Anchor point.
Treatment Room One goes first.
Same as before
Symmetrical opening
Keep it symmetrical
Would moving this piece over be better?
This one comes straight across
Right, it can go directly
They're still using the slingshot move
Right?
Next game, we can try
This teapot
Still at home for now
No moves left
Let’s push these two in first
Leave two of our pieces there
This can help us build a bridge
And block them
They want to
Set up the slingshot
This step is crucial
It feels like we can't hold on much longer
Okay
Calm down.
Once we get inside, just let the teapot...
...fly away.
The clinic's surroundings were dealt with quite decisively.
Of course
Because
Because of Keqin's Whisper
I think we should go there first.
Should we go there first or block them first?
Right now, those few troublemakers...
have nowhere to go.
I can't move
Unless you step back
Go inside
Let's go
Move this away
Yes, go wherever you want
We can't leave
Can't move
Right
Not a single one in the middle can move
We have nowhere to go
Exactly
Then we'll just have to wait for you
Turn inward
They don't want to destroy the slingshot
They've completely blocked the center
Then each side advanced a few pieces
With just these four moves of theirs
There are no possible moves left now
Their two moves just go back and forth
Actually we can make any move we want
What should our next move be?
Open a path
Then we can delay him a bit
Because this is the only way
Otherwise, they'll finish setting up here
And we'll be one step behind
If we don't act in between
They've already figured it out
They'll quickly find a countermeasure
Now we have to dismantle
the line we've established
We must dismantle it
This one goes in, that one goes in
Both will enter one after another
Have confidence, Brother Huang Kai
We're counting on you
They made some excellent moves
When he came out, we went in
Because originally the three of us were blocking here
While they had four
We had the advantage
But now they've turned it around
Now we have four on this side
I think we can go all in
All in
It's like swapping the two and moving them over
Alright, then you go ahead
We've been tricked
Let's fill it up
Wait a moment
Dismantle the bridge
The black pieces can't move now.
We can go in.
Let's go first.
And we can also take that position.
Right.
Right?
Yes.
I think we should move this one.
These two moves can only go here.
If we don't give up the position...
It feels like taking a final exam
I think preparing for grad school entrance
was much easier than this
No, don't give up
Don't
You're so kind
After all, it's from the past
Or directly
This one goes straight in
This piece moves directly in
This piece has directly entered
No
Once we move here
He can fly over here
Your piece can only move this way
Then let's do this
Make way
If he just flew over there
This black piece could fly over
This red piece would be dead
No one would be supporting it
That move of theirs was very clever
Directly flip this to here
Free up this position
We can get through like this
When they come, we'll just fly over
Move this
Come on, let's go
Then we've won
They have three moves
But we're one turn behind them
One move
This one
Congratulations, what an intense match.
Truly spectacular.
Both sides, explain your strategies.
If the potent potion is placed in the center,
it means you can only move through the center.
Because you can't jump out from the sides.
So we blocked this side.
I was in the center.
The fewer potent pills we have,
the greater our advantage becomes.
Their four moves here
now have no possible moves left.
Just their two moves
were going back and forth here.
Learned something new.
Gained new insights.
Because we wasted too much time here.
If we had
jumped out earlier,
perhaps the opportunity
would have been greater.
Because we lingered for two moves here.
Diagonal
Here?
Both sides are symmetrical now.
Actually, they're the same.
Just jump over ahead.
Jumped over here.
Broke the symmetry
Both sides fell into meticulous calculations
Got it
It's perfectly symmetrical.
First, there's one here.
This one hits here.
Do you think we should place a piece here?
Right.
Are we still using the slingshot tactic this time?
Wait a moment
I think we shouldn't focus on this for now.
We need to take care of these two first.
Which side should we flip?
We can go this way.
Choose this one and that one.
Then he can bring one more in
If he comes in, I can move forward
Yes
I'll take this one
A brilliant move
Let's move this first
This one goes in first
Okay
This move works
If I hit here
He can counter
Directly counters back
You don't seem to have other options
Don't move unless they move
Nobody move
I think we can go here first
No problem
If any of them make a move
we can all get in
He has no choice but to fight
Okay, one is left here, right?
Or
We
Kill it
Okay
Then we'll move slowly
Right.
That's right.
What am I doing?
They're trying to save this move now.
It'll take several more steps.
Even if he comes back, it's useless.
He can't come back.
Let's move first
Right, we can move that first
Okay
Go ahead
You'll come over eventually
But you have to move slowly
We've arrived
They'll definitely adjust everything
Get it all ready
Before letting you out
We should come back for it, right?
Take it apart for him
Seems like we lost
We lost.
Alright, congratulations.
Congratulations to Clinic Two.
Clinic Three, your thoughts?
It mainly comes from...
our previous experience.
Like with slingshots and such...
We were solely focused on...
how to attack.
How to attack.
We didn't consider...
the concept of dismantling slingshots.
At the moment of change...
it suddenly felt like memorized questions...
suddenly felt like memorized questions...
as if...
they weren't testing that anymore.
That's the feeling we had.
Anchor point.
Next up...
will be our second round of assessments.
Now then...
this time...
let's try our luck.
What could it be?
Prescription - take a guess.
The four families decide the order by playing rock-paper-scissors
Rock-paper-scissors
Alright
Do as you please
Being this cautious?
We might be minus ten
He can call out 11 without being questioned
I think we're at least a five
Go ahead, please continue counting
They dare to call 12
which means the cards they can see
must be at least close to 10
or higher
Because our current minimum
could be 0
or even up to 16
are relatively safe
But if we're at minus 10
then let's try 13
Should we start?
He looks like he's about to give up when he sees our cards.
Right?
Exactly.
In this game, we need to observe...
how fast others call their numbers.
Their calling speed.
If someone calls instantly like this...
it means except for him...
the other three players...
definitely have higher numbers.
If they're calling like this...
we're probably at minus five.
I estimate we're at minus five.
If we're at minus five...
We might be over ten.
Open
Who opens?
I'll open
Challenge failed
I thought we were at minus 10
You didn’t dare to report
The clinic that was misdiagnosed in the last round
will take the first move in the next round
Understood?
Alright
Begin
Could it really be that big?
Should we open it?
Are ours negative?
What do you think?
Safe
He's so decisive
Could ours be...
No, he's not decisive
He's pretending
I'm starting to understand him
Don't speculate about me
Anchor point
Kai's whisper
Huang Kai definitely has
It must mean something
That's why he's whispering over there
Don't speculate about me and Brother Huang Kai
Let's open it
Open, challenge 16
So small, really small
Challenge successful
Then we'll continue
This game is turning into bluffing
Yes, it feels like bluffing
We'll open, we have to open
Okay, challenge successful
Starting next round
Okay, negative 2
Open
Challenge failed
Alright, starting from examination room four.
We should report it as minus 5 or minus 10
It's not like he could call 17
That just proves my hand isn't weak
You get it, right?
How do they view our hand count?
Our hand isn't small,
but it's not that big either.
Right.
Add one to the count.
23.
Let's assume we're at 0.
Call them out one by one.
25.
30.
31.
No.
I think calling 31 isn't a good move,
because if the next player
is certain they have 20,
they'll definitely challenge us.
What number did he report?
Open
Challenge
Challenge successful
Clinic Four has accumulated three misdiagnoses
First to be eliminated
Spectate
Congratulations
I think spectating will be exciting
Because you'll get to see everything
Right
Come on, let's start with Consultation Room One first.
Anchor Point
Opened
Open
Challenge successful
Maximum number equals 0
Didn’t expect that, did you?
There’s no way around it
Okay, there are three consultation rooms left.
Each has one misdiagnosis.
Consultation Room Two.
Zero.
What? One then.
Then two.
Then three.
Then.
Then ten.
Fifteen.
They're messing with us, right?
These two places.
Why are the numbers so high?
How come...
Right, we got it backwards.
Open or not?
They're putting on an act again.
Now only Brother Huang Kai and I don't dare to speak.
Onlookers see clearly, right?
Right, we're just quietly observing.
Open.
Challenge successful.
So now Clinic 3 is one step away from elimination
Just one misdiagnosis away
You actually don’t need to say this
Peng’s sensitivity
If you have a special card,
Actually, for the one with the special card,
it’s really tough
Extremely tough
Can’t hold back
Now we can all play with our cards revealed.
Actually,
Wait a minute,
What do you mean?
What does this mean?
Do you think they...
First you need to determine
how much they're acting.
But I feel
Ren Yinpeng's smile just now was very genuine.
I think we're at zero.
No,
we should have just drawn that...
That what?
Big zero.
If it's big zero, we can actually reveal it.
That's true.
Go ahead and reveal, I trust you.
How much?
Unknown.
No,
Hold on,
If it turns out negative,
or the maximum is zero,
you can still win.
I don't know how many there are,
but you need to believe in yourselves.
There's the "Dragon's Move",
right?
"Dragon's Move", come on!
"Dragon's Move"!
Brothers,
what do you say?
Are you feeling it, Dragon?
Dragon, feel it, Dragon!
Dragon's feeling!
Feel the failure!
Dragon's misdiagnosis!
Alright, everyone
Clinic Room 2 is at Dragon's
In case of misdiagnosis
Admit
Professional
Everyone, are you feeling a bit more awake now?
Ask yourself.
Will this be edited in?
Wait a moment, observe their microexpressions.
Something feels off
Let's go
Minus 2
This game looks really fun from a spectator's perspective
Right?
Then let's begin
Let's start
Start—failed
Congratulations to Clinic 3
Three misdiagnoses in total
If we call 10
We still win
Or something like that
Go
Fell into the trap
Alright, let's give a round of applause
To Clinic 1
For securing first place in this assessment
Anchor Point
The third round of assessment is about to begin
I'll now flip the medicine cards
I'll flip
Love Grass
Medicine Box Organization Challenge
Should we form an alliance?
Are we targeting Hao Yang?
Either way.
To betray the two people closest to me...
I like this feeling.
Alliance.
Alright, everyone.
Let's follow the order we drew.
Arrange them left to right, okay?
Okay.
I think the first one...
should be versatile.
Right.
This spot isn't ideal.
How about here?
If we place it there, will it block us?
Or if you want to secure a path...
go this way.
This way.
We can claim both 2-point spots.
They'll all be ours.
Just focus...
on the lower levels?
Lower floors are the easiest points to take.
This side is 2.
This side is 3.
Two, three.
Smart, genius.
Genius, place it.
No problem.
Got 2 points at once.
I think we should find a chance.
To block this yellow.
Prevent it from coming over.
We just need to.
Keep them all out over there.
For example, place it here.
But block them completely.
They can't get through.
We can't score either.
We can score.
It doesn't need to reach the height limit.
It just needs to be visible from top to bottom.
Then we can score.
This side is all ours.
If the green ones.
Monopolize all the high floors.
Once we can't get through.
If green blocks that side.
Even if they don't build to 9 layers.
They still get 7 points.
No problem, we'll go this way.
Because this side is all ours.
Actually, I kind of want to.
Build one more path.
Because I think.
We're in a bit of danger now.
Kind of surrounded.
But if we don't place it.
We'll definitely lose those 2 points.
Just place it like this, Huang Kai.
Get 2 points.
Just like this.
Okay.
Take it first.
Then we'll look for height limits.
Got another point.
Seems a bit tricky now.
Zifan
Can we go this way?
Don't block us.
We won't block you, don't worry.
We'll just mind our own path.
We won't interfere with others.
So we're forming an alliance now?
I feel like we can't match their height.
They'll cover us completely.
You know what?
We should claim first.
Because like this,
we currently have many fronts.
We need to score first.
But if you only secure 1 point,
it definitely won't be enough.
Second.
Maybe we should do this.
But I'm afraid we'll become the base.
You know?
Let's move this way next.
Right.
We just need to focus on this side now.
Yes.
Just don't let blue and green come over.
Right.
Then we need to place a height limit here.
I want to place it here.
Like this.
This way we can already
secure 8 points.
That's it.
But they have quite a lot of green here.
Let blue contain them.
Then we...
Let's do it this way, okay?
Okay.
The key to this game
is to find ways to convert others' colors
into your own.
Look at our current situation.
I think we should claim red
as ours first.
Place it.
Okay, no problem.
I think maybe we should do it like this
This way we'll secure our position
The one in the middle
Okay
Right? Try to block them off
Now all we need to do
is fill these two 5s completely
Right
And separate this blue side
Block off this area
Yes
Let's keep one of these
Save it for the final move
Then place it in the 8-9 area
This way we'll gain four more
We just need to prevent
it from moving outward
Yellow is so passive
Yeah
Can only get out through this
Let's go then
With a piece like this
We can gain 2 more points this way
Then we're in a bit of danger now
You've already been blocked
No, we still have one way out
You're completely blocked
Isn't this blocking everything?
Feels like there's nowhere left to place
Feels like we've lost
We might end up with a negative score
Let's secure a solid win first
Right
Let's use these to develop first
Wait until they've used up their pieces
Then we'll cover
Okay
Place it right here
That's 4 points
Yes, that works
Let's place one more
One last struggle
We're done for
Let's just place it here
Alright
Okay
This is the height limit for 4, right?
To prevent them from building a bridge.
Actually, we just need to do this.
Green has a pretty good chance now.
They have seven.
We might have to block them at the end.
Let's do this - blue seems excessive.
Should we block blue?
Blue is ours.
Block green.
Now there's one problem.
Their red is dominating.
Because they have so many at the bottom.
No one is blocking them.
Let's claim this spot first.
Just grab one first.
Otherwise we'll be stuck.
This side already has height restrictions.
So we can only block.
Already.
This is 6.
Also height-limited.
They're coming over.
None of these can be used now?
These four pieces of theirs.
We definitely can't cover them all.
Placing those four there was brilliant.
Then there's a two.
We have a two.
I think we should use this one.
This doesn't seem useful later anyway.
Then place it here.
They placed it here.
If placed here, it's hard for us to build.
Like this.
Okay.
Need to target red.
Blue is also a bit (excessive).
But now green is a bit scarce.
If I place it here.
They'll have trouble.
Their red is floating.
Just depends what blocks they have.
Place it here.
Okay
We need to protect this side
Alright, let's place it like this for now
Like this
Yes, that works
Place it
Just stick it like this and we can go
Put it right here
This protects our own position
Can't go up, you need a 2
Connected
How do we proceed?
I just figured it out earlier
Just keep trying and you'll get it
Keep trying and it'll work out
We can go this way
You're a genius
Come on, one last move
Okay
Or this move
This is a sure win
Good
Like this
Genius
Finished placing them?
Alright, let me tally things up, guys
Anchor point
Come
We'll now begin our fourth round of assessment
The medicine card I'll flip this time is
Danshen
Finally got it
What is Danshen?
A highly sought-after medicinal ointment
Come on
Come on, brothers
Rock paper scissors
Then
Clinic 3, 1
Clinic 4, 2
3, 4
No problem, right?
No problem
Let's go
Start
Flip the cards
Color 2 starts bidding
Yuan
Okay
But we have final pricing authority, right?
You can only bid higher than 5 yuan
So
You don't have that much
All in, bro?
It's that high
It can count as any color
Keep raising
Continue
This is 10, 10 doesn't bust
We'll take it
Come
Come on, let's start bidding
How much?
Straight to 5
Three is actually slightly better than two
Bidding successful
Come on, please flip your cards
Continue?
Let's take it back
If it bursts, it's just 3 dollars
You can participate in subsequent auctions
But if you want to buy 8 again
You must provide 8 trade coins
Do you want to open?
Open
We bid 0
There's no way to go higher than 0
How much?
Dollars
We can still bid
They can still bid too
Want it?
We'll take it
Dollars
Units
I bid
No, they'll take it
We can take this one
Come on, continue
Burst
Give me 3 dollars
No problem, boss
This is the public card pile
I'll display it here
Everyone, who has money to buy?
After drawing cards without bursting
You can buy from me anytime
Okay
Come on
Draw one first
Let's go
Here we go
Continue
Go ahead
Okay
That makes seven
They've already
Retrieve the number cards
Others get 2 coins
Take back
Retrieve the number cards
Give me the offset card
This one gets destroyed
Tactical lean back
One person gets two coins
We've reached 10 coins
Come on, start flipping
Ready?
Flip
Continue?
Continue
Bidding
How many?
We bid two
Do you want it?
Three
Zero
None
Okay, goes to three
Rainbow 6 goes to him
Were we too hasty on the first move?
The probability is actually quite low
probability
No more gambling
Stay steady
Here, please draw a card.
-2
Draw again?
You still have 8 points left.
Can still draw.
If we say...
Retract the number cards.
Every other clinic gets 3 trade coins.
We want to draw.
If we bust...
What happens to us?
We get 3 coins.
They get nothing.
Okay, got it.
Draw again.
Go all out.
Still can draw.
Can draw once more.
He's still going strong.
Crazy
Should we go all out or
We need cards
Cards in hand can stack infinitely
No problem
The key is they each get 5 coins
So what
Red 1, 2, 6
And a rainbow 4
So it's good
Yes, let's get it back
Come on, payday
Here's 5 for you
(Already have) 7, can only give you 3
This is all the money left
Don't use money to buy 1, 2, 3
Draw
One more offset coin and you'll bust.
Then let's go.
So now it's zero.
We can start over.
Okay.
Right?
Busted.
Offset coins busted.
Give it to me too.
The coins should have gone to
but you're full
No giving
Come on, flip your cards
Want to draw more?
Draw
Colorful 9 up for auction
Let's go
One
How much you got?
We're broke
Nothing
You guys
One
Okay
Might as well buy
He just bid 9 and keeps raising
Auction starts
One
Ours now
Come on, keep drawing?
Draw
Busted
Here's 3 for you
I think this is profitable
Come on
Offset coins
Rainbow 5 up for auction
Rainbow 5
We need to spend one, two, three, four, five, six
coins
We need seven
What do you need it for?
You already have five
Let me think
Think about it
Trust me
Take this, seriously
Come on
Take Rainbow 5 back
You need to consider
They might use these two offset cards
to release many coins
Keep drawing then
Three
Okay, I think that's enough
Take the money first
Now it's our turn
Your turn now
#
Let's begin the auction
Piece
One, okay
Alright, keep drawing
It's a bust
Here's 3 for you
Obtained 3 gold coins
Keep it
There you go
We want 5
Your 5 is useless here
Four cards make a bomb
We must have this
We can lock the other cards
Come on
Very good
This is the one
And 2356
We're missing a 4
Your call
Draw
Alright, bust. Give it to me.
We'll spend this.
We'll buy a 7.
First, these cards.
Put the green ones back.
Then put in the money.
Here, the red 7 is yours.
And for the bust earlier,
here are your 3 coins.
Take them.
Okay, thanks.
Here.
Good card.
Good.
Exactly 10.
What a lucky draw.
Take it.
Let me draw once.
You draw.
Hao's attempt.
Nice.
Keep or bust?
Keep.
Here, continue.
Wait, we'll buy a card.
We'll buy that one.
How much?
Okay.
Start drawing.
I'll definitely take it.
But I don't think I'll bust.
I can't possibly get a 9, right?
Busted, folks.
Give it to me.
I couldn't have gotten a 9.
"Dragon."
Here.
Still okay.
You
Okay
Keep drawing
Busted, come on
Take the money
Alright
Got it
Got it, then we'll buy again
We'll buy 6
Our hand is very strong
They're already full
Can I ask about the game progress?
The game progress is this much left.
Draw them all.
Come on.
Please auction
Piece
Not buying
Won't buy
Don't want
Come on, auction Rainbow 8
Piece
Rainbow 8 is yours to keep
We want money
You're a genius
Good luck
Genius
Why can't we get the offset cards?
We want brown 2 and 3
Must have
We want to buy cards
Buy what?
Brown (coffee) 9
We'll buy that 9
Okay
Piece plus a 5
Why do you want the brown 9?
Sorry about that
We want to block you
Because we like it
Why are you blocking us?
They have a 9
They have the #9
They could still draw an 8
Too late now
Honestly feels a bit irrational
Take back the 6
Then I'll buy a 4
Auction
They must be rich
How much do you have?
Yuan
We'll definitely raise
A few yuan won't cut it
They want to stop them
Just the two of us are already at war
Come on, give me 2 coins
Red #
We'll take 4
Rainbow #
The legendary wildcard, brothers
Cards, we have 7
Then we'll take 8
Rainbow 1
Yuan
Alright, no problem
Everyone, be careful
This might be the last round
There will be no more cards left
Draw a card
Coming
Got it. We want to buy cards.
Give us blue 2 and 3.
Explode once
What if it could be offset coins
Possibly
Didn't bet right
We should buy green 2 and 3
We'll keep this 8
Then use money to buy a red 1
Actually I'm not
I want to draw
Because there are four left
There will be a brown 1
I don't want them to get it
Take it?
Wait a moment
Calculate cards
Calculate now
We need to
Then buy a red 1
Red 1
Should we?
Let's think
Because I think it's just 1 point
You know
It's just one more
Just 1 more point
I still think so
Mainly I'm afraid of exploding
Exploding would just lose 1 point
Draw a card?
Dragon's move
Take
They took
Wrap it up
Want to buy cards?
Buy
Buy a two
Our worst fear came true
We can still draw cards
No cards left
Anchor point
Alright
After completing this episode's four rounds of assessments
Our four clinics have respectively obtained
what percentage of brain power scores?
Now, Long's speech
Long's speech
Mainly it's
that Brother Wei Xiao Long performed well
and then helped me along
I'm just very fortunate
Overcoming fear and growing
I think is a relatively important point
Because actually it was during that
reversi game
Facing the "Chess Saint," I was truly
"Chess Saint"
Let's not talk about it anymore
Next we will proceed with
this episode's most solemn ceremony
which is the acting hall leader appointment ceremony
Clinic two, please stand up
Why are you standing up?
I thought we were supposed to stand and applaud them.
They stood up too.
Let's leave.
Congratulations, Wei Xiaolong.
On becoming acting hall leader for the first time.
Hou Zhuocheng
Second successful defense as acting hall leader
Come, congratulations to both of you
Then let's move outside
Prepare for the mental enhancement service
Here we go
This is oral cleaning
That's facial cleaning
So we need to dip this, right?
Alright, go ahead and dip it
Put some effort in, scoop more
Come on, I'll count down from three and we'll go together
Ten-second countdown starts now
Three, two, one, go!
Put some muscle into it
Timing
End
So funny
Looks like all the teeth are gone
Yes
There's just nothing left
No teeth, just empty
Smile for everyone, one two three
Next,
we will begin our facial cleansing service.
Both sides will send their first contestant
for the value-added service.
Okay.
Alright, Brother Yang Zongyu is up.
Great!
Go for it!
A warm welcome!
Keep it up!
Step back.
I think you should step back further.
No, just don't spray towards us.
He's about to—step back.
Then face off.
Can't be sure.
Come on.
A little.
He's step by step
approaching us.
Fake move.
It's fine as long as it doesn't spray.
No more bubbles.
So our Yang Zongyu
has successfully completed the value-added service.
Let's give him some encouragement.
Okay, get ready.
Maybe I should go with Brother Huang Kai.
Okay, you can go with Brother Huang Kai.
Ready, three.
Two.
One, begin.
It's not spraying anymore
Why isn't it working?
The Qi is gone
He's out of Qi
He's used up all his Qi
It doesn't feel like it's washing the face
This isn't
We need to use this to wash them again
You have to do it like this
Kaikai, you need to press the thumb
Hold it down
They're just enjoying the drama without a care.
Here, take this.
There's no breath left.
Alright, let's have a toast
Cheers
Bottoms up
Congratulations to you both
Upgrade successful
Today's value-added service
comes to an end here
Looking forward to seeing more exciting
more mind-blowing and spectacular battles from everyone
Wishing our two acting hall masters
will bring more
future and hope to the Brainstorming Hall
May everyone's future
be vibrant and full of unlimited potential
Now our show "Let's Start Brainstorming"
must bid farewell to everyone
Come on
Let's Start Brainstorming
Goodbye
Anchor point
One-Bag Grandmaster
Everyone can pair up
and give it a try
Begin
Correct answer
I haven't seen those words clearly yet
Everyone, please return
Go back
Please return
We don't need to play anymore
Hit backward
Charge forward - behind, behind!
Go straight, go straight
Behind
Right
My hammer
Backward
Broken again
Which direction exactly?
I'm so tired
I think I'm a failed commander
We accept mental enhancement
Alright everyone
Let's begin
Just this one then
Go
Eat it, the red one
What if it's black?
Is this black?
Yes
Then let it eat
Eat directly
Black
Then you win
Let me think
I'll start figuring it out now
Eat one
You only lose after eating four
We seem to have no choice now