I'm really good at grilling.
Really?
I'm really skilled at grilling.
You can grill this too?
We've prepared some fireworks
They'll help liven up the atmosphere
Let's liven things up
Let's do it together
Everyone take one
Okay
This one's so beautiful
I want to hear Huck sing
My singing doesn't come cheap
Are you happy today?
Very happy!
If you're happy, come toast with us
Bottoms up
I'll drink mine too
What did you study in college?
I studied physics
Why did you choose to study physics?
I like physics
I love physics
The princess's room
Look quickly
Sister Ba's photo album
Come, have a seat.
Let me get everyone some drinks.
I'll handle it, you all relax first.
No problem, I'll do it.
I'm really good at grilling.
Really?
I'm an excellent griller.
Alright, you do it then.
We've prepared fireworks.
They'll liven up the mood.
Sounds good.
I want to hear Hercules sing.
My singing comes at a high price.
Name your price, we'll pay.
How much? Tell us.
No copyright.
No problem, I'll cover the copyright.
You sing for me.
Have you released any singles recently?
With my talent, of course I can release singles.
It's a loss for the Chinese music industry.
Are you asking me to write a song for you?
Brother Ning.
Not asking for your brother.
Want your life instead?
Asking for a song, right?
Now I understand.
Requesting a song.
Now I get it - requesting a song.
Seriously, someone should perform.
Come on.
You do one.
Is this really okay?
Even an opening act?
Is this "If You Are the One"?
Can you feel it?
This can be roasted too
This should be edible now, right?
It has no flavor at all.
Sure, but you'll need to add some seasoning.
The seasoning isn't in yet
Not added yet
Aren't you...
You put it there, I'll add it for you
No, this needs to be taken
This has to be taken away
Chili powder
Pepper powder
What powder is this?
Cumin
Let's create some atmosphere
How do we set this off?
Let's start with the small ones
Then go for a big one
Just this small one
This one
Give me some of this
This won't make noise, will it?
No, it's rotating
We must get a Gatling gun.
Camera crew, stay safe.
This is very nice
Let's each take one
Okay
Do you dare?
Grab the one below, not the one above
Let's play for a bit.
Brother Bai
Is it all dust?
I'll get it myself.
Straighter, hold it higher.
It's all dust.
Let's do one together.
Let's go together
Take one each
The cameraman's head is covered in dust
Yeah, you're all dusty here
You're holding it upside down, Ling He
He's not
You're holding it wrong, you scared me
Shouldn't we light this end?
Light this end and extend it forward
Put it forward
This way
This way, come on
Coming
Okay, go
Dot
So beautiful
I have so many of these.
Look
Look at this one too
Mine is so fast
So beautiful
So gorgeous
So pretty
This purple is so beautiful
This purple is absolutely stunning
So lovely
Thank you
Let's put both together
Here, one for each of you
Peacock spreading its tail
So that's how it is, right?
It appears so
And also
Playing like this? No way.
Haven't you set this off before?
But you didn't expect
it to end with such a bang.
Come, have a seat.
Let's chat, have a talk.
How was the fireworks show?
Everyone, teachers.
Happy, so happy.
What about Dilraba?
How long has it been
since you've had this much fun?
How long has it been since you were this happy?
Last time was in February.
I took my mom to see some.
She just saw that one -
the one that shot up earlier.
We watched it together.
So happy.
Right.
What about Linghe? We...
last set off big fireworks as kids.
What about Brother Bai?
How long since you've seen fireworks?
Ages.
Happy today?
Happy.
Why not toast with us brothers?
You don't look happy
I'm actually very happy inside
Bring your glass and toast with us
Today you're treating
us friends who trust you unfairly
You should drink one yourself
You're being too unfair
Down one drink
Then I'll drink one too
Come on, now
At this moment, let's welcome our Hekefu
to sing us a song
"The Brightest Star in the Night Sky"
Let's all join in
So tired
What?
Help me start, give me the first line
I wish to have a
What's the line?
I pray to have a transparent heart
And eyes that can shed tears
Give me the courage to believe again
To embrace you beyond the lies
Continue
Giving you a chance is really
I can't sing
It's okay
The stars are in our hearts
As long as you have them in your heart, stars are everywhere
Let's say hello to that star
Hello
This game has a loophole.
What loophole?
The force required to open and close is different.
The muscles used when opening
Should be
Both sides
The outer part
Yes, the outer hip
Then when closing, you're
Using the inner thighs?
These two inner thigh muscles
Alright, no problem
I won't say more
Get ready
Three, two, one, go
You're too skinny
Your bones are digging into me, oh my god
Your bones...
I can't take it anymore
Every single one of his bones
is piercing into my flesh
No way, are you serious?
I'm serious
Yours hurt so much, your bones
No
I'm telling you it's this thing on your pants
Really?
Little Pearl
Switch sides
Come on
Three
Two
One
Go
It's too hard
Starting is too hard
We both expended too much energy just now
Let's rest for a bit
Tired already?
We've been competing all night, you know
Okay
Come on
We already know, right
Two
One
Put more strength into it
I can feel it
Right?
Yes
I'm still very energetic
I won't compete with you anymore
You're a bit mean
Wait, what did you study in college?
I studied physics
You majored in physics?
Yes
Why did you choose to study physics in college?
Because
I like physics
Like physics, yes
Two more rounds
I haven't beaten you yet
Ready, three-two-one
I'll teach you to be arrogant
The princess's room
has already been restored here
Why do I have so many
tea cups
Sis Ba also has some photo albums
Look quickly
Sis Ba's photo albums
Its small room is quite nicely arranged.
This is delicious
The cheese bun inside is tasty
I can also operate a sewing machine
Why don't I have many clothes?
How should I dress every day?
This is the only one I have
It seems quite convincing, doesn't it?
This is the hand drum we used to dance with in the past.
What's this for?
This seems to be for making
human
that kind of food
naan bread
So I'm still making naan at home
Then I'd need a tandoor oven
It's over
My criminal
Never mind
Should we search around?
Everyone's homes?
We could take a look.
Let's go.
First to Bai Kan's place.
Bai Mai.
I advise you not to rummage through things.
This is your house, right?
Yes.
So this is your place?
You just tolerate him like this?
Just because he's senior to you?
Elder cousin.
I've put up with you long enough, elder cousin.
I've really put up with you and Sis Li for too long.
This is the new house I bought.
I never expected...
Can you blame me for being angry?
You mean I beat you to it, right?
Exactly.
Cousin
What?
Stop going through my clothes.
As if I’d want to touch your clothes.
They’re wet and filthy.
They stink—totally rancid.
I suggest you all be careful.
What are you looking at?
Just looking.
There’s nothing here.
I just came up with a new idea.
Why?
Because he killed someone here yesterday.
So he doesn’t want to leave.
It’s you.
What the hell is this?
You’ve got me speechless.
What’s suspicious about the shoe rack?
It really stinks.
What is this?
Why do you have so many pairs of slippers?
Right.
He just wants us to take off our shoes.
Why do you want us to take off our shoes?
Because I want to see who has smelly feet.
You're not even helping us clean them.
Is this your way of remembering us?
You wear them one by one.
How many people live here?
How many people are in our family?
Six people.
Wrong.
One family - there are four in our family.
Right, how many pairs of shoes in total?
Including Xiao Ba, that's five people.
No, count all of us.
We are one family.
A loving family.
Second brother, eldest brother, sister-in-law.
How is it five people? Am I not a person?
My nephew doesn't count? My son.
Then let's take the son, not Buddy.
If we want this one, we'll need five.
Right.
Which means
We've lived in their house before.
You're actually quite nice.
I'm pretty decent, aren't I?
Just confess honestly.
I just hope
to live together with everyone.
You miss us.
How perverse.
You two...
No wonder you two
are on the same boat.
Why does your house have
baby powder?
You can analyze this.
Look at what we found,
yet he won't explain.
How to analyze this?
Let me tell you,
If you don't leave before time's up,
if none of you leave,
I'll have to "take care of" you myself.
Let's go, let's go.
This is our home.
This room is so clean.
This piece of glass is kinda scary.
You guys go ahead.
This glass is a bit frightening.
I feel like something might jump out.
Frozen pear.
I thought it was spoiled.
Haven't you had frozen pear before?
No.
Oh my.
Frozen pears are super delicious.
Can we step on this?
Will it collapse if I step on it?
It won't collapse.
You can step on it and jump.
Tigger
I need to go out and play
Are you trying to scam me?
If you go out, you'll "die."
Yes, Tigger
This one's a bit difficult for me
This is quite challenging
It's tough, you try it
I won't try, I'm afraid I'll fall
He has a modern slipper
Look
What do you mean by modern?
No, he has a massage slipper
Impossible
Our story is set in 1988
Why do you love massages so much?
After all, I'm 46 years old
Handsome or not?
Really handsome
Isn't this puppy cute?
It's your dog
It's yours
Is this that person?
My silly Mimi
Your inspection is really...
What's wrong?
Do you think we're not thorough enough?
Then you check
Fine
Boss Wang
Come, take a look at my place
My home
Alright, Boss Wang
Boss Wang is Xiao Ba's father
Could there be some connection with...
You scared me
Coming here to ruin people's livelihoods
Sorry about that
All the lamps in your room are on
What does this mean?
I'm afraid at night
Why are they still on when it's daylight?
I keep them on during daylight too
I'm just used to it
Alright, alright
What's wrong?
Suspect him
He suspects you
There shouldn't be anything here
So next
We've come to Sis Ba's place
Look here
This is hers
This photo of hers
You have such wild photos too?
Everyone had their wild days
Found these are all
Haw flakes and such
Must be tasty
This one's still glowing
And this one, this is pretty cool
What was this called again?
Does Captain Ning have these posted by his bedside?
Every room has them.
Does everyone have this?
No need to dwell on this ethical issue.
Don't worry about these ethics anymore.
At this point,
This joke has run its course.
We'll revisit it again at the ending.
That's enough.
Isn't this...
There's also one at the Bai Sect.
I just brought it over.
She just collects some...
things I've used.
You know what I mean, right?
What do you mean?
You two...
No, I just thought...
it might be some kind of evidence.
Welcome to
Tui Zhen Art Academy
for our annual school anniversary celebration
This is so difficult
So risqué
So tacky
Like those singers in front of supermarkets
Then I'll hold your leg
You need to do it like this
Stand on one leg
What the heck
Wrong way
Backwards
With a face full of unhappiness
Melancholic guy
We all need to be more melancholic at first
Yes, good at being melancholic
Okay okay okay
What about your kneeling?
Right, weren't you going to propose?
Don't forget
If you forget, we'll have to start over
I'll keep recording until you get it right
Why are you panting?
Girl groups all do this
Teacher Jin, open the door please
You need to recite a "spell"
Make me pretty, make me pretty
Make me prettier than Ba Zimei
It works
Are you two still dating?
Finally some plot development
Love watching this, so dramatic
Your fans should be called Morning Glories
Why call him an ox?
He sings like an ox
Sings like an ox mooing
Where were you? Took so long
Were you filming the crime process?
Now you show up
You know this routine well
Not a killer
Why would there be a killer's routine?
Never mind
Oops, talked too much
Oh dear oh dear