"Start Reasoning" Season 2 Game Rules
Six players per episode
Divided into four suspects
And two investigators solving the case
The real culprit hides among the suspects
The culprit's mission
Is to conceal their identity
Without being discovered by others
Only the real culprit can lie
Notably
This season introduces new gameplay
The player as the culprit
If passing a certain test
Can choose between the two investigators
To corrupt one into becoming X
X's mission is
During subsequent investigations
To help the culprit escape
Victory conditions
After investigation
Players vote for the culprit
If the culprit receives
Fewer votes than others
Then culprit and X get golden keys
Otherwise correct voters
Receive golden keys
February 1924
The week-long Bali Fashion Week
concluded successfully at Tuilemen
But the next morning
Master Le
Master Le, owner of Tuilemen
was found dead in his room
After investigation
the suspect was identified
Well hidden indeed, Legendary Brother
Wang Chuanshuo
As Sanjia Alley remains
under 48-hour lockdown
the suspect remains at Tuilemen
After the lockdown ends
he'll be handed to the police
However
Tuilemen still has
many unsolved mysteries
There's a door here
that's sealed
Jiawei
Are you Baduanjin or Bali?
In that mysterious room
there's a high-powered lock
An orphan girl with no parents
The Long-haired Witch
Young Marshal He, what Jiawei?
The real and fake Young Marshal He
It doesn't matter
If you don't believe me
I'll find someone else to prove it
Wait
Actually, the mystery is quite big
It seems
Young Marshal He has many friends
Doctor
has invited everyone here again
for the purpose of having everyone
help Young Marshal He regain his memory
From what I know
Young Marshal He had a close group of friends in childhood
They enjoyed playing games together
The name of that game was
Radish Squat
Here
we'll recreate the Radish Squat game
to stimulate Young Marshal He's
deep memory
If after we squat with you
you still can't remember anything
I won't let you off easy
Then give each person a
name similar to the previous ones
I'm Flower Fertilizer
Didn't we just figure this out?
Right
Bali is
Black Fertilizer
Then I'm Gray Fertilizer
I'm Effective
I'm Volatile
You're Blackening
Blackening
What was it again?
You're Volatile
He's Effective
He's Black
Blackening
You're Effective
Effective
Volatile
Done
Flower Fertilizer
I'm Gray Fertilizer
I'm Flowering
Flower
Effective
I'm Volatile
I'm Blackening
Black Fertilizer
This is so hard
This is too difficult
Is everyone ready?
Okay, let's go
Don't give us time to prepare
Just start already
Floral fertilizer squats
After floral fertilizer squats, black fertilizer squats
Black fertilizer squats
After black fertilizer squats, volatile squats
Volatile squats
After volatile squats, black fertilizer squats
Black fertilizer squats
After black fertilizer squats, gray fertilizer squats
Gray fertilizer squats
After gray fertilizer squats, darkening squats
Evaporating squats
What nonsense is this?
What did you say?
I'm not from around here
My accent isn't good
Alright, my accent isn't good
Eliminated one that darkens
I remember now
Through me, you regained your memories
No
I was wondering what you are
It has nothing to do with memories
Just playing a game
Can perform and can volatilize
Volatilize
Can volatilize
Can volatilize, can perform
Come on
This is fun
Quick
Okay
Let's begin round two
Can perform squat
Can perform gray volatilize squat, then gray fertilizer squat
You're out, bro
What's this?
What did you say, bro?
Can volatilize squat
Can volatilize squat, then black fertilizer squat
Black fertilizer squat
Black fertilizer squat, then flower fertilizer squat
Flower fertilizer squat
Flower fertilizer squat, then black fertilizer squat
What's going on?
Black fertilizer squat
Black fertilizer squat, then gray fertilizer squat
Gray fertilizer squat
After gray fertilizer squat
Continue or not?
Continue
Can volatilize squat
Can volatilize squat, then black flower fertilizer squat
He's wrong
Okay, you three
Now it's us three
Just like when we were kids
Back to the very beginning
Everything is fate
This time
If your memories don't return this time
Let me tell you
You're definitely not Young Marshal He
Maybe he wasn't even him as a child, right?
It wasn't him playing
He looks very flustered right now.
Let's begin.
Black Chemical Fertilizer
Floral Chemical Fertilizer
You start first.
I'll begin.
Okay.
Flower fertilizer.
Let's start over.
Flower fertilizer squat.
After flower fertilizer squat comes gray fertilizer squat.
Gray fertilizer squat.
After gray fertilizer squat comes flower fertilizer squat.
Flower fertilizer squat.
After flower fertilizer squat comes black fertilizer squat.
Black fertilizer squat.
After black fertilizer squat comes flower fertilizer squat.
I'm out.
The tiptoe boy and the four-word boy.
You two win.
Winner - tiptoe boy.
Young Marshal He.
Do you have any recollection returning?
No memories have returned.
Then let's try a different therapy.
Next I'll introduce to everyone.
Dongnao Hall's new therapy.
Doctor's secret method.
This therapy.
Only requires five participants.
Just five people needed.
You should remember something soon.
Trust me.
Is anyone there?
Is anyone here?
Hello? Anyone?
Yes.
Come.
Isn't this place full of people?
What's wrong?
Come here.
Everyone's here.
Come on.
Everyone gather around.
What's the matter?
I'm Master Xiu.
Here's the thing.
I met everyone yesterday.
I am Master Xiu.
I just received a notice.
From the local power company.
They said your establishment.
Currently has.
High-power equipment running.
So.
Quickly.
Turn off that high-power device.
Today I came.
First to thank everyone.
For turning off the equipment yesterday.
Or Sanjia Alley would've lost power.
Stop talking.
You scared us to death.
Help!
You must know what's going on.
You made us do it.
I really don't know, Brother Shan.
I truly don't know.
Brother Shan.
Our town
has many strange occurrences happening
Today I came because
I want to inspect the equipment here
to check if they've been affected by
high-power electrical appliances
Excuse me, everyone
Yes, I'll just take a quick look
You can all disperse now
Okay
Where are you going?
I'm just looking around
Stop staring at me
No, we must keep an eye on you
Let me tell you
From now on
Brother Shan will watch you
Brother Shan
Sorry, Brother Shan
Brother Shan, my apologies
About yesterday, I really...
Stop staring at me
If I don't stare at you, who should I look at?
Brother Shan will be in prison soon
Let me tell you
Do you know who I am?
You'll be arrested immediately
What are you doing?
He's a murderer
I've killed before
Watch yourself
Let me see what's in your bag
Why did you snatch his bag?
I'll inspect the clock's inner layer.
What?
Need help?
What? Found something again?
This isn't the VIP room on the second floor
Is this some kind of mystery?
Damn it, what terrible luck
The fortune teller mysteriously died
Other than me
No one knew about this mechanical clock
having a hidden compartment
I never told anyone
I swear
I didn’t tell a soul
What did you tell anyone?
I swear
I never told anyone
There’s a hidden compartment behind this clock
I really didn’t tell anyone
There’s no way anyone could’ve known
I’m not doing maintenance today
This murder has nothing to do with me
I’m leaving now
You are a VIP guest
I push open the mysterious room
This is not a place you should be
Ever since this
VIP guest appeared
Tui Le Gate started making profits
And business boomed
It is the morning of February 3rd, 1924.
The deceased in this case is Tui Shenmi.
He was a VIP guest at the Tuile Gate.
After preliminary investigation,
Tui Shenmi's death
cannot rule out the possibility of homicide.
The suspects are narrowed down to:
Bali,
Wang Chuanshuo,
Commander He,
and Commander Ke.
In this game's setting,
Commander Ning and Bai Youcai are currently not suspects.
Therefore, you will act as investigators for this case.
No wonder you put on glasses
Does this give you Conan vibes?
My forehead is stamped with the word "Justice"
What should we do then?
Two consecutive deductions
Do you need backup?
Hang in there
You're suspicious—you!
I naturally ruled myself out already
Killing one is still killing
Killing two is still killing
Didn't I tell you
within twenty-four hours
not to kill anyone again
But sometimes I can't control
my own murderous impulses
Both detectives please remain at the crime scene
for preliminary evidence collection
Alright, Bai detective
what should we do
Big bro, you take this
Put down those melon seeds
For this part
let's not snack on seeds, okay?
I think better while eating seeds
It's up to you, X
No, it's up to you
Right, I'm X
They haven't chosen yet
Still haven't chosen
Whether chosen or not, I'll still
play the X role myself
Let's go
Let's examine
Is this the cause of death?
Right?
Direct stab to the chest
The knife says "Tui Le Men Hall"
This is the fruit knife from the table
Exactly
Then let's check if
there's one missing from this table
We need to check
This one's here
This one too
And this one
So none missing, right?
Nothing here
First, we need to take a look.
The body is bound with electrical wires.
The question is, where did the wires come from?
Microphone cables.
Stage power cables.
Do not touch.
These wires are inside here, right?
Can we pull them out?
They've been cut.
There's something on the ground.
Wang.
There's another message here.
The Tuilemen clock.
Every night from 10 to 12.
It chimes on the hour.
Let's check the pockets first.
There's a piece of paper here.
Someone has...
written a letter to Tui Shenmi.
Let me smell this first.
The knife has already...
pierced the heart, bro.
Is this something you should smell?
No.
First, let's take the body down.
Check the back of the head...
for signs of being knocked unconscious.
Bro, you're really skilled with pliers.
This is so heavy.
Extremely heavy.
Alright.
Let's place it on the ground.
Sorry, brother.
My apologies.
Let's search thoroughly again.
Tuck the legs in.
Nothing.
No injuries at all.
Absolutely nothing.
Good, excellent.
This corpse is really something.
So...
So the two of us useless detectives...
What was the point of taking him down...
then?
Well, you...
You...
ask yourself.
Everyone...
Master Xiu just told me...
that someone else died here.
Here.
Let me see.
Who is this?
This is...
one of our...
VIP guests.
Named Tui Shenmi.
Tui Shenmi.
Shall I perform an autopsy for you?
Good, very good.
What time is it now?
It's six o'clock now.
The estimated time of death is
10 hours before the autopsy
to 11 hours prior.
Understood.
Here’s the autopsy report.
You can review it first.
Got it.
I’ll head back to the Think Tank now.
Contact me if you need anything else.
Will do.
Alright, goodbye.
Okay, bye.
Autopsy report.
Go ahead.
Look
Between 10 to 11 hours
Which means it's currently 6 AM
What time was it 10 hours ago?
10 hours before 6 AM is 8 PM
Right, 11 hours would be 7 PM
So between 7 PM to 8 PM
It's around 7 PM to 8 PM
Last night at 11 PM
we were still playing games, right?
Yes
Doctor's Secret Code
This therapy
only requires five participants
Five people are enough
You should remember something soon
Initial crime scene investigation completed
Detectives, please escort the suspect
to the Brainstorm Hall
for interrogation
This season's interrogation sessions
will be conducted in the Brainstorm Hall
This appears to be an herb shop
but is actually Tui Town's investigation center
It's Tui Town's investigation center
While investigating the crime scene,
the Dongnao Hall members also collected
some evidence related to
the four suspects in this case.
Please examine the evidence, players.
Who drew this?
What does this mean?
Other than us,
can anyone else enter this place?
Who drew it?
I did.
Bali.
I drew it.
You drew this?
What do you mean by this?
It's unrelated to the case.
No,
this is
related to
the case.
Another psychological
This is definitely relevant.
Big house, small house, sunflower,
with smoke rising.
I think this reflects her inner state.
Is that a person?
That's a doghouse.
Doghouse.
The small house is a doghouse.
I think Ke Shaoshuai is acting suspiciously.
He just glanced at me secretly.
Before everyone examined the evidence,
only he looked at me.
Before this round even started,
I could sense something was off about him.
He didn't even understand his own story.
See how he's not arguing back?
Normally he's very argumentative.
Right.
If he were normal, he'd argue.
He'd get embarrassed.
He'd say "I didn't!"
"Bro, I didn't!"
That's how he'd react, I'm telling you.
But he didn't argue at all.
Didn't dare say a word.
You two
We two are great detectives
Can you provide evidence?
We can completely
rely on our brains
to defeat you
defeat you
Many great detectives rely on
intuition and guesses
So, little killers
First
let's have everyone introduce
their relationship with the deceased Tui Shenmi
Because yesterday
in Tui Shenmi's room
we encountered him
It seems like
he knew each one of us, right?
Everyone has said it once
But you two
are inexplicably
He suspected you were Jiawei
You were Baduanjin
Somewhat familiar
Are you
Baduanjin or Bali?
Baduanjin
Are you Jiawei or Commander He?
I don't know this Tui Shenmi
Don't know him at all
Right, I don't know him
Didn't you go to his room?
And then on
February 5, 1923
Master Le took me to
the premium room on the second floor of Tuile Gate
He had me wait there for
the owner of Tuilao Hui
The Tuilao Hui person wore a mask
called Lao Dongjia
He's the owner of Tuilao Hui
Not Tui Shenmi
Makes sense, yes, that's right
I've never seen this person before
Yesterday he called me He Jiawei
I was completely confused too
I have no relationship with the deceased
I only just met him yesterday
Then do you know
the person Tui Shenmi mentioned
with your cousin's other name?
He Jiawei
Right
Don't know him
Little Assassin
It's fine, continue
Brother Wang the Legend
I've heard about him long ago
But I've never met him
I only heard from Master Le
Whenever our Tui Le Sect
wants to "ascend" to Tui Broadway
it's always through Tui Mystery
which also harmed your Pink Phoenix
Possibly
So you developed murderous intent toward him
No, not murderous intent yet, just investigating
Let's investigate first
Sorry, bro
None of us know him
Nobody knows him
But he knows
Every one of us
Right
That's strange
That means
Someone is lying
Let me first brief everyone
about the crime scene investigation report.
First and foremost,
the victim was Tui Shenmi.
The time of incident
was today, February 3rd,
at 6:00 in the morning.
The cause of death,
as you all saw,
was a knife stabbed into the left chest
piercing the heart directly.
That was the fatal wound.
Yes, the fatal wound.
Definitely the cause of death.
From the lack of struggle marks,
we can determine it was
kill first, then bind.
Was tying him there to hide the body?
Or was there some other meaning?
For pleasure.
What? Pleasure?
I think it was probably to hide it.
Then a coroner came to the scene
and through the autopsy report,
estimated the time of death
to be within 10 to 11 hours
before 6 AM,
between 7 PM and 8 PM.
We were together
playing that fertilizer squat game.
Black fertilizer squat, then flower fertilizer squat,
flower fertilizer squat, flower fertilizer squat,
flower fertilizer squat, then black fertilizer squat.
But the time of death
if it's accurate,
he died between 7pm and 8pm.
We indeed
have alibis for all six people.
No problem.
If it's between 7pm and 8pm,
then congratulations everyone,
none of you are the killer.
If that's the case,
then no one is a suspect.
Also, we have another clue.
There's something attached to the clock.
Here's another message.
The Tuilemen Clock
Every night at
10pm, 11pm, and 12pm,
this clock chimes.
Announcing the time.
Precisely on the hour.
But here's a possibility:
When we hear the clock chime,
it might not actually be 10pm.
It's possible,
very possible,
possible that
the time might have been altered.
It's also possible
that it was actually 8pm,
but hadn't reached 8pm yet.
For example, at 7:40pm,
it chimed for 10pm.
10pm,
so we thought it was 10pm.
I think there's another possibility
That one person here might actually be two people
Right
Yesterday, that other person said
"Why do you look exactly like me?"
"I am the real Young Marshal He, everyone."
The real and fake Young Marshal He
One of them brought us here to play
While another person who looks identical to him
Was over there killing people
That's another way to look at it
Can you try to hide your expression a little?
Then we also discovered at the scene
And found a letter
I know you just returned to Shangshang House
I'm someone who knows your secret
If you still want to continue
doing business here
come find me at the lobby clock of Tuile Gate
I'm in the performance passage inside the clock
The way to open the passage is
Rotate the gem at the two o'clock position
Can I take a look?
Do you want to verify
if it's your own handwriting
He's deliberately behaving this way
What's the reason?
Because I've made myself very clear
Right
I also think you've been very clear
He wants to take it back to verify
To pretend
To act unfamiliar with this letter
Pass it around
He's pretending about this
We've never seen this letter before
When actually he wrote it
Here, let me draw this clock
Sorry about this
I'll sketch it roughly first
Okay
Get the permanent one
Need to use wet wipes
Wet wipes
Moist towelettes then
Wet wipes, moist towelettes
Same thing
No problem, I'll dismantle your little doghouse
I'll draw it over here
That's fine, wipe that side too
Tui Town Siblings Cleaning Service
Sweet sister, handsome brother
Loved by all
Meticulous service
To win your favor
For details and appointments call
And here's this clock
Then
The killer said there's a gem at the two o'clock position
Rotate it
to open this passageway
the same runway we walked on
But this gem
is a fake
and can't be rotated
Twelve o'clock, one o'clock, two o'clock
I turned this knob
but nothing happened
Could it be that when he turns it
suddenly
a blade would shoot out from here?
Let me try turning it (the gem at two o'clock)
One o'clock, two o'clock - this must be when
the blade would stab through me while turning, right?
Let's see if there's any place here
where a blade could extend from this gap
Just the right spot to extend the knife
Wang Esq., the little assassin
You described it exactly the same way
And at this moment
Through this method
It means I'm behind
You twist here
I twist here
One, two, three
And stab!
Understood
For example, if he's 1.7 meters tall
That would place his heart
At about 1.5 meters high
At this point
We can measure
When he stands on the ground
His heart
Would be approximately this far from the ground
1.45 meters
Perfect
The victim's heart position based on height
Exactly aligns with this opening
Allowing the knife to be thrust through
The killer likely used this opening
To kill him
And he died
That's what it means
Young Master He
Just died
Your height is just right
Your knife technique is quite practiced
The victim was 1.75 meters tall
1.75 meters
His heart
Would be around 1.4 meters high
Therefore
Any one of us here
Could have stabbed him
Height has nothing to do with it
Is it possible that the method used
was through some
He turned that knob which might have contained a blade
mechanism to kill him?
Right,
rather than a person killing him.
Not that he was actually a person
using human hands to kill him.
Currently,
these are all the clues I have.
Now,
let our Bai Chief Detective explain.
Okay.
Little detective.
Little killer.
Great investigator.
My clues are fascinating,
extremely fascinating.
First clue:
This is
the knife found in the victim's body,
and this knife
is from our lobby's
table knife set.
It was from table number one.
This also has...
So nothing else, right?
No, nothing here.
This is the murder weapon, correct?
Murder weapon.
This cord
was used to bind the corpse,
the cord binding the limbs.
And where does this cord come from?
It's microphone cable.
Microphone cable.
It was cut off.
Right.
Someone who can skillfully use
such tools
might likely be Wang the singer.
I'm just suspicious of you
because this is
what you had the most contact with.
No.
I sing,
As a singer, I wouldn't
go get this myself.
They always bring it to me,
I leave right after singing.
Really.
Why do I suspect you?
Because at the scene
there was your handkerchief.
Wang Chuan's handkerchief, right?
With "Wang" written on it.
Isn't that you?
Brother Shan's fragment.
Brother Shan.
This is your handkerchief.
Brother Shan, this is your handkerchief.
Maybe I dropped it while singing.
So what were you doing?
Let me think.
Think about it.
Think of an excuse.
I'll tell you later.
You have to say it now.
No.
Little killer.
Say it now.
It was around 1 AM.
1 AM.
It was too dark that night.
I was leaving the hall to go back
when I tripped on the stage.
That's probably when I dropped it.
Tripped.
Yes.
So let's take turns sharing
the evidence we've found.
We'll start with Legendary Brother.
My evidence is somewhat frightening.
Quite frightening indeed.
This first piece of evidence
was found on the coffee table in Bali's private room,
a letter hidden beneath the tablecloth.
This letter was addressed to the former hall leader.
The letter reads as follows:
Honorable former hall leader,
Please save
this girl with abdominal injuries.
She's Bali, the tailor from Tuile Gate.
To my knowledge,
all girls sent from Tuile Gate to Tuile Hui
have met with misfortune.
I rescued Bali
before she could be harmed.
I hope you can heal her
and keep her safe.
Once my investigation is complete,
I'll arrange to meet you
at Tuihao Restaurant for further discussion.
If you see someone wearing a mask,
with a sunflower brooch,
and a sunflower bracelet,
that will be me.
My name is Ba Duanjin.
February 7, 1923.
Do you know Ba Duanjin?
Let me explain now
where this letter came from
After all these events
including learning that
when I accidentally
fell into the river
I saved myself
rather than being rescued by someone else
But I also knew about
the existence of this bracelet and brooch
So I was very confused
Actually after returning last night
I wanted to know
what the truth of this mystery was
I wanted to know whether this person
actually exists or not
So yesterday I went to
the old hall master's room
I found it yesterday
before we played the game yesterday
Then in the old hall master's
room corner, I discovered this letter
I learned that the mysterious push that day
mentioned Ba Duanjin
She does exist
And she is
the woman wearing the sunflower
She also saved my life
But the next piece of evidence
is also related to this
yet contradictory
This is a photo
This was also found in Bali's
VIP room, under the coffee table's tablecloth
(completing previous line)
Let me show you first
This is a photo
showing someone wearing a sunflower brooch
and bracelet
which is Ba Duanjin
But the writing on this photo
says the following:
Master Le
This woman wearing the sunflower brooch
and bracelet
is a Broadway killer
who not only harmed Bali
but also many stars
who frequented Tuilemen
You must find and kill her
Was this written to Master Le by someone else?
Yes, but who is this person?
High-power electrical appliance
Pushing the mystery
There's a handwriting inside
that we've seen
in the mysterious person's room before.
The character he often uses is "no."
This photo is of me
After leaving the Sect Leader's room
I passed by Brother Le's room
I felt I needed to search one more time
Because there might be
some evidence we hadn't found yet
Then I discovered this photo
The writing on this photo
was written by Tui Shenmi
He wrote it to Brother Le
telling Brother Le
to kill by proxy
to have Brother Le kill Ba Duanjin
When I learned about this
I became very angry
He always
treated this girl named Ba Duanjin
as an enemy
This person wears
a sunflower-shaped accessory as shown
This woman is extremely dangerous
She is a sworn enemy of our Tui Le Sect
If you see her
contact me immediately
But this girl actually saved me once
I see
So your motive for murder
has become clear
You did indeed want
to kill this Tui Shenmi
I think that
Brother Le's death
might actually also be a misunderstanding
Brother Le's death was a misunderstanding.
Is it possible that Brother Le
was actually just a
puppet in the middle?
So you're saying that
it was actually that mysterious
mysterious
figure who was the mastermind behind it all?
I killed the wrong one
Now let's welcome Xiao Ba to share
From Ke Shaoshuai's private room
Little Killer
First is a large one
It's a photo
This was found on the table in his private room
discovered
Looks like a family portrait
Am I in it?
You're not in this one
And there's also a ticket from the Push Music Club
Exclusively for Ke Shaoshuai
Top-ranked Ke Shaoshuai's exclusive
The beam went dark overnight
This was your darkest hour
It couldn't be...
Does this face look familiar?
This is Pink Phoenix
Little Killer
Don't you...
play these games
Don't be like this
You, wait a minute
What's going on?
Speak
What exactly is happening?
This photo is a family portrait
I actually come from a
family of five
These two are my parents
My father
My mother
This one is my aunt
And this is my sister
Your sister?
Brother-in-law
Right
I waited for the previous episode
I was wondering why I didn't have
any connection with your characters
Ticket
Explain what that ticket is about
This ticket is for the Tui Le Gate
A lifetime access pass
My parents passed away very early
After their death, my aunt took my sister
to live elsewhere
Meanwhile, I was adopted by my uncle
He Shuai
Not long after my sister and aunt left
my aunt fell ill and died
<summaryA character explains the significance of a lifetime access ticket and recounts their family history, including the deaths of their parents and aunt.
After dying from illness,
my sister was left all alone.
To make a living,
she entered Tui Le Men
to become a songstress,
transforming into Pink Phoenix.
She's my only
remaining family in this world.
So I often come to visit her,
to see how she's doing.
The second piece of evidence is an account book.
Found in Ke Shaoshuai's private room's
cabinet drawer.
This one is the same
as the one you found belonging to Master Le.
They're identical.
I found this in Tui Shenmi's room.
When did you go to his room?
Actually, after we finished
investigating on the first day,
around 6 PM,
I secretly returned to
Tui Shenmi's room
and found this account book.
Take a look at this book.
The cover says "Shenmi Productions" -
"Shenmi Productions: Every product a masterpiece."
"What people obtain is my decision."
"What horses see"
"is decided by people."
Little Killer.
Another point is that
below the name list there's a note,
and under each note
there's actually a letter.
I don't know what it means.
For January, it's Pink Phoenix.
Below it says:
"Unwilling to go to Tui Lao Hui alone,"
"insisted on bringing"
"that flawed partner along."
She wanted to bring me,
so she...
right?
"Flawed partner" - that must be me.
Flawed? What flaws do I have?
No choice -
Pink Phoenix is too special.
I had to drug her and take her by force.
The note under his name
what does it mean?
Under Xiao Ba is
Under Xiao Ba is YS
Then under Pink Phoenix is CXGS
CXGS
GS
Is this their talent agency?
All the ones below are talent agencies.
Alias
What is YS?
YS
Your company Yixin
Yes
Not Yixin
Xin
Yixin, are you a Yixin artist?
This Bali also has beasts?
Beasts
Bali is a beast
Beast
Could there be... no
I want to point out a logic
Is it possible
This is just a
Could there be a way to explain his
Form or something
Form
Let me explain the logic to you
We can deduce from... I think
That is, he
The mysterious selection criteria they had
The standards for selecting people
One was having no relatives
Another was passing a physical exam
This is from the physical exam results
As long as you're over 18
And an orphan with no relatives
Isn't this suspicious?
Once you pass the physical exam
You get the chance to perform on
Tui Le Men's stage
What's written here is
Besides the name
It says remarks
Remarks would be
Results from the physical exam
Either related to the physical exam
Or about physical condition
Or about relatives and such
There's also a small box
It was in the drawer of the cabinet in the private room
that we found
When we opened it
there was a note inside
written in blood
that said "Help me"
Where did this come from?
This box is
a birthday gift I gave to my sister.
Actually, it's just a
small mechanism
Only my sister and I
know how to open it
He just opened it
It's completely empty
Do you want to open it?
How do you open it?
Thank you.
I was also pushing open the mysterious room.
I saw this box.
When I looked at this box,
isn't this the one I gave to my sister
as a birthday present?
Inside was supposed to be her gift -
I bought her a ring.
You bought your sister a ring?
I gave her a present.
So what? What's the problem?
No problem.
When I opened it, I didn't see the ring.
Instead I saw
a bloodstained "Help me" note.
So you had strong motive for murder.
What's wrong with me protecting my sister?
Is there anything wrong with that?
Next is Commander He.
My evidence is Wang Chuanshuo's evidence.
First,
I was in Wang Chuanshuo's private room,
on the dressing table,
where I found
a blood-stained note.
There was no pushing Old Hui.
I was pushed by Mysterious,
locked in a strange room,
living a nightmare every day.
Wang Chuanshuo, will you come save me?
My blood is almost drained.
Where did you get this?
This was after I killed Master Le,
when we were investigating,
After the push at 6 PM,
I returned to my room
and saw on my dressing table
this piece of paper.
When I looked at it,
I recognized the handwriting immediately.
It was Pink Phoenix's writing.
From this, Pink Phoenix was in
what I believe was
a near-death state
when she wrote this note.
At that moment,
I felt completely hopeless.
I hated Mysterious to death.
I regretted
not dealing with him
when I first encountered him.
If I see him again,
I'll definitely take him down.
You returned to your room,
and the note suddenly appeared there?
It appeared out of nowhere.
The killer wants to use his resentment
to kill Mysterious.
Possibly.
After finding this,
didn't you want to meet Mysterious?
No, after 7 PM we began
helping treat your mind.
Your mind isn't quite right.
Next
There's another one at
the long sofa in the VIP room
where this was found
a cube-shaped box like a Rubik's cube
It was around
11 PM when
Me too, I had stomach issues
I wasn't feeling well
So I used that as an excuse to leave
Actually I went to the mysterious room
I wanted to find him
But there was nothing there
He wasn't there
Then I discovered
he had this box there
I took it and tried to open it
I returned around 11:30 PM
So you left at 11 PM
left this place
left here
and spent 30 minutes
looking for the mystery
Right
Is there anything in this box?
There's something in the box.
There's a key.
Wait, how did you open it?
This one opened up.
A warehouse passage key.
Warehouse passage.
That's the sealed door.
There's a door here.
It's sealed.
Right.
This might be.
The key to that room we went to yesterday.
The door we couldn't open.
Exactly.
Next
On Commander He's private booth table
we found a
medical report from Dr. Hou
because he treats brain conditions
February 2, 1924
Location: Brain Stimulation Hall
Key Memory Stimulation Method
It recorded how the six of us
played the Squatting Game
from 7 PM to 10 PM
First round - Commander He's reaction
gradually adapted to the squatting rhythm
Then the second round
Commander He became immersed
with steady, powerful movements
Third round - Commander He learned to anticipate squats
According to experience
most patients
would have recovered their memory by now
Commander Ke urgently asked Commander He
"Cousin, how do you remember me? With a smile"
or
"How do you remember me?"
"With a smile or in silence"
Is that the lyric?
Yes
"All these years"
"has anyone kept you from being lonely?"
Commander He remained silent
Later
The sixty-sixth time
Finally, after Marshal He squatted down
his brows furrowed tightly
and he stopped his leg movements
as if something
as if some important memory
was about to surface
He slowly raised his head
and looked at Marshal Ning with eyes
filled with complex emotions
What kind of storyline is this?
I finally learned how to love.
But sadly, you were already gone.
Vanished among people...
It's chaotic, really chaotic.
Who exactly are you, bro?
Go on, finish what you were saying.
No, I mean...
Then, turning to Young Master Ning, he said:
Do you still remember me?
Brother...
I'm numb.
Give me a hand.
My leg's numb, help me up.
Bro, my leg's numb, give me a hand.
This is what you remember?
Evaluation.
Change the treatment.
Communication-activated memory therapy.
It's a new type of therapy.
The doctor's secret five-person session.
Between 10 PM and 11:30 PM.
So that means...
We started losing people.
Right.
Correct.
Because there were only five people.
Each time one person was missing.
First round: Tuile Gate clock.
Chimed ten times.
Bali returned to Tuile Gate.
Adjusting clothes.
10 PM.
First round: Bali was absent.
Second round: Bali returned.
Said it was already...
10:25 PM.
Then Ke Shaoshuai...
Returned to Tuile Gate to eat.
Third round: Ke Shaoshuai returned.
Said it was already...
10:45 PM.
He Shaoshuai left.
He Shaoshuai actually left.
He said he needed rest from over-treatment.
Fourth round: He Shaoshuai returned.
Tuile Gate clock chimed eleven times.
At 11 PM, Wang Chuanshuo left.
From 11 PM when Wang Chuanshuo left until 11:30.
The doctor concluded:
He Shaoshuai, your memory...
Could return at any moment.
Any patient...
Actually during this process...
You've already recovered.
But the medicine hasn't taken effect yet.
My memories haven't returned.
I haven't remembered anything.
Is there a possibility
that before he left
and after he returned
he wasn't the same person?
You're saying between 6pm when he left and 7pm when he came back
It's possible.
But if that's the case,
then the person here at 7pm
might not have been him, right?
It's that simple.
I'll maintain this suspicion.
This is what I found in that
hidden layer of Commander He's sofa
Mysterious buddy
You've been pushing me
to find that Sunflower Woman
She appeared today
Turns out she is
the long-haired witch who's been harassing
Tui Town residents for nearly a year
Who exactly is she?
But don't worry, mysterious buddy
Now that we know
Sunflower Woman is the long-haired witch
I'll definitely find her quickly
and kill her
to avenge my singers
January 30, 1924
Boss Le
It's over
Let me tell you
You are the mysterious one from Tui
Mysterious buddy
Where did this letter come from?
This letter...
After we finished investigating that day,
I remembered something.
When I encountered
the mysterious person,
didn't he say I was Jiawei?
So I decided to find this mysterious person
to talk about this matter.
So I went
to the mysterious person's room,
but didn't see him.
What time did you go?
Around 6 o'clock in the evening.
The words written in that notebook
were also found by me
in his room.
There's another part, why didn't you read it?
There's another section...
He's quite familiar with letters.
If, as Master Le said,
the sunflower woman
that is, Ba Duanjin,
hasn't been killed by Master Le yet,
then the Ba we met today
is she Ba Duanjin or Ba Li?
So you and Ba Duanjin
look very much alike.
I probably look very similar to her.
Then you might actually be Ba Duanjin.
Also,
He who seems to remember nothing,
is he Commander He or He Jiawei?
If Dilraba and Huang Zongwei
reveal my secrets
then my business at Phoenix Nightclub
won't be able to operate here anymore
Even if I have to eliminate Dilraba and Huang Zongwei
together
I won't hesitate
Phoenix Nightclub
wants to kill Huang Zongwei and Dilraba
But when Phoenix Nightclub saw us today
they weren't sure
if we were Huang Zongwei and Dilraba
so they decided to kill indiscriminately
These four people
No matter who you are
(all must die)
How ruthless
This means
that Huang Zongwei and Dilraba
know all the truth about Phoenix Nightclub
Right
And then
because the person who invited him out today
knew he was coming to Phoenix Nightclub
to do business here
which means
you two are highly suspicious
So now there's a question
Here's the thing
She might not be Dilraba
He might not be Huang Zongwei either
There are two people with you
So here's the logic:
Let's go verify this now.
All four of us had motives to kill, right?
You, because...
you wanted to protect my sister.
What about you?
I just saw that blood-written letter.
The one from Pink Phoenix.
Right, and you saw this...
to protect yourself.
And to protect Bali.
At this point,
stop playing the devoted lover role.
Okay?
But I am the devoted lover type.
Very suspicious.
Very suspicious, Jiawei.
You're really something.
Is it possible that...
you're not Commander He?
You knew this person...
knew you might not be Commander He,
so you killed him to silence him.
Based on current evidence,
he had the strongest motive to kill (mystery person).
Right.
Most likely.
Because he might be Jiawei.
Yes.
Now she has the same issue.
Yes, she has the same problem.
No, I didn't know he wanted to kill me.
I thought...
he wanted to kill my savior.
And he's already killed...
Bro, I feel like...
they're working in sequence.
Breaking down the actions,
each of us did one part.
Each did one part - killing,
tying up,
then finally resetting the clock.
This is getting very mysterious.
Next, we will enter the X confirmation phase
In this season's program
Players acting as the murderer
will all face X's challenge
If the true murderer player
succeeds in the challenge
they can then choose between the two detectives
to corrupt one of them
I wish I were X
Just you wait
You'll see what I'll do today
He's over there
That's so scary
He looks like he just killed someone
When he comes out, he'll definitely say he's X
Hello, X
Did you see that?
The real X
They only opened the door a tiny bit.
Let's go
Let's go back and discuss first
Go
Take this key
You keep the key
Move
Let's go
Still lying around here?
Earlier, in this evidence,
did he find a key?
Next, we'll go
check the warehouse
Let's go then
Come on
Ke Wuku
You little killer
I'm really not
a killer
His tactic is
to attack first,
then see how the person responds,
whatever it is.
He plays mind games.
Only we rely on logic.
The final decision is uncertain.
There's a door here
It's sealed
Next,
we're about to open this mysterious passage.
Of course, before opening it,
with so many wooden planks,
let's... uh...
Brother Bai,
this season, I'm not in charge of demolition.
This board is practically useless.
It's not even nailed properly.
True.
Let's go.
Come on.
Here, Brother.
Your turn now.
So it's my turn, huh?
Then I'll do it.
This building doesn't belong to this era
Right?
This definitely
Modern?
Very modern?
There's an opening here
Come here
Another secret passage
He's a tank leading the way
We'll just
go all out
The tall ones are tricky
I can dodge them
There might be someone below
Below
might be someone
No one
Don't mess around
Push Lao Hui's room
Did you see Push Lao Hui?
Isn't it written here?
Push Lao Hui
Right
You remember now, don't you, Bali?
Yes.
Which means...
This place is called "Push Lao Hui."
Because this door...
has no handle.
So she can't get out.
Meaning she's trapped.
Seriously...
Let's search the place first,
alright?
We'll do a quick search.
Here's a diary
This is a journal
You
February 5th
I met a fairy at Tui Health
What's wrong?
Yes
It's you, right?
This diary
I had someone bring over the costumes I've worn
All of them
Tried them on one by one to show her
I decided to be her muse
And encouraged her to start a brand
Then after a while, someone came
He was wearing a mask
He didn't tell me his name either
He brought me some
Exceptionally beautiful
Clothes I've never seen before
For the first three days I actually took notes
I listened to what that person told me
About how to grow and strengthen my brand
It was written by a man
The one I met at that time
That man wrote it
Who is that man?
This man
Let me tell you
The man is that, uh
Called Jiawei
Do you know who this man is?
I don't know
Is it you?
How can you not know?
How would he know?
Isn't that the one wearing a mask?
You mean the guy with the mask on?
Is it really him?
Bro, I can't cover for you this time.
How can you not know?
It's you.
There's more written on the back.
Jiawei
You must wear your mask properly here
to avoid causing a commotion
And take this
This is my necklace.
Yes.
Pervert.
What are you doing?
You pervert.
What do you want?
You disgusting creep.
I was right to hit you with that stick.
Talk.
That's right.
It was you, Wei.
Are you the one who pushed the mysterious assistant?
I don't know.
Then what do you know?
There's a question at hand.
You see,
February 5th,
I met a fairy at Tui Jiankang.
She was wearing a qipao,
sitting quietly in a
retro-style room.
What kind of person would say
"this room is retro"?
Modern people.
Exactly.
Does this logic hold?
To say your design is retro,
but you're designing what's most trendy.
Right.
Because you're from this era.
I had someone bring all the costumes
I've worn before.
I tried them on one by one to show her.
She specifically adjusted
the costumes - she's also an actress.
Possibly.
Yes.
Then here,
the fairy disappeared.
Tui Jiankang staff said
no such person exists.
You're actually
the version of you he saw
doesn't exist in this era.
And didn't exist in his era either.
So this is Tui Jiankang.
I returned to Tui Jiankang again
and discovered
that going up the stairs
from the retro room
might lead to some
unknown place.
Namely, that place earlier.
Returning to our era again.
Is it possible that
this Tui Laohui
is sending our people
to the modern era?
In that small photo just now,
that person
was together with him in this photo,
right?
This...
Yes, together.
My necklace...
which means
the person who wrote this diary
might be Jiawei.
Exactly.
Or it might be him.
He might actually be Jiawei.
He's not from this era.
Right.
That's why his memories are confused.
Correct.
Good.
We've finished deducing this part.
Is there anything else you need to confess?
I'm not Jiawei.
Then who are you?
I'm Marshal He.
You're lying.
Still being stubborn, huh?
You've already regained your memories.
What else can you say?
You've definitely regained your memories.
Is it time for torture now?
Come on, tie him up.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Tie him to the bed.
Tie him up.
Tie him.
Little brother.
Nobody touches him.
Next,
let's search for more clues.
Alright?
Wait a minute
There's writing underneath
There's writing under the bed
Could it say 15 by 15?
Pull the mattress off
Makes sense
Careful, get out
Let's take this out
You guys move it
Come on, just drag it out
Okay, let's go
Can you drag it?
Is it easy for you to drag?
I can drag it
What's so hard about dragging this?
This is super easy to drag
You're too strong
Way too strong
Slow down
1, 2, 3, lift
Every night I hear
a terrifying woman's voice
screaming
We moved into this luxurious room
but only death awaits us
There's a demon
Never leave through the stained glass
door
Leaving through this door means death
Wait a moment
There's so much hair down here now
This hair loss is worse than mine
So terrifying
Seriously
So what's behind that door
What could it be?
It must be the gate to a new world
What's the meaning of this photo?
This photo should have a
As I mentioned earlier, it should
The room in this photo
should be different from
the room we're currently in
in some aspects
But now you can't tell anymore
Everything's already messed up
Let's look for other things
Alright?
Jiawei
answered instinctively
He answered instinctively
So that's how it works
Here
Put your fairy necklace around your neck
This belongs to you
Belongs to you
The lovesick persona is established
Jiawei
There are two bracelets
And a jade necklace
Are the jewelry pieces the same as above?
Take a look
Maybe if we arrange the jewelry correctly
that door will
This one's different
Which one?
The teapot
One of the things here
Where's that bowl?
Is it this one?
Seems like it
Wait a second
It's nothing
So exciting
Can that door be opened now?
No, let me move forward a bit
This...
Come on
Sorry about that
This door is...
The door's open
What are you guys doing?
The door opened
No, where are you guys?
Where is the light?
Where is this?
What is this thing?
Where is this place?
Artificial human
It's possible we're artificial humans.
This is...
Harvesting organs.
Removing the right kidney.
Tui Shenmi wants to take the organs.
You are...
Jiawei, right?
You went missing before.
Why did you disappear?
Ke Shaoshuai's whereabouts are unknown.
We just don't know when he died.
She's your great-granddaughter.
She's actively involved in medical work.
She came to save me.
Bai Youcai.
You've lived all these years.
Tui Shenmi.
Call you grandfather.
Death is too good for you.
What is this?
As long as we're alive, there's hope.
That means back then we...
The person we remembered in our hearts...
Was Ba Duanjin.
Where exactly are you?
Dead or alive?
I'll make Tui Shenmi pay for this.
Pink Phoenix.
This is too terrifying.
The Long-haired Witch had motive to kill Tui Shenmi.
Everyone wanted to kill him.
I was protecting Ba Li.
To avenge Ba Duanjin.
Both of us were protecting my sister.
The only possibility...
Is Ba Duanjin.
Are you Ba Li or Ba Duanjin?
I really am Ba Li.
And what about Jiawei?
Brother.
I really don't remember.
You're lying.
So it must be him.