We need to enter the game world
Find that B Sect
Loading
All things return to one
It's open
Is anyone there?
Even if you've figured out my plan,
you still can't stop Organization B.
Play the piano.
Come on, Peng.
We'll have one person play,
while eight others search for the stick.
The door's open.
You counted too slow.
Hurry back.
Hou.
What's the situation?
We're the same kind.
We're done for.
Behave yourself.
Okay, later.
It hurts—help me up.
I don’t see where the stick is.
Go.
Where’s the stick?
No one survives this.
Take them to the secret chamber.
Understood.
Behave and cooperate.
I'm about to enter
your memory systems
to find that crucial person.
It's open, I'm out.
We've found a way.
I don't know why
you're out too.
We're out.
So we're really out, right?
It's already begun.
Then what was the point of locking us up?
Probably to prevent us from communicating at first.
Didn't we communicate?
There's something here, folks.
What?
A password.
Boss, as you instructed,
we've changed the password hint for this room.
They'll never figure it out.
I think this place is useful.
3628.
How did you know
Fold this and it becomes 3
Fold it once
This is 6
This is 2
This is 8
Chongqing scores big
I'll grab a brick
What if I encounter danger
There's an axe here.
And a hammer.
And eggs.
Eggs.
Scrambled eggs with tomatoes.
Scrambled eggs with tomatoes
We must catch these five people
Retrieve memories to find the goose
Director He, 8D, and Shouruan—these three
Look, their identities have been verified here
So their identities are already known
I feel
In the end, we’ll definitely
return to this place
Let’s first see where we can go
Okay
Gather some useful information
Let’s check the cabinets first
There are many cabinets in this room
Can we break it
Can we pry it open?
Do we need to open this box?
We need to open this one
But I really will pry it open
It really can be pried open
What's up?
Do we need to do that thing...
Stand inside here
And then do something or whatever
Maybe
This part is where you stand inside
It can strike
You go in
Who's holding me?
Me.
All roads lead to Rome, brothers.
All things return to one.
Everything comes full circle.
What?
I just touched that cabinet earlier.
Has it started already?
No, there's not a single light here.
Where should we go?
There should be some scary parts.
Go in, enter this place.
I feel like we should go inside here.
Really? Just this one?
Let's go in and see.
There's another one here too.
Actually, there are two more over there.
You can go over there and try standing at those two.
Over there - who's there?
Who dares to go?
No one dares to go.
Someone's approaching over there.
Really?
You saw it?
Wait a moment.
Let me go in too.
Why is everyone going in?
Harmony.
You're just scared.
Hello
Hello everyone, I'm Xiao Ting
I've already discovered
the secret of Tui Town
It's in the hands of a robot named Beiju
This Beiju
is a member of a mysterious organization codenamed B
This organization is destabilizing Tui Town
And my true identity
is actually the guardian of Tui Town
I came here today
hoping you can help me
stop Organization B's conspiracy
Alright
During my investigation, I discovered
they repeatedly mentioned a game called
"Mysterious Player"
We can split into two teams
You enter the "Mysterious Player" game
to look for clues about Organization B
while I continue tracking Beiju's whereabouts
Okay
As far as I know
That area over there is the virtual gaming room
This is the access card I found
You can start from there
the "Mystery Player" game
When needed
I'll contact you with this
This belongs to us
Alright, good luck to you
Let's go look for clues
Pass through
If she wants to split up
I'm not too fond of that
She goes that way, we'll go this way
With all this
Her going alone on one path
I'm not scared
I just don't want to be separated from you all
Here
What are you doing with that chain?
Why are you taking this chain?
I'm controlling myself
What are you doing with that axe?
You're asking me?
To protect me
To protect everyone
Insert the game cartridge
to start the virtual game
There's a password here
Super Cyber Monkey Game
Contra Bull
123 124
Why? How did you figure it out?
Look
One
Let me guess
I'll take a wild guess
But this feels a bit... you know
That's the character count plus word count
Let's try it
Give it a try
Let me observe more carefully
See, Super Cyber Monkey is just one monkey
Contra Bull has two bulls
Following the zodiac order
Monkey ranks
9th
Ox ranks 2nd
Tiger 3rd
Let's see if this works
No
Monkey
How did you do it
Just push it to the side, don't press
So what's the number
It's 923
It's starting
The game plot of "Mysterious Player"
is set in two eras 100 years apart
A mysterious time-space tunnel
connects 1924 and 2024
The tragic songstress of Tui Le Men
was traded as a commodity
to the unscrupulous Tui Health Company
and became a victim of organ trafficking
The fates of people in both eras
were thus completely transformed
Game protagonists:
Bali, Bai Youcai, Ning Shaoshuai
He Shaoshuai, Ke Shaoshuai, Wang Chuanshuo
Supporting characters:
Le Ye, Tui Shenmi, He Dao, Fen Fenghuang
Dongnao Tang doctor
and tragic songstress Mei Yunlianlian
So we need to enter
this game world
Right, we'll find Organization B inside
Loading
Later that...
This door should change
I'll check if the door's open
Smoke's being released
It's that this door will change
Isn't this the premiere?
People might rush out here
It's just...
Okay, don't be scared, stay calm
I can't take this anymore
Brothers, all roads lead to one
Scanning? We're scanning here
Okay
They released some smoke
Scan me
Are you still there?
I'm here
I thought you got eliminated by lasers
This sound is really loud
Welcome to
the game world of "Mysterious Player"
Please explore freely
Wishing Director He continuous masterpieces and complete success
A small flower basket
Wishing Director He great achievements and career success
Warmly celebrating Director He's new work
"Office Mysteries"
Mysteries
Come on brothers
Can we eat this?
Can we really drink this?
Today's the wrap party, right?
"Office Mysteries"
Isn't this just about office ghosts?
Isn't that it?
Just these mysteries
No way
It couldn't be that...
That number must be some clue
I don't dare eat this
Zifan, did you come with a mission?
Yes
You've been holding an axe this whole time
In the end you'll need to
silence us
In the end, you must eliminate us to leave
No one survives
No survivors
This has intoxicating, fruity, and sweet aromas
Hello everyone
Director He
You all know me
Hello
You look familiar, my friend
You too
What's up
Director He is here, Director He
Come on
Welcome everyone to my new movie
"Office Mystery" premiere party
I'm Director He, the director of this film
Hello Director He
I believe you've all heard of my legend
Because I've won three major awards
Have you heard of my legend?
Absolutely, it's legendary
Now let me introduce this person beside me
She is
A Lian, who just joined our studio
Hello everyone, I'm A Lian
Please guide me well
Hello A Lian
A Lian
You all don't seem excited enough
A Lian! A Lian! A Lian!
Alright, come on
No need to rush the excitement
Let's bring something more exciting
Not over here.
How about here?
Are you going to perform magic?
Found it, everyone look.
That's right.
Movie screening passes.
This is what we'll do next.
Next we'll attend a private screening.
To watch my movie.
Good.
But if you want to get...
these screening passes...
It won't be that easy.
Grab them!
Let's go, brothers!
We can't...
force people to do difficult things.
Look here.
There are some golden eggs.
Inside these golden eggs...
are the challenges I've set...
for obtaining the screening passes.
If you fail the challenges...
you can still grab them...
and that's fine.
You can keep trying...
but the golden eggs are limited.
So everyone...
should make the most of this opportunity.
Just pick one directly.
Randomly select one.
Pick one and be a good man.
All nine of us can...
use great strength.
Corny pickup lines challenge.
Make another player's heart rate rise.
This requires something...
A heart rate monitor.
You can choose any male participant.
Come on, I'll do it.
Let me try first as an example.
What if it drops later?
My heart would freeze.
86.
Then let's begin.
Okay.
Now I'll perform something for you.
Do you like songs?
I like you too
Success
It's rising
Singing nursery rhymes while crying
The kind that makes you burst into tears
You must shed tears
Tears flowing
Two tigers, two tigers, running fast
The emotions are there
I have to give it to you
I’ll contact you for my next project
Leave me your contact info later
Thank you, Director He
Unity is strength
Inviting everyone to complete the song chain
Ten years ago, I didn’t know you
Stop
You don’t belong to me
My hometown
You didn’t even finish this line—no good
I live in this village
This won’t do
I was born and raised in this village
As time flies by, I only care about you
You are my eyes
Only then can I see happiness before me
Waiting a thousand years for this moment
Come back, come back
Take your heart, take my heart
String them together
String a lucky clover
String a circle of unity
Circle of unity
So you’re the luck I wanted to keep
Turns out we and love
Were once so close
Today you’re marrying me
Not bad
That was quite tough
Yeah, it was tough
Pretty tough
Next
I’ll go
No
Then the middle finger goes here
The middle finger presses the little finger
Okay
Actually it's the same
It's just (the fingers) are too short, really
Wait a minute
No, I won't do this part
That's ambitious
Are you ambitious?
No
Okay, here
Decibel challenge
You use whichever body part to make (sound)
I'll place this on whichever body part
I nominate our
PKU soccer team's leg king
That's amazing
Alright
Truly the Leg King
The split exceeds two and a half meters
We're here.
Alright, challenge completed.
Spread the word.
Wei Xiaolong has legs 2.5 meters long.
I'll gain Director He's friendship.
Come on, let's hug.
So envious.
Director He.
Straight to you.
So impressive.
A Lian's friendship.
Good Guy King.
I thought it was something else.
I thought it would be directly...
Names of good friends.
Okay, no need to think now.
3, 2, 1, go!
Zong Yu, Zhuo Cheng,
then Shao Yang,
then Zi Fan,
then Director He,
then A Lian,
then Brother Long,
then Brother Kai,
Outdated, only eight.
One more, Director He is generous.
Director He is generous.
Director He is particularly refined and amiable.
And also exceptionally capable.
Alright.
Next.
30 in 1 minute.
1, 2, 3, 4...
25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30.
20.
Amazing.
20 seconds.
Okay.
Congratulations everyone.
You've all earned my movie screening passes.
Now then,
let's go to the screening room together.
To the screening room, come on.
A Lian, lead the way.
Over here
The atmosphere is too lively
One will come soon
Bring out that little cutie
Something's fishy
Contrast
This must be that thing
Alright, everyone, this way please
I'll sit inside
Why?
Sitting inside makes it harder to run later
Come on, move inside
I'll sit in the middle, come on
Are you ready?
Then next...
The premiere of this movie will begin
Isn't this us?
So handsome
How did it turn out?
Not bad.
Did Director He fly this drone shot himself?
Of course.
I don't believe it.
If you don't believe it, suit yourself.
Did I scare you?
As expected of Director He
No
This scene wasn't in my movie
Someone definitely tampered with my movie
Someone tampered with your movie?
The character Tole in my movie
He couldn't possibly know about Buddy
hidden in the abandoned space of Twitter's backend
Besides, Tole doesn't even know Buddy
Then why would he go looking for him?
to alter the "Cold Blood Academy" comic?
Unless...
Absolutely impossible
"Cold Blood Academy"
It's changed
This movie has changed
This manga has changed too
Look
This Xiao Xi
He was clearly cursed before
and turned into a dinosaur's head
But now, why in this manga
he's back to normal?
It says Xiao Xi escaped the curse
So originally, he didn't escape the curse, right?
Yes
In this manga
Xiao Xi was cursed
and became a dinosaur's head
But look at him now
He has a normal human head
Let me see again
All things return to one.
You say even ghosts are afraid
There are nine of us
Unity is strength, this power
Alright
Where did Director He and A'Lian go?
The work ID fell
Director He, Employee A'Lian
Pull it out and take a look
Feels like there are two
Yes, tear it open
There's a paper sandwiched inside
Mei Yun Lianlian
As far as I know
A'Lian, the new employee at Director He's studio
Was absent from the premiere due to illness
You could disguise yourself as A'Lian to sneak into the premiere
And kidnap Director He when the chance arises
Before that, you can hide in the props room
It's very safe there
The way into the props room is hidden
On Director He's poster
She kidnapped Director He
So that person just now was Mei Yun Lianlian
Yes
Let's open the props room first
Let's go
This is the props room
Favorite poster
Got it down
It fell down
Here
There's a clue here
Chaos inside the house
What kind of nonsense is "flying dogs jumping"?
You need to go in and input that thing
Input this
There's more over there.
Each one has it.
All have it.
There's none here.
Here, it fell down.
Don't be a sneaky thief.
Now there's chicken and dog thieves.
The whole household is in chaos.
Come, let's piece them together.
Let's see what they look like combined.
Now there's...
Probably chicken thieves.
Chicken.
This also means household chaos.
This also means complete pandemonium.
Complete pandemonium.
This means petty theft.
Petty theft.
Chicken.
Related to chickens.
Means there's no chicken.
No chicken.
Nonsense.
Playing with homophones again?
Only this one has a chicken in it.
Right?
5G rooftop.
Rooftop.
The clue is on the rooftop.
I'll cover up all the chickens, unless...
Cover up all the chickens.
No chickens here.
Should we cover up that character?
There's a chicken character here.
I don't have it.
I only have two hands.
We need one more person.
Take this...
Be careful.
Slow down.
Will this work?
Quick, gather together!
Don't move.
Wait a moment.
Stay still.
Don't worry, no one will jump out to scare you.
Don't go.
I'm here.
Watch out for that.
We can let go now, right?
Let go, careful, someone's coming down.
You guys up on top...
Take it slow.
Yes.
Easy does it.
Looks like the door opened.
Flashing
Then let's move forward slowly
Wait, hold on - I have night blindness
Okay, give him a hand
Whose hand is this?
Mine
All things return to one
Brother Kai, slow down
One team
Is the door open?
It's open
You can come in
It's fine
No problem, come in, it's okay
Go inside, it's fine
Move inward
This is a suona
Wait, be careful - this door is too narrow
Careful
Don't push
Okay, after entering let's stand properly
No problem
Last person in, close the door
Okay
Alright, no problem
Stand still now
Everyone's in, right?
Stop moving
All in, good
Not bad
Hello everyone
Go
No, I'm getting a bit of photosensitive "epilepsy."
Let's go.
Wait, I can't see.
Can't see.
Just a little.
Take it easy, guys.
Come closer, closer.
Is anyone there?
Stop grabbing me.
Grabbing my armpits is uncomfortable.
Are you A'Lian?
No.
A'Lian was hiding in the props room at first.
Which one of you is A'Lian?
How was our acting?
Excellent.
Our acting skills...
...should get us selected.
For "Office Horror 2," right?
Of course.
Do you know where A'Lian is?
I'm not sure about Director He and A'Lian...
But I just saw a strange...
...woman in a qipao.
She was sneaking around...
...stealing evening gowns.
I think she's over there.
Yes, seems to be that way.
This...
Let's go, sisters.
We'll come back for the audition later.
I feel like I touched something paper-like.
Paper? Is there a letter?
Read it.
"Trapped in days promoting health."
I often reminisce about the stage of Tui Le Men
As an orphan, I originally thought
I could make my mark there
But never expected
The day I ascended to Tui Lao Hui
would mark the beginning of my nightmare
My pancreas was cruelly removed
Then my corneas
Just one second before I was to be incinerated
a group stormed into Tui Health
I seized the chance to stumble
and escape to Wu Kenai River
Unexpectedly
I found Bei Ju
a note from another world
Another world
Yes
Because Tui Le Men was in 1924
and one was in 2048
Though hard to believe
subsequent events proved
I, Bei Ju, Xiao Xi, and Tuo Le
were all tragic figures sharing similar fates
That's why we call ourselves Group B
If there's any chance to change our fate
even the slightest possibility
I'm willing to try
Bei Ju, Xiao Xi, Tuo Le
all share this tragic
Nine nines return to one
Brothers, there's something behind us.
Stop pushing against me.
Lian, don't run away!
Where is she?
We'll save you.
We'll save you, Lian.
Lian, we know what happened to your cornea.
Even if you know my plan,
you can't stop Organization B.
Before the movie is re-edited,
I won't release Director He.
Won't what?
Won't release Director He.
She won't release Director He.
Which means she kidnapped Director He.
Right.
It's Mei Yunlianlian.
She time-traveled from 1924 to 2024,
then formed an alliance with Beiju, Xiaoxi, and Tole,
creating Organization B.
But why kidnap Director He?
Because she wants to
edit
She wants to change the movie.
Because she altered that comic,
Xiaoxi wasn't cursed.
Since both she and Xiaoxi belong to Organization B,
she hopes that by
changing the movie and comic,
she can save Xiaoxi from being cursed.
The curse of turning into a dinosaur.
She wants to change things herself,
to save herself.
By altering the movie.
So that woman earlier
was Mei Yunlianlian.
Now that we know this,
her motive is clear.
She kidnapped Director He
just to
change the movie.
So should we go to the projection room now?
We need to find a favorite portrait
and find clues from it.
Find the portrait Director He's son loved most.
There's a portrait over there.
Right.
His favorite portrait
I see a line of small text here
Call out my name
Three, two, one
Bali
Young Marshal Ning's descendant
could never write a bestseller
Young Marshal Ke's descendant
will open the most famous shop in Tui Town
Young Marshal He's descendant can't win the Three Tui Award
No matter what, Young Marshal Ning's descendant
can't win the Tui Nobel Literature Prize
Years later
This seems like a logic puzzle
Their descendants each achieved
one of four accomplishments
won the Three Tui Award
won the Tui Nobel Literature Prize
published a bestseller
opened the most famous shop in Tui Town
Regarding the predictions about their descendants' achievements
only the one whose descendant opened a shop predicted correctly
So what achievements did the descendants of Bai, Ning, Ke, and He
respectively accomplish?
Young Marshal Ke's descendant will open a shop
Therefore Young Marshal Ke
was correct
Young Marshal Ke predicted correctly
because the one whose descendant would open a shop predicted correctly
That was Young Marshal Ke
But Young Marshal Ning might be lying
No
Not necessarily, it might not be this
Right, I think one of these two is correct
One is right
Bai Youcai's descendant opened a shop.
I understand now.
His descendant opened a shop.
That means what he said was wrong.
He didn't win the Nobel Prize in Literature.
Young Master Ning's descendant wrote a bestseller.
Young Master He's descendant won the Triple Prize.
And then Young Master Ke's descendant...
won the Nobel Prize in Literature.
Is this correct? Let's verify.
Young Master Ning's descendant wrote a bestseller.
This proves Bai Youcai was telling the truth.
He didn't win the Nobel Prize in Literature.
Meaning his (Bai Youcai's descendant) opened a shop.
His (Bai Youcai's) descendant opened a shop.
That means what he said was wrong.
This proves Young Master Ke...
This proves Young Master He's (descendant)...
won the Triple Prize.
Young Master He's descendant won the Triple Prize.
Right? And then...
What's still missing?
We've accounted for the shop.
Only the Nobel Prize in Literature remains.
This means Young Master Ke's descendant...
won the Nobel Prize in Literature.
No problem, right?
No problem.
So, do we need to trigger something?
I remember now
The password for the editing room
is the names of these people
Like the shop names and such
In the past, we had to go there to open it.
Go.
Let's go.
Let's talk one by one.
Bai.
Bai opened a shop.
Ning.
Bestseller.
Ke Shaoshuai.
Nobel Prize in Literature.
He Shaoshuai.
Three-time grand prize winner.
It's opened.
What's wrong? What happened?
Just now, A-Lian threatened me.
She asked you to edit it, right?
Yes.
She's not even from our company.
We know, we're aware.
Can you help me get my keys?
My keys should be on that box.
Help me undo this.
Can you tell us in detail now?
She tied me up and brought me here.
She made me edit the scenes in this movie.
The plot about Tole.
How should it be edited?
She said she wants Tole.
Not to board the No. 4444.
In my work.
Tole boarded the No. 4444 ship.
And then?
He disappeared on the Wukenai River.
4444.
Exactly.
Said this could end.
The tragic cycle of Zhen Tui.
He wants to change the editing to.
Tole.
Save Tole.
I sincerely apologize for today's premiere.
Because of what happened.
It's okay.
But as the director.
I think these things are sources of inspiration.
So I want to go back and revise the script now.
Alright, you can go. Bye.
Your phone.
Hello
I'm Xiaoting, can you hear me?
Have you found any traces
of Organization B?
We've found some clues.
I've infiltrated
the robot scrapyard
where Bei Ju is located.
I'm getting closer to uncovering Organization B's plan.
I'll send my investigation notes
to the screen near you.
Your next steps
are also in the notes.
Good luck.
Okay, thanks.
Let's go check it out.
Take it slow.
The Secret of Tui Town
Actually, Tui Town has no river
The so-called Wukenai River
is actually a connection between four
four dimensions
The shape of Wukenai River
symbolizes an infinite loop
This infinity links four different dimensions:
The gaming dimension
The comic dimension
The film dimension
The novel dimension
Each dimension is created by
authors from higher dimensions
forming a closed loop together
If water from Wukenai River
is used to water the wooden cabinet
it can activate the dimension-breaking mechanism
to send messages to lower dimensions
According to my investigation
this book sunk at Wukenai River's bottom
"The Secret of Tui Town"
was accidentally obtained by Beiju from the novel dimension
Following the book's instructions
he gathered four people to form Organization B
Here's their plan:
If their plan succeeds
the stability between dimensions will collapse
causing unpredictable disasters
across all four dimensions
Their current plan is like this
The game dimension we're currently in
"The Mysterious Player"
"The Mysterious Player" is Director He
who created "Office Ghost Story"
and created the movie dimension
Within the movie dimension exists a comic dimension
There's a comic dimension in the movie dimension
where Brother Bai created "Cold Blood Academy"
Under Tole's guidance, Xiaoxi
kidnapped Hu Jie
Hu Jie is the soft-handed novelist
who altered Beiju's fate
Hu Jie wrote "Five Elements" in the novel dimension
"Five Elements"
"Five Elements" was from 2048
Under Xiaoxi's guidance, Beiju kidnapped Goose
to change Meiyun Lianlian's fate
Goose the game designer
designed this "Mysterious Player"
It's a closed loop
So we must stop them
Next step
Xiaoxi's fate in the comic dimension
has already been altered
You must find a way to contact Tole
to have Brother Bai fix the comic
To contact Tole,
we need to water the wooden cabinet with Helpless River water
to send messages to the lower world
Water the cabinet - where is it?
Helpless River water
I know
It's that flower-arranging cabinet outside
Let's go check outside
Helpless River water
Wooden cabinet
This one, this
This is where we pour water
We need to find Helpless River water
Helpless River water
Is there any alcohol
mixed with Helpless River water?
Check its ingredients, right?
Produced in Tui Town
No
Tui Drunkard
All come from Tui Town
This
Tuixiangnong
Specialty brand
Contains 1% Wukenai River water molecules
Amazing
There's a pen here.
We might need to write him a message.
Tell Dilraba to change the comic.
Immediately.
Change it back.
Otherwise, neither you nor us.
will get away unscathed.
Change him back to a dinosaur head.
Please.
Okay.
Put it in.
Done.
Mission accomplished.
Let's see.
Whether Tole has relayed the message back.
We can only judge.
by the changes in the real world.
whether we succeeded or not.
So let's find a comic.
This one, "Cold-Blooded High School."
This.
Left behind a curse of despair
Red dress, bald head
Doesn't he look like a dinosaur head?
Then just flip to the next page
Turned into a dinosaur head
Xiaoxi became a dinosaur head
So we've broken this cycle
Right
We succeeded
If we just leave now
Wouldn't the game end?
Let's try it
Is anyone there?
Can anyone hear me?
This is Xiaoting
I was accidentally captured
Captured with me
Is the game designer Keke
Keke
We're currently
Probably locked in the Cyber Robot Pavilion's
Secret Room No. 3
They took my communicator
So Keke can only use in-game items
To communicate with you
Let's go into the game
Anyway
Right now the Cyber Exhibition Hall
Is full of dangerous robots
Earlier in the VR Game Center
I saw information about
Forcing robots into hibernation
It should be near the virtual harp
This
You should search carefully
Virtual Harp User Manual
Play the harp
Come
Peng
This harp serves as
a security backdoor for Cyber Robots
Play the following musical notes
to put the robots in the exhibition hall
into emergency hibernation for 1 minute
The robots will wake up after 1 minute
The harp has a 5-minute cooldown period
Then play this sequence of notes
Note:
To put robots outside this exhibition hall
into permanent hibernation mode
you need to activate the permanent hibernation device
Activate it using the reading pen
Have you seen this?
Tap to read the sensor point
This, isn't it in that...
a circle?
The sensor point is in the hall
Outside, in the hall
So we'll use this one minute
to go to Room 3
No
We'll use this minute
to put them into permanent sleep
Find the reading pen
Right, we need to rush out to find the reading pen
If we find the reading pen later
we need to hold the thick end
point it at the star on the left
then swipe toward the center
Like this
Let's have one person play
while eight others look for the stick, okay?
Yes, that works
Come on, get ready to play
Like this, we'll do it like this
We should leave one person here to watch the clock
Okay
Four of us can stay out
Hide in the hibernation pods?
Even with lights on, he can't catch us
There are hibernation pods
Okay
I'll go to the hibernation pod room
Then when the lights come on
we can observe
Let me test the hibernation pod first, alright?
Before entering the pods
we should try to find the switches first
I'll do it, I'll count at the door
You focus on searching
I'll count second by second
Okay
Let's go, Pengpeng is already playing
Come on
Coming
Go
The door opened
9 10 12 13 14 15
Counting a bit slow
16 17 18
Counting too slow
19 20 21
Feels like it's almost 30
22 23 24 25 26 27 28 29 30
I'm back
Go back first
Back, I'm back
Hurry back
Quick
Wait, let me take a look first
Don't close it yet
Just a quick look
Mine
I'm afraid he'll come in
He's so scared
No, I'm afraid you'll get caught
I'm not afraid
What about Hou?
Hou
How's it going?
It's fine
No problem
We are the same kind
There's a hint of that in his cry
Mockery, right
Big brother
I've been captured
I heard him say he's been captured
Is anyone with you?
Xiaoting is here
Where?
Does Xiaoting know where the magic wand is?
Where's the wand? The magic wand
I haven't seen it
But Xiaoting is with me
My name is Xiaoting
He can't...
Can't hear him speaking
How did you get captured?
I'm looking for the pen
Do you know where the pen is?
Don't you know where the pen is?
I don't know where the pen is
I'm waiting for you to rescue me
Now I need them to rescue me too
Let's make a plan
I'll go find Brother Hou
Let's still try our best to find it
You go find Brother Hou
We need to stay united, okay?
Okay
Elevate our purpose, broaden our perspective
Alright, let's go
Alright, get ready, brothers.
Ready.
这次是猥琐模式 好吧
Go.
Hurry up.
Find Hou first.
Where's Hou?
I'm here.
But I'm in jail.
Don't worry about me.
Do you know where the stuff is?
I didn't see it just now.
You'll have to look for it.
Can't find it
How many seconds?
Go back a bit
Where is it?
49 50 51 52 53 54
Come back
55 56 57 58
Don't close it, not yet
59 60
Not closing
Keep looking
Stop shouting
You didn’t see anything
Tell him to look
Why are people missing?
Who are you
Me
Please
Come in quickly
Okay, wait a moment
I'll go in first
We're done for
Okay, we're coming in
Do we really have to come in?
Hi
Fall down
Okay, I'm going out
Fell down
It hurts
Behave
Okay, wait—ow, that hurts
Give me a hand
Behave yourself
How did you all get captured?
Come on
I'll do it myself
I searched everywhere outside
Didn't find anything
Me neither
I've been arrested
I don't see where the stick is
You can come out
Can come out
Go
Scream
I found the stick
Where is it?
Quick, play the piano!
Mi Suo Re Mi Fa
Mi Mi Re Mi Fa Re Do
They've gone dormant.
He's right at the door.
Tap.
It'll connect.
Bottom left.
Go bottom left, like this.
Yes.
Topmost.
Above.
Bottom.
Swipe to the middle.
Okay, it worked.
Done.
Done, it's lit up.
Good.
Not easy
They're in permanent hibernation, right?
They should all be in permanent hibernation now
They didn't move when we turned on the lights
That proves they're permanently dormant
This... the access card
The access card, the access card is here
Open it
We can rewrite the ending now
Is it finally over?
Yes, it is
Oh my god, you guys are amazing
Oh my god
Your combat power is off the charts
We're really so grateful to you
Thank you for your contributions to Tui Town
It was a pleasure meeting you all
Hope we meet again someday
Goodbye
The story of Tui Town comes to a perfect conclusion
Thank you all for your wonderful performance in Tui Town
Now
The exit from the alternate dimension of Tui Town
is now open
Please exit the Tui Cyber Robot Exhibition Hall
and return to the real world
Okay
Good work everyone
Okay, good work everyone
Alright everyone, dig in
Dig in
This season passed in the blink of an eye
We've basically
received the reward we deserved
How do you feel about participating in
this season of "Start Using Your Brain"?
Any thoughts?
I think honestly
At first I came with just
an attitude of wanting to experience it
But after coming here
it was really quite fun
It was really quite fun
What about Zhuocheng?
You've grown a lot.
In what ways have you grown?
Before, I always thought I was someone who...
acts impulsively,
or doesn’t consider the consequences,
when doing things.
But after joining the show, I realized...
I truly learned that...
after participating in *Start Using Your Brain*,
and *Start Deduction*,
I now feel that many things...
require planning before action.
That’s the biggest lesson
I’ve taken away.
From a warrior to a soldier.
Became a general
Both cultured and martial
Yes, capable of commanding
But I can really feel the change
I think this recording session
Made me rediscover this feeling after so long
Just a few people
Playing board games together—that kind of feeling
So it was really joyful
Like going back to high school
That most carefree time
Right, I actually want to add something about this
This feeling
Just now, Lin Hao put it perfectly
I feel the same way
I just think
I could really let loose
I felt like
I’d returned to that version of myself
In that especially happy environment
And my biggest takeaway
Was truly getting to know all of you
Really
Cry, everyone, cry
First, I feel
That coming here
The luckiest thing for me was
Meeting all of you
I’ve learned so much from everyone
Because everyone has their own strengths
It’s a process of mutual learning and growth
And shared happiness
Okay
Happiness again
Yes, happiness again
I realized that
During every assessment
I discovered my flaws
It's about competitive spirit.
Can't say it's bad.
Right.
Within the game rules.
Everyone naturally wants to win.
With a little encouragement, they definitely will.
Okay.
They'll surely do that.
Alright.
Good.
Yes.
So I think many games.
Are very enjoyable to play.
But.
Just started getting into the rhythm
and already want to play again
So I really hope to play with everyone again
Everything that happened here
felt much more natural than I expected
I'm quite introverted
and not great at playing games with others
But coming here
I felt everyone was really considerate toward me
And
playing games together felt very close-knit
and natural
Like brothers
Yeah
I think these feelings
are quite personal things
That everyone's willing to share them
shows we've really become family
Now, our Zifan
Listening to him made me feel guilty
Because I...
You didn't feel... okay
No, that's not it
Actually, I'm the complete opposite of him
When I first arrived
I didn't care about winning or losing at all
But eventually I became
increasingly eager to become the hall leader
That was my transformation
So I'm actually quite happy
that we've all grown in our own ways
Yes, we've all grown
Every single one of us
Well...
I think we've all written down
some impressions of each other
So
Let's start from the far right
with Zifan
We'll go one by one
and share our thoughts
Tell us what you wrote about everyone
and why
Alright, elaborate please
Okay
Shaoyang
I wrote four words for Shaoyang
Warm and intellectual
Intellectual
I can somewhat relate to being warm
But how about intellectual?
Please elaborate
Shaoyang is a very warm person
Especially in the earlier episodes
He could sense
When many of us felt uncomfortable
When we were feeling
Awkward or restrained
He would always help us
Zifan's crossing his arms again
I should learn from that
*Laughs*
He's enjoying this
So I think he's
A very warm and intellectual big brother
As for Brother Kai
I wrote "just smile" for Brother Kai
Because I always feel he has this
"Journey to the end of water"
"Sit and watch the clouds rise" vibe
When that mental challenge
Actually comes to him
He would just say
"Ha, bring it on"
It's like
He gives people that composed feeling
Then Pengpeng
What I wrote for Pengpeng was very simple
I just wrote two words for Pengpeng
Chess King
We should do this
Then he can't move
Actually we can, why not?
Will this get stuck?
But we're getting another one
We go this way, right?
We're still missing a 2 here.
We're still missing a 3 here.
Here we go, I'm getting the hang of it.
There's one thing I really admire about Pengpeng
It's because Pengpeng
fully embraces his strengths
Everyone knows he's the Chess King
What are you talking about?
And he knows he's the Chess King too
No, this is actually good
I think it's an excellent quality
To face oneself honestly
Right
Being honest with yourself
And accepting yourself
I believe
Self-acceptance is a process in itself
Exactly
As for Minghao
I'd describe Minghao as composed and calm
Composed and calm
Yes
I've noticed that often
Unlike the rest of us
who might get flushed during games
and visibly worked up
To the point where
our hands are shaking
But Minghao always remains
very steady
Except that time you betrayed me
Betrayal Room Two
Hurry, I can't wait
Alright
Okay, good
Room Four
In the following two rounds
He got a little angry that time, right?
His hands were shaking then
You know?
That kind of...
Getting a bit heated
Then there's Xiaolong
What I wrote for Xiaolong was
"A man remains a boy at heart until death"
Because I just learned today
Xiaolong is slightly older than me
Actually much older
Right
With all
including physically demanding games
he stops holding back
When he moves
he seems even more agile than Zhuocheng
So I think
At that moment
what truly radiated from him
was that very charming youthful energy
Then there's Zhuocheng
What I wrote for Zhuocheng was "worth investing in"
Actually I later observed
that even when alone
fighting solo
he actually has the ability
to handle all types of games
That's why he's worth investing in
For Zongyu I wrote "brainpower leader"
Because I truly think Zongyu is
I don't know
No
But in my impression
I think he's the quickest thinker
Maybe it's related to his age
Then for Haoyang I wrote
Boundless energy
Perhaps he's genuinely strong and energetic
It might also be related to age
He's a few years younger than us
Understood
What about Haoyang?
Let me start with Shaoyang
I described him as full of vitality
Another description is "the life of the party"
Because Brother Shaoyang gives me the impression of
being very warm-hearted
He's really good at bringing
joy to those around him
As for Kai
Actually I think he's more of a
very kind person
Compared to being rational
I feel he leans more towards
the kind-hearted type
Then there's Yinpeng
I wrote three keywords for him
First is "Chess King"
Second is "strong"
Third is "adorable"
What? "Strong"?
"Chess King"
His mental abilities rarely decline
His rankings
seem to consistently remain
relatively high
The "adorable" part is hard to explain
It's just a feeling
You know, a vibe
For Minghao, what I wrote was
rational, calm, and straight to the point.
His comments often give me the impression
that he always hits the nail on the head.
Although he doesn't speak that much,
For Xiaolong, I wrote three traits:
one is competitive,
one is diligent,
and one is agile.
Xiaolong and I only partnered in the final episode,
but when I played games with him,
although I didn't show it,
I felt that
our attitudes toward gaming
were quite similar in many ways.
As for agility,
Xiaolong seems to
excel in all physical challenges,
performing exceptionally well.
Except for those times he got hit,
when I hammered him 17 times.
Lightning Five-Whip Combo!
I remember
"Xiaolong, minus 8 points."
Then Zhuocheng
I wrote two words for Zhuocheng
One is "considerate"
The other is "good teammate"
Because between Zhuocheng and me
How was he considerate to you?
Please elaborate
For example
Before the game starts
Zhuocheng would cheer me on
And even when I hold bottles
He'd tell me which muscles to engage
"Hold on, lock it in"
"Engage your core"
"Use your waist"
"Time's up"
These details make me feel
If you were teammates with him
he's considerate about countless details
That's why I wrote "a good teammate"
Next is Zongyu
For Zongyu, I listed four keywords
clever, free-spirited, impulsive
and a walking encyclopedia
When it comes to humanities
including classical poetry and idioms
he's like a
living database
seeming to know everything
List ten works by Lu Xun
"Call to Arms", "Wandering"
"A Madman's Diary"
"Dawn Blossoms Plucked at Dusk", "Wild Grass"
"Hot Wind", "Storm in a Teacup"
"Village Opera"
"From Hundred-Plant Garden to Three-Flavors Study"
Correct
Please answer
Lure the tiger out of the mountains
Correct answer
Practice medicine to save people
Drag through mud and water
Correct answer
Without changing facial expression
The land is picturesque
Correct answer
In my memory
I believe it was
a Chinese soprano singer
who received the first resident ID card
In the end, I wrote Zifan.
Then I wrote three keywords.
Pleasant voice, easygoing.
And high emotional intelligence.
About the first one "pleasant voice" - I think...
his voice is truly pleasant.
Indeed.
And "high emotional intelligence" because I feel...
Brother Zifan is really good at helping others out of awkward situations.
This room is already full.
No problem.
I hope you two have fun.
My two former teammates.
Actually, I think
If theirs was red,
they wouldn't have
to discuss this much.
Right.
The reason they're discussing
is because it's black.
That's why they need to discuss it.
How about we place it here,
then move this here,
and block this path first?
That could work.
Blocking three this way...
Yes.
Very smart. Genius.
It gives people the impression of being very emotionally intelligent
Understood
I'm not very good at describing things
So I gave everyone the title of "handsome guy"
But with different modifiers in front
And I also drew some little sketches
There are some below too.
And actually, there are some on everyone's faces too.
Some drawings.
Shall we pass them around?
And you...
Okay.
Can you remember it?
I can remember.
Then I'll follow the order of these episodes.
The sequence of my partners.
Because I've partnered with...
everyone before.
First is my partner from the first three episodes.
Yang.
My description for him is "macho man".
Really tough.
When facing certain challenges...
you often have your own...
unique perspectives.
That is to say...
For this game...
my strategy is...
First accumulate power pills in the middle.
Put this here first.
Then jump over here.
There's already a simple bridge here.
Then at this point...
accumulate another power pill.
Store these two here.
This acts like a slingshot.
Launch it like this.
Then bring this back.
Then launch again.
Keep sending pieces here.
Remember the last column is 3453.
4 is upright.
The rest are inverted.
Then subtract it from 10.
This has proven very successful.
Right.
The description I gave Brother Kai...
is "handsome whisperer".
But I drew two chess pieces for him.
Wrote "first"...
If Pengpeng is the Chess King...
then Brother Kai should be the Chess Sage.
I see.
Clear a path
Then we can stall him
Because this is our only option
Otherwise they'll finish setting up here
And we'll be one step behind
Then it'll be five immediately
Place it here, then jump over
This would be fatal
And Brother Kai, I think he's someone
who makes everything seem possible
like there's always a turnaround
Next is Brother Minghao
My keyword for him is "cool handsome guy"
"Cool" meaning
Egg
Person
Not showing much emotional fluctuation
Just calmly composed
Within just a few words
he demonstrates his capability
And sometimes
he sees through things clearly
That's how it is
Next is episode six with Long
The mysterious handsome guy
Sometimes he shows more
than we expected
More explosive power
More powerful feeling
Time starts now
Get him
Long, Dragon Fist
"Dragon Seize"
It's too intense
He's locked
Chokehold! I'm in a chokehold!
Stop! Time's up
One
Dragon card position
Next is our Cheng
Lucky handsome guy
I feel Brother Hou is also
someone with clear thinking
and acts decisively when needed
A very decisive person
Right
Then comes Zifan
99-point handsome guy
Last time his luck score was 99
I also hope he can
maintain this
Not just 99-point luck
but also 99-point ability
Thanks
And finally there's
Pengpeng who partnered with me last time
White Tiger handsome guy
I'm truly impressed
No
I feel Brother Pengpeng is also
very resourceful when facing challenges
a very strategic person
Actually quite decisive too
Once you've decided on a strategy
you act on it decisively
Okay, finally there's Shaoyang
I've already seen it, I don't understand
The keyword I gave you is
Handsome crazy guy
I think it's the moment we need
To provide us with some
Very lively emotional support
Just like our backbone
Bringing us together like this
Okay, that's all from me
Okay, thank you
Let's go
The first one I give to Zongyu is
The witty idiom king
First, he's indeed very smart
As the idiom king, I think
When we play idiom games
Zongyu basically never loses
And he's basically always first
So we gave him
This title
For Minghao it's "unpredictable"
Unpredictable
Sometimes he's amazing
Other times at chess he
Can't play at all
Right, no points scored
That's why he's unpredictable
What I give Zifan is composure
And exceptional memory
Because I've partnered with Zifan for three seasons
I genuinely feel his personality
Or his choices
Are quite composed
For Pengpeng, I wrote:
Cute, agile, handsome, elegant
Elegant
Because he plays the cello
Wait, why are you reacting so strongly?
It's not about you
For Shaoyang, I wrote:
The king of comedy
Where's this "king" you speak of?
Actually he's really good at perceiving
the emotional changes in people around him
Okay
Then Haoyang represents youth and energy
That's true
I think Haoyang has brought
this kind of element to us
He's also mobilized our collective
energy
With my trembling
Yes, so full of vitality
Kaikai represents hard work
dedication and diligence
Because I've heard Kaikai say many times
"I want to be number one"
So Kaikai definitely wants
to excel at these games
Works very hard
Right
Then Xiaolong, first as Brother Long
And also as the King of Buffs
Brother Long really has
so many qualities
Another is being a true man
For example in highly competitive events
Brother Long gives his all
Alright, that's my commentary
Let me go in order
First is Shaoyang
I think he's the team's soul
Without him we'd struggle
to reach our current level of
emotional connection
We probably wouldn't have made it
Thanks
Brother Kai is very emotionally stable
And very considerate
Then Peng
Actually shows maturity beyond his age
A sense of maturity
Because in private with Peng
We've had casual chats
I've noticed Peng has
some very clear ideas about
his life direction
I think this is a great quality
Understood, I know
As for Minghao
He's actually full of contrasts
He's both the King of Great Jokes
And the King of Bad Jokes
As for Hou,
I wrote "charge forward."
Why did I write that?
Because when Hou and I are together,
we often just exchange a glance
I know what you're thinking,
and you know what I'm thinking.
Especially when we're on the same team,
Yes, you know my intentions
So we often
don't need to say much.
We just charge ahead.
Though I don't know where
this feeling comes from,
maybe it's because we share
some similar personality traits.
For Zongyu, I chose a word
that might not be entirely accurate -
"deer-like grace."
It's like
I feel it's a kind of
ethereal quality.
It's abstract, I just wanted
to express this understanding.
Right.
For Haoyang, one word:
"giving his all."
He truly puts forth
his full strength every time.
But I think this is great
because when you're young,
you should be more expressive.
Maintaining this attitude
is completely fine, I think.
As for Zifan,
he's actually someone who
comes up with unexpected moves.
I think through observation,
he accumulates these unique techniques
and applies them.
This is quite impressive.
Yes.
Let me start with Cui Shaoyang.
I wrote "best MC" for him.
At the very beginning,
without his hosting presence,
we probably couldn't have continued.
But I think
everyone might discover beyond his hosting
that he's actually someone who—
why he's called the best MC—
you'd realize if he plays games,
he's incredibly skilled too.
Because every time
during our post-game reviews,
he offers
his own insights on the game.
Next is Huang Kai.
Since Huang Kai
and I previously
interned at the same law firm,
so
this time I wanted to highlight
something different from what
I observed in the show—
his chess skills.
It's interesting how
you get to see
another side of someone
you thought you knew well.
That's how it is.
For Ren Yinpeng, I wrote "master strategist"—
whether in chess
or strategy games,
he excels exceptionally.
Long Wo is described as a tough guy
In all physical challenges
he's extremely agile
and exceptionally brave in battle
Hou Zhuocheng is portrayed as immensely strong
This strength
first refers to muscular power
and secondly, his boyfriend charm
This is what I've observed.
He's genuinely considerate and gentlemanly.
In daily life, I've noticed
he's also very caring toward others.
So these are two sides of his great strength.
Next is Yang Zongyu.
I wrote "little clever one" for him.
He's indeed very smart,
and you'll notice
besides being academically excellent
(a top student),
he also dances, paints,
and has various hobbies.
He tells all kinds of jokes too,
showing his humorous side.
So I think
it's rare for someone to have both intellectual depth
and an interesting personality.
That's truly exceptional.
Next is
Yu Haoyang - I wrote "well-informed" for him.
This actually partly comes from
outside of gaming.
Because Yu Haoyang
often discusses movies with me,
philosophy,
and other concepts.
I've noticed he's watched many films,
many works,
and read many books.
So we can always have great conversations.
Next is Dong Zifan.
I wrote "poker face" for him.
Because I think he's actually
quite composed.
I don't think I've ever
observed in Dong Zifan
any extreme emotional changes.
It's like he always
comes home and starts smashing things.
She has a serene and unassuming demeanor.
Just sitting there,
his deep and steady voice,
expresses things with great logic,
and delivers very composed remarks.
So I think
this is my overall
impression of his demeanor.
Good.
Very good.
Pengpeng.
Let me start with Shaoyang.
For Shaoyang, I wrote "considerate,"
meaning he's very understanding.
That is to say,
early on, he had a lively image,
but later, he would
encourage us to contribute more,
or things like that.
I just feel
he's actually a very considerate person.
As for Brother Kai,
I wrote "approachable,"
meaning his overall vibe is very
unassuming and non-competitive,
and he's an especially gentle person.
Then there's Minghao
I'll just write three words
I'll write something meaningful
I would think
First, he doesn't have much output
But when he does output
it comes unexpectedly
suddenly hitting everyone
expressing everything that needs to be said
perfectly conveyed
Think about it, if you
Whether you question or not
you're actually elevating them to
a higher position
Consider
If your questioning succeeds
he loses
If your questioning fails
they'll move from their current
third place to second
For Brother Long, I wrote "indomitable"
There are many
spears of perseverance
Perhaps Brother Long
lost this round
but in the next game
he still maintains that fighting spirit
and keeps striving forward
That's why I find him truly tenacious
As for Zhuocheng
I wrote "sunny and cheerful"
I feel he's particularly
both physically strong and well-rounded
I think
he gives off a very approachable
and friendly vibe
Regarding Zongyu
I find him exceptionally humble
Because every time
whether we're playing word games
or memory games
or any other challenges
even when Zongyu wins
he never reacts excessively
He just seems
to radiate genuine humility
And then
for Haoyang I wrote "brave and resourceful"
When I first met him
I thought philosophy students
must be very cultured
But later
after several episodes
I realized he's not just smart
but also courageous
with remarkable boldness
I find him quite versatile
For Zifan I wrote
"deep, textured voice"
Because since the first episode
I noticed this quality
that's quite distinctive
So I
Really?
Yes, exactly
And that's that
Okay
First let me say
Zifan
Zifan, I really think
he's as composed as everyone says
I haven't noticed
many emotional fluctuations in him
even when teaming up with him
As for Haoyang
I'd describe him as adorable
Although he's quite tall,
I've noticed that sometimes
he can be quite adorable.
And then,
for Zongyu,
I wrote "composed" -
he does make decisive choices
during games,
but he remains very calm
about the outcomes.
For Zhuocheng, I wrote "motivated" -
he gives me the impression of going all out
when playing games.
For Long, I wrote "driven" -
during our team-up episode,
his emotional shifts were quite noticeable.
He wanted to win more than I did.
While I keep my desire to win
more controlled internally,
he expresses it more outwardly.
But I think that's good.
For Minghao, I wrote "chill" -
what I observed during our internship
was quite different.
He's changed.
For Pengpeng, I wrote "energetic" -
he's quite young,
and his whole personality
is full of vitality.
Right.
For Shaoyang, I wrote "joyful" -
I've noticed whether he's present
really affects us.
It's not just about Shaoyang's absence -
actually missing anyone
creates a noticeable gap.
Alright, that's all.
That's it.
We're about to reach the end of this episode.
Or rather, this season's
final segment.
What is it?
Hall Master's Consecration Ceremony
Award Ceremony
Alright
Now is our season
The most exciting moment
The Brain Hall is about to be revealed
The highest honor in 124 years
The Ultimate Brain King
Applause
Good
This applause
is to thank yourselves
From the innovation wave of 1924
to the retro trend of 1988
From the visual boom of 2004
to the cyber trend of 2048
Now start thinking
Great Brain Development
handles everything with ease
serving the residents of Tui Town at the Brain Exercise Hall
Now
let us announce the Ultimate Brain Master winner
who will receive from Tui Town
the Thousand-Tempered Golden Gourd
This physician has over 124 years
accumulated 420% brain power
He has fully proven himself
across all eras
with extraordinary intellect and outstanding ability
Who is he?
Who could it be?
He is
Hu Minghao
No
Come on
Now let's
present our golden gourd
Solid gold
Made of pure gold
Real gold
Authentic golden gourd
Real or fake?
What's the current gold price?
Alright
Our previous hall leaders
had one special privilege
The choice
of intellectual enhancement services
But now we're skipping the enhancement
You'll choose a physician
to help you wear this sash
and also put on this
thousand-tempered, furnace-refined genuine golden gourd
Can I choose separately?
Sure, you're being particular
Not really
Just having two people assist
No problem
First I'll choose Pengpeng
Because previously
Well
Until my last time as hall leader
Every time I became leader, he was with me
So I think
You want me to serve you?
He deserves credit, much credit
Let him put it on for you
And this gourd?
Who should put it on for you?
Let me think
Give me a moment
Of course, everyone here is
a very good friend of mine.
But
you started
stirring up these fake emotions.
Ultimate Brain King
Who should give you the golden gourd pendant?
Golden Gourd Selection
For the golden gourd, I choose Huang Kai
Because we've known each other for quite a while
We've worked together professionally
And collaborated in games too
I feel we've witnessed
Each other's different
styles and
various aspects as friends
Let's do it
The gold price is very high
Alright, where's the applause?
Thank you
I really didn't expect this
Let's still congratulate our Minghao
for becoming our Ultimate Brain King
Do you have anything you'd like to say?
I'm extremely shocked
Well...
I never expected
I didn't think to prepare for this beforehand
It's just that I feel
When I lost before
we sometimes said it was just bad luck
Like in the first two rounds with Long
when we were building blocks
we never scored
but still came in second
But I don't think
that having this gourd trophy
means I'm better than everyone else
I'm really grateful to everyone this season
for playing together
And whether
as teammates or opponents
it's been truly enjoyable
In my opinion
this "Ultimate Brain" title
should really belong to everyone
That's the bigger picture
So I think
this just happens to be with me
Thank you all so much
It's been wonderful playing with everyone
Let's take it down
Just kidding
Come on
Alright everyone
Let's give our most sincere applause
to our Ultimate Brain champion
Come on, everyone
Let our applause echo through past, present
and future
Once again, congratulations
to Hu Minghao, the winner of the grand prize
As we move forward,
we hope all members of the Brainstorming Hall
will continue to surprise us
Lastly, remember to keep smiling and love brainstorming
Now, let’s all shout together
our slogan
Ready, three, two, one
Start brainstorming
Unlock your brainpower
See you next season