A doctor drinking cooled boiled water
The physician who drank cooled boiled water
Formed a team to establish a clinic
You've had three cups of "magma" in a row
Tone down your veins a little
Crying, Brother Huang Kai
You're all acting
It's truly cooled boiled water
Another familiar assessment for everyone
There are two self-proclaimed "Chess Kings"
The divine dragon "1" move keeps appearing
Four words for everyone
Returning to the martial world
If you play this, won't you be ready to win?
Then you'll block, right?
Should we block or not?
Arrived one step too late
Can't block anymore
Come on, the "god" of show effects
He's specifically blocking us, right?
Just happened to have time to check over there
Weaving a cocoon around oneself
Locked "tight"
What else can we move?
Annoying me to "death"
You're surrounded
Not necessarily
Paper can't wrap up fire
Quick, this is the spot! Go now!
Hold your breath, focus your energy, and strike with your palm!
With a loud *bang*—
*Bang!*
Shattering the inner and outer secret doors into pieces.
Come on
Alright, everyone
Welcome to
"Let's Start Thinking"
This is Tuizhen Town's
centuries-old renowned pharmacy
Thinking Hall
I'm the assistant director of Thinking Hall
Cui Shaoyang
This year marks
the 164th anniversary
of Thinking Hall's establishment
has also implemented the acting hall master system
for the sixty-fourth year
We look forward to more
exceptionally talented apprentice physicians
taking up the role of acting hall master
to shine and contribute to the Dongnao Hall
Now
let's review the assessment rules
This week's two value-added services
They are
The ultimate summer cooler
Ice bucket foot soak for chilling relief
And refreshing
Effortless wet towel cannon
I hope all physicians can during the assessment
maintain clear minds
with coherent thinking
to win honors for our clinic
The triage rules for this session
It's just plain boiled water
Really just plain water
Excellent
Not bad
Try to relax your veins a bit
His swallowing seems slightly strained
He's crying, Brother Huang Kai
Furrowed brows
The acting is a bit poor
Somewhat exaggerated
Feels like acting
Then let's deduce, brothers
Which two cups are plain water
Seems none of you drank plain water
I think there's no plain water
Unless you're all acting
Everyone's got some acting skills
Those who didn't drink plain water
Take one step back
Come on
Three
Two
One
Please step back
Let's congratulate Ren Yinpeng and Hu Minghao
For forming today's first consultation team
Bottoms up, truly bottoms up
This is very much plain water
Very plain water
Right, I think so too
Drank and laughed
Like it
Brows furrowed
His eyes are getting teary again
Feels like something's off
Quick, act it out
Acting
So sour
Who drank water this round
Let's all step back
Three
Two
One
Okay
Congratulations to Hou Zhuocheng and Huang Kai
For forming today's second consultation team
He laughed
He's enjoying it
Enjoying
You've had three "Magma" drinks in a row
This is a bit too much
It's really a bit too much
This feeling is really not
Let's first invite two
brothers who have become clinic staff
to analyze it
Xiaolong must be saltwater, right?
Xiaolong keeps swallowing saliva here.
Just drink it.
Indeed.
I guess Yu Haoyang is also saline water
I saw that drop dripping from the corner of his mouth
It looked a bit murky
So, who exactly drank the saline water
Is it our Haoyang?
What about Xiaolong?
Those who didn’t drink saline water, take a step back
Please step back
Congratulations
Reunited by fate
The two of you have continued
A bond from 64 years ago
In the third phase, 1988
You’re still paired together
This is the third time you’ve been assigned to the same clinic
Do you have anything to say?
Fate
Good
I want to say
Our first win might’ve been luck
The second win was skill
The third win is dominance
Do the two in examination room one have anything to say?
New combination
New mental enhancement service
You speak
Don't
Still a bit
Still just a little bit
New combination
New starting point
Same destination
Same fate
Okay, collapse
Say something
Well
Go for it
Keep it up
Okay
Okay, wish you success then
Our new team
What do Zifan and Xiaolong say?
I think it's a brand new beginning
Boring
Didn't you say you wanted one or three?
Sixty-four years ago,
One day I was fourth place,
another day I was second place.
Today let's see
if it's third place or first place.
No problem, this time you're third, I'm first.
We'll meet at the top.
Not necessarily.
It might be us first and you third.
It hasn't even started yet and here we go.
Starting to feel like we're becoming rivals.
What do you think?
What's your opinion?
I thought your previous collaboration
wasn't that unpleasant?
Okay.
Huang Kai and Zhuocheng,
this is also a new pairing this time.
Do you two have anything to say?
With Huang Kai by my side,
I suddenly feel confident.
Brother Zifan,
that's not what I meant.
As expected, the collaboration wasn't very smooth.
That's not what I meant.
This...
The more I say, the more mistakes I make. Forget it.
No, let the results speak for themselves.
Alright.
Huang Kai, anything you'd like to say?
I'm really looking forward to it.
Yes.
Because suddenly seeing them
still as a team,
I feel we have confidence.
They won't be first place.
Right.
I think this time we're like
"The six major sects besieging Bright Peak."
Good.
That's something.
Let's go, brothers!
Okay.
Alright.
Now let us
officially begin the assessment.
(I choose) Dandelion.
Doctor hey hey goji.
Goji berries
Another familiar assessment for everyone
There are two who claim to be "Chess Kings"
I'd like to interview first
Ren Yinpeng and Huang Kai
Come on, you two speak up
I think
I was able to achieve that state last time
Because with Brother Huang Kai
We reminded each other
And then summarized together
That's how we played that chess game together
You're hinting at me
No
What I mean is
This thing is
Minghao would be better
You're hinting at me
That's not what I meant
It's just
Both are good
So what's your opinion about this chess game?
Zhuocheng is better
Good
Remember in our last assessment
There were frequent appearances of the "Dragon 1" move
I'll give you four words
Return to the martial world
The first consultation room
Consultation Room Three matches with Consultation Room Two
Come on, rock-paper-scissors
To decide who goes first, come on
Rock-paper-scissors
Exam Room Two goes first
Both sides are evenly matched now
Just like this or...
No, we can't do this
If you play here, aren't you ready to win?
Right.
Then you'll block us, right?
Yes, we'll block.
Attack.
Here we attack while defending.
Yes, activate both paths.
Draw.
Draw one.
Okay.
This move is so neat.
Should we fill this up again?
Then Kai's Whisper... no, that won't work.
Cheng's Rebellion, I insist on playing here.
Two.
I think we should take the initiative.
Protect ourselves.
Right.
Draw a 3 to block
Should we block?
Bet
The Gambler's Wager
Dare to bet they don't have it
Bet
Definitely not
No, this is 11.
11.
No regrets in the move.
I just
No, I thought we had won
I saw Brother Huang Kai didn't react
What were you thinking at that moment?
It was too late, I should have whispered
Horizontally, it no longer works
The horizontal sum is already over 10
He listened
He has to go there
I think 1 is useless
But we can block him
We're a step too late
Luckily we blocked it
Then let's do this
Okay
Or maybe we can go here
That works
But it's not that easy to win
They will definitely block
So we have to go there
Ready to win
Can't block it
This placement works too
We can at least make a pair of 2
Come on, let's bet
Here comes the tense moment
Bet they can't flip a 2
Come on, let's go
This decided the outcome
Well done
Congratulations to Clinic 3 for gaining 20% mental energy
Clinic 4 goes first
Everyone's got good luck
I think this spot is better
Wouldn’t expanding sideways here work?
You mean here?
Okay
Block his side
Blocking this side makes no sense
Another three
Right, I think we should place it here.
Because the two 3s can merge together.
And it can also connect with this 2.
Right.
That makes sense.
If we place it here,
it would actually be a bit weaker.
Right.
Okay.
3.
Let's go directly above.
Okay.
My thinking is this.
Even if I place it here,
a 3 appears here.
But on both sides,
next turn,
I can directly place this.
Sure, no problem.
3.
We've reached 7 pieces.
Okay
Pretty good
Block here
Can't go over it
He only listens to the three of diamonds.
I think we should go this way.
If we go this way, I can listen to both ends.
And I'm also listening to this card.
Okay.
Let's bet.
Yu Haoyang
Keep your personal bias in check
Understood
Your personal bias is showing a bit too much now
Here we go
Now we're getting somewhere
Then let's congratulate Clinic One
for winning this round of assessment
Okay
Alright
Let me be the first to draw the medicine card
Rou
What?
Rougui
Pearl
I choose
How about the pearl closer to me?
Fine
Herb Competition Battle
First,
Each clinic will send one representative
to play rock-paper-scissors.
You go.
Rock-paper-scissors, right?
Or maybe you should do it.
I'll go.
You do it.
Come on, rock-paper-scissors!
Nice!
Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
That works too.
Clinic Four goes first.
Clinic One second.
Clinic Two third.
Clinic Three fourth.
Now draw position cards.
Why am I feeling
so nervous about this?
You draw, I have terrible luck.
Okay.
Each person draws one card.
Very good
Good cards
Okay
Exam Room Four goes first this round
We declare
We claim to be pharmacists
We'll take two cards from Exam Room Two
Take two herb packs
Herb packs, right
From us
Right
Wait
Hold on
We can stop this
We have the Administrative Director
We must stop it
First
Does anyone challenge their pharmacist claim?
No one
Okay
Is anyone questioning whether they are the administrative section chief?
No one
questions
doubts
challenges
They question whether you're the administrative section chief
Please present your credentials as administrative section chief
Doubt
There is an administrative section chief.
Discard a card
My smile suddenly faded
And this time the alchemist
their skills are ineffective
Understood?
Alright
How many rounds will this game last?
The game ends when someone gets eliminated first.
Just one round.
Let's begin the clinic round.
We need one medicine package.
Here.
Please take it.
Peace.
This means they have nothing.
This means we're nothing either.
We want...
three medicine packages.
Clinic Director's ability.
Claiming to be the Clinic Director.
Attempting to obtain three medicine packages from the storage.
Does anyone wish to challenge this?
Five, four
No, I mean
Three
Do it
We question
Question
Do you even have an outpatient department director?
Please show
Goodbye
What? It's over just like that?
The game is over?
They actually...
No, why is this happening?
You have obtained three medicinal herb packs
Not bad
Come
Examination Room 3
Please begin your turn
We'd like to take from Examination Room 2
two medicine ingredient packs
They claim to be pharmacists
and want to take two medicine ingredient packs from Room 2
Does anyone object?
(whispering)
Then take them
Received
Two medicine packs sent
Examination Room 1 begins
Take one more
No problem
Examination Room 2
We are
We are the chief surgeons
We'll make them
lose one position card
Any objections?
No objections
Then you must lose one position card
We challenged the wrong person
Now it's Examination Room 3's turn
We'll take two medicine packs from Examination Room 1
Five
Four
But there are already two there
There are already two here
Two
One
Challenge
Please reveal your identity
Challenge failed
Surrender one position card
Here
This one
Done
Come on, it's your turn at Clinic One.
We want to obtain a medicinal herb pack.
No problem.
Clinic Two.
We'll take three.
Any objections?
Five, four, three, two, one.
Okay.
Let's swap cards.
Let's take them on.
We...
We either succeed or die trying.
Alright, successful card swap.
Do we have no choice but to go through with it?
We have no choice but to proceed.
What else can we do otherwise?
Come on, let's go to Operating Room 1.
We are the lead surgeons.
Don't "kill" us
"Kill" them
Right
Okay
So we can only challenge now?
We'll "die" if we don't challenge
We have the head nurse
You can also stop it
Then we have to challenge
Challenge
We either succeed or perish
They're challenging if you're the head nurse
Okay, goodbye.
Goodbye.
Only we're left now.
Come on.
We'll submit three herb pouches.
Make them lose one position card.
They claim to be the lead surgeons.
Do you wish to challenge that?
Challenge.
It's gone.
Alright, let's congratulate Clinic Two.
for securing first place in this assessment.
They've successfully accumulated 25% brainpower.
Brothers from Clinic Four,
regarding this outcome,
do you have anything to say?
We only scratched the surface of this game.
Next time, we'll strive harder.
Yes, we've fully realized
the true essence of this game.
Next time,
perhaps we'll make a triumphant return.
Alright.
Looking forward to it.
Do you believe it?
We believe.
Then applaud for us.
Okay, thank you.
He's manipulating you.
I'll still be responsible for the physicians
I'll continue overseeing the doctors
drawing the examination topics
Alright, I'll choose this one then
Golden Drink Flower
Miraculous Healing Hands
It seems like
the building blocks one
That's right
Answer questions then build blocks
This time I
will absolutely not touch those building blocks
What's important is
building with blocks
Right
Indeed
Correct
Now let's present our first question
Year
Which of these films can't be seen in theaters?
"God of Gamblers" is very old
I remember "God of Gamblers" being very old
Three long and one short
Choose the shortest one
Please answer the question.
A C B
Come on, no more changes.
B
Good.
Now let's congratulate...
Clinic One who chose the shortest option among three long and one short.
The correct answer is C.
Now let's congratulate Clinic One.
for accumulating 15 seconds of construction time in advance.
Presenting the second question immediately.
Year.
Which of the following pop songs cannot be heard?
Please answer.
A C B C
We have two clinics choosing C.
They are Clinic One and Clinic Three.
Come.
Clinic Three, explain your reasoning first.
I'm most familiar with this song.
How does it go?
She always...
only leaves her phone number.
This song...
never lets me walk her home.
So I feel...
it should be closer to my generation.
We thought similarly to them.
It just feels a bit vaporwave...
a song with that kind of vibe.
Congratulations to Clinic One and Clinic Three.
Correct answer.
Successfully accumulated another 15 seconds.
Year
received China's first
resident ID card was
what profession?
I know
Painter
Merchant
Singer
Teacher
Either C or D
D
D C C B
Clinic 2
Why?
Three long
Right
Other classmates
anyone confident about
this question?
In my memory
it was one of our country's
female sopranos
who received the first ID card
I think it might be
Congratulations Clinic 3, Clinic 2
Awesome
Alright
Which of these celebrities
wasn't born in 1988?
I know
Zhu Yilong
Older
Tan Jianci probably
He's not even thirty
Clinic 4 and Clinic 1
both chose A
Why?
Not referring to other teachers
Meaning they don't look young
But
But Teacher Tan looks
exceptionally young indeed
Same
Seconded
Congratulations to Clinic 1 and Clinic 4
The answer is A
Okay
Teacher Tan is indeed very young
Alright, get ready for the next question
Year
Which of the following dramas cannot be seen on TV
is which one below
Consultation Room 2
Could you explain why?
"Misty Rain" and "The Deer and the Cauldron"
These were both relatively early works
As for the Four Great Classical Novels
"Journey to the West" was from 1986
And "Dream of the Red Chamber" was probably
either 1987 or 1988
So we chose "Romance of the Three Kingdoms"
What about Consultation Room 4?
If a director films two simultaneously
He needs a proper creative cycle
I remember "Dream of the Red Chamber" was
probably the 1987 version
I think "Romance of the Three Kingdoms"
came slightly later
That seems quite reasonable
Congratulations to Consultation Rooms 2 and 4
for successfully accumulating 15 seconds of build time
Which of these poetic lines
originated from the 1980s?
B A D B
Congratulations
Congratulations to Clinic 3
Successfully accumulated another
seconds of setup time
This polymer thing...
Are you also knowledgeable about poetry?
Somewhat
Alright, now for the final question
Brothers
This is the last question
Which of the following events occurred in 1988?
already happened
Definitely doesn't seem like it
Have you ever seen Boss Bao take the subway?
No
Lotteries should have existed long ago
China Sports Lottery
China Welfare Lottery
Because they're both state-run lotteries
Right
I think it's B and D
Should choose C
D C D B
Then congratulations to Clinic 4 for the correct answer
Are you ready, everyone?
Ready.
Three, two, one.
Start building.
Ignore what falls.
Consultation Room 2, please stop construction
Okay, stopping
Five, four, three, two, one
Stop construction, everyone
Stand down, we're done
They might not have more than us
Clinic Four gets 61 points
Clinic Three, 51 points
Clinic Two, 33 points
Clinic One
Top layer has eleven
This layer has two less
Good, this layer has two fewer again
Good, two less again
We can still get third place
We actually got third place
Clinic One, 11 points
Congratulations to them
Impressive, impressive
Thank you
My mistake
I'm the "curse" of miraculous healing
But they did build it quite beautifully
Right
Beauty takes time
This is a real shoddy construction
Pretty on the outside
but inside it's all...
I'm about to draw
the final assessment for this session
I'm so nervous
I'll choose
the curtain
medical ring set
Come on, everyone
Let's draw
the two clinics for the first round
Okay, Examination Room One
Second examination room
Alright
Come on, guys
Gather around
Put Consultation Room One first
Place five circles
Come on, let it go
I feel like the world is spinning
I'm already starting to feel dizzy
This game is a bit too difficult
I'm kind of
Maybe we should just play casually without overthinking
Can't calculate it all
Your possible moves
Each move takes forever to calculate
The sky's vast for birds to fly
Let's go this way
Alright
Jump over it
Is this okay?
Yes.
The one above, come here.
Okay
No arrest
Let's go
I think we should go that way
I'm so afraid of making a mistake
This game is truly difficult
Huang Kai
Seems doable
Either arrest him alone
Just (stay) here in Lvteng
Useless
Then this is set in stone for us
He can still come back to mess with us
Let me think about this
I roughly know
Wait a moment, let me think
Diametrically opposed
Want to try?
Like this
Then flip this over to here
Let's push it up there
Push it upward
Okay, I think it works
Is that what you want?
Okay, that works too.
Just choose one of the two.
Here or here.
Place it like this.
You can only have one.
We
This side is locked
Can't move this side
Play this one
Go up and take two of his pieces
What else can we move?
Nothing left to move.
Feels like we have to give up.
Let's move this one.
I'll take these five.
Should we still move this ring?
We need to move it one more step.
Then you need to take one more.
Put that ring away.
That one seems a bit cumbersome.
Then move the green one here.
Right, they blocked that
Luckily we saw it
Not this one
Move it here
Right?
Then change these two as well
There's one more here
Okay
You're surrounded
Not necessarily
He took another step and jumped back
Wait, let me think of a way
We have to do it this way
Then he won't be able to move
Actually, it's possible
Why can't we?
Is it lagging like this?
But we got another one.
Fun
Can both clinics comment on this assessment
Share some thoughts
Too difficult
This is too complicated
Requires sufficient energy
Attention and meticulousness
It really requires what should I say
That kind of all-seeing awareness
Because I didn't expect
You could jump directly from here to there
Missed that
That was still an excellent match
Now, Clinic Four and Clinic Two
Please come up
Clinic Four goes first
Here comes the "God" of show effects
First take the side
Yes, first take the corner
This feels so right
He's specifically blocking us, right?
Corner first then
Okay, no regrets once placed
Place it here
Then put the red ring here
This one
Sure
Good move
This can also handle it
Put this here
Okay, go ahead
Ring Restraint
Lock Down
But he needs three rings
to lock our two rings
We don’t want to be locked
Might as well take the time to check it out
Kai is messing with their minds
Right now, everyone seems like useless pawns
Why not take control of these two as well
Find a chance to break through
Then charge out
I don’t think we need to charge out
Because he can’t possibly take all three rings
Lock my two rings
Then these two rings of yours
would be useless, right?
Look
What about your plan?
You two should join in
Put the rings here
There'll be five rings soon
Then we can take them all at once
No
We have another way to win
Another way to win
There's another way to win
Yes, there's another way to win
What is it?
The main focus now is adjusting the positions
Because there aren't enough cards yet
Right, adjust the positions first
I think we need to block its three rings
Correct
But if you place it there
Move the next one to this position
Then we can't move this one for now
Then place it here
Shift green to the left
Move it down to this point
It has five chances
But these five chances
Can easily be flipped away
Leave this circle here
Then it can't be flipped no matter what
Okay, then place it there
We'll place two rings ahead of them
That should do it
Right
Then he won't be able to jump over
They're withdrawing one by one
Withdrawing one by one
Then we can eliminate them first
Otherwise these two rings of ours
Right
Dead
Here
Then eliminate this one
Oh no
How interesting
Hoist with his own petard
I'll claim this spot first.
Truth will always come to light.
Wait, I'll place it here.
Move this ring over here.
Okay.
Let's make that ring move away.
This should work here.
Go ahead, place it here.
Actually, we could go for area control.
This is another way to win.
This is an alternative winning strategy.
Because we'll run out of cards soon.
It's based on quantity.
They currently have more in quantity.
If we flip this one,
the green one can immediately capture it.
Let's do this one.
I think the priority right now is
He wants to take this side
I'll just move this piece here
and occupy this spot
then his corner formation (won't work)
I think you should pretend to focus on the side
while actually connecting lines
I can hear everything
You're being way too loud
Conspiring out loud
So Huang Kai's method actually works
We really need to say it this way
Whispering, right?
I think this is exactly how we should do it
Move this one here
Take this position
Right
And once he moves this
we can just go there
If this row gets blocked
This feels much better
Put one here
Move it over here
It's just four
This is acceptable
We already have five here.
We must eat one right now.
But you know...
After this goes here...
Where does this go?
This goes this way.
You must eat one
That was really hard to take just now.
Holding on
Now they've got us in these two rings
Stuck here
But we can move this first
Now there are only nine left in the public deck
Okay
Kai moves the piece
He wants to gather five
Place one and move up
This one of his can't be removed no matter what
Place
It's over
He already has five
Once I'm here, he can't get past
At least two of his escape routes are blocked.
Yes.
We've already lost all of these.
We're out of options, right?
There might be a way.
Both of these are our pieces.
So he can't connect five.
If we move this over...
Flip this one and he'll have five.
Then shouldn't I just block it?
Genius.
You're a real genius.
Then go ahead and block it!
Fine, then let's place it there.
Then hurry up and block it!
You've got something waiting for us, don't you?
Just waiting for you to make your move.
Let me move over here.
Only two pieces left now.
Both sides have one move remaining.
Actually, you can make your move now.
No matter where you move, you'll lose.
No matter where we move, we'll lose.
Just these last two moves.
As long as they don't succeed, we win.
Place it here, move it there.
Then I'll have one more.
Okay.
Alright, no regrets after placing the piece.
I see it.
It's your turn now.
And this one is public
Right
Forming five
You must remove one ring now
Go ahead and take it
Okay
Now it's our turn, right?
Then let's take our own path
We'll be one step ahead of them
What should we do? What should we do?
Actually, we've already...
It feels like we've lost, right?
Yeah.
It feels like a loss.
Okay.
Then let's congratulate Clinic Two...
for securing...
the final 20% of the brainpower score.
Congratulations to you.
Come on.
Here, thank you all for your hard work.
I believe everyone
is eagerly awaiting
the announcement of the final results.
We will now announce
the rankings from the four rounds of assessments.
For the first time,
since the premiere of "Start Using Your Brain,"
we have consulting rooms tied for first place.
Congratulations.
After sixty-four years of evolution,
the acting sect leader position (reward)
has been materialized as a golden gourd
into an acting sect leader appointment certificate.
Student Ren Yinpeng,
becomes acting sect leader for the first time.
Next, student Hu Minghao,
Congratulations to Huang Kai from Consulting Room 2,
on his first appointment as acting sect leader.
Congratulations to Hou Zhuocheng from Consulting Room 2,
After more than sixty years
of intellectual enhancement services,
this is their first time becoming acting sect leaders.
The service has paid off.
This proves our enhancement services are effective.
This is...
seems good for propping up instant noodles.
I think this is...
good enough to get once.
Because if you never get it,
what would you tell everyone?
No offense meant,
but currently we're the only two
who haven't received it yet.
I've realized having some ambition
is still important.
Because over sixty years ago,
when I first came to the Brain Hall,
I said
I wanted to erase
that clear-eyed foolishness of a college student
from my gaze.
Now after sixty-plus years,
I've finally graduated -
after delaying graduation for fifty years.
I'm extremely happy.
Let's move outside
Now our Zifan and Zongyu
are ready to take on
the ice bucket foot soak challenge
Do you two have anything to say now?
I'd like to nominate someone
to pour this ice water for me
That person is my former teammate
Hou Zhuocheng
I have nothing to say
I'm just taking the straight-face challenge
to last thirty seconds
What?
Last thirty seconds
Three, two, one, begin!
Okay, start the timer.
Eight hundred soldiers rush northward
Eating grapes without spitting the skins
Not eating grapes but spitting the skins
Artillery fears hitting the soldiers
Soldiers fear the artillery's guns
Not a single moment apart
Three, two, one
Challenge succeeded
Awesome
Alright, let me briefly
explain to everyone
the rules of the wet towel cannon game.
As the name suggests,
one person receives the cannon,
and one person fires it.
First, you two need to choose
who will help you shoot the cannon.
Okay.
Yang Zongyu then.
Before receiving the premium service,
does Xiaolong have anything to say?
Prepare your "last will and testament."
Alright.
The "will" as in "last will."
Got it.
Didn't see it
Can we do it again?
Now then, next up
is our classmate Haoyang
Any words before the premium service?
I think we should let the storm
rage even fiercer
Whirlwind Charge Tornado
Bring it on
Then let's congratulate Haoyang
And our Xiaolong
Value-added service completed
It's nothing.
So today,
the intense and exciting brainstorming session
is coming to an end.
All the doctors have worked very hard.
Today was also
a day of having great minds together.
So today,
our 1988 "Let's Start Brainstorming"
must bid everyone farewell.
"Let's Start Brainstorming"
Goodbye.
Choose your favorite food
to determine your teammates.
Waiting for my Houttuynia cordata brothers.
Am I about to be kicked out?
Excuse me.
Sorry.
13.
11.
17.
Being this cautious?
Why are the numbers so big?
They're messing with us, right?
23.
25.
This game is turning into a bluffing contest.
What number was called?
Open.
Challenge.
"The Dragon's Move" coming up.
Feel the dragon.
Actually, we can just make any move.
"Kill" him.
You don't seem to have any other choice.
They're going to
set up a slingshot.
We must come up with
a way to counter the slingshot tactic.
They've made some excellent moves.
Those teapots of theirs now
have nowhere to go.
Feels like we can't hold them back anymore.
Calm down, calm down.
Can't come back.
Oh my, what am I doing?