♪Destiny's choice♪
♪The moment I fell into the nightmare♪
♪Struggling in the whirlpool♪
♪Piercing the devouring darkness♪
♪Who remembers the sorrow in my eyes♪
♪Endless regrets, better unsung♪
♪Fate twists thrice, fire runs deep♪
♪Crossing endless mountains and rivers♪
♪Conquer fear, carve my path♪
♪Crushing wasted time, under vast skies♪
♪We grow wild and cling close♪
♪Dreams aflame, life a song♪
=Threads of Destiny=
(Adapted from Qi Xing Jiu Yue's novel, Reborn Matriarch Watches,
Prince Heir Destroys from Zongheng Chinese Network)
=Episode 18=
Jiang Yu'er!
Get out right now!
Father and Mother,
why have you come so suddenly today?
Yu'er, tell me.
How could our family's
old residence be seized?
That's our family's legacy!
I...
It was all Xueying's doing!
(Crying again.)
(Anyone can cry.)
(What are you...)
I've never returned home
since the homecoming day.
I know nothing
about Jiang family affairs.
What nonsense are you spouting, Yu'er?
Where's the deed?
You swore back then
mortgaging the old house
to get money for stamp loans
would multiply our wealth!
You two colluded to deceive me?
Master!
Ungrateful daughter!
I...
If you weren't pregnant,
I'd beat you dead!
(Jiang Xueying!)
You stole the deed?
No, Master...
You've destroyed our entire family!
Calm your anger, Master.
I have matters to attend to.
I'll take my leave.
We heard Your Highness enjoys fine wine.
This is our region's rarest vintage.
Please honor us by tasting it.
Please.
Well.
Rich on the palate
with a lasting finish.
Excellent wine.
Your Highness,
I've been remiss in hospitality.
Someone!
I offer
this tribute to Your Highness.
Please accept it.
I dare not accept
such a generous gift.
If these were government funds...
Rest assured.
These are all from my personal assets.
As a mere county vice-magistrate,
you own such substantial assets?
Guards!
Confiscate Master Qiu's properties.
Use them for plague control.
Y-Your Highness!
Your Highness.
Here's Qin Shouyi's portrait
I commissioned.
His last known location
was the western suburbs.
Okay. We'll investigate there tomorrow.
We owe Your Highness our lives!
No need for thanks.
Indeed.
Your Highness is our savior!
My sick wife and child remain at home.
I beg for extra medicine, sir.
Are you ill too?
Take another dose.
Here.
Thank you, sir.
Jiuyue,
that might be Qin Shouyi.
Follow him discreetly.
Understood.
Your Highness,
Yimo Village nearby
has more than ten new plague cases.
Our medicine isn't enough.
We've been containing the patients.
Why did Yimo villagers get infected?
Their medical supplies are low too.
Has Jiuyue returned?
Not yet.
We're not waiting.
Gather some men to forage herbs
in the mountains with me
for new medicinal bags.
Understood.
(If he's convinced it's you,)
(even if you take no action,)
(he'll still come after you.)
(I haven't found the chance to act.)
(If I return empty-handed,)
(how do I explain it to Prince Ning?)
Master, a yamen runner
contracted the plague.
Should we quarantine yamen now
to prevent the spread?
Yes.
Hold.
Immediately transport the infected
to Yimo Village.
W-Why should we do that?
I'm Prince Ning's
appointed military supervisor.
Do as I command.
Understood.
Remember, absolute secrecy.
Watch out!
Junxing,
don't blame me.
If you harbor hatred
and seek vengeance,
go to Prince Ning.
His Highness fell from a cliff
while herb-gathering last night.
We found no trace of him below the cliff
but only this.
This sachet
was my brother's personal belonging.
It seems my brother has...
My condolences.
Come in.
These are the assets
my brother took from you.
I've reclaimed them for you.
What do you mean?
You've worked tirelessly these days.
Should I be promoted in the future,
I'll recommend you most favorably.
The people of Xinyang
owe their deliverance from plague
entirely to your exhaustive efforts
and ceaseless hard work.
I'll personally draft the memorial,
detailing your merits
with utmost precision.
What's happening?
My right eye keeps twitching.
Has something gone wrong?
Why
are there no guests at all?
My lady!
A notable guest reserved the place
and wanted to see you.
A notable guest?
Who is it?
I don't recognize him.
But his attire suggests great nobility.
(Why is it him?)
(In the past life,)
(after Lu Liang introduced me
to Prince Ning,)
(he repeatedly harassed me.)
(In this life, we've never met.)
(Why would he come to me?)
(I'll have to improvise.)
May I ask why you seek me?
You don't recognize me.
In Yu City,
there's only one prince
of such age and status.
You must be Prince Ning.
My visit today
is to inform you of something.
Lu Junxing
is dead.
Whatever Your Highness's purpose,
spreading baseless rumors
is beneath your dignity.
Very well.
Let's not discuss him then.
I've reserved the entire Jingwu Hall
to meet you today.
Won't you share a drink with me?
If Your Highness seeks amusement,
you've chosen poorly.
Jiang Xueying,
I've watched you for some time.
Become mine.
I care not that you're already married.
How would Her Highness
the Princess Consort Ning think
about your offer?
I'll take my leave.
Good day.
No one has ever dared defy me thus.
The more you resist,
the more
I'm determined to make you mine.
(It can't be.)
(In the past life,)
(Lu Junxing returned safely
from Xinyang.)
(Right.)
(He said that deliberately.)
(Lu Junxing will be fine.)
My lady!
Master Liang has come back.
What is His Highness?
Why didn't he return with you?
While searching for medicinal herbs,
my brother had an accident in Xinyang.
He accidentally fell off a cliff.
♪Flowers bloom and fall,
never to return♪
Impossible!
We found this below the cliff.
♪Endless disputes, ever changing♪
♪Yet no wrong or right♪
Alas.
The dead cannot return.
I'll report his merits in Xinyang
and request His Majesty
to grant him posthumous honors.
I must see him,
alive or dead.
You brought back only this
and claim he's dead?
From such a high cliff,
his body likely shattered completely.
Where is Jiuyue?
Jiuyue is his personal guard.
Why hasn't he returned either?
Jiuyue disappeared
before my brother's fall.
The plague claimed many lives.
Perhaps Jiuyue
also fell victim to it.
♪Awake from dreams, see it all again♪
His Highness fell,
and Jiuyue disappeared.
How can these be mere coincidences?
I'll investigate thoroughly to find out
what truly happened in Xinyang.
♪Through storms I marched♪
My lady!
♪A lifetime's calamity
for one drunken night♪
Chunmei,
prepare my visiting card.
I must meet the Princess Royal.
♪How should I face♪
♪Through bitter storms, no regrets♪
♪A grudge's weight brings endless pain♪
♪A fragile dream, shattered at touch♪
♪Awake from dreams, see it all again♪
♪Flowers bloom and fall,
never to return♪
♪Time flows swift towards decay♪
♪Endless disputes, ever changing♪
♪Yet no wrong or right♪