♪Destiny's choice♪
♪The moment I fell into the nightmare♪
♪Struggling in the whirlpool♪
♪Piercing the devouring darkness♪
♪Who remembers the sorrow in my eyes♪
♪Endless regrets, better unsung♪
♪Fate twists thrice, fire runs deep♪
♪Crossing endless mountains and rivers♪
♪Conquer fear, carve my path♪
♪Crushing wasted time, under vast skies♪
♪We grow wild and cling close♪
♪Dreams aflame, life a song♪
=Threads of Destiny=
(Adapted from Qi Xing Jiu Yue's novel, Reborn Matriarch Watches,
Prince Heir Destroys from Zongheng Chinese Network)
=Episode 4=
Why have you come?
Lord Lu.
My love,
I've missed you so much.
Look at this bracelet.
It's clearly imperial-grade emerald,
the finest quality.
Yu'er is so capable.
Father,
I have urgent matters to attend to.
I must excuse myself.
The Prince Heir didn't come.
How could she still smile?
Exactly.
Your husband's been out long.
Where did he go?
(Had you not insisted
on switching grooms,)
your current husband
would be your brother-in-law.
That wretch!
Could she be plotting something else?
What...
Why have you come?
My lord,
days apart
made me yearn for you.
So I became a maid at Prince's Manor.
I couldn't bear the longing any longer.
Be good.
Be good. Go back now.
I'll visit you tonight, alright?
Will you deceive me again?
I...
Or
does your new wife
serve you better than I do?
No.
It's the Jiang Residence.
We'll be caught.
They're all at the banquet.
No one will notice.
You little vixen!
I'll teach you a lesson.
Wait, Yu'er.
I advise you not to go there.
Now you try to stop me?
When you seduced my husband,
did you ever think of me?
Some secrets are best left unexposed,
and they'll burden others.
Exposing them
will only burden yourself.
You wretch!
Move aside!
Lu Liang!
How could this be?
You adulterous couple!
No.
Adulterers!
Stop hitting!
You wretch!
I'll tear you apart.
Die!
She's a mere maid.
Why stoop to her level?
Such jealousy
makes you unfit to be my principal wife.
You humiliated me for a lowly maid?
How could you?
Lu Liang,
today's her homecoming.
How could you do this
in the Jiang Residence?
If this spreads,
how will Yu'er face others?
You... you...
Utter scoundrel!
Mother!
If I'm not mistaken,
Xueying brought this woman here.
I...
This is your doing.
Jiang Xueying,
you couldn't stand our marital bliss.
So you used cheap tricks
to drive us apart, didn't you?
By your logic,
I made your husband lose control,
enga...
engaging in such indecent acts
in broad daylight?
- Shut up!
- Stop arguing!
Lu Liang,
regarding today's incident,
you must give our family
a proper explanation.
Father-in-law,
this is a matter between me and my wife.
Please refrain from interfering.
You!
Look at the husband you chose!
(Lu Liang!)
I am your wife!
How could you commit
such a vile act today
and refuse to offer any explanation?
Where does this leave me?
Explanation?
You caused a public scene
and humiliated me,
disgracing me completely!
I haven't settled accounts with you.
My household still answers to me.
Defy me again and see what happens!
Haven't you always wanted
to see Lu Liang?
Now's your chance.
How do you know?
I...
(The husband you so carefully chose)
(has many surprises in store for you.)
(In my past life,)
(I never heard of Lu Liang
having mistresses.)
(But in this life,)
(why is everything different?)
Shouldn't you be savoring
your glorious homecoming today?
Why do you look so devastated?
(Blossom Pavilion)
It's all Jiang Xueying's fault.
Alright.
Crying won't help.
Either go charm Lu Liang
to keep him close,
or find a way
to deal with Jiang Xueying.
What can I possibly do?
Even you, Ms. Tian,
fell victim to her
- and lost...
- You...!
I underestimated her,
that's all.
Ms. Tian,
let me kindly remind you.
For today's homecoming,
she brought Master Shiyi along.
What?
She took Shiyi to the Jiang family?
Though Shiyi isn't your biological son,
he's been raised by you.
Today he kept
calling Jiang Xueying 'mother',
sounding like they're mother and son.
My sister has always
been skilled at manipulating hearts.
That wretch!
I should teach her a real lesson.
Why are you here?
To request you
to honor your promise.
The time has come?
Yes.
I demand the Prince's Manor's
household authority.
The household authority
lies with Grandmother.
You should go to her.
Just cooperate, Your Highness.
As for Grandmother,
I'll figure out a way.
I thought you only wanted
the title of Princess Consort.
Never imagined you'd be so ambitious.
The Princess Consort title is merely
temporarily useful to me.
Rest assured,
in one year I'll willingly
divorce you.
Divorce?
You schemed so hard for this position.
Would you abandon it?
We share no affection.
Forced relationships bear no fruit.
You'll lose nothing.
In your future matters
where I can assist,
I'll help you fully.
You?
Help me?
Though the Lu family's fortune
runs deep,
you constantly revel in pleasure houses
and show no responsibility.
You likely won't be able
to preserve your family legacy.
I can't preserve the legacy?
You want a divorce?
Fine.
Draft the agreement now.
And no takebacks later.
Jiang Xueying,
you did come prepared.
Men can't be relied on.
Better safe than sorry.
(Divorce Agreement)
You even stamped it.
(Signed by Jiang Xueying, Eternal Joy)
(Signed by Jiang Xueying,
Signed by Lu Junxing)
Honey,
I acted rashly today.
It's because
I care too much about you.
I made your favorite pastry.
Would you like to try some?
Honey,
don't be angry.
How about I
make it up to you?
Oh dear.
Why won't this untie?
Honey, help me please.
Honey,
why did you prepare a gift for me?
You little vixen have so many tricks.
Let me show you
my various skills.
Your Ladyship!
Your Ladyship! Your Ladyship!
Please save Shiyi!
What happened to him?
Last night he suddenly fell unconscious.
The physicians couldn't
determine the cause.
I fear he's been cursed.
We beg your permission
to summon an exorcist.
What... Hurry!
- Find someone!
- Yes!
Find an exorcist!
(Supreme Valor)
Great calamity!
This is an omen of great calamity!
What is it, Master?
Someone in this household
bears heavy sins,
with resentment soaring high.
It disrupts the young master's destiny.
Master,
who is it?
This lady
committed grave sins in her past life.
Evil spirits haunt her,
and their grudges linger.
Master,
is there a way to resolve this?
Wretched creature, kneel at once!
I can endure for Shiyi's sake.
But that doesn't mean
I'll suffer your abuses.
Someone!
This woman can't remain here any longer!
♪Traces of intertwined fate♪
♪Silent jade carves the foreshadowing♪
♪Among all living beings, only you♪
♪I'd willingly drown♪
♪Lantern in hand, fingers entwined♪
♪You light my life, day and night♪
♪Into your arms, through life and death♪
♪I gaze at the moon and stars afar♪
♪May your longing linger forever♪
♪In dreams and beyond, I'll be with you♪