The Untamed
Episode 18
Tianzhen, go and call her family.
Tell them to bring her child and send her off.
Professor Ren.
It's no use to hold me.
No.
This is the first time I've seen a dead cat.
She looked too beautiful with hooked arm.
You must be so kind to your dad.
What are you looking at?
You scared me.
I was freaked out.
She's quitezenie.
Behind the Ref Texas Hospital,
she has a fight.
Xu Tian is a good kid,
but he's still a good kid.
You...
Chen Yinmei is dead
and you lie to her?
Today you had a great performance.
Your OED role
when you came in
made me smile and said
that Chen Yinmei is still alive.
Am I not
I have to help you play this play.
Right?
My master was right.
The stone can turn into a monkey.
But...
What stone can turn into a monkey?
Come on.
Rock sugar.
Let's enjoy this.
Ye Xiaosu,
next time they're right in the right place,
let's eat it and sleep together.
Dad, laugh.
That time,
I will cheer up our mother for you only by your side.
Great.
Let's go.
Okay.
Professor Ren, if I get caught and jailed,
could I ask you to do my medical examination?
In my life, I didn't choose Jansi.
She's your daughter.
Okay.
Then I'll go apologize to them.
I'll kneel down and kowtow to them.
I'll give them all my money.
As long as they can let me go,
let me take care of my Jansi.
Why would you let them let you go?
Didn't Cheng Ying hit your daughter?
Isn't she dead?
What else can I do?
If you give them all your money, what will you use to save your daughter?
As long as she's alive,
I can sell my house and my body.
There's always a way.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Professor Ren, you're so kind and kindhearted.
Can you take in our daughter?
I can do anything.
I used to be an accountant. I can be a receptionist.
I can also clean and do cleaning work.
As long as you can take in our mother and daughter,
I can do anything.
You're going to jail soon.
How are you going to work here?
Do you have any relatives at home?
Call them quickly.
What if the police take you away?
How am I going to deal with your daughter?
You should make a decision quickly.
What do you think I should do?
I'm going to jail.
I'm going to be a police officer.
If I die,
I won't even have someone to entrust my daughter to.
No.
Cheng Ying is still alive.
Get up.
She's still alive.
I just went to see her. She's still alive.
She's still a little sick.
She's still alive.
As long as I'm here, it's up to me if she's still alive or not.
Professor Chen,
I beg you.
I beg you to consider my daughter's sake.
You must save her.
Okay. Okay. Get up. Get up.
Come. Come. Come.
Be careful.
Come.
Be careful. Be careful.
Do you still hate me?
From sadness to happiness,
do you have any feelings?
I'm asking you.
When you were in love with someone and left,
did you ever think of going with him?
When a person dies,
there's nothing left.
Your hatred and grudges
have no origin.
You said you wanted to leave.
What about Jian Xi?
Okay.
Today, the worst thing in your life
has passed.
Anger is a secret in your heart.
As long as you get angry,
you are your own effort.
In fact, you're forgiving others
just to return to your original self.
You don't have anything.
You still have Jian Xi.
Right?
Have you found your child?
You've been putting your main energy
in the lawsuit,
money, and curse.
What about Jian Xi?
I'll go find her.
I must save Jian Xi.
So, you must put all your energy
in the most important thing.
When you got angry,
you forgot about Jian Xi.
If you didn't have the power to help you,
what would happen
if the wheel fell?
You're forgiving others
just to return to your original self.
The most important thing is to let go.
You must be hungry.
Jian Xi hasn't eaten yet.
Right.
She is not dead yet.
Every child has to be resurrected.
Explain everything to Jian Xi.
No need to explain.
Don't ðŸ˜Š
Do not stand on her side.
I'll tell him.
Let her go first.
Boss.
Do you want to go somewhere?
Of course.
I've got some important thing.
Again,
let's be fast to the elevator for a while
and then go out again.
No problem.
Boss?
Excuse me a moment.
×›Î’ÏŒÏÎ±Î½Î·ê³µÏ†Î®
I'm Jae Oops.
Hello.
Jun Da.
Yes,
I have something to you for a favor.
Thank you for today.
It's nothing.
I found a job.
Can you
tell them
I work in the clinic?
I have a
I tell them I have.
You want me to lie?
I tell you,
I never lie.
I can't lie for you.
You know,
there are ten lies
behind a lie.
If you want something,
you must fight for it.
You can't use your power.
Understand?
I see.
Sorry that I'm late.
I don't recognize your dress.
What…
What dress?
I don't like mayonnaise.
The roasted duck is the best.
I forgot that you're vegetarian.
The roasted chives and pork
are also delicious.
Don't order for me.
I've been waiting for you
mainly to refuse you in person.
The relationship between us
has ended.
Okay, that's it.
What are you doing?
Give me back my bag.
You...
You can keep the bag
in my place first.
After the class is over,
I'll give it back to you.
Madam.
Give me ten skewers of...
Roasted pork and pork waist.
And one more skewer of
roasted mushrooms and chives.
Okay?
Okay.
Didn't I tell you
not to order for me?
I don't eat junk food.
Order for me.
It's delicious.
It's a pity that you didn't eat it.
I told you in advance
that I would come here
today
mainly to consider
coming closer to your hospital.
But it won't be the next time.
Yes.
But in my limited
life and economic background,
I can still open a restaurant
at this time.
It's not a bar.
It's a barbecue stall.
Bar?
It's too noisy.
It's not suitable for class-rehearsal.
Can't you
change the time?
I'll come back
to rehearse at night.
I'll come back to rehearse at night.
Then I can go to the clinic
on my day off.
Let me start.
You eat
such a heavy oil
and salt food at midnight.
Is your lifestyle
so unhealthy?
You and you
are both healthy.
You are a doctor.
I'm a Chinese.
But you are in the Chinese medicine class
with me.
The Chinese medicine is focused on health.
Health is before treatment.
According to your Chinese theory,
at this point,
you should put your phone in the living room,
lie on the bed and be a director.
If you want to help me
make up for my bad habits,
I can only
repay you
by this way.
What about this one?
We focus on
the relationship between the heart and the soul.
The human history says
that if we
do our best to keep our health,
we can only
achieve 10% of our health.
The remaining 40% of our health
comes from
the spiritual level.
The health of the soul
is the most important thing.
Look.
Am I right?
The Chinese medicine and the Western medicine
are finally agreed.
It doesn't matter what the medicine is.
If I die,
I'll die without a surname.
It's not the surname you're talking about.
It's the surname of the mood,
the surname of the spirit,
the surname of the heart,
and the surname of the energy level
and the surname of the life.
The inner spirit says
that the body is like a god
and a healthy body.
It's not only the body of the body,
but also the body of the heart,
which is sweet and weak
and has a spiritual inner hand.
What I'm talking about
is the surname.
The teacher said it last time.
Language is the external language of thought.
No, it's the extension.
What do you think
of all these thoughts?
I'm just teaching you.
It seems that you don't want to learn it.
Let's end it.
You're angry.
Aren't you a lawyer?
Aren't you a Chinese doctor?
Emotions are only beneficial to people
when they are harmful.
You can't treat people with personal emotions
when you're in a lawsuit.
What Chinese doctors pay attention to
is the joy, anger, sadness, and happiness
to keep the loyalty.
How is it?
I'm good at it, right?
I'm not angry.
I just want to go back
to sleep and get a beauty sleep.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm sincerely sorry.
You're a good teacher and a good student.
It's not easy for me to come to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm not a good student.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't come to study Chinese medicine.
Why?
I've learned a lot of things before.
Every class is excellent.
But I still don't understand
the meaning of life.
I used to work hard to become excellent
to make my mom happy.
I worked hard to make money
But when my mom left,
I suddenly realized
that working hard to make money and being excellent
is meaningless.
Pi Yi.
So,
my goal
is to get a good matter
as my aim to work hard.
I want to prove my status
to you.
The course is a mess.
If you Brilliant whereas I Linked
We will enter the main course,
so tomorrow.
Don't try to comfort me.
When I'm in trouble,
my audience is all emotional.
I can't.
You're painting me.
I'm not that capable.
You're so stubborn.
You're eating such a trashy meal
in the middle of the night.
I'm lucky.
I'm open-minded.
I can afford to put down.
This is the root of health.
Open-minded.
You're picking thorns in our Chinese medicine class.
You even fight with the patients' families.
How do you know everything?
How do you know
that I'm the undercover?
It's not a secret.
The teacher knew it the first day you came.
You looked at your phone in class.
You were always busy.
To be honest,
the teacher asked me to come
to tutor you today.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be here
with you.
The teacher knew it?
Of course.
Then why did she ask you to tutor me?
The teacher
put her and the class
in the microscope
to show you.
The doctor saw the illness of life.
The Chinese doctor saw the illness of people.
You can pick thorns in the class.
But the teacher
wants to cure you.
Madam.
Bring me a bottle of yogurt.
Okay.
I want the sugar free one.
Why are you here?
Are you following me?
You...
Do you know how to play this?
I know a lot.
Wait.
It's cool.
I want to learn it.
You want to learn how to skate?
Yes.
You want to learn it?
I don't want to teach you.
If you don't teach me,
I'll go back and tell your parents.
I'll tell your grandparents.
I'll tell them that you're playing
this kind of dangerous project.
It's dangerous.
It's fatal.
I'll go back and tell them.
You want to learn it?
You want to tell the teacher?
Go ahead.
You can tell me after you finish it.
It's okay.
I'm a parent.
No one cares about me.
But some people are different.
You're the treasure of their heart.
If your grandparents know it,
they'll scold you.
They'll say you're a bad mouth.
They'll say you're a man.
Stop.
I'll teach you.
But you have to swear.
You know everything.
You can't tell anyone else.
I swear.
I won't tell anyone else.
If you play this,
you'll never have enough food.
Good enough.
I promise.
When did you teach me?
I made it with the medicine.
What medicine?
Bye.
Teach me.
You're welcome.
Hello.
Madam.
I want a delivery.
312, Xiaoming.
Thank you, aunt.
You're welcome.
Hello, aunt.
Hello.
What's wrong?
Well,
power outage again.
What's going on?
Why is it power outage again?
Power outage again.
Sorry.
Open the door.
Go away.
Power outage again.
Coming.
You're using a scarf again.
A scarf.
You can't use it.
You're making dumplings.
Sorry, aunt.
I'm hungry.
I won't do it again.
I'll never do it again.
Okay?
I've told you many times.
Try it.
Who are you?
Why are you here?
Aunt.
You're here.
Where do you live?
I found a cheap
place.
I can live in it for about 30 days.
Can you take a shower?
Why would I?
I can live in a good place.
You'd better not talk to me.
I'll find you a place.
See?
You'll move this bed
into the warehouse when you sleep at night.
It's not appropriate.
What's wrong with it?
I'll take care of it.
Besides, you're so stubborn.
If I were you,
I'd be a doctor in this hospital.
I'd solve the problem of survival first.
We're different.
I've been in this hospital
for ten years
like those nurses.
I've got my own clinic.
Can anyone take care of me?
You know
our industry
is only worth it
after we grow up.
You're different.
If you're born with the antidote,
if you grow up in a famous family,
which teacher you worship
is the top in the industry.
As for me,
I can only say
which teacher has a crush on me.
I'll learn from him.
After five years,
maybe I'll be able to do it alone.
You tell me.
If I can't
take care of my family,
what should I do?
So, this free chance
to learn from my teacher
is for someone like me.
This is the key to the clinic.
Just remember
to move the bed
before you go to work.
Okay.
You don't thank me?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Why did you give me money again?
I was in a clinic with my grandpa
and earned some money.
Of course I should share the good things with my friends.
Your grandpa is in a clinic and he still gives you money?
Yes.
It's all mine.
We've discussed it.
As long as I'm willing to follow him,
he'll give me a raise.
I'll take my leave then.
You're welcome.
Mr. Ren.
What are you two doing here?
We're cleaning.
You're cleaning
and not taking anything?
I'll go now.
Mr. Hu.
Young man.
How is it?
Did you receive the invitation?
I received it yesterday.
This year,
Mr. Zhang is the chairman of the reputation.
You're the senior.
You're the main guest.
I still want to give Huang Weijia
a chance to be the successor.
Give the successor a chance.
Who are you going to bring with you?
I want Tianzhen,
Li Quan
and Sun Tou.
He's the one
I like.
Who are you talking about?
Sun Tou is the successor of Jiang's Zhen Sect.
He's in that position.
He has to go no matter what.
I'm afraid
he'll embarrass Zhong Zhen.
This is Zhong Zhen's first time.
He's the one
who will judge you
and Zhong Zhen.
It's his business.
It's his business
to be the successor.
It's my business
to bring him or not.
Everyone has their own responsibility.
It's simple.
You're not involved in the case.
I'm the principal
to take part in this case.
You should
put my school
and those stupid people
in the same place.
They'll think we're loyal.
Don't forget.
I'm in this position for you.
You should consider my embarrassment.
That's your business.
Well...
It's everyone's business.
Everyone's business?
Yes.
How depressing.
You're so annoying.
Mengmeng,
This marmer
will bringê° bad fuls
to theko.
Look.
Good?
Wu Jun's
This one...
He needs tournament.
You're so funny.
Well,
will Jian Xi
have a check-up the day after tomorrow?
Why are you here today?
We're not only here today.
We'll come every day.
What do you mean?
Wait.
I mean, Miss,
there are some things
you need to think about.
Don't be nervous.
I'm not here to fight.
I'm here to help.
I told the professor that
I used to be an accountant.
From today on,
I'll be a doctor in our clinic.
I'm officially working here.
Really?
I've never heard of it.
You'll be there every day.
Then...
Then you won't look for me?
I will.
I've asked someone to ask.
I'll leave as soon as I get news.
In the meantime,
my Jian Xi...
It's okay.
Mengmeng.
It's okay. Go.
Come here.
Mengmeng.
Mengmeng, come here.
I'm not here to fight.
Look.
I scared you that day.
No.
Yes.
I'm not here to fight.
It's okay.
Don't be afraid.
Zhu Xia, you're here.
Dr. Sun.
Don't be afraid.
Let me tell you.
Get up.
Yes.
This is...
This is not good.
Take this.
Let me see.
Yes.
Mengmeng likes to draw.
It's not good.
I'll leave this to you.
I'll do it.
Don't worry.
Meiqi.
Dr. Song.
You've improved a lot.
What's this?
You're not good at it.
You're really good.
Look at Mengmeng.
She's drawing so well.
Dr. Song
It's by reverse.
We see some death.
Am I cute?
No.
Medical Education
in medicine.
So this is the difference between
Chinese medicine and Western medicine.
So I think
Western medicine's future development
should be
to the best of its ability.
So what about Chinese medicine?
Chinese medicine should be
to the best of its ability.
Today we are going to talk about
in modern society,
what is the biggest loss?
What is it?
It's the loss of people.
Du Wei,
do you know who is the
top in our Chinese medicine industry?
Who?
Ren Xinzheng.
Professor Neng?
He's quite famous.
What?
He's in your company?
We've been friends for years.
He's teaching in our school now.
He's the head of the research
and he's the treasure of our area.
Teaching in the class?
We're going to build
a top-class
Chinese medicine talent training center here.
The projects of the city's
state-of-the-art research and development
are not in the direction of investment.
Moreover,
the school is the way to expand
in the last century.
It's hard to say.
How long do you think
we can do this?
It's hard to say.
We're just thinking.
We can learn for free.
We've invited
a lot of top-class people to teach us.
Once the news spreads,
if you want to work in the Chinese medicine industry,
you can come to me.
It's not like you're in the Chinese medicine circle.
We can say it with our eyes.
I'm the business school of Chinese medicine.
The school has learned hundreds of thousands of moves.
It's free here.
Can you compete with me?
People have emotions.
They have hatred.
It's annoying.
What should we do?
Take a look.
Is it okay to take the medicine?
Obviously not.
What should we do?
The Chinese medicine is good.
The happiness is in the stomach.
But,
we're not the Bodhisattvas in the temple.
If you have a grudge,
you must say it.
The following sentence is
called
the end of the end.
We've known
that our emotions are out of the middle.
We've hurt our body.
What should we do?
We can still
adjust it.
Let's talk about
how to adjust
our bad emotions.
Chinese culture
is a time-traveling skill.
The Taoist
is a good thing.
If the culture
has no effect of painting,
how can it be related to culture?
What should we paint?
What?
What are we painting?
We're painting the negative emotions.
If a person
has negative emotions,
you must use action to paint it.
Escaping and delaying
will cause great harm to the body.
I think your thinking pattern
is a little problematic.
I agree with Mr. Liu.
You must
stay in the first place.
Then you can make Internet home.
The money is from the people around you.
The medicine and medicine transactions,
online bookings,
and the mutual recommendation of Zhong Xixi.
These are all projects for making money.
The biggest advantage of this school
is the 17, 27, 37
of Huangpu Military School.
That's right.
This idea is good.
If you organize it and pull it out,
it's a complete plan.
This is the most valuable thing in the Chinese medicine world.
Yes.
It's a day in your place.
Your original area will be full of play.
That's right.
Another important thing is
not to talk about the profit model.
If we talk about the profit model,
it's not a small project.
Don't talk about the vision.
Talk about the ideal.
Like Musk.
Talk about the fire of the people.
The world is not going to be built.
The passion of the big and old.
If you talk about the ideal,
you are not suitable.
Think about it.
In the past,
people would definitely think
that your corporate culture
is not about the ideal,
but money.
Professor Ren is right.
If he talks about the ideal,
the whole world will believe him.
Well,
we have a four-a-month meeting next month.
You invite Professor Ren here
to tell everyone
the vision of Chinese medicine development.
Let's talk about the rest.
I think it's
very suitable.
It's settled.
Let's go.
Hello, Professor Ren.
Today is the day you have a re-è¨º.
I have finished my class.
Why haven't you arrived yet?
Actually, I have been there.
At the door of my classroom,
I heard the emotional class you taught.
I feel so happy.
My mood seems to be
all cleared up.
I feel my disease is all cured.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Professor Ren.
I'm here!
Where's the skateboard?
You don't have any illness.
Why are you here?
Are you here to have food?
Today
I came back.
Why is parties and dances
always drunk?
Ca matar?
No...
I'll teach you first.
I mean, you guys,
why do you like
this kind of things?
You're so happy to be called your master, right?
Are you childish?
You have to be famous in the world.
Since I promised to teach you,
I must be serious.
Otherwise, one day, you...
If I'm embarrassed
and make trouble outside,
I'll kick you out, okay?
It's a deal.
Okay.
So numb.
What?
There's a trick to drink wine.
Look.
This is the good wine
my grandpa has been collecting for years.
It's absolutely good.
How is it?
Is it interesting?
It's strong.
It must be.
Don't be greedy.
Please.
Brother,
we can't just drink here.
Although you're not sensible,
it's not appropriate.
Can you be more careful?
My time is very expensive.
You've been waiting for these lines.
I can't focus on it.
Pass it onto me.
Okay.
Why are you still so determined
of this uniform?
As for me,
it's done by Taobao,
the exclusive spit box for commentaries.
From head to toe.
One set costs 55 CCPR,
the dayoking collection series.
By the way,
if we count the cash dollars
for the tots in one attempt,
it's 80中共R.
Really?
You're also shopping for Tao'sy Openure?
I'm not going.
By the way, let me tell you.
During the break,
we have to stop
our regular classes.
Why?
Are you going on a trip?
I'm going to join the Chinese-Japanese forum.
But...
I don't think you're in the forum.
Besides, they won't ask
a half-wit, half-baked, half-baked person
to join.
This time,
I'm invited by the organizer.
Why?
Why are you asking me?
The organizer is an old friend
of mine who has been
a customer for many years.
I'm going to
bother the customers
and join the forum.
I think you're going to
support the forum.
Take me with you.
Those who work as undercover like me
have to be in the old school
to be able to see the bottom.
Take me with you.
You're an adult.
You're not easy to deal with
except for one person.
Besides,
there are many ways to go.
I've seen the schedule.
You have to go up the hill
before dawn.
You must go on the night road.
What if you meet a bear
or a fight?
The most important thing is
it's a long road.
You have to change your driving style.
As a bato manufacturer,
there are rules that
the idea of building a car
may be misrepresented
in the day light,
I'm sorry.
I'll light up your life.
The people in the light are just ordinary identities.
Light up the ordinary people's souls with ordinary bodies.
Burn the passion of the
one-shot gun.
Use one sentence,
we are only in this world.
The people in the light are just ordinary identities.
Light up the ordinary people's souls with ordinary bodies.
Burn the passion of the
one-shot gun.
Use one sentence,
we are only in this world.
The people in the light are just ordinary identities.
Light up the ordinary people's souls with ordinary bodies.
Burn the passion of the
one-shot gun.
Use one sentence,
we are only in this world.