The Long Ballad
Episode 16
That girl is dead?
No, no, no.
She's just a crow's mouth.
She's back.
I'm scared to death.
What are you doing?
Half of the bookshelves
of that girl were cut off.
How many people are there in the bookshelves?
Two.
Isn't there one left?
What's this?
Stop writing.
What's wrong with him?
I saw what explanation a young man would mention
as he was brake this dating letter.
He has the uterus' to the Factory.
Has the uterus?
Is that what he thinks?
He looks like...
Like a fool strain his brain a little.
Toto,
if you're serious,
I only believe you.
Why are you three so nervous?
It's not like you're pregnant.
There's a head and a head.
In the subjective sense,
you've done a good thing.
You've done a good thing, you know?
A good thing.
You're relieved?
Then we'll meet again.
Will you save me or not?
I guess you're naive.
You're blinded by your own idea.
It's not a big deal.
Sun.
Listen to me.
I think in this life,
as long as you don't harm others on purpose,
you deserve to be forgiven.
Just like me.
I've broken my bones.
But I'm brave.
I can't write it down
in my personal dark history.
Everything
should be seen from a bright angle.
Don't blame yourself.
We'll meet again
in the future.
We'll still
have to
have a birthday party
when it's time to.
We'll have a party
and celebrate.
We'll celebrate.
Tao Tao.
Don't learn Chinese medicine.
Really.
You're good at cooking.
You should cook for others.
I came here
because I'm good at cooking.
Look.
What do you want to eat?
Oh, my.
It's a big world.
Food is the most important.
Sun.
You said that
there are two abalones.
What are they?
They're twin abalones.
Twin abalones.
It means
there are two heads
on one abalone.
Yun.
You lied to me.
I've never had abalones.
I've never had them.
Where can I buy twin abalones?
I'll buy them for you.
Let's not go anywhere.
I'll go.
Fine.
Sun Tao Tao.
Sun Tao Tao?
Reverie,
You really got up Ladies first time.
I didn't see it.
Wait.
Can you lend me your clothes?
I studied last night.
You can use your own things
when you study.
But if you don't get permission from others
and take others' things without permission,
it's called stealing.
What?
What do you mean stealing?
You're talking too seriously.
We're like roommates.
You're always yours and mine.
It's narrow-minded.
You should know how to share.
I...
I want to ride alone, you know?
Will you care about the next person?
No, you won't.
You'll leave after you finish riding.
If you're really unhappy,
I'll give it back to you.
No need.
Go away.
Ruocha.
What do you mean?
You don't want it?
If you don't want it, then leave it to me.
I'll buy it.
I just wiped it.
Thank you.
Monitor.
I want to tell you something.
It's about the things he stole from me.
Steal?
What did he steal?
It's not stealing.
It's taking.
Taking.
If you don't get permission from others,
you'll steal things from others.
You can steal a lot of things.
A coat costs tens of thousands.
Tell me.
What did he steal from you?
This.
This?
I thought it was something else.
It's just a human model.
Don't be too petty.
You two can use it together.
I think so too.
We can use it together.
First of all,
I don't like things that others touch.
Second,
I don't like Sun Tao.
So I'm going to apply for a new dorm.
I'm sorry.
There's no empty room.
Then we need to make three agreements.
From now on,
you can't touch my things.
Anything.
Do you remember?
Tao, what do you think?
I'm generous.
He can touch my things anyway.
And I think...
Move your butt.
He has a fair rule.
Don't worry.
I won't touch anything.
So please don't touch my things.
No.
It's a two-sided relationship.
You can't decide it alone.
I allow you to take my things.
You should allow me to take your things.
Is that right?
Right?
Good morning, Mr. Ren.
Good morning, Mr. Zheng.
Mr. Ren.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to live in the same room with Mr. Sun.
How about this?
I'll go home every night.
I promise I won't be late every morning.
Why?
I...
Ren Xu.
I want to go home and sleep too.
Any other students
want to go home and sleep?
Yes, sir.
I'll go to wake up Boss Cui.
Bye.
Mr. Yang.
Since we're in the first postrec migrant class,
Who wrote it?
I did.
You say it.
If you want to learn,
you can't go home and sleep.
No.
You can't go home and sleep.
What Sun Toto said
is true.
If we don't live together,
the shortcomings we have
are biased in Chinese medicine.
We don't have a middle-class disease.
Chinese medicine is different from Western medicine.
Western medicine is based on machines.
Once the data is out,
where are you biased?
Machine medicine.
Chinese medicine is different.
Chinese medicine is based on pulse.
The first level of pulse is liver.
Liver is a word.
In Chinese culture,
it's very advanced.
I want to ask
a quote from
the Big Diction of Yin and Yang.
In my opinion,
in the opinion of the audience,
how can I know
you are sick
by using your pulse?
The word is
the word for the word.
Everyone knows that
we are usually mischievous.
We measure things with the word.
How can I know
I'm biased?
Who will tell me
I'm right?
Your roommate,
your classmate,
your teacher,
after living together for 24 hours,
they know what your shortcomings are.
They will bring it up to you
and let you correct it.
In the end,
our class
has been living together
for 24 hours
for three months.
The purpose is to
find the mirror.
Usually,
we forget to take מע calmly
to try different ways
to help him接下來.
So,
if his reading doesn't go well,
he may stay awake
and read book all day.
This is also
my comeback,
to be with your classmates for a while.
It's not about 75 yuan.
If you want to be a good student,
it's not about 75 yuan.
If you're fierce and threaten others,
It's not about 75 yuan.
Tongtong,
why does the teacher always stand by your side?
My nephew is a good student.
He always helps me
no matter he's an old man or a friend.
Right?
You look happy and energetic.
Mr. Zheng, you look so happy.
It seems that Hefeng Hall
is in the top ten this year.
I heard that
your company's health products are very popular.
To be honest,
our company used to focus on
medicines and injections.
But this area
is very competitive.
Right.
Compared with those
hundred-million-dollar medicine factories,
we have no competitive advantage.
The year before last,
the principal came to teach us.
I was stunned by it.
In the past two years,
we have been working hard to develop
health products and health care products.
He also helped us
improve the drink recipe.
If we can get it,
the principal is the biggest achievement.
Today, I came here
to thank the principal in person.
Is he in the door?
Don't you know?
The principal has resigned.
He has run a
Chinese medicine ten-year-old class outside the school.
He has resigned?
That's a good thing.
Our company is planning to add
the school-age subsidy
for the poor students
of our Chinese medicine university this year.
It can be used to support the ten-year-old class.
No.
Mr. Zheng.
What do you mean?
You know that
our company takes 1.5 million yuan every year
to help us
to make the school-age subsidy.
I know that.
The corresponding school-age subsidy
takes half a month's time
to come to our company
to give free lectures and medical certificates.
Okay, Mr. Zheng.
If you are worried about the lecture,
you don't have to do it.
I have been a friend of Professor Ren for 30 years.
I can guarantee that
I can teach him
the lecture and medical certificates.
You can ask me for anything.
Our school will be your strong support.
Of course I believe in Professor Wu's level.
But Professor Ren
is our chief consultant expert.
When he started,
he helped me a lot.
If I don't give him the scholarship
because he left,
it's not enough.
Am I right?
My senior
is a man of personal merit.
His good deeds are for personal use.
You have been in the class for a day.
Are you tired?
Well,
at the end of the class,
let's play a game together.
No, no, Mr. Zheng.
I'll take part in it.
Okay.
What game?
Guessing the language.
The smell of the sound and the sound of the sheep.
The one who knows is kind.
The one who knows is lucky.
The one who knows is wise.
The people use it for a day.
That's it.
I don't understand it.
What's this?
It's a coat.
Yes.
Is it an object?
How do you know it's an object?
Prepare the card.
Is it hanging on the wall?
Is it edible?
It's said to be a daily item.
Really?
I know it.
Say it.
Wash the leaves, wash the hair,
brush the teeth, rub the feet,
and wash the dishes.
Almost.
One is always right.
Thank you.
They're all wrong.
Listen carefully.
The sound and the sound of the sheep are the same.
Think about it.
It's chopsticks.
Yes.
Tell us why it's chopsticks.
The sound and the sound of the sheep are a group.
But gloves are a group.
You wear gloves in summer?
People use it for a day but they don't know it.
It's a frequency.
It's a habit.
I remember I read an article
in high school.
It's chopsticks.
Chopsticks are the culture of China.
Yes.
You're right.
Chopsticks.
Who can tell me
which side of the chopsticks
are the sound and the sound of the sheep?
The upper side is the sound.
The lower side is the sound.
The hand is the middle.
So let's be honest.
If you hold the chopsticks well,
you can hold anything.
Thank you.
Why are we having fun today?
It's for the theme of the next class.
The Chinese medicine.
Why is it called Chinese medicine?
Is it the Chinese medicine of the Central?
The Chinese medicine in the middle.
Listen to the next section.
By the way,
Qingming is coming soon.
The students have to make some offerings.
Ms. Song will teach you.
You'll win today.
You'll arrange the time at night.
Okay, everybody.
Class is over.
I'm really impressed
with Mr. Ren.
He always told me
as long as you're firm,
and when you really need it,
money will come to you.
Look,
your godfather
is here today.
Our class
needs money everywhere.
These 2 million
really solve our problem.
Support each other.
Professor Ren is popular.
He needs us.
We deserve
Professor Ren's return.
It was so difficult to start a business.
I had no direction.
Professor Ren instructed me
to plant love in Qichun,
to grow oil, cover the land, and raise the rich.
When I save enough money,
Professor Ren helped me
develop Chinese medicine.
In the end,
my money is Professor Ren's.
I can't afford to lose money.
As long as he needs it,
I can open the door at any time.
It's getting late.
Let's go first.
We won't bother you.
You've come a long way.
You're leaving without seeing
the real person?
I think it's time for you to come back.
Have some tea.
Come on.
You two,
why are you
coming to my temple today?
Let's go.
Xing Chen
sent us money.
He gave us the scholarship
for the school.
The school doesn't need money,
but we need it for our school.
I can't take this scholarship.
Why not?
Look.
The scholarship is for the school.
I've resigned.
Look, I've resigned.
I can't take the money away.
Right?
I know.
You should thank me.
Actually, I should
do all these
when I was in school.
I should thank the school
for the help and support
to me.
So the scholarship
is for the school.
Well...
You're not qualified to study.
The elder sister said
you should be careful.
How about this?
I'll give 1.5 million to the school.
How about I leave the rest to you?
It's a big deal
to let poor students
finish their studies.
Right.
Mr. Ling is right.
We don't need it.
What about the lecture?
My employees and clients
all recognize you.
I can tell the teacher.
The way is good.
The lecture is good
for the patients.
The lecture
is a must.
Professor Ren,
I believe you.
Mr. Wu,
I don't mean to offend you.
You're a good student.
You're not qualified to study in Jiangzhou.
But, Professor Ren,
the important clients
are all for you.
You're not qualified to study.
I'll go to the lecture.
I'm not qualified to study,
but I still want to go to the university.
Don't worry.
But I have a condition.
Shandong,
is it okay?
If we have the lecture,
we'll be half of the students.
What do you think?
No problem.
It's a great deal
to have Shandong.
What time is it?
Why hasn't the teacher
invited us to dinner?
I've told the students
that the teacher will be on duty tonight.
They won't have dinner.
We've been in the class for a day.
They won't even let us eat.
No money?
I can give you one month.
My agency's
이트 withdraws over Labor Day.
I'll take care of the pain.
It's not the time
to start a fire yet.
If you can,
don't spend my parents' money.
don't spend the money of the hospital.
I'm just in love with Master.
If I don't love Master,
I won't marry you.
Master is so fierce.
How can you not know it?
What's up?
I want to ask you
if you'll bring us
the treasure of Zhiyuan tonight.
Yes.
Zhe,
get ready first.
I'm going.
Yes, sir.
Aren't we due yet?
They also store well hones.
No poison.
You could have told me earlier.
The poison is about to come.
I'll be done soon.
Division commander,
I searched the internet.
Youais have to buy1,000 of these
for 30 yuan on the drinks.
But you pay.
I don't.
I have no money.
Toto,
this is our gratitude.
This is our respect and yearning for the immortals.
Now,
technology has developed.
If you want to contact someone,
you can not only hear the voice on the phone,
but also watch the video.
Seeing the people on the phone,
unlike the old days,
a letter from a family,
a year back and forth.
People's lifestyle has changed.
But there are still things that haven't changed.
Just like what Mr. Ren said today.
There is a long way to go.
If there is a change, there must be a change.
When you see it clearly,
you will be able to see it clearly.
What's not changed?
I used to think that my salary would not change.
Now even my salary has increased.
What hasn't changed is the human emotion.
Thousands of years ago,
parents passed away.
The child will cry.
Today after thousands of years,
it's still the same.
But if Dad always dries the money,
would you still near him,
put out the money?
Not to us.
So because of this,
my family is well senior.
But now I am still with two children,
who gave up their life and wanted to live,
be weak,
and live a lonely life.
impress
Rebecca
what is that?
This is the first time
that I have been cleaning the tomb for you.
I hope that every classmate
will have the same experience, okay?
Actually,
I just want to clean the tomb for my mother.
Okay.
I will tell Mr. Ren
to give you a holiday after cleaning the tomb.
You are so smart.
It won't affect you if you miss a class.
Thank you, Ms. Song.
What does that mean?
If Rebecca is smart,
I am not smart.
I won't be able to do it if I miss a class.
That's not what I mean.
Ms. Song means
no matter how many classes you miss,
it won't affect you.
No matter how many classes you miss,
I thought you were praising me.
I was just thinking about it.
Tongtong.
Sit here.
Let me see what you have.
You are talking back to me.
If I keep talking back to you,
you will clean the tomb for me tomorrow.
Then you should have more.
Naive.
Sit down.
Is that you today?
Yongchun.
Ye Wen.
Don't be hard on me.
I know it.
No.
She abused me.
Tongtong,
your legs
areそうですね,
graceful,
and graceful.
I instantly
concede to your magazine pech42.
Really?
Because of you, manicure-de Kern is no longer as easy as itu hiking
Have you eaten
This one
And how about Ou Yue's profile
what
This face
Let go of me!
Stop!
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
You are still so excited.
How about this?
You two keep this posture.
Don't move. Don't let go of it for an hour.
This is not fair.
I am bending my waist.
He is sitting.
After an hour, I will be more tired.
Yanzhen, let go of it first.
You two, go to the front.
You know how to lie to your son.
Take your legs off.
Get up.
I know my son.
If you don't bother him,
he won't fight with you.
He has been a martial arts coach since he was a child.
He is the champion of the country.
You can beat him.
If he wants to fight with you, you would have been dead.
It's your son.
First, he looks like a man.
Are all the clothes suitable?
Yes.
No.
Why not?
I...
I don't want to wear a dress.
I designed it wrong.
I want to wear pants like them.
Why?
I don't like this suit.
The dress must be
a little smaller than the long dress we usually wear.
But on holidays,
we must wear the dress.
This is called etiquette.
You don't feel good wearing it.
You don't live in etiquette.
Look at which girl
is like you, with a bad temper.
If you sit on the chair,
you won't feel uncomfortable.
Why don't you tie me up?
I'll be honest.
Mr. Song, I have a rope.
I can't tie you up.
You are really a monitor.
You are a monitor.
Don't go to the
It looks like you didn't wear it.
This is the eighth great miracle of mankind.
You wore it all.
Enough.
I'll buy you one.
My nephew loves me.
If there is no problem with your clothes,
wash it quickly
in the next two days.
We will wear this.
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Our Qingming Ji group
needs to cook
the dishes themselves,
including the Qingtuan.
So these two days,
prepare the ingredients you need.
No.
If I know that it's going to be a festival,
I won't celebrate it.
Mom, I'm too tight.
It's too tight.
What's wrong?
Look.
Isn't this good?
Little idiot.
Okay, get in the car.
Okay.
Good morning, Mr. Song.
Good morning.
Hao Zong.
Hao Zong, where are you going?
Slow down. Don't fall.
I'm going to see the thing.
Go.
I bought you a pair of underwear.
Why didn't you wear it?
That one.
My sister's.
It's too tight.
I can't wear it.
Slow down.
You two saw it.
I can't wear this little girl.
Shengda, I'll leave it to you.
How dare I say she?
She's my uncle.
No hurry.
We're not in a hurry.
Five hundred years.
We can definitely get it.
Five hundred years?
I'm not going to live like an old witch.
Tang Zeng became a monkey
and became a prisoner.
We just put a fake kid
back in the palace.
It's much simpler.
Let me ask Mr. Ren.
You used to be so strict with students.
Students are afraid of you.
Why are you so partial to Toto?
You have no principles, right?
Mr. Ren,
I'm asking you the same question.
Is that true?
Yes.
Tell me.
You caught a cold?
Go and drink some soup.
I felt a little heavy
when I touched your pulse today.
I'll take it.
I'll put it in the car later.
No, no, no.
Go.
Mr. Ren.
Uncle.
Your wife.
Every tree behind your wife
is like a red thread.
What kind of ritual is this?
This is to bring back
all the ghosts in the mountains.
I don't feel good about it.
Students, listen.
There are many
different paths in this mountain.
If you get lost
in the night when you go down the mountain,
you can't go wrong
if you go down
along that sign.
Please don't fall behind.
Because there are wolves,
bears and wild boars in this mountain.
You must pay attention.
Okay.
You're lying to me.
There are so many people
walking along this road.
How can there be wolves,
wild boars and beasts?
How can it be possible?
There was no wolves before.
Now,
after more than 20 years,
young people in the local area
have gone to work in the city.
Some of their parents
are old.
Some of them have passed away.
So,
some houses are abandoned.
The forest
is slowly growing.
Wild beasts
can also be seen here.
Come on.
Let's go.
You're here.
Yes.
Isn't the wild boar
natural fertilizer?
Why do you pick it up?
It's a medicine.
Medicine?
Guys,
have you ever
done a medicine experiment?
When I was in college,
I learned
the basic theory of winter.
I knew
that bats and snakes
are not the same.
I knew that
bats and snakes
are not the same.
I knew that
bats and snakes are the same.
It's also called the same.
But I was confused.
Bats eat different things
every day.
They can't pull out the same things.
How do you know
which bats can pull out
the same things?
How to say?
You can pick one up
and give it to the patients.
It's irresponsible.
Do you like
cat's poop coffee?
Are the standards
you have checked
the same?
They're different, aren't they?
Eating poop is not just a medicine.
Don't underestimate
the poop.
In this world,
any existence
has its own meaning.
Some animals' poop
is more expensive than gold.
You can check it online.
At this moment,
it should be
eight thousand to ten thousand.
What animal?
It's so expensive.
Then tell me.
I'll go back and raise one.
Then I'll send it to pull it every day.
I'll change the money when it pulls it.
The name of this animal
is Mo Xiang Jing.
A head of Mo Xiang Jing
weighs about
50 tons.
You can raise it.
It's amazing.
The poop that Mo Xiang Jing
pulls out
is called Long Xian Xiang.
For example,
we burn incense
and use perfume.
It's amazing
to have it in it.
So,
don't underestimate the poop.
The poop forweigh
Shi Ji wages,
in wholeovy dried plants,
it becomes more expensive
if we should use
the poop during the Up upset?
You can get the definition
from Wu Ling Zhi.
Up upset is still being used at present.
So what's the spot
of Similarity between the Japanese medicine
and Western medicine?
It's hope that
one can stay healthy for a long time.
If one is unhealthy,
each day one can use medicine
and everything to maintain a healthy life.
That's not the protox landmark for bake have weight gain.
It's
It's hard to live with them.
Uncle, where is the animal?
Where can we find it?
In the sea.
Let's go.
How much can the horse we just picked be worth?
There will always be some youth
Like a rain without a trace
There will always be some people
Like the stars in the long night
Time is silent
Don't say that
The one who is in the wilderness has really been here.
The fruits are fresh.
Right?
This teacher Huang Mei is very famous.
She died for decades.
Still, someone came to pay her respects.
What?
Come here.
The ceremony is about to start.
The doctor is going to treat you.
Come here.
The doctor is quite accurate.
I sometimes wear more pants than they do.
Tie the cord.
Tuo Tuo, you have to look carefully.
You are the successor of Jiang's Zhen Sect.
After Jiang's Zhen Sect,
you will lead the juniors
to the ancestors.
Members, today is still Qingming Festival.
Then we will take a vacation.
Qingming Festival is one of the 24 festivals.
The emperor's inner spirit says that
people are in line with the heaven and earth.
Then the sick people
are in line with the heaven and earth.
Then what does the Chinese doctor see as a disease?
He sees the sick people
instead of the disease of life.
If you are in line with the heaven and earth
and let him feel the changes of the four seasons,
and act according to the rules,
then you are not far from loyalty and justice.
Secondly,
Qingming is still an important event
for the ancestors of the four seasons.
I hope that everyone will be sincere
and pay respects to our holy ancestors.
Qingming Festival
Tao, your luggage.
I don't know anyone.
I'm not a young girl.
I think it's too much.
Suddenly.
It's strange.
Let us read the Great One Book of the Capital
before Mr. Huang's tomb.
To the ancestors.
There is someone in the future.
The original intention is not changed.
The old dead is injured.
It's the wisdom of the five branches.
Great One Book of the Capital
Can he hear you reading it?
He can't hear you.
He can't.
There will be some youth
that has nothing to do with hatred
There will be some people
like the stars in the long night
Time is silent
Memories are hard to memorize
The food and drinks in memories
are warm and equal
If there is no pain in life
I will light a lamp for you
The people in the light
are just ordinary identities
Light ordinary people's souls
with ordinary bodies
The people in the light
are just ordinary identities
Light ordinary people's souls
with ordinary bodies
The people in the light
are just ordinary identities
Light ordinary people's souls
with ordinary bodies
The people in the light
are just ordinary identities
Light ordinary people's souls
with ordinary bodies
With a sentence
We cure the coldness of this world
The people in the light
are just ordinary identities
Light ordinary people's souls
with ordinary bodies
The people in the light
are just ordinary identities
Light ordinary people's souls
with ordinary bodies
The people in the light
are just ordinary identities
Light ordinary people's souls
with ordinary bodies
The people in the light
are just ordinary identities
Light ordinary people's souls