(Names, businesses, places, and incidents
mentioned herein are fictitious.)
Bride and groom, bow to each other.
The bride and groom
will exchange rings now.
(Episode 8: The Start of a Rift)
Gosh. Hello.
Slow down. Chew thoroughly.
Dad. Where's Mom?
Mom
had to go to work early.
Okay.
Dad, I've made up my mind.
About what?
I'm going to become a chef.
A chef? Why?
Didn't you want to become a fireman?
I did, but I changed my mind yesterday.
Now, I want to become a chef.
Yesterday? What happened yesterday?
It's a secret.
Anyway, I'm going to become a chef,
so you have to help me.
Just work hard.
I'll support you all the way.
And you know you have to study hard
as a basic principle, right?
I'm going to school now, Father.
-Have a nice day.
-Thanks.
(My woman)
(My man)
Sweetie. What are you doing?
It's eight o'clock already.
Okay.
Why didn't you put on your tie?
Eun-sil.
I forgot how to tie it.
What? You forgot?
You've been tying it for decades,
but you forgot?
Exactly. How could I forget that?
You could've just asked me to do it.
Don't scare me like that.
Your skin became silky soft
from using a mask just once.
Is it? Really?
Yes.
I'll take care of your skin from now on.
Thank you.
And you know, sweetie.
I thought about it all night...
About what?
If you really want to get plugs,
I'll make you a wig using my hair.
Do you want to wear that?
-Your hair?
-Yes.
Sit down.
Look.
Ta-da. Like this.
It looks great on you.
You look 30 years younger. Oh my goodness.
I look like a baby.
-Gyeong-ja.
-Excuse me.
Where are you, Gyeong-ja?
-Darn it.
-Honey, what's with you?
Let me go!
-My goodness!
-My gosh!
-What is this mess?
-I'm...
Darn it. You idiot.
You've lost your mind!
How could you not come home for two days
without even calling?
Do you think being in a slump
is a badge of honor?
Where were you?
Where's your head?
Why are you suddenly doing this?
What?
Tell me. You twerp. Tell me!
Are you trying to kill me, you jerk?
Why you...
Where are you going? I'm not done!
Where are you going?
You punk.
You should've just told us
that you got a girlfriend.
Your mom isn't that narrow-minded.
If you felt uncomfortable telling her,
you could've told me.
I'm more progressive than others.
I've been waiting
for my only son to bring home a girl.
I don't have a girlfriend.
You brat. Must you lie to me too?
What do you mean?
Your mom found a girl's hair clip
in your room.
She clutched that hair clip
and mumbled all night long
like the world was ending.
I was terrified.
I thought she was going to lose her mind.
What does she do?
Is she pretty?
How old is she?
She isn't older than you, is she?
-I don't know yet.
-You don't know yet?
If you say you don't know yet,
it means you're still learning about her.
There is someone.
You do have a girlfriend.
You punk. Now you're finally spilling it.
Did you know Mom was a porn star
from the moment you met?
Of course, I did. Why?
Just asking.
You liked her anyway?
I didn't just like her.
Your mom was the queen.
Porn stars now don't compare.
Hey. Even if she took off a stocking,
she pulled it down a millimeter at a time,
and put her soul into it,
and rolled it down.
When I saw that, I thought
my heart would explode.
Why do you ask?
Is your girlfriend a porn star?
If only you hadn't done that back then
to that jerk,
I could've directed that movie.
Kang Gyeong-ja.
All of this
is because of you.
It's your fault.
It's me, Kang Gyeong-ja.
Mom, how have you been?
I've been well.
No.
Actually, I haven't been well.
(The Late Seo Kyeong-hui)
I've been going through some tough times.
The thing is,
his first love showed up.
Do you remember Hae-suk?
We were close back in high school.
You're the pathetic one.
You're so wary of and on edge around
your husband's first love
from over 20 years ago.
But then again, I'm sure you're anxious.
You're the reason
something that horrendous happened.
I tried hard to forget,
but I can't seem to do that.
What am I going to do now?
What should I do, Mom?
The chairman is waiting for you.
Why are you here?
Do you think you have the right
to be here?
I'm not here to see her.
I came to see you.
You came to see me?
Why is your face so worn out?
Why do you care how my face looks?
Then why did you ask me for a favor?
If you wanted to talk big
and act so arrogantly,
you should've lived a better life
without having to ask for favors.
You acted as if
you're the most prideful in the world.
Why are you such a mess?
I paid you back right away the next day.
So what? That doesn't change the fact
that you asked for a favor.
Hate me for what I did wrong,
but you need to learn to thank me too.
You can't even tell such things apart.
What's the use of being a big professor?
I'll never ask you for another favor.
So I don't want to see you ever again.
It's a relief that he died.
What would you have done
if he had spread those pictures?
Did you get someone
to run a background check on me again?
How much do you know?
I lent you 500 million won.
Did you think I'd just sit on my hands?
I just know who the dead man is.
I don't know who killed him.
That's all I know.
Did you say
you'll never ask me for a favor again?
You said that to me 20 years ago
right before you went to study abroad.
You never know what might happen in life.
You never know
you might have to ask me
for another favor in 20 years.
But when that day comes,
I might be long gone already.
You should live long.
If you ended someone else's life,
you should live for them too.
Still, I'm relieved to see you holding out
and going on with life.
I thought you'd die after her.
I don't need her life,
so you can live for her sake.
(My man)
Hello?
(Jeong-hae, where are you?)
What do you mean? I'm at the hospital.
(Professor Nam Jeong-hae)
(Announcement: Office closed today)
(What is it?)
No, it's nothing.
You left for work without a word,
so I was worried.
You weren't answering your phone either.
I had a lot of work.
Everything is okay, so don't worry.
I'll see you tonight.
(Yeongang University Namseo Hospital)
Mom! Guess what I brought.
Mom?
Mom.
Mom, where are you?
Mom, are you in there?
Mom?
What's going on?
Mom.
(Jeongrip Urology Clinic)
(Middle-Aged Men, Stay Confident!)
Could you show him to the X-ray room?
All right. Please come this way.
-This way, please.
-Oh, okay.
Ms. Sophia Choi? Please come in.
Hello.
What brings you here?
Is it for your husband?
Or perhaps your boyfriend?
My so-called husband
isn't interested in sleeping together.
I thought he might be
sexually dysfunctional,
so I came for a consultation.
I see.
In that case,
it's better for you to come with him
for a consultation.
I need to check his condition in person
to see what and how
his condition is failing.
He's here
with me.
My husband is right here.
(Patient name: Sophia Choi, Choi Mo-ran)
Have you been well?
Choi Mo-ran, you...
Hey, you...
What on earth happened to you in America?
It was filled with surprises.
I'll see you at home.
Tell me what the passcode is.
No, wait.
Why would you go to my place?
What do you mean?
You said you'd take me back
if I lost weight.
It was empty talk. Just get a hotel room.
Why? Is there a reason why
I can't go there?
If a woman is there,
I'll pretend like I don't see her.
You still are awfully rude, aren't you?
You and I got divorced.
We're as good as strangers.
Isn't it rude to be at a stranger's house
all alone?
"Rude."
All right.
In that case,
I'll wait until you're done, honey.
I have nowhere else to go
or the energy to leave.
Then I'll see you later.
Wait... Wait a moment.
Please send in Mr. Yeo.
Doctor. Did you want to see me?
Yes. I need to leave urgently.
Please have Dr. Shin
see the rest of my patients for the day.
Yes, doctor.
Come with me.
Honey, it's still broad daylight.
Mr. Ahn.
Thank you. How did it go?
The pictures from the funeral
that your wife received
and the video you received
were from the same burner phone.
I was right.
That means Joo Gang-san's murderer
was at your friend's funeral.
Probably.
Maybe we should check the guest list
from the funeral.
It may provide a lead.
Would someone who sent pictures like that
have signed the guest book?
Then we can check the security videos
from the funeral home.
I called and asked,
and the videos from that day
have been deleted already.
Mr. Ahn.
Have you heard of Dahan Care Home?
No, I haven't.
Your wife went there
the day of the incident.
My wife
volunteers at a nursing home.
That must be it.
Why? Is there a problem?
Your wife deleted the videos
from her dashcam that day.
She says she deleted them out of habit.
I wondered if you knew anything.
First you suspect me,
now you suspect my wife too?
-Mr. Ahn.
-My Jeong-hae would never.
How many times must I tell you that?
You should catch the killer.
Why are you suspecting
and following innocent people?
Married couples often think
they know the most about each other,
but it's more common
for them to know less than others.
Your wife may have
many more secrets than you think,
and a past you may not know about.
That's all I'm saying.
Where are you going?
I forgot I had plans to go golfing.
(Your wife deleted the videos
from her dashcam that day.)
(Dahan Care Home)
(Calculating your route.)
If you come to the bar drunk again,
I'll throw you into the Han River.
Do you doubt me?
No. You're more than capable.
So behave.
Let me hold you.
What?
Why? Suddenly?
Get over here.
Don't drink because you're miserable.
Got it?
Okay.
I didn't drink because I was miserable.
I drank because life is so hard.
That hurts.
I totally look like a college kid.
He was acting so suspicious,
that I sneaked a look
at his cell phone before he left for work.
And they were chatting about
Hae-suk opening a bar,
and what they should bring,
how they're going to dress...
How much they should chip in...
He was so excited.
No wonder.
He was doing yoga and working out
with dumbbells all night long.
(Exactly.)
I mean, he did a face mask,
which he never does.
He even brought up getting hair plugs.
I thought it was all for me,
but it was for that woman.
Stop crying. It's not worth crying over.
(Gyeong-ja.)
What do I do now?
What do I do?
What do you mean?
You should fight it head-on.
What are you doing tonight?
Let's crash their little party.
Crash?
We should haze them
so they get their heads on straight.
Okay. Let's crash.
Okay. I'll call you after work.
You have to dress nicely.
Okay.
I won't forgive him.
Who cares if she's his first love?
I won't let you take my husband.
Hey you, Baek Hae-suk. Just you wait,
you old hag!
Oh, no. What do I do?
Thank you.
Stay here until you get a place.
I booked it for a month.
Bye. Take care.
Ms. Kang Gyeong-ja.
I'm so happy that you called.
Let's not waste time and go upstairs.
Already? That's good for me.
Isn't that Hyeong-u's wife?
(Ero Hyeong-u)
-Please make it pretty.
-Sure thing.
When are you coming?
I'm going to be late, so meet up first.
Are you meeting your friends?
Can I go too?
Bye.
Why don't you shower too?
Yes. That's good.
I need you to promise me something
before I shower.
What?
Promise you'll make that movie
with my husband.
What?
Darn it.
I can't do that. I can't trust that loser.
But then again,
depending on what you do today,
I may reconsider.
Forget it.
Fine! Okay, I'll do it.
Where? Where should I sign?
You are so impatient.
Here.
Here?
(I, Park Si-o, hire Cho Hyeong-u to direct
the movie being filmed in 2021.)
(Memorandum)
Happy?
Okay, then. Shall we begin?
(Koo Yeong-seon)
Excuse me.
I've heard a lot about you from him.
He said you were his best friend.
Did you meet Man-sik here
at this nursing home?
Yes.
I'm Ms. Koo Yeong-seon's caretaker,
and Mr. Cheon took care of her
for several years.
And we grew close naturally over time.
No.
I respected
and liked him a lot.
I couldn't
control my emotions at the funeral,
so I'm sure some people
got the wrong idea.
But I swear,
we did nothing to be ashamed of.
I mean it.
I know Man-sik would never do
anything like that.
He was a very warm
and good person.
Let me ask you one more thing.
Do you know
what relationship
Ms. Koo Yeong-seon had with Man-sik?
Yes.
You do know?
I heard from him.
He said after what happened,
he was miserable every minute
of every day.
That he wanted to just die
countless times.
Did my wife
know that as well?
Please tell me.
I heard my wife introduced him
to this place.
Does that mean
my wife knows everything?
You'll feel a prick.
You'll feel better
once you finish the bag.
You must be busy.
You didn't have to come all the way here.
Exactly. If you had gone to the hospital
yesterday when Gung-cheol came,
she wouldn't have had to come
all the way here.
If you feel worse later,
you have to go to the hospital
and get a full check-up.
Okay, Father?
Okay, I will.
It'll take about two hours, so take a nap.
It may not taste good, but eat up.
I'm sure it'll taste good.
I wouldn't have called
if I knew you'd come.
I only called to ask you
to calm Gung-cheol down
because he was so upset when he left.
I know how you feel.
I came because I wanted to see
the two of you, so don't feel bad.
My gosh. How could I not feel bad?
It's not like you bum around at home.
You fix people's illnesses.
You do a great thing.
But you skipped work to come here.
I came to eat your cooking
and get rejuvenated
so that I can work even harder.
I didn't make much.
Thanks for being so sweet.
Gung-cheol is good to you, right?
Yes, he's good to me.
You know,
he hates his dad so much,
but they say you can't escape your genes.
Sometimes, I feel like
he has the same temper.
I know he's very lacking,
but please be patient and understanding.
I don't know about anything else,
but he won't cause you grief
because of other women.
That is
the only reason I'm still with him.
Because I can trust him in that regard.
I don't have to be patient about anything.
He's the one being patient with me.
He'd better be patient.
He's living with a pretty, smart,
and successful woman.
It would be his loss if he wasn't patient.
Am I wrong?
You're so right, Mother.
Jeong-hae.
Thank you very much.
You married into a family like this
that has nothing,
gave us a grandson,
and are living well without any problems.
Thank you so much.
Mother.
I get so happy whenever I see you,
that I get silly.
Eat up. Go on.
Chew slowly and thoroughly.
I will.
My gosh. Where's my head?
I'm making scorched rice.
I'll be right back. Keep eating.
Okay?
Goodness.
(Theory of Business Administration)
(Here we go.)
Look this way. One, two, three.
-Congratulations.
-Thanks.
-See you later.
-Okay. See you later.
Okay.
My gosh. How could she not have
any family at all?
Is she an orphan?
No wonder there are no guests
on the bride's side.
Goodness gracious.
She was bragging all over town
about getting a doctor daughter-in-law.
Gosh. My goodness.
How could he marry an orphan?
Then again,
why would a doctor from a good family
marry a guy from a family
that's completely ruined?
I knew my brother looked depressed.
He must've been heartbroken
to let his perfectly good son
marry an orphan girl.
Leave. You don't deserve to be here.
Get out of here.
Come on, brother. Don't say that.
Why are you telling us to leave?
This is a place only for those
who want to celebrate their marriage.
All of you don't deserve to be here.
Get lost now!
-Come on.
-Come on, don't say that.
I was just concerned.
-My goodness!
-Will you let me go?
Please welcome the bride and groom.
Please give them a big hand.
-All right!
-Looking good!
Bride and groom,
please turn around and face the guests.
Everyone, just for today,
the groom's mother, her mother-in-law,
will be a mother for the bride.
Give them a big hand!
(Gyeong-ja)
(Jeong-hae,
let's go destroy their first love.)
(See you in front of the convenience store
by the apartment at 8 p.m.)
(In the Mood for Love)
-Hello.
-You're the busiest guy ever.
(In the Mood for Love)
I'll take another glass.
(Congratulations, Hae-suk.)
(In the Mood for Love)
Don't say that.
(Congratulations, Hae-suk.)
(Art Director Jung Jae-hun
of Phoenix drama club)
(I hope your business does well.)
-Keep ordering.
-Excuse me!
-Order some more food.
-What's this?
You're here.
You gave her a plant, a flower basket,
and even framed artwork? You're insane.
You're showing off with your money.
You two must have done some legwork.
I got everything with one call.
Man.
-Goodness.
-Hey, we'll take it. Leave it there.
Congratulations on your new business.
Gosh, thank you. It's so pretty.
Hey, you're wearing Ji-uk's clothes,
your golf player son.
It suits you well.
What? Your son is a golf player?
Yes.
I understand
how you miss your college days,
but this is way too pathetic.
Were you trying to be funny
when you put this on?
-Is this funny?
-Yes, it is.
I was trying to be funny.
Hey, you're here.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
What? Didn't you bring anything?
What? Did you really come empty-handed?
Ahn Gung-cheol, come on.
I had to come in a hurry,
so I couldn't prepare anything. Sorry.
Don't say that.
I'm just thankful that you came.
Hey, where did you go and with whom?
What were you up to?
What's with your face?
What about my face?
-Gyeong-ja!
-You're here.
I am.
You must have cried a lot.
I didn't cry that much.
Anyway, where's Jeong-hae?
I don't think she's coming.
We should get going.
Okay.
Wait!
I'm sorry. My work finished late.
Don't be sorry. Let's go.
Anyway, thank you for coming
despite your busy schedule, Chun-bok.
I'm not busy.
And thanks for making time, you three.
Don't thank us.
Of course, we should come for Hae-suk.
Isn't that so?
All right.
Let's drink to our eternal love.
Cheers.
Cheers!
-To eternal love.
-My gosh, you.
Jeong-hae.
Eun-sil.
Hello.
Well, as you can see,
there are no empty seats. I'm sorry.
What do you mean?
We can join our husbands.
This way, please. Take a seat.
All right. Dr. Nam?
My goodness!
Sweetie, you're here.
What are you doing?
Bring some chairs over here.
Okay, I'll do that.
-Over here.
-Come here. Sit down, Eun-sil.
Why is this bar so shabby?
Have you had dinner?
Do you need anything else?
Why would I need anything
at a place like this?
I'm just drinking because I have to.
Just let me know.
I have expensive liquor too.
I'll charge you much less
than what you charge at your place.
(In the Mood for Love)
As a token of gratitude
for everyone who came today
to celebrate the opening of my bar,
I'd like to sing a song for you.
(In the Mood for Love)
("Raindrop" playing)
♫ It's raining quietly ♫
♫ As if it's speaking of my memories ♫
♫ When it rains like this ♫
♫ I'm always reminded of that day ♫
♫ The one who pulled up my collar ♫
♫ And held an umbrella for me ♫
♫ I'm still unable to forget him today ♫
♫ As I walk down the rain alone ♫
(In the Mood for Love)
♫ Rise up, rise up, Phoenix ♫
Fly!
-Fly!
-Phoenix!
♫ It feels like you're coming to me ♫
♫ But when I look back ♫
Hyeong-u, three.
Hyeong-u.
♫ Just lonesome raindrops, raindrops ♫
Applause!
♫ It's raining quietly ♫
♫ As if it's comforting my memories ♫
♫ When it rains like this ♫
♫ I'm always reminded of him ♫
-All right!
-Great job!
-That was awesome!
-All right!
-Yes!
-That was great!
-All right!
-Encore!
-One more time!
Encore!
-Encore!
-Come on!
-She's good.
Encore!
-Encore!
-Sing one more song!
That was awesome!
Not bad.
She has an awesome voice.
I can see why she was the campus queen.
Don't you think so?
No?
You should stop. Let's go home.
Let me go.
-Be careful.
-Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Where are you going?
No, don't follow me. Don't.
Hae-suk.
I want to sing.
I'm going to sing.
Okay.
You sing something too.
Unbelievable. You.
Do you think I won't if you dare me?
I can't believe this.
Man, move aside.
Get down.
Hello, everyone.
I am
going to sing a song
for all of you today.
She's going to sing.
It's such a beautiful night.
("Pink Lipstick" playing)
♫ Who knows since when, but it's you ♫
♫ Since the first day I met you ♫
♫ I secretly put on pink lipstick ♫
♫ It was such a lovely color ♫
♫ Just like my trembling heart ♫
♫ You looked at me quietly ♫
♫ With such warm eyes ♫
♫ Tonight, I will put on ♫
♫ Pink lipstick just for you ♫
♫ I'll stamp my lip stain on your chest ♫
♫ Erasing my pink lipstick ♫
All right!
Jeong-hae!
-Are you okay?
-Let her go, you punk.
I'm her husband.
Hurry up and take her home, man.
Jeong-hae, stand up. Let's go home.
No, I don't want to.
I have to sing.
I'm not done singing yet.
Jeong-hae, what's with you?
Then we can go to a karaoke room.
Let's go to a karaoke room.
No, I'm not going.
Hey, why would I
go to a karaoke room with you?
You idiot.
-Go.
-Get up.
-No.
-Let's go home.
-Get up.
-Let me go. Let go.
Let go. Let go of me.
Let me go. No.
Let me go.
Let go of me.
-Let me go.
-You can put her down.
-Let go.
-I'll look after her tonight.
No. Let me go.
-Let go.
-Jeong-hae. Jeong-hae?
Get in.
Watch out.
Please take good care of Jeong-hae for me.
And call me right away
if something happens.
Don't worry,
and you can enjoy your time with them.
It's a special day.
-All right.
-Don't worry.
Hey.
Sir, to the intersection
at Hajung Station, please.
Sure.
Are we heading over to your bar?
I haven't seen Jeong-hae
get that drunk in a while.
When was that?
The third year of med school?
You're one smart guy.
I don't even remember.
True. Jeong-hae needs to vent
once in a while too.
She should drink,
especially on a day like today.
What do you mean?
Why don't we sit for a bit?
Hey, man. What do you mean,
"especially on a day like today"?
("Love Tonight" playing)
♫ Tonight, without anyone knowing ♫
♫ The two of us will share our love ♫
♫ I'm scared of the night
if you're not with me ♫
♫ Stay with me ♫
♫ If you and I dance to the music ♫
♫ I'll be happy ♫
♫ I'll promise to love you ♫
♫ So that you and I can be
together forever ♫
♫ One, two, three, four ♫
♫ Tonight, without anyone knowing ♫
♫ The two of us will share our love ♫
♫ The two of us will play with fire ♫
You need to sing too.
I can't sing.
Come on. You said earlier
that you wanted to sing.
Come on, sing something.
This mic is awesome.
No one will criticize you
for singing badly.
-Get up.
-That's right. Go.
-But...
-Get up. You know you're going to.
Come on. Get up.
Okay.
Let's go.
Sing a song!
"Nocturne."
("Nocturne" playing)
♫ The wind blows ♫
♫ To calm my burning heart ♫
♫ As the seasons change ♫
♫ All I do is fret ♫
♫ Late spring when the flower petals
fluttered in the wind ♫
♫ I could still smell my love's scent ♫
♫ Will he come now? ♫
♫ All I do is fret ♫
♫ A hopeless late spring evening ♫
♫ Like those flowers
that tragically fade ♫
♫ Will he come now? ♫
♫ All I do is fret ♫
Jeong-hae, are you all right?
Gyeong-ja.
At times like these...
I miss her...
so very much.
Whom do you miss so much?
Whom do you miss so much, Jeong-hae?
My mom.
I miss my mom so much.
I see.
Your mom...
is someone you'll always miss.
So cry all you want, Jeong-hae.
Don't cry.
Today is the anniversary
of Jeong-hae's mom's death.
What?
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Who told you?
Who told you, punk?
Jeong-hae.
There was a medical college gathering
last night.
(Your wife may have)
(many more secrets than you think,)
(and a past you may not know about.
That's all I'm saying.)
Did my wife know that as well?
Ask your wife.
I can't tell you anything.
Today is the anniversary
of Jeong-hae's mom's death.
(Ahn Gung-cheol)
(Ahn Gung-cheol and Nam Jeong-hae
Sunday, October 17, 2004, at 12 p.m.)
(In the Mood for Love)