Yi Shuo.
Be good.
Alright.
Come, come, come.
Get up quickly.
Fang Xian,
you must have learned quite a bit of your grandfather Fang Banxia's skills.
I'm sure you've picked up many of the essentials.
Be sure to behave yourself in the future.
Help your beloved wife Meiyuan take care of the business more often.
A loss of 300 taels in one month.
How much skill would it take to be of any help?
Isn't that Fang Xian who has arrived?
It will get better in the future.
Right, Father?
Exactly.
Fang Xian has joined the Kan family.
he'd better behave himself.
It's best not to do anything unnecessary.
What do you mean by unnecessary things?
This Fang Xian has joined our Kan family.
He is now a member of the Kan family.
Of course he should manage Tianxiang Pool.
Father-in-law,
you're mistaken about this.
I think Second Mother and Meiming
have a point.
The Kan family business is of great importance.
The matter of inheritance is
Meiyuan's own affair.
How can we rely on others' strength?
As the saying goes,
natural talents will always find their use.
How can we lose faith in Meiyuan
because of a small setback?
Does the Kan family really need
an heir who only relies on others?
If that's truly the case,
then my Fang family is indeed unworthy of this match.
Well said!
Truly worthy of being Fang Banxia's grandson.
My son-in-law is indeed a dragon among men.
I wasn't wrong about him.
That's not right, Father.
I've already said all this.
you shouldn't angrily say,
'Get out!'
'Do I not have a son-in-law as arrogant and domineering as you?'
Meiyuan,
hurry and bring your worthy son-in-law
to take a look at Tianxiang Pool.
Meiyuan, Meiyuan!
Yes,
mother.
My lord.
Cooperate, cooperate.
I'll take him there.
Look at this young couple.
How lovely.
Alright.
Well, let me see what this son-in-law of yours can do.
What skills do you have?
Look.
This is our Kan family's Tianxiang Pool.
Please, come in. Please, come in.
Please.
Please, please, please.
Our Kan family's Tianxiang Pool
is the largest bathing pool in the Southern Kingdom.
Our clientele ranges from royal relatives
to common people.
And next month,
we will be responsible for
the bathing of Marquis Yanqing before he enters the palace to see the emperor.
Let's go.
Let's move on to the next place.
Miss Kan really knows how to do business.
Impressive, impressive.
My dear,
it seems you're getting along well with the customers.
Of course.
You must remember,
they've paid money,
which shows their trust in our Kan family.
We must provide the best service in return.
I understand, my dear.
I will definitely
revitalize the bathing pool for you.
If you're capable, help me lose a lot of money,
completely ruin my qualification as an heir,
so I can rightfully divorce you.
It's killing two birds with one stone, and grandfather won't blame me.
I'm such a genius.
Darling,
where are you going?
What are you doing?
I'm going to inspect the bathing pools.
No,
darling,
that's the women's bathing pool.
We've switched bodies now.
It might not be appropriate for you to go in like this.
Going to the men's pool doesn't seem right either.
Greetings, son-in-law.
Don't look, don't look, don't look.
Welcome.
What are you doing?
Are you looking for trouble?
Don't go, you guys.
Come back!
Your father is just playing favorites.
Kan Meiyuan has lost so much.
You still hope that finding a live-in son-in-law can turn things around?
What are you doing?
Do you know you're getting in the way of me greeting the hunks?
do you understand?
Useless.
The tattoo was treated with a foul-smelling potion.
It was discovered before I even got in the water.
Is this the discerning eye of the Jinyi Merchant Guild's heir?
I must help my lady well.
But I can't use my identity as the Shadow Master.
Otherwise, it will implicate him.
What should I do?
What are you doing?
There are no customers, right?
We can't let the chefs stay idle anymore.
It seems that the dining area of Tianxiang Pool
needs to change its business model.
Father-in-law,
Father, husband.
I've given you a little demonstration of my skills.
Your cooking skills are really good, my dear.
If you like it,
I can cook for you for a lifetime.
Is this the charm of being a live-in son-in-law?
The young lady has changed completely.
The power of love, indeed.
Come here.
What are you all looking at?
I've got an idea.
I'll teach you to mind your own business.
Is that all you wanted to say?
Yes.
I plan to start from tomorrow.
Let Fang Xian take over the catering area.
It will surely go bankrupt in no time.
When that happens,
you'll take over the family business.
I'll wander the world from then on.
Perfect.
Take it.
What?
Miss,
Miss Meiyuan is intentionally trying to incur losses,
so that you can inherit the family business.
Intentionally incurring losses?
Where in the world would such a good thing happen?
Are you sure?
She and Fang Xian are still sleeping in separate rooms.
Fang Xian.
My dear wife,
you're back.
What are you doing here?
Go sleep in the side room.
My dear, there's no need to make a fuss.
it's just that the weather is getting colder,
I'm here to warm the bed for you.
A grown man
indulging in such trivial matters,
what a waste of manhood.
I indeed don't want to be some great man.
I just want to be a good husband to you.
I'm warning you, Fang Xian.
Don't use my body
to do those strange things anymore.
Otherwise, I'll divorce you.
So,
my dear, will you still kiss me?
Alright,
I'll go rest in the side room then.
That's right.
We only exchange kisses.
How could I possibly kiss him again?
Why haven't you left yet?
My dear,
You-
I beg your pardon.
Don't come any closer!
What are you doing?
Meiming,
This matter is inappropriate.
If word gets out,
People will surely say Grandpa is a dirty old man.
Never mind, never mind.
I'm going back.
Grandpa,
Since you're already here.
Since I'm already here,
You're right.
My dear,
I can do it myself.
Fang Xian,
You, you stop right now!
I can't, my dear.
I can't stop.
Will you stop or not?
I can't, I really can't stop.
Listen,
How much noise your sister and them are making.
Will you stop or not?
I can't.
You-
Grandpa!
My dear,
I really can't hold on anymore.
I'll be the death of you!
Miss,
are you and the young master for real?
Why would you ask that?
Didn't you two yesterday...
...make such a ruckus that the bed collapsed?
Ting Yu.
Let me tell you,
this matter absolutely cannot be spread around.
Otherwise, I'll...
Miss.
Isn't it a bit late to say that?
Meiyuan, Meiyuan.
Where's Fang Xian?
Father has a jar of top-grade Three Whip Wine here.
Miss.
Miss, wait for me.
My worthy son-in-law,
this Three Whip Wine is very nourishing.
Starring
Kan Meiyuan, Wang Luqing
Fang Xian, Liu Zhiyi
Cast
Ye Yi
Chen Ming
Cai Song
Hao Qian
Kan Xiang
Wang Churan
Song Kangwang Tianxin
Ting Yue, Lu Yang
Lin Wan, Wu Chunxiao
Li Chengjia
Gao Wenjun
Wang Xiaopin
Wang Dehua
Liu Qingquan
Master Kong, Cheng Wenbo
Fatty Qu Fengguo
Also Starring
He Zaiye, Huang Shuyu, Chen Hui, Yuan Zhiqiang, Liu Lingling, Li Mingming
Gu Yousheng, Huang Qinfen, Fang Laijian, Rong Changsheng, Sun Minggui, Chen Bin
Zheng Ziqian, Xu Chenyu, Lu Qiaoyi, Wang Yide, Bao Lishuang, Zeng Qizi
Han Yufei, Meng Yanchang, Li Yunbo, Bao Shengpeng, Feng Qibing, Li Xiaowei
Xu Xiaolu
Executive Producers: Li Ruoyi, Ma Mingjun
Jia Wenting
Xue Fantian
Li Jialiang
Adapted from the Tomato Novel 'Hoping Husband Becomes Dragon'
Author: Spicy Pork Chop Burger
Production Team
Jiao Jianwei
Hao Qian
Zhao Tiefei
Lu Jiaping
Starring: Xu Xiaolu
Zhou Zehan
Liu Lu
Ma Xiang
Action Director: Wu Yingcai
Photography Team
Li Qianjin
Li Shuai
Lighting Team
Pang Menggang
Chief Lighting Assistant: Wang Mengtao
Kang Xudong
Ma Yingbo
Liu Changxing
Cong Rong
Chen Ruizhu
Zhao Junqi
Lv Xinglin
Fang Junhua
Zhang Zhicheng
Styling Team
Styling Director: Wang Lei
Makeup Artists: Xiao Yang, Zhang Hongxia, Zhou Lihong
Production Crew
Wang Dahong, Yu Kai, Huang Zihang
Liu Xudong, Feng Xiaofei, Ying Linkang
Wang Peng
Post-production
Beijing Mingyang Alliance Film and Television Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Chen Shunting
Post-production Supervisor: Ma Mingjun
Visual Effects Supervisor: Rao Xianjun
Wang Pei
Xiong Fei
Wen Jiahao
Liu Encheng
Packaging Designer: Lv Lv
Sound
Han Jichao
Yan Jun
Dubbing Team
Dubbing Director: Tian Zhongxiang
Voice Actors
Shen Tu, Wang Guannan, Ma Jiaxi, Liu Jianhao, Dong Can
Yang Xi, Zhu Xiao, Yang Zijiang, Feng Zhuangzhuang, Bi Yingchao
Wang Jinyun, An Juntong, Wang Junzhe
Sound Post-production
Beijing Heyin Yuanzou Music Studio
Sound Designer: Wang Kexin
Theme Song
'Two Thousand Springs and Autumns'
Lyrics by Luan Fuhai
Composed by Luan Fuhai
Arranged by Chen Lin (len)
Guitar: Yang Chun
Theme Song Production Team
Beijing Gongyu Chuangyin Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Cheng Guang
Producer: Chen Lin (len)
Recording Studio
Haining Jinhuan Film Co., Ltd.
Douyin Vision Co., Ltd.
Xiamen Qiao Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Shenzhen Jincheng Yinsong Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing Mingyang Brothers Film and Television Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Production Company
Haining Jinhuan Film Co., Ltd.
Distribution Company
Xiamen Qiao Culture Media Co., Ltd.