[English subtitles are available]
[First Love]
[Episode 19]
Why are we eating western food?
It's expensive and cold,
and also too little to eat.
Since we haven't ordered yet,
there's a hot pot restaurant next door...
How about we go there?
Sit down.
Do you think this is just a regular meal?
This is a date.
I know it's a date, but we are still in a restaurant.
Our goal is to eat.
No.
You got it wrong.
You're obviously a beginner in love.
It doesn't matter what you eat on a date.
The point is the place.
Look around.
What a romantic atmosphere.
You can talk in whispers while eating.
It's so romantic.
Think about it. If you choose to eat hot pot,
you two will be separated by the pot,
and your sweat will mess up your makeup.
And also, garlic sauce is inevitable.
When you two get closer, all you can smell is garlic.
Okay, got it.
Western food is better.
When they arrive later,
remember to be more reserved.
Your relationship is different now.
You're Ren Chu's girlfriend,
not his bro anymore.
Do you hear me?
Here!
Sit down.
This is a western restaurant.
Keep your voice down.
Do as I do.
What do you want to eat?
I ate too much this morning.
I'm not hungry at all.
I'll order a vegetable salad.
You can order some snacks to your preference.
Then I'll order a pasta set.
If your food is not enough,
you can eat mine.
Then I'll order a vegetable salad too.
Not enough.
The main dish should be sirloin steak, medium well.
Appetizer, cream of mushroom soup.
And one more pasta.
This shrimp looks good.
I'll order one.
Dessert...
Tiramisu.
Please serve the dessert after dinner. And the same set for me as well.
Thank you.
Okay.
Please wait a minute.
Aren't there too many dishes?
I might not be able to eat all of them.
I know how much you can eat.
These are barely enough.
I don't eat much.
I've been so close to him before we got together.
I can't even pretend to be reserved now.
Fan, can you help me to fix my hair?
Thank you. Luckily, I have you to help me.
Enjoy your meal.
Wan, do you want to tie your hair?
It's troublesome if you don't tie it up.
I'm okay.
Thank you.
Much better now.
Right. Lu Wanwan,
do you want to go to the bathroom?
I guess you want to.
-Let's go. -I...
I deliberately put the hair ring
by Ren Chu's side.
Why did you do it yourself?
Why did you give it to him?
Does he know how to use it?
He might even hurt me.
Indeed, you did it well.
Is this a hairstyle competition?
This is a date, my girl!
Can't you give your boyfriend more chances
to show how much he loves you?
I see.
Your dishes.
Thank you.
Please enjoy.
I want some pasta.
I'll mix it for you.
Is that okay?
My pasta..
Now you can eat it.
Do you want to share it with me?
No, half is not enough for you.
Wanwan.
Why is he suddenly so affectionate?
Is he going to say something sweet to me?
I'm ready.
Is it enough?
Excuse me, one more pasta, please.
Okay.
Thank you.
[The Moon Represents My Heart]
This song is for my love, Qiao.
♫You ask how deep my love shall grow♫
♫And how much I care for you♫
Why don't you ask me which song I like?
I know what songs you like.
I've chosen them with my phone.
How do you know?
♫The man with a lasso pole you never let me down♫
Lu Wanwan,
you shouldn’t have done that!
[Good Man Song]
Who-Who chose this song?
I chose it dor Wanwan.
What do you think? You like it, right?
I have chosen all of the
similar songs as
"The man with a lasso pole".
So that you can sing as much as you want.
I don't think it's a good idea.
♫The big river flows to the east♫
♫Stars in the sky pay homage to Wain♫
♫Pay homage to Wain♫
♫Life-and-death friends, a bowl of wine♫
♫Say go then we go♫
♫You go, I go, we all go♫
♫We all go♫
♫In fire, in water, no turn around♫
[My Best Bro]
Qiao!
This was our favorite song when we were freshmen.
Come on.
I didn't.
Since you like it so much,
I'll sing with you.
No.
♫In your moments of glory♫
♫Let me sing you a song♫
♫My best bro♫
♫Tell me when you feel some pain in your heart♫
♫Let's face the future together♫
♫Even if there is a big river in the front♫
♫Bitter and hardness are no big deal♫
♫Our friendship♫
♫is higher than the sky and wider than the land♫
♫We will remember those years forever♫
-Lu Wanwan. -Friend...
Go to the bathroom with me.
What's wrong with you?
You're singing happily, aren't you?
I...
I like all those songs.
I couldn't help but sing.
You two should have sung some love songs.
What did you sing?
Best Bro?
Don't you think something's wrong?
Lu Wanwan,
think carefully about the failure
of your love confession in the past.
I know you're good at making friends.
But we can't make
the same mistake all the time, right?
I just got used to be myself
when I was around him.
But now,
I have already shown him my true personality,
so it's harder to beautify myself.
What should I do?
You can't sing anymore.
Play games. You two can interact.
It's boring to sing. Let's play a game.
Let's dice for the larger number.
The winner can ask a question,
and the loser must answer it.
I agree.
I-I have a question.
I want to ask Qiao.
Have you ever liked someone
before you met me?
Of course.
But the only one whom I like and want to get together with
is you.
Wanwan, what about you? You have to answer too.
I...
I know everything about her. It's okay.
Next round.
How could I cry so hard because of An Jiaxian
in front of Ren Chu?
I was so immature.
-Come on. -Come on.
I know everything about him.
Just ask a similar question as he did.
Gossip or something.
Do you have any gossip girlfriends?
Gossip girlfriends? So many.
Let me think.
Like Jing,
Qing and Pi...
So many?
How about I help you recall more names?
No, no, no!
All rumors.
You know everything about me.
We know each other too well.
Again.
Come on.
One, two, three.
I'll ask one more.
I want to know
what style is Qiao's nightclothes.
Nightclothes? In summer, I wear slip dresses.
And long sleeve shirts in other seasons.
No patterns. Pure color.
I'm just that simple.
I'm simple, too.
You're not.
In autumn, you wore a monkey pajamas.
I stepped on its tail once.
And in winter, you wore a sweater.
Your mom knitted it.
There are also some words on it.
I also have one of the same style.
What? You know too much!
You don't look like a couple who just begin the relationship.
You're like an old couple.
It seems that Fan Yi is right.
There's no secret.
No surprise.
No romance.
Does he also think that we are too close
and it doesn't look like we're dating?
Is it really because we've been friends for a long time?
You don't like KTV, do you?
You seemed uncomfortable just now.
I've been thinking about it.
Let's go to the library afterward.
I find we can always get along well
when we are in the library.
When we were friends, yes.
But we're dating "for the first time".
I've already set the date place with Qiao.
Guess where it is.
The aquarium.
Isn't it romantic?
Ren Chu, how was your date?
Fan Yi said he had chosen the aquarium.
Then I guess you should choose outer space.
What's the big deal about the aquarium?
Lu Wanwan and I have already been there before.
Why are you two so different?
I think he is a little depressed today.
You're obviously right.
He is depressed indeed.
Why?
There is a long way to go.
You won't understand.
Lu Wanwan was not in a good mood today.
Did I do anything wrong?
It seems that even if we are a couple now,
I still need to keep studying.
I should review the course about dating.
Okay, time for class.
I need to announce something before class.
The anniversary festival of our
neighbor, Qingyao University, is in a few days.
As a peer college,
we will give a performance on the festival.
Solo dance.
Anyone interested in it
can come and find me after class.
Xibai will come and see it...
Finally, I have a chance!
I will blow your mind with my charms
and make you love me again.
Teacher!
Teacher, I want to sign up for the solo dance!
-Me too! -Me too!
There's only one place.
Let's compete fairly. The best dancer will get the chance.
OK?
OK. Come on.
Let's get ready for class.
Stand still.
Get ready.
Five, six, breathe. Seven, eight.
One, two, go.
-Four, five, six, seven, eight. -They are all my rivals.
What are you doing?
I'm looking for some information.
Wait a second.
Are you cold?
I'm just curious about its texture.
I almost forgot.
Here.
Thank you, Senior. Let's continue studying.
Why is she still so polite to me?
♫I'll accompany you from rain to sunny♫
♫Let's enjoy the scenery along the way♫
♫Although it's quiet to stand side by side♫
♫I can hear you missing me♫
♫Your voice just got in my head♫
♫You stay by my side and make everything transparent♫
♫It's all crystal clear♫
♫Those dreams about the future♫
♫You must be there♫
♫I want to live in your heart forever♫
♫No once can replace me♫
♫I'm attracted by your heartbeat every second♫
♫The secret of this little universe♫
♫Let's explore the magical story of love♫
♫I'll take your territory♫
♫And put our names on it♫
♫There's no need to prove our connection♫
♫The story will continue♫
♫The philosophy of love you mentioned♫
♫I've been studying it over and over again♫
I came as soon as I got back from the aquarium.
I'm a loyal friend, huh?
By the way,
why did you suddenly ask me out for dinner?
Where's your boyfriend?
I also want to ask about that.
Where's my boyfriend?
What's wrong? Didn't you just get together?
Don't do anything stupid.
Many girls like Ren Chu.
As soon as you break up with him,
a bunch of girls will line up to take him over.
Don't curse me. I don't want to break up.
But,
even if we have already been together,
we do not seem like a couple at all.
We talk about nothing except study.
I've been polite to him on purpose today,
but he didn't show any unusual reactions.
When we were one-day couple,
he was quite a good boyfriend.
If he's already with you but still using the same tricks
he used when you were one-day couple,
he's not sincere at all.
In my opinion,
you two just have been friends for too long
and know each other too well.
Just as normal as your left hand touches your right hand.
You are in this stage in advance.
Is it "love comes in time"?
Isn't that what most couples do?
It's different.
Most people fall in love by appearances,
and then love will come in time.
It's mysterious and fresh.
But you two are different.
You know each other too well.
He has even visited your parents many times.
You've already past the stage when you were just getting together
and everything you did seemed fun.
I shouldn't have invited him to my home during the Spring Festival.
What should I do?
I want to date every day.
I didn't even go to the aquarium alone with him.
Don't worry. You can go to the aquarium later.
The most important thing now
is to make up for your lack of freshness in a relationship
by increasing the intimacy between you two
What should I do?
Eating together.
Already. It didn't work.
I mean, eating the food cooked by you.
It's totally different.
You can also show him your cooking skills which he doesn't know yet.
Although I'm not good at cooking,
I'll try my best.
I'll have a try.
Come to my home for dinner this weekend.
Qiao, although we haven't been apart for long,
I've thought about you 98 times.
When I miss you for 100 times,
I'll go to see you.
What should I do? This is the 100th time.
Can I come to see you now?
Is he crazy?
You have medicine to cure that?
You've gone too far.
[Come to my home for dinner this weekend.]
Is it for meeting your parents formally?
I'll prepare four presents.
I did some research.
Usually the gifts for such an occasion should be tobacco, liquor, candy, and tea.
If your parents like anything else,
you must tell me.
It will greatly increase the success rate of this meeting.
I want a sweet relationship too.
So there is also something that even a top student can't do.
Don't worry. Give him some time.
Let's go.
[Qingyao University Anniversary Festival]
That's all for today. Thank you.
Thank our principal for his statement.
Now let's start the first show.
Let's welcome the friendship performance from School of Dance.
Let's give her a round of applause.
I finally got this place after fighting out of the encirclement.
Xibai, you must fall in love with me again.
Where is he?
He didn't come?
I practiced so hard for this chance,
and my knees were bruised because of dancing.
I can't even lift my arms now!
It's school anniversary!
I can't believe he didn't even show up.
I finally found out why he doesn't love me.
He doesn't even love his alma mater.
Let alone his girlfriend!
Xinyu?
Why are you here?
Why didn't you show up at the school anniversary?
I was doing an experiment.
You performed today?
I don't care about you at all!
Let me tell you. Many people are pursuing me.
They can line up from Qingyao University
to our dance studio.
No, they can line up to France.
Meng Xibai, listen well.
We broke up.
Haven't we already...
broken up?
Hey.
Yes?
Are you here to shoot the video for the school anniversary?
You missed your girlfriend's show again, right?
Thank you.
[Lu's Fruit Store]
First, marinate the meat.
And prepare 500 grams of spring bamboo shoots.
Dark soy sauce, light soy sauce, white sugar,
chicken powder and salad oil...
A little.
How much is "a little"?
I should have learned more
when my dad was cooking.
Come in.
I've already told you my parents are not home.
Why are you dressed so formally?
It's safer to dress formally.
This is for you.
Chocolate?
A notebook.
Oh no, my dish!
Do you need help?
It's no big deal.
No big deal?
This is how we cook fried bamboo shoots.
The water boiled dry.
Actually, I'm making fried bamboo shoots.
It's a special recipe, yeah...
-I'm okay. -Don't move.
Luckily, it was not very serious.
Rinse the wound, and you won't feel any pain later.
Don't cry, Wanwan.
I didn't!
If it really hurts,
just pinch me. Don't hold yourself back.
You can cry if you want.
♫Life is like a farce♫
♫One second it's great weather, but the next it's pouring♫
♫There are too many wonders in life♫
♫Such as me falling in love with you. Love you♫
♫I disliked you, but why do I have butterflies in my stomach now?♫
♫I slowly get close to you despite myself♫
♫The inexplicable air and atmosphere here♫
♫Make me feel out of breath. The affection is heating up♫
♫How have I been taken captive by your love?♫
♫For no reason, without noticing, I just fell for you♫
It's not a big problem.
I thought since I could make desserts,
then cooking must be easy for me.
I didn't expect it to be a complete mess.
Don't cook anymore. Promise me.
Let me do it.
Okay.
It's okay.
♫For no reason, without noticing, I just fell for you♫
It finally looks like we are dating.
-Ren Chu is here! -Ren Chu, you're here.
You're so handsome in a suit.
Hello, Mr. and Mrs. Lu.
Hello.
Lu Wanwan, you can cook?
You've grown up.
You can even cook and treat your classmates.
You only invited Ren Chu?
Even though you just invited him,
how could you just cook one dish?
Didn't you say you wouldn't come back today?
It's your mom's fault.
She remembered the opening hour of the market wrong,
so we went there at the wrong time.
How could it be my fault?
You got it wrong too.
We're just in time.
We can taste the dish cooked by our daughter.
But we can't just eat one dish.
I'll cook more.
I'll help him.
You guessed it right.
Did you burn your hand just now?
Why are you so careless?
You...
You dress like you're going to a banquet.
Do you want to change your clothes?
Mom.
I usually dress like this at home.
It's comfortable.
How is it?
The meat is overcooked.
Too salty. Too much salt is bad for health.
I didn't even recognize these are bamboo shoots.
Next time, you can cut it vertically.
Are these bamboo shoots?
I thought it was houttuynia cordata.
Can houttuynia cordata be cooked like this?
These must be bamboo shoots.
The bamboo shoots are inedible after being cooked in this way.
It's not appropriate to
complain in front of the cook.
Ren Chu,
how have you been?
Do you have a girlfriend?
Everything is fine, Mrs. Lu.
I have already had a girlfriend.
What a pity.
I wanted to introduce a girl to you.
Is your girlfriend also a top student?
She's excellent.
What a pity.
One of my best friends has a daughter. She is excellent.
I met them this morning,
and we even talked about this.
That girl really suits you.
Suits for what?
Let me introduce myself.
I am Ren Chu's girlfriend.
When did you two get together?
I started to like her a long time ago.
We just confirmed our relationship recently.
Then... What do you like about her?
I like everything about her,
but I don't know exactly what I like about her.
Young man,
from now on,
you will live a hard life.
What do you mean?
I'm also a very kind and considerate girl.
Why will he live a hard life?
Not at all.
Yeah.
-Come on. Let's eat. -Come on.
Let's eat.
Let me do it. Your clothes will get dirty.
Ren Chu,
I have something to tell you.
Mr. Lu, just say it.
Indeed, Wanwan
has many defects.
But she is also our beloved daughter.
I hope you can treat her well.
Mr. Lu, please don't worry.
Wanwan is also my beloved girlfriend.
Okay.
Ren Chu is a good boy.
You need to get along well with him.
We get along pretty well.
The key is to be nice to her.
When you encounter some problems, you need to...
Communicate more.
Romantic relationship requires more than just liking each other.
Use "AA Payment" when dating.
Don't think it's natural
to spend his money all the time.
Don't worry, Mom.
I know that.
You've grown up.
I'll do some housework. You stay with Ren Chu.
Go chat with Wanwan.
You don't need to do this.
Go. Go.
I'll go then.
Go ahead.
Mrs. Lu.
Have a seat.
Do you want to watch TV?
Do you feel uncomfortable here?
What about we talk in my room?
Accident! It's an accident.
My room is very clean and tidy in usual.
Yeah, clean and tidy. You need help?
No.
Don't look at it.
Wait a moment.
Had I not worry that you might
feel uncomfortable in the living room,
I wouldn't have invited you to my room.
Wanwan, you're so considerate.
I need to thank you.
Alright.
Let me introduce.
This is the certificate I won by taking the first place of an eating competition
in my upper kindergarten.
This is the champion certificate of a tug of war
in my third grade in primary school.
And this.
This is the handmade dessert award I won
when I made the dessert for the first time.
There is also a trophy.
But I touched it every day and got the paint off,
so my mom put it away.
You're so great, Wanwan.
Although
compared to your merit student certificates,
mine are not that valuable,
they're still my highlights.
I want to share them with you.
[Lu's Fruit Store]
Are you sure you don't want to open it now?
Are we going to do the exercises now?
Take a look first.
It's not an exercise book.
[To Wanwan:]
Ich Liebe Dich.
I like you.
Jet'aime.
Taimi｀ngraleat.
I like you.
So you went to the library
to do this?
Fan Yi said we've been friends for too long,
so we're not romantic enough.
I just want to do something romantic for you.
I wonder if you like it.
I like it. I like the romance from a top student!
What did you write in Chinese?
[Don't call me "Senior". Call me "boyfriend". I'm super sweet.]
Why are you laughing?
I'm super sweet.
This is not your style.
Why did you say that?
Isn't it fresh?
Yes.
Do you want something sweet?
Was it sweet?
I thought of a sentence said by Edison.
You are thinking about Edison by my side?
Edison said that
genius is ninety-nine percent perspiration
plus one percent inspiration.
But dating
is one percent technique
plus ninety-nine percent sincerity.
Even if I learned the technique a little late,
it didn't affect
my sincere feelings for you.
These are the sweetest words
I've ever heard.