[English subtitles are available]
[First Love]
[Episode 22]
I'll call it a day.
Fully recovered.
How about you?
♫I'll accompany you from rain to sunny♫
Let's call it a day together.
♫Let's enjoy the scenery along the way♫
♫Although it's quiet to stand side by side♫
♫I can hear you missing me♫
♫Your voice just got in my head♫
[Lu Wanwan]
♫You stay by my side and make everything transparent♫
The step rankings.
I walked all day in the hospital.
♫It's all crystal clear♫
I've hit the record again!
♫Those dreams about the future♫
♫You must be there♫
Congratulations, Dr. Lu.
You're again on the top of my list.
♫I want to live in your heart forever♫
Did you go to the park again?
♫No once can replace me♫
♫I'm attracted by your heartbeat every second♫
♫The secret of this little universe♫
♫Let's explore the magical story of love♫
Yes, I come here every day,
relaxing myself and missing you passingly.
♫I'll take your territory♫
♫And put our names on it♫
♫There's no need to prove our connection♫
♫The story will continue♫
♫The philosophy of love you mentioned♫
♫I've been studying it over and over again♫
I'll go for a run,
planning to reach 25,897 steps,
so that I can be next to you on my list.
Then you have to work hard.
It's hard to chase me,
because I will keep walking.
I will catch up with you.
♫You stay by my side and make everything transparent♫
♫It's all crystal clear♫
♫Those dreams about the future♫
♫You must be there♫
♫I want to live in your heart forever♫
♫No once can replace me♫
♫I'm attracted by your heartbeat every second♫
♫The secret of this little universe♫
♫Let's explore the magical story of love♫
♫I'll take your territory♫
♫And put our names on it♫
♫There's no need to prove our connection♫
♫The story will continue♫
♫The philosophy of love you mentioned♫
♫I've been studying it over and over again♫
♫I want to live in your heart forever♫
♫No once can replace me♫
♫I'm attracted by your heartbeat every second♫
I learned something about retouching in a short time.
♫The secret of this little universe♫
Please check my masterpiece.
♫Let's explore the magical story of love♫
♫I'll take your territory♫
It's perfect. Worth to be shared in WeChat Moments.
♫And put our names on it♫
♫There's no need to prove our connection♫
♫The story will continue♫
Copied in sync.
♫The philosophy of love you mentioned♫
Today's love online.
♫I've been studying it over and over again♫
I'm just kidding.
Don't take it seriously.
I'm not a brave person by nature.
I have no ambition or greed.
My only wish
[Ren Chu]
is to let my childhood sweetheart Yang Xiaoyang...
The internet in our dorm is not so good.
It's loading.
It's okay.
I'll wait for you at 39:25.
No hurry.
But I was thinking about
[Ren Chu]
the universe may want to be noticed...
and what I had to is to notice it
[Wanwan]
as much as I could.
I felt that I owed a debt to the universe
that only my attention could repay.
And also, I owe a debt to everybody who didn't get to be a person anymore
and everyone who hadn't gotten to be a person yet.
[Wanwan]
Wanwan,
I'm on page 295.
We can meet
when I finish reading it.
Good night, Wanwan.
[Orthopaedic intern schedule April 2021]
Page 300 for the novel tonight.
There are 49 pages left before we can finally meet.
I'll read faster
and try my best to finish the research.
So I come back early on May 1st.
Okay, see you then.
Senior,
I have something to discuss with you.
What's wrong with the schedule?
Why is Lu Wanwan's schedule so full?
Sorry, Teacher.
I asked her to change the schedule for me.
I have something to do during the Labor Day holiday,
so I want to finish my work in advance.
Can you handle it?
You'll be very tired.
I can do it.
Here.
[Nurse Station]
Had I known it was so tiring,
I would have had two more bowls of rice for lunch.
[Wanwan, are you busy today?]
[I had fish head with chopped pepper for lunch today. But the fish head was deeply covered in chopped peppers.]
[Someone asked me for my number just now. I've refused her. Don't worry. I'm all yours.]
[The battery might run out soon, 2% battery capacity left.]
[Sorry I've been so busy today that I didn't have time to check my messages.]
Lu Wanwan, come here.
A patient from orthopedics is looking for you.
Orthopedics?
I almost forgot that Wang was to be discharged today.
I haven't given him the medical record yet.
[I had fish head with chopped pepper for lunch today. But the fish head was deeply covered in chopped peppers.]
[She hasn't replied my message since this morning.]
Let's go.
Look who is texting his girlfriend again.
Why do you have so many things to talk about every day?
Do you want to share it with me and let me learn?
You're not accurate.
Not every day.
You're a perfect boyfriend anyway.
He went out a few days ago
and bought a lot of gifts for Lu Wanwan.
She must be so excited.
The gifts will be delivered today.
I haven't told her yet.
I plan to tell her later.
Please go back first.
I'm going to work overtime
and finish my work before the holiday.
So he's going to deliver himself
to his girlfriend too.
You talk too much. Just go.
Don't disturb him.
-Let's go. -Let's go.
Bye.
Although you're discharged,
you still need to be careful.
Don't do strenuous exercise.
Don't eat spicy food.
Pay attention to your diet.
And
go to bed early and get some rest.
What's wrong? You're still unhappy after being discharged?
My girl in the game has someone else.
She went to play games
after saying good night to me the day before yesterday.
And she invited another friend to play the game.
She has another jungle now.
We haven't talked to each other
for 24 hours.
She didn't reply to my messages.
She hasn't contacted me for 24 hours!
Isn't it a signal to break up with me?
You think too much.
What's the big deal about not keeping in touch for 24 hours?
Maybe she's busy.
You don't know anything.
If you really like someone,
how can you not reply to the other one for such a long time?
Didn't you see my post on Wechat Moments?
So many people gave a Like to my post.
What did you post?
Love is like sneezing.
I can't hide it at all.
If two people in a relationship lose contact for over 24 hours,
that means they don't love each other enough.
Show me your medical record.
Hurry up.
What?
Didn't you see it yet?
I just want to check
if you were given the wrong medicine.
Otherwise why do you look so jealous?
[Building 1-6 Student Apartment]
Why isn't Wanwan back yet?
The door of the dorm is about to be closed.
That's weird. Her phone is off.
Did something terrible happen?
What took you so long?
Working overtime is tiring.
My phone was out of power.
I didn't reply to Ren Chu.
He must be worried.
You started to talk about your boyfriend as soon as you came back.
Our worries are not worth it.
Didn't you think that we'd be worried?
I'm back safely.
Go wash up and
go to bed early.
Wanwan.
Wanwan...
Wash up before you sleep.
No.
I have to text Ren Chu.
[Your package has arrived and was put into the cabinet of Qingyao University. Sign for it with the code: 021968]
[Wanwan]
Wanwan, I bought you...
What's wrong with her?
The subscriber you dialed is powered off.
Please redial later.
Her phone is off.
Did I send her too many messages today?
I shouldn't have texted her
when she was working.
She didn't post on Moments or
give Likes to others either.
Maybe she didn't ignore me on purpose.
Love is like sneezing.
I can't hide it at all.
If two people in a relationship lose contact for over 24 hours,
that means they don't love each other enough.
Is this a new love law?
Twenty-four hours...
We contacted each other at
10:30 a.m.
It has been
13 hours and 40 minutes.
Fan Yi,
can you do me a favor?
Wanwan.
You're still in bed?
I'm back from my morning reading.
Aren't you going to the hospital today?
Yes.
Then get up.
The alarm didn't ring.
You didn't reply to Ren Chu last night.
He was so worried
and asked Fan Yi to call me.
Don't forget to reply to him today.
Oh, no. It's 7:30.
Dr Zhang needs to talk about the medical record.
Slow down. Don't fall down.
I'm going to be late.
Let's talk when we get back.
[Qiandao Delta Hospital]
[Wanwan]
Hello, Ren Chu.
I'm sorry.
My phone was off yesterday.
I didn't have time to contact you.
But I have to go to the hospital now.
I'll call you later.
Wait for me.
[Fan Yi]
Fan Yi.
Are you free today?
Okay, that's all for today.
Get back to work.
-Okay. -Okay.
You're late.
Sorry.
I was too sleepy yesterday and
I forgot to turn on the alarm.
Don't think that you can work so hard just because you're young.
Health is the foundation of the revolution.
If you really think you can't handle it,
just let me know and help you change your shift.
Don't act tough.
No need.
I can do this.
Sorry.
Wear this white coat right first.
This is the image of a doctor.
Doctor.
Hello, doctor.
May I ask
if my son's bone fracture
will affect him in the future?
He wants to be an athlete.
Are you the family of the patient in bed three?
Yes, the patient in bed three.
He went to take the rehabilitation treatment.
My son has been playing ping-pong since he was young.
He wants to join the national team in the future.
Look...
The fracture is quite serious this time.
I'm really worried.
Let me take a look.
He has a left ulna radial fracture
and a fracture of the right medial epicondyle.
If there are not any problems
in surgery and rehabilitation,
then...
What's wrong, doctor?
Is there a problem?
I'm not a doctor.
I'm just an intern here.
I'm not sure about the patient's condition.
How about this?
I'll ask the doctor for you.
How can you not know?
You walk around in the ward every day.
And you're wearing a white coat,
which means you are a doctor.
Even if you're not my son's attending,
you can help me check the patient's medical record.
What does it say?
Sorry.
I'm late today.
I missed some information the doctor said about the medical record.
Aren't you shirking the responsibility?
Did the surgery fail
and the attending doesn't allow you to tell?
I just want to know
my son's current condition
right now.
Will it affect his future?
Whether he can play ping-pong in the future or not?
Your hospital needs to be responsible.
What is the current situation then?
Hello.
Are you the mother of the patient in bed 3?
Yes.
Your son's surgery went well.
He has a left ulna radial fracture
and a fracture of the right medial epicondyle.
As long as
the bones are back in place
and appear good bony union,
then it won't affect
his joint function.
And it won't affect
his potential as a ping-pong player.
You can rest assured.
Okay, I'm relieved.
Thank you, doctor.
You're welcome.
Do you know what your problem is?
My professional knowledge is not solid.
And I couldn't answer the patient's question.
You're only a sophomore.
It's normal that you can't answer.
The problem is your attitude.
This morning,
I've talked in detail
about the case of the patient in bed 3.
If you had arrived on time,
you wouldn't have been so passive
in the ward just now.
In other words,
even if you missed it,
you should've admitted that you weren't so clear about the patient's condition
and come to me immediately
instead of being confused and uncertain.
The patients and their families are very sensitive.
They trust the white coat you're wearing,'
not you.
Once you give
a vague and wrong answer,
the patients' trust in doctors
will be damaged greatly.
The enthusiasm of medical students towards this major
will be greatly damaged as well.
You must always remember
to be careful about what you say and do.
I'm sorry, Teacher.
I'll remember that.
I won't make the same mistake again.
You don't look very well lately.
Are you so exhausted
that you can't handle the work?
I can do it.
How many times have you said that?
It's not embarrassing
to admit that you can't.
You've been working so hard
to take a leave on May 1st.
If you're so exhausted
and make any mistake,
then that will be a matter of life and death.
Have you thought about the consequences?
Go back and rest today.
You can work after the holiday.
You may leave now.
Thank you, Teacher.
You're only a sophomore.
It's normal that you can't answer.
The problem is your attitude.
This morning,
I've talked in detail
about the case of the patient in bed 3.
If you had arrived on time,
you wouldn't have been so passive
in the ward just now.
Sorry, Teacher.
I'll remember that.
I won't make the same mistake again.
If you're so exhausted
and make any mistake,
that will be a matter of life and death.
[Ren Chu]
You're off work?
You seem busy lately.
I'm busy at the hospital today.
I didn't have time to reply.
I'm sorry. Don't be angry.
I'm not angry.
Are you tired?
Did anything happen?
I'm fine.
Lu Wanwan.
If you're unhappy because of something,
just tell me.
I'm really fine.
I'm having a burger in a small park right now.
Today's burger is really good.
And there are fries of a new flavor.
They're delicious too.
We'll go to the dinner together when you come back.
What are you doing?
Just sit there.
Wait for me.
Wait for me?
Is Ren Chu back?
He's so busy.
I haven't washed my hair yet.
Turn around.
♫I disliked you, but why do I have butterflies in my stomach now?♫
♫I slowly get close to you despite myself♫
♫The inexplicable air and atmosphere here. Make me feel out of breath♫
♫The affection is heating up♫
♫How have I been taken captive by your love?♫
Follow the light.
♫For no reason, without noticing, I just fell for you♫
♫Life is like a farce♫
♫One second it's great weather, but the next it's pouring♫
♫There are too many wonders in life♫
♫Such as me falling in love with you♫
♫I disliked you, but why do I have butterflies in my stomach now?♫
♫I slowly get close to you despite myself♫
♫The inexplicable air and atmosphere here♫
A gift for you.
♫Make me feel out of breath. The affection is heating up♫
♫How have I been taken captive by your love?♫
You always need to wash your hands at the hospital.
So I prepared hand cream for you.
♫For no reason, without noticing, I just fell for you♫
I don't know what brand you like.
So I bought one of each brand.
They don't have any fragrances.
Keep following the light.
Your gift is under the seventh tree.
You've been in the hospital
either standing or walking around.
♫Life is like a farce♫
Put the shoes on.
Don't mind their appearance.
I want you to be comfortable.
♫One second it's great weather, but the next it's pouring♫
♫There are too many wonders in life♫
I love your gifts very much.
♫Such as me falling in love with you♫
Anything else?
Take 20 steps to the left.
One, two, three, four, five.
twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen,
seventeen, eighteen, nineteen,
Twenty.
Don't always eat fast food.
It's still hot. Are you really nearby?
Ren Chu, I saw you.
You really...
It's us.
Why are you here?
It's your fault.
Ren Chu bought you gifts.
But he couldn't find a chance to tell you.
And he's worried about you.
So he asked us
to give you a surprise
to make you happy.
What do you think?
Do you like it?
I didn't even know he had bought gifts.
Of course you don't know.
You are so busy.
It's hard for him to contact you,
let alone ask you to sign for the package.
I did all the hard work.
Really.
I never had such a grand party for my birthday.
Stop asking for credit.
We just did a little favor for Ren Chu.
It was all arranged by him.
This is his love for Wanwan.
Don't take credit for it.
Did he ask you to decorate it?
How did he know?
Although he's not here,
he knows everything about your life.
He said you would come here
after work every day.
So he asked us to decorate in advance.
Yes.
These light bulbs are very troublesome.
I've never been so romantic in a relationship.
I feel sorry for my Qiao.
You make it up for me later.
Actually, the decoration work is not that hard.
The most difficult thing is making soy milk.
I saw Ren Chu making soy milk
just like doing an experiment.
Things like the proportion of water and beans
and the proportion of sugar... He really worked so hard on it.
I thought I could do that too.
But when I helped Ren Chu
make soy milk this time,
it was a lot more difficult than I thought.
I failed in the end.
So I bought you a lunch box.
Stop it.
So the soy milk I've been drinking
was made by himself all along.
Wanwan.
Can you pretend you don't know?
I don't want to be accused of betraying my buddy.
Thank you.
So many hand creams.
You must have gone to many places.
No.
I went around the school.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I hope my girlfriend will like it.
How did you think of the shoes for old people?
They're really comfortable.
I tried them in person.
And I bought a pair for myself.
I feel comfortable after wearing them all day.
Luckily, I have you.
I didn't know you did all of this.
I told you
I would protect you like the Saturn Ring,
even if you're not by my side,
Now can you tell me
what happened recently?
I was late to the hospital today.
And the doctor happened to give a lecture about a patient's case
in the morning.
But I missed it.
Then the patient's family came to ask me.
I didn't know anything
and got scolded.
It's not your fault.
The patient's family is so sensitive.
But I was late.
Otherwise,
I could've
given her a proper answer.
Why were you late?
Was it because you were too exhausted?
Or you've been so tired because you wanted to make time to meet with me?
You don't have anything to do with this.
I wanted to change my shift schedule.
I overestimated my ability
and did something beyond my ability.
So I messed it up.
Wanwan,
if you're upset because of anything,
you have to tell me.
I'll share your burden.
We can be honest with each other.
You don't have to make a sacrifice
for me.
I can do that for you.
I don't want you to worry.
We are far away.
Even if you know,
you can't help me.
And I'll make you worried for nothing.
Okay, I'll tell you everything in the future.
Our long-distance relationship will end soon.
I'll keep you company as much as I can.
I won't lose contact with you
for more than 24 hours.
Because
there is a saying that
if a couple loses contact with each other for more than 24 hours,
that means they don't love each other anymore.
Did you read Wang Yuyang's post?
Don't believe him.
I know it's not trustworthy,
but I'm still a little scared.
I can't bear to lose you.
So cheesy.
Do you miss me?
I miss you too.
Go back to school and rest early.
See you on May 1st.
[Qiandao Delta Hospital]
[Emergency]
Hurry up.
Come on.
Liu, your shoe!
Doesn't matter. The patient is more important.
[Outpatient/Inpatient]
Ren Chu.
I have something to discuss with you.
Come in.
[Please close the door.]
I told you to go home and rest.
Why are you here again?
Teacher.
I have something to discuss with you.
Go ahead.
I've thought about it.
I want to be on duty during the holiday.
Let's follow the previous schedule.
Didn't you say you have something to do during the holiday?
You even switched the shift.
I've solved it.
You're right.
We should communicate more
and stop hiding things from each other.
And we shouldn't always make sacrifices for each other or cater to each other's needs.
I want to ask you.
We'll be together for a long time, right?
Of course.
I want to be with you forever.
Then work and love are my norm.
The work in the hospital is always busy.
You're doing scientific research too.
I hope we can
get used to this busy state,
instead of just
catering to each other's needs.
I don't want any of us
to have such a complicated situation like I had today.
So,
you mean
we might not
see each other during this holiday?
Although
I miss you too,
and I'm sorry we can't see each other this time,
I hope you can understand. Alright?
It's a pity
not to meet you this time.
But I support your idea.
We are together
to make each other happier
instead of pressuring each other.
I'll work here during the holiday.
Arrange your time well.
Don't work too hard.
Don't feel pressured.
Wanwan.
You sound
different today.
How?
It just felt like you've grown up.
Wanwan.
I don't want you to grow up so soon.
Because you still have me.
I can always protect you.
I can also protect you.
If you're having a hard time,
you must tell me.
I can share your burden.
Even if I can't come to you right away,
I can comfort you
and accompany you.
I know
you're a grown-up now.
But I don't want you to feel lonely.
Promise.
[Ren Chu]
[Promise.]
Why do you bring me here?
This is totally not your style.
Are you doing some medical research?
Like... How would pink color affect food?
No.
I saw you give a Like to this coffee shop
on Weibo.
I think you like this place.
Our previous dates were
based on my preferences.
We went to the teahouse, went fishing, and took a walk in the park.
I never thought about your feelings
or even asked about your preferences.
I think I was being too selfish.
Sorry.
Xibai.
Are you alright?
Why do you suddenly care about my feelings?
I wrote a paper,
reviewing every detail of our relationship
since we met each other.
I reached some conclusions.
Do you want to read it?
I'll email you.
Is there a picture of me in the paper?
Well...
No.
I only used words to describe.
I won't read it then.
Tell me about it.
I'll give you some suggestions
so that you can pursue me in an easier way.
The most important conclusion is
I shouldn't ask Wang Xinyu to do things
according to my own will.
Let's take our previous date as an example.
Obviously, I ignored that
you needed time to dress up for our date.
And that affects your study indirectly.
I'm responsible for that.
If I can get her back,
I want to sincerely apologize
and finish this dating schedule with her.
That depends on your performance.
More people come to the hospital
when the holiday gets closer.
Our hospital is not a famous spot.
[Ren Chu]
Hello.
Let me tell you.
There are many patients in the hospital today.
I'm exhausted.
How about you?
Turn around.
What?
Did you ask Fan Yi
to give me a surprise again?
Don't always bother him.
I'm in a good mood today.
No need to make me happy.
I thought you'd grown up.
I didn't expect you to still act like a kid.
I got no one here.
Of course I have to be an adult.
Now that you're back,
I can be like a kid again.
What is this called then?
Adorn me with borrowed plumes.
Then you'll be punished.
What punishment?
Put me down!
Help!
Why did you come back suddenly?
Don't you have to do your experiment during the holiday?
Actually, I have already finished it.
But I didn't say that because I didn't want you to feel stressed.
A straight A student has learned to lie.
Are you hungry?
I'll take you to eat.
By the way,
I brought you soy milk.
Drink it first.
Where did you buy this soy milk?
Dining hall, of course.
Isn't it closed during the holiday?
They're still selling soy milk.
Does the manager still plan to train his employees?
You're not his only apprentice, are you?
I want to learn it too. I'm a smart fast learner.
You know?
Fan Yi...
Don't blame Fan Yi.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for making soy milk for me.
Thank you for remembering my preferences.
Thank you for everything.
I should thank you too.
Thank you for showing up in my life.
We'll go on a trip
after you finish your internship.
We can finally spend some time together.
The last piece of chocolate.