[English subtitles are available]
[First Love]
[Episode 20]
Oh no.
Qiao
must see me at the first moment.
Our timing is perfect.
If you aren't too slow,
we will see them the minute their class is over.
Who is slow?
I used to be an athlete, too.
Used to? In what life?
Elementary school or junior high?
No.
When can you fix
your bug of cruel tongue-lashings?
Are you such a fickle friend?
The suit you wore at her house last time
was bought with me.
If you hadn't dressed up so nicely that time,
could you and Lu Wanwan
get on the right track so fast?
We didn't get on the right track by a suit.
Also, being mean is not a bug.
It's a specific program.
You should read more.
No.
Ren Chu, wait for me.
Wanwan.
Why are you here?
Boyfriend Rule No. 1: waiting for his girlfriend after class.
Give it to me.
What?
Boyfriend Rule No. 2:
carrying the backpack for her.
-It's heavy. -That's enough already.
The public display of affection is just too much.
There's someone right here.
Just let him take it.
Do you forget what I said?
-Ren Chu. -Are you hungry?
What do you want to eat?
I've called you so many time,
but why didn't you wait for me?
You're sweating.
Where did you go? Were you in a running race?
I came to pick you up from class. Let's have lunch together.
Do you see?
We are the first ones to be joined together.
Let's go.
What do you want to eat?
Boyfriend Rule No. 3:
treating your girlfriend...
Anything is fine.
Boyfriend Rule No. 3:
obeying your girlfriend.
It's my treat today.
Just use my card freely.
Is your pre-internship in the hospital tiring?
It's okay. I went home for dinner last week.
I recharged myself.
I've been busy for another week.
It's finally my day off tomorrow.
-Let's go on a date tomorrow. -Let's go on a date tomorrow.
Since we were together,
we haven't had a proper date yet.
Are you nervous?
This is our first formal date.
I'm not nervous.
As people say, you've at least seen a pig,
even if you've never tasted pork.
I'll arrange the date tomorrow.
Okay.
You're back so soon.
Doesn't it feel good to have lunch together?
Aren't you back too?
Fan Yi's mentor
recommended him an internship.
He has an interview this afternoon,
so he went there in a hurry.
Why are you in such a hurry?
What happened?
I came back to look for some strategy.
Strategy?
About what?
Are you and Ren Chu going to...
It's not what you think.
What was I thinking? I didn't say anything.
You have images in your mind, don't you?
We're going on a date.
A normal and serious date.
Why do you need a strategy if you're just going on a normal date?
I'm inexperienced.
I'm finally officially in a relationship.
But I don't even know what to do on a date.
The last meal was so bad.
This time I boasted of myself again in front of Ren Chu.
So I have to come back and check the strategy.
Let me help you.
[Five Dating Tips to Avoid Embarrassment and Take the Initiative!]
♫I gently take a bite♫
♫of the love you expressed to me♫
♫Still savoring the tenderness from you♫
Luckily I was agile,
or my shoes would be dirty.
The hairstyle is not messy.
The internship is introduced by my mentor,
so I can't embarrass him.
Why did you bring Ren Lu?
It was not around at the professing ceremony.
So I must take it with me on our first date.
Otherwise, it will blame me when it grows up.
A family must stay together.
Not one should be left out.
Family?
Are you so eager
to sign and seal it with me?
I'm not eager.
Okay.
Where are we going now?
Normally on the first date
people go to the cinema.
Let's go to the one we've been to last time.
We have common memories there.
Are we watching The Martian again to learn English?
We don't have to watch a foreign movie.
I'm in charge this time.
Just look forward to it.
If you want to watch a movie with a straight-A student,
the movie must be classy.
It can't be too shallow.
There should be an atmosphere and a rhythm
of being in love.
It's better to be a literary romance movie,
which can resonate with the lovers.
But nowadays the literary romance movies
are all heartrending.
That's exactly why they're suitable.
You have to choose the kind
which makes you feel sad and want to cry.
That way, when the movie is over,
the couple would hold each other's hand
and sigh,
"it's so good that you're here with me."
So sweet.
Don't move. It itches.
Luckily, I didn't drool.
How did I fall asleep?
This movie is highly-rated online.
The dating rhythm is ruined by my dreaming.
It doesn't matter if the rhythm is not good at this step.
I'll keep up the good work.
Being a boss means that if you like fish,
I'll give you all the fish ponds in the world.
If you like to do exercises,
I will...
[Real Game Experience Hall]
Room escape!
All the People with a high IQ like to play this.
You can use your brain as much as you want,
because I chose the hardest one.
You like it very much, don't you?
I can't wait.
I knew you would like it.
After you go in,
just go ahead. I've done my homework.
If there's any problem you can't solve,
just ask me.
As long as you turn around,
I'll be there.
Okay.
You haven't played room escape before, have you?
Let me tell you the rules of the game.
We are now trapped in this room.
We need the key to get out.
And the key...
the key must be hidden in that password box.
And a password box
needs a password.
And the password?
This painting looks a little strange.
The password must be hidden...
It's open. Let's go out.
There are 4,274 passwords
if you use 4 numbers from 0 to 9.
I stuck the tape onto the code lid and lifted it off.
And I found the most fingerprints on 1, 9, 6, and 0.
It means the password is formed by these four numbers.
So the range is narrowed to 24 combinations.
I've only tried five times and it was opened.
We are lucky.
But this
isn't the right way to get the password.
Let's go.
This round looks quite difficult.
It should take a long time.
It's open.
How did you do it?
It's actually very simple.
When I came in,
I saw the reflection angle of these rays of light.
And then...
No need to explain.
You have offended this room.
I checked before we came.
This is the most difficult room escape
in Qiandao City.
It's a big loss for me.
I spent hundreds of Yuan,
but we walked out of it in ten minutes.
Wanwan,
I see that you frown and don't want to answer.
Actually you don't like room escape, right?
If you don't,
why did you reserve it as our dating place?
I thought you liked it.
Before, you
did a lot for me.
I also want to spoil you.
Spoil me?
Aren't all the good girlfriends like this?
Take you to the place you want to go
and do whatever you want to do.
Then I'll be there,
watching and smiling.
But it's so hard.
Actually,
I've already felt your love.
As long as you are happy,
you're spoiling me.
Would you like to love me again?
Of course.
What do you want to do?
Do something you like.
Why did our school suddenly
arrange a checkup for the dance department?
It has never happened before.
What happened today?
Did our department make a fortune?
Our department makes a fortune?
It's faster to dream.
I heard that the intern doctors from the city hospital
come here for gratuitous treatment.
Many students got injured
during training.
So they said they could do a checkup
for us in passing.
It's gratuitous treatment.
I knew it.
If our school has that kind of funds,
they might as well change the floor.
Look how cracked it is!
I wonder who
this kind angel is?
Attention, everyone.
Let me introduce them to you.
These two are doctors from the city hospital.
They're here to give you a checkup.
Please cooperate.
Line up in order.
Let's start from this end.
Could it be more obvious?
Do you regret it now?
Now you must how popular I am.
Check your vision first.
Up.
Right.
You need to protect your eyes.
Last time you said
your admirers lined up from here to France.
The distance of superior arc between Paris and Beijing
is 14,000 km.
It's not realistic.
But no matter what,
don't be fooled.
You have to choose an upright person,
like me.
Check your hearing.
Can you hear it with this frequency?
Xibai’s voice
is still so low and attractive.
Can't you hear it?
Let me have a check.
I can hear it.
I thought you couldn't hear it.
Next.
Too much sweet words
will impair your hearing.
So you still have to find someone honest and reliable.
What on earth are you trying to say?
I watched the video of your performance.
You danced well.
It's like the first time I saw you dance.
Did you come to the gratuitous treatment to see me?
You didn't reply my email.
I wanted to invite you to go fishing.
I don't like fishing.
I can't sit still at all.
I went there because I liked you.
Also, I hate emails the most.
We modern people use phones to contact each other.
Thank you, Dr. Meng. I'm going to practice dancing.
It's easy for a girl to pursue a guy.
But it's much more difficult for a guy to pursue a girl.
The old saying is so true.
Next.
Come.
Here.
Sir, are you looking for a phone?
Yes.
What brand do you want?
I can introduce it for you.
I don't have preferences.
Do you have any demands?
I want one that can make calls.
Do you like playing games
or taking photos?
The newly-arrived phones all have
a camera of 80 million pixels.
There's a micro-cloud platform, too.
Don't bother.
WeChat is a must.
Don't worry. All of these can send WeChat messages.
You want to do this?
I've always wanted to make wooden sculptures.
It seems to be quite similar to DIY desserts.
I was embarrassed to come before.
Why?
Look at them.
They're all lovers.
It would be awkward
to be among them by myself.
So I set a goal.
When I'm in a relationship, I'll bring my boyfriend here
to make handmade works
and give him as a souvenir.
Am I too old-fashioned?
Not at all.
Very good.
I'll be the first one to come with you.
Of course,
I will be the last one, too.
[Woodcraft]
I thought it was difficult.
It turns out to be so simple.
Your tool is not suitable.
Try that one.
You're holding it upside down.
Use this side.
Then cut the wood with a 30 degree angle.
Push forward slowly.
See?
Let me try.
It can be remedied.
Do you want to make it pointed here?
What are you waiting for? Do it.
Okay.
Do it yourself.
Look, your mom is also a straight-A student.
Let's not open it.
Let's look at them when we're home.
Okay.
I'm hungry.
I didn't eat much for lunch.
What do you want to have?
We should go to the place where everything started.
[Restaurant]
Wait, let me show you something.
Do you remember this place?
Isn't this a glass wall?
This is a one-way mirror.
This is where you blinked at me
back then.
Your seduction
has succeeded.
I...
I didn't know
it was a one-way mirror.
I don't care. You have to return the favor.
Ren Chu.
Wink.
Childish.
I want to post it on Moments.
This is where our scandal started.
I'm going to announce it now.
I remember someone said
if she falls for me one day,
she'll live broadcast the process of cutting the appendix.
Let's go eat.
[I'm finally with the boy I like.]
[This photo is definitely edited. How can you steal Guan Ai's boyfriend? You're the other woman.]
What's wrong?
Everyone on Moments is asking me
if I edited our picture.
Edit?
They just don't believe that we're together.
They said I added you to the picture using Photoshop.
They even found the evidence.
It's a picture of you attending an event.
I must have used image matting.
How is it not real?
Back then, a vague photo
started a great rumor.
But now
I made an official announcement.
No one believes me.
Don't be mad.
They also said that I stole Guan Ai's boyfriend.
I'm the third person.
Rumors stop at the wise.
Don't bother arguing with them.
Don't be mad, okay?
I just can't swallow it.
Wanwan, do you like me?
♫You come with the light♫
Is it that exciting?
-Look. -Who are they?
Ren Chu and Lu Wanwan.
Really?
♫The first encounter between two hearts♫
I like you.
I like you too.
♫You come with the light, dispelling the melancholy and raindrops♫
When did they become a couple?
I don't know.
Look.
♫As if I see the sky clears up, and the expectation continues♫
♫Within the touching distance, a moment of glow♫
They're really together.
How could they be together?
♫Can't stop wanting to explore♫
♫how attractive the story is♫
♫If I gently press the pause button for our encounter♫
♫Maybe we'll miss the blooming season♫
Let's go.
♫The glow at the first glance in youth, is it destined?♫
♫No one else can compare♫
Are you satisfied with the official announcement?
Yes, 100% satisfied.
I'm the woman
who's conquered the man at the top of the pyramid.
You're glowing.
And you even announced it in public.
We all saw it on Moments.
Tell us.
Did Ren Chu forcibly kiss you?
No, did you forcibly kiss him?
What?
We're together now.
It's only natural that we kiss.
What is that?
A gift from Ren Chu?
Yeah, it's an artifact he made.
It's from the top student?
Open it and let's have a look.
D-Did he carved
a radish?
Doesn't look like it.
It's kinda like
pork liver...
How did you look?
This is a heart.
It's Ren Chu's sincere heart.
Ren Lu, isn't your dad great?
Love makes people blind.
It also affects intelligence.
I'm going to have dinner with Fan Yi.
You two can continue to enjoy the masterpiece of the top student.
Bye.
I have something to do too.
Enjoy it yourself.
[Liang Xia]
I saw your Moments.
You being so happy,
I'm really happy for you too.
I'm going abroad in three months.
An Jiaxian and I chose to break up.
I hope you can take care of yourself
no matter what.
Hello?
Why did you break up?
We talked it through.
We can't guarantee anything for the future.
This is the best choice.
We broke up peacefully.
We're friends now.
I thought I should tell you.
Should I come over?
No, it's expected.
I've already been prepared.
How should I put it?
It feels like a big rock is being put down.
If it's convenient for you,
you can see me off at the airport.
After all, we used to be best friends.
We won't see each other often.
Liang Xia.
Wanwan.
Believe it or not,
you are my best friend.
You too.
Liang Xia finally made her choice.
But it's okay.
That's what growing up is.
Ren Chu, how was your first date?
Did you...
Oh no.
Why are you holding a skull?
Does it look good?
Is it delicate?
Is it real?
My girlfriend made this for me herself.
Why did Lu Wanwan
carve a skull for you for no reasons?
What does that mean?
What was she thinking?
Yeah.
It is so special!
This is the most special gift I've ever received.
No.
Ren Chu, do you like this?
Of course.
This is the token of our love.
The student from Department of Clinical Studies is so special.
Look at the details of the skull.
Ren Chu, we don't like it.
Which normal person would like a skull?
Yeah.
Goodbye.
What's wrong?
You'll be an intern tomorrow.
Why are you so unhappy?
Did you make a mistake and got scolded by superiors?
Are your colleagues unfriendly?
They all shared snacks with me.
They are all nice.
Is it because your work is too boring?
It's exactly what I learned.
Then why?
You look so unhappy.
Because I was harassed.
I have to take the same bus tomorrow.
What if...
Who dares to touch my boyfriend?
I'll break his hands.
Eat up.
Excuse me.
My hand is broken. Let go.
It can't be broken.
This could only be soft tissue contusion.
You rascal!
If I see you touch anyone again,
I'll break your bones. Do you hear me?
You bastard! Don't let me see you again!
Qiao.
It's okay. I'm here.
Don't be afraid.
I have classes. I'm off now.
Try it.
I made it myself.
For me?
Yes, I hope you'll like it.
Of course I will.
I take back what I said.
It turns out a straight-A student is not omnipotent.
With all due respect, your cake
tastes like plaster.
You need to strengthen your hands-on ability.
So this is the taste of plaster.
I'll be in charge of making the cake from now on.
You'll be in charge of eating.
I want to tell you something.
Don't be mad at me.
What is it?
The lab organized an exchange activity.
I won't be back for a month.
I'll go find you.
It's in another province.
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
It's not your fault.
No wonder you made me a cake.
I prepared something else for you.
What is this?
Guarantee of Long-Distance Relationship.
During this period,
you can ask for anything,
and I promise I'll do whatever you ask.
I'll ask then.
Write it down.
First, you must make my WeChat account on top and starred.
Reply my WeChat messages as soon as possible.
But if you're too busy to check WeChat,
when you're done,
you have to tell me what you were doing.
Boyfriend Rule No. 3:
Obeying Wanwan on everything.
Also, answer my call as soon as possible.
Call my name first.
You can't hang up until I hang up.
By the way,
give me a super cute nickname.
How about "Girl Out of Oxygen"?
What does that mean?
Think about it yourself.
What else?
I want a video call every day.
Okay.
Don't add other girls on WeChat casually.
Well,
if a beautiful girl
wants to add you on WeChat...
I don't have a phone.
Anything else?
That's all for now.
[Guarantee of Long-Distance Relationship]
[Party A: Lu Wanwan]
Won't you sign it?
I'll seal it.
♫I disliked you, but why do I have butterflies in my stomach now?♫
♫I slowly get close to you despite myself♫
♫The inexplicable air and atmosphere here♫
I'm out of oxygen.
♫Make me feel out of breath. The affection is heating up♫
♫How have I been taken captive by your love?♫