=A Puppetry=
=Episode 25=
Master imparted
his skills and techniques to you.
How could you be so cruel?
You're the one who led
your loved ones to death.
It's useless even if you kill me.
All of you are just puppets.
No one
can control their own destiny.
You're just hopeless.
Song Keyang.
I'm fine.
Are you alright, Song Keyang?
The female Gu will die
after the poison is cleared.
While the male Gu would sense her death
and die.
The person who has planted the Gu
will die of poisoning eventually.
Musician Song.
Mark my words.
Only use this method
if you have to.
It's a method of replacing one's life
with another's.
Xiaoxiao.
Song Keyang.
Thank you for weaving a sweet dream
for me.
I should
wake up now
and
take responsibility
for bringing those innocent people
back to life
and restoring peace to the world.
Song Keyang.
Farewell.
Xiao...
♪Time passed by but I can never forget
the look in your eyes♪
♪If dreams can prolong our encounter♪
(Song Keyang.)
(This time,)
(I'll fight)
(for the Puppet Clan and sentient beings.)
(Even though everything is predestined,)
(I'll strive with all my might)
(to fight against the destiny)
(and rescue the sentient beings.)
Sir, please cover for me. Thank you.
This is inappropriate.
(I'll handle this. No worries.)
♪I can still remember how beautiful
the thimbleberry bloomed♪
♪Time passed by but I can never forget
the look in your eyes♪
♪If dreams can prolong our encounter♪
♪Can I drink with you again?♪
♪As I see the blooming and passing
of the thimbleberry♪
♪When will we meet again
after this separation?♪
♪The language of flowers cannot answer
the questions my heart poses♪
♪It can only sway with the flame♪
The sky is starry
but the moon is gloomy.
The world is full of lives
but justice does not prevail.
In the mortal martial arts world,
the vainglorious pursuit
is but a dream.
A big round of applause, please.
Bravo!
Let's continue.
Yuji forsook her life
to protect sentient beings.
However, she and the musician
never got to meet
ever again.
Where did Yuji and the musician
go then?
There's another saying about them.
Perhaps the couple
lived their lives carefreely
up in heaven.
(The Book of Yuji)
(Song Keyang, the new comic author)
(published a new comic,)
(namely, The Book of Yuji)
(which sold 200,000 copies)
(upon release.)
(The romance of the couple)
(has won over the readers' hearts.)
(The comic book
is based on the puppet show)
(of the Song Dynasty,)
(the experts)
(specially visited
the puppet theatre troupe)
(to learn more about
the Chinese traditional culture.)
(New book listing)
♪The dusk outside the window
is spreading♪
♪The lanterns light up
with anticipation♪
♪The sea of lights illuminates
the entire theatre♪
♪The galaxy sprawls across the sky♪
♪The moon shows itself♪
♪Gazing at the myriad lives♪
♪The bell chimes and the lady dances♪
♪Her movements
are mysterious and graceful♪
♪A woman can solicit cheers
and applause too♪
♪Chatters fill the well-lit hall♪
♪Holding a red candle by the stage♪
♪Witnessing the blooming and wilting,
oh, the freedom♪
♪The theater welcomes you♪