Morning.
Good morning.
You're covering up.
That's because I just woke up...
Yeah?
And... it is a little strange to be in bed with Kurosawa-san.
- Let me see your face.
- No!
- Why not?
- Nope.
- Come on.
- No!
Let me see.
No, not yet!
- Don't be shy.
- No!
Hungry?
A bit.
Then I'll whip up breakfast.
What?
Really?
Yeah, nothing grand though.
Do you normally eat breakfast?
Usually just some toast, that's all.
I see.
What should I make for us...
I'll head on out first,
to go home to change my clothes.
Do you have to?
I can't go into the office wearing the same thing as yesterday.
Then just swap your shirt. The jacket can stay.
I suppose, but...
Maybe you can fit into one of mine.
Huh?
- One of yours?
- Yeah.
I have smaller shirts I don't ever wear.
It's fine! If I leave now, I would still make it...
How about this?
Yeah, looks good.
You'll fit.
- You think so?
- Definitely. Here.
Then I'll take you up on your offer.
Now you can head to the office, without making an extra trip.
Thank you.
And before I forget.
Here.
Huh?
It's a key. For you.
Since you might wrap up earlier than I do on some days.
You're allowed to drop by whenever you want.
Thank you.
I'm thinking we should clock in at separate times, too. What do you think?
I agree.
I mean, if we arrived together...
Yeah.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Good morning—
You scared me.
- Sorry!
- Are you okay?
Why are you even so strung up?
If the revisions could be done by next week's end, that would be ideal.
That would be everything from our end.
You now have Friday free. Spend it with your girlfriend.
Great, I'll get to work on this, then.
What's up?
Huh? Oh, nothing.
- Thanks.
- Anytime.
- Thank you for your time.
- No, thank you.
- Good morning, ma'am.
- Morning.
Every person has boundaries they ought to abide by. Myself included.
Some relationships may seem ideal in the short term, but fizzle out in the long run.
It's a boundary I should never cross.
Yet sometimes, logic and emotion are at odds with each other.
Ichikawa-san, here are the documents from Sales.
[The Reason We Fall in Love]
Thanks.
Sakamoto.
Oshima-san, please don't scare me—
Why do you look so depressed?
- I'm not depressed.
- Don't be shy.
We've both got our share of troubles. I mean, look.
At what?
This salad here, what else?
I'm on a diet to lose the 4 kilos I gained.
Oh really...
In any case, eat heartily and cheer up, yeah?
Eating well is the least of my troubles.
I envy your relationship.
Huh? What? Who?
You're not fooling anyone, sir.
I know you're in a relationship with Ozu-san.
- You do?
- Of course.
How? Did Ozu-san tell you?
- What are they talking about?
- I wonder.
You're so lucky though.
Lucky?
I mean, you're open about your relationship, even at the office.
I guess so. I'd never given it much thought.
But things are going well on your end, too. Right?
They are, yes.
One question though.
What's up?
Are you wearing that straight from Kurosawa-san's place?
Yeah.
Oh my gosh!
- I'm so happy for you!
- Shh, quiet, Kei-chan!
Things are going well indeed.
You know, I feel like my relationship with Kurosawa-san will last.
Why?
Something about this relationship feels different.
He makes me want to stay with him.
Ichikawa-san.
Sakamoto-kun?
Um...
Have you been... avoiding me?
What? No, of course not.
- But—
- Sorry, I've just been busy and all.
Did you need something?
If it's about work, I can talk, but I need to prepare for—
I've been lonely.
I miss your company, when you avoid me like this.
- Look, I haven't been—
- I love you.
Sorry?
Ichikawa-san, I love you.
Thank you, come again.
[Mid Dining]
I apologize for the sudden confession earlier.
Don't worry about it.
But I meant every word.
Although it was a spur-of-the-moment declaration,
know that I am entirely serious.
All right.
Could I just make one thing certain?
Of course.
Did you mean it in a platonic way of expressing your admiration?
No. I meant it in a completely romantic way.
I... see.
Except...
I saw you crying while talking with a girl the other day.
I didn't mean to intrude, really.
But I assumed...
That was my younger sister.
- What?
- My sister was visiting me in Tokyo.
We were talking about her upcoming wedding
and I had gotten a bit emotional about it.
I see, so that's what had happened...
No way, I'm unbelievable.
Give me one second.
This is so awkward.
Ichikawa-san?
Sorry for the weird misunderstanding.
It's fine.
Still, I couldn't help but think you two were right for each other.
I mean, from my perspective, two youngsters were hitting it off.
Meanwhile, I'm eight years your senior.
- That's—
- Does that really matter?
Personally,
I don't think our age makes much of a difference at all.
Hey, Sakamoto-kun.
Yes?
I'm honored you feel that way about me, really.
If anything, I don't deserve it.
You're a wonderful person, Sakamoto-kun.
Even so...
I'm sorry.
I...
Ayaka? Is that you?
It is. Ayaka, what a coincidence.
What's up?
Nothing much.
Your boyfriend?
No. He's a junior from work.
It looked like a date to me.
We're just wrapping up.
Now, goodbye.
Let's grab a drink then.
I said I'm going home.
Don't be a poor sport.
Just a glass, yeah?
There's a nice bar nearby.
Come on, I promise it'll be good.
Let go.
Aw, why so stiff?
Look.
Don't even bother reaching out to me anymore.
Hey, no need for the cold shoulder.
Come on, let's go.
Excuse me.
We've actually booked another bar to visit.
Huh?
We'll be leaving now.
Hey.
What should I choose...
Look, it's your Akira-kun-lookalike mug!
We can match.
I didn't realize there were color variations.
The one I have is a gift from Oshima.
I never knew he had such an eye for cute aesthetics.
I think I'll get this color.
I see they sell chopsticks, too.
Kurosawa-san!
Kurosawa-san?
Yeah?
What's wrong? Is everything all right?
Nothing wrong, it's okay.
Did you find a nice pair of chopsticks?
I did. What do you think?
Good choice.
There are so many other options though...
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
You shouldn't gun down those drinks...
I might not ever recover from this.
I can't believe you of all people had to witness that.
Just end me now.
And you know what?
The real insult to injury...
The guy was wearing a ring.
Right here.
No, then he's...
Yeah.
I bet he was keeping it under wraps this whole time.
I bet he made sure to take it off whenever we met.
But tonight, we bumped into each other.
He didn't have time to hide anything.
Hilarious, really.
I had a feeling he had someone else.
I could tell I was his "second choice" or whatever.
I knew.
I just didn't care.
Except...
I promised myself that I wouldn't get involved in an affair.
I never wanted to and yet...
This is seriously the worst.
How horrible.
Huh?
Why is Sakamoto-kun crying?
Because this is all too horrible.
You shouldn't settle on being someone's second choice.
Ichikawa-san, you deserve to be cherished.
What he's put you through is unforgivable.
You're a wonderful, beautiful person. You deserve none of this.
Sakamoto-kun.
You might be the most kindhearted person I've ever met.
Ichikawa-san, let us drink.
- A refill, please.
- Coming up.
Let's drink ourselves away.
Are you all right?
- Sakamoto-kun.
- Yes?
Ma'am...
We've made it.
Ichikawa-san?
Ichikawa-san.
Are you all right?
Ichikawa-san, I'm coming in.
How are you faring?
Here's some water.
Please, have a seat.
It hurts.
It all hurts.
Sorry?
It hurts.
Where does it hurt? Did you sprain something when you tripped?
Everything hurts.
What?
Everything. Everything hurts.
At some point, I became the second choice and I didn't realize it.
You've seen me at a new low.
I can't even face you with any dignity left.
I'm in my thirties.
My period flow stays heavy.
My skin dries out.
My shoulders ache, my back hurts.
I've gotten insomnia.
I get cold easily.
Fortune says I'm unlucky this year. Next year, too.
And to top it all off...
I've fallen in love with a younger guy at my age and it all hurts.
I can't believe you had to see all that.
Ma'am.
This is the worst, the absolute worst.
- The worst!
- Ma'am.
♫ I held your hand and laughed ♫
♫ Realized that day ♫
♫ Also your ambiguous pretense, because... ♫
Am I...
the younger guy in question?
♫ I try to smile, but the smile fades into the mirror ♫
You are.
♫ Maybe I know ♫
♫ But you know what? ♫
♫ The cityscape blurs and melts away at dusk ♫
Then our feelings are mutual.
♫ I'll always be next to you, any time ♫
♫ Your teary eyes and your voice ♫
♫ We can go beyond any night, because...  ♫
Why are you crying?
♫ Your eyes narrow as you smile ♫
Ichikawa-san?
♫ I held your hand and laughed ♫
♫ Realized that day ♫
♫ Also your ambiguous pretense, because... ♫
[Regarding the transfer to our Osaka Branch]
♫ It's you more than anything else to me, because... ♫
- Ichikawa-san.
- Just call me Ayaka.
Ayaka-san, you're cute.
What do I even mean to you?
We haven't even been dating for long.
You haven't given our future a single thought.
Does this mean we're breaking up?