I can't ever leave you be.
Let's get you back.
Right.
Good morning.
You could have taken the day off today.
Thank you, but I feel much better now.
That's good to hear.
I also just wanted to see you.
I'm counting on you for this afternoon's meeting.
Of course.
Hey.
- You show off.
- What?
He made a mad dash to the hospital and then...
Right?
Stop teasing me.
Love adds color to life.
Whether it's the painful of unrequited love or the joy of mutual love,
they're all emotions that build upon the other.
And that's something I find to be a miracle.
[The Reason We Fall in Love]
Glad to see Aoi-san up and kicking again?
What is your deal...
You're too open today.
Thanks for your help on Friday, really.
I have to say, you made some smooth moves that night, sir.
You swooped in like a fairytale prince.
Quit mocking me.
Would you have rushed to help, if I were the one who collapsed?
- Why would I?
- See? Any normal "boss" wouldn't.
You've always been overly conscious of Aoi-san.
- I would know. I've been watching.
- Huh?
See you around, sir.
Something's up?
Just wondering if there's a prince out there to swoop me off my feet, too.
If you need a prince to help drink your sorrows away, you have one right here.
Imamu...
- You're not my type.
- Hey.
But I'll take you up on that.
- You are so not cute.
- Hey, I'll pay.
- Morita-san.
- Yes?
Have you ever done work with Ichikawa-san before?
No, I don't think so.
But I have been called out to assist her...
So him and Aoi-chan, huh?
Ozu-san?
No... Does she... towards Tomonari?
Yeah, I bet she likes him.
He's better for her.
But then...
What am I supposed to do?
Nope, no more.
Got any plans after this?
I might grab a parfait somewhere.
I thought you avoided indulging.
Not anymore.
Why the change of heart?
My exercise buddy converted me.
It's a recent development.
Another gym bro...
She's a younger lady.
Then a gym girl.
Wait, a woman?
Yeah.
So... Anyway.
I want to introduce you to her. You'd get along great. How about it?
That was sudden.
She's a bold lady, true to her heart.
She's not afraid to express herself.
She's got some real spirit, I tell you.
So how about it?
No, thanks.
Why? Is it something about her?
Or did you get a girlfriend?
Not yet.
"Yet"?
I didn't realize you had someone special like that...
Who is it? Where did you both meet?
Is it someone in the company?
Do they work in sales? The same division, even?
Yeah.
Wow...
Which means...
If anything, aren't you the one crushing on your training buddy?
- What?
- Judging by your face when you talk about her, you know.
You know what? Tell me about what "not yet" means.
Nope, no more of this.
Good afternoon.
Oshima-sans nefarious plan is progressing, I see...
- Jealous?
- Sure...
But he turned me down for lunch, again.
Oshima-san, would you like to grab lunch with me today?
We could get some soba, to stay healthy.
Sorry! I have prior plans today.
Let's go out some other time!
Did he notice my feelings? Is he avoiding me?
He might just be busy.
But our work isn't especially busy right now...
And what brings you here?
I'm waiting for Ichikawa-san.
She's out eating lunch.
Alone?
I wonder where? And what?
Oh? Do you have something for Ichikawa-san?
- No, well—
- What's this about me?
Nothing! We were just speculating what you were having for lunch.
I had ramen today with Oshima-kun.
- Ramen?
- With Oshima-san?
Yeah.
I'd love to join sometime.
So a rich ramen was the correct choice here?
Aoi-san, is this...
What happened?
Nothing, I just got an eyelash in my eye.
- Are you all right?
- Fine.
I already used some eye drops.
How did it even get in there?
I don't know, but it sure does hurt.
Let me see.
- Huh?
- What are you doing?
- Great work as usual.
- What?
Morita-san, a moment.
P-Pardon?
Uh, did I miss something?
What's wrong, sir?
I won't know unless you say something...
Itami was touching you.
And I didn't like it.
Sir, it wasn't anything—
Still...
I reacted before I...
How absolutely unprofessional of me.
Sorry.
But I...
Well...
I want to have a long chat with you.
And without the influence of alcohol.
Because there's something I need to tell you.
Something... you need to tell me?
I want to talk calmly.
I can make dinner for us.
- So if you'd like to visit my—
- I'll go.
Kurosawa-san, perfect timing.
Could we get your opinion on this?
- Sure.
- Did we interrupt you?
No, I wasn't busy.
Then I'd like to go over some designs we covered last week...
Sakamoto-kun, you're like the perfect salesman.
You think so? Thank you for the compliment.
I mean, you're so lovable and charming.
Qualities that I don't even remotely have.
Well, I personally want to get better at giving sales pitches.
Yeah? I'm rooting for you.
Ichikawa-san.
Do you have anything after this?
No, I think I'll be heading straight home.
It's early evening, after all.
Then if you're free, would you like to grab dinner together?
Sure.
I live in the area, so I know good places.
Really? Let's go, then!
- What are you in the mood for?
- Good question.
Where do you usually eat dinner?
Just local eateries that sell set meals.
Eateries are nice.
No way, was there rain in the forecast?
Hold on.
Here, share my umbrella.
Thank you.
- This came out of nowhere.
- Unbelievable.
Watch your step.
- Let's take shelter there.
- Good idea.
This is a heavy downpour...
It sure is.
It doesn't look like it'll let up any time soon either.
Are we far from the restaurant you recommended?
We're actually quite close, but...
Sakamoto-kun!
You're drenched!
Looks like I am.
I didn't even notice.
You'll catch a cold in the restaurant.
- Let's head to my place first.
- Huh?
O-Oh, right.
Hold on, I'll bring you a towel.
Thank you.
- I can dry myself...
- It's fine, let me.
This isn't working.
Let's hang your suit.
Oh, thank you.
The shower's in here.
Keep warm, don't catch a cold.
Right...
This is bad...
Especially since I'm his superior and all.
[Yuji Shiraishi: Can I come over? I need a place to wait out this rain.]
There, there...
This rain hasn't let up one bit.
I'm glad we made it indoors before it started pouring.
Do you cook often?
Relatively so. Especially since my mother passed.
Don't let it bother you. It happened a long time ago.
Let me help.
Except, all I can really make is a simple salad...
Okay, then. I'd appreciate it.
Yes, sir.
At first...
I was only curious. I wondered why you were always so tense.
You were also a bit careless about yourself.
I felt like I was responsible for watching over you.
Eventually, I couldn't take my eyes off you.
But I'm already 33.
And when you get to my age...
you have to deal with problems aside from your own, like it or not.
Romance isn't something I can take lightly anymore.
We're coworkers.
You're my subordinate.
Our situation would involve risks, plenty of them.
What happens if we break up?
What if others find out?
I've given this careful thought. But as I do...
I realize all the hassle it would be.
I don't want to get you involved in all of that.
You're still in your twenties.
There are better people out there for you.
People your age, who share similar interests.
People you could get old with, without leaving the other behind.
At least, that's what I was trying to tell myself.
But despite it all...
Despite everything I've told myself...
I love you.
♫ Even if they are reborn someday, decades from now ♫
♫ I will find you and embrace you ♫
♫ I'm embarrassed to say this, but... ♫
That's what I had wanted to tell you.
♫ I just want you to know this feeling ♫
♫ I like the way you are ♫
♫ I pretend not to notice my feelings ♫
♫ I'm used to faking my emotions ♫
I love you, too.
Kurosawa-san...
I love you.
♫ I want you to always, any time, be by my side ♫
♫ I'll wipe your tears away ♫
♫ I'll never let go of your hand on any night, Let's go! ♫
♫ You always nod to me just the way you are ♫
From now on,
Kurosawa-san...
will you share your cooking with me?
Sure. I'd love to.
♫ I can't spell very well, but... ♫
♫ You are the reason for everything I do, because... ♫
Thank you for letting me borrow your shower.
They've issued a weather warning.
What?
What to do...
Stay here until the rain lets up.
We could drink to pass the time.
Would that be all right?
Of course. Here, sit.
Thank you.
[Can I come over? I need a place to wait out this rain.]
[Sorry, not today.]
- Cheers.
I see you work at home as well?
Something like that. I feel bad working overtime in the office.
All those design books, too...
Those? Yeah, those have accumulated over the years.
Sorry, I shouldn't be scrutinizing a woman's room.
Are you all right?
I'm fine—
Ichikawa-san?
I'll be borrowing your restroom.
If you'll excuse me!
That was so embarrassing...
What is it?
Nothing really. It just feels like time passed in a blink.
Kurosawa-san.
I want to make sure I'm not dreaming.
Can you squeeze me back?
To make sure I'm not dreaming.
- Are you free for dinner tonight?
- Yes.
[Next Episode]
I can't reciprocate your feelings.
Would you be willing to hang out with me again?
Are you still seeing that one guy?
I never once thought I would fall in love again.
And at the office, no less.