Welcome to X-Hunter, Charlie.
From now on, I will prohibit Dean
from going to the garage or practice field for one week.
I don't want you to be a Babe's boy anymore.
Why?
Let's be boyfriend.
When will you stop calling me Kid?
If I don't want to call you Kid,
what do you want me to call?
Darling?
Can I have your necklace?
If there's an amulet from Pit Babe,
then one day
I might be able to move a little closer to you.
Way even threw away the necklace I had given him.
Here it is, child.
-Thank you, Auntie.
-Thank you.
Alan, let me ask honestly.
What's wrong with my relationship with Charlie?
You have to understand him a bit that right now Way is rowdy.
In the past, everything was Way.
Now everything is Charlie.
People who are close to you like him must naturally feel this way.
You know that Way and I can only be friends.
Sometimes
in the past I felt like I didn't dare to love or have a boyfriend.
Part of it was because Way made me
feel like I wasn't worthy of loving anyone.
He likes to say
that being alone is the best solution.
Well, you give him some time.
Oh, Way!
Hey, are you lonely?
That's why you called me here.
You're all grown up and you're still attached me?
Why are you making a face like that?
I touched Babe and I used my senses on Babe.
Pictures of the future that occur.
I see something.
Even though I had never seen a picture like this before.
After you guys are in a relationship.
What do you see?
The X-Hunter team's car had an accident in the field.
I think it's Babe's car.
There were people lying in a pool of blood.
But I don't know who the person lying in the pool of blood is.
Brother.
I think it's becoming more and more dangerous.
You know when I see the future it never fails.
We withdraw now, it's still time.
We don't need to risk this much.
The closer you are to Babe,
the more at risk you guys are.
That guy
wouldn't stop.
Brother.
That person lying in a pool of blood might be you.
You don't have to say, I can't leave Babe right now.
If I have to take a risk, I will.
Please give me whiskey like this one.
Today you came alone, didn't you come with a team?
Mr. Pete.
I thought you wouldn't remember me.
The only sponsor of the X-Hunter team.
I can definitely remember.
It's just that Alan didn't put your picture in the garage.
You can just call me Pete.
I'd like one more glass of this for this guy, please.
I treat.
Two glasses on the rock please.
I don't like to owe anyone anything.
You probably didn't think I was flirting with you, right?
Isn't it like that?
I just saw you sitting alone.
So I'd like to come say hello.
Actually, I feel like you're sad.
You might want to talk to someone.
Did I guess correctly?
I said I wasn't going.
Why did you bring me here?
Got home.
I want to keep drinking.
Please, please, bring me some liquor.
Bring some liquor.
Way!
I will drink.
Oh, I still don't want to go home. Why are you bringing me here?
Huh!
Where is Babe?
Why did you bring me home?
Babe.
Babe, don't leave me.
Babe, please don't leave me.
(Antianxiety Drugs.)
(If you need a drinking buddy, you can always contact me.)
Give me back my phone.
Are you investigating this?
What do you plan to do?
What I want to do is up to me.
Yes, it's your business.
Don't you know what you're doing?
It has a negative effect on the team.
So, do you know who the person behind Babe's accident is?
I don't know and I don't care.
The only thing I care about
is that Red Racing has to win.
You don't understand me.
How long have I had to put up with Babe?
I've waited a long time for this moment
to throw Babe away.
And Mr. Tony has already paved the way for you like this.
You just stomp him into the ground.
But if you don't want to do it.
I'll do it myself.
And then you go back to Korea.
Don't get in my way.
And if I still see you dealing with these things, it won't have to be Tony.
I'm definitely not keeping you.
Please come, sir.
What did you come here for?
Why are you doing this?
That's too bad, Kenta.
If next time you make a mistake again,
I'm probably going to have to punish you.
I'm sorry. Next time I'll be more careful.
Does this mean you accept it?
That you guys were the ones who caused Babe's car to have an accident.
Why would you be surprised?
I did everything
to make Red Racing win.
And in that race you also came in 1st place.
Why are you complaining?
I don't want a victory like that.
I'll beat Babe myself.
You still don't know?
Even if you race to the death, you'll never beat Babe.
Your skills aren't even half as good as Babe's.
If you don't believe in me,
then why did you spend millions to get me?
The truth is, I can take anyone to compete with Babe.
It doesn't have to be you.
And the wage I paid you
was considered very cheap.
If compared to the actual value that I will get back.
But you don't have to do this much.
Babe could be dead.
I won't make him die.
Babe is more valuable than you think.
So,
whatever you're investigating right now,
stop it.
And then you don't have to go back to Red Racing again.
Our contract
ends now.
You can leave now.
Regarding Babe's price,
have they negotiated at all?
Not at all.
They are willing to pay if we can deliver on time.
That's good.
Reply to him that he will definitely get it.
Yes.
I'd like another glass of this, please.
Look at this.
The person who caused your accident on the racetrack
If I were to guess,
you and Tony would have serious problems.
He's going to cut you out of the will, right?
You're so involved in my affairs.
It seemed like you would make a huge profit for him.
What did you know?
He raises children like you to sell.
You are the highest priced person on their list.
And there's another thing that I think you don't know yet.
Please calm down.
Have you met Jeff?
When you were at home, you were closest to him.
I haven't met him at all.
Hello Mr. Suwat.
Hello!
This is my adopted son Charlie.
Hi Charlie.
As for those who can see the future,
I am rushing to find him in time for the auction.
Okay.
Hopefully, it'll be in time.
Babe.
Charlie.
Babe, how did you get here?
Don't ask me how I got here.
Have you been fooling me all this time?
You are Tony's adopted son.
You are a partisan with him.
Babe, I...
-I can explain.
-That's enough.
What else are you planning to lie to me about?
Do you dare to say that you have never lied to me in the past?
I'm so stupid.
I was so stupid I should have believed what Way told me.
I shouldn't trust anyone.
Get out of my life.
Babe.
What is the matter that brought you here?
I want to drink with you.
Sure.
Oh wow.
Is that enough for tonight?
Won't we get so drunk at all?
Why did you come alone today?
How about your boyfriend?
Let it be!
Way.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything.
I should've believed you from the beginning.
Charlie is exactly as you said.
He's lying to me.
He lies to everyone.
Wait, what did Charlie lie about?
He is another adopted son of Tony.
He has been fooling us all along.
Do you know?
How sorry I am
that I brought people like this in.
You know I've never loved anyone.
I gave everything in my life.
I give it all to him.
It's okay, it's not your fault.
It's my fault.
It was my fault for making our team like this.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault
Don't cry anymore, I'm right here.
As for the matter of Charlie, you can stop thinking about it.
Tonight, sleep here and return tomorrow morning.
Is this ok?
Oh, Way!
Are you hungry?
Yeah!
Tonight, I'm going home.
So you want me to go with you?
If you go back, won't you meet Charlie?
If I have to meet him, I will meet him.
If I meet him, it's good too, I'll be able to clear things up.
I don't like the unfinished business.
So you're sure you're okay?
You haven't forgotten that I'm here, right?
I know.
You're so good, how can I forget?
So if I have any problems, I'll come back to you immediately, okay?
Sure.
So let's go have dinner today?
Auntie's restaurant, the same restaurant.
Okay, okay.
Consider it a celebration of my singleness.
Babe.
Even if I chase you back several times,
you'll still be bold and back again.
It's appropriate to be partisan with him.
You'd better pack up your things and don't come back here again.
My house doesn't welcome people of that family.
Do you understand?
Babe.
Can you listen first?
Babe, I can explain.
Can you calm down first?
-Can you listen to me first?
-Let me go!
Babe, hey!
Pick up your things too.
Babe, it's not like that.
Didn't you hear me when I said it?
Huh?
Come here.
Babe.
You and I broke up, Charlie.
I have neither love
nor benefit for you any longer, do you get it?
But I love you.
Yes, I actually know Tony.
I am actually his adopted son.
But I brought myself in to help you
in order to protect you from his plans.
You had no idea
how much Tony intended to take advantage of your senses.
I know that, I've known it for a long time.
Tony wants to sell me to those millionaires, yes I know.
You know?
I know.
I've been running away for a long time.
All you're doing is buying yourself more time.
You believe me, Tony never thought about letting you go.
You look at this.
Other children at the foundation are raised separately
to practice special skills.
You weren't the only one who was raised like this by Tony.
Orphans that Tony took in to raise from the charity.
There are many people.
Everyone is Alpha.
Some are elite Alphas with special skills within them.
If trained well, Tony will take care of him like his beloved son.
Didn't you intend to practice your senses like the teacher taught you?
Even though it's really your only advantage.
If you're still stuck like this.
Daddy won't come to see you anymore.
And you will have to stay here alone for the rest of your life.
But if you don't do it well,
your daily life is almost no different from being in solitary confinement.
Charlie, I advise you to find
your special potential as quickly as possible.
We've been wasting more than 2 years now.
I still don't see anything in you.
I will delay sending the report on you to Daddy but it won't be long.
You don't want to get kicked out, do you?
I...
I'll try harder.
I will definitely get better.
I've always wondered why there are so many children in the foundation,
but I hardly see any of them.
These 8 kids
are my group with the most potential.
Their age is still not that old.
I guarantee that if you teach them more,
They will bring more enormous business benefits to us
than anyone can imagine.
Buy it, I guarantee.
You guys won't be disappointed for sure.
And your Chinese millionaire friends
offered any prices yet?
How much will they offer each person?
-Not everyone voluntarily leaves their home.
-Sure
-They were not adopted willingly elsewhere.
-I sell so cheap.
-But the truth is, everyone is raised like animals.
-I'm willing to sell.
-Everyone is waiting for the day to be resold.
-How much is the cost?
And I was kicked out of the Chen family.
Because I don't have any special sense.
Tony intends to adopt children and then sell them.
Such as people with special potential like you
and me.
You are not an ordinary Alpha, but a special Alpha.
But what is more valuable than you
is the child that is born from you.
Child?
Child is from me?
Tony intends to force you to have a child with Enigma.
The 1% on Earth are more capable than the special Alpha.
And that child born will have a bounty of at least 100 million.
Don't tell Charlie that you first approached me because you were Enigma.
No, I'm a normal Alpha.
I was adopted as well.
But I don't know
who the Enigma that Tony plans to pair you with is.
Charlie actually infiltrates Babe's side
in the X-Hunter garage.
We just ignored it because we didn't think Babe's Boy,
which was only played temporarily, would be a problem.
It's true that I be kind to you.
But I didn't think you'd make this many mistakes.
How could you let Charlie go stay with Babe?
Didn't you say that Charlie has no use for us?
There was no use and he had to leave the mansion.
It was my fault that I didn't work properly.
Will you let me handle it?
Don't have to.
If Charlie plans to get close to Babe,
he must have some kind of plan in mind.
I'll wait and see him a little more.
What exactly does he intend to do?
Kenta.
Yes.
You've really never seen Charlie and Babe together before, have you?
You are the person who keeps useless people like me to raise.
I absolutely do not dare to lie to you.
Since I found out Tony was taking you back to the foundation.
I also searched for your information.
Then go to The Hallow field.
I'm trying to make you notice me.
Because I want to know what Tony will do next.
And I hope I can warn you.
What will happen next?
Can I have that glass?
But after I really got to know you.
Learn your talents, strengths,
and weaknesses.
Then I want to be the one beside you
Protect you
from Tony and Enigma who try to get close to you.
But in the end,
it was me who was selfish.
I'm afraid that if you know the truth, you'll hate me like you do today.
Have you told all of your lies?
No, I haven't.
What else are you hiding from me?
I have the same special abilities as you.
I'm the one who made your senses disappear.
My Sense disappeared because of an accident.
It's not like that.
My special ability is absorption.
The simple explanation is
I took other people's power for myself through touch.
The closer I am to someone,
the more I can steal other people's power as my own.
For now, my wounds have healed
but I still have no sense left
because of you?
I can return it to you.
If I die,
the power I took will automatically return to its owner.
I can die for you.
Don't joke like this, Charlie.
Don't think
that even if I don't have any sense left,
but I'm Pit Babe.
Any special abilities are not necessary.
So, do we think we can reconcile yet, Babe?
Anyway, I won't break up with you.
Can I?
Can Mama not break up with Papa?
Is it time to joke?
Later, if there is anything, you must not hide it from me again.
Do you understand?
Thank you, Babe.
Thank you for forgiving me.
I won't break up with you.
But I invite you to pay for your entire life's karma.
You have to take care of me.
Do you understand?
Of course!
As you wish.
Why are you crying?
I didn't cry.
You've become an arrogant.
Huh!
Oh, dear!
Who will go on a date to Auntie's restaurant?
Over there, they went to a nice restaurant.
No matter how beautiful the restaurant is, it's just not meaningful.
So what will you eat today?
I'd like the same as before.
Okay.
What's wrong, Babe?
I invite you to come out for a ride and breathe in the fresh air.
Why are you still frowning?
Have you really stopped being angry at me?
I told you I'm not mad at you anymore.
It's just that many things are mixed together.
Does that mean you're still stressed?
That's right.
Why?
May I help you relieve stress?
Are you serious?
Are you sure you can handle it?
It's secretly cramped.
Must try it first.
I'm not in a hurry to go anywhere.
Or are you in a hurry?
If that's the case, I could try all night.
You're just lying there.
I'll do it for you.
Sorry, I just finished clearing things up with Charlie.
I'll tell you later.
Thank you so much for always listening to me.
Are you saying that Charlie and Jeff are also Tony's adopted children?
And they are also people with special abilities like you.
Yes.
And Tony, a wealthy philanthropist
who helps sponsor nearly 50 children one year.
The truth is they are scumbags who run the human trafficking business.
I don't know if I couldn't escape from Tony's house back then
and you didn't recruit me,
what my life would be like now.
You can't leave it like this.
Both about you and other children.
Anyway, your fucked-up adoptive father must be in jail.
So what can we do to him?
Even if it were news,
I believe Tony has enough money to silence all the reporters.
If we do anything blindly,
let me tell you, it will be us who are all in trouble.
Alan, did you hear any news about Kim?
He was such an insult to Tony.
Tony wouldn't let him go.
I'm afraid he will be dangerous.
Babe is Tony's adopted son.
Charlie is Tony's adopted son.
And Jeff is also Tony's adopted son.
And how many children does Tony have?
How difficult will it be?
The children in the foundation are all orphans.
All children are considered to be Tony's adopted children.
Oh!
Hey!
Look, if it's like this,
it means Charlie loves Babe very much.
But think about it,
they've never met at the foundation.
But when he found out that Tony was going to harm Babe,
Charlie rushed to help.
I couldn't believe
that someone as generous as Tony would actually do such a thing.
It's like the proverb says
that you can't see your heart by looking at a face.
Know your personality but don't know your nature.
Fucking North.
I lost the game.
Oh, Babe.
The two of you never thought about practicing.
Only paying attention to nonsense.
Babe, what nonsense?
There is no impact on our team at all.
That's right, have you ever heard of
One who knows the enemy and knows?
Have you seen Way?
I haven't met him.
Last time
I invited him to drink but he didn't answer me.
I don't know how he is now.
Babe, if I didn't know you,
I'd think Way secretly liked you.
You think about it since you dated Charlie.
Way has completely changed, irritated like a person in menopause.
North, shut up.
You talk nonsense.
Way and I are just friends.
If Way contacts you, please tell me.
All right.
What's wrong with him?
Speaking at an inappropriate time
What the fuck?
What did I do wrong?
You still don't know?
Let me go, let me go.
You're so naughty.
I'm giving you a chance to get out of this game.
Why are you still stubborn?
The Thai racing industry isn't for you, Kim.
Shylock like you
should not have a place in this world.
Playing dirty and biting like a dog
You sell people alive.
How did you do it and are you still human?
Shut up now.
You did a lot of research about me.
But you still don't know me that well.
Do you know?
I'm not selling just living people.
Dead man...
I also sell.
I just want you to bring him back to me.
I promise I won't do anything to him.
If you're afraid, what can you do?
Now they're targeting us.
No matter how we escape, Tony will attack us anyway.
I don't want to live in a cave like before, and it's all because of you.
Hey, I'm your friend.
And who said I love you like a friend?
But shouldn't you have told me that you had reconciled with Charlie?
Or have you seen that I've been waiting for you all this time?
Do you really want to help him?
Charlie goes!
If Way contacts you, please tell me.
(I almost get told off.)
(Get told off!)
Cut
(Already reconciled.)
The benefits you want I don't have for you.
(Puppy hurriedly reconciled.)
Cut.
(Crying until exhausted.)
(Someone helped console him.)
(I hope you get better, Pavel.)
Being abused.
(The face is covered in blood.)
(This scene is prepared to be filmed.)
Not realistic.
(Daddy will help you add makeup.)
(I've given up.)