(Shin Ye Eun)
(Ryeo Un)
(Kang Hoon)
(Jung Gun Joo)
(The Secret Romantic Guesthouse)
(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
You are here for me, are you not?
Go ahead and arrest me!
Drop your sword first!
What are you waiting for? We must go.
- Return to the palace. - Yes, sir.
We must get the rest.
Among those that got away is the watchman.
We cannot delay. His Majesty awaits.
My lord.
We got Lee Seol.
We can go after the rest another time.
- Come along. - Yes, sir.
(Episode 17)
My goodness. Oh, dear.
Are you all right?
I was so worried something terrible would happen.
I am sorry.
I always make you worry.
Hong Ju looks shaken up.
My gosh.
Lay down the body in one of the rooms.
We must bury Hwa Ryung first.
I will get a coffin and grave site.
I will help with that.
Yu Ha was taken?
What on earth happened in the woods?
Master Jang got the Department of Justice involved.
If not for Yu Ha,
none of us would have gotten out safely.
I see.
What should we do now?
I will rescue him.
I should,
at any cost.
How despicable.
How little did you think of me...
that you deceived me?
My lady.
You should...
not have smiled and joked with me.
I had no idea you had killed my fiancé.
I laughed...
at your jokes.
You disgust me.
How many lives did you take...
with the hands that once held mine?
I apologize.
None of my words will be enough...
to wash away your broken heart...
Why must only the innocent lose their lives?
When others deserve to die?
(Pyeong)
What is this?
We found it while searching Garden of Flowers.
I see my nephew has grown up.
I see why I did not recognize you.
That is because you do not have a good eye.
How shall I kill you?
The thought excites me already.
Enjoy it while you can.
All good things do not last,
and neither will your reign.
Blabber all you want.
But know that your voice will never be heard.
I will pluck your flesh from your bone bit by bit...
until not even the soul is left.
My poor brother...
will not see his son's face even in the afterlife.
Why is the interrogation lasting so long?
Is the heir to the throne being tortured?
Lord Sin, you were here?
Your Highness.
I cannot stand the grief and disappointment.
- Your Highness. - Your Highness.
My gosh.
What on earth happened?
Do not worry.
Kang San is safe and well.
You mean to say...
I bought him time. Now we wait.
Accept a drink.
You played a great role in Lee Seol's capture.
I will have you promoted soon.
I am honoured, Your Majesty.
So...
how did you know...
Jung Yu Ha is the deposed heir?
The chief eunuch confessed.
Who the deposed heir is.
Then...
all that is left is to execute him.
Poison is too light a sentence...
and decapitation too simple.
I cannot gift my only nephew such a boring death.
Do you have...
an idea in mind?
I heard you told His Majesty who the deposed heir is.
Were you always aware?
Do not be too offended.
Were you not...
promised a promotion?
Is His Majesty aware that...
the Lee Seol you found...
is a fake?
He is a fake?
What nonsense is that?
Can I inform His Majesty this nonsense?
That Kang San...
is the Lee Seol he is looking for?
What is it you want?
Tell me.
I wish to know only one thing.
The watchman.
Where he is.
I truly do not know where the watchman is.
You are testing my patience.
I do not know his location,
but I do know the temple that trains the watchmen.
But...
how did you know that...
Jung Yu Ha is an impostor?
The watchman never leaves his master to escape.
That is impossible.
Where are you going this late at night?
To see the first vice-premier.
Do you think he would be safe and sound?
Once the day dawns, check the situation...
No one knows when he will be executed.
This is the moment the king has been waiting for.
- Your Highness. - I cannot...
let Yu Ha suffer in my place.
I could not forgive myself for it.
However hurried you may be,
you should not forget your sword.
Go ahead.
I will wait for your return.
Okay.
I will not be long.
Will you stand there all night?
I thought it best...
that I stay away.
It would make me a hypocrite...
to say I understand how you feel.
Are you going somewhere?
I will come with you.
You do not have to.
I am sorry I was not able to...
release you sooner.
Your Highness.
You can follow your heart now.
Choose to stay...
or to leave.
If I were to fail to protect you too,
would my life be of any worth?
You can save Yu Ha.
I must protect you as you do so.
Tonight, you should stay here.
Assistant Magistrate Jang might return,
and knowing you are here...
will put me at ease.
Stay safe.
I waited for you here...
in case you came.
Garden of Flowers was empty.
Where is Lord Sin?
He is in prison.
I heard...
Lee Seol was captured.
The longer we take, the worse our chances become.
We must raise men to attack the palace soon.
I was told...
Lord Sin had things arranged.
The head of the Military Training Command...
agreed to join the coup.
But a lot has happened since.
Arrange a meeting.
I will persuade him.
Very well.
- Master! - Master!
Who are you?
Where is the deposed heir's watchman?
"Watchman?"
I have no idea what you are talking about.
Tell me...
before I kill everyone.
How can the answer change...
if the question remains the same?
No.
This place is not safe either.
- If they find you... - So what?
I should save my skin?
When Yu Ha could be executed at any time...
and everyone's life hangs in the balance?
You have others to care of.
In order to keep them safe, you must leave Hanyang.
You are family to me too.
I cannot do that.
Dan O, please.
I will not be a nuisance,
so please...
do not tell me to leave.
I will crumble.
If I were...
to lose you too.
- San. - I barely clung on until now.
I will not be able to take another step.
I can...
protect myself.
I did so far,
and I will keep doing so.
I know that.
You are stronger than anyone.
Whatever crisis you face, you will get through it.
Yes.
So trust me and...
But Dan O.
Even people like that...
break and disappear without a trace.
That...
is what a coup is like.
They have captured His Highness.
I need your help to rescue His Highness.
Even if I gather those who are sick of the King's tyranny,
it will be difficult for us to get past the palace walls.
I used to be in the Palace Guards,
so I know their system very well.
I will help, so...
If they seal the palace gates and fight back,
the King will buy time to get the Five Military Camps involved.
What if someone on the inside lets us in?
Do you think we could win?
If that is possible, we should be able...
to take down the King's bodyguards and make him surrender.
(Geumgun: Royal bodyguards)
Perhaps, you should tell them that you are the deposed heir.
I do not think I deserve the title.
After all, Yu Ha is the one...
who is putting his life on the line to bear the weight of the title.
Your Highness.
The head of the Military Training Command...
will mobilize his army to protect the deposed heir.
Their determination to fight will save Yu Ha.
So for now,
Yu Ha should remain Lee Seol.
Because of them, our customers will not want to drink.
Why are they all here?
They are soldiers from the Capital District Office, right?
Why is Madame not here today?
I wonder if something happened.
I saw them going through Madame's room earlier.
Did Master Jang not say anything to you?
Ban Ya.
Someone is here to see you.
Come out for a moment.
Me?
Who could it be?
(Buyounggak)
- What? - Just follow me.
You are alive.
I was so worried when I saw...
that everyone at Garden of Flowers was gone.
You were at Garden of Flowers?
Yes. I went there to check because I was worried.
I heard the deposed heir had been captured.
Does that mean...
Come with me. I will tell you on the way.
On the way? Where?
The truth is...
Madame is...
I am glad you are here.
I was hoping someone from Buyounggak would be here.
I cannot believe this.
Pour her a drink first.
I will...
put my everything on the line to save Yu Ha.
So please...
rest in peace.
A banquet, did you say?
Yes. The civil service examination will take place at the palace.
Those who pass the exam...
will be invited to a grand banquet.
Many of the kisaengs at Buyounggak will be invited too.
They are hosting a banquet?
But it is strange.
I thought the state exams would be postponed.
Perhaps...
that is the day...
Yu Ha would be executed.
What brings you here?
I saw the signal kite.
The signal kite?
Something happened at the temple?
Venerable Sir.
It was Assistant Magistrate Jang.
The children are gone.
He took them to the Capital District Office.
He said if you did not show up,
the children would be...
Please take him inside.
Will you go to the Capital District Office?
I cannot let that scoundrel kill the children.
You must not forget your duty as the watchman.
Master!
If the watchman risks his life in this manner,
who will protect our king?
They are young children.
They did nothing wrong.
(Capital District Office)
Who is it?
You did not see his face?
No, he was already gone.
I will go to the Capital District Office.
Just give me three days.
Pack light.
We will find most things we need at my brother's house.
Gosh.
We should not show up empty-handed and inconvenience him.
As for the upcoming state exam...
You will not be able to take it, right?
The family's safety is my top priority now.
I was very surprised when you passed the exam.
I suppose you are not destined to pass the state exam.
You never sugarcoat anything, Ms. Naju.
- You are very honest. - Oh, dear.
My ladies. You are ready, right?
Wait for me.
- When I finish my job... - I know.
You will not be too long.
And about Si Yeol...
Oh, about that...
He and my sister should talk it out amongst themselves.
I should not step in.
I am not saying you should.
Your sister must be heartbroken too.
Do your best to comfort her.
I bet she resents him and is feeling deeply betrayed.
Although...
Si Yeol must be devastated too.
Do not resent Si Yeol too much.
At least you should not resent him.
It all started with me.
It is my fault that Si Yeol is in such a rut...
and that Yu Ha got caught. It is all my fault.
No.
It all happened...
because of the tyrant king who stole the throne.
Do not...
ever forget that, San.
Do not look back.
Let us get going.
I am sorry, Ms. Naju.
I truly...
cannot leave like this.
Do not say that.
I cannot let you throw yourself into such danger too.
Over my dead body!
Knowing they are in such a precarious situation,
I must do something.
Lady Dan O, please.
Go.
I will take good care of Ms. Naju and Hong Ju.
Do not do this!
You need to help me dissuade her.
It is not like she will listen to us.
She has already made up her mind.
Must you go?
Yes.
I am sorry, Hong Ju.
So you are alive.
I thought you dropped dead somewhere.
Thankfully, I am not dead.
I was right.
The banquet is where...
the execution will take place.
He wishes to execute the deposed heir in front of everyone...
as a deterrent measure.
I will...
save His Highness no matter what.
When I first set my mind to do this,
the first person that came to my mind...
was you.
Me?
The King has crossed the line.
After killing the deposed heir, he will go on to hurt countless people.
If you are hesitant,
you may leave.
I will not blame you.
Do you trust me that much?
What if...
I report you to the Palace Guards?
Trying to gain something without giving up something in return...
is just greed.
Perhaps, we were already on the same path.
To tell you the truth,
I thought the tyrant got what he deserved...
when you shot him with an arrow.
On the day of the banquet,
we will go to the palace.
We must stop the banquet to save His Highness.
However, the King will not cancel the banquet...
just because he hears of some traitors.
Gosh.
Can we truly pull this off? It is just the five of us.
If everything goes according to the plan,
it will stir up the King too.
During all those years when the deposed heir was on the loose,
the King was haunted by the fear...
of losing the throne.
Listen.
Even if we manage to enter the palace and deceive the King,
he will quickly realize he has been deceived.
We just need to hold out until sunset.
Then the head of the Military Training Command...
will arrive with his soldiers.
But...
did you not say someone on the inside would let them in?
We will go to the Queen Dowager and get her appointment notice.
With that,
we can make the guards at the gates surrender.
Gosh. We cannot enter the Queen Dowager's residence.
Well...
I suppose we could ask the court maids to deliver our letter to her.
You have been quiet, immersed in thought.
I think someone is outside.
What are you doing here?
I told you to leave.
I just could not take my feet off the ground,
so I could not force myself to leave.
Dan O.
How about I go there and pick up the notice?
Nonsense.
Let me escort you. Get ready to leave.
Why is it nonsense?
I am the only one here who can actually look like a court maid.
Well, she should be able to enter the Queen Dowager's residence.
Let us entrust Dan O with the job.
We do not have much time.
You know...
that Dan O has been inside the palace.
What if someone recognizes her?
All will be fine if I manage not to run into the King.
You see, on the day of the banquet...
As soon as the job is done,
I plan to leave right away.
You will leave?
Even if I leave without saying goodbye,
please understand.
Gyeom.
My son.
Find...
happiness.
I am sorry,
Mother.
The banquet is just around the corner.
There is no way for us to find out what is going on.
Even if things go wrong,
I will die as Lee Seol.
It is the price I have to pay for living as Lee Seol.
Your Highness.
You must stay strong.
I may die, but my brother lives.
And he will bring down His Majesty.
What are you hoping to achieve at the palace?
I am not complaining since it gained me an ornament, but still.
A banquet will take place.
Imagine how splendid and beautiful it will be.
I take it you are adamant about attending it.
Your Majesty!
The honours banquet will soon take place,
and I would love for you...
to grace us with your presence.
It will truly be grand.
No... Not Seol...
You should witness the body of your beloved grandson...
be vainly torn to pieces.
What will you do to him?
Attend the banquet, and see for yourself.
I have already sent word, so head to Queen Dowager right away.
Of course. You have said it many times.
Please do not fret.
I share your sentiment.
If I lose you,
I will not be able to take another step forward.
So from this moment on,
you will put yourself first.
That Gu Nam or whoever he is should be here by now.
Maybe we should wait some more.
The banquet will begin soon.
Falling behind on schedule could endanger Yu Ha.
Enter.
Goodness.
We are the troupe from Namsan Village...
and are here per His Majesty's order.
Hold on. You look oddly familiar.
I highly doubt we crossed paths when I am of lowly origin.
No.
I definitely recognize you.
Allow them to enter.
What brings a palace guard out here?
If they are the reason the banquet is delayed,
His Majesty will breathe fire.
Enter, then.
Sure.
Go on.
(Capital District Office)
Do not let your guard down, not even for a second.
- Yes, Master Jang! - Yes, Master Jang!
What does this concern?
The deposed heir...
will be executed during the honours banquet?
Yes, Master Jang.
Come and rescue me.
I will be waiting.
How is that?
That was it.
That was why you asked for three days.
Let us move out.
It is the sword you had me keep safe.
Are you Innkeeper Yoon from Garden of Flowers?
Yes, are you one of Queen Dowager's court ladies?
This way, please.
Stay hidden in here...
and leave as the banquet comes to an end.
Yes, Your Highness.
There is one more thing Seol requested.
He said you were to protect yourself.
Are you skilled in archery?
Yes, His Highness taught me himself.
- Your Highness, you cannot. - Your Highness, you cannot do this.
Royal Consort Park, you cannot barge in like this.
What is the meaning of this?
His Majesty asked that I escort you myself.
Shall we?
Goodness, I am experiencing vertigo.
Help me walk, will you?
Are you that entertained by their dancing?
Does it not lift your spirits?
But the grand finale...
will be crimson in colour and even more splendid.
That is right.
Assistant Magistrate Jang has requested an audience.
Master Jang?
Yes, he says that time is of the essence.
Please inform His Majesty...
that those loyal to the deposed heir might have infiltrated the palace.
How sure are you?
My lord, we are having trouble...
locating a few of the palace guards that are on patrol.
This could be their doing.
Locate them while I inform His Majesty.
My men will be at your disposal.
Of course, my lord.
Your Majesty.
Lee Seol's men have infiltrated the palace.
I am sure they can be captured.
In fact, they could join him out there.
Maybe you should end the banquet...
while we handle the situation.
That is all you will say.
I am just about to have some fun.
How can it not bring joy to the royal family...
when the traitor who has been eluding authorities for decades...
has been caught?
It is why I will execute deposed heir Lee Seol...
as the banquet's grand finale.
Execute him!
- Yes, Your Majesty. - Yes, Your Majesty.
This cannot be.
Has he ordered a dismemberment within palace walls?
What madness is this?
He is the Crown Prince's son.
(Geoyeolhyeong: A punishment where one's limbs were torn off)
You wait and see.
My fresh blood will remain...
and continue to smother you.
The officials and people of this nation...
are strong enough to stand up to fear.
What are you waiting for?
Tear off his limbs this instant!
- Yes, Your Majesty. - Yes, Your Majesty.
The watchman.
So here is where we meet.
Keep moving.
Leave them to me.
Are you sure?
There is no time.
Now, go.
The children.
Are they alive?
Who knew...
you had compassion?
I will take your life at all costs...
and appease the soul of my late son.
This...
This is what you will remember.
This side of you...
is who you...
truly are.
Watchman,
you are nothing...
but a bloodthirsty ghoul...
who will always be hungry for the next kill.
You disgust me.
How many lives did you take...
with the hands that once held mine?
I knew...
I would die at your hands,
but I still had to find you.
That was...
the commitment of a father...
who had lost his son.
(The Secret Romantic Guesthouse)
Even if I do leave, I will only do so after he is dead.
Answer me this instant!
What are you plotting?
I am here to take my rightful place.
I am Lee Seol.
Find Lee Seol and tell him this.
That I will wait for him at his execution site.
For as long as I live, I will resent and loathe you.
A new king has been crowned, so accept his order.
Surrender willingly, and you will keep your life.
This nation is mine.
It is my Joseon that I secured with my bloodied hands!