[English subtitles are available.]
[Make a Wish]
[Ep18]
Mingming,
I need to talk to you.
Two more kilometres.
Keep up.
I really need to talk to you.
After this.
I really need to talk to you right now.
Fine, go ahead.
I...
I have a phobia
and it got worse recently.
Whenever I hear the word, you know,
I throw up.
The word?
[Marriage]
Marriage?
When I was little,
my parents got divorced.
I know my mom and sister love me.
But I witnessed a lot of fights
between my parents.
After they got divorced,
my mom didn't forgive my dad.
She is regretful.
So, I am scared of marriage
since I was a kid.
Later, I went to college,
there was this girl who liked me.
I said yes without much thinking.
I was young
and I never really thought about
the future.
But she thought
I don't want to... You know what.
So, she tried to commit suicide.
From then on, I became even more scared
about that word.
Have you ever visited a therapist about this?
The doctor said
this is because of my psychological issue,
medicines won't help.
It got worse recently
and I think the reason is that
you are the girl that I love the most.
I care about you too much.
You must be thinking
that I am a jerk,
or I am trying to
find an excuse for myself.
But the truth is...
I believe in you.
But to be honest,
I am not the kind of girl who doesn't want a marriage.
My parents passed when Liangliang and I
were little.
We were raised by
Uncle Gao and Aunt Lou.
They are very nice to us
and I am really grateful.
But
I always feel
there's an empty space in my heart.
So, I always
want a small family
of my own.
We can spend a lot of time
happily together.
Many claim that piece of certificate unimportant.
But I actually care about it.
However,
what's more important is that
you're being honest with me,
and you're willing to share it with me.
So, relax,
I won't give up on you this quick.
I would love to see where things go between us.
Mingming,
thank you.
I won't let you down.
Care to join me for two lapses?
Sure, let's go.
Haven't found it yet.
We'll search for it in the old mansion tomorrow.
Hugh?
Don't come upstairs.
You cover the ground floor.
I'll look for it on the first floor.
Why did you come up here?
We have no idea what a cat seal looks like.
How can we find it?
But we have to try.
That seal
allows a human and a cat
to make a love pact,
it's important.
Stop looking for it
and follow me.
Nature is so amazing.
Being with you is amazing.
A lot of amazing things happened
since then.
So, rest assured,
we can be together forever
even without the cat seal.
What,
you are willing to let go now?
My girl has grown up.
She doesn't need me as she used to now.
As a parent,
you only get to be with them for part of the journey.
They need to be self-dependent
for the rest of that journey.
I know,
but I still can't let go.
If there is someone out there
who can protect and take care of her for you,
you should be happy.
Now,
I can only wish for the best
for them.
Humans have a saying,
you will eventually cross the bridge
when you come to it.
Don't think about
what has not happened yet.
Prepare for the worst
and work hard towards the best.
Here.
We didn't find the cat seal today.
We will keep on looking for it tomorrow.
As long as I take the cat seal away,
I can hurt him, right?
Xu Zihao?
He used to be a chubby little boy.
Yep, that's it.
Right, right, right, he told me about that.
He said,
he was trying to lose some weight
and you used to jog with him,
right?
He forced me to jog with him.
Your friendship hasn't changed a bit.
These books
were my favourite when I was a child.
How about I read to you?
Sure.
Two tiny, free bubbles
Rise from the depth of dreams
A vague haze, a silvery mist
Lifts in a soft breeze.
Like a little child
I cling to you, as you fade away.
And dream of the soft look
your eyes once had,
and of their
shadows deep.
This one sounds romantic.
It reminds me of happiness.
That's how we'll be.
Happy.
We will be.
I remember you once told me
about something that a writer said.
Love is
wanting to touch something
but too afraid to do so.
I always find it difficult to understand.
That's not the case for me.
For me, love is
all those moments
when I want to hold you tight,
like this.
I won't let go.
I want to show you something.
This book
was my grandpa's favourite.
It's so beautiful.
Can I keep this?
Sure you can.
Never mind.
This book belongs to your grandpa.
He wanted you to have
whatever is inside this book.
You should keep it.
This bookmark is important to my grandpa.
But you are also important to me.
If he gets to meet you,
he would like you a lot.
So,
I give it to you on behalf of my grandpa.
Thank you.
It's a little cat.
it's a...
Revenge?
I heard that a cat
was asking about the cat seal.
He even returned to the Meow Planet
to ask those senior cats.
Nobody takes the cat seal seriously,
they all consider it just a tale.
Also, there are rumours about that cat.
Something about revenge
for his dead lover.
It can't be the one you ran into, can it?
What does the cat seal have to do with revenge?
You don't know?
Rumour has it
that we can't kill a human
with the cat seal.
So, that cat is trying to find a way
to destroy that cat seal.
Oops.
What's wrong?
Xiao Xu has been looking for the cat seal.
I was wondering,
she used to doze off in history classes,
how come
she suddenly got interested in history?
I think Chi Yan is in danger.
Is it far from the city here?
Nope.
Let's go now, immediately.
I'll explain it to you on the way.
Hurry up, hurry.
Calm down and listen to me.
The one who murdered your sister is right next-door.
I won't let him harm you.
Sorry.
Wait here.
It will be all over soon.
Lin Mo!
Lin Mo, stop! Listen to me!
Hugh!
Stay away!
Lin Mo!
Lin Mo, listen to me!
Chi Yan can't be the one who murdered my sister!
Lin Mo!
Lin Mo, are you out of your mind?
What are you doing?
The white cat that you killed back in high school
was Hugh's sister
and my lover!
Careful!
Get lost!
Chi Yan?
Chi Yan, Chi Yan, Chi Yan.
Chi Yan.
Chi Yan, we are at the hospital.
Chi Yan?
Chi Yan!
Excuse me,
you'll have to wait outside.
Xiao Xu!
Dad.
Xiao Xu?
Hugh.
Are you all right, Xiao Xu?
Xiao Xu, it's okay.
Chi Yan will be fine.
There there.
Dad.
Chi Yan will be fine.
Don't worry.
It's okay.
It won't hurt.
Hugh,
I have something to tell you.
Hugh, Hugh?
Let's get out of here.
Here.
Chi Yan gave the cat seal to you
and lost the Meow Planet's protection.
That's why Lin Mo could hurt him.
The cat seal.
How did my sister die?
Your mom and I want nothing but happiness for you.
Are you relatives of the patient?
He's awake.
Relatives may visit him now.
Chi Yan!
How are you?
Uncle Fu.
Mister.
The doctor said,
it may hurt a little.
Dad and Uncle Fu are here.
I'm sorry.
Why?
Now that I think of it,
Lin Mo only approached me
because of you.
Chi Yan, I'm sorry.
Don't be. I feel much better now.
Look.
Hugh.
Uncle Fu.
I'd like some time alone with Xiao Xu's dad.
Don't move.
Stay still. Don't move.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't protect her.
But I guarantee you,
I will find the murderer.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
You are not the one to blame.
All these years,
we've been trying to avoid talking about it.
But I think of Hugh's sister every day.
I can tell,
Hugh's mom does the same thing.
But she won't be back
even if we have revenge.
So,
I hope that you can
live a happy life.
Don't be like us,
carrying so much burden
and couldn't let go.
Hatred is never a solution.
Now I know
why you hated me.
I misjudged you.
There, you see,
hatred is never a good thing.
Mister, be assured,
I will take good care of Hugh.
I won't let you
lose another daughter.
I won't let myself lose her.
Lin, Lin Mo,
how is he?
Fu and I will go find him
and bring him here.
You need to solve this face to face,
the misunderstanding must be solved.
Lin Mo,
you listen to me.
your body won't be able to handle it
for long.
It's time to go home.
I don't care.
You still think Chi Yan is the murderer?
Fu told me.
Chi Yan and his grandpa
were nice to stray cats.
They used to feed those cats.
Chi Yan loves Hugh so much,
there's no way he killed her sister.
After all these years,
I've always wanted to go home.
This planet is so filthy and hypocritical.
But whenever I close my eyes,
I see her dying body
and there's nothing I can do.
I know you love her.
But what's more difficult than love
is to let go.
Lin Mo,
come visit Chi Yan with us.
Hugh.
Xiao Xiu!
Hugh, Hugh!
Xiao Xiu, calm down!
Xiao Xiu. Xiao Xiu!
Hugh, calm down!
I asked to see him.
I have something to tell him.
Then I also want to hear it.
What did the doctor say?
It's not a big deal.
Just need to stay here for a couple more days.
I stabbed you
while you were trying to save me.
I'm sorry.
You still think I did that,
right?
Back then, everyone believed
that I was the one who killed Hugh's sister.
Nobody tried to find out the truth,
or nobody cared
about the truth.
Now that I'm with Hugh,
believe it or not,
I want you to know,
I know how you feel.
I was just trying to protect Xiao Xui.
I didn't know...
Uncle Fu kept trying to help me let go.
He told me
that revenge would solve nothing.
But I just couldn't let go.
I have to find the murderer.
Then, even without doing anything,
I must have closure.
We'll help you find the murderer.
I'm sorry.
I used you for the cat seal.
The first time we met,
you reminded me of your sister a lot.
I didn't know
the two of you were sisters.
I will never forgive you
for what you did to Chi Yan.
But I know
what you did is  for my sister.
My sister's death is unfortunate.
But she was fortunate to meet you.
Thank you for loving her,
remembering her,
and trying to seek revenge for her.
But you don't have to be like this.
You can't stay here in human form
for a long time.
So, even if you return to the Meow Planet
and start a new life,
my sister would understand.
My sister is family,
I am obliged
to find that murderer.
Can you and your dad really let go?
How can we let go?
My mom and dad never talk about it.
But I can tell,
it's impossible for them to let go.
That's my sister.
But do you know
what's the biggest difference between you and us?
We try to live in the moment
and cherish everything we have.
We always try to protect our kind
from suffering like that.
When we die,
we turn into a star and fly up into the sky.
I
always believe
that the earth shares the same sky with
the Meow Planet.
That's why my sister
must be looking at us right now
somewhere in the sky.
Hugh,
take care of yourself.
What are you doing?
Did I wake you?
Stay here, let me.
What if your wound hurts?
I wanted to make you breakfast.
You don't know how to cook.
You can teach me.
Let me teach you.
I should just put it in, right?
Yes, also, break this egg.
Stir.
Silly,
nobody stirs like that.
Here, hold the chopsticks
like this.
Right, now stir.
I don't see the difference.
Yes, there is a difference.
Now, some salt.
Dad.
Mister.
What is it?
You told me that you don't want a third wheel.
So, I'm leaving.
Where are you heading?
Mister,
do you feel uncomfortable
living here?
I can find you another place.
Never mind.
I have things to do on the Meow Planet.
I can't stay here for too long.
Don't you want to spend more time with me?
You have no idea,
we have rules on our planet.
A cat should pay its benefactor on its own.
If I continue staying here,
my baby daughter
would never return home.
You,
you just want to go home
and eat those dried fish.
Nonsense,
these
are for your mom and our neighbours.
You just want to eat them yourself.
Bye.
Honey.
Darling.
I made it!
I, I made it.
Chi,
it's an emergency.
How many times did you throw up?
You know that I
have a problem with that thing.
But I really do like Mingming a lot.
I've thought this through.
It's time to get rid of it
once and for all.
Wait a second.
Which problem?
He has
a phobia about you know what.
He throws up
whenever he hears his girlfriend
say you know what.
You know what?
You know what means this.
It's...
Did Mingming
say anything about this?
She said that she is okay with this
and would like to keep dating.
But I want to give her happiness.
I will definitely solve this!
How?
By setting a thief to catch a thief.
Set a thief to catch a thief?
Dr. Xu,
here are the pills you asked for.
Thanks.
[Anti-nausea]
I can't rely on pills.
Li,
take these away.
Dr. Xu,
lunch?
No, I don't want to throw up.
A big dinner tonight?
A really big dinner.
That way, you should eat more.
Let's go!
[Marriage Registration]
This is too much.
If you are afraid of this,
how will you make Mingming happy?
I'm not scared.
Who said anything about being scared?
Are you ready?
Why are you here?
Divorce!
To get married!
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Three.
Two.
One.
Look.
Stop it.
It's him.
Xiao Xiu!
Stop!
Hello? Uncle Gao?
Someone's seen him done it again.
Stop it.
Okay.
Thank you.
It should be him.
He got bailed out.
It must be him.
Xiao Xiu,  just identified him.
He was obviously trying to get back at her.
If that's the case,
then it's more than
cats and cars.
But it should be fine, he has a record.
It shouldn't be hard to catch him.
Those guys probably
belong to a group.
we have to catch them all.
If not, there will be more cats
missing.
Yes, we need to catch them all.
Relax.
I've looked him up.
He has a complex background
and he is sneaky.
There's not much information about him.
I can ask Kebei to help.
He helped us find him last time,
I bet he can
find something on the internet
this time.
Fine, fine.
Just take some rest.
Don't move.
I'm sorry.
I was busy
with other patients.
Hi.
Hugh, how do you feel right now?
She should be fine.
Let me see the report.
Everything seems fine.
Just have some rest.
What?
Didn't the doctor tell you about her condition?
It's nothing to be worried about.
Why are you being so nervous?
We were just talking about
how to find the cat capturer.
Hugh got hurt because of him.
The cat capturer?
More cats are missing?
Haven't they caught him?
He was bailed out of prison.
So, we were trying to figure out
how to find
those who are like him
and arrest them together.
Sounds like a plan.
Again, if you need anything,
just come find me,
anytime.
Thanks a lot.
It's fine.
I'll see myself out
and check up on other patients.
Have some rest.
I'll walk you out.
It's okay, spend more time with her.
Bye.
Don't move.
Come on.
I need to take this.
Hello, sister.
Where are you?
I'm being super nice,
helping you walk Nietzsche.
When will you come home?
I'm at the hospital.
Hugh is hurt, I just visited her.
Is everything okay?
Sure, no need to worry.
She's just weak right now.
I should pay her a visit tomorrow.
Never mind, she'll be discharged from hospital
tomorrow.
No way,
Chi Yan is like a brother to me.
You are so eager to come to the hospital.
It's because of Dr. Luo, right?
Watch your tone.
This is called being active.
You made me sound like a pervert.
Enough with the nonsense,
hurry up and come home.
Bye.