[English subtitles are available.]
[Make a Wish]
[Ep02]
It must be the truest desire.
Make me rich overnight
Come on.
It's not working.
You think about it.
Your true feelings
and true desires.
You name it, I realize it.
OK. OK. OK.
Time traveling.
Where to?
Anywhere.
Okay.
Nothing.
Still nothing.
Did you really think about it?
You have to feel it here.
Deep down in your heart.
Think about it!
Immigration!
Immigration to Finland.
It's not working at all!
Have you really thought about it?
Making a wish is very sacred.
You must feel it here.
Come on!
Making wishes is sacred.
It has to come from the heart.
The license plate!
A plate of this city.
Seriously?
Nothing at all!
Have you seriously
made a wish at all?
Deep down.
Feel it.
I can't drive.
I don't have any wishes.
Give me a break.
Why don't you have wishes?
Human desires
are known to be inexhaustible.
Weird.
Haven't you heard of an exception?
No.
I have no desires,
or cravings.
I know that
you want to go home.
But your favors and wishes
are not working on me.
Maybe you should try another way.
But there's no other way.
I can only go home if you make a wish.
If you don't have a wish now,
I'll stay with you for a while
and wait till you have one.
No. No. No.
You can't stay with me.
I have to!
Don't move.
You can't live here.
Then make a wish.
Look.
I got it!
I wish that
you leave my house.
The truest desire?
The truest desire.
That's easy.
I'll leave now.
You lied!
That was not your true wish!
I have no wishes.
How dare you lie...
[Chi's Bookstore]
[How to tame a cat]
Spank your cat when they are naughty.
I want noodles,
like the one from yesterday.
No noodles.
Clean up the kitchen when you're done.
I'll clean it.
Be patient with bad-tempered cats
and pet them often.
Don't rub her the wrong way,
and give her treats.
Chi Yan,
I got the script.
Well done.
Your novel hits big recently.
Let's work on the next one.
Seize the day.
Got it.
Anything else?
I've got a new project.
Are you interested?
What project?
A sweet romance.
First Love Sweetheart, My Shy Little Master.
It's in a hurry, and we are shorthanded.
How about making some extra money?
Did you just meet me yesterday?
That's it.
I'll never write a sweet romance.
Get out.
If your favors
are built on others' pain,
then leave.
Open the door.
Please.
I will fix it.
Can you forgive me if I fixed it?
I know you are mad at me.
I can leave now.
But please tell me when you have a wish.
Otherwise, I can never go home.
Where are you going?
The streets,
a dump,
or under a bridge?
You can live here for a while.
Only for a while.
Do you know what that means?
Yes!
I will fix it!
Hi, everyone!
I'm Xu Zihao, the vet.
[Chi's Bookstore]
Today we're talking about pets.
Keeping a pet has so many benefits.
They can provide companionship
and pleasure.
Staying with pets
can increase our oxytocin levels,
and make us happier.
♫I wanna start an easy relationship with you♫
♫Every time I think of how cute you are♫
They can also help us reduce stress
and depression.
Research has found that
♫I just wanna spoil you so bad♫
the happiness brought by pets
helps secrete serotonin and dopamine,
thereby regulating mood disorders,
♫I can feel your presence♫
such as depression and autism.
♫So simple and easy♫
For people with poor social skills,
♫It feels so natural♫
pets can be helpful.
The understanding and sympathy for animals
are often transferred to people,
♫No more questions or doubts♫
resulting in the same understanding of
and care for people.
♫No need to guess your thoughts♫
Of course,
We also need to take good care of them,
♫I start to realize I can't live without you♫
such as preparing snacks
and comfortable beds.
♫Be my sweetheart, be my cutie♫
You can live here from now on.
♫I'll carry you in my pocket♫
♫And you'll accept me♫
♫A silly, naughty manchild♫
They can also help us exercise more.
♫You can't act out or be mean♫
For naughty pets,
we need to be patient with them.
♫I'll cuddle you so tight♫
Pets will force lazy folks to exercise,
♫Would you let me♫
and help people to socialize.
♫love you until the end♫
♫I wanna spoil you so bad♫
♫Hey, you. Look at me♫
Hugh.
You can read!
Looks like dried fish,
easy-peasy.
[An Exclusive Biography of Hugh Williams]
What about this word?
Wil...
Go on.
William.
What's this?
Report.
This one?
This one looks different.
Shakespeare.
The Complete Works of William Shakespeare.
So unfair.
Yan.
Who is she?
She is a friend,
who's staying at my store for a while.
Staying at yours?
Is he your relative?
No.
I come here to read.
I am Qin Liangliang.
Hi,
I am Bigili Bagilibu.
My name is
Bigili Bagilibu.
Liangliang.
Your favorite book, Possession,
I found one.
It's there.
Go read it.
It's okay, I can read at home.
Take it.
Plus,
One Hundred Years of Solitude.
Take both of them.
I can read at home, really.
You two go on.
I gotta read.
Remember our deal?
Don't do anything suspicious.
What are you doing?
But my name can only
be pronounced in cat language.
Just pick a name.
I know you can read.
Name...
What's your name?
Read.
My name is Chi Yan.
Chi Yan.
Sounds like eating salt.
With that dirty look,
you may become a smelly salted fish.
We are talking about your name.
Too hard, you pick a name for me.
I don't want to.
Yes, you do.
No, I don't.
Yes.
Yes, you do.
One more bite.
[Antiemetic]
Zihao.
I know it's hard for you.
But we've been dating for over three years.
My parents are giving me a lot of pressure.
You must decide today.
Lulu.
This medicine has a lot of side effects.
You wouldn't even do this for me?
Alright, I'll take it.
Zihao,
I've thought it through.
We can hold the wedding in my hometown.
My dad has so many friends.
Maybe 70 to 80 tables.
The finest hotel in my hometown
will be available in six months.
Before that,
We can go to Maldives or Greece
to take the pre-wedding photos.
The wedding dress has to be from Pronovias.
All my besties have got one,
so gorgeous.
Right,
The diamond ring has to be from Tiffany.
Didn't you take that medicine?
If my disease were to be cured,
why would I wait?
Sit down.
We must have it out today.
Xu Zihao, stop right there!
You are sick and afraid of marriage,
I can understand that.
But I have tolerated it long enough.
you can't make me do this forever.
Xu Zihao.
I am asking you!
Honey,
have dinner with me tonight?
[Dinner tonight?]
Bye, Miss.
See you.
Goodbye.
Bye, take care.
See you tomorrow.
You too.
Hi, Liangliang.
Have you got my text yet?
No, my phone was in my bag.
Let's eat together tonight.
We should celebrate my raise.
I'll pass, got a thing.
What thing?
Come out now. I'm at the gate.
Where are you now?
Your school.
I see your classmates coming out.
Where are you?
Are you at my school?
Why didn't you tell me in advance?
Why?
I can't come to your school?
No,
but you didn't come to the PTA meeting.
I am surprised.
I was busy.
If I don't work, we'll starve.
Class one, this way.
Sis,
which school did you go to?
Binhe No.1 Primary School.
What else?
Sister,
I am in junior high.
No, what?
Wait for me at the gate.
I will be right there.
That's fine.
I'm gone.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye.
See you.
See you, take care.
Good girl.
Still up?
This is so cool.
Good night.
Turn into a cat!
And don't come to my room.
I've made an important decision.
I know what my name will be.
Please call me Born in the Moonlight,
Valerie Edward II,
Mouse Buster, the Meow Planet's Guardian.
Too long.
No one has a name that long.
It's not.
I have deleted a lot.
OK.
It's your name.
Say my name.
No.
Say it.
Born in the Moonlight,
Valerie Edward II,
Mouse Guardian.
Mouse Buster.
the Meow Planet's
Guardian.
Again.
Born in the Moonlight, Valerie Edward II,
Mouse Buster,
the Meow Planet's Guardian.
You don't remember it.
I...
Then you must memorize it tomorrow.
OK.
Memorize it.
If you want to know someone's wishes,
you'll have to know their needs.
Maslow's hierarchy of needs theory
divides people's needs into five levels.
The first level of Maslow's hierarchy of needs
is physiological needs.
Second level,
safety needs.
Wait.
Beg me, beg me.
Help! Help!
Make a wish.
Mouse Buster.
Cat Planet's Gua...
Help me!
Third level,
Love and belonging needs.
In the pyramid of needs,
at the bottom of the needs pyramid
lies physiological and safety needs.
After those needs are met,
humans begin to pursue the spiritual pleasure
obtained in interpersonal communication.
The strongest pleasure among them
is the satisfaction brought by love.
As a foodie,
how can I not go to the market often?
Now I’m going to teach you
how to choose particularly succulent,
fresh raw prawns.
What is this, Uncle Fu?
Everyone seems to have one.
This is a phone.
In this society,
human beings cannot survive without it.
This...
This is a filter.
It's not real.
I don't understand.
We finally become human and come here.
But they want to become cats.
I just got a human name.
Listen up.
OK.
My name is Born in the Moonlight,
Valerie Edward II,
Mouse Buster, the Meow Planet's Guardian.
Human names are very short
and mainly used for addressing.
Most names are simple and nice
or mean something.
Yours is too long.
Had I returned his favor,
I wouldn't be worrying about names.
What's wrong?
Having trouble returning his favor?
He said he has no desires.
He's not interested in anything.
I can never go home with him being like this.
A human without any desires.
It's very rare.
Uncle Fu,
what is the most important need for humans
in interpersonal relationships?
I read it in a book.
It says it's...
Love.
But what's that?
Interpersonal relationships include family,
friends and lovers.
But for humans,
love is the most important one.
Love.
What's love?
For humans, love is probably
the nervous but exciting feeling
a single man feels
when he sits in front of a girl he likes.
He won't know where to look.
He'll also blush,
and his heart will race.
Chemistry and stuff.
Then how do I get him...
To sit in front of her?
It'll happen if they meet each other.
If they haven't met yet,
do everything to make sure they meet.
Hmm...
In one word,
it's called fate.
Fate?
Chi Yan, are you going out?
Chi Yan.
How old are you?
I'm two years old. What about you?
Chi Yan.
Twenty-six.
Twenty-six?
And you're still single?
No wonder you're so grumpy all the time.
[Human Desires]
[Spring Mud Flower Club]
Hello.
How can I help you?
May I ask if you know how to cook?
How to cook?
I'm from the bookstore next door.
Could you cook a meal for Chi Yan?
Chi Yan.
And you are?
I'm a guest staying with him.
A guest...
As far as I know,
Chi lives by himself.
Would you like him to live alone?
May I ask why you're staying with him?
He saved my life.
I must follow him.
Sounds like he's a nice guy.
He's super nice.
So, could you cook a meal for him?
But why me? Why do I have to do it?
Because he just reads books all day,
and he doesn't cook at all.
He's either staring at books
or the other thing...
What thing?
The...
What?
The computer!
He owns a bookstore.
It's normal that he reads a lot.
But if he doesn't cook,
you can cook for him.
I don't know how to cook.
I wanna have some fish.
You haven't answered my question yet.
I do know how to cook, but...
Great. Then let's go!
Alright.
I'll teach you how to cook.
But will it upset him
if we go to his place?
Nah, it should be fine.
Chi Yan probably likes fish too.
Also if he gets mad at you,
just say you're here to teach me how to cook.
Alright. It's a deal.
I'll teach you.
But I still haven't got your name.
My name is...
I'll tell you next time.
Okay.
What's your name?
I'm He Meng.
He Meng.
Can I call you Meng?
Of course.
Any flowers you like?
Take some.
Cool.
This one.
Alright. Take it.
Your bubble tea is ready.
Stop.
Stop right there.
Excuse me.
Where is it?
Where is what?
Don't move.
Get up.
Get up now.
Where is it?
I don't know.
Thank you, Journalist.
You're welcome.
Stand up straight.
Don't move!
What are you doing?
Don't move.
Officers,
it's here.
What's here?
What's this?
Eh...
It's not mine.
I don't know why I have it.
Officer,
let me explain.
It's not mine.
I don't know why it's on me.
Stop making excuses.
You can talk later at the police station.
Let's go.
Gentle. You're hurting me.
Right.
You need to come with us for a statement.
Thank you.
Alright.
It wasn't me.
Please make a bubble tea for me.
My colleague will pay later.
Thanks!
I didn't take it.
Let's go.
Chi Yan.
Hello.
Anything wrong?
Nothing!
She's here to cook for us.
The kitchen is upstairs. I'll show you.
Don't worry!
Just wait and we'll cook a delicious meal.
Right,
do you guys eat spicy food?
You can try it later.
We do.
What's wrong?
Be careful.
Headache.
Sit down.
Here.
Careful.
Besides the headache,
any other discomfort?
Not really.
Any medicine in the house?
I'll go get it.
Yeah, it's in the storage room.
Alright.
That way. On the left.
Okay, wait for me.
I'll be right back.
He Meng.
What are you doing?
She's having a headache,
so I came here to get some medicine.
There is no medicine here.
What are you doing?
Open the door!
Now you can feel the chemistry.
Open the door.
You two enjoy your time there.
No need to thank me.
Open the door now.
Let us out.
Hurry.
Right.
Open the door please.
It's too crowded here.
Let us talk outside.
Meng.
The fish you made is amazing.
It's not funny.
Open the door.
Open the door!
Stop this nonsense!
I wanna use the bathroom.
I can't hold it.
Let me out.
Hold it!
Hurry up.
I'm not in the mood for this!
What are you doing?
It's dangerous! Don't...
Please open the door.
Let me out.
Open the door now.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Eh...
Careful.
Be careful!
What's wrong with these two?
Stop right there!