[English subtitles are available]
[Make a Wish]
[Episode 13]
You're awake.
Good morning
How's the headache?
You took care of me all night?
It's fine.
I'll make you breakfast.
Take some rest.
Be careful. It's hot.
Good?
Take your time.
I need to tell you something when you finish it.
What is that?
You should eat more.
I'm full.
Xiao Xiu.
Recently, many stray cats disappeared.
Right?
Are they dead or alive now?
None of us knows.
So you may also be in danger.
So...
So you should go home.
Leave here.
The sooner, the better.
Do you like me?
No.
I told you so.
How can it be?
You take care of me,
protect me, and care about me.
So,
You lied.
You are wrong.
You got it wrong.
Ever since I met you,
I've found you troublesome.
I feel the same way to this day.
So taking care of you
is just to save me some trouble.
OK, then.
It's easy to let me go.
Make a wish.
Then I'll leave,
and never coming back.
I wish,
that Xiao Xiu goes back to the Meow Planet
and will never be in danger.
Coward. Big liar.
When I was in the Meow Planet,
my neighbor was a Maltese cat.
Speaking of this breed,
since the Egyptians
regarded them as gods in ancient times,
they've never got out of that character.
It took me over ten years being their neighbor,
to finally receive some reaction
when I said hello.
Why are you telling me this?
I just wanted to say that
your Chi Yan
is much nicer than this kind of cat.
You are such a spoiled girl,
and he can bear you for so long.
It's really not easy.
What are you talking about?
I'm telling you he is a big liar.
Uncle Fu.
He obviously likes me.
Why didn't he admit it?
For human beings,
affection is not just staying together,
rubbing necks, licking fur like us cats.
It means that
you'll have to share the pain
and sorrow of the other half,
and face the difficulties together.
Never leave,
and always help each other.
There is a huge responsibility
behind the word "like".
I think Chi Yan values ​​this very seriously,
so he didn't admit it easily.
Yo... You...
You'll speak for him anyway.
Why are you giving me this?
Because I think that's good with butter, too.
Butter it for me, please.
If you have nothing to do, go away.
Don't sigh at my place.
I don't have anything to do.
But you do.
I'm worried for you.
I didn't ask you to do that.
It has nothing to do with me.
Bro,
page 137 of that book,
you've been reading that for 20 minutes.
Can you stop being stubborn?
She told you her feelings!
And you finally get an admirer.
What's holding you back?
You two should be together!
This can't be solved
impulsively like you always do.
Impulsively?
If Qin Mingming did the same to me,
I would be so high.
She is a girl.
And she took action.
But you are so cold.
No matter how carefree she is,
she'll feel hurt. I'm telling you.
I...
You don't understand.
Stop. Stop.
I'm exhausted.
Let me find someone for you.
Chi Yan.
What are you...
Coach Wu was my classmate in college.
He told me you were practicing kendo here.
So I came here to play against you.
Don't be merciful.
fine.
Good coordination.
But too slow.
Again.
Did you throw the game?
Nope.
Come on.
Are you scared?
Too slow!
Again.
Come again.
Slow.
One more.
You let me win.
I didn't.
You are so strong.
I thought
it would be awkward for us to meet again.
Didn't see this coming.
Thank you
for giving me this opportunity
to defeat the person who rejected me.
Before now,
I used to think
if I told you my feelings
in high school,
would things be different for us?
Of course,
although it took me ten years to say it,
I don't feel sorry.
I have no regrets.
Have you heard of
the Salzburg Bough?
No.
What's that?
Something created by a writer.
He wrote that,
in the salt mines near Salzburg, Austria,
Miners would throw a leafless wintry bough
into the abandoned workings
When the miners pick it up in two or three months,
the bough will be covered with
a shining deposit of crystals.
Even the tiniest twigs become
scintillating and dazzling.
The original bough is no longer recognizable.
It's actually the same as being in love.
The man in your fantasy
is cast with a charming light.
But it's just a leafless,
ordinary bough.
Someone compares himself to a
tree branch to comfort me.
Mingming.
Rather than telling you that I'm sorry,
I hope you can come out of the past.
I also hope you don't blame me
because all I can say to you now is comfort.
I get to listen to Chi Yan talking so much
and so long,
I feel like it's a win.
OK.
Enough about me.
What about you?
What about me?
I can see that
you like Xiao Xiu, right?
In the game,
if you don't take the initiative,
you will never have a chance to win.
One more game?
Sure.
Lin Mo.
Are you on the day shift too?
It was a busy week.
I'm finally free.
♫Happy birthday to you♫
Lin Mo, happy birthday.
Why didn't you tell me about your birthday?
How's that?
Surprised?
I...
I saw it on the employee registration form.
Today is your birthday.
Happy birthday.
I don't celebrate birthdays.
I'll blow it for him.
What's wrong?
Why don't you celebrate your birthday?
Today is not my birthday.
Then why does the form say
today is your birthday?
Confess.
What are you hiding?
Who are you?
Today is a very important day for me.
A very important day?
Isn't that your birthday?
Or date of death.
Date of death?
The girl who died.
That...
Do you...
want to talk to me?
Actually, I don't know
when my birthday is.
The reason why I chose today
is that this day
has a special meaning to me.
This is the day I met her.
Slow it down.
When I see you,
you always remind me of her.
But didn't you say that
we are not that alike?
I know.
You are two completely different people.
But sometimes when I see you
I can't help but think about her.
But I don't want to face
the fact that she is gone.
It's like a thorn in your hand.
It hurts if you pull it out or press it in.
I have a thing. Gotta go.
Isn't that contradictory?
Xiao Xiu.
Hi.
Excuse me,
is Xiao Xiu here?
She worked the day shift today,
and had already left with Lin Mo.
What's wrong?
When?
About
five or six pm.
What's the matter?
Do you have Lin Mo's number?
Yeah.
You called me?
Where is Xiao Xiu?
How did you have my number?
I'm asking you. Where is she?
You should know that.
We're having dinner together,
She said she got a thing and left suddenly.
I found this coat
in an alley.
Did you drink?
Yeah.
What?
She can't drink.
Search together.
Hurry up!
Search different places!
Hello?
I'm here.
Rest assured.
If you find this girl
please call this number.
Thank you.
OK. Fine.
Hello?
Where are you?
I walked the dog to your house.
I knocked for ages, but nobody's in.
I can't find Xiao Xiu.
Her phone turned off.
What?
When did this happen?
Could it be she playing somewhere
and the phone is dead?
She...
She never does that.
A lot of drugged cat food
is placed in the green belt of the block.
And this photo.
Look.
Even in residential buildings.
These are places where
there are many stray cats.
But there isn't much drug.
If they just sprinkled it like this.,
no one will find out.
Hello?
Wait there.
I'll be right there.
Don't be too worried.
She can't go too far in a while.
Hello, got anything?
I've searched the neighborhood,
but nobody saw her.
Chi Yan.
Any news?
We can't keep searching like this.
Maybe you should go home.
She might have come home.
If not,
I will ask my friends at the radio station tomorrow
to send out a message of missing people, okay?
No.
If something really happened to her,
the later we find her,
the more danger she faces.
I must find her tonight.
But,
no one's in the bookstore now.
What if she comes home?
If so, why didn't she contact me?
Enough.
You guys worked hard tonight.
You should go home.
I'll keep looking.
Bro.
Calm down.
It'll be meaningless
if you keep looking without a clue.
Think about it.
Does she have any friends?
Is there any place
where she might stay over?
There is no such place!
Wait a sec.
Xiao Xiu has a friend.
City...
[City Market]
Thanks.
I will jump when I get there.
How is it, Uncle Fu?
Every resident of the Meow Planet
has an odor as a signal.
Sig...
But there is no Xiu's odor
in this area.
Food stalls.
The community garden.
The beerhouse.
We've looked everywhere.
Where can she be?
I'm going to ask other people of my kind
to search more places.
Don't worry.
We'll find her.
Hello.
Where does this ship go?
To Tongye Island.
What island?
Hello?
Chi Yan.
Xiao Xiu.
What happened to you?
Are you okay?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Chi Yan.
Where are you now?
I am on the sea.
The sea?
Why are you at sea?
I'm in a boat.
I don't know.
I got in a car,
and it was full of cabbage.
I thought,
when I get to the city, I will jump out of the car.
And then I fell asleep.
I fell asleep and then...
I woke up in the middle of the sea
A boat
took away all the vegetables.
It's fine.
Calm down.
You...
Do you know the specific location?
Location.
Tell us.
Specific...
Where am I?
We are heading to Tongye Island.
We'll be there in about half an hour.
We have half an hour.
Chi Yan.
Tongye Island is not far away.
We're going there right now.
OK. OK. OK.
No worries.
When you get ashore,
find somewhere safe and contact me.
Uncle Fu and I will pick you up by boat now.
Don't worry.
Hi.
To Tongye Island?
Can't go.
Hello.
To Tongye Island?
No, no.
Hi.
That's it.
I want you to meet someone.
Come.
Why are you so late?
Come and sit here.
Look at the menu.
What do you want? Are you hungry?
How about some tea?
Are you going to go fishing at night?
It's not gonna happen.
We were going to go to the island.
But there are huge waves.
The boat can't get out of the sea.
Will no one go to sea in this little rain?
No. No. No.
I...
A kid in my family wanted to take a ride,
but she somehow went to the island.
In the middle of the night,
it's so dangerous
for a girl.
I want to pick her up, but I can't.
You have to wait till tomorrow morning.
Master, master.
The girl he's talking about...
To me...
She...
She is very important to me.
Tonight,
I have to find her tonight.
So please,
help us.
So you guys are here for my boat.
Sorry, but yes.
To be honest,
we've been to the pier just now.
The weather is terrible,
so no one is willing to go out to the sea.
The girl we are talking about
is kind of silly
and afraid of water.
Now she is on the sea alone.
We have no choice but to ask you.
Please help us.
You young people
are always troublesome.
All right, let's go!
Thanks a lot.
Thank you.
Go. Go. Go.
Let's hurry up.
Uncle Fu.
What?
The weather is bad now.
You stay here.
I'll go with the master.
I know my ways around the sea.
It's okay.
You. You.
You stay here
and look after my shop for me.
They're going on a date.
Do you want to join them?
Let's go.
Alright.
Wait for me, Uncle Fu.
Tell me when you find her.
Hello?
Hello.
Hi.
May I ask that
if there is a girl next to you?
Yeah. Yeah.
Please put her on the phone.
Miss.
There's a phone call.
It's for you.
Thanks.
Hello?
Xiao Xiu.
I'll be there soon.
Wait for me.
Don't go anywhere. I'm coming.
Master.
Is it there?
♫The wishes♫
♫will come true one day♫
♫The fates♫
♫will be written in our way♫
♫Walking around the world holding hands♫
♫Even if the past is forgotten♫
♫The wishes♫
♫will be fulfilled by you♫
♫The fates♫
♫won't be stranded in love♫
♫I will celebrate every day with you♫
♫by your side♫
♫All the way to the farthest♫
♫I heard the sail of love♫
♫won't dock easily♫
♫Shout hard♫
♫until you hear the answer♫
♫We rush to the beach♫
♫Look at the blue in the distance♫
♫we have already been♫
♫implied by love♫
♫The wishes♫
♫will come true one day♫
♫The fates♫
♫will be written in our way♫
♫Walking around the world holding hands♫
♫Even if the past is forgotten♫
♫The wishes♫
♫will be fulfilled by you♫
♫The fates♫
Have you caught a cold?
♫won't be stranded in love♫
Here.
Drink it.
♫I will celebrate every day with you♫
♫by your side♫
♫All the way to the farthest♫
What's this?
Ginger tea.
Drink it so that you won't catch a cold.
I've been looking for you all night.
Don't you want to tell me
what happened tonight?
I accidentally drank Lin Mo's beer.
Then I felt like
something was wrong.
So many people there.
I panicked.
So I ran, covering my ears.
I didn't expect so many people
on that street at night.
I thought maybe it's better to turn into a cat.
I went into that alley and turned into a cat
After that,
I want to hide my clothes.
Suddenly a net fell from the sky.
And then...
I was unconscious.
Take another sip.
What about that person's face?
Did you see that?
Nope.
He wore a mask and a hat the whole time.
I can't see anything.
Where did he catch you?
Can you recall anything?
Are there any landmark buildings nearby?
There seems to be a farmhouse.
There are a lot of instruments and cages inside.
And there are cats in those cages.
OK. Let's drop it now.
The fact that you were taken away tonight,
only Uncle Fu and I know about it.
You must remember that
when we meet Xu Zihao and others tomorrow,
don't mention it.
Because they don't know that you are...
Thank god I got you back.
Otherwise,
I can't forgive myself for the rest of my life.
Xiao Xiu.
I'm sorry.
You had to suffer this today.
I promise you,
every day from now on,
I'll be with you.
I will try as I may to protect you.
I won't let you get hurt again.
I like you.
You know that?
Before I met you,
I've always been a coward.
Really.
It's like I've been running away.
My time seems to have stopped in the past.
I ran away from the people I meet,
and things happen to me.
I couldn't laugh from my heart,
nor could I cry with abandon.
I couldn't do anything.
I feel like,
I am the only one left in this world.
Those who I loved and who loved me
were gone one by one.
So from that moment, I started thinking,
since you are all leaving someday,
then I won't be attached to you in the first place.
Then, I met you.
When I first saw you,
I thought this girl is acting like crazy.
Jumping up and down every day.
Causing new troubles every day.
Here and there, non-stop.
I need to pay attention to you,
look after you and protect you.
But as time goes by,
I gradually found that,
it's not you need me,
but I need you.
When we are about to be together,
The disappearance of stray cats
happened in the neighborhood.
I was thinking at that time,
this is enough.
See,
I have the bookstore left by my grandpa,
stories that I want to write,
friends who treat me like a family,
and you by my side,
trusting and supporting me unconditionally.
That should be enough.
I shouldn't be greedy anymore.
Why?
Because it's useless to be greedy.
Because...
What if things get worse
because of your greed?
I feel like I know
what you are talking about.
It's like...
I used to go fishing with my sister.
We were so happy
when we caught big ones.
But after the happy moment,
I started to worry.
What if the big fish escaped?
I feel like you are doing the same thing.
In the face of sudden happiness,
we can be terrified.
Maybe.
On the way to find you with Uncle Fu,
here was a moment I was thinking,
I was wrong.
I cannot be more wrong.
Compared to the pain of your leaving,
I'm more afraid of you disappearing.
Those fears and cowardice
that I told you before,
and my sadness and misery
since childhood,
those are all very lame
and selfish excuses.
I should be more courageous.
I should face the world bravely.
I should view the world with colors.
So thank you, Xiao Xiu.
You made me not afraid.
You make me brave.
I want to be with you till the end of my life.