What?
Wait, are you firing me?
The agency said Teddy Merry
has to be dudes-only to debut.
Our sound is aggressive, right?
The band's got an image, you know?
I can change my image!
I'll dye my hair.
- Shave my brows!
- So annoying.
There's something I don't like
about your sound to begin with.
It's too heavy.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Please don't run!
Please don't run, it's dangerous!
This is an announcement
from the organizers.
Due to bad weather,
we must cancel today's live concert.
What?!
- Are you kidding me?
- I'm sorry!
Bullshit!
To everyone who came,
please be careful as you leave.
Please walk slowly
without pushing those in front of you.
The floor is slippery, so be careful.
Hurry up!
- Please walk slowly.
- Hey, let's go.
Please be careful and keep moving forward.
There's no problem in walking slowly…
Please walk straight to the exit.
Please don't run.
Slowly, please.
The exit is that way.
Please watch your step.
Walk slowly without running.
That girl is crazy.
There was only sound there.
The rain, the scenery…
and even me.
The boundaries between everything blurred,
and I realized
I was born to meet this sound.
I'm sure this sound…
was a gift from the gods.
BAND MEMBERS WANTED!
Okay, that's good. Thank you.
That's enough. Thank you very much.
Well, that's all for today's audition.
We'll contact you later with the result.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
GRAB YOUR DREAM
Hello?
Is this Akane Saijo?
Thank you for coming to our audition
earlier today.
Yes.
Well, let's see.
Unfortunately, we can't accept you
this time.
Huh?
If you'll excuse me.
Excuse me.
AUDITION: LAST CHANCE
MUST PASS!!!
What was wrong with me?
Well…
Your drumming can't see its surroundings.
It lacks sensitivity.
Okay, then.
Hello, this is Vermilion.
Akane, can I ask you to do a delivery?
Sure.
Here. They specifically requested
that you deliver this.
- They requested me?
- Yeah.
Oh, right. Listen.
I heard from one
of my fellow writer friends
that Sho Takaoka is forming a band.
Huh? With who?
Naoki Fujitani.
Naoki Fujitani?
That guy who was struck by lightning
at the festival three years ago.
Nobody knew where he went after that
so I wondered how he was doing,
but who would have thought
he would be forming a band.
Is something wrong?
Huh?
- You know…
- Yes?
I failed the audition, after all.
Right.
Thank you for supporting me
so much until now.
Are you giving up?
Yes.
I had decided today was the last one.
Are you sure?
You know, I…
I gave it my all these three years.
Yeah.
That's why…
I have no regrets.
I see.
Even now, at this very moment,
many new sounds are being born,
and many people are taking them in.
The dream that has been
ringing in my heart
is about to disappear
without anyone knowing.
Excuse me.
Huh?
Is that my name?
Why?
What?
TO AKANE SAIJO:
I'M BUSY WITH SOMETHING, SO PLEASE COME IN
I've been searching for this sound
for a long time.
I've longed for this sound.
The sound…
I kept looking for…
is now…
Who are you?
Oh, the curry…
Sho Takaoka.
Yes?
Oh, I'm not someone suspicious!
I came to deliver curry!
I see, it's you.
Naoki.
Mr. Naoki Fujitani.
Sho Takaoka is forming a band.
Huh? With who?
Naoki Fujitani.
The Amadeus of the rock industry
who debuted as a composer at 14 years old.
Oh, we've lost him.
He won't hear a word now.
What's that? It wasn't that kind of song.
Oh, you didn't like it?
But then, the keyboards won't work.
Yeah. That's why…
- Well?
- I see.
Well,
in that case.
You can go crazier, Kazushi.
Crazier.
Sho!
What?
- To finish…
- Yeah?
Just for four bars, cover it
with a 0.2-millimeter thin veil.
Like a lemon-flavored candy,
not too sweet.
Oh, okay.
- Nice.
- Yeah, it's not bad.
What about the drums?
Like this, I think.
Four sounds that should never have met.
The mysterious and elusive genius
behind countless hit songs,
Naoki Fujitani.
A top-tier support guitarist
for superbands in Japan and abroad,
Sho Takaoka.
The music maverick
who went viral as a lone track maker,
Kazushi Sakamoto.
And me, an unknown drummer
on the verge of a broken dream,
Akane Saijo.
Led by Naoki Fujitani,
four sounds have come together
and now begin to play a single story.
Well, that's it for today. Thank you.
Hey!
Just how sleepy are you?
You were sleeping like a log in class,
which must mean
that you were out last night.
Yeah, they didn't let me sleep all night.
What?
My body hurts everywhere.
Hold up, Akane.
That's a world far too adult.
How can they so casually dump
whatever they say "won't work"?
Oh, a smash-and-dash?
The song we wrote.
- Huh?
What? You got invited
to join Sho Takaoka's band?
Yeah.
Huh? Why you?
I don't know.
Well, that must mean someone was watching
how hard you've been working.
Yeah.
So, what kind of person is
that Naoki Fujitani?
What kind?
- Huh?
- What?
Excuse me.
Oh.
It's Akane.
Where are you going?
Where? I'm on my way
to help with the café.
Is that urgent?
Huh?
This is so interesting.
I picked it up earlier.
Right?
You're right!
Um…
Hey.
Where are we going?
Oh, right.
Sorry.
I'm no good.
Right now, my head was in composer mode.
Once this happens, my memory blurs.
Ordinary stuff, common sense…
everything becomes so difficult.
Must be hard on you.
Welcome.
Hello.
I'm Kai, the manager.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, Miyako, this is Akane Saijo,
who will play the drums with us--
Of course not.
The agency knew Fujitani on vocals
and Takaoka on guitar
would generate plenty of buzz.
The plan was to rely on backing tracks
or session musicians.
But you went and forced Kazushi
into the mix.
Still, we said marketing him
as a "rising star"
and the group as a three-man band
could also work.
It's how we finally got
the record label on board with it.
Now you want to tell them
you're adding a total amateur girl?
The concept, the project, and everything
will have to be redone from scratch.
Is that the only problem?
Did you really hear what I just said?
I really did.
But listen,
with the agency's current strategy,
I'm saying we'll only sell
"moderately well" at best.
That's why I'm preparing in my own way,
to make sure we blow up big.
I know that I'm not wrong.
I understand what you want to say, Naoki.
Telling the big shots, "Don't worry,
I'm confident," won't cut it.
Anyone can say what they want.
So we just need to show results.
Yeah. Nice. Let's do that.
Huh?
Hey, wait, please!
Ms. Saijo.
Yes?
Let me just say one thing.
The sound of a genius
brings misery to ordinary people.
- What?
- The concert is in a week, okay?
Hey, Sensei, just wait a moment.
That's different from the original plan.
What was the original plan?
Um…
Well, whatever.
But why do we suddenly have to play
on an outdoor stage
in front of 3,000 people?
I happened to come across
a last-minute booking at the Yaon,
right before my eyes.
Pretty shit gig, if you ask me.
Do you think so?
I mean, opening for OVER CHROME?
Are you for real?
And in just a week? That's impossible.
What about the songs?
This is the song.
Here.
Yours.
You too, Akane.
I'll finish one more song quickly
and bring it to the rehearsal.
- You guys prep for the show.
- But--
You may be fine, but…
what about her?
Stop.
The sound is too rigid. Again.
One more time.
Okay.
That's mine.
Sorry.
Surely, if a cup is this distinct,
you'd assume it's not yours to use.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for the wait.
- Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
What?
Okay.
Yes. I'm sorry.
Good.
When he's focused,
he doesn't even notice the temperature.
I see.
Are you talking about the fourth bar here?
Yes, don't bounce there.
Like figure skating, keep an edge.
Of course.
Akane, you added some arrangements
to that part, right?
What? Did I really?
Yes, it was different from the music.
But that was better. So play your version.
- Incredible. That was so cool.
- Wow!
You must be a pro.
Oh, no.
Oh…
Here you go.
I've never heard
such a cool version of "Für Elise."
Thanks.
You're amazing, Kazushi.
Sensei and Sho are truly amazing as well.
You all completely change
when you play your instruments.
You all feel beyond my reach right now.
I totally agree with you.
What?
Your sound lacks sensitivity.
It drags around the surrounding sounds.
A drummer unaware of their surroundings?
That's fatal.
If you feel we're beyond your reach,
then step down. Please.
I…
don't like your sound.
NAOKI
Yeah, this is the brand-new era
Yeah, what do you wanna scream?
Come on
Kick up a fuss and switch it up
Disastrous, it's a furious turbulence
Play a deep, deep, deep and killer tune
Ignite a mental fire like a fool
Damn it! Damn it!
Dummies all around me
Be crazy, crazy!
It's our brand-new era
Damn it! Damn it!
Expose the dark around me
I don't need no love or dreams, okay?
Now shake off any doubt
Ain't no good or evil here
With your…
Sensei.
…turn the dark to radiance
Embrace the voice you always believed in
Hey, turbulence
Get me, get me higher!
I'm looking through the shadows for a sign
The memories I ripped from my mind
You who felt the same pain, been maligned
Stand together now and bring the fight
Kick up a fuss and switch it up
Disastrous, it's a furious turbulence
Play a deep, deep, deep and killer tune
Ignite a mental fire like a fool
Damn it! Damn it!
Dummies all around me
Be crazy, crazy!
It's our brand-new era
Damn it! Damn it!
Expose the dark around me
Give it to me
I'll devour your scream
Great work tonight.
Toya, don't bring trouble here, please.
He's the one causing it.
What? Are you planning to disrupt
our Yaon show?
But you said okay, right?
Thanks, I'm looking forward to it.
Sure. So you're not going to complain
even if OVER CHROME wrecks you guys, huh?
That's fine.
Fans will stick with whoever they like.
But I have no intention
of fighting with you, Toya.
It just happens to be like that this time.
I just
want to play my own music.
You can easily do that.
You alone are enough.
Stop playing these boring band games.
I don't want to.
Hey, you.
What? Yes.
Are you confident?
What?
Guarantee that his music
won't be destroyed because of you.
I'm asking if you have that resolve.
Answer me.
You can't answer me.
No.
That's not true.
It's true
that I don't have confidence right now.
But…
I have ambition.
Huh?
I mean, music is just sound
created in a moment.
So about the guarantee
and my determination--
Huh?
Whatever.
We'll completely wreck you guys.
Excuse me.
Sensei.
Hello.
Oh, Akane? It's me, Sho.
Yes.
Naoki isn't back.
Do you know where he went?
It's true
that I don't have confidence right now.
Huh?
Hello?
I might have made him angry.
Huh?
Because I couldn't say I was confident.
Sensei!
Sensei, are you okay?
Sensei.
Sensei!
- Are you--
- Wow, I got it.
Oh, wait. It's Akane.
What are you doing here?
What are you doing at a place like this?
What?
A song has been floating around
in my head recently.
I just completed it. Even the arrangement.
It's a masterpiece.
I thought I might die
and leave this piece as my final work.
So you weren't angry?
Why?
Wait, did you just forget
what happened before and after?
Oh…
I might have.
I went to Toya's concert today.
Wait.
Why am I with you, Akane?
What a relief.
I'm sorry.
About Miyako.
And Toya as well.
They have no idea about your sound.
They only talk about what is external.
Like your position, age, and career.
Those are powerless
against the actual sound we make.
For me,
if such bias gets in our way,
I'd rather make an even bolder move
and shake up what's conventional.
But… I'm glad you have ambition.
So you do remember.
That's good enough for now.
Someday in the future,
tell me you're confident.
We'll definitely
achieve something amazing.
Yes.
Wow, that was impressive.
A relentlessly provoking,
sadistic drum beat.
Akane brought us that sound.
- Sensei!
- What?
Is he okay?
He's okay.
Open the door, Kazushi.
Thanks.
Naoki.
Listen to me, Naoki.
I won't let you leave me.
I said to wait!
Are you doing okay, Akane?
Yes. I'm totally fine.
You're tough and cool.
It's like my only strength.
That day,
your drumming made it resonate again.
I hadn't even realized it had been broken.
The precious sound inside me
that had gone silent.
Some sounds can't be made alone.
That's the sound I'm searching for.
That's why I went to see Sho.
And I found Kazushi.
I searched for you, Akane.
I was called
by your sound.
The instruments are ready.
On in five.
Okay.
OPENING ACT: FUJITANI BAND
Band members, standby.
Akane,
let's do it.
Yes.
Oh my gosh. I'm super excited.
- Huh?
- Who's that?
- There's an opening act today?
- Never heard of them.
Who is it?
A new band? We don't need you.
Wait. Isn't that Sho Takaoka?
Why is he here? Just helping out?
- What?
- It's a surprise.
What the hell?
You look like a corpse.
Oh, it's Toya. You look cool as usual.
At the very least, act cool.
Otherwise, it's no fun wrecking you guys.
I got it.
Just watch.
I'll turn it into a legendary performance.
Who just came?
It's Mr. Isagi, the producer.
Excuse me. May I check your pass?
No, no. It's okay.
- Forgive us.
- This way, please.
Actually, today,
I'll be watching from the audience.
What?
It's my precious friend's
first live performance.
Then this way, please.
Please.
Is OVER CHROME not coming out yet?
Get Mahiro out! Mahiro!
Toya!
- The drummer seems out of place.
- Can you really play?
I told you this was going to happen.
Get OVER CHROME on stage now!
How long are you making us wait?
Enough already.
- We didn't ask for you.
- Go home!
Come on. OVER CHROME!
The fear of not being wanted by anyone.
It is similar to the fear I have felt
since I started playing music.
But I'm not afraid anymore.
Because I know
that I was wanted
by his sound.
Nice to meet you guys. We're TENBLANK.
TENBLANK…
On guitar,
Sho Takaoka.
On keyboard,
Kazushi Sakamoto.
On drums,
Akane Saijo.
On bass and vocals…
Naoki Fujitani.
Subtitle translation by: Emily Noguchi