♪That day♪
♪Nothing stays together forever♪
♪I've quit romance♪
♪Who hasn't failed again♪
♪Crying in death♪
♪And in life♪
♪Even now♪
♪We keep learning♪
♪It's no surprise♪
♪Being happy is so hard♪
♪Weirdly, I became a role model♪
♪On the day we met again, we said hi♪
♪It was a reminder,
a test, and a complaint♪
♪Who can do anything without regret♪
♪I am all right♪
♪May you live in peace♪
♪Let the world roar♪
♪Sounds like a carnival♪
♪Being alive is never dull♪
♪How wonderful to be free♪
♪I became even better without you♪
♪Nothing can be perfect♪
♪We bless each other in pain♪
♪We nod and smile♪
♪May we both be well♪
= Love's Ambition=
=Episode 27=
Chen Lin.
What do you think of me?
You're kind,
wise,
open-minded,
visionary, magnanimous,
and calm in crisis.
Am I Mr. Shen of Jinda Group,
or Shen Haoming?
Well...
What's the difference?
Mr. Shen,
I have a suggestion.
We're going to invest
in cultural tourism
in Gubei Town, right?
You take Haochen there every year.
The environment is excellent.
Give yourself
some days off.
I have so much work.
Why not set aside
the business for now?
I heard they're
hosting some folk festival there.
There's local food,
local handicrafts,
and botanical dyeing workshops.
It's so lively.
Take over the company affairs.
I'll be on a business trip.
I understand.
We'll get back to you after
re-evaluation.
Okay, talk later.
Yan.
(Paid Promotion Plan)
Here is
my paid promotion plan.
I plan to upload six to eight
original videos across platforms.
(After sale)
In one to two hours after posting,
if the completion rate,
likes, and comments look good,
we'll go for
paid promotions.
Alright.
Do as you say. Let me see.
Got it, Yan.
I'm off then.
Okay.
Yan,
take a look and sign this.
Right.
Mr. Zhang from Gubei Town called to ask
when you're visiting.
I forgot.
Sorry, I was swamped.
No worries.
Take a break.
Consider this field trip
a vacation.
Stop bottling things up.
Okay?
If everything goes smoothly
with this new episode, I'll go.
I'll leave the work to you.
Okay.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Your signature.
Okay.
(Signed by Party B: Xu Yan)
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all,
just getting nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
Ms. Xu.
We've been eagerly
waiting for you.
Hello.
♪The love that I should deserve♪
Sorry for all the trouble,
Mr. Zhang.
Not at all.
Welcome to Gubei Town for inspection.
It's been a long journey.
It's even prettier than I imagined.
It gets better.
Let me show you around.
Alright.
Your room is there.
Thanks.
Come on.
This place is thriving.
Yeah.
We need experts like you
to help promote us.
You can count on me.
Be careful.
Alright.
Well?
To be fair,
you've become a better boatman
than me.
I learned from the best.
Thanks.
(Watertown Gubei)
This is stunning.
It's beautiful.
This place fuses the majestic northern
architectural styles
as well as the delicate elegance
of Jiangnan water towns.
There is nothing
like this.
So unique.
Gubei Town has seen
remarkable development.
We've built our own canteen,
tourist center,
organic vegetable farms,
and dyeing workshops
that have improved
our quality of life.
That's impressive.
But not many tourists know.
That's why we need you
to help promote
our town.
Rest assured.
- We will certainly do our best...
- Sir?
What's up?
I'm showing our higher-up
around the town.
Hello.
I'm Xu Yan.
Have...
Have we met before?
You do look familiar.
Let me introduce you.
This is the owner of
our town's Sky Lounge.
This is Ms. Xu.
Hello, Ma'am.
Nice to meet you.
Our Sky Lounge offers
the best panoramic views in Gubei Town.
Yeah.
I'll give you a discount when you come.
Welcome.
I'm honored.
Okay.
See you.
I'll visit.
I promise, Ma'am.
Okay.
Hospitable, huh?
Wu.
Haoming.
Where are you going?
Won't you come to make kites today?
Not today.
I'll learn botanical dyeing.
The kites you made last time
were exceptional.
They're sold out.
You've mastered this skill.
What do I do?
Maybe, I can open
a branch store.
You...
Just take over my shop
and be the manager.
No way.
Remember that agave-shaped kite
you asked for?
Let me fetch it.
Okay.
When is the botanical dyeing class
going to start?
I've scheduled it for you.
The workshop is near
your accommodations.
Check in.
Get settled.
Head there
and study as long as you want.
Thank you.
Our Commercial Street.
Okay.
Go ahead.
I've got kites to finish here.
Okay.
- Ride safely.
- Bye.
This shop
sells unique kites.
They fly high and far.
You think
it's gone.
Pull the string
and it's back.
People wonder,
"Is it gone?"
But they can always pull it back.
Everyone loves their kites.
Ms... Ms. Xu.
Ms. Xu.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Let's keep going.
This is
our best guesthouse.
The room you're staying in
is the finest room
specifically
reserved for you
by our director.
Thank you, Hua.
Thank you.
No problem.
Right.
Our town
isn't exactly small.
We've prepared an electric scooter
for you to roam around.
Ms. Xu.
Can you ride?
Yeah.
I thought you
couldn't ride it.
Well,
rest well.
Call me
later.
I'll show you the itinerary.
Thank you, Sir.
Thank you.
Get some rest.
- Okay.
Bye.
Take care.
Doesn't beep.
♪It's no surprise♪
♪Hard to be happy♪
♪I only hope that one day♪
♪What's mine will come♪
♪Emerging from the crowd for me♪
♪Then regrets won't linger♪
♪I am all right♪
♪May you live in peace♪
♪Let the world roar♪
♪Sounds like a carnival♪
♪Being alive is never dull♪
♪Overcome♪
♪The obstacles and love ourselves♪
♪Be so good that you can't recognize me♪
♪When I can look up♪
(Yongshun Botanical Dyeing)
♪At different clouds♪
♪I'll embrace the memories♪
Throughout the history,
our ancestors developed
vast insights
into colors
and discovered methods
to extract pigments
from nature.
Botanical dyeing
utilizes natural plants
to color textiles,
which is a technique deriving from
and returning
to nature.
"The Exploitation
of the Works of Nature"
recorded over twenty methods
of plant-based dyeing.
In modern terms,
they're natural
and
eco-friendly.
Take a look.
Blue, red, yellow, white, and black.
These are
primary colors.
Mixing primaries
yields secondary hues,
while mordant treatments,
color blending,
and overdyeing techniques...
Excuse me.
I'm late.
It's okay.
These methods
yield infinite color variations.
Furthermore,
botanical dyeing accommodates
various fabric types.
Silk, cotton, and linen all work.
Do you know
which plants produce
these different colors?
Botanical dyeing transforms
nature's palette
onto textiles.
For greens,
you can use fresh leaves,
sophora buds,
or dye flowers.
Yellow hues
come from turmeric,
mugwort,
or gardenia.
Even common foods and fruits
like blueberries,
bayberries,
and red cabbage
can serve as dyes.
Well done, Shen.
Your extra classes show.
Today,
we'll practice
basic dyeing techniques.
Follow me.
There are some
plain pottery blanks.
Choose one and dye it
with the colors you like.
Very few people know
that our traditional
24 solar terms
have corresponding colors.
The Minor Snow solar term in winter
starts with crimson-purple and evolves
into pale purple
then transforms into rouge purple.
Ms. Qiuzi.
I read a book
from the Eastern Jin Dynasty
back in college.
It recorded,
"Upon the Cloud-Reaching"
"Terrace,"
"the king's lamps"
"shone for miles,"
"and their smoke"
"was crimson-purple."
I've always wanted to know
what kind of purple it is.
So,
may I choose purple?
You're talking about
"Record of Heretofore Lost Works"
by Wang Jia,
the earliest documentation
of crape myrtle cultivation.
Alright.
Today, let's try
to dye fabric
crimson-purple.
Due to limited space,
we'll work
in pairs.
Please pair up.
We'll team up.
Okay.
Thank you.
♪Separated♪
♪Like the world shook off its dust♪
♪Your toughness, your innocence♪
♪How can I lean on you? Yet not let go♪
♪My life was fine without you♪
♪I was happy with or without you♪
♪Why am I missing a piece of soul♪
♪Some stubborn fools just lose all hope♪
♪That moment♪
♪I knew love♪
♪You're my one♪
♪I realize when I lose you♪
♪The more I let go♪
♪The more it hurts♪
♪I was the one♪
♪Who chose to walk away♪
♪If given another chance♪
♪Life's unwritten space♪
♪Now I anticipate♪
♪Your toughness, your innocence♪
♪How can I lean on you? Yet not let go♪
♪My life was fine without you♪
♪I was happy with or without you♪
♪Why am I missing a piece of soul♪
Be careful.
Let me do it.
♪That moment♪
♪I knew love♪
You can
gently knead the fabric.
♪I realize when I lose you♪
Apply enough pressure
to ensure even dyeing.
♪The more it hurts♪
♪I was the one♪
Today we're using
sappanwood for coloring.
Sappanwood has strong dyeing power.
But its natural color is red.
To achieve purple hues,
we add alkaline for color fixation.
This way,
we can produce
the unique
crimson-purple we envision.
Leave the rest
to time.
Whether we succeed
in producing the color
remains uncertain.
What a surprise.
You did
a perfect purple dye on the first day.
Tomorrow,
let's experiment with blue.
Okay.
Shen Haoming.
Don't tell me it's a coincidence.
But it is.
What now?
Mr. Baraikin is here?
I've told you
to be open and honest.
Don't hide anything
or beat around the bush.
You're busy being
my neighbor
and classmate.
What do you want?
I've been here for days.
I don't buy it.
I'm not justifying myself.
But
I have no idea you're here.
Alright?
Whatever.
I don't care.
If it bothers you, I'll leave.
Just stay out of my sight.
Hello? What's up?
You've settled in?
How is it?
It's nice.
Beautiful place.
Shen Haoming lives next door.
What's going on?
He followed you there?
And he lives next door?
How should I know?
What else could he want?
It's so obvious.
He went there for you.
My goodness.
He's so persistent.
But he's only
perceived as persistent
if he doesn't bother
anyone.
But if you find him annoying,
then he's just
clingy and shameless.
Come on.
It's not that bad.
Feeling sorry?
You can't admit you still care?
Aren't you my sister?
Did you forget his scheme?
I'm your sister and that's why
I need to be fair.
Forget about
his scheme.
He helped Yan Studio,
which also benefits himself.
As CEO of a listed company,
he has a vision, doesn't he?
If he were truly lovesick,
could you stand it?
But he always approaches me
with ulterior motives.
Now, I can't tell
what he wants.
You just won't face your feelings.
Are you still into him?
You won't
answer?
Silence means confirmation.
Yan,
he's not that bad.
You've rejected him so many times,
but he persists.
He'd get anyone
he's trying to pursue.
He doesn't pursue anyone.
That's it. I have to go.
Still working?
I still have
some work to do.
You're working too hard.
You should've gone with Xu Yan.
Enjoy the nice scenery
and take a break.
Get makeup inspirations.
Someone needs to look after the company.
Why are you still here?
Well,
we need to pay a supplier soon.
I checked the accounts
and our cash flow
is insufficient.
Short by how much?
A million.
A million?
We increased factory orders
for urgent production,
so we diverted funds
to advance payment
for the factory.
Okay. I'll handle this.
You're managing everything alone.
Take a break.
Let me get you
some dinner.
No need.
Braised pork rice.
No need, Lin Tao.
Dr. Yu.
Why did you come?
I'm free today,
so I thought
I'd come.
Work can wait.
Now that Dr. Yu's here,
go have dinner.
Rest early.
Well...
Guess I'm done for today.
Wait for me.
We're off.
Turn off my PC, please.
Thanks.
Okay.
What are we having?
Hot pot?
Okay.
Bring my makeup bag.
Did you hear me?
Yeah.
Where'd you put it, honey?
In the suitcase.
Look properly.
Okay, let me check.
Ms. Xu.
Would you like
housekeeping service?
Yes, thank you.
Excuse me.
Where is the guest who stayed here?
He has checked out.
He really left?
(Yongshun Botanical Dyeing)
These items
displayed here
are the raw materials for dyeing.
These materials
may look ordinary.
But in reality,
each of them
has hidden properties
you wouldn't expect.
Xu Yan?
Ms. Qiuzi.
Do you know what this is?
Sorry.
I have no idea.
This is called Chinese Indigo.
The common indigo blue we see
is extracted from this plant.
Blue?
This can produce blue dye?
Yeah.
Take a look.
These indigo leaves
need several days of soaking
to release their pigments.
Then we add lime,
ferment it, and let it settle
to get the indigo paste.
So today,
we'll try using this indigo paste
to dye blue.
Follow me.
Hello, sir.
Feel free to browse.
These are all handmade.
Do you like it?
Look around.
It's pretty.
Handmade.
Okay.
I wanted to ask
if you have
an agave-shaped kite?
That's customized.
Do you know the person
who ordered an agave kite?
Haoming.
Shen Haoming from Jinda Group.
Right?
We're old acquaintances.
On your way here,
did you notice
the tourist center, the vegetable farm,
and our canteen?
Jinda Group built those.
It's been years.
So he wasn't pretending?
He was.
He was?
To be a tourist.
At first,
we thought he was just a tourist.
But then, the townspeople
said he's from Jinda Group.
Interesting guy.
He came here and said,
"These are handmade, right?"
"Teach me."
Skyscraper builders
are different, I tell you.
Fast learner.
The kites he made
all got sold.
He stole all my techniques.
There's nothing else to learn.
And then
he went to steal
techniques of
botanical dyeing.
You know?
Do you know him?
Are you his friend?
A classmate.
Pick a kite
you like.
I like it.
I'll take this one.
But I want to customize
an agave one.
Mr. Shen.
I just don't get it.
Did you come to Gubei Town
for Xu Yan
or botanical dyeing?
She said she wanted
to create a botanical dyeing series.
That's why I came
to study this technique for her.
She's still mad at me because of
Mr. Baraikin.
I can only
secretly support her.
Love the tree, love the branch.
But
since we've run into Yan here,
it's destiny at work.
Why did you move out of the guesthouse
to avoid her?
You think I wanted to?
I wouldn't believe
such a coincidence either, okay?
She must think
I'm someone
scheming
and clingy.
She even told me
not to show up again.
I don't want to upset her,
so I'm staying away.
A man like you
is truly our role model.
I have so much to learn.
I almost forgot
about the theater play
rehearsal.
Rehearsal?
At least grab a bite first.
(Execution of Chen Shimei)
Casting for The Execution of Chen Shimei
begins now.
Bravo!
Wu!
The guesthouse owner said
there's a play rehearsal
at the theater tonight.
Which play?
Something about Chen Shimei.
She's playing the princess.
Really?
Let's see.
Don't you dare become Chen Shimei.
Never.
I'll always support you.
Such a sweet talker.
Chen Shimei.
Do you recognize your wife,
Qin Xianglian?
Your Honor.
I'm Chen Shimei's
one true wife.
If Qin Xianglian drops the lawsuit,
I'll give her 500 taels of silver.
You abused your power
and showed no remorse.
This is outrageous.
Guards.
Execute him.
Understood.
Judge Bao, show mercy.
Don't kill my husband.
No.
Your Honor.
Execute him.
Wait.
I mean,
can we revise the script?
What?
Go ahead.
It's a modern adaptation.
Shouldn't it reflect
contemporary values?
In today's context,
the protagonist
shouldn't be Chen Shimei.
You mean...?
Focus on the ladies.
Think about it.
Chen Shimei is an ungrateful
social climber.
Why would two women fight over him?
Yeah.
Brilliant insight.
Mr. Shen, this is genius.
He really loves acting.
I get your point.
Listen.
See if I'm right.
Qin chased her husband
for a millennium
and arrived at our Gubei Town.
This is destiny.
For such a destiny,
shouldn't we let Qin Xianglian
enjoy her life
and have some fun?
Make the guy
pursue her.
Let Chen Shimei pursue his wife.
Something like that.
No wonder I couldn't get immersed.
Yeah, let's do this.
Pursue her?
Genius.
That's what I want to see.
Yeah, good point.
Excellent.
Make up
some lines then.
Right?
We'll follow your lead.
Great idea.
Something came up.
Mr. Shen.
- Come back.
- Where are you going?
But this is
your idea.
Where are you going?
Come back.
Mr. Shen.
Don't go. It's your idea.
Go on.
I don't know how to change
the script.
Chen Shimei.
Why are you shunning me?
I'm not.
Am I scary?
I'm tired.
Tired or guilty?
You said you didn't
want to see me, so I'm trying
not to upset you.
Why don't you leave?
I came
to learn botanical dyeing.
What for?
I want to share some common topics
with you one day.
♪I just wanna take my time tonight♪
What are you plotting now?
I mean it.
You said you want to learn
botanical dyeing.
So I wanted
to study it first.
Maybe it becomes our common interest.
Besides,
regarding the question you asked,
I want to find the answers here.
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
Please don't get me wrong.
♪I'm giving it all,
just getting nothing back♪
Suit yourself.
Stop shunning me.
Can I still be your classmate?
Just don't be late.
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love that I should deserve♪
You and I fly together forever.
People in our town
have practiced ancient dyeing techniques
for over a century.
The exhibits here
showcase works
by our master artisans.
You've learned the theory
and basic practice.
Here,
you'll feel the charm
of botanical dyeing.
Look.
(Zhaxie)
This is Zhaxie,
commonly called tie-dye.
Botanical dyeing
is a fusion of nature and time.
It's calming
and soothing.
Ahead is Jiaxie.
Jiexie.
(Jiaxie)
This
carries a rustic vibe.
The blue hue is powerful.
(Laxie)
Over here is Laxie,
also known as
traditional batik.
(Laxie)
Look.
You have to
draw the lines
with beeswax
before dyeing.
But modern industry
uses machines
to replicate
handmade effects
at a lower cost.
Craftsmen who insist
on the manual approach
are dwindling.
Excuse me, Ms. Qiuzi.
Is there no original piece of this?
Why is it a photo?
This is
the work of
a local veteran craftsman.
We're displaying the photos
because we can't get the original.
A local craftsman?
Yeah.
A local artisan created these patterns
peculiar to Southwestern
ethnic minority groups.
This master craftsman
once lived in Miao ethnic villages.
Therefore,
he brought back
their techniques.
Look.
His style leans heavily
towards traditional
folk patterns.
Our designer at Yan Studio
happens to be from the Yi ethnic group.
If she saw
such a design,
she'd be thrilled.
Ms. Qiuzi,
could you share his contact?
I want to inquire about
licensing this pattern.
I'm afraid that won't be possible.
He stopped making these three years ago.
Why?
Creative block, perhaps?
He's reluctant
to discuss batik.
He even took back
his displayed works.
That's so bad.
What a shame.
You can try.
But
I don't know
if he'll agree.
(Laxie)
I actually know
Master Chu.
You know him?
Years ago,
Jinda ran welfare programs
in Gubei Town
where we delivered supplies.
I delivered supplies to Mr. Chu.
And I saw him again here last year.
But he's quite reclusive
and doesn't like
social interactions.
I didn't know that
he was an expert in batik.
If you want to meet him,
I'll go with you.
(Cash only,
10 yuan per pile, self-service)
Who is it?
Haoming, why are you here?
I brought something.
You're so kind.
And this is?
My friend.
Please, come in.
Thank you.
Take a seat.
Let me make some tea.
Haoming.
It's been so long.
Yeah.
I've been busy with work.
The gardening techniques
you taught me last time
were amazing.
Look at all my plants.
I noticed.
Next time, I'll bring
some gardening books
that you can use.
Thank you.
Your friend here...?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Xu Yan.
I run a clothing company
in Jingzhou.
I'll cut to the chase.
We're currently integrating
intangible cultural heritage
into our designs.
We saw your batik works
at the dyeing workshop.
They're stunning.
It would be meaningful
to feature your patterns
in our latest
batik-inspired collection.
We hope you'll authorize us
to use the patterns.
Haven't you heard?
I quit ages ago.
Then
could we use your previous works?
Haoming.
I invited you in
out of respect.
Sir.
Please don't be mad.
She was genuinely moved by your work.
I'm sorry.
Stop trying
to fool me.
My mediocre creations
couldn't move anyone.
Let me be honest.
I'd rather let
my batik works rot at home.
I don't care.
I enjoy it.
I think you should leave.
Sir.
Give us a minute.
- Master Chu, sorry.
- Let her explain.
I've been thinking.
Actually,
I was indeed rude.
I jumped straight into business matters.
That's why he was
so irritated
and harsh.
It's not your fault.
It only shows
that he's still
against batik art.
But
he hasn't let go yet.
I was about to tell you.
I saw blue-dyed fabrics
covered by plastic sheets
in his backyard earlier.
Did you notice the Assam indigo
soaking in vats?
That's the botanical dye for blue.
Why'd someone who hates coriander
keep it in their fridge?
Then why...?
Let's see someone
who knows everything.
Who?
Chu
got divorced three years ago.
He's just making excuses.
He blamed it on the divorce
that he lost
his inspiration.
Lost his inspiration?
How did that happen?
He lost
his dyeing partner.
Chu knows batik techniques
but indigo dyeing
is his wife's specialty.
They were the perfect partners.
Truth be told,
her indigo blues
were mesmerizing.
If they're such a perfect match,
why did they divorce?
His wife
was a Miao girl from Guizhou.
She met Chu when she was 19
while he studied dyeing in her village.
It was love at first sight.
She insisted on
marrying him
and left her homeland
with him.
That sounds
quite romantic.
Romantic beginning.
Ugly ending.
She thought Chu
was outdated.
Chu felt that
she despised his lack of ambition
and earnings.
Living with mutual resentment
doomed
their marriage.
So they got divorced
and cut all ties.
The painter
and the dyer
ended up like a pen
without ink.
Nonsense.
Those are excuses.
Guys are the same.
No offense.
From what I just heard,
there are no fundamental issues
or severe conflicts between them.
Why
don't they reconcile?
Master Chu and his wife
met due to batik art.
Now Master Chu refuses
to produce any artworks.
He's clearly holding grudges
against his ex-wife.
The real pity
isn't the batik craft,
but their relationship.
Caught a cold?
Maybe. It's chilly.
You're burning up.
You have a fever.
It's fine. I'll rest a bit.
This won't do.
Ask Dr. Yu to pick you up.
He's got major surgery today.
It's just a fever.
Don't distract him.
(Yan Studio)
And I can't walk away
from so much work.
Is it about the loan?
I've been talking
to our suppliers all day,
asking for payment extensions.
Nobody would budge.
I'm going crazy.
What about Mr. Liang's investment?
Yuanhang wants us
to expand offline markets.
That funding is earmarked
and allocated.
I've approached several banks
about loans.
With Yan Studio's current scale,
they can approve two million.
Really?
Chill.
Let's see.
We'll work on it
if there's progress.
Alright.
Let me find a thermometer.
39.8 Degrees Celsius.
Lin.
Let's go
to the hospital.
Hurry.
Don't be dramatic.
Lin.
You need to rest.
I'll boil some water for you.
No need, Lin Tao.
I got this.
Could you
go back to the office
to fetch my phone?
Sure, I'll get it for you.
Take care of yourself.
(Certificate)
Thanks.
No problem.
(Yu Yiming)
Yu Yiming.
Lin Tao?
How come it's you?
Where's Lin?
She's having a fever.
We rushed to the hospital
and I came to pick up
her phone she left
at the office.
Where is she now?
At home.
Head there now.
I'm on my way.
Meet at her place.
Okay.
Be right there.
Lin Tao.
Finally.
Where's Lin?
In her room.
Fever's gone down.
It almost
turned into pneumonia.
Her phone.
Thank you.
No problem.
Well,
don't get me wrong
for taking her back.
We're just fellow townsfolk
and coworkers now.
I won't.
Good then.
I left the medicine
on the table.
I wrote down
the dosage.
You're the doctor. You know better.
Go ahead.
I'm off.
Lin Tao.
Thank you so much.
Take care of her.
Go on.
Master Chu.
Why are you here again?
You're not welcome.
Master Chu.
Don't call me master.
Please.
I just don't get it.
There are plenty of dyers around.
Find someone else.
We...
Sir.
Good artworks
call for sharing.
If you hide them from people,
you'll never know
how others view your work.
Okay.
You say you lack
inspiration.
Then why not
try to communicate
with others?
That's how you infuse
your creations with vitality.
Oh boy.
I don't need your lectures.
I wouldn't dare lecture you, sir.
I just want to
help you break through
and see if you can
keep producing artworks.
Listen.
New things
aren't scary at all.
Modern technology assists humans
in overcoming confusion
about creation.
If you can't weave
or draw
certain patterns,
AI could help with that.
Technology serves us
and helps us...
What nonsense!
I don't believe
in AI stuff.
If computers can replace humans,
why do you still
come to me?
You think creation is that easy?
Computers can't replace human minds.
You're not resisting new things.
You don't want to change, do you?
You're right.
I won't change.
I'm successful
because I stay true to myself.
I never cater to others' opinions.
So you're not against batik.
You're avoiding your true self.
If you've stopped creating
batik works,
what's the indigo in the backyard for?
You and your ex-wife
were spouses
and the best partners.
Without her color-mixing,
you'll never find
that perfect shade of blue.
Is that it?
Enough.
Don't be so smart.
I'll tell you the truth.
I'm out of inspiration.
Master Chu.
- Master Chu.
- I...
So it's not like only his wife
could create that blue hue.
In fact, that blue hue
embodies his wife.
He knows it very well,
but he refuses to admit it.
Failing to dye blue
and lacking inspiration
are not the real issues.
Deep down,
he hasn't let go of her.
You can't
wake someone pretending to sleep.
I actually understand him a bit now.
You think he's right?
He reminds me
of who I used to be.
Extremely self-centered
and controlling.
Do you remember
how to cultivate agave?
We can't
let it grow on its own.
We have to
intervene all the time.
Master Chu is the same.
He doesn't want to change.
Once changes occur,
he becomes uneasy.
He forces people around him
to follow his ways.
So, he didn't get divorced
because his wife
looked down on his failures.
He was running away
from his wife's attempts
to make him break out
of his shell and adapt to the changes.
So?
Have you cured your need for control?
Still working on it.
Look.
See this bridge?
We've crossed it many times.
I just never realized
it looks so beautiful from afar.
When we rush towards destinations,
we miss the scenery.
It's like
how we interact with nature.
When you stand
on the bridge,
it feels like self-reflection.
But when others
see you standing there,
it's a different view.
That's why
self-awareness
isn't easily achieved.
When was your
first visit?
I first
visited here
when Haochen was four.
I came back from my studies abroad
and brought him
here.
He must have loved it.
Yeah.
He was curious
about me, the brother
who had just returned.
One day, he said he didn't
want to go to kindergarten.
So I told Mom that
I'd take him to school.
But I drove him out for an adventure.
And we came here.
So, Haochen's
mischievous nature
is half your fault.
Fair point.
I missed much of his growing up.
That's not entirely true.
You've done well.
A child's attitude and reactions
tell the whole story.
Haochen adores you
and relies on you.
You did well.
The first time
we came here,
we had so much fun.
Everything here
felt new
and exciting to me.
There was this
amazing ice cream shop.
He wolfed down two scoops at once
and made me promise
not to tell Mom.
He gave me
a huge hug
and a kiss.
That was
his first time hugging me.
It was so warm.
That's when I realized
that this town
could give him
childhood joys
that every kid
deserves
and help him
rediscover the nature of a kid.
Later, I made this town
his personal paradise.
I hoped he could
live like regular kids,
being mischievous and joyful.
This place works the same way
for me.
It's simple
and pure.
No matter
what troubles come,
whether I argue with my dad
or face issues at Jinda,
coming here
always calms my mind
like magic.
That's why I've been
renovating buildings and facilities
under Jinda's name
over the years.
It's not for profit.
I just hope to make this place
even better.
Want to try?
Like this?
No.
Like this.
Put strength.
Here we go.
Come on.
Put strength.
Same posture as yours?
One, two, three.
Go!
Natural talent.
One more.
♪Like fireworks that loved♪
♪Rushing toward the stars♪
♪Undaunted by pain♪
♪Fearless of flames♪
♪Even if just a fleeting sparkle♪
♪We shed tears♪
♪Deep blue seas turn to foam♪
♪We regained freedom♪
♪If you remember me♪
♪Then I'm pleased♪
♪I just wanna take my time tonight♪
♪To do all the things I said I'd try♪
♪I go surfing, go diving, go driving,
and go flying to a different place♪
♪I go drink, go party, and go dance♪
♪Even if I'm lonely♪
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all to get nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love I should deserve♪
♪When the time is right♪
♪You realize♪
♪It will all be alright♪
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all to get nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love I should deserve♪
♪When the time is right♪
♪You realize♪
♪It will all be alright♪