♪That day♪
♪Nothing stays together forever♪
♪I've quit romance♪
♪Who hasn't failed again♪
♪Crying in death♪
♪And in life♪
♪Even now♪
♪We keep learning♪
♪It's no surprise♪
♪Being happy is so hard♪
♪Weirdly, I became a role model♪
♪On the day we met again, we said hi♪
♪It was a reminder,
a test, and a complaint♪
♪Who can do anything without regret♪
♪I am all right♪
♪May you live in peace♪
♪Let the world roar♪
♪Sounds like a carnival♪
♪Being alive is never dull♪
♪How wonderful to be free♪
♪I became even better without you♪
♪Nothing can be perfect♪
♪We bless each other in pain♪
♪We nod and smile♪
♪May we both be well♪
= Love's Ambition=
=Episode 02=
At first,
because of the sunlight conditions,
our entire project
sacrificed some green spaces.
You see.
You just mentioned...
Turn off the AC.
Okay.
So...
We can
continue pushing this
forward.
Okay.
Next,
let's discuss
the other proposal.
Basically,
we have...
Excellent.
If there's
no further questions,
shall we end the meeting?
That's it.
Thank you.
Okay.
Miss Xu.
Mr. Shen.
I'm sorry
for keeping you waiting.
Let's have lunch.
And we'll talk.
Miss Xu?
♪You once shone like the sun♪
♪The flowers bloomed and withered♪
Miss,
please be gentle.
♪Then tangled into waiting♪
♪I've lost those beautiful moments too♪
♪Passing through my eyes
a thousand times♪
Please keep an eye on the patient.
Call me if needed.
Okay.
Thanks.
♪When you speak, the universe halts♪
♪Even fate grows still♪
♪Sunset glow caresses♪
♪Your silhouette♪
♪Till sunset takes dreams away♪
♪Leaving me, unbroken♪
♪Envying dust♪
♪Resting in your heart♪
♪Like fireworks that loved♪
♪Rushing toward the stars♪
♪Undaunted by pain♪
♪Fearless of flames♪
♪Even if just a fleeting sparkle♪
♪We shed tears♪
You're awake?
♪Deep blue seas turn to foam♪
♪We regained freedom♪
Come on.
♪Then I'm pleased♪
You got a fever at my company
and fainted.
I brought you here.
Thank you, Mr. Shen.
You're welcome.
I was careless this time.
I thought two pills
would power through it.
The doctor said
you were overworked
and must rest properly.
Excuse me.
Mr. Shen,
go ahead with your work.
I can take care of myself.
Thank you.
I'm the one who asked you out,
so I'll take full responsibility.
When you recover,
I'll accept your interview.
Oh, right.
The doctor said
drink more water.
Come on.
Thanks.
After the nurse removed the needle,
I feared you'd keep bleeding,
so applied a band-aid.
Haoming's back.
Take it to play there.
Mom,
let me formally introduce.
This is Xu Yan,
my girlfriend.
Hello, Ms. Yu.
I'm Xu Yan.
This is Ms. Ma.
This is Ms. Meng.
Nice to meet you,
Ms. Ma, Ms. Meng.
Haoming's often told me about you.
I finally get to meet you today.
Welcome.
Take a seat.
Thank you.
Haoming,
your father's waiting in the study.
He wants to talk to you.
Okay.
Take good care of Yan.
Got it. Don't worry.
Have some water.
I'll pour it myself.
Let me refill it for you.
Thank you.
Let me top it up.
Bu is truly clever.
No wonder it won a championship
at the World Canine Organization
dog show.
I'm terribly sorry
for being late.
I took Pudding to the groomer's.
Indeed.
Take it to play.
And this is?
Let me introduce you.
This is Xu Yan,
Haoming's friend.
Hello, Miss Xu.
I'm Sun Meiling,
a friend of Ms. Yu's.
Hello, Ms. Sun.
I'm Xu Yan.
Ms. Sun,
please sit.
Thank you, Miss Xu.
Miss Xu.
Do you like dogs?
I love dogs very much.
Do you have a dog now?
My work keeps me too busy,
so I haven't had time to keep one.
I'm afraid I can't take care of them.
It barked.
Come here.
Bu.
Our Pudding here
is just a silly dog.
It's nothing,
but looks good.
It's fine.
Nonsense. It's quite clever.
Pudding's great.
Come on.
Do you want to go play too?
Hui,
bring fresh fruit and a new pot of tea.
Let me help you.
Okay.
Thank you.
Ms. Yu, I'll go with her.
Okay.
Let me make you a braid.
Miss Xu.
I think
you're different
from the ladies coming
to this place.
What's different?
Your hair looks dry and frizzy.
Ms. Yu and others
really prioritize hair care.
My work keeps me too occupied
to tend to it properly.
They
regularly get this
special hair treatment.
Afterward,
their hair shines like satin.
It's very popular.
Even Ms. Ma and Ms. Sun
go regularly.
You should try it too.
Hui.
Ms. Yu.
Is the tea ready?
It's ready.
Let the staff handle it.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Miss Xu,
stay for dinner?
Okay.
I've ordered dishes from the club.
When they're ready,
go collect them.
Exit and turn right.
You'll find it.
If it's a club,
maybe we can have them deliver it?
I don't like
strangers coming to my house.
Okay.
Then I'll go get them now.
Miss Xu.
It's crowded today.
We can't really chat properly.
Later,
after you bring the food,
just give them to the nanny.
You can go now.
I'll let Haoming know.
Okay.
Are you free Saturday morning?
Yes.
Good.
I'll pick the place.
Let's talk?
Come in.
Sir,
the proposal for the next episode
is here for you.
Xu,
have a seat.
Sit.
Xu,
during your interview,
I spotted your potential at once.
Since you joined us,
I've invested much effort
in mentoring you.
I have high expectations for you.
Come on.
I know that, sir.
So I've always
been grateful to you.
No need for thanks.
Xu.
Over these years,
food shows have been popular.
I assigned you to develop
the Family Feast,
so you could polish your resume,
move up,
and become a host later.
Look.
You have great presence,
intelligence,
and diligence.
But sometimes,
things don't go as planned.
Your application to become a host
was rejected.
Why?
Why what?
Because I remember
you previously told me...
Xu,
sit down.
S-Sit down first.
Mr. Zhou,
when I first came here,
I applied to be a host.
Yes, yes.
Is that right?
You said I lacked experience
and needed more.
So I took on planning
for three years.
Yes, yes.
When I first started Family Feast,
there were only
these two words on the proposal.
Launching the project,
inviting guests,
conducting interviews,
filming, post-production,
and subtitles...
One by one,
I checked them all.
I understand
shows aren't made through theory.
So I paid to learn cooking myself.
I wanted to upgrade
the show's ingredients.
I even used my own salary.
Family Feast has run
for three years now.
I earn it with countless overtime hours
and late nights.
So I want to know
why?
Xu,
you can't accept it.
I understand.
I also know you've worked hard
and sacrificed a lot.
But the leadership
has their own considerations.
Stop obsessing over this.
I'm not obsessing.
What am I lacking?
I can learn.
Let me be direct.
Our program department
is committed to media integration
and transformation.
Staff allocations
for subordinate departments
and production budgets
have been largely reduced.
At this critical moment,
adjustments to host positions
require comprehensive evaluation
of all factors.
I advocated for you.
If Sun Siwei
is unavailable,
you'll step in.
Three years, sir.
Now I only get
a disposable temp position?
Don't say that.
Xu,
I know you're upset.
But Sun Siwei's performance
has been excellent.
The leadership has decided
to keep Sun Siwei as the host.
This wasn't solely my decision.
When the time is right,
you can get back on the starting line.
Isn't that enough?
Only by staying on the starting line
will I get the chance to run.
Xu...
(Ms. Yu calling)
Hello, Ms. Yu?
The restaurant location and time
were sent to your phone.
Okay.
Madam,
the hair treatment
you requested.
But there's no discount.
Is that okay?
Okay.
Please wait.
I'll prepare it.
That lady
wants the full treatment.
We need to prepare accordingly.
Gather the supplies.
Good afternoon.
Ms. Yu.
Please sit.
Feel free.
Would you like
something to drink?
Not yet.
I'm waiting for a friend.
Okay.
We'll order together
when your friend arrives.
Ms. Yu.
Jiaqi, over here.
Ms. Yu,
it's been so long.
Indeed.
You look radiant as ever.
Let me introduce you.
This is Lin Jiaqi,
from investment banking.
And this is Xu Yan,
Haoming's friend.
Hello.
Hi.
Pleasure to meet you.
Jiaqi,
I heard you were thriving
on Wall Street.
What brought you back suddenly?
It was my father's wish.
After so many years,
he should be satisfied now.
Recently, I received
an offer from Hong Kong, China.
The terms were good.
So I returned.
Domestic opportunities
are promising now.
By the way,
about Dewei's project,
thank you for helping select partners.
My pleasure.
You and Mr. Shen
watched me grow up.
What've you been up to?
I just got back recently,
still settling in.
Xu Yan,
Yutong's a rising star in law,
specializing in cross-border M&A
and financing.
Now she's working
at her family law firm,
handling international cases.
Hello.
Yutong,
I met your mother recently
and heard you just resolved
a cross-border M&A case.
Impressive work.
Let me campaign for myself then.
Ms. Yu,
keep me in mind for your
cross-border business.
Absolutely.
I wouldn't trust anyone else.
Miss Xu,
what do you think of these girls?
They're good.
Lovely and exceptionally talented.
Yes.
Girls like these
suit Haoming best.
I dislike beating around the bush
and wasting time.
Your appearance
and education are impressive,
and your job is decent,
but
your family isn't that well-off, is it?
Last time, we spent
so much time together.
You never truly fit in.
Yet you didn't complain at all.
Even when I made you fetch takeout,
you stayed composed.
You were slighted
and forced to smile.
Just like how,
you're still not angry now.
Miss Xu,
your flaw
is being too submissive.
You saw it yourself.
Those girls just now all had a kind
of ease, as if nothing really matters
to them.
That's what Haoming needs
and what you lack.
You should find someone
who truly matches your pace.
(Qiao Yan,)
(an orphan with no parents.)
- An orphan with no parents!
I'm not!
- The orphan hit someone!
I'm not an orphan!
I have parents!
They're abroad
in a faraway land.
- Qiao Yan, the liar!
Break up with Haoming now
to avoid humiliation.
Syracuse University.
It is where my parents
work overseas.
They taught me since childhood
that composure and good manners
are the basics of courtesy
in any situation.
But I never expected
you'd perceive it
as timidity or weakness.
My career here
is earned by myself.
I rarely mention my parents.
But in your eyes,
it means a poor family background.
All I can say is, you're wrong.
I know
you don't like me.
That's understandable.
But I love Haoming
and won't leave him.
(Six months later)
What's on your mind?
Nothing special.
Just feel this family
is just odd.
Odd how?
I can't name it.
They seem fine to me.
Look,
they're an intellectual family.
Marrying into them
would boost our company's image
and other aspects.
Don't overthink it.
I think
our son has a good taste.
Stop overthinking.
Maybe I'm overthinking it.
(New District Development Plan)
Morning.
Morning, Mr. Shen.
Qu hasn't arrived yet?
I haven't told you yet,
Mr. Qu isn't feeling well today.
He can't make it.
Alright then.
Let's start the meeting without him.
Regarding the New District
commercial complex project,
I plan
to work with our upstream partner,
Shifeng Group.
They've
expressed
preliminary interest in cooperation.
Shifeng
is currently the largest
and best-capitalized
company in the industry.
If we secure partnership
with them,
this project is settled.
We've got a good chance.
Exactly.
Haoming.
Dad.
You stayed silent during the meeting.
Why?
I don't have confidence in Mr. Zheng,
the new Chairman of Shifeng Group.
Your reasons?
First,
after the accident
at Shifeng's resettlement housing site,
his response was
to conceal it,
suppress public opinion,
and shirk accountability.
Second,
he's a parachuted executive,
meaning he lacks
reliable loyalists within Shifeng.
Third,
he brought three confidants.
One has strong networking skills
but is self-righteous,
offending everyone.
Another one
is senior and experienced,
but was playing mahjong
when the accident happened.
The third
and lowest-ranked one
is the most competent.
He handles heavy workloads,
but suffers unfair profit distribution.
Impressive.
You've dug deep
into their foundation.
Dad,
I believe internal turmoil
is inevitable.
If you think
Zheng
has so many flaws,
how did he become
the Chairman then?
That's an even bigger red flag.
Dear Haoming.
In construction,
unless you've worked
from the ground up
and fought your way up
through decades
in this industry,
you'll never grasp its workings.
Understand?
Understood.
Besides,
I want to bid for the New District's
Plot 178 development.
This large company
will
be handed to you.
For now,
maintain stability and avoid mistakes.
That's your main task.
Clear?
Yes.
A dish to savor, a moment to cherish.
This episode of Family Feast
concludes here.
Thank you for watching, everyone.
Got it.
See you
- next time.
- Next time.
Cut.
(Family Feast)
You've worked hard, Siwei.
What process is this?
Recording for so long.
Thank you, Mr. Sanmu.
It's way too late.
You've worked hard too.
Xu Yan.
To be honest,
the reason I came here
isn't just because of Haoming,
but mainly
I was moved by your sincerity.
I was on business in America for a week.
Your messages kept coming nonstop.
And whenever I texted you,
you replied right away.
I'm curious.
Do you never sleep?
Sorry for disturbing you.
That's how our job works.
We're on call 24/7.
So feel free to contact me
for any future issues.
Good.
Good for you.
Next time,
le t's have dinner with Haoming.
No problem.
Must be exhausted.
Get some rest early.
Come.
Okay.
Take Mr. Sanmu
to the guest room to change.
Yan,
the backstage director said
we need close-up shots
of those dishes.
No problem.
(Ms. Yu calling)
Hello, Ms. Yu?
Now?
But I've got...
No problem.
Please send me the address.
Okay.
(Cuijin Royal Garden Sales Office)
Thank you.
I'm coming in now, Ms. Yu.
Okay.
This
is the Tongzhou Canal.
And
there's a CBD nearby.
Sorry I'm late, Ms. Yu.
There was traffic on the way.
We've been waiting.
It wasn't easy
to get Ms. Meng
to see the house with us today,
yet you kept her waiting.
Ms. Meng,
my apologies.
It's fine.
Let's go take a look then.
- I'm occupied this afternoon.
- Okay.
This entire property
covers an area
of 35,000 square meters.
There are eight buildings in total.
Six garden villas
and two high-rises.
The unit sizes range
from 199
to 143 square meters.
Ms. Yu,
may I ask
who this house is for?
My son.
He's getting married.
Really?
Congratulations, Ms. Yu.
Mr. Shen is marrying so soon?
I wonder which lucky girl
gets to be his bride.
How careless of me!
Hello, Madam.
I'm Lisa.
If you need anything,
just let me know.
You'll be satisfied.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Lisa,
which units did you prepare for me?
I've reserved for you
the prime unit of the entire complex.
Unit 606,
706,
and 808 in Building 6.
These three units
are undoubtedly
the finest
and the most spacious.
I reserve them all for you.
Madam?
What do you think, Madam?
They're all good.
Ms. Yu,
should we ask Haoming's opinion?
Miss Xu,
when it comes to buying a marital home,
Ms. Yu will make the decision.
You young people
don't have a sense of real estate.
Forget everything else.
Just concerning the orientation
and the floor level,
you surely don't understand, right?
You'll have children
in a few years, right?
Shouldn't you decide
how to lay out the rooms
or what interior style to choose?
This isn't a joke.
If you pick the wrong property,
it could severely impact
your married life.
Thank you, Ms. Meng.
When buying the house,
we'll surely follow Ms. Yu's advice.
I was just thinking, maybe we should
have Haoming
come take a look too.
No need.
He's too busy.
We'll decide for him.
Okay.
I got it.
Miss Xu, you probably
don't house-hunt often
and lack experience.
But don't worry.
With me here,
I'll help you two lovebirds
pick the perfect unit.
Thank you.
Don't say that.
We're older now.
We truly don't know
young people's minds.
Xu Yan's father
was an architecture major.
She grew up immersed in that field.
Perfect.
Give us your professional opinion.
Which of these units
is more suitable?
(Property information)
Mom.
♪I like it when it's just me and you♪
Haoming,
why are you here?
Did you tell him?
No, Ms. Yu.
I didn't.
It's not that.
I asked the driver.
He said here.
I guessed you were buying me a house.
I forgot to tell you.
I've already picked one out.
Since when?
I don't know that.
It's been a while.
I didn't even tell Yan.
I wanted to surprise you.
Oh, you.
- But the units here...
- Mom.
If there's nothing else,
my girlfriend and I will have a date.
Bye-bye.
Bye, Ms. Meng.
Okay.
I spent a long time selecting it.
Lisa.
Sorry about that.
Okay, okay.
Take your time.
Bye-bye.
We'll head out now, Ms. Yu.
Thank you.
Goodbye, Ms. Meng.
♪What already happened♪
♪Feeling so lost and feeling♪
♪So much distractions♪
♪Never imagined♪
♪You'd stay by my side♪
♪Comforting my sorrows♪
♪On the midnight streets♪
♪In shadowed corners♪
♪Remember that moment♪
♪You smiled and looked at me♪
I've always forgotten to ask you.
Why
do you love agave so much?
An agave blooms
only once in its lifetime.
After decades of growth,
it exerts all its life's energy
into one cloud of blossoms.
I especially admire
Its tenacious vitality
and
how it gathers
strength within,
waiting for that
once-in-a-lifetime burst.
A species that's existed
for hundreds of millions of years.
This kind of resilience
is unique among plants.
Yan,
come try
the tacos I made.
It's ready?
It comes
from the same origin as agave.
Is it good?
♪What already happened♪
Your cooking's amazing.
♪Never imagined♪
This is for you.
Why are you
suddenly giving me gifts?
You've been taking good care
of my mom lately.
I'll tell her
not to take up
too much of your time.
Your mother always
schedules with me in advance.
She never interferes with my plans.
Don't worry.
Your calendar's packed
with my mom's appointments.
But you've never
complained once to me.
So what's this?
A reward for model behavior.
Yan,
your kindness
makes me want to give you every single
good thing I see.
♪Want to preserve this feeling♪
♪Forever in my heart♪
♪I like it when it's just me and you♪
I heard you're competing
for the host role at Family Feast?
How did you know that?
I also know
the current host
has a domineering attitude
and often tattles to his mom.
Don't worry.
I can help you
handle all these issues.
♪About you and me♪
Thank you for your kindness.
But I don't need your help.
She has family backing,
and so do you.
Haoming,
you've shown me
the finest man in the world.
Thank you for loving me.
But for work matters,
you should trust me.
I can handle them.
Okay.
I trust you.
Eat before it gets cold.
Another one.
Another one?
Okay, come here.
Let me show you.
Come on.
(Every time Haoming confesses
with sincerity)
(and every time he's supported me,)
(it was like a constant question:)
(Are you worthy of such pure love?)
♪Like fireworks that loved♪
♪Rushing toward the stars♪
♪Undaunted by pain♪
♪Fearless of flames♪
♪Even if it's just a fleeting sparkle♪
♪We shed tears♪
♪Deep blue seas turn to foam♪
♪We regained freedom♪
♪If you remember me♪
♪Then I'm pleased♪
♪I just wanna take my time tonight♪
♪To do all the things I said I'd try♪
♪I go surfing, go diving, go driving,
and go flying to a different place♪
♪I go drink, go party, and go dance♪
♪Even if I'm lonely♪
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all to get nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love I should deserve♪
♪When the time is right♪
♪You realize♪
♪It will all be alright♪
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all to get nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love I should deserve♪
♪When the time is right♪
♪You realize♪
♪It will all be alright♪