television set
I'm not afraid of anything.
50 years of scalp learning
Qingyang Second-class
Huaxi Jingxie shampoo
Cells and repair damage
Jingche blood flower crab
Four-week
Let me watch
Ok
Qu Mingcheng's land transaction
Has been frozen by the government
There is no way to complete
The map of the board of directors
The next days
It's not easy
He's like a crazy man
Suddenly fell down
Then fell
Dizzy
When I woke up
I found myself
I was tied up
I have to thank you for your cooperation
Anyway
You are in my heart
Always my big brother
Although
You compete with me in business
But
But I
I really don't want to see you like this
You don't have to say it again
Anyway, my dad can't hear
He has been unconscious
No awareness at all
Hao Ming
Your dad
Sudden brain hemorrhage
This is not predictable
He is like this
I feel very uncomfortable
I want to come and see him again
Have you finished watching
Anyway, my mom will come in a while
He won't want to see you
Good good
Take good care of your dad
What is the need
I will do my best
You think
I and Lao Qu
Who is better?
It must be your dad
You are better at acting
Be careful
Before the end of the bidding
I have to tell you
I still want you to work hard
Stay here for a while
Row
Listen to you
You let me live in the hospital
To let Qu Mingcheng relax
The board of directors and his team
It's also your hand
Right
Mainly in the board of directors
In the board of directors
Many of the uncle and aunt
Are on your side
I went to them in private
I told them about this topic
They all agree
But
There is one thing
I didn't think too much
Qu Mingcheng and Huang Chu Ming
The bidding is internal news
Not everyone
You can ask around
Ok
Mr. Huang
Qu Mingcheng has been officially approved
The diamond block project
Designs a huge amount
Qu Mingcheng can't escape the legal sanctions
This scene
Finally ended
If it weren't for you, Mr. Huang
If you are in the game
The move to Qu Mingcheng's plan
It won't go so smoothly
Mr. Huang
Why did you choose
To cooperate with me?
To be honest
You and Shen Haoming
Have the same conditions
But you have the golden answer
Shen Haoming is too small
But I have a request
Say it
Except for our good deal
I also want you
In Hong Kong
Those two companies
I want you to be in Hong Kong
You are talking big
This is my only condition
You should know
That's what I have been thinking for years
When you become the official chairman
You won't be able to do anything for that side
But those two companies
Are very important to my layout in Hong Kong
You are the man
I won't force you
Is there any other choice?
This time I will accompany you to be the official secretary
I will get more revenge
One more
I don't think so
He is greedy
I am more greedy than him
He can trust me
According to the situation of both sides
He is indeed on the upper side
I have been thinking about one question for a long time
Why did Mr. Huang choose to trust me?
First, he pulled me as the target
He made a mistake at the beginning of this game
Second, you are very generous
You met my requirements
Third, you have been in the business for so many years
You have seen a lot of people
But there are few people you can trust
You should be honest
Haoming
I like both of you
I believe you will go further
Thank you
I have to go now
The phone is ringing
Grandpa
I just broke up with Mr. Huang
It went well
What?
Fang Lei came home
Ok, I will be back
What do you want to see me?
Look at this
I am sorry
Chenchen
He is not your child
What are you talking about?
Say something
What's going on?
My sister came to me suddenly
She told me she was pregnant
You are pregnant?
Whose child is it?
I don't know if the child belongs to Shen Haoming
What are you talking about?
You broke up with Haoming
Yes, but we have been separated for two months
Did he know?
I can't guarantee that he is the child
I went to the bar to drink on the day of the breakup
I met a Chinese painter
I didn't know he was the painter
I doubted the painter
We both drank a lot that day
Then
But it was the only time
Who is the painter?
Where is he now?
I didn't even keep the contact
What are you going to do now?
Later
My sister came to you
Tell me
The paternity test that year
Why does it prove that Chen Zhen and I are related by father and son?
Why?
It's all my fault
I thought
As long as you always think
Chen Chen is your biological child
Me and you
The relationship of this life
Can't be separated
Stay together
More smoothly
It's me
I know you're going to do the paternity test report
After the report
With the fake self-proclaimed
Replace the real result
You are a lunatic
I know I'm ridiculous and childish
Is this ridiculous and childish?
Is it your selfishness?
I know
I know I'm wrong
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I can go to Jingda now
I'll tell them
Chen Chen's real identity
So you and Uncle Shen
Can go back to the board of directors
Fang Lei
You are not human at all
You have no heart
Have you ever thought about Chen Chen's future?
What will Chen Chen do in the future?
Chen Chen finally got Haomi as a father
Do you know how much we have done?
How much he has done?
I tell you
I won't allow anyone to hurt Chen Chen
He can only stay with me
Do you understand?
Chen Chen will always be my son
Yanyan and I are his parents
This home
Is Chen Chen's home
I know
I'm sorry
I'm really sorry
Have some drinks.
Though more than that.
Great.
I'm a lawyer from the 15th District.
If you need anything,
just call me anytime.
What else do you want?
Steve went in with your godfather.
You should be glad
that you were abandoned by them
and became their wife.
Waiter,
get me a bottle.
I'm sorry.
So you're here to laugh at me, right?
Let's drink while we talk.
I'm going back to England.
Go ahead.
Come with me.
Compared to those people I don't know,
at least I know
that you're a bad person.
In order to avoid you going into society,
you'd better stay in my hands
so that you don't harm others.
I'll give you a day to think about it.
Haoming,
although Qu Mingcheng has left,
the case of Shen Family
has caused a great loss to Jin Da.
You're now proposing
to return the board of directors
and Jin Da.
We also want to ask you
what you can do for Jin Da.
Captain,
without a solid performance,
we can't get the board of directors.
My plan has never changed.
I'll take the North Overseas Spring and get the diamond money.
Jin Da has lost the right to bid.
The original funds
can be invested in my company,
Xinye.
You're going to do your own business
with Jin Da's money?
This...
When the bidding is successful,
Xinye will get the block
and we can develop it together with Jin Da.
We need to review
the bidding plan and development strategy.
I'm ready.
Please open it.
Before we start the meeting,
let's welcome
the new members of Yan Yifang.
Welcome.
Yan Yifang and Cao Muran's cooperation
has made the number of tourists in Gubei town
increase to 32%.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'd like to say something.
Yan Yifang's offline physical store
is about to start.
I hope we can not only promote
the new Chinese service,
but also create a chance
for more people
through offline layout.
It's very important.
So now, let's let Mr. Qiao
tell us about our offline layout.
Okay.
Next,
we'll focus on the plan for the next three years.
Our plan is to add 50 new stores
to the offline physical store.
We're expected to provide more than 300 job positions.
Okay.
Great.
Our marketing department
will combine the online and offline sales
to further enhance the platform.
Then, Cao Muran's new series of summer football
is looking forward to it.
Don't say that.
I can't wait.
You know, I practice so hard
at home every day.
Let me tell you.
Among our JTC colleagues,
there are your fans.
You know, they're all young.
Cao Muran.
Where are you going?
I'm not going to be a good friend of yours.
I'm going to be a good friend of yours.
It's definitely you, Wang Xiaolu.
I hope you'll continue to be wonderful.
The child has a cold.
Use the Kuihua child's Anfen Huang's immune system
to relieve the child's severe cold.
Kuihua invites you to continue to be wonderful.
What's wrong?
What did the board say?
They rejected it.
What's the reason?
They have no objections to the bidding plan.
But they are not very satisfied
with the development plan of North Overseas Sichuan.
They are not very satisfied with the development plan of North Overseas Sichuan.
They think it's a fair game.
Duygusal.
Take away a laugh.
No.
I can't do it.
Keep saying it.
No.
we've been looking for
the characteristics of the brand.
I remember the first time
I showed the proposal to Jiang Liang,
he rejected it completely.
That's why we changed the direction.
From the ultimate pursuit of fashion design
to the actual demand of the public
in fashion,
this change
opened Yan Yifang's eyes.
Yan Yan, do you remember
you told me
that you found that governments
are very important
to the inheritance and protection of human history?
That's right.
So,
can I hire you
as the co-pilot
of the North Overseas Ship?
Show me the proposal.
Here it is.
This one.
Look at the next one.
But this ship has been
followed by many
famous developers.
Thank you, shareholders,
for coming to our
project introduction
of the No. 1137 piece.
Mr. Shen,
please introduce
the features of the project.
After all, the last time we came back
was at this critical point.
This is our main building.
The elements of our design
are the core of Jiangshui.
The mobile water-wood wall technology
can enhance
our light and shadow effect.
Not bad.
This is a beautiful piece of art.
Mr. Shen,
this main building,
although we think it's good,
how can you be sure
that the No. 1137 piece
will become
the top piece of the project?
Regarding the cultural positioning
of our project,
please welcome
the famous art director
of our special project,
the famous
founder of Yan Yifang,
Miss Xu Yan,
to introduce the project.
Hello, shareholders.
I'm Xu Yan.
Regarding the design of the No. 1137 piece,
our initial plan
is to improve the value of the project
through cultural activities
and art exhibitions.
Most of the business complexes
in the past
were made by foreign brands
to show the core value.
However, in recent years,
consumers are increasingly interested
in Chinese style and consume for it.
So we can see
the rise of Chinese culture
and the improvement of national honor
and cultural confidence.
In the past three years,
the annual increase in the V-E consumer market
has exceeded 40%.
The market has now reached
150 billion yuan.
Last year,
the sales of Chinese style clothing
increased by 43%.
The increase of non-event handcrafted products
has increased by 60%.
Tell us more about your plan.
The core strategy of this project
is to introduce a series of
Chinese style lung brand.
We have three stages.
The first stage
will introduce
traditional textile memory brand,
such as Suzhou Su Xiu Memory,
Nanjing Yunjin Zhizao Memory,
and Hunan Xiangxiu Memory.
The second stage
will introduce
traditional craft brand,
such as
Yixing's Zishatou,
Longquan Qingci,
and Henan Ruchi.
The third stage
will introduce
jewelry and art brands.
Jin Si Fahlang Craft,
Hua Si Xiangqian,
and Jingtai Lan.
These brands
are all for our purpose
to create a non-event.
The purpose of our project
is to create
a sustainable and economic
cycle.
We want these craftsmen
to have a sustainable
and secure
sustainable development.
We hope
this area
is not a short-term
activity
or a exhibition.
We want them
to live here,
work here,
and have a sense of belonging
here.
How do we avoid
Jin Da's investment risk?
Shen Family's free funds
will be used as a reserve fund.
Jin Da's investment funds
will be used as priority funds.
You can get the profit
and take the risk.
I hope that
Jin Da's investment risk
will be reduced to the lowest.
After two and a half hours
and 186 rounds of sale,
the new building
has been sold for 38.06 billion yuan
and has been successfully sold
to the overseas market.
The price is 27.4 percent.
Mr. Shen,
do you have any plans
for the future development of Xinyi?
I want to say that
today is a day
of our company's ceremony.
I hope that everyone
will continue to follow us.
Thank you.
Today's meeting
is very meaningful.
First of all,
we need to get rid of
Mr. Shen Jinsong
and Mr. Shen Haoming's
compensation lawsuit
and recover all the jobs of the two people.
Next,
we need to re-discuss
the new personnel and mission arrangement.
Currently,
Jin Da and Xinyi
have successfully reached
the acquisition agreement
and jointly developed
the No. 1137
of Beiwai Pass.
Mr. Shen has made a great contribution
to this major cooperation.
He has shown his outstanding management
in the project operation.
After that,
he will build
a strong leadership team.
He will be in charge
of the whole project development.
After careful consideration,
I suggest
that Mr. Shen
officially join the board of directors
and be promoted to
the president of Jin Da Group.
Raise your hand if you agree.
Okay.
All votes are passed.
Congratulations, Mr. Shen.
Thank you, directors,
for your support and trust.
Thank you, everyone.
Okay.
I hope you can lead everyone
and Jin Da Group
to the right path.
Mr. Shen,
I will do my best
and not let you down.
I won't let you down.
I won't let you down
and my expectations.
Make more stuffing.
Grandma.
It's obvious that I made it.
It's obvious that you made it.
Why does it always look like this?
Yanyan,
no matter what you make,
I like it.
I think Haoming
will like it too.
He will.
He must like it.
Grandma, look.
How's my dumpling skin?
Not bad.
It's improved a lot.
Haoming,
actually, making dumplings
is a kind of goodwill.
You can eat it
and feel blessed.
You rolled the lucky wrapper here.
You made the stuffing.
I made the stuffing
and I'm the lucky one.
You're so good at talking.
Are you watching this online?
Are you staying up late again?
No.
Look at these
chubby dumplings.
I'm so happy.
And
we made
beef stuffing today.
It's so red.
You're a family.
The dumplings
will be the future of the imperial family.
We'll be blessed with a bright future.
Grandma.
Look.
If you stay here,
Haoming and I
can have a meal
every week.
But if you leave,
where can we eat dumplings?
How about
staying here?
I've been living here
for a while.
I miss
the flowers and grass in my yard.
And those chickens and ducks.
I ask my neighbors
to take care of them.
I think you're
really nice here.
You're happy.
But I still
want to go back to my yard.
I just want you
to have a happy life.
I'm contented.
What are you doing?
We're taking photos.
Today is reunion dinner.
Let's take a photo.
With dumplings?
Yes.
Let's take a selfie.
Here.
I...
Is it okay?
How can I take a photo?
Look at this.
Dumplings.
One, two, three.
Look.
What's wrong?
Grandma.
You're so beautiful.
She took half a photo with you.
No.
Look.
I'll perform a magic trick.
Okay?
Look.
Get ready.
Be careful.
Let me see.
Why did it run away?
What's this?
Why did it come out of the top?
What's going on?
Come on.
Change the line.
Look.
You have to dance.
Come on.
How can I use it?
Hold it.
Change it.
This is magic.
Hold it.
Okay.
Come on.
Warm up.
Okay.
Do you want to perform a magic trick?
Let's give it some power.
Okay.
Can I open it?
Yes.
Don't disappear.
It's colorful.
Yes.
Look.
The eyes in the photo are so big.
It's a line.
Line.
What does it mean?
Grandma, this is called...
This is called Pairide.
Grandma, look at your head.
It's stuck here.
You're so good at Pairide.
Look how happy you are.
I'm so happy.
Grandma, you're asleep.
Yes.
What are you looking at?
This is the gift I gave you.
Isn't this my photo album?
Look.
How old were you when you took this?
Twenty-three.
You've thanked me.
The flowers are blooming.
I've found the answer.
I've been through it all.
In the future,
it will become our family portrait.
Here.
Fill it up here.
I think by now you know it.
About me and you.
You're so happy.
I am too.
Right now, I'll still be here with you.
Yeah.
I like you here in my arms.
What already happened.
Feeling so lost and feeling so much distractions.
I never thought you could be with me.
You comfort my sadness.
At the street in the morning,
the vague corner of the street.
Right then,
you smile at me.
Yeah.
At that moment,
you and I are the only ones in the world.
I want to say I'm holding your hand in this world.
Laola.
I'll remind you again.
Call me if you need anything.
I know.
I've kept it in my heart.
Yan Yan, don't worry.
You and Ling Ling work hard.
We'll take care of Laolao.
Your mom and I want to sell the hair salon.
Then move to live with Laolao.
It's convenient to take care of her.
I'm relieved then.
Let's go. I'll see you off.
Don't see me off.
You'll be late for work.
Pack up quickly.
Mom, let's go.
Bye.
Mom and dad, you can come here anytime.
Come with me next time.
Stay a few more days.
Hold the phone on the ground.
Weint Uhm,
go back with me to Island of W especies.
I'll make some
Don't be afraid, it's cold.
Let's go.
Get up.
Actually, you don't have to be so anxious.
Who said Yan Yifang
is also one of the key targets
of this North Overseas Ship project?
Who asked me to sign the contract?
Now you say you're not anxious.
What's the matter?
Thank you, Director Xu, for agreeing to add me.
Okay.
Thank you.
Where's the operation?
Father said I can go now.
You...
We've already
agreed on the contract.
If Mr. Xu
has no problem,
we can sign the contract.
Mr. Shan,
have a good cooperation.
Have a good cooperation.
You...
That's all.
The bar is full
Let's walk forward
Look at the traffic line
Is this the Haar Organ?
The neatly-made warehouse
marked on the background
was named
It's the beginning of the new style
People who were SA
prefer to stay away from it
Better to stay way away
I just want to take my time tonight
This is so cool
So beautiful
Is it good?
Yes
I'll show you
I'll show you what I'm wearing
Are you going to post it on WeChat?
I don't know if you're more popular
My designer
I'll show you
The one Mr. Qiao wears is beautiful
You look so good
Yes
Thank you Mr. Qiao
Go try on the body coat
Dancing even if I'm the only one
Because I just have been here too many times
I want to wear this dress
I'm so busy
Who cares about who I'm not
You can't take it off from now on
Until the end of the winter
Keep wearing it
I saw this dress the next morning
So beautiful
You're about the same height as Yu Yiming
Go go go
You two match
I'll see if it matches
Go
So good
Is it suitable?
I think so
Not suitable
Don't move
Is it good?
So good
Wait a minute
I'll change the angle
Take a photo of this side
Don't move
Sweeter
You two look at it closer
Come on, come on, come on
I want to take a photo too
Come on
Don't move
I'll take a photo of this side
Because I just have been here too many times
I'm giving it all just getting nothing back
I was lost in the dark and too hurt to even see
See the world how it flows
What is yours will never let go
So I take my time to reunite
The love that I should deserve
When the time is right
And you realize that it will be alright