♪That day♪
♪Nothing stays together forever♪
♪I've quit romance♪
♪Who hasn't failed again♪
♪Crying in death♪
♪And in life♪
♪Even now♪
♪We keep learning♪
♪It's no surprise♪
♪Being happy is so hard♪
♪Weirdly, I became a role model♪
♪On the day we met again, we said hi♪
♪It was a reminder,
a test, and a complaint♪
♪Who can do anything without regret♪
♪I am all right♪
♪May you live in peace♪
♪Let the world roar♪
♪Sounds like a carnival♪
♪Being alive is never dull♪
♪How wonderful to be free♪
♪I became even better without you♪
♪Nothing can be perfect♪
♪We bless each other in pain♪
♪We nod and smile♪
♪May we both be well♪
= Love's Ambition=
=Episode 3=
Run!
Good for you!
Awesome!
Impressive!
Come on!
Give it to me!
Good!
Incredible!
Well done.
You're so clever.
Let's do it again!
Come on. It's inedible.
You can't eat it.
Ms. Yu.
Come on.
Come here.
Ms. Yu.
I bought you a scarf,
the latest fashion.
I hope you'll like it.
Miss Xu.
Next time I...
Miss Xu, what did you buy?
Let me see.
A cashmere scarf?
Miss Xu.
You're mistaken.
Your future mother-in-law
prefers a solid-colored scarf
without printed patterns.
Ms. Ma.
If she hasn't paid much attention,
how would she know?
Then you should be careful.
Or you'll make a fool of yourself again.
Miss Xu.
Cashmere scarves
have many details to consider.
The higher the thread count,
the softer it is.
She definitely won't
wear the scarf you bought.
Bu.
Over here.
Sweetheart.
Bu.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Amy, come.
Miss Xu.
The scarf Miss Xu bought
is Italian,
100% cashmere.
It's good stuff.
Back then,
when I was at school,
I didn't study hard.
I always ran off to travel.
When short on money,
I traded cashmere scarves
for cash.
That's why it's called cashmere.
I already
have many scarves of the same color.
It suits your fair complexion.
Keep it for yourself.
I have to go.
Look, Bu.
Brilliant!
Come here.
Bu.
Lan.
I think that girl
has poor taste in every aspect.
Think again.
Don't rush the engagement.
Claire.
Come.
All done?
Miss Xu.
You're so kind.
Very easygoing.
You're even shopping with me.
Haochen and Haoming
both love
your cooking so much.
You master
both Chinese
and Western cuisine.
Hui.
You must teach me how to cook.
With enough practice,
you gain experience.
Miss Xu.
Grab me a box of lychees.
Sure.
Is this okay?
Yes, absolutely.
I'll put it in.
Thanks.
No problem.
Here.
Hui.
I found another advantage of you.
You take good care
of Ms. Yu's family.
And you also
care for her friends.
You're a perfect domestic worker.
Miss Xu.
People like Ms. Meng
aren't as easygoing as you.
They're all calculating.
Ms. Yu
spends much time with them.
If they badmouth me,
I'll lose my job.
But from what I see,
Ms. Yu is an independent lady.
She actually listens to them?
Miss Xu.
I genuinely think you're a good girl,
so I'm telling you this.
In the past,
someone tried to set Haoming up
with a girlfriend.
But that girl
just couldn't
win Ms. Yu's friends over.
They all
chimed in
and eventually convinced Ms. Yu.
So, Ms. Yu
rejected that girl outright.
Ms. Yu's friends
hold significant influence, huh?
You said it.
Those whom they dislike
won't be accepted by Ms. Yu.
They're critical
of Ms. Yu's daughter-in-law.
Hui.
Wait a moment.
Are two boxes enough?
In this season,
cherries are a must.
I remember
you love cherries.
I'll buy them for you.
Go.
These two boxes cost hundreds!
This is too much.
Take them for your children.
Thank you then.
I forgot to buy shrimp.
Let's buy it.
Alright.
(I know)
(Yu Lan and her friends)
(haven't truly accepted me.)
(To marry Haoming,)
(I must fully fit into the family)
(and the circle.)
(My only option)
(is to take the initiative.)
Nice shot!
Take a break.
It feels good to sweat.
It is hot today,
right?
Coach.
Let's take it easy today.
Yes.
Wipe your sweat.
Hurry.
I'm sweaty.
It's so hot.
Ms. Yu is as energetic as ever.
Absolutely!
After all, I do yoga every day.
You invited her?
Yes.
She's free today,
so I asked her here.
It's a chance to get to know her.
Unexpectedly,
she can't play tennis.
Have you met her parents?
Yes.
They're intellectuals.
They've lived abroad for years.
Her father
is a professor at Syracuse University.
No wonder she's so well-mannered.
She is
quite sensible.
To marry into Ms. Yu's family,
she has to be sensible.
I think
she is low-key and unassuming.
She is not simple, anyway.
Miss Xu.
No need to do this.
The coach will
collect these balls.
I can do it quickly.
So you won't have to wait long.
Miss Xu.
You really don't have to.
You're doing just fine.
Just relax.
Don't be on edge all the time.
Sometimes, being too tense
is not good.
Thanks, Meiling.
Ms. Yu.
Ms. Meng, Ms. Ma.
What a coincidence!
You're here too.
Ms. Meng.
You look much slimmer
than the last time we met.
Not really.
Honestly,
you've lost weight.
I've been
to some parties
with my husband.
Some late nights made me
gain weight.
Really?
You're not showing at all.
- Exactly!
- You think?
You're not showing.
Please.
We all know
you're a social person.
Without you, your husband
wouldn't have met Mr. Zheng
and secured the biggest project.
That's just
part of my job.
You're luckier than me.
You have a good husband and a good son.
I'm just born to worry too much.
I-I've been the same lately.
You know what?
I've been hitting the gym daily.
My husband
tries to do business with the CEO
of Boyue Group.
His wife happens to
be a fashion designer.
To get closer
to her, I need
to squeeze
into the outfits she designs.
Going all out for your husband?
Demand a bigger bonus this year!
Ms. Yu, stop teasing me!
I'm telling you,
a socially adept wife
is essential to her husband's business.
Some bachelors
focus solely on work.
They're competent,
but without a wife's support,
they're like one-legged men,
unable to get far.
Remember the last gathering?
Ms. Qu is here.
Ms. Qu, you're finally here!
- You finally came.
- You made it!
We haven't started yet.
You should've begun.
Take a seat.
Ms. Qu.
Your complexion looks much better
than last time.
Truly,
you look so well.
By the way, Ms. Qu,
I heard your husband
landed major projects.
He never stays idle.
I keep telling him
health matters more than money.
Ms. Qu,
could you have your husband
help my husband?
Let's go
and play.
Come on.
Let's go.
Coach, I need a break.
- Let me help.
- I'm tired.
Thanks, Miss Xu.
No problem.
Have some water.
Thanks.
Who is that?
That is the director of Lanshan Capital,
and also Mr. Xiao's wife.
Lanshan Capital
is hot these days.
Women want to use her connections
to benefit their own husbands.
Impressive.
Women try to please her.
She is very proud.
I once asked my friend
to arrange a meeting with her.
But she put on airs
and refused.
Go.
Two, two, three, four.
One.
Two.
Three.
Not bad.
You're dancing very well.
Let's try
one more move.
Okay.
Watch me.
See?
Two wrist rotations.
One up
and one down.
Combine two into one move.
So one up,
and one down.
Sure. Try it.
One up, one down.
Well?
Like this?
Too hard.
Watch me again.
Like this.
My friend told me
that Ms. Qu
doesn't have many hobbies,
except being crazy about Kunqu Opera.
She even funded
a Kunqu Opera competition
for amateurs.
Up, down.
Not like that.
Take your time.
Let me show you.
This is so hard.
It is challenging.
Here, watch.
One, two.
One, two, yes.
Today
is our first lesson.
So,
we'll start
with the basics.
- The opera...
- Ma'am!
Excuse me,
can you just teach me how to
swing sleeves?
Swing sleeves.
Haste makes waste.
You're a beginner.
I suggest we start
with the basics.
I have a question.
If I practice day and night,
how long until I master it?
At least a month.
So we should
start with the basics.
You have to
be patient.
No.
I only learn water sleeves.
Doing water sleeves, remember
not to use
your upper arm.
Use wrist and forearm.
Switching sides,
it's
one up, one down.
Up, down.
Correct.
Keep them flat.
Your upper arms shouldn't
exert too much force.
Same with both hands.
See? The upper arms barely move.
Let your forearms and wrists lead.
Then turn.
Up, down. Up, down.
Give it a try.
Use your forearm and wrist.
Like this.
Yes, good.
♪There's no reason
not to lose control for this♪
♪All the year round♪
♪I feel different about you♪
Up and down.
♪As lucky as we are♪
♪Two passionate hearts are♪
♪In perfect harmony♪
♪Since the day I met you♪
♪I've been looking forward to each trip♪
♪We can go anywhere♪
Xu Yan.
All departments are almost ready.
Good.
Run through it again,
and we'll start recording.
Xu Yan.
What are you doing?
Tenosynovitis.
Typing too much causes this.
Come on.
Let's get ready.
Get ready.
Come on.
Okay, let's begin now.
Be ready to start.
♪I've been looking forward to each trip♪
♪We can go anywhere♪
♪With you by my side♪
♪Rain or shine♪
Well done.
Go back and rest.
That's all for today's class.
Ma'am.
Can I stay here
and practice?
Sure.
No one's using it later.
Keep practicing.
Thank you.
♪Since the day I met you♪
♪I've been looking forward to each trip♪
♪We can go anywhere♪
Can't you take a break for once?
(Grandma)
It's different.
Kunqu Opera emphasizes posture
and techniques.
Practice is essential.
By the way,
the hospital's follow-up report
came back.
Your cholesterol levels are still high.
So I got you fish oil capsules.
Three times daily,
take them half an hour before meals.
Remember
to take them daily.
Okay.
Send them by courier.
I will
send them all.
Remember to collect them.
Okay.
How's your Kunqu Opera practice
coming along?
Did the teacher comment
on your progress?
The teacher praised me,
saying I'm learning fast.
I should thank you.
You always told me as a kid,
"Learn various skills.
Having more never burdens you."
So the teacher praised me.
Right?
Listen to me more. It pays off.
Okay, I will.
Well, one more thing,
do you have time to come visit me?
After I
finish this busy period.
Then I'll return
to keep you company.
I even bought you a set
of Kunqu Opera costumes.
I'll teach you then.
We'll both practice.
Okay, you go ahead.
I'm going to sleep.
Okay, go and rest.
It's already late.
Sleep soon. Goodnight.
Focus on your waist movement.
Side waist.
Watch the hands.
Final pose.
Finish with the waist.
Yes.
Right.
Good.
Excellent.
That's all for today's lesson.
Go rest early.
Ma'am.
I know.
Extra time?
Okay.
Bye.
Thanks.
Miss.
Is that girl new here?
I haven't seen her before.
Right, she's new here.
She's smart.
She achieved this in days.
Hello.
I noticed your water sleeve techniques
are excellent.
Thank you.
The teacher mentioned
you just started learning?
I've loved it since childhood.
Back then, I just found it beautiful.
Now that I'm older,
I finally grasp its deeper essence.
So I'm studying it now.
That's rare.
To be so young
and already love Kunqu Opera.
Likewise, I've loved it since childhood.
We're organizing
a Kunqu Opera enthusiasts competition.
I'm the organizer.
I was thinking,
as the organizer,
if I couldn't perform,
people might laugh at me.
So I came here to learn intensively.
By the way,
I'm Qu Li.
Hello, Ms. Li.
I'm Xu Yan.
You're talented.
You should join
our competition.
No problem.
Wonderful!
The class has ended.
Let's practice together.
Help me get the rhythm right.
Perfect.
I was just needing a break.
Let me observe you.
My water sleeves
never flow properly.
Can you find out what's wrong?
Look. See?
I can't move them like you do.
Try keeping
some space between your body
and your sleeves.
Toss them outward slightly.
- A gentle toss.
- Like this?
Right.
Release and retrieve smoothly.
Maintain distance between
your hands and torso.
Right.
Like this,
they'll flow naturally.
That's right.
Got it.
You pinpoint key details well.
That's it.
I need to take this call.
Okay.
Zhao?
Yes.
That
Rhine International School.
Yes.
It's for Hao.
They have
absolutely no vacancies?
Alright.
You must have prior training.
Judging by your posture,
you've surely studied dance.
No, I haven't.
Actually, I'm a TV host.
A host?
What show?
Family Feast.
Seen it?
Wait, I think
I've watched your show.
It features celebrities
cooking together?
Right.
But we're
revamping the format.
We're planning to invite
influential women from various fields
to join us.
I'm sorry.
But I'm needed
somewhere else.
Qu Li?
She'll really come?
Of course.
That's why I'm inviting you
to join Family Feast.
Miss Xu,
if Ms. Qu is coming,
I'll definitely be there.
Meiling,
I've prepared a provisional guest list.
Please see if there's anyone you know.
For the show recording,
having familiar faces around
would be better.
Miss Xu,
good thing you came to ask me.
You should know
there's a lot of tension
among these women.
Let me explain in detail.
You want to replace guests?
Yes.
Here's the revised proposal.
Xiao Nanpeng's wife?
Lanshan Capital's
global executive partner.
She's agreed
to join our next episode.
What about other guests?
We've already secured Ms. Qu.
I believe
female representatives from other fields
shouldn't be an issue.
Mr. Zhou,
our show has been
running for three years.
Nowadays,
celebrities are losing interest
in our format.
We need to reignite audience engagement.
Besides keeping celebrity guests,
we should invite
influential figures from various fields
to participate.
This could create fresh dynamics.
If the show delivers,
viewers will naturally want
to join future episodes.
This is an excellent idea.
I support you.
But I have one condition.
Resubmit my request
to transition
to hosting.
I'll make it happen.
Just go for it.
Thank you, Mr. Zhou.
Ms. Li,
I understand
you have zero interest
in joining our show.
Then why approach me?
What if it's a show
tailor-made for you?
(Special Guest: An Yaqin)
A board member
of Rhine International School
will be attending.
You investigated me?
Just trying to assist.
I could meet them
without your help.
With your capabilities,
connecting with them is possible,
but building relationships quickly
isn't that easy.
Through a TV show,
you could naturally
develop friendships.
It's mutually beneficial.
Right?
Unfortunately,
I don't cook.
How about being
the Kunqu Opera
competition's initiator?
Join our show,
and I'll create a special segment
showcasing Kunqu Opera for you.
Joining our show
would both
help promote Kunqu Opera
and allow you to connect
with like-minded individuals.
Most importantly,
the broadcast could spread
Kunqu Opera's beauty
to wider audiences.
You've devoted
your life to this art form.
Isn't this what you want?
Additionally,
I'm willing to host
your opera fan competition
free of charge.
Though I wonder
if I'm worthy of this honor.
Thank you so much, Ms. Li,
for using a traditional Chinese opera,
Kunqu Opera,
to give us
such a magnificent opening.
First, let me introduce
today's distinguished new guests.
The renowned actress,
Ms. Xue Yuqing.
Hello.
I'm Xue Yuqing, an actress.
Welcome to our show.
National Class-A Public Nutritionist,
Ms. He Jingshu.
Hello.
Board member
of Rhine International School,
Ms. An Yaqin.
And young female entrepreneur
representative,
Ms. Sun Meiling.
Welcome, all of you.
By the way,
Ms. Yuqing,
I heard your new drama
is currently trending.
In the series, you play
a strong-willed
female imperial chef.
What dishes
left a deep impression
on you?
Qianlong-style cabbage,
cherry-braised pork,
and braised deer tendon.
When you participate
in the cooking process,
you realize
the craftsmanship,
the precision,
and every detail involved
culminate in
truly achieving
acme in color, aroma, taste,
concept, and presentation.
Well articulated.
Ms. Li,
your husband is known
in business circles
as the 'Iron Man of Commerce'.
He often works around the clock.
Caring for such a dedicated partner
must be demanding.
Could you share
your signature homemade dish
with us?
Xiao's work keeps him extremely busy.
In terms of diet,
we prioritize quick and simple meals.
What we regularly prepare
are staple foods,
paired with light congee
and side dishes.
The Qianlong-style cabbage
you mentioned earlier
is also Xiao's favorite.
It's Qianlong-style cabbage too.
Why don't we have
a live cooking challenge?
Let's have Ms. Li and Ms. Yuqing
both prepare that dish
and see whose is more authentic.
Meiling,
I heard your culinary skills
are exceptional too.
My husband particularly loves
my cooking.
So
I cook for him daily.
Then let me divide the teams.
Meiling,
you'll join Ms. Li
and Ms. Yaqin.
I'll team up with Ms. Jingshu
and Ms. Yuqing.
Okay?
Wonderful.
Let's move to
our kitchen.
(Family Feast)
Many of my friends' kids
attend Rhein School.
They all praise its excellent ethos.
This is the most meticulously
prepared cabbage I've ever seen.
I learned this during filming.
Need any assistance?
Not just yet.
You can observe first.
Should I add honey first?
Absolutely.
Honey is essential.
That explains it.
I hadn't added honey before,
so it tastes odd.
Check their progress.
When making this dish,
the taste's not right.
What's going on?
Someone
is trying to steal our secret.
Ms. Yuqing,
Ms. Jingshu,
they secretly added honey.
It's fine.
We have our own secret too.
Don't copy us now.
This is Ms. Li's secret recipe.
Looks nice on camera.
Meiling.
Your husband's building
a hot spring resort in Wenzhou.
He's been wanting
to discuss investments with Xiao.
Now you helped him
connect with Qu Li.
It's a major contribution.
Looks like
the year-end bonus came early this year.
You mean this?
Just a small reward.
The year-end bonus
has to be something bigger.
Stop watching.
Let's chat for a bit.
You see how I am,
not photogenic and a bit chubby.
Not bad.
Looks good.
If you say so, then it must be.
Miss Xu,
your show is quite interesting.
Thank you, Ms. Ma.
For the next Family Feast episode,
Ms. Qu will still attend.
Ms. Ma, Ms. Meng, I wonder
if you will have time.
Ms. Yu said
she reserved spots for both of you.
Ms. Yu,
why are you so kind to us?
Thanks.
Of course.
When good things happen,
I think of my besties first.
So when's
the next episode?
Monday.
Monday?
That's just a few days away.
I'll go back first
to do my hair.
I also need to go get a facial
and a manicure.
I get it.
Alright, Ms. Yu.
Thank you.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
See you Monday.
- See you Monday.
- Bye.
Thanks. See you.
Miss Xu.
So can I be
on the next episode?
Of course.
Ms. Yu said
you looked especially dazzling on TV.
Then I should go back
and make myself presentable.
I've got to go.
I need to hurry
and contact my tailor,
Mr. Fang.
My dresses have embroidery.
Top-notch.
I'll introduce him.
Bye, Miss Xu. Thanks.
Yan.
Ms. Yu.
Running a show is tough work.
How could you casually push those favors
onto me?
The caliber of guests
determines the show's quality
and value.
I'm just a planner
and on-screen host.
I have limited influence.
But you're different.
With you guiding me
and paving the way, I'm confident
we can create
a good and well-received show.
Here, sit.
Many people get things done,
but few have real vision.
I still have much to learn from you.
Good girl.
Ms. Yu.
It's still hot.
(To seize every opportunity
for a comeback,)
(never pin your hopes)
(on others.)
(It's simply)
(using what you have)
(to get what you want.)
(Ratings)
Miss Xu.
This episode's results are excellent.
In both ratings and reviews.
Impressive.
Keep this up in the future.
Sir,
as for Sun Siwei...
Don't factor her in.
Sent to outdoor shoots.
You know her temperament.
Arguments aside,
she can't deny the show's quality.
No grounds for complaints there.
Thank you for your support.
I'd surely
support a good idea.
Miss Xu.
Earlier, you mentioned
there was something else to discuss?
It's about the show's sponsorship fee.
This company
keeps pushing to finalize the contract.
The sponsorship fee
is 12% higher than before.
If you approve,
we can proceed.
Why are you negotiating
sponsorship fees with me?
Mr. Liu,
I'm in charge now.
(Celebrity and Special Guests)
The latest guest list
for Family Feast.
Please review it.
Are you sure these people
can be invited?
It can be written down,
but with a 12% increase
in the sponsorship fee.
(12% sponsorship fee increase)
Miss Xu.
I knew you wouldn't
betray my trust.
(Party B: Anya Mountain Dairy Co., Ltd.)
Pen.
Yan.
Did you see
Mr. Zhou's expression
when he saw the weekly report?
He was grinning from ear to ear.
Our show's comeback success
has agents bombarding our phones.
They're eager to collaborate.
Even the top-rated actress
for the next episode
is confirmed.
Thank you.
(Yan, money transfer)
Yan,
what are you doing?
I can't take it.
Your father's hospitalized.
You need money.
Don't refuse.
Introducing Director Lu to me
was helpful enough.
Without you,
I could never reach
a hospital director.
Huanhuan.
Resources exist to be utilized.
Besides, right now,
the surgery comes first.
May the operation go smoothly.
Juggling work and family lately
must be exhausting.
Eat a lot today to replenish.
Choose.
My treat.
What'll you have?
The usual food.
Okay.
Congratulations, Yan.
You become Family Feast's host.
We've all witnessed
your dedication
to this show.
Thank you, Liao.
Oh,
join us for dinner tonight.
You're too kind.
Siwei.
You're here early today.
What are you implying?
Siwei always starts
makeup at this hour.
Wait.
Your outdoor shoot
is scheduled for 6 PM,
arranged after Family Feast.
It's only 3 PM now.
Don't we usually
do makeup two hours beforehand?
Show schedules are one thing,
makeup schedules are another.
Since when does the makeup team
have the authority
to dictate
our filming schedule?
I...
You can't do my makeup?
Fine.
Your phone.
Wait.
I'll call Mr. Zhou to clarify.
If the outdoor shoot today
runs overtime,
who takes responsibility
for missing the golden hour?
No, Siwei.
You got me wrong.
I mean...
Liao,
do her makeup first.
I can wait.
Okay.
Siwei,
please wait a moment.
I'll get your touch-up kit.
You need touch-ups now?
Your makeup will be ruined
during the shoot.
Why make things hard for others?
Who do you think you are?
You just hosted one episode
and suddenly act
like my equal?
Other shows invited me,
but I worry about you.
My episode averaged
a 4 rating.
Yours got 1.
How could I leave?
Did you write
the proposal yourself?
Or did your rich boyfriend buy it?
You know my capabilities well.
My team and I
can complete such tasks
on our own.
No boyfriend assistance needed.
You couldn't compete fairly,
so you went to get a rich boyfriend?
Xu Yan,
I never realized
you were so ambitious
and scheming.
I secure exclusives,
handle full production
and have professional skills.
Why shouldn't I compete for it?
I never consider
ambition and strategy
to be insults.
I'll take it as praise.
Thanks.
How can she be this shameless?
Right.
When she first joined,
I distinctly remember
her saying she only had a grandmother.
Now, suddenly her parents are overseas?
A highly educated family?
Is she hiding
her background and working
'to experience life'
like some reality show folks?
Impossible.
Her shabby appearance
doesn't seem faked.
Must be it.
The other day,
I saw her wearing
a diamond bracelet
with one-carat stones.
Isn't she marrying
a construction company's heir?
Those families
care most about women's status.
Yan.
I've emailed you the proposal.
Anything else?
Send the interview outline
to the guests beforehand.
Okay.
I'm off.
Go.
(Good evening, everyone.)
(Welcome)
(Global Stock Market Trends)
(to tonight's Financial News.)
(This year,
the global stock market faces)
(both opportunities and challenges.)
(The downside,)
(the tech stock bubble burst)
(is still weighing on the market.)
(The upside,)
(the rise of emerging markets)
(has provided)
(new growth opportunities.)
(China, leveraging)
(its stable economic policies)
(and vast market potential,)
(has captured global attention.)
Qiao Yan is recovering well.
She'll be discharged in two days.
Thank you, doctor.
Thank you.
After discharge,
make sure she
gets enough sleep.
No exhaustion.
I will.
I'll take good care of her.
Good.
(Acquire and disseminate
cultural information.)
(It has made China's stock market)
(a prime target)
(for international capital.)
Yan.
How did you get in?
I met Huanhuan downstairs.
She swiped me in.
Are you here alone?
Working overtime?
What can I do for you?
Perfect timing.
I can't decide
on some dishes.
Your taste is good.
Help me choose.
Let me look.
Go.
(Hangzhou Cuisine)
Look.
This is the Hangzhou cuisine series.
Here's Longjing shrimp.
The recipe.
This is Dongpo pork.
This is...?
A pearl necklace.
Congratulations
on your promotion.
A gift for the hostess
of Family Feast.
Thank you.
Your surprises always come first.
Do you like it?
Of course I do.
Now that you're officially a hostess,
do you have your own office?
Program hosts don't get one,
but news anchors
have private offices.
Then become a news anchor.
News anchoring
is highly competitive.
And I don't even
have news reporting experience.
It's an uphill battle.
Others might struggle,
but for you,
I've always had faith.
I believe you
can make the impossible
possible.
You trust I can do this?
Pursue what you want.
I'm waiting
to throw a party for you.
But first,
let me solve your current problem.
Leave work soon.
It's getting late.
(Everything moves)
(towards my desired direction,)
(but I refuse to believe)
(that lies can be seamless.)
(They only tighten their grip)
(around my throat,)
(choking me slowly.)
(Perhaps deception's purpose)
(isn't to fool others)
(but to delude oneself.)
(The family I tried to erase)
(was never truly gone.)
Look at this one.
It's truly exceptional.
Our past events
are all
pretty similar.
Everyone's long found them boring.
Your program is fantastic.
They are so enthusiastic now.
Some even pull strings to join.
True.
Smart people always
know how to mobilize resources.
Right?
I didn't understand before,
Mr. Shen.
Thank you.
It's through spending time
with Ms. Yu recently
and attending several banquets
that I've just started
learning a little.
Such a sweet talker.
You little rascal.
Slow down, okay?
I want cartoons!
- Your homework?
- Be careful.
- Homework done?
- Yes.
Remember.
Only half an hour of TV.
You're spoiling him again.
Have some tea.
(Now,)
(let's welcome...)
Dad!
Isn't that you?
(Mr. Shen Jinsong)
(and merchant representatives)
(will cut the ribbon)
(for the street project.)
(Let's count down together.)
(Three,)
(two,)
(one.)
(Please cut the ribbon.)
(Let's applaud to congratulate)
(Yunjiangli, Dayun County...)
Honey, you look good on camera.
Not too old to look at yet.
Right?
(Let's move to the center)
(for a group photo.)
(How do you feel?)
(Well, very...)
(I-I-I...)
(On behalf of all the merchants)
(in the street,)
(let me say thank you)
(to Jinda Group and Chairman Shen)
(for creating)
(a good business environment)
(and boosting)
(commercial development.)
(Yunjiangli Commercial Street Project,
Dayun County, Shanxi Province)
(We'll continue as always)
(to fulfill our duties)
(and serve our fellow villagers.)
(Yunjiangli...)
Xu,
you're from Shanxi, right?
(A representative project)
(to promote urban development)
(and life quality.)
(The former Yunjiangli had)
(narrow roads.)
Right.
Uh,
have you been to Dayun County?
(Widening the roads)
(and adding accessible pathways)
(throughout the area.)
My grandmother
is from Yunlai Village in Dayun County.
♪Like fireworks that loved♪
♪Rushing toward the stars♪
♪Undaunted by pain♪
♪Fearless of flames♪
♪Even if it's just a fleeting sparkle♪
♪We shed tears♪
♪Deep blue seas turn to foam♪
♪We regained freedom♪
♪If you remember me♪
♪Then I'm pleased♪
♪I just wanna take my time tonight♪
♪To do all the things I said I'd try♪
♪I go surfing, go diving, go driving,
and go flying to a different place♪
♪I go drink, go party, and go dance♪
♪Even if I'm lonely♪
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all to get nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love I should deserve♪
♪When the time is right♪
♪You realize♪
♪It will all be alright♪
♪Cause I just have been hurt
too many times♪
♪I'm giving it all to get nothing back♪
♪I was lost in the dark,
and it's too hurt to even see♪
♪See the world and how it flows.
We never let go♪
♪So I'll take my time♪
♪To reignite♪
♪The love I should deserve♪
♪When the time is right♪
♪You realize♪
♪It will all be alright♪