Characters, actions, occupations and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only. They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series. Viewer discretion is advised.
UNAR is well-known but he’s anonymous.
Nobody knows who he truly is.
Don’t follow me
if you want no regrets.
You’ve been worse after the fire, Black.
I just feel like Black has changed.
It isn’t like him at all.
Stay with me at the garage.
I will train you to be as good as you once were.
No.
It’s not true.
Sean.
Help me.
Why are you huddling me?
I’m not. You are.
It’s like you’re having a fever last night.
I checked up on you. Then you pulled my hand close and hugged me tightly.
That’s how I ended up like this.
Did I really do that?
It’s tear gas. Watch out!
Open up!
Move.
Take it.
Don’t rub your eyes.
You two took so long to realize it and get out.
What the heck are you playing?
I’m not playing. I’m coaching you.
Coaching what? We almost died.
If you could put out the gas quickly, you wouldn’t end up like this.
That’s your way of coaching?
We were sleeping.
In the real situation,
you will get shot if you act like a sitting duck.
They don’t care what’s right or wrong.
You must always be wide awake.
Be ready for what’s to come.
What could we have done?
That’s a bedroom.
We must flee as soon as possible.
Black, there are blankets and water in your room.
You have things to use to put out the gas.
Remember to extinguish it as soon as possible.
Who could even concentrate in that situation?
Always have a presence of mind, Sean.
You’ve changed so much.
Why?
You’ve never been this kind.
Do you remember the first day we went out for a mission?
(I just never thought dilemma could come from such a small thing like this.)
Why do you look like you don’t remember?
You can’t remember, can you?
Why?
Did you bring that up just to reopen my memory?
No, I don’t want to.
But what you just did today was odd.
What did I do?
You helped me.
You never cared about me or helped me before.
You were an asshole, you know that?
You’re the one that formed our group after we ousted the chancellor.
You couldn’t tolerate him because he deprived the students’ right to share their views.
You do that end.
Quickly.
I know.
Come on. Someone is here.
Sean, faster.
Let’s go.
What are you guys doing? Stop!
Stop!
Freeze!
Let go of me!
Black!
You got me suspended, remember?
You also said if we got caught, we must admit what we did.
If we didn’t want to go down, try to survive the situation.
You remember every word I said?
You forgot your own words.
What a scumbag!
I am a scumbag.
So?
I helped you because I knew Gumpa was testing us.
Yeah?
If I didn’t help, he would yell at me.
So you’re afraid of him yelling now?
No. I’m just annoyed.
Is that so?
Yes.
If that was real, I would just let you die.
Don’t hold me back next time.
Don’t you want to know who hurt Black?
Think about it. A girlfriend must be someone close to him.
And someone close should know everything.
Call her.
Is she Black’s girlfriend?
‘I’m sharing my old paintings for now.’
‘I might stop going out there to paint for a while since I’m being watched.’
Why did he paint me?
He must have lost his mind.
Who is this?
‘Don’t share it anywhere. I’m afraid you might be in danger.’
(Hello. My name is Black.)
(Let’s see what I’m gonna do today.)
(Don’t.)
Just a little.
Black, I don’t have a video of you.
Can’t I keep some?
Let me record a video.
(No.)
Why not?
(Are you done with the dance practice?)
I am.
So tired.
(Show me the dance.)
What will I get if I do?
What will I get?
Is she Black’s girlfriend?
Are they keeping their relationship a secret?
(Why did you send me a picture of Eugene?)
(Where do they normally do the dance rehearsal?)
(But you two broke up, didn’t you?)
(I just have something to talk to her about.)
(Try the faculty.)
Which faculty?
♪ I carry my hawker, selling things to others ♪
♪ I’m poor, I endure the hustle ♪
♪ Never hustling my wife and kids ♪
♪ I never got used to being enslaved by the bill ♪
♪ Grit my teeth and keep on saving money ♪
♪ While the ruling class still reign over the country ♪
♪ I have a voice but hold no right ♪
♪ I have ideas but they are constrained ♪
♪ They say I’m a serf, a farmer, a labourer ♪
♪ They say I’m leeching off the country ♪
♪ A slave to the politicians ♪
♪ I’m a f*cking pawn in the power game ♪
♪ Be whatever they desire ♪
♪ Anything but a human ♪
♪ Human worthiness is worthless while we’re still standing ♪
♪ Branded a working animal, but we’re still human ♪
♪ Degraded, humiliated, but we’re still human ♪
♪ Made to grovel, be trampled on, but then… ♪
♪ Because I’m afraid, so I rise to question ♪
♪ Because I’m enraged, so I rise to question ♪
♪ Because I’m oppressed, so I rise to question ♪
♪ Because I’m dispossessed, so I rise to question ♪
Wow! She’s good.
Excuse me one second.
Black.
Black!
Mr. White is here, sir.
This is your room?
How much is the rent?
I’m not renting it.
It’s my building.
Your building?
Is it over 10 billion?
No idea.
I got it after my dad died.
Follow me.
What is your father’s business?
Import, export, produce, retail,
whatever there is, I do it all.
You’re imperial.
I should start calling you President Todd now.
Nope!
Call me Mr. President Todd.
So why did you sound anxious over the phone?
I found a girl.
Is she Black’s girlfriend?
I am not very sure.
I just met her.
You met her already?
I didn’t talk to her though.
She saw me and I ran away.
You ran away from her? What a chicken!
I’m not Black. Why would I want to see her?
All the more reason to see her.
Don’t you want to know who hurt Black?
Think about it. A girlfriend must be someone close to him.
And someone close should know everything.
Call her.
No.
I don’t want to get caught.
Caught?
You two are like two peas in a pod.
She can never tell. Trust me.
What did you say her name was again?
Eugene.
Are you calling her?
She didn’t pick up.
She might not be available.
If she calls back, ask her to meet up.
Meet up?
Yes, at your place.
My place?
If you take her out to eat and talk, you might get caught.
But if you two meet at your place, you can just stay quiet.
It won’t be weird.
Do you think it’s a good idea?
Are you afraid?
You’re afraid something sexy might happen.
Are you nuts?
I won’t do anything to my brother’s girlfriend.
You guys are twins.
You are exactly alike.
Or maybe you don’t have it?
I do.
I just don’t want to make her look bad.
Stop joking around. What should I do?
If I were you, I’d definitely meet her.
She might know something about Black.
And I’m sure you can get out of any troubling situation.
(Please call me back. I’m waiting.)
You’ve been very punctual these days.
You are 15 minutes early.
Honey.
Are you keeping up with the news on the fire?
Not really. I’ve been busy.
What’s up?
It’s becoming quiet.
Tawi isn’t even charged with anything.
We did everything we could.
If the media won’t be our mouthpiece,
and the officers don’t dig into it,
things will always end up the same way.
It’s always been like this.
How can we just stand and watch, right?
Sean.
Why is he here?
It’s a special lecture class for both faculties.
What’s the problem between you two?
Tired of seeing his face.
We’re honored to welcome one of the most anticipated guests.
He is a specialist in Thai history and has a significant number of academic work.
Please welcome Dr. Charus Kanchananiran.
I’m just going to leave this class to you.
Thank you very much.
Thanks to Professor Supoj and every one of you for having me.
Today, I've been requested to go in-depth on the exemption from punishment, or, in a nutshell, Impunity.
Impunity is a legal privilege to conduct wrong acts without being penalized.
It’s the privilege that absolutely breaches rule of law principles.
It’s has become an identity of the Thai legal system.
This privilege is exercised both indirectly and publicly.
Indirect uses of this type of power include using connections
or powerful people asking or ordering someone to do something for them secretly.
And to use the privilege publicly is to make any legal case disappear.
When we have conflicts with the rich, the powerful, or bureaucrats,
these guys are always clear of charges.
Yes, sir. You’re right.
Just pay attention.
(Thai political histories are mentioned as examples in this lecture class.)
(Some of these I learned and heard from my father.)
(I've been told to learn it and keep it within when discussing these topics.)
And how great is the impact of impunity?
We can understand it by taking back old legal cases and reopening them with the rightful justice system,
Impunity for those powerful people will be very unlikely to happen.
Because we now have a standard that says no one is above the law in this country.
Everybody is equal under the law.
It's unfortunate that the reality of our history is the complete opposite.
Students, now that you’ve listened to all of it, can you name one impunity case for me, please?
Please.
The extrajudicial execution of a truck driver of Tawi’s company in 2018.
Tawi was free of the drug trafficking charge since he claimed he wasn’t involved with the man.
The police didn’t even investigate further or question witnesses.
The blame was all on the scapegoat who was extrajudicially killed.
Thank you very much.
If you follow political news, you may know who Tawi is
and the powerful people he’s connected with.
And you will get the concept of impunity.
(That was only the first example brought up in a classroom.)
(A small case that I and many others had never heard about.)
(I'm curious why a reserved person like him chose to be the first to speak.)
Thank you so much. Is there any other case you all would like to mention?
What’s that case?
It was a long time ago.
Then why did he bring it up?
Sean hates Tawi’s guts.
Anything about Tawi is worth mentioning.
Guys.
For the next mission,
we will let the crocodile decide.
You first, Black.
He sounded very sensible.
Gram.
When did Sean leave the class?
I need to talk to him.
You guys didn’t even look at each other’s faces when the class began.
And now you’re asking for him.
You can talk to him when we meet him later.
By the way, Sean’s example was so on point.
Tawi bribed his way out before the case even gets to court.
Hey, how do you know he bribed?
The information on this case is very weak.
It isn’t even on the way to court yet.
It’s pretty obvious.
One man couldn’t manage to run that huge amount of drugs.
If Tawi wasn’t rich, he would be in jail by now.
We quarrel every single day.
Well, well. I’m just a trans ex-girlfriend you forgot about.
I know you’re courting someone in Fine and Applied Arts.
What are you even talking about?
I’m always with Black.
Right?
Come on. I’ll take you home.
Bye.
See you later.
Let’s go. I have something else to do.
[Eugene]
Don’t you want to know who hurt Black?
Think about it. A girlfriend must be someone close to him.
And someone close should know everything.
Call her.
Sean.
Sean, hold on.
Can I ride with you to the garage?
Where is your bike?
Gumpa took it back for repair.
He chew me out saying I wasn’t careful with his bike.
You’ve been riding a lot to where?
To get inspiration.
Hop on.
Sean.
Can I ask you something?
Has Namo ever painted or drawn for you?
No.
You two are in a relationship but you never got a drawing from her?
I never asked her to be my girlfriend.
So you guys are just talking?
Why so many questions?
Hop on.
Stop talking nonsense.
It won’t catch fire if you light it like that.
When will we get to eat?
Give it here. I’ll do it.
I can do it.
I said give it here.
Here.
Add them in.
Why are you staring at me?
You’ve been staring since the lecture class.
I just wondered why you mentioned that case.
How is that related to you?
Everything about Tawi is always related to me.
I think it’s more to the story.
It’s burning me. Can’t you see?
I can.
Now you know how it’s like to play with fire.
To Black’s plan.
Cheers!
For the next mission,
is there any issue in our society you’d like to address?
Me.
I want to reform the justice system.
I’m a law student but it doesn’t apply in real life.
I want to rebuild it from scratch.
How are you going to do that?
I don’t know.
Why did you even start it?
I will tell you later when I figure it out.
If you really want to do it,
let this crocodile decide.
And you, Yok?
I want to address disability rights.
I don’t want them to be more privileged than other people.
I want them to have equal rights to us.
They should have work opportunities, access to public transport,
and easy stuff like being treated like normal people.
Your mom must have been through so much.
And you, Sean?
I want to destroy every business Tawi is running.
Damn! That’s personal.
But it’s not.
His business runs on his connections with the powerful lads who abuse people.
If we can bring him down,
it won’t be just me who benefits from it.
And you, Black?
I’m not telling.
Try to act cool?
I wish you don’t get a chance to speak at all.
Let’s do as I said.
We will let the crocodile decide.
Start with you, Black.
Why are you doing nothing?
Press a tooth.
Did you forget?
My turn.
Hey!
That tooth is reserved.
Go for some other ones.
And why must I do that?
Damn you!
What the hell? You also got it last time.
Will you tell me now what you want to do?
Let’s do what Sean proposed.
Let’s not follow my plan twice, or he might be fussy like a child.
Quit bullshitting!
I pressed the tooth you wanted.
But you’re the one that pressed it.
Will you take it or not?
If you won’t, give it to me, Black.
You’re normally a control freak.
Why are you going easy on me? What do you want?
I'm curious to see if you can attack Tawi harder than last time.
Yeah?
Someone like you will let me lead?
Did I say I would let you lead?
Then why did you give me the shot if you wouldn’t let me lead?
You make a plan.
Every time I make a plan, you always interrupt.
What is the matter now?
Why are you letting me do it easily?
I want to see a super privileged man like Tawi get punished too.
Fine.
Just wait and see.
I will make a man with impunity like Tawi pay.
Are you not wearing the perfume I bought you?
I thought I’d put it on before I met you.
But you came first.
You, you, and you.
Why aren’t you calling me like you used to?
Hi, Black.
What’s wrong?
You called me but you seem surprised.
I just didn’t expect you would be in my room like that.
Why not? I missed you.
What’s the matter?
What do you want from me?
I just wanted to see you.
You’re so mean.
You pushed me away with no explanation.
And now you want to see me?
You never let out what’s on your mind, Black.
(Shit! Black’s girlfriend is sulking. What should I do?)
Didn’t you miss me too?
I did.
I have something for you. Just wait here.
Vodka?
Why do you want to drink it?
To cool it down.
You’re crazy.
It will make us even hotter.
Who’s calling?
You can take it.
It’s fine. I want to be with you.
It’s very strong.
Drink up. You won’t get drunk.
Hold this.
Here. Bottoms up.
Are you not wearing the perfume I bought you?
I went to class today.
I thought I’d put it on before I met you.
But you came first.
You, you, and you.
Are you still mad at me?
Why aren’t you calling me like you used to?
(Damn it! What did Black call his girlfriend?)
Fine. Call me whatever.
No one can make Black do anything he doesn’t want.
Right?
I like it when you’re drunk.
When you’re drunk, you become very gentle.
You’re sweet.
I’m so sorry for being foul-mouthed to you.
I was so scared you wouldn’t want to see me again.
Can we go back to what we used to be?
Do you still love me, Black?
Drink up and I’ll tell you.
So?
What are you telling me?
I love you, Black.
Black.
[Are you meeting up with Black?]
[I wanna talk to you. Meet me tomorrow at…]
(Maybe Black was injured because of Eugene?)
Directed by Anucha Boonyawatana
I think Gram might be the one that hurt Black.
Black is acting really weird.
And you are too, Sean.
How?
You’ve been taking extra interest in him.
Are you all ready?
This is nothing like when we burned his house.
His business unit is full of his employees.
So I asked Gumpa to train us exclusively.
Prepare to jump.
You’re not the first one to look for UNAR.
I want to know who you are.