[Elegy of ZhaoLi]
[Episode 14]
I want you to go to the palace
and beg His Majesty
to make you his concubine!
Go!
Come with me!
How is it you? Shouldn't you be...
Surprised?
My bride.
I've come for you.
My Lady, run!
Xi'er!
Such deep loyalty
between mistress and servant.
Go ahead, run.
Don't worry, Li.
After you're gone,
I will surely make this girl
suffer terribly.
No!
Xi'er. No!
My Lady, run!
Shut up!
Take me away. I'll go with you.
If you sincerely beg me,
I can let her go.
But when you're begging me,
what should you call me?
Please, husband,
release Xi'er.
Too quiet.
I can't hear you.
I beg you, my husband, to release Xi'er.
All right.
However,
it's not sincere.
My Lady, don't be afraid.
Xi'er!
Xi'er.
Did you see that?
You killed her.
Just wait.
I'll make you pay with your life!
Who's there?
Traitor Xun Simo,
release Miss Jiang immediately!
A dog of Xie Jiuzhao—
how loud you bark.
I want to see
if you can actually bite.
[Moonlit Spectacle]
Jiuzhao, why did you invite me
to the Imperial Garden?
You're not asking me
to appreciate flowers, are you?
Twelve years ago,
if I hadn't been taken away,
the one sitting on the throne today
might have been you, Nianzhao.
You are destined to rule.
[Moonlit Spectacle]
I respect and love you,
and have never harbored
any treasonous thoughts.
Besides,
as long as you're here,
you'll always look after me, your brother.
Don't overthink it.
It was just a passing thought.
Yes.
The traitor Xun Simo escaped last night.
Stay within the palace these days
to avoid any mishaps.
How dare Xun Simo be so brazen!
He must not be spared this time.
Jiuzhao.
I believe...
I believe Mother has
nothing to do with this.
I humbly request
that you not direct
your anger toward Mother.
[Moonlit Spectacle]
Nianzhao.
If you still consider me your brother,
then stay out of this matter.
My Lady.
Li, wake up.
Xi'er.
Mother.
Li.
Xi'er.
General.
Darn it!
Who told you to touch her?
Please calm down, General.
Miss Jiang kept resisting,
so I had no choice...
Please calm down, General.
Take him away.
Yes, General.
Li,
I'm sorry you were frightened.
It was their fault.
Seeing you like this
breaks my heart too.
Xun Simo.
You make me sick.
Don't come any closer.
Stay back.
Li,
you can't do this.
Xie Jiuzhao isn't here yet,
so you can't die now.
You're willing to kill yourself for him?
Do you love Xie Jiuzhao that much?
Don't be delusional.
Xie Jiuzhao
won't come.
You just don't want him
to come and die, right?
Fine, let's wait and see.
Report!
How did it go?
Your Majesty,
I have failed your mission.
I beg for your punishment.
Say no more.
Go tend to your wounds now.
Where is Jiang Li?
Dismissed.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Where is she?
Miss Jiang
is in Xun Simo's hands.
Where are they?
Speak up!
Your Majesty,
if I tell you,
I would be the greatest traitor
in the Great Zhao State.
Are you deceiving your emperor?
I consider you my brother.
Must I beg you?
Xun Simo sent a message.
He wants you to go
to Chunliu Garden alone.
Otherwise,
Miss Jiang's life will be in danger.
Your Majesty!
This is surely a trap.
I dare to suggest
that you reconsider for a moment
and find a safer approach.
I have made up my mind.
If you try to stop me again,
our relationship will be over.
Your Majesty!
Guards!
Take the commander away
to treat his wounds.
After he recovers,
exile him to Suzhou
and conscript him into the army!
I
never want to see you again.
Jiuzhao, you cannot go!
Get out of my way.
You are the ruler of a nation.
You must not be bewitched by a woman
and lose your judgment.
I told you
not to interfere anymore.
Have you forgotten?
If you insist on rescuing Miss Jiang,
then let me take men to do it instead.
Please trust me.
Why should I trust you?
If anything happens to her,
can you bear that responsibility?
Jiuzhao.
Please prioritize the empire
and your people.
The empire and the people
don't conflict with saving her.
There have been
many wise rulers throughout history,
but Jiang Li only has me.
Please don't go!
I don't want you to go.
If you truly care about me,
after I leave the palace,
don't do anything rash.
Really?
Jiuzhao.
Is this
your final choice?