Xiao Yang,
Even though Da Niu is considered crazy,
crazy people often tell the truth.
So, who did he see?
Who exactly killed her?
Or did she fall to her death herself?
I can't figure it out.
The Li father and son are no good.
They took the crazy woman back with them.
There must be some plot.
Logically, it should have been Li Zhenzu who got into trouble.
But it turned out to be Li Xingzong instead.
I don't know either.
But...
Master Ruyin insists it has nothing to do with the Blood Fox.
It's one thing to curse the Li father and son,
but why curse Master Hu?
And put him at the top of the list.
She and Master Hu—
do they have some kind of grudge?
How many people can even write these days?
Could a crazy person have actually gone to school?
Kun,
why don't you believe in the Blood Fox?
I just don't believe it.
Here, take this.
I'm not eating anymore.
I'm saving it for my dad.
If you really want to be good to your dad,
then grow up quickly,
and earn lots and lots of money,
so you can buy your dad good food.
How about that?
Okay.
Son.
Dad.
Dad, you're back!
You...
Brother Shitou
Let's talk.
No matter how you ask, my answer is the same.
The kid really hasn't gone out.
But if you're talking about murder,
that's possible.
She wanted to kill Li Xingzong.
So how did Li Zhenzu end up dead?
That, I don't know.
Is there anything else?
No, that's all.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll head out first.
Wait a moment.
Did Master Hu help you in the past?
Yes.
I ran into bandits when I came here.
If Master Hu hadn't come to save me,
I would've been dead long ago.
I'll be honest with you.
I came here
to prevent the Li father and son
from framing Master Hu.
Brother Shitou,
I know Master Hu has helped you too.
You don't want Master Hu to be framed either, right?
I'll say it again.
The kid really didn't go out that night.
Even if I wanted the Li father and son dead,
I wouldn't lie against my conscience.
But...
Li Xingzong,
he wanted to know why that crazy woman
attacked Master Hu.
He had bad intentions.
Everyone in town knows
Li Xingzong wants to ruin Master Hu.
Li Zhenzu,
that woman wanted to kill Li Xingzong.
Li Zhenzu chased after her and killed her.
Then he came back and pretended to be asleep.
No, no, that's not right.
If Li Zhenzu really killed her,
then how do you explain the wooden plank?
Was he cursing himself?
Maybe he was trying to create confusion.
Or divert attention.
It's all possible.
You don't know him.
He's not that smart. Impossible.
Who could it be, then?
This person
with the Hu family and the Li family
has some deep grudge against them.
Is it possible to think of it this way?
The Hu family and the Li family
are they connected in any way?
Are you saying the Hu family has something to hide?
And Li Xingzong knows about it and helps them keep it secret?
He even helped them kill that woman?
I didn't say that.
You said it.
Who is it?
Xiu'er, is that you? Are you back?
Xiu'er
Who is it?
Brother-in-law
Come on, come on
Come here
Oh my gosh
Brother-in-law is here, come quickly!
Alright, alright
Xiu'er, you're too much!
Wait a minute, wait a minute
Let me have a sip of water
Brother-in-law, you're back
Brother-in-law
Darn it, Old Wang
The vegetables have gone up in price again
Life is getting impossible
Xiu'er
This darn girl
The sun is already high in the sky
Why aren't you up yet?
This family can't go on like this
There's been a murder!
What should we do now?
How could this happen?
Xiu'er
Wake up, Xiu'er.
Xiu'er's mother is awake.
Xiu'er
Xiu'er's mother
Don't move, Xiu'er's mother.
Calm down.
Xiu'er's mother
Xiu'er's mother, please accept our condolences.
Xiao Kun, Xiao Kun
It's all because of that jerk Li Zhenzu.
He ruined her.
Go arrest him!
Ma'am, please calm down.
Listen to me.
If it really was Li Zhenzu,
I'll go arrest him right now.
He insisted on coming to my house two days in a row.
Does that count as evidence?
He slept with Xiu'er and then killed her.
Does this count as evidence?
He thinks I don't know.
But I saw everything.
Go catch him, quickly!
Oh, my Xiu'er!
Xiu'er!
Xiu'er's mother, please accept my condolences.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Come out.
Are you crazy? Are you trying to rebel?
Everyone, get out.
What are you doing, rebelling?
What do you want to do?
Put down the weapon.
Put it down.
Xiao Kun, have I been too lenient with you?
Again and again.
Aren't you done yet?
Hurry, catch them!
Catch them!
You old woman!
Go after whoever did the killing.
Why are you coming after me?
Li Zhenzu, you're truly inhuman.
My daughter was pregnant with your child.
And you still killed her.
Did you hear that, Li Zhenzu?
I'm going to fight you to the end.
Did you hear that?
What are you doing?
Calm down, step aside.
Li Zhenzu, Xiu'er's mother saw everything.
What else do you have to say?
Nonsense.
Let me tell you.
I didn't even go out last night.
They can all vouch for me.
That's right.
Isn't that so?
We can all testify.
A life for a life.
If someone can prove you went out,
you're done for.
Who can prove it?
Who?
No one can prove it, right?
Then it wasn't my son who did it.
That's right.
It was the Blood Fox.
Everyone knows that.
My Li family only has this one heir.
Yes, he's not very promising.
He only has two daughters.
But he got Xiu'er pregnant.
Doctor Huang also checked her pulse.
He said it's a boy.
I also promised Xiu'er
that as long as she gives birth to the child,
I would let Zhenzu marry her.
Xiao Kun, this is the heir of the Li family.
He went crazy and tried to kill her.
He's nothing but a beast.
What did you say?
Hit her.
Stop!
I'll testify.
Get out of my way.
Don't move.
That night, Li Zhenzu went out.
Liar!
It was him.
My daughter.