Please, please, come in.
Master, please take a seat.
Mr. Hu, after you.
The last time we parted, Master,
was already a few years ago.
Today, Master, you have come to Hu Li Town.
I apologize for not welcoming you properly.
Please forgive me, Master.
Mr. Hu, you are too polite.
I am a wandering monk by nature.
I make my home wherever I go to cultivate myself.
But as for you, Mr. Hu,
even though we haven't met for years,
you are still as spirited as ever.
Master.
Look,
about today's matter—
the deceased has already been placed in a coffin and put in the old temple.
You can rest assured about the ritual for the departed, Mr. Hu.
But now something strange has happened in town.
Rumors of the Blood Fox's curse
have spread throughout the whole town.
Everyone is
living in fear.
Master,
could you perform a ritual for the town?
First,
it could suppress these evil spirits.
Second,
it could ease people's fear and anxiety.
As for the ritual,
you can rest assured, Mr. Hu.
But I must offer a word of advice.
Evil spirits are but illusions.
It is time and cultivation that shape one's life.
Kun, what does that mean?
You ask me? How should I know?
Murder.
The Blood Fox has killed someone.
Daniu.
Are you okay?
The Blood Fox killed someone. Untie him.
Untie him! The Blood Fox killed someone.
It's okay now, Daniu.
Daniu.
Look at me, I'm Zhengkun.
Brother Kun.
The Blood Fox has killed someone.
I'll take you home.
Your mother is waiting for you at home.
Come on.
Butler.
I'm taking him with me.
Since last night until now,
he's caused trouble several times.
The master can't do anything about it either.
He doesn't dare let him go out.
The town is so chaotic right now.
He's afraid he'll get into trouble if he goes out.
Thank you for your trouble.
Then I'll have to trouble Officer Hu.
Let's go.
Sir, Young Master Yang has arrived.
Come, come, come.
Please, have a seat.
Xiao Yang,
you are both smart and steady.
I’ll get straight to the point.
I invited you here today
because there’s something
I need your help with.
Please, Mr. Hu, just say it.
Last night, did you
go to that abandoned house?
I’m sorry, Mr. Hu.
I acted on my own.
It’s just that I see Juan’er
as my own little sister.
For something like this to happen to her,
I really...
I’m not blaming you.
I just want to ask,
did you find any clues?
Was it man-made,
or just a misfortune?
Mr. Hu, are we really just letting this go?
Even though I know
you want to protect Juan’er’s reputation,
and don’t want this to get out,
but there’s still Hu Zhengkun.
He won’t let this go easily.
He’ll definitely get to the bottom of it.
The reason I invited you
is also because of this matter.
I want to repair the old temple.
What about you?
I’ll be working with Master Ruyin on this.
Also,
I’ll help Master Ruyin
hold a grand ritual in town.
But Master Hu,
when the blood fox was mentioned yesterday,
you said it was just a scare tactic.
So why are we now making such a big deal
about repairing this old temple
and holding a grand ritual?
Rumors are powerful.
I want
people to believe
that what happened to Juan’er wasn’t done by a person
but by an evil spirit.
This way,
everyone will sympathize with and pity Juan’er.
Juan’er’s reputation
can be somewhat preserved.
I understand.
Master Hu,
when the master said that today,
I noticed you seemed troubled.
Did you already suspect
that you also suspect Li Zhenzu?
Since we’ve come this far,
I won’t hide it from you.
The matter
goes back to a few days ago.
Take a look.
Would you like to order something? No.
Get lost.
Juan’er.
Where are you going?
Have a drink with me.
Juan’er.
Don’t run.
Kneel down.
Juan'er.
I'm sorry.
She hit me.
Forgive my rudeness.
Master Hu, since there has already been such a lesson,
you should be even more cautious.
The Li family,
after all, is also a prominent family in town.
They've already admitted fault and apologized.
What more can you do?
It's better to resolve enmity than to create it.
If the two families really start fighting,
both sides will suffer.
No one will save face.
Perhaps I was too soft-hearted.
In the end, it still hurt Juan'er.
But regarding this matter,
I won't let it go easily.
I've already sent people to investigate in secret.
Once we have solid evidence,
if the Li family is truly heartless,
the Hu family won't be bullied either.
Before the truth comes out,
I'd like to ask you to help me.
For now, hold Zhengkun back.
That child is very impulsive.
I'm afraid he'll act rashly
and cause more trouble.
Yes, Master Hu.
Sister, brother-in-law...
Is he alright?
Maybe you should go talk to him.
What is it?
Feeling sorry for him?
Sister.
What are you talking about?
Xiu'er doesn't understand.
Come here.
You little flirt in heat.
I'm not dead yet.
And you can't wait to snatch him away.
Feeling sorry for the master inside, are you?
Sister, you've misunderstood.
There's really nothing between me and brother-in-law.
If I hadn't pitied you back then,
and for the sake of my family,
since we're still somewhat related,
I wouldn't have kept you here and given you food.
Don't think I don't know about your dirty deeds.
Let me give you some advice.
Put away those twisted thoughts of yours.
Don't be so eager
to jump into the Li family's fire pit.
Be careful,
or not even ashes
will be left of you.
Something's wrong, Master!
Miss has hanged herself!
Someone, come quickly!