The hatred in your heart
still hasn't been let go.
I'm already a dying man.
I just can't stop worrying about Anan.
Back then, he risked his life
to save me from the hell of Nanyang.
I owe him.
Now I'm repaying him with my life.
This is the karma between him and me.
Years ago, my enemy sold me to Nanyang.
That led me to meet Anan by chance.
Now, because of Anan, I've found my enemy.
This is the karma between me and my enemy.
I'm just worried about Anan.
That because of hatred,
he'll become someone consumed by hatred.
Maybe
only hatred can make him let go of hatred.
All these years, he hasn't been able to let go of his hatred.
It's the only obsession he has in this world.
Once his great revenge is fulfilled,
from then on,
what else will he have to hold on to?
Kun.
Kun is in trouble! Open the door, quick!
Kun!
Open the door! Something terrible has happened!
What happened?
Li Zhenzu is dead.
Kun, look, he's smiling too.
Could it be the Blood Fox again?
Don't talk nonsense.
What Blood Fox?
Zhenzu
What's wrong with you?
Wake up!
Why don't you listen to your father?
Zhenzu, what are you doing, Zhenzu?
I'm begging you, please wake up!
Father
You have to avenge Zuer!
How much have you been hiding from me?
I...
The smile on Zuer's face
and the smile on the dead man's face on the mountain
What's going on with that?
Do you think you can fool me?
Yes
The dead man on the mountain was a child kidnapper.
It was from him that I accidentally got the information.
He was also the one who killed the person.
Yes
Foolish
Does anyone else know about this?
Hu San'er
But he's already dead.
I thought that if I put everything
on the Blood Fox
it would all be over.
But Zuer
still met a tragic end.
You suspect
Zuer was forcibly given drugs by someone
which caused heart failure and death
Li Qiang had me beat him half to death
He finally confessed
That night, Zuer
went to Wang Xiaohua's place with something
You suspect
Wang Xiaohua
Wang Xiaohua has been missing and still hasn't been found
It must be her
If she hadn't seduced Zuer
Zuer wouldn't have died
Enough
Shut up
It's clearly your own fault for not raising your son properly
You brought this on yourself
So Zuer died for nothing
Let me handle this matter
Dad
I think the recent events have been a bit strange
Especially after that crazy woman showed up
Could it be that another enemy is after us?
Is that why Zuer...
Brother Xiaokun
Let's have a drink, just the two of us
Come on, let's drink, let's drink
Isn't this awesome?
Awesome.
Big Bull.
What are you doing, Big Bull?
Bull, come have a drink.
Want to drink, Bull?
What Lian'er? Lian'er died a long time ago.
Are you stupid?
Wake up, Big Bull.
I'll go take a look.
Big Bull.
Come drink.
Wake up.
Wake up, Big Bull.
Blood Fox.
Blood Fox killed someone.
Blood.
Brother Xiao Kun.
I heard from Shuanzi.
Ever since Li Zhenzu died,
you've locked yourself at home.
If you have anything on your mind, you can tell me.
Why? Why did it turn out like this?
Brother Xiao Kun.
So this is what you like.
Kun
What are you doing?
Da Niu is dead.
What?
The Blood Fox killed again.
Yeah.
That slash was right on the neck.
It even looked like he did it to himself.
Juan
Stay here.
I'll come get you in a bit.
Brother Xiao Kun
I'm scared.
Er Zhuang, you take her.
It's okay.
Brother Xiao Kun
Let's drink together next time.
Can you lock the door?
If you dare tell anyone, see if I don't beat you.
I won't, I won't.
It's a secret.
Let's go.
No, Kun.
Why do you think Daniu keeps hurting himself?
Could it be...
The Blood Fox is acting up again, right?
He must be bewitched by the Blood Fox.
On their faces...
He was even smiling like that.
Stop talking to me about the Blood Fox.
Did you all see it?
Shuanzi saw it, ask him.
We're talking about Daniu.
Why are you dragging me into this?
Until we figure out what's going on,
no one should jump to conclusions.
Did you hear me?
Heard you.
Go back and get some sleep.
Alright, alright, let's go, let's go.
Don't drink so much if you don't have to.
Okay, okay.
We're leaving.
Let's go.
Kun, I'm not a superstitious person.
But this is just too weird.
My whole body...
I've got goosebumps all over.
You drank too.
You're a young woman,
sneaking into a man's room in the middle of the night.
This is disgraceful and improper!
I like him.
I want to marry him.
How is that disgraceful?
You're going to be the death of me!
Master Hu, please don't blame Juan.
Calm down.
How can I calm down?
She did something like this!
You—
Say it.
Go on.
Grandpa,
I...
I'm already Xiao Kun's woman.
Please let me marry him.
You—
By doing this,
how am I supposed to face anyone?
I'm leaving now.
Goodbye, Brother Yang Nan.
You—