(Reiko/Reiko) Is this enough? (Naruse) I'll do the best surgery.
(Narration) <I am reborn through plastic surgery➡
Take care of children in your neighborhood➡
She continued to take revenge on Saori and her friends who took her daughter's life.
(Saori) It's a declaration of war.
It's what I want.
<However, 22 years ago by Saori's husband Mikihisa➡
My ex-husband was accused of murder.
It's cancer. There's nothing we can do about it.
I'm thinking of marrying this person.
I need money.➡
So sky➡
Buy it.
purchase?
100 million. How about it?
100 million?
No, that's impossible. How do you get that kind of money...
(Sachi) I want to keep the sky, so I put up 10 million ➡
I live in such a nice apartment.
There's nothing left.
Sky! I'm going home with my real mom.
Stop it!
I can't pay 100 million yen.
Sacchan, go home now.➡
Go home.
♬～
(Sky) Hey, Mom.
yeah?
Did my mom come yesterday?
Why?
It smells like cigarettes.
Hey, what did you come for?
I was wondering if the sky was fine.
Me…➡
I have to go back someday.
The sky can stay here forever.
real?
real.
(Reminiscence Sachi)((Do you want to keep the sky?))
I'm going.
``But now, he has become irreplaceable.''
(Sachi) Haa~｡
I came to pick you up.
♬ “Karon”
♬～
(Kenji) Goho, goho! Goho…｡
<While Kenji is still alive➡
I decided to expose the darkness of the Shindo family.>
That's enough.
Huh?
thank you.
Because that's enough.
(Mobile phone) (ringtone)
(mobile phone)
Yes. (Mobile phone) Sora-kun is nowhere to be found.
Huh?
(Mobile phone) We are now splitting up and searching around the kindergarten.
(Mobile phone) At Sora-kun's place...
♬～
Don Don Don! Sky!
Don Don Don Don! Sky!
Sky! Sky!
(mobile phone)
Hello. (Mobile phone) (Sachi) Fu me.
Where is the sky? Are you with me?
Please give me back the sky!
Ha, where is my 100 million?
That's terrible! To kidnap the sky.
Haha, kidnapping.
What is kidnapping about taking your child back?
Please give it back!
Give me back the sky!
Please contact me when you have 100 million yen ready.
(Mobile phone) Butch twos (no tone)
♬～
(Mobile phone) Puzzle…(Ring tone)
(Mobile phone) Pull…
(Sachi) Hey, it worked out just like I said, right?
Look, he'll bring 100 million here soon.
Hey, it's 100 million. 100 million.
(Takuya) You did it, Sacchan. (Sachi) Hmm.
Ping Dong Ping Dong! (Intercom)
It's here, it's okay.
(Sachi) Yes, hehehe.
Huh.
Who are you? Where is the sky?
Sky! Sky!
(Sachi) Before that, give me 100 million.
I don't have that kind of money!
Ready...➡
Did you cheat? What do you mean?
(Takuya) Hey, what is it?
Is there one?
Please give it back! Give me back the sky!
Give it back, the sky is my child.
In the empty body...
I still had the scars of being abused by you.
(Sky)((It hurts... It hurts, Mom.))
♬～
That's the mark of a cigarette being pressed against it.
I have a duty to report it to the child guidance center.
Child guidance center?
Do whatever you like.
But, I am the mother of the sky.
You are not qualified to be a mother.
♬～
Sky Sky!
Wait.
Ugh…｡
null!
null.
Are you okay?
Mom, did you come to pick me up?
Yeah.
Hey, that's not your mom, right?
Can I go back to mom's house?
Let's go home, sky.
Mama.
It's okay now.
♬～
Isn't it heavy?
heavy.
Sorry.
Sky: I feel relieved.
Ah.
Hey, Sky, wake up.
What happened?
Ah.
null.
Take a look. Wow!
♬～
＜I once saw a rainbow like this on this road.＞
(Kenji)((Haha))
(Yuna)((Ah, look, look!))
((Dad, Mom)) ((Oh~➡
Look, Yuna, you're beautiful.)) ((Yeah.))
((Amazing haha))
I almost lost my precious child again.
♬～
Thank you very much.
Kenji-san: We have two or three days left in the mountains.
Huh?
♬～
I'll come check you out.
Ah... Yuna.
Yuna: Huh...
Kenji-san: We have two or three days left in the mountains.
Ah... Yuna.
♬～
Ugh...
Yuna.
<Even if I am accused of an innocent crime➡
The daughter I tried to protect.＞
Reiko.
Ugh...
sorry.
Ugh... I'm sorry!
♬～
Tons!
Don't cry, don't cry.
♬～
Keita.
I'm sorry for doing something selfish.
Kenji-san.
Ah...｡
Who is this child?
This is Yuna's son Keita.
Ah...｡
Your grandson Keita-kun.
Hahaha…｡
Keita.
(Sky) Grandpa?
Grandpa.
Ah... Keita｡➡
Keita Ah...
Keita drew it.
♬～
Ugh...
When I grow up, ugh...➡
Build a big house.
With dad and mom ➡
With grandma... ➡
With you...
We're all going to live together.
Sigh…｡
You're good at it, Keita.
♬～
Ah...｡
Thanks to the teacher➡
Kenji was able to depart peacefully.
♬～
He noticed you.
Huh?
((No matter how much the outside changes ➡
There are some things that don't change.➡))
((The warmth of the hand that rubs your back➡
The taste of porridge.))
((A gentle look looking at me.))
♬～
((Sigh... what the hell happened?))
Even if you notice➡
I guess he realized something and didn't say it.
♬～
((Who the hell are you?))
((I am➡
I'm just Yuna's friend.))
<Kenji-san has always been there➡
He pretended to be fooled.＞
Ugh...
♬｢Light｣
♬～
Uuuuuuuuuuu...
Keita.
(Akihiko) Keita.
(Akihiko, Reiko, Yuna)((Itadakimasu.))
((Hmm? Delicious! Yeah.))
♬～
⚟Wow!
⚟Amazing! Hahaha. That's crazy. So good.
I thought I would meet a handsome macho man that I like➡
Wow, that was a huge disappointment.
⚟(footsteps)
Oh, it's finally here➡
My accomplice.
♬～
Who killed Yuna-chan?
With me...
It's you.
♬～
Stop taking revenge.
Your goodness as a person is getting in the way! I can't run away.
You decided to take revenge, right? Be strong.
You're the one I killed. Your smile is➡
He saved me.
I will absolutely take your life away.