Here it is.
Now that we’re all here,
how about taking a photo?
Now?
What? You don’t want it?
Yes, I do. I want it a lot.
He was a quiet and sensible boy.
A couple lost their child
in the amusement park.
Upon seeing Seo Jun,
they decided to adopt him.
Seo Jun, come.
They said Seo Jun looked like
their lost child.
You’re Seo Jun?
They’ll be your parents.
Glad to see you.
When he was a student,
he sometimes came back here.
He talked about you every time.
Me?
He said there was a friend
he liked and cherished.
By the way, how’s he doing lately?
After that, I received no news from him.
=Blue Birthday=
=Episode 4
Rule of Equivalent Exchange=
Long time no see.
Thank you, Hye Min.
By the way,
what were you going to ask?
Ah.
What was that?
Seo Jun...
What was he used to be like at home?
Mm.
He was an ordinary boy
just like other boys of his age.
As kind and outgoing
as he appeared to be.
Hye Min, in fact, I...
But Ha Rin...
I wonder if you know
Seo Jun was adopted by my parents.
It was my fault
that Seo Jun ended up dead.
What?
I don’t know when, but Seo Jun got
on bad terms with my parents,
especially with our mother.
Specifically, it started
in May of that year
when I came back home.
I was happy to find
my long-lost parents.
But to Seo Jun,
my sudden returning
may have hurt him.
About you.
I’m getting to know something about you.
I was your friend for ten years,
but I exactly knew nothing about you.
I hate myself for this more and more.
From this day on, I’ll get to know you.
But...
I haven’t finished reading the diary.
Ah.
Out of films?
The camera is broken.
Nothing is left now,
but these seven photos.
Anyway,
no matter what I have to do,
I must get you back to life
before using up the photos.
If there’s any change on the map,
then...
The time travel ends
with weird tinnitus.
I must hurry up before it happens.
What are you doing?
What?
Where are you going again?
I’m a bit...
Come on, Ha Rin.
What?
What are you doing?
Why are you talking loudly with Su Jin?
Aren’t you disturbing other students?
Sir, I...
I want to go to the toilet.
Urgently?
Yes.
But what did I say last time?
You don’t remember?
Come on. What did I say last time?
Look at my hand. Does it remind you?
Pig’s feet.
Who said that?
I asked you not to say that.
I told you to raise your hand
and request permission to the toilet in a low voice.
But Ha Rin, did you raise your hand?
No.
Everybody, if any one of you
raises your hand,
Ha Rin can go to the toilet.
Raise your hand if you support her.
Well, what’s going on here?
You don’t have even one ally.
Isn’t Su Jin your friend?
Sir, I’m really urgent.
All right. I see. I see.
Work out this problem, then.
After you work it out,
I’ll let you go.
It’s a very simple problem.
Is it a promise?
Sure. I’m a man of my word.
You sometimes go back on it.
Who said that? I’ll get you!
The one who just said pig’s feet, right?
It’s simply a high school problem.
I’ll just go to the toilet
during the break.
Come and help Ha Rin.
Help her.
She can go to the toilet
after she solves the problem.
I’m so tortured
to be a high school student at this age.
It was not a very difficult problem.
I was good at solving it, you know?
Was?
Nothing. Forget it.
Come on!
You’ll help me later.
Don’t be weak already.
Help you with what?
Didn’t you say you would help me?
Come on!
Did you forget it again?
I didn’t.
Actually, I did.
I only have time today.
So, don’t ever forget it again.
What exactly is it?
Ui Yeong Kim.
What are you doing?
Looking at the poster
of the Photo Contest.
Oh.
You want to sign up for it?
What are you talking about?
Didn’t we agree that
we would all sign up for it?
Did you forget it again?
Why don’t you go to the hospital
and have a check-up?
Yeah. You’ve been weird lately.
Haw-haw.
Come on!
I’m not weird.
I’m doing all right.
Are you sure?
Yes.
That’s good.
Anyway, don’t be late.
Or I’ll break with you.
I won’t be late.
But what am I supposed to...?
Feels like I’m having low blood sugar.
Let’s just go.
(Instructions)
Nothing goes right.
Ah!
So…
What photos are you going to take?
What do you mean?
Ah, the Photo Contest?
We must at least take the photo tomorrow
so that we can revise and submit it.
You’re right.
The theme is family.
Why not just take a photo
of our parents?
- You can take a photo of your parents.
- No.
I’ll pick another family member.
Another family member?
- Cloud.
- Cloud?
My dog Cloud is super lovely.
Do you have a dog that barks fiercely
when your mother grumbles?
You don’t, do you?
I kind of envy you for that.
What about you, Ha Rin Oh?
Oh?
I...
Haven’t you finished yet?
I’ve got something else. I’m going up.
Where are you going?
I’m off, too.
What…?
When did you finish eating it?
How can I become a real family?
Can I get close to them?
Even thinking about it frustrates me.
I’m exhausted.
It was my bad last time.
Ah!
Mom, tonight,
are you available?
Other people would think
you’re texting your ex-girlfriend.
What?
You freaked me out.
What makes you hesitate
when texting your mother?
I’m not hesitating.
You are, all right?
Will you text her or not?
You typed and deleted it by turns.
What text is it?
An apology text.
Apology?
I did something wrong.
Give it to me.
Give me your phone.
What for?
I’m experienced in quarreling
with my mother. Watch and learn.
No need.
It’s always the hardest
to make up with families.
Let me help you.
All you need to do is trust me.
I must handle it
so that you won’t get hurt again.
How will you help me, then?
Give me your phone.
You just sent it!
The first step to inviting someone
is to be brave. Be brave.
But what if she doesn’t reply?
(Mom, tonight, are you available?)
(Yes, Seo Jun. Why?)
Ah…
Oh…
Ha Rin Oh, you...
(Answer questions with a smile.)
Shall I not go meet her?
Don’t say that.
You’re good at studying anyway.
Just recite it.
What’s this?
The secret to making up with families.
Secret?
First, ease the tension.
- Let me get you some water.
- All right.
Thank you.
How was your day at school?
When your mother asks a question,
answer her with a smile.
I...
No one pulls a long face
to a smiling person.
I had a happy day.
Very happy. Haw-haw.
Very happy?
What made you so happy?
Ah...
In the end, tell her
your everyday life willingly.
I...
If you have nothing to tell her,
talk about me.
Tell her my embarrassing things.
You have a special offer today.
Say anything you want.
Because of my friend.
Friend?
I have a friend, Ha Rin Oh.
She’s quite dumb and also forgetful.
We’ve been friends since we were eight.
So far, she hasn’t changed at all.
Enjoy your food.
You really told her
my embarrassing things?
- Tastes great.
- Yes.
Have you decided what to order?
Ah…
- Let’s go.
- All right.
I’ll come next time.
(Answer questions with a smile.)
I knew it.
He couldn’t keep it properly
and he dropped it.
(Su Jin Do)
(Su Jin Do, 4 Missed Calls)
Seo Jun,
may I ask you a question?
Why did you suddenly
invite me to dinner?
I just wanted it.
Before you called,
Hye Min had called, too.
She invited me to dinner, too.
She did?
Yes.
Then why did you choose me,
instead of her?
Because it was the first time.
Seo Jun,
you invited me to dinner
for the first time ever.
Seo Jun.
I’m sorry.
What you said
isn’t wrong.
Stop wasting your time
forcing yourself to be nice to me!
Anyway, I’m a substitute for my sister.
What did you say?
Without me, you would adopt
another child, right?
We did adopt you
because we couldn’t forget Hye Min.
Your eyes, nose and mouth
look exactly like hers.
You’re even a left-hander
just like her.
At first, we did regard you
as her substitute.
But after raising you for one year
and then two years,
suddenly I wondered something.
If you disappeared like Hye Min,
what would I do?
I would die.
Seo Jun,
I did adopt you for selfish motives.
But I’ve never stopped loving you.
Nor has your father.
I’m sorry.
I got you wrong.
Never mind.
I’m sorry to make you think like that.
It’s my fault.
I’m not a good mother.
I’m sorry, Seo Jun.
If you don’t end your life,
everything will be solved naturally
as time goes on, right?
Oh?
Where’s my phone?
How many of you?
I left my phone here.
This one?
Yes, yes. Thank you.
(Su Jin Do, 4 Missed Calls)
I only have time today.
So, don’t ever forget it again.
(Su Jin Do)
I only focused on
getting Seo Jun back to life
and I forgot about Su Jin.
The subscriber you dialed
cannot be connected.
Ah!
It’s driving me crazy.
Hello, Su Jin Do?
It’s me.
Seo Jun.
Where are you?
May I meet you? Are you available?
Now?
Will Su Jin be all right?
Hello?
Ha Rin Oh?
Yeah, it’s more important
to save Seo Jun.
All right.
Where are you now?
Ah…
The sky isn’t falling.
Is there anything bothering you?
What? Nothing.
Nothing is bothering me.
How was your dinner with your mother?
Not bad.
The weird note you gave me
really helped a lot.
It helped you, but you dropped it.
What did you say?
Nothing.
I’m glad it helped.
Ha Rin Oh.
Mm?
Thank you.
You indeed helped a lot.
Without your help,
I wouldn’t dare to expect
such a conversation with my mother.
Come on. I just sent a text for you.
It was really hard
to text her like that.
But after I talked to her,
I realized that I needn’t have worried.
Anyway, thank you.
I mean it.
Is he all right now?
Don’t die.
Seo Jun Ji,
please don’t die.
I should find Seo Jun first.
Seo Jun.
Seo Jun Ji.
Oh?
Shouldn’t there be photos
of Su Jin and me?
Disappeared?
Su Jin.
Hello, Ha Rin Oh?
Ui Yeong Kim,
are you with Su Jin now?
Why are you suddenly asking about her?
I’m walking to her home now. Is she...?
Why are you going to see her?
What?
You’re back on speaking terms?
Didn’t you break with each other
when you were in Grade 2?
Su Jin,
yesterday I...
Wait a second.
- Go without me.
- All right.
I really had an emergency yesterday.
I’m sorry.
What emergency?
Seo Jun Ji was...
It’s him again! It’s always about him!
You care most about Seo Jun Ji!
What about me?
It was all right
when you always broke your promise!
But this time I requested you.
I thought it would be different.
I had thought you would
keep our promise.
But what did you do?
I had thought I could get everything
back to normal.
Our friendship is so fragile
when only I take you as my friend.
But that is...
I’m too tired.
Simply my illusion.
Su Jin!
Shall we go to the shop?
- Enjoy it.
- Come on!
This is not the change I want.
Maybe changing nothing
is the best thing.
Ha Rin Oh.
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪Even if I suddenly disappear today♪
♪Whatever we say Whatever we say♪
♪Even the day we say goodbye♪
♪Somewhere♪
(A changed past affects the present.)
♪My dream time♪
♪Will also become the light
like an old movie♪
One, two, three.
Yeah!
Su Jin, this is yours. And this is mine.
Right? Su Jin, enjoy more.
Why doesn’t she just have two?
You don’t understand.
It’s love that we want to
give everything to the other half.
Ah?
Must I understand?
Will you take a photo of your parents
for the Photo Contest?
Or what?
Why? You want something else?
No. I just wonder if you will do that
like Ui Yeong Kim.
Is it okay that we take the same photos?
Our parents are different, anyway.
Yeah.
The theme is family.
I guess the photos will be similar.
Seo Jun Ji, will you also...?
Now that we’re all here,
how about taking a photo?
Now?
What? You don’t want it?
Yes, I do. I want it a lot.
One, two, three.