♪ If it's a fate ♪
♪ Why is the distance
sometimes near, sometimes far ♪
♪ Looking at each other, there are ripples
that can't be blown away ♪
♪ I think we are ♪
♪ Being too persistent ♪
♪ If it's just a vague promise ♪
♪ Why should there be anxiety then ♪
♪ Whether it's a long-lasting
or momentarily closeness ♪
♪ Our heart will gradually warm ♪
♪ This is the most beautiful part of the story ♪
♪ We're not tired of our sweet smiles ♪
♪ I found the biggest reason
behind childhood sweetheart ♪
♪ I used to be afraid of being together ♪
♪ Perhaps there was too much hesitation ♪
♪ I must face the truth ♪
♪ Ever since our companionship
sweetens the meaning of love ♪
♪ I understood the meaning
behind childhood sweetheart ♪
♪ Happiness comes in the same style ♪
♪ Two lovely hearts together ♪
♪ An eternal truth ♪
=Sweet First Love=
(Adapted from the novel
The Days When My Brother And I Live Together)
(Episode 12)
(Devil Brother)
(Su Muyun)
Wake up!
This is my bed!
Sorry...
Go away! That's mine too!
(Mingxian University)
Just get through tonight.
(Student Hostel No.4)
Ten minutes left!
I'd like to remind everyone that
it's been unsettling in the hostel.
Things kept missing.
Hurry and go in.
The doors will be locked soon.
(Student Hostel No.4)
You couples.
And you guys!
Yes, you! Get moving!
Hurry up!
All of you, get going!
(Student Hostel No.4)
Hurry up!
You don't live here, right?
Madam, my classmate
forgot her things.
I'll just send them to her.
I'll be out when I'm done.
What things?
I'll send them to her for you.
Sure!
But you have to be careful.
We're from the Department of Medicine.
They're organs
and some small animals in it.
You have to be careful
not to scare other people off.
Go in and send them yourself.
Okay. Thank you, Madam.
(Student Hostel No.4)
Hurry up. Come out before the curfew!
Okay.
I told you, the one before...
That person just now...
Was she a thief?
Let's... Let's call the madam.
Hurry. Hurry.
Let's go...
Who are you?
Why are you here?
Let's go! Follow me to the security office!
I was wondering
why things kept missing in the hostel.
You stole them, right?
No, it's not me.
I'm really from the Department of Medicine.
Where is your student ID?
I forgot to bring it.
But I'm not lying.
Look! These are all medical textbooks.
I remember now.
I saw you at the beginning of the semester.
Don't you have a younger brother?
The one... The one that was quite tall.
The good-looking young lad!
His name was...
Su...
Su Muyun!
What a posh name!
If I had a daughter,
I'd definitely get him
to be my son-in-law! I...
Fine. Let's get her brother to come over.
Are you Su Muyun?
Yes.
This is Mingxian Security Office.
Your sister trespassed the girls' hostel.
She's here in my office now.
Come to pick her up.
(Zhuo Yifeng: Sorry to disturb you.)
(I've been detained in
the school security office.)
(Can you come over?)
(Non-motor Vehicle Ramp)
This idiot...
Mister, please head to Mingxian University.
Please drive faster.
Sure.
Sorry to disturb you.
I'm Su Muyun. I'm here to bring her back.
Please sign here.
Why are you here?
Shut up.
Go back with me.
Next time, if you wish to live on campus,
just apply to the school.
Don't trespass the hostel late at night.
It might disturb others.
She's not living on campus.
We don't live far.
Okay. Sign here and go back.
(Student's signature: Zhuo Yifeng
Family member's signature)
All done.
Go back. Be careful next time.
Let's go. Go back home.
Stop messing around.
Let's go back home first, okay?
Mom and dad are worried.
I'm not messing around.
That's your home, not mine.
I...
I don't have a home anymore.
Xiao Feng, I'm here to pick you up.
Why are you here?
I asked him to come.
Stop sticking your nose
into my business.
Uhm... Sorry.
I didn't mean to trouble you.
Where do you plan to go?
You can go back and rest.
I can find a place to stay.
Are you going to sleep
on the bench at the park
or under the bridge?
I know things are complicated
between you and the Su Family.
I also know that you don't want to
spend their money.
How about...
you stay at my place for a day or two?
No. No need.
Just like when I gave you tuition,
I'll ask for payment.
I'm short of a chef.
It'd be better for someone
with medical background.
Come stay at my place for two days.
You can move out once you find
somewhere suitable to live.
Take it as you're looking after me.
Then... I'll stay for two days.
Sure.
You can still cook, right?
You'd cry for my tasty food.
I'll start to order then.
I want to eat...
(Staple; Liquid Diet)
I found a recipe online.
Eat according to the recipe this month.
Take care of your stomach.
(Mingxian University)
(Advance Bravely and Surpass Yourself)
Xiao Feng hasn't back home yet?
Don't tell me she is with Le Diyin?
Can you just shut up for a moment?
No.
What exactly happened
between you two this time?
How could you end up like this?
Something happened at home.
I'll tell you the whole story next time.
(Advance Bravely and Surpass Yourself)
What's important now is
you should
bring Xiao Feng back
from Le Diyin's place.
I'm not going.
I think
Le Diyin
is quite a charismatic man.
He is elegant and a gentleman.
Apparently, he has a serious illness as well.
It's easy to get sympathized, isn't it?
It's just like those Korean dramas.
Maybe you can even see Xiao Feng
being in a 'till death do us part' scene.
No way!
Anyway,
if he does get together with Xiao Feng,
you'd definitely regret it.
Le Diyin's home address...
Find out for me.
I was joking.
You really cooked all these?
We made a deal.
It's my payment.
Grab a seat.
Here.
This is the bitter gourd and honey juice
that I improved.
I added some celery.
It is pretty conducive
to cardiovascular system.
Drink it up.
I'll get the door.
You...
You're trespassing!
Report me to the police then.
You...
Are you hungry?
Why don't you sit down and eat with us?
The toast
is burnt.
The beef
is overcooked.
The salad
isn't fresh.
The bitter gourd and honey juice
smells disgusting.
None of your business!
Go back home with me.
Su Muyun.
Before we find out the truth,
please stop interfering with my life.
I don't want to see you.
Please leave.
I'm not leaving.
Fine.
If you don't leave, I will go.
She was just blowing off her steam.
She's actually sadder than you.
I know.
I don't need you to tell me.
Even if you didn't look for me today,
I would look for you.
Don't be so fierce.
Sit down and talk with me.
I'm sick.
Standing makes me tired.
Why did you go back here?
I want to help her.
This is our family affair.
I think
if someone wants
to get Xiao Feng into trouble,
the enemy of my enemy is my friend.
Wouldn't it be better
if we help her together?
You're done considering?
As to the issues of Zhuo Family,
Ouyang Qingxue was the one who told her.
This is her recording.
I think there's something wrong with it.
But I can't be sure.
I have an idea.
What idea?
Tell me.
Follow me.
Is this person that you're contacting
good?
He has been the champion of
China Cyber Hacking Competition
for a few terms straight.
He's good.
We'll just have to wait for him.
Noob.
Let's get food delivery.
What do you want to eat?
Why don't we have hotpot?
I learned the recipe of a nice dip
from Xiao Feng a few days ago.
Hotpot dips are the least of her forte.
You're so short-sighted.
When did you two have hotpot?
Do you also want to ask
what we ordered
and what she told me?
Aren't you sick? How can you eat hotpot?
Are you worried about me now?
The audio track of this recording
does have been edited.
Uhm...
About the recording,
we haven't gotten to the bottom of it yet.
Just keep it from her for now.
Don't worry.
I'll persuade her to go back.
At least to talk things through
with your parents.
You're so good to her
just because you two are friends?
Trust me.
Fine.
Come in.
I thought it was Su Muyun.
He just left.
Didn't you bump into him?
No.
After I left,
he didn't bother you, did he?
Did he talk any nonsense?
Did he do anything...
I...
I'm not concerned about him.
I'm worried about you.
You're sick. I need to take care of you.
I think you like him.
What are you talking about?
Why don't you go back?
Have a good talk with them.
After all, your relationship goes way back.
You should listen to their explanation.
Xiao Feng!
Xiao Feng, you're back.
I...
I'm back to take my stuff.
Xiao Feng...
Let go!
I will never let you go.
I have to leave this place.
Then at least have a talk
with mom and dad.
They
are my biological parents?
Your mother's name was Qin Nianyun.
Your father was Zhuo Mufeng.
We were childhood friends.
We grew up together.
We were best friends.
We studied together,
travelled together.
Even our wedding photos
were shot together.
Then
we wanted to start a business together.
So we decided to
come back here and work our way up.
But it was easier said than done.
We've been through a lot of hardships.
Your parents were very determined.
They never gave up.
We tried to persuade them
not to be so harsh
on themselves.
But then...
Then...
I want to know
if you had anything to do with
the car accident that killed my parents?
Then, both our families
started doing business together.
We once accidentally,
unknowingly,
leaked out a trade secret.
It caused our company
to fall into a crisis.
In the end, we had no choice
but to declare bankruptcy.
In order to save the company,
your parents were
working day and night
to raise funds everywhere.
In the end, it was because
drowsy driving that...
Can you explain it in detail?
What do you mean by leaking trade secret?
What does that mean?
So do their deaths
have anything to do with you?
It was an accident, a traffic accident.
None of us wanted it to happen.
Why should I trust you?
The recording that Ouyang Qingxue gave you
was edited.
The reference materials she gave you
might not be real as well.
I'll be by your side and
find out the truth with you.
No need.
As for the truth,
I will find it out myself.
Thank you for raising me all these years.
I'll never forget your kindness.
Xiao Feng...
But before this is settled,
I don't want to have anything
to do with you Su Family.
Xiao Feng...
♪ Every smile of mine ♪
♪ Comes from the joy of being with you ♪
Xiao Feng...
♪ And have doubts in another me ♪
♪ Although our meeting is by chance ♪
♪ I won't lose you even if we missed ♪
♪ I don't have to worry
inside out of my dreams ♪
Xiao Feng...
♪ I'll give you my best self ♪
♪ I'll love you more than I thought ♪
♪ I'm not afraid to give up for love ♪
Don't cry.
♪ I'll give you my boldest self ♪
♪ And understand the meaning of hugging ♪
♪ No matter where our memories start ♪
♪ I just want to hold you tight
for a long, long time ♪
Come in.
You're awake. Do you want breakfast?
Nope.
I need to get to class in the afternoon.
I'll head to school now.
Are you okay?
Time to eat.
(Monica - Director of R&D Department)
Miss.
What?
She's Monica.
Both her parents are involved in business
and from a wealthy background.
(Curriculum Vitae, Overview, Project undertaken)
She graduated from an Ivy League university.
Half a year ago, she
accepted the offer of Ouyang Group
to be the director of the R&D department.
Strict, disciplined,
a perfectionist.
But in private...
Go on.
It's said that
she's very ambitious
always wants to be the girlfriend
of the chairman.
Whereas she has always laughed it off.
Interesting.
Then how is her relationship
with Zhuo Yifeng?
She is very against the idea of
hiring interns for the chairman.
Zhuo Yifeng
is only still an undergraduate student.
She's got good grades in school,
and the chairman seems to be
especially fond of her
and even entrusts her with important tasks.
Monica has always seen her
as a thorn in the flesh.
To have
an intern that came out of nowhere
steal her thunder in front
of someone she likes.
I understand why she's upset.
Get back to work.
-Yes.
-That's all for now.
Monica.
I've seen you a few times
in my brother's company.
I have a really good impression of you.
Really?
Thank you.
You're an exceptionally smart woman.
So let's get straight to the point.
The reason why I looked for you
was my brother.
He's old enough to have a girlfriend.
My mom is hurrying him up
and I'm worried about him as well.
Qingxue.
Why are you saying all these?
In my heart,
only the finest woman
is worth being with my brother.
For example, you.
This is too valuable.
But...
I heard that my brother
is getting close with an intern
in the company.
I'm afraid that...
It's nothing to worry about.
She's just an undergraduate intern
whose looks and capability
are way below par.
The chairman will never fall for
this kind of girl.
Xiao Feng is my schoolmate.
She's a simple person.
I don't think she gets close
to my brother on purpose.
Maybe my brother rarely
gets to meet such an innocent girl.
That's why he thinks she's special.
Innocent?
Not necessarily.
Girls who seem innocent on the outside
are usually more dangerous.
But I feel that
the chairman won't
waste his time with this kind of girl.
Don't worry.
I know what to do.
Finish all these before you get off work.
That's too much.
Even if there were three of me,
I couldn't finish them
even if I work overnight.
If you're incapable, you can leave.
But there's been too much work this week.
I've been going back at midnight everyday
and sleeping only four to five hours a day.
You can actually hire one more intern.
The company is trying to save budget.
Someone as incapable as you
would quickly be overtaken
if we get another intern.
I'm only doing this for you.
You can think about it.
Monica!
Can I ask for
an advance on my salary this month?
Salary?
You were absent and late for work
without any reason a few days ago
and you dare to ask for a salary advance?
If everyone is like you in the company,
how can the company even work?
I've heard that
you got in there
by pulling strings, right?
If I were you,
I would feel really embarrassed.
She pulled strings...
Things went pretty well this morning.
I think our cooperation
would go very smoothly.
Happy to work with you.
Sure. See you next time.
Where have you been these few days?
I'm sorry, sir.
Something happened at home recently.
But I'll finish off
the rest of my work as soon as possible.
Sir.
I wonder
why you'd hire me?
Are you too tired recently?
How about this?
Let me bring you to a place.
Take it as employee welfare.
Let's go.
When in a bad mood,
everyone needs a glass once in a while.
The color looks so pretty.
Have a taste.
It's so sweet.
One more?
Don't drink anymore.
You'll start to feel unwell.
I still want to drink.
You really can't drink anymore.
If you're upset about anything,
you can tell me.
It's easier to talk with a stranger
than people whom you're close with.
What should I say?
Anything.
Your past
or your present.
Past...
In the past...
I was rarely to be noticed
and was always ignored.
But
I still wanted to live my ordinary life.
You can't drink anymore.
In the school,
I had few friends.
Oh, yeah...
Le Diyin was my only friend.
Le Diyin?
Who's Le Diyin?
He kept encouraging and supporting me.
He's my best friend.
I got into medical school for him.
Is he sick?
He has a very serious heart disease.
I'm sorry.
(Thomas)
Mr. Ouyang, are you free to talk now?
Please wait a while.
Have you finished writing
our recent lab report?
It's due this weekend. Don't forget it.
I need this to get the scholarship.
Don't hold me back.
I know.
Be careful!
Where am I?
Are you an idiot?
Su Muyun, why are you here?
♪ How many days have passed ♪
♪ The familiar back ♪
♪ At the crossroads of fate ♪
♪ Should I remain still or rush over ♪
♪ I'm glad that we met ♪
♪ No matter how heavy the rain is ♪
♪ I now have the courage to face it ♪
♪ The cherished moments
that were hard to part with ♪
♪ Little by little ♪
♪ The story slowly reveals our memory ♪
♪ There are laughter and tears ♪
♪ We'll be together eventually ♪
♪ For the best of you in the world ♪
♪ At that most beautiful age ♪
♪ I've exhausted myself ♪
♪ For unwavering growth ♪
♪ For the best of you in the world ♪
♪ Giving eternity a name ♪
♪ Looking back many years later ♪
♪ What a warm and strong companionship ♪
♪ I'm glad that we met ♪
♪ No matter how heavy the rain is ♪
♪ I now have the courage to face it ♪
♪ The cherished moments
that were hard to part with ♪
♪ For the best of you in the world ♪
♪ At that most beautiful age ♪
♪ I've exhausted myself ♪
♪ For unwavering growth ♪
♪ For the best of you in the world ♪
♪ Giving eternity a name ♪
♪ Looking back many years later ♪
♪ What a warm and strong companionship ♪