Thank you for your support.
Come in, please come inside.
Boss Tang.
Chairman Qi.
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Director Ma.
Boss Qiu, what a rare guest!
Come, please.
Commander Guo, Boss Shao.
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Thank you, thank you.
No need to be so polite, we're family.
Second Master Tang.
That's not quite right.
We should be even more courteous among ourselves.
Alright.
Then I'll accept it.
Anyway, later on,
I'll probably lose it back to you at cards.
Alright.
Excuse me, make way.
Move aside, move aside.
Make way, make way, make way.
Boss Shao, Commander Guo.
Congratulations, Boss Tang.
Section Chief Zhao.
Why trouble yourself?
You came in person.
Who doesn't know?
Boss Tang.
Your status in Director Xiao's eyes
is second to none.
He specially told me
to personally bring the golden plaque
to congratulate Boss Tang.
Alright.
Open it and take a look.
Lift the cover.
Then please thank Director Xiao for me.
Of course.
Let's go inside and chat.
Let's go.
Alright, please, please.
Please, please.
Just a small token.
Section Chief Zhao, you went to too much trouble.
It's only right.
Please.
Band leader.
The young lady is sitting in the back room.
At dusk, she lifts the shop sign and steps outside.
The shop sign hangs outside the main door.
She stands sideways and greets the guests.
Travelers from the south and north,
those heading to the capital, those taking exams,
all come to stay at the inn.
Come in for food and lodging.
I, your humble servant, will serve you.
Section Chief Zhao.
Please take a seat.
Pour the wine.
Section Chief Zhao, have some.
Alright.
Let me toast everyone first.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you for your support, thank you.
I'll drink first to show my respect.
Enjoy your meal.
I'll be right back.
Alright.
One day, riding a horse,
I rode forward.
Suddenly, something flashed before my eyes.
Let me do it, let me.
Boss Lady.
How can you do this kind of work?
I've been through worse, this is nothing.
Besides,
it's our grand opening today.
I want to join in the fun too.
If the boss sees this,
he'll surely give us both a slap.
Let me do it instead.
You just rest.
Boss Lady.
It's smoky here, hard to breathe.
Go outside and rest.
We've got it covered here.
Alright, alright, you go ahead.
Are you saying you're the owner, sister-in-law?
Mentioning the boss,
I'm just a servant.
Stop.
Change to another piece.
This part is boring.
Alright, sir, let's switch to another piece.
As long as we know how to sing it,
you can request anything you like.
If we don't sing it well,
please give us some pointers.
You—
Get lost.
It's early spring.
Why are you bundled up so tightly?
It's such a wonderful day.
Make everyone happy.
Sing a piece for me.
Eighteen Touches (a traditional erotic song).
How about it?
Good, that's a great choice.
Sir, you—
How about today,
you listen to the full version of Scholar's Portrait first?
For good luck.
It's a special day.
Then in a few days,
when the weather gets warmer,
I'll sing for you officers
in a private show.
With so many people around,
everyone's so impatient.
It's embarrassing.
Oh my!
Little beauty,
you're really quick with words.
Sir, sir, sir—
On this stage,
no touching allowed.
Just one touch.
It's not like you'll lose a piece of flesh.
What,
is singing so precious now?
That's not what I mean.
I just want to touch.
Business is business.
You—
Sir, what are you doing?
With all these people here,
you're still getting rough?
I know.
I came with money in my pocket.
Go get the boss.
Alright.
Tonight,
you're coming home with me.
Sir—
Sir, please let go.
Sir, sir—
Let go, let go.
Don't make things hard for her.
I invited this troupe.
Sis, it's fine.
I can handle it.
I've dealt with people like this before.
Boss lady,
don't misunderstand.
These are Liu's men.
They dare to cause trouble here.
Commander Guo.
No rush.
Wait until De Yuan comes in.
Then we'll go down.
Second Master
Vice Officer Xu seems a bit upset.
The lady boss asked you to go check.
Got it.
This opera troupe,
was invited by your lady boss.
Then I have to show respect.
How about this,
tonight,
you all come to my barracks
and perform a show for me.
Whatever you usually get paid,
I'll pay double.
How's that?
This troupe
I've already booked them
to perform here for three days straight.
If you want to book them,
you'll have to wait.
Lady boss,
you're not giving me any respect?
Isn't that troublesome?
Don't be ungrateful.
Vice Officer Xu,
What's going on here?
Look how busy I am.
Come on, help me set up the chairs.
Sorry for not taking better care.
Sorry, sorry.
Come on.
How about this,
I'll drink a penalty cup.
Let me apologize to you.
No, no, no.
Second Master Tang,
Business is business.
What does that mean?
In front of all these people,
I just want to invite a performer for a drink.
And you won't even give me that respect?
How will I look in front of my men after this?
How am I supposed to get by?
These brothers,
once they leave this door,
I can't control them anymore.
How about this,
I'll drink for them, problem solved.
It's just a drink, right?
That's the officer showing us respect.
I'll drink it.
Here.
I'll drink for her.
Caifeng.
Alright.
I have to give Madam some respect.
Let's let the drinking incident go.
Okay.
But—
Commander Liu.
His birthday is coming up soon.
I can't even get an opera troupe for him.
How am I supposed to explain this when I go back?
How about this?
I—
I'll set up a few special tables then.
Invite Commander Liu and his men.
Alright, alright.
That's for later.
That Xu guy—
Had a couple shots of horse piss.
Now he doesn't even know what he's doing.
Really?
Don't push your luck.
Get lost.
Tell Commander Liu—
If he's not happy,
let's see whose gun is tougher.
Fine.
Today,
I'm here on behalf of Commander Liu.
To support Second Master Tang.
Since
Commander Guo and Second Master Tang
aren't giving Commander Liu any respect,
Brothers,
we'll just accept it.
Right?
We'll see about that in the future.
Brothers,
Let's go.
Take care, Deputy Xu.
You all carry on.
Thank you, Second Master Tang.
Everyone,
eat and drink as you please.
Sorry about that.
Sorry.
Come on.
Band leader,
please.
Grasshopper.
He really thinks he's a lobster.
They're all here just to stir up trouble.
Running this restaurant—
a lot of people are jealous.
Good thing Commander Guo was here.
Otherwise, today would've been hard to handle.
We're family, don't be polite.
Chief Xiao's business
is my business too.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Let's go upstairs.
I'll have a few more drinks with you two.
Let's go.
Close the door.
What's wrong?
Boss,
Did I cause you trouble?
No, you didn't.
I know.
Those people are all about guns.
They're not easy to deal with.
But I invited the opera troupe.
I can't just stand by
and watch them get bullied.
Of course we can't let them be bullied.
I don't understand these social situations.
You need to teach me more.
I promise I won't do this again.
From now on, I'll listen to you in everything.
Is that okay?
You said it.
Alright then.
No more drinking that kind of liquor.
I know.
You know, but you still drink it.
I just craved the taste.
You're driving me crazy.
Why are you in such a hurry to leave?
Section Chief Zhao.
I've conveyed Director Xiao's message.
It's not convenient to stay long.
So I don't hold up
Boss Tang's business.
No,
you're actually
the real God of Wealth here.
Without your permission,
who would dare open for business?
Right?
Are you mocking me?
No.
You're just the section chief for economics.
You only manage
iron pots, copper kettles, and small hardware.
Shovels, pokers, and ear picks.
Second Master Tang's big business
is out of our league.
Anyway,
from now on, business here
will need Section Chief Zhao's support.
I'll set up two tables next time
just to apologize to you.
No need for apologies.
Goodbye.
Take care.
Almost forgot.
Director Xiao said
he'll be waiting for you tonight.
He also said
the wind's strong lately, eat more pork skin.
And dress warmly.
Got it.
Finally got to eat here.
Who are you?
Boss Tang.
Slow down while eating.
Where did you come from?
From Congshan.
I was a bandit.
Had no choice.
Just trying to survive.
So why did you come down?
Couldn't stand up to the Japanese.
They attacked and tried to recruit us.
The bandits in Congshan couldn't last.
I hid in the mountains for two years.
But I just couldn't hold out anymore.
So I thought I'd come down and find a way out.
Begged my way into the city.
Haven't been here long.
I just wanted
to find some short-term work.
Fill my stomach.
But the Japanese are checking too strictly.
No one dares to hire me.
Every day I just
beg here, steal there.
Never thought
I'd end up stealing from you today.
How did I end up like this?
Boss Tang.
Looks like you've done well these years.
Life's been good for you.
You've got a solid background.
Built up such a big business.
This business
isn't something just anyone can do.
What are your plans next?
No plans.
Just taking it one step at a time.
Honestly, I never thought
I'd run into you today.
Boss Tang.
You gave me this meal.
I'm really grateful.
Don't worry.
I promise I won't cause you trouble.
I'll leave as soon as I'm full.
What are you saying?
It's pitch dark out.
Where would you go?
We've been through life and death together.
Did you forget?
Listen,
Stay here for now.
Remember,
as long as I have food,
you'll never go hungry.
No matter how long this war lasts,
victory
will definitely be ours.
If anyone
can make it out alive,
head straight
to Mudanjiang,
Songlin Town,
to the eight pine trees north of town.
Find
the thickest
and tallest pine tree.
Carve your number
onto it.
Then in Songlin Town,
hide yourself well.
Wait for regrouping.
As long as I, Old Shandong,
have a breath left,
I'll lead everyone back to the team.
Let me tell you,
you've been inside too long.
You don't know what it's like outside.
Now out here,
it's all under the Imperial Army's control.
The Anti-Japanese Allied Forces?
They're long gone.
Second Master,
sorry about this.
Here.
Alright.
Second Master, this bag of yours
must be
Chief Xiao's stuff, right?
Are you blind?
You don't even recognize Second Master Tang,
who comes here all the time?
Section Chief Zhao.
It's just the rules, no problem.
Come on, come on.
Here.
Let the brothers have a treat.
Thank you, Second Master.
Second Master Tang is always generous.
It's nothing, times are tough for everyone.
Alright, I'll head over.
Okay.
Thank you, Second Master.
Brother,
come on.
Wet your throat.
No rush.
I've brought all the gift money
over for you.
Gift money?
And
I turned all the gifts
into cash.
This
is the gift list.
Take a look.
Boss Tang sure has face.
Brother,
who are they here for?
You don't know?
Commander Liu,
about Vice Officer Xu's situation,
I want to apologize to you.
They said another share was added.
Morita went too.
Didn't you notice?
Look,
he even gave a gift of money.
Boss Tian is actually Director Morita.
Here in Mudanjiang,
how many Boss Tians are there?
I didn't recognize him.
It's mainly because there were too many guests today.
It's fine.
Go ahead.
He can't find out anything anyway.
Nothing will come of it.
Don't worry.
Deyuan,
our restaurant
is finally thriving.
In all of Mudanjiang,
everyone knows
it's run by me, Xiao Tielin.
Take a look,
at these golden-yellow yellow croakers.
They're lively and fresh.
They came swimming right to you.
Come on, come on.
Work hard.
Brother,
That's a lot.
Take it.
Deyuan,
these times
are not like before.
We don't know how long the Japanese
can hold out.
While things are like this,
grab what you can.
Well then,
thank you, brother.
So,
how does it feel to touch the yellow croaker?
It's different, right?
It is.
Hurry up, hurry up!
Move faster!
Open up, make it lively, welcome the guests!
Everyone, show some spirit.
Bring out your energy.
Sir, please come inside.
Our restaurant is newly opened.
Whether business will prosper
depends on all of you.
I won't say much else.
If you work well,
money
won't be lacking.
Let's get started.
Let's begin!
Boss Lady,
what you just said
was really clear and straightforward.
Very open and bright.
Even the managers of century-old shops
can't compare to you.
Alright, let's get to work.
Get busy.
Brother Gao, are you awake?
Brother Gao,
I've been so busy this morning, I'm all confused.
I'm Tang Deyuan's wife.
My name is Caifeng.
Sister-in-law,
the boss
asked me to bring you a set of clothes.
They're newly bought.
I think you two are about the same size.
Both tall guys.
They should fit you well.
No, no, no.
No, sister-in-law, this...
No need to be polite.
Your old clothes
when you change out of them,
I'll have someone wash them for you.
Alright.
Sorry to trouble you, sister-in-law.
It's no trouble at all.
The boss said
since you're here at our home,
just rest and recover for a few days.
Don't worry about anything.
If you need anything, just let me know.
Alright, sister-in-law.
I'll head back to my room now.
Excuse me, make way please.
Make way.
Move aside, move aside.
Take care.
Sorry, sorry.
Young Master.
Don't chase me, don't chase me.
Careful, watch the steps.
Watch the steps.
You shouldn't play like that.
Kid.
Come here.
Come over here.
Mom, he's chasing me.
Thank you, Boss Lady.
I'll get back to work then.
Alright.
Were you being naughty again?
No.
Then why did you take that?
Sister-in-law.
Changed into it.
Fits well.
It fits.
Thank you.
This kid is so sturdy.
Just like Boss Tang.
Kid, say uncle.
Uncle.
Mom, I'm going to play now.
Alright, go ahead.
Don't be naughty again.
This kid is really good.
Sister-in-law.
Building such a big business with Boss Tang,
isn't easy.
It's alright.
Sister-in-law, where are you from?
Born in Phoenix Mountain.
It's almost noon.
I'll have the kitchen make a couple of dishes.
Don't bother, Sister-in-law.
No dietary restrictions, right?
None.
I eat anything, not picky.
That won't do.
The boss is busy right now.
But he gave special instructions.
He said you two
are sworn brothers.
You must be served the best.
Just wait a moment.
Thank you, Sister-in-law.
It'll be quick.
Stop.
What are you doing?
Where's your travel permit?
I'm delivering wine.
Inspection.
Don't poke holes in it.
How am I supposed to explain this to my boss?
It's real wine.
Go, go, go.
Hurry up.
Stop dawdling, move faster.
Where are you going?
Alright, enjoy your meal, take your time.
Serve another jar to Chairman Ma's table.
Bring another jar of wine.
Put it on my tab.
Thank you, Second Master.
No need to thank me.
It's my duty.
Why did you come out here?
Just getting some fresh air.
This is what the provincial capital is like.
Everyone's eating well and drinking fine wine.
Downstairs, it's just
the lean season right now.
Let me put it this way.
Anyone dining here
isn't an ordinary person.
I can't afford to offend anyone.
No.
That outfit suits you.
No, it doesn't.
Why not?
The clothes are too fancy.
Doesn't fit a rough guy like me.
What are you trying to say?
Just say it.
I...
Boss.
Maybe I'll just wear this.
Since I'm here with you,
I can't just eat and drink for free.
I've done this job before.
I'll definitely do it well for you.
Go to the kitchen.
Alright.
Okay.
Sir, you've had enough to drink.
You're treating me to wine?
Take care, take care.
Alright.
I'll save your wine for you.
I'll take you to a good place.
Hope you enjoyed your meal, sir.
Take care.
There are people everywhere on the streets.
Police and secret agents.
Mudanjiang is bigger than before.
It’s expanded quite a bit.
Those are all Japanese.
Newly built houses.
There are also puppet army checkpoints.
Every main street has them.
I roughly counted.
There must be dozens of them.
How’s the police station area?
I pretended to be a wine delivery guy.
No one stopped me.
But I didn’t dare get too close.
I just took a look from afar.
That Mudanjiang police station,
It was complicated even before.
After the Japanese came,
They added another wall outside.
Now, I think,
Even a fly can’t get in.
If we want to get in,
It’ll be really tough.
These days,
I’ve been wandering the streets too.
I even followed a few puppet police.
Wanted to see
where they like to go.
But those places,
I didn’t see
any sign of Xiao Tielin.
That guy really doesn’t leave home.
Not even a step outside.
Looks like if we want to get close to him,
we’ll have to rely on Deyuan.
What about Yunhu?
Why isn’t he back yet?
You know,
if Yunhu can stay at Deyuan’s place,
and settle down there,
that’s a good thing.
Hope when Yunhu comes back,
he brings Boss Tang back too.
Band master,
please.
Drums beat at midnight.
It’s the middle of the night.
Liu Jinchan is upstairs.
She calls for her maid.
Come, come.
Hurry up.
Above the main street,
bring the lanterns to see.
The maid walks ahead.
Miss Liu Jinchan follows behind.
One in front, one behind, moving quickly.
The main street is just ahead.
Remember Liu Jinchan.
Let’s leave that aside for now.
Let’s hear from Li Bao.
Li Bao isn’t slacking off here.
What happened just now?
What do you mean?
You tell me.
Ran into an old acquaintance.
An old flame?
These past two years,
have I been too nice to you?
Are you asking for trouble?
Daring to boss me around now?
No, I wouldn’t dare.
I really wouldn’t dare.
Wouldn’t dare ask, Miss.
Who was that acquaintance?
May I ask where they live?
And which county?
Why did Miss go to see the lanterns?
Didn’t see them all?
See your head, more like.
He’s just a jinx.
Better not mention him.
You miss me,
in the middle of the night,
and play the zither.
That rich guy from Songlin Town,
do you still remember?
What happened?
Such a charming rich guy.
Always kept the door open for him.
Almost wanted to give him everything.
But look at him,
didn’t want the person or the money.
Left the rich guy and ran off.
So if he didn’t want this or that,
what did he want?
No idea.
Judging by his attitude,
he probably joined the Anti-Japanese Allied Forces.
Otherwise my sister
wouldn’t still be thinking about him.
If you ever treat me like this again,
just watch what I do to your arms and legs.
I'll break them for sure.
You pinched my thigh, it's all bruised.
If you break them, how am I supposed to play the fiddle?
I take care of you.
Who's taking care of who?
I'm taking care of you!
Damn fiddler, you—
What are you two doing?
Auntie.
Boss lady, what's up?
Any orders?
It's time to go on stage, hurry up.
It really hurts.
Hurts my ass.
Quit showing off.
Go, get out there and perform.
Zaor.
Why did you just call her auntie?
I'm used to calling her that.
It slipped out.
Don't let it slip halfway through.
Tell me what's going on.
Seven prostitutes, eight actors, nine musicians.
Do you get it?
We're actors.
So by the rules,
we have to call her auntie.
From the brothel.
You—
Keep your voice down.
She doesn't do that anymore.
So you can't call her that now.
But you used to
play the horn for funerals.
By the rules,
you should call me auntie too.
Call you auntie?
What?
Call me auntie.
Auntie.
What auntie?
It's time to go on stage.
Little auntie.
I'm back.
Going to sleep.
I'm going to wash up.
Boss.
Your brother came to join you.
Why'd you put him to work in the kitchen?
What's wrong with that?
Am I supposed to support him?
I, Tang Deyuan, never support freeloaders.
By the way,
business at the restaurant is good now.
Later, put up
the hiring sign outside.
From now on, if you see anyone
slacking off or being lazy,
let them go.
Alright, I'll do as you say.
Put it here, put it here.
Alright.
A little to the right.
Okay, okay, that's good.
It's good.
Teacher
Today's performance seems different from usual.
Around the fortifications in Suifenhe,
we've also confirmed their traces.
There's no doubt.
Their target is our military stronghold.
I've already reported to my superiors.
I don't care about other areas.
The "migrating fish" in Mudanjiang
must be found as soon as possible.
My men have already set up
checkpoints and mobile patrols in and around Mudanjiang.
They've also checked all the inns.
No suspicious people have been found so far.
When Matsushima Kuma was assassinated last time,
the gun, the location, the retreat—
it was all planned.
One person couldn't have done it alone.
I've already investigated the place
where Matsushima Kuma was killed.
Someone there spotted
a person resembling our target.
This person used to be
an employee at Dayou Trading Company.
By the time my men arrived,
that person was already gone.
The owner had changed too.
They said the original owner
had already left Mudanjiang.
It's now renamed Xinyi Trading Company.
In other words,
this trading company
could be an underground station for the Anti-Japanese Allied Forces.
They'll come back.
Keep watching that place patiently.
Yes.
That's also
why I chose to work in secret.
In the face of war,
a single valuable piece of intelligence
can be worth an entire division.
It can even decide the outcome of the war.
Yes.
I understand.
So,
what about Tang Deyuan?
Recently, they've used the police station's rationing rights
to open a new restaurant.
In my view,
Xiao Tielin is a parasite of the Manchukuo government.
Tang Deyuan is his accomplice.
They only care about money.
Are there any new faces around him?
Tang Deyuan is very cunning.
Since opening, he often hires and replaces staff.
There are always new faces coming and going.
So it's very hard to investigate.
What?
What an interesting opponent.
Teacher
Please give me a little more time.
Don't rush, Morita.
If there are fish,
they'll bite the hook for sure.
Find someone who used to be in the Anti-Japanese Allied Forces
and send him to Tang's restaurant to test the waters.
Yes.
Kid
Stay at the door.
Don't wander off too far.
Okay.
Hey, kid.
I'm thirsty.
Can I
get a drink of water at your house?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Kid
Dad
What's going on?
Second Master
This guest got thirsty while walking
and asked for a bowl of water.
Here.
Take the kid
out to play for a while.
Okay.
Go on, go play outside.
Let's go.
Come on, kid, let's go.
Are you
Second Master
Please have mercy
I'm hurt
There are police checking outside
Can you
let me hide here?
Where are you hurt?
My leg
Come
Sit down, sit down
That's a gunshot wound
What do you really do?
Let me tell you
If you don't tell the truth in times like these
no one can save you
I'm with the Anti-Japanese Allied Forces