Uncle
We've been walking for three days.
We'll starve before we even get there.
Don't talk like that.
Look at this whole forest.
There's bark and roots everywhere.
We won't starve.
Eating that won't give us any strength.
What if we run into a big animal?
Either it eats us,
or we eat it.
Uncle, you're really fearless.
I need to rest for a bit.
Alright.
It's fine to take a break.
Let's rest.
Old Mountain God
This mountain is split in two.
Everyone digs for their own food.
Everyone fattens up on their own.
But this ginseng
grew right on the border.
We found it first.
The ginseng lock is already tied.
It should belong to us.
Exactly.
Who says that's the border?
I say this is our territory.
That's right.
No, Lin the Tall.
If you talk like that,
you're being unreasonable.
What are you gonna do about it?
You want to fight?
You think I'm scared of you?
It's just a few of us.
Don't act tough just because you have more people.
Don't throw your weight around.
Let me tell you,
The Mountain Deity won't stand for this.
Stop wasting time, guys.
Lift the ginseng.
I dare anyone to try.
Watch me.
Lin the Tall
Lin the Tall, you're going too far!
Stop, stop, don't fight!
Alright.
That was too much.
You asked for it.
Stop, stop.
I'll kill you.
Listen to me.
What is it?
Everyone, stop!
Our people
Let go too.
This ginseng
I'll decide today.
You can have it.
Foreman
Why give it to him?
Shut up.
Why should we let him have it?
Did you hear that?
You can't just take it for free.
So, what do you want?
First,
Leave all your money here.
Second,
your food supplies,
leave those too.
Most importantly,
for the next three years,
this territory
belongs to Old Mountain God.
You can't come back here.
Deal?
That's not fair, that's not right.
Enough, enough.
Definitely not.
Fine.
Put it down, put it down.
Money and food,
you can have them.
This place,
I don't care to come back anyway.
Foreman,
Are we just letting them off this easy?
Just this little money and food,
what good is it?
We're here to make money.
Is it worth risking our lives?
Brother,
We just met by chance, thank you.
Don't mention it.
And you, young man,
you're young but skilled.
When you see injustice,
you step in to help.
It's the right thing to do.
Well said.
What's going on?
Gui'er,
I'm starving.
Really starving.
Can you spare some food?
We got lost in these mountains.
Haven't eaten in days.
Time to start work.
The blazing sun shines down on us.
Everyone, get up!
The women in our dreams have grown old.
Is he still okay or not?
He’s fine. Get up and get to work.
No, he’s not.
Are you blind?
Can’t you see what he looks like?
He’s done for, isn’t he?
If he’s useless, drag him out for the dogs.
Just try to move.
Foreman.
My brother is sick.
Can you get him a doctor?
Sick, huh?
Can he still eat?
What do you mean?
If he can eat, he can work.
Gold pit.
No freeloaders here.
Please do me a favor.
I’m begging you.
I’ll take him.
Is that okay?
Trying to run, huh?
You really have no idea.
You think I don’t know who you are?
Get him.
Go all out.
Alright.
So you want to escape?
Brother.
Uncle.
Let’s talk this out.
What do you want?
I told you, my brother is sick.
He needs a doctor.
Around here,
no one’s ever heard
of anyone being a doctor.
If there is one,
he’s far away.
Coming here would cost a fortune.
No matter the price,
I’ll pay for it.
Otherwise,
think again.
If someone dies here,
and has family,
we’ll give them some money.
And a plain white coffin.
Forget it.
Brother.
Let’s test it on your nephew today.
Let’s see if there’s really a doctor.
There is.
Uncle.
Yes, yes, yes.
Er, go!
Go find a doctor, quick.
Alright.
Right away, bring him here.
Run yourself, hurry up!
Our team
is getting smaller with every fight.
The Japanese sweep squads
haven’t let up for months.
Our people
are wounded or scattered.
Those who return to us now
and keep fighting the Japanese
are the backbone of the Resistance.
Our lifeblood.
As long as we have our lifeblood,
the flame of resistance
will never die.
Brothers,
no matter how hard it gets, we keep searching.
We gather our sparks
bit by bit,
and bring them all back.
Understand?
Got it, Squad Leader Zhao.
Good.
Let’s go.
Brother,
We meet again.
Yeah.
Nice shooting.
Let me ask you something, brother.
Have you seen anyone in the woods lately?
Run into anyone?
Yeah.
A few.
Just one.
He's a tough guy.
He killed a wolf by himself.
But he's pretty decent.
How can you tell?
He was starving but still shared his food with me.
Where did he go?
Songlin Town.
Songlin Town?
How far is that from here?
Through the woods, it takes at least ten days.
With your leg...
It's risky.
In a couple of days,
I'm heading to Songlin Town.
To sell pelts.
We can go together.
As for you,
Take care and heal up.
I can't wait.
I've got urgent business.
Did he say
why he's going to Songlin Town?
No, he didn't.
Brother,
Can I ask you a favor?
If you see a stranger again,
keep him here.
Don't let him leave.
Just say someone's looking for him.
Got it.
Thanks, brother.
Comrade
How are you?
Which unit are you from?
The Fourth Army
From the Fourth Army
Slipped.
Just right.
Let's take a break.
Comrade.
Listen to me.
If we keep this up,
we'll both die in these mountains.
Just make it quick for me.
You go.
No way.
If we go, we go together.
Why?
You want me to fight the Japanese alone?
I have to take you with me.
Comrade.
What's your name?
My name is
Li Ermao.
I'm Tang Deyuan.
Comrade Li Ermao,
if in two days
we still can't get out,
I'll do as you say.
Deal?
Alright.
Okay.
What are you looking at?
Thinking again, huh?
Hey, brother,
could you draw us a map?
Let us
try to find a way out.
Why won't you listen to me?
Did you forget how you
ended up meeting me?
Without me leading you,
even if you get out of this valley,
you'll just fall into another trap.
The fighting is fierce right now.
The Japanese are all down the mountain.
All the paths down are blocked.
I won't stop you from fighting the Japanese.
I support you.
But shouldn't you
make sure you survive first?
Come with me.
A little more time won't hurt.
Xiao Gui.
What's wrong?
Didn't you see the snake?
Stop looking.
It's gone.
In the mountains,
you need eyes in the back of your head.
Ginseng.
Smooth going, smooth going!
Hurry!
Set up the pole.
Come on, come on!
Here, hold this for me.
Did you see clearly?
What grade are the leaves?
Guys,
Grade seven.
Grade seven! Grade seven! Grade seven!
This is a real treasure.
We're rich!
We're rich! We're rich!
Over a hundred years old.
Grade seven.
King Ginseng.
How much is this worth?
Then we can make a fortune!
We'll definitely get a sky-high price!
Scissors
This
This one's huge.
How about it?
The shape is perfect too.
We're going to strike it rich this time.
We'll have money now.
Come on, bring the bark.
Hurry up, come here.
Give me another piece.
What a treasure.
Come on, moss.
Moss.
Seeds.
Yunhu.
What do you think?
We've all been here
working for so long.
But we haven't seen much gold.
Yeah.
It doesn't seem right to me either.
And there are so many people here.
You pinned down the gold foreman.
And his nephew too.
Why doesn't he say a word?
How would I know?
You should ask him.
What's the point in asking?
When he saw you risking your life,
he didn't dare touch you.
That gold foreman,
he looks tough,
but he's just like those traitors.
Deep down, he's rotten too.
Let me tell you,
it's just the two of us running for our lives now.
I reckon
he can't do anything to us.
Squad leader.
They've probably reached Songlin Town by now.
Yeah.
Maybe we're the only ones left.
I bet the squad leader now
is here.
Who's here?
I need to take a dump.
You keep working.
I'll be quick.
Lazy donkeys always need a break.
Hurry up.
There's no rice left to cook today.
What I'm afraid of is
a family of four, young and old,
might not survive till tomorrow.
I'm holding the door plank.
Why is it this noise again?
I'm waiting for my husband.
Collapse!
Someone help!
Getting a doctor won't help this time.
Yunhu
Why did you leave him outside?
You guys,
Hold him down for me.
Grab him!
Go after him!
Chase him!
Stop!
Hurry, over here!
Quick!
Hurry!
Don't dawdle!
Let's go, move forward!
Comrade Tang Deyuan
It's dawn.
Two days have passed.
It's morning.
Come here.
It's daylight.
Drink some water first.
I don't want any.
Why not?
I know you can't do it.
Put the knife down.
Go pee in the woods.
I'm begging you.
You're helping me.
I'm really struggling.
In the next life,
let's be comrades again.
Comrade,
what's your name?
My name is
Li Ermao.
Comrade,
don't worry about me.
I can't make it.
If you can eat, you can survive, you know?
Didn't you say
you're from Huachuan?
Oh my,
Huachuan pork head,
it's so delicious.
Comrade,
just make it quick for me.
You go.
No way.
If we go, we go together.
Why should I?
Fight the Japanese alone?
I have to take you with me.
Comrade Li Ermao.
Li...
Hurry up.
Get off quickly.
Get off.
Come here.
You, come here.
Go over there.
Move it.
Go.
Hurry.
Hurry up.
Stop dawdling.
You too.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
You too, keep up.
Stop dragging your feet, move!
Hurry up, what are you doing?
Hurry up.
Stand up.
Go to hell.
Good.
All strong workers.
Yes.
What's your name?
I-I'm Zhao Fugui.
Where are you from?
Bai Gangzi.
How old are you?
I'm twenty-four.
Next.
What's your name?
I'm Shinji Katayama.
Japanese?
I'm Japanese.
That one.
Come here.
Yes.
Lift your head.
You're no longer Japanese.
You don't deserve it.
Know your place.
You deserters
are our disgrace.
Here,
you're no different from those stupid pigs.
No difference at all.
Listen carefully.
You, who betrayed the Emperor,
will stay here
and spend your life repenting.
Here,
you're all the same.
Understand?
Understood.
The new guy.
That one over there.
Hey, you.
Old Tang.
Keep your voice down.
Quiet! What are you saying?
It's fine. He just asked me for soup.
No soup. Just eat.
Okay, okay.
The new guy.
Yes.
You're okay?
I was fine.
But you shouted.
Almost got us in trouble.
I thought you were dead.
How did you end up here?
On the way to Eight Pines.
Got caught by the Japanese.
What about you?
Me too.
So, you...
Do you have news about anyone else?
I was with Xiaohua.
We got separated in the mountains.
No idea how she is now.
Do you know about anyone else?
At first,
I was with Yunhu.
Then,
The two of us
were tricked into Jin Gouzi.
Then we got set up.
Yunhu was buried alive.
What about the squad leader and Xiaogui?
You have no news at all?
None.
But
seeing you today
makes me feel a lot better.
The Japanese are capturing so many people.
What are they planning?
Who knows?
But I heard
around here
there are more labor camps like this.
About twenty or so.
At night, often
I can hear
explosions in the mountains.
Are they mining?
I haven't seen them
dig up anything.
Bastard.
You want to eat that badly?
You cut in line.
And you think you're right?
Wait, that's a Japanese.
What are you doing?
After working all day,
you still have energy to fight?
Me,
I have a good temper.
I'm kind too.
But all this
is only for those who obey.
Answer.
Say yes.
Yes.
No next time.
Whatever they're up to,
we need to find a way to escape.
Get the information from here
and report it to our superiors.
Right.
Escape.
Do you have a plan?
No.
Not yet.
Boss.
You’re here.
Why are you here again?
I missed you.
Get lost.
A bear came into the yard in the first half of the night.
It took my pickled cabbage jar.
Then in the second half of the night,
you dragged in a pig carcass.
Is it ever going to stop?
Isn’t that just perfect?
One goes out, one comes in.
As long as you don’t make me pay.
Autumn rain brings a chill.
Pour me a bowl of wine, quick.
I need something warm.
What kind of weather is this?
It just keeps raining.
Rain is good.
Water brings wealth.
Enough.
Stop cooking dishes and soup.
Did you bring the money?
All you care about is money.
That’s not right.
I only brought what I owed last time.
The higher-ups are getting suspicious.
They asked why there were two collapses in one month.
Even the King of Hell can’t keep up.
Take it easy.
There have been a lot of collapses.
You take a big cut too.
I do a lot of work myself.
Brother.
I know you’re not easy to fool, Big Safe.
But still,
We agreed on this beforehand.
I’m in charge of bringing in the living.
Dragging out the dead.
And pretending to be relatives of the dead for money.
I do just as much as you.
Who told you to bring them into the yard?
Bad luck.
Everyone’s seen this kind of thing these days.
It’s all pure silver.
This wine—
So soft and mellow.
Feels like little hands.
It’s deadly tempting.
Quit with the nonsense.
Can’t touch, can’t even—
Just want to enjoy the taste.
If you don’t shut up,
I’ll cut out your tongue.
And stuff it down your throat.
Fine.
I’ll wait for you inside.
Restless spirits, don't haunt me.
Go bother whoever you're looking for.
Let go of me.
I've seen every kind of ghost there is.
Gluttonous ghosts, starving ghosts,
hanged ghosts, drowned ghosts,
ghosts who died of illness, ghosts who froze to death,
even drunkards and lechers.
Any ghost who sees me
has to bow their head.
and keep their distance.
They all steer clear of me.