[English subtitles are available]
[Burning Flames]
[Episode 28]
What?
You left just like this?
It's you again.
He's not my Gou.
Why would I stay by his side?
You finally know
he's not your Gou.
Then, where is
your Gou now
and why did he
impersonate your Gou?
I don't know.
You actually know very well.
Your Gou
is already dead.
Poor Gou.
He only wanted to protect Bai Cai when he was alive.
Who would care
about him after he died?
Who would avenge him?
Avenge?
Do you want to know
how your Gou
really died?
I can let you
see the true natures
of the people around you.
Bai Cai.
Gou.
Gou, Gou.
Gou, bad news!
Lan just came back.
She said Bai Cai left Bai State.
The Immortal Realm is watching eagerly now.
It's too dangerous
for Ms. Bai to be alone.
Where is Uncle Ziyu?
Uncle Ziyu said
he wants to find a remote place
for qi cultivation.
Gou.
Gou, Zhou Qiao is here.
Zhou Qiao,
what are you doing here?
Don't be so nervous.
I came here alone.
I have no time to chat to you.
I need to find Bai Cai.
I can help you find her,
but things have different priorities.
Now, you have
a more important thing to do.
Enter the palace with me.
Enter the palace?
What do you mean?
You said it yourself.
You want me to pay homage to the Xin King and Queen,
help clear their names,
and also expose to the public
the truth of the Immortal Realm
using the Eternal Fruit
to kill people.
These things
have all been prepared.
They're in the palace,
right before the portraits
of the Xin King and Queen.
You mean
ancestral worship?
That's right.
Tomorrow is an auspicious day.
Tomorrow morning,
I will open the palace gate
so that all the people
can enter the palace to worship the Xin King with you.
At that time,
you can tell them
about the Eternal Fruit
and take advantage of the public anger
to go up in arms
and strengthen your anti-immortal army.
This is killing two birds with one stone.
Your reputation
will be at the level
of the Xin King from before.
When did you
become so kind?
What are you trying to pull?
You chose
these two things,
but now you ask me what I'm trying to pull?
Okay.
I'll go find Bai Cai first.
Tomorrow,
I'll enter the palace with you.
According to etiquette,
the day before
worshipping a late king, you need to burn incense and bathe,
you can't eat or sleep,
and you must pray quietly in the palace
for the blessings of the ancestors.
Have you forgotten?
Your Highness,
what Zhou Qiao said
is reasonable.
Although
the Xin State is gone,
that means we must
follow the etiquette even more.
Just go to the palace.
I can help you find Ms. Bai Cai.
It'll better than you
looking for a needle in a haystack.
Your Highness,
we found traces left by Bai Cai.
Zhaixing Pavilion.
Bai Cai's aura is here.
She must have been here.
What's your name?
You look like a puppy.
I'll call you
Gou.
No,
I'm Wu Geng.
Gou!
Miss.
You look so tired.
Have some tea.
Here.
My Kongshi Dream has been completed.
Bai Cai is now delirious
and completely
under my control.
Plus,
the juice of the Eternal Fruit
can make one's divine spirit dazed,
waver,
and even
produce hallucinations.
What should we do with this pot of tea?
I believe
you understand.
I understand.
Don't let me down.
I'll take her to Zhaixing Pavilion.
You know what to do.
This is Zhaixing Pavilion
and where your Gou
was killed.
Gou...
Gou died here.
Your Gou
died at the evil empress's Zhaixing Pavilion,
under Xinyue Hu's sword.
Xinyue Hu?
The late Queen?
That's right, Xinyue Hu.
In other words,
Wu Geng's mother.
Impossible.
Since you don't believe me,
I'll show you.
This is my memory.
I want you to see the truth with your own eyes,
lest you think I'm lying to you.
This is Prince Wu Geng.
Although his body is dead,
his divine spirit
is in Xinyue Hu's hands.
Gou.
In a short while,
he won't be your Gou anymore.
Open your eyes wide
and take a good look.
Mother,
what are you doing?
I'm going to transfer your divine spirit
into this child's body.
From now on, his body
will be yours to use.
You're a lowly slave,
but you look a bit
like Geng.
Having Geng
live in this world for you.
is your good luck.
You're a fool
and, furthermore, a slave.
Poor child.
In this world,
you're just a useless person,
but Geng is different.
He inherited
the Immortal Clan's bloodline.
He's the prince of Xin State
and also the hope of Xin State.
Having him live in this world for you
will be much more important than you.
Gou.
Gou!
Xinyue Kui.
So at that time,
Gou was already dead.
He'd died in your mother's hands.
You're just a human.
How could you know the tactics of the Immortal Clan?
Besides,
they were fully prepared
to deceive you.
How could they let you know?
Poor Gou.
He died in Wu Geng's place
just because they had similar looks.
Wu Geng!
Wu Geng, come out!
I need to get a clear answer!
Wu Geng!
That's right, Bai Cai.
You want to kill Wu Geng
to avenge Gou.
Kill Wu Geng
To avenge Gou.
Do you remember
what I said before?
When necessary,
kill Bai Cai.
Don't worry.
Wu Geng will appear
in front of you soon.
By then,
you can ask him clearly.
Why, Lan?
I didn't want to kill you,
but now it seems
that I must.
Don't blame me.
Why do you want to kill me?
The High Priest ordered me
that if anything happens,
I must kill you myself.
Does Wu Geng know
that you want to kill me?
He doesn't.
He loves you wholeheartedly.
I've never told him.
Bai Cai,
why are you going against Wu Geng
with Xinyue Kui?
He loves you so much.
Why do you have to hurt him?
He killed Gou.
He killed Gou,
you know?
Bai Cai,
I used to think
that I could ignore
those unfounded prophecies
and even disobey the High Priest's order.
Prophecy?
Bai Cai,
I'm sure now.
You will definitely hurt Wu Geng.
Whether it's his body
or his heart,
you will hurt him.
Bai Cai,
you asked me before
if I have any other feelings for Wu Geng.
Love between the Immortal Clan and human race
will be cursed.
The Xin King and Xinyue Hu,
Shi Xing and Mingyue...
The human will be the one who gets hurt in the end.
I'm from the Immortal Clan
and Wu Geng is human.
Even without you,
we can only be
a teacher and student,
comrades, or friends.
I can fight for him
and die for him,
but nothing else,
other than that.
You can blame me,
but don't blame him!
Lan!
Don't hurt her.
Tomorrow
is a big day.
All of this
relies on you, Ms. Bai Cai.
Have you made up your mind?
I don't need to repeat
the rules for tomorrow, right?
Prince Wu Geng,
I found this on the street.
Look.
Does it belongs to Ms. Bai Cai?
By the way,
this is the ritual for the sacrificial ceremony tomorrow.
Your Highness, please have a look.
[Sacrificial Ceremony Ritual]
Welcome the Immortal half a quarter before sunrise?
Tell Zhou Qiao
this is unnecessary.
I'm rebelling against the Immortals.
Yes.
Congratulations, High Priest.
Our plan was successful.
Wu Geng is in the palace now.
According to etiquette,
he can't eat or rest
today.
Just this
can also consume some of his strength.
Well done.
As you can see,
once Wu Geng is eliminated,
you can
ascend to the throne without any obstacles.
Zhou Qiao,
I know
you have your own purposes.
But my divine power
of the Kongshi Realm
allows me to see through
your every move.
I... I dare not
lie to you.
Do you want to replace Gui Mu
as the immortal resident in the mortal world forever
or become the second Xin King
or Zhou Fa?
I advise you to think carefully.
Before I come to the mortal world,
take care of the rest problems.
Don't leave any hidden trouble.
Okay, High Priest.
Are you saying
Wu Geng will mourn Brother and Sister-in-law
in front of the palace?
That's right.
At noon the day after tomorrow.
Don't worry, High Priest.
Tomorrow,
Ziyu definitely will not show up.
As for Lan,
High Priest,
this is what I think.
Wu Geng's divine power of the Colorless Realm
is very strong.
I think we should keep her alive.
If anything happens tomorrow,
Wu Geng will have to think twice for the sake of her life.
You're very thoughtful.
Then let her live one more night.
Ziyu won't show up tomorrow.
Lan and those slaves
are in our hands.
Also,
Bai Cai will turn against him.
High Priest,
we have a very careful plan.
I really don't know
how Wu Geng can survive.
Trying to send a message?
Father,
Mother,
please bless me
with a smooth day tomorrow.
[Tianji Palace]
Adjust your hats.
Kneel.
No need to kneel.
My father's ambition
[Tianji Palace]
is to make the human race
hold their heads high, become strong,
and not kneel to immortals.
My mother always believed
that everyone was born equal.
Father and Mother
didn't like people kneeling to them.
The Immortal Clan killed my parents
and left their bodies in the wild.
It also destroyed Xin State, which has a 100-year history.
This is a personal grudge.
The Immortal Clan has occupied Xin State
and enslaved the people.
They have even used the Eternal Fruit
to harm the people.
This is a public grudge.
Although my strength is weak,
I won't yield to power.
We should know
we don't need to be afraid of immortals
and destiny is nothing to be afraid of.
My father once said
what people pursue in this life
is not about never failing.
It's about being able to stand up again
when you fall.
That's what he said
and did.
My parents
had a clear conscience towards Heaven, Earth,
their hearts,
and the people.
Today, I'm going to fight against immortals.
Maybe
I'll fail like them.
I'll die like them.
But I hope
you can remember what I said today.
Remember,
the people come first
than immortals.
The people come first
than Heaven.
Well said.
Let's begin.
Bai Cai?
Bai Cai,
I'm glad you came.
Come.
Mourn my parents with me.
They would be very happy.
A sage is someone whose spirit lives on after he dies.
[Tianji Palace]
There's law in the world. The great virtue can be demonstrated widely.
Bow
and show your respect.
Xin King will be remembered forever.
[Tianji Palace]
If they
really had a clear conscience
towards Heaven, Earth,
and the people like you said,
how did my Gou
die?
The wind has risen.
Wu Geng,
Lan,
are you okay?
If destiny really exists,
what did my Gou
do wrong?
Bai Cai,
what are you doing?
What's going on?
Protect Prince Wu Geng.
Gui Mu's Poison Locust!
Zhou Qiao!
Gou.
-Hurry.
-Gou.
What's wrong?
Go protect the people.
But... what about you?
Go!
Let's go. Protect everyone.
Be careful, Gou.
Okay.
Hurry! Leave now!
Get out of here!
-Leave!
Hurry!
Everyone, leave now!
Don't stay here.
Leave!
Leave now!
Bai Cai, why?
[Tianji Palace]
Why?
Run!
This way.
[Tianji Palace]
Wu Geng,
why are you so distant?
Today is the big day of mourning my sister.
Why didn't you tell me?
Don't you
regard me as your family?
You have colluded with each other
to set a trap to kill me?
What else do you think?
Should we let you, a rebel from the previous dynasty,
mourn Xin King, an anti-immortal rebel,
openly?
If I don't kill you,
how can I
sit on the throne at ease?
Gui Mu,
Plague Immortal,
can't miss this scene.
Zhou Qiao,
go ask your godfather here now.
Yes, High Priest.
Wu Geng,
today,
I'm going to let Fu Xi know
what destiny is.
[Tianji Palace]
This dagger
was specially made.
It can suppress the divine spirit.
Now,
you can no longer use
the divine power of the Colorless Realm.
Accept your fate.
High Priest's divine power of the Kongshi Realm.
Zhui Ri's divine power of the Wanxiang Realm.
Great.
They are here to save me.
Zhou Qiao,
I'll make you pay the price.
Stay away!
Good, Bai Cai.
Wu Geng
is the one who killed Gou.
You must avenge him.
Wu Geng,
because of you,
I can never
see my Gou again.
If anyone
dares to hurt my Gou,
I will never let him go.
Darn it.
The ancient divine power is so strong.
It's resisting
my divine power of the Kongshi Realm.
Bai Cai,
Wu Geng killed Gou.
Now I order you
to kill him.
Kill Wu Geng.
Answer me now.
Are you Wu Geng
or Gou?
Bai Cai,
whether I'm Wu Geng or Gou,
I will protect you
forever.
Fine.
I trust you.
The divine power of the Colorless Realm.
The nature of humans
is endowed
by Heaven.
What is destiny?
The strong are destiny.
The powerful are destiny.
Immortals are destiny.
But in this world,
the people's will
and all the living creatures
are destiny too.
Kui,
if you don't understand this,
what's the use
of having my eyes?
Fortunately, the livestock used on the memorial ceremony
is fresh enough
to let me apply some blood on my body.
Otherwise,
it would've been really difficult
to put on this show.
Xinyue Kui,
everything you saw
is what we wanted you to see.
You thought you would surely win.
Actually,
it was just
a show.
Xinyue Kui is evil and cunning.
She likes to play tricks secretly.
So in the future,
she definitely will try
to deal with us.
We must
think of a perfect plan
to make sure we can defeat her with just one blow.
The Demon Realm
is the Demon Clan's territory.
She definitely won't show up here.
This is also another reason
why I want to return to Bai State.
As long as I appear in the mortal realm...
She definitely will show up.
By that time,
we can catch the turtle in the jar.
I knew it
when you approached Bai Cai for the first time.
By the way, Gou,
what's your opinion
on the mysterious person who saved me today?
There's no secret between us.
This is what you can't see.
So,
Gou asked me to pretend not to know
and play along with you.
-Gou.
After I figured out your intention,
I used the divine power of the Colorless Realm
to isolate your divine power of the Kongshi Realm.
Then I told Bai Cai
about the relationship between me and Gou.
This is also what you can't see.
Actually, I'm Wu Geng.
I'm also Gou.
Bai Cai pretended to be bewitched
to make you think
you succeeded
in driving a wedge between us.
This
is our first step.
Actually, I knew
you would use Bai Cai to hurt me
on the day of the memorial ceremony long ago.
So we followed your plan
to catch a turtle in the jar.
This
is our second step.
I was worried that we couldn't fool you.
I didn't expect
the Immortal Realm's high priest
to fall into Wu Geng's trap so quickly.
Xinyue Kui,
you underestimated
Bai Cai's trust in me.
This is the first mistake you made.
Good.
Very good.
You have many tricks.
You know how to play along.
So what?
I'm going to attack the Immortal Realm
and destroy
all the powerful immortals like you!