[English subtitles are available]
[Burning Flames]
[Episode 15]
No! No!
Thank god.
Not everyone here is a monster.
It's time to eat.
What's the matter?
Do you not like the buns I made?
Give it a try.
Everyone says
the buns I made are good.
Why are you locked up here?
Where are you from?
Are you from Xin State?
How is Xin State now?
I guess
you've been locked here for a long time.
Or you wouldn't have asked that.
Answer me!
You monsters
are all so brutal!
Tell me
how to get out of here first.
What happened to Xin State?
Tell me now!
Xin State doesn't exist anymore.
The Immortal Clan conquered Xin State
and replaced it with Bai State.
How about the empress of Xin State?
Is she still alive?
No.
The empress took the prince
to the Zhaixing Pavilion and set it ablaze,
perishing in the flames with Xin State.
The fire burned for a day and a night.
Both of them were burned to ashes.
Shi Xing.
I underestimated
your divine power of the Asura Realm.
The Seal of the Dead
hasn't weakened you at all.
On the contrary, it has made you stronger.
Father.
Look.
Your eyes
fit me perfectly.
Very good, Hu.
Recently,
your divine power of the Kongshi Realm has grown much stronger.
And your prophecy skills
have improved quite a lot too.
Father,
but I still can only see
blurry visions.
I still can't see
more specific things.
Don't worry.
Take your time to feel
the change of the divine power in your body.
Transform it and control it
so that you can make use of it.
Don't be like your sister.
She just wants a shortcut, and her foundation is weak.
Father.
The prophecy skills
are what my sister wants to learn the most.
She just wants to master them as soon as possible
to make you happy.
Your sister
is gifted,
but she's too ambitious.
The more divine skills she learns,
the greater
her ambitions become.
It'll cause her to lose her sanity in the end.
Father.
Forget it.
Come on. Let's practice together.
You praise my sister for whatever she does.
But no matter what I do,
I'm still a thorn in your eyes.
Just wait and see.
High Priest. High Priest!
I'm Gui Mu.
It's you again.
Gui Mu.
Fu Xi is very cunning.
How did you
track him down?
High Priest.
The person I tracked down
was not Fu Xi,
but a slave girl.
Through this girl,
I found Shenyin Village.
I also found that
this girl possessed
a mysterious power.
What mysterious power?
I don't know it yet.
Gui Mu.
Speaking of which,
you got injured again
in the battle at Shenyin Village.
Look at you now.
How pitiful you are.
High Priest, please show me mercy
and give me some pills.
Think about it.
If it weren’t for me,
you wouldn’t have found
Shenyin Village so easily, right?
You're right.
In that case,
compared to fighting in battles,
you, the Plague Immortal,
are better suited
to gather information.
Why don't you go to Xuan Chai
to ask for a job?
Gui Mu.
You should be grateful
that I didn't punish you for your incompetence.
Get out.
Don't let me
see your embarrassing face again.
Okay. I'm out of here. I'm out of here.
Stop.
If you can't
find out who that girl is,
I'll kill you.
I understand.
I'm your loyal servant.
I'll go find it out right away.
Father.
How many secrets
are hidden in your eyes?
Who killed him?
Should we take a break?
No.
It's cooler in the desert at night
than during the day.
We can walk fast at night.
But we don't even know
where the King's City is.
It's useless to be anxious.
The sooner we get there,
the better chance we stand.
High Priest.
Should we take action now?
Have you forgotten what Shi Xing said that day?
Whoever wants to kill him
will be killed by me.
At this moment,
they're too close to the King's City.
If we take action now,
Shi Xing can feel
our divine power immediately.
He's a crazy man.
We need to wake the King of Immortals from his seclusion
to take him down.
For such a trivial matter,
we can't afford to disrupt
the King of Immortals' seclusion.
Then, High Priest, what do you think we should do?
Trap them in the desert until they die.
Keep it quiet when you do it.
Don't let Shi Xing notice it.
Lan.
Stay still.
We're surrounded by quicksand.
Why is the tornado
following us wherever we go?
It's the divine power of the Wanxiang Realm.
The divine power of the Wanxiang Realm?
This is the Immortal Clan's doing?
It's strange.
The wind can't hurt us
but can trap us here.
I wonder
what this is for.
I know.
Someone is using the tornado
to lure us into quicksand.
The quicksand can't trap us,
but it can lead us astray.
In the end,
we won't be able
to find the King's City.
So the right way
is in the direction of the tornado.
After all,
no one dares to run into the tornado.
So the direction of the tornado
is the direction of the King's City.
You're right.
Lan, let's go.
Look. How funny they are.
Tai Ji.
Make your tornado
stronger.
I'm afraid that
it may tear them apart.
Look.
I'm only using 30% of my power.
Look at them.
They're already in over their heads.
They're biting off more than they can chew.
In front of us,
they're like powerless ants.
They think too much of themselves
and try to challenge us.
However,
we can crush them
and reduce them to ashes
without lifting a finger.
They're so vulnerable.
It's not worth it
to waste our time and energy on them.
You're right, High Priest.
We just need to stand here
and watch them invite their own deaths.
You leave first.
Let's leave together.
The wind can't hurt me.
Go save Bai Cai.
It's just a small trick
of an insignificant deity.
It doesn't matter.
Since he wants to go in,
and she wants him to go in,
we'll just help them fulfill their wishes.
Shi Xing.
Although you're hard to deal with,
you won't let me down
when it comes to killing.
What the heck?
The divine power has run out?
[Liusha City]
This must be the King's City.
Liusha City?
When Lan sees this gourd,
she'll know that I've entered the city safely.
I can't tell directions at this place.
Is this
also because of the divine power of the Immortal Clan?
[Dongling Tea House]
If Lan can't get clear of the tornado
before dark,
she'll be in even greater danger.
[Dongling Tea House]
Take a look.
Please come in.
We just got some great tea from the Central Plain.
It's sweet and has a great aftertaste.
[Dongling Tea House]
We've got some great tea from the Central Plain.
It's sweet and has a great aftertaste.
To celebrate the city governor's wedding,
we've got some great tea from the Central Plain.
It's sweet and has a great aftertaste.
[Dongling Tea House]
Sir, by the city governor,
do you mean Shi Xing?
It's sweet and has a great aftertaste.
To celebrate the city governor's wedding…
Sir.
We've got some great tea from the Central Plain.
It's sweet and has a great aftertaste.
[Dongling Tea House]
To celebrate the city governor's wedding,
we've got some great tea from the Central Plain.
It's sweet and has a great aftertaste.
Please come in.
Life is going to
get better for us very soon.
I passed here several times just now.
I didn't see anyone.
When did they show up?
This dish tastes good.
Waiter. Waiter.
Waiter.
Have you prepared the desserts
for the city governor's wedding?
Coming.
Look.
I've long prepared them.
Sir, welcome.
Watch out!
I'll wear this dress
to dance for the city governor.
Can you afford
to ruin it?
Sorry.
Sorry. I'm late.
Waiter, tea.
Let me drink to you.
You came just in time. Let's drink.
Coming.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Sir, your tea.
Enjoy.
The city governor is getting married.
After finishing this cup of tea,
we're going to his mansion to congratulate him!
Great, great!
Come on. Drink.
Back then, I should've learned
self-defense skills
with Wu Dong and Wu Xia.
If only the seal on me
could be broken.
That way, I wouldn't have
become a burden to Gou.
Waiter.
Why haven't our dishes been served?
Have some more.
This dish is delicious.
Try this.
Waiter. Waiter.
Have you prepared the desserts
for the city governor's wedding?
Coming.
Look. I've long prepared them.
Watch out!
I'll wear this dress
to dance for the city governor.
Can you afford to ruin it?
Sorry.
Sorry. I'm late.
Waiter, tea.
Let me drink to you.
Sir, your tea.
Enjoy.
Come on.
Cheers.
The city governor is getting married.
After finishing this cup of tea,
we're going to his mansion
to congratulate him!
Great, great!
Have some tea.
Come on. Drink.
They are living
at a different time.
Maybe
they're not even real.
Where is the food?
I'm starving!
Where's the food?
Shi Xing, I want to eat!
To celebrate the city governor's wedding,
we've got some great tea from the Central Plain.
It's sweet and has a great aftertaste.
[Dongling Tea House]
To celebrate the city governor's wedding,
we've got some great tea from the Central Plain.
It's sweet and has a great aftertaste.
To celebrate the city governor's wedding,
we've got some great tea from the Central Plain.
It's sweet and has a great aftertaste.
To celebrate the city governor's wedding,
we've got some great tea from the Central Plain.
It's sweet and has a great aftertaste.
To celebrate the city governor's wedding,
we've got some great tea from the Central Plain.
It's sweet and has a great aftertaste.
To celebrate the city governor's wedding,
we've got some great tea from the Central Plain.
It's sweet and has a great aftertaste.
To celebrate the city governor's wedding,
we've got some great tea from the Central Plain.
It's sweet and has a great aftertaste.
To celebrate…
It seems that
they're monsters that only come out at night.
That's the only place that has light.
Shi Xing must be there.
Shi Xing, let me out!
After I get out, I'll kill you!
Let me out!
Could Bai Cai and Uncle Ziyu
be locked up here?
Looks like someone has a death wish.
Come here. Let me out!
I'll kill Shi Xing for you!
Let me out!
Who is she?
Who on earth is she?
It's time to eat.
Who on earth
is that woman?
Tell me.
Tell me!
Who on earth is that woman?
Let go of me!
You lunatic!
I don't know what you're talking about.
Bai Cai, how are you?
Gou.
Gou, you're finally here.
Gou, what took you so long?
Gou.
Sorry. I'm late.
I'm fine.
By the way, Gou,
many people are imprisoned here.
Over there,
there seems to be someone from Xin State.
Xin State?
Could it be Uncle Ziyu?
Gou, let's run.
We can't beat him.
Without taking him down,
we can't get out of here.
You really came.
Shi Xing, I've come as promised.
Why didn't you keep your promise?
So what?
I didn't expect
the battle at Shenyin Village
to give you
quite a bit of combat experience.
Shi Xing.
Although you're from the Immortal Clan,
you must not underestimate
the wisdom of the human race.
The human race is ignorant.
Do you really think
you can hurt me just like this?
Gou.
Gou!
You haven't improved at all.
I feel humiliated by the fact
that you actually came to me with a crippled arm.
Didn't I tell you
to elevate your cultivation to its peak
before coming to me?
Look at you now.
You're a total wreck.
You're not qualified to be my opponent.
Let Bai Cai go.
Since you care so much about her,
tomorrow,
at midnight,
come to defeat me.
If you fail,
both of you will die.
Actually, it's easy to defeat you,
as long as you do me a favor.
What's it?
Send me
into the cell in the middle.
Interesting.
Boy,
you are the first person
who has intrigued me.
Don't let me down.
Gou.
Were you
taken here by Shi Xing as well?
How long have you been kept here?
How long?
I don't remember.
Don't you want to escape?
The people I care about
are all gone.
To me, the outside world
is just
a bigger prison.
Are you from Xin State?
Xin State is gone.
He's gone too.
Uncle Ziyu.
It's really you.
Back then, when Xin State was at war,
you and my father
fought against Hei Long together.
Uncle Ziyu, it's me.
I'm Wu Geng.
You're Wu Geng?
I don't know who you are.
But one thing's for sure, you're not Wu Geng.
That day, I rushed back to the Xin capital
to rescue the people there
before the Immortal Clan attacked the city.
However,
she set fire to the Zhaixing Pavilion.
She and Wu Geng
are long gone.
No, Uncle Ziyu.
My mother
saw the future
when I was born.
So she took out
a shred of my primordial spirit
and kept it in the mortal world.
Before she died,
she protected me with her divine spirit
so that I could
take on Gou's identity
to evade the Immortal Clan's pursuit.
It's your mother's wristband
and her remaining divine spirit.
Are you really Wu Geng?
You're not dead?
Uncle Ziyu.
I guessed
that Shi Xing would have brought you
to this place.
Before I arrived in the King's City,
I was nervous
all the way.
I was afraid that I'd be disappointed in the end.
But now, I'm finally looking at you.
Great.
Wu Geng.
Since you were born,
I had been traveling around the world.
I've never taken a close look
at you like this.
Your eyes
look exactly
like your father's eyes.
Wu Geng.
Uncle Ziyu.
Break!
Wu Geng, wait for me.
Who's she?
That woman.
Where is she?
Why can't I remember anything?
Who on earth is that woman?
Who is she?
Why can't I remember anything?
Where is she?
Tell me. Who is she?
How would I know
who that woman is?
You're lying.
You definitely know
who that woman is.
Tell me.
Tell me who she is!
I…I don't know.
Who is she? Answer me!