[English subtitles are available]
[Burning Flames]
[Episode 16]
Tell me.
Who is she?
How would I know
who that woman is?
You're lying.
You definitely know
who that woman is.
I…
Tell me.
Tell me who she is!
I don't know.
Who is she?
Tell me!
Uncle Ziyu.
Were you taken here
by Shi Xing
after Xin State lost the war back then?
Shi Xing is a lunatic.
Over the years,
he's been gathering great cultivators from around the world
and keeping them confined here.
After the war at the Xin capital,
he thought
I was a rare opponent,
so,
he's kept me imprisoned here.
But given your cultivation,
this place can't trap you.
Why did you stay here
instead of escaping?
I became homeless after Xin State fell.
I'm dead inside.
To me, the outside world
is no different
from this place.
Uncle Ziyu.
It's not your fault
that Xin State fell
and my father was defeated.
Hei Long was so powerful back then.
The Immortal Clan was unstoppable.
Even if my father
used the divine power of the Undying Bird,
he still lost the war.
Both of you did your best.
Uncle Ziyu.
You're the best Great Swordsman of the human race.
You're the deity slayer.
When Xin State was at war,
you fought against Hei Long
with my father
and made all of us
see hope.
You showed us
that deities were not invincible.
You and my father brought hope
to us all.
Both of you are heroes of Xin State.
Before my mother died,
she told me to find you no matter what.
She said
you were our hope.
I can see it.
One day,
you'll be Geng's hope.
I understand it now.
Over the years,
I've been through some tough times,
but I gritted my teeth and toughed it out.
Because
I want to be like you and Father.
I want to be able to resist Hei Long
and fight against him.
So, Uncle Ziyu,
please trust me
like you trusted my father.
We can definitely lead the human race
to live a new life
where no one is a slave.
Uncle Ziyu.
Our priority now
is to leave this dump.
To leave here,
you have to defeat Shi Xing first.
But now,
you're no match for him.
If we work together,
we can definitely defeat Shi Xing.
Uncle Ziyu.
What are you doing?
Without divine power,
you're no different from a mortal.
Uncle Ziyu…
Listen.
Whether you can defeat Shi Xing
is all up to you.
I'll use qi cultivation
to channel your acupoints now.
As long as you can make it through,
your body will become much stronger,
and your divine power will greatly increase.
There is actually another power
hidden in his body.
No.
He'll die if this goes on.
Uncle Ziyu.
Don't hesitate.
If I can't make it through this,
how can I fight against Hei Long?
Okay.
Since you've made up your mind,
it's better to channel the power than to suppress it.
Keep breathing.
Stay calm.
Next,
try your best to control the power in your body.
Geng.
You're the prince of Xin State.
You're my son.
You're also the hope of tens of thousands of people of Xin State.
Geng.
It's gonna be a difficult journey.
Your father and I will always be with you.
You won't be lonely.
I can't lose.
I have to become stronger.
Father.
Mother.
Wait to see me defeat Hei Long.
Control the power and qi
in your body.
What's going on?
Didn't I die just now?
Shi Xing?
What's going on?
I can't see.
The mirror and all the rouge
you prepared for me
are just a waste.
Although you can't see,
I'm always by your side.
From now on, I'll do the makeup
and tailor clothes for you.
I'll marry you.
I want you to be my wife.
Is she the woman
Shi Xing has been asking about?
Shi Xing.
I like it when you call my name.
It makes me know how much you love me.
Call me again.
Call my name.
Your name…
Why can't I remember
your name?
My head hurts so much.
Who are you?
Shi Xing.
What's wrong with you?
I don't remember your name.
Who are you?
Shi Xing?
My head hurts so much.
It hurts so much.
Am I
in Shi Xing's memory?
Bai Cai.
Now, qi cultivation
is already in your body.
However, you still have a long way to go
before mastering it.
There are two types of qi in your body now.
Only by combining them
can you achieve something.
Back then, I failed to activate my divine power.
How come
I still have divine power in me?
I think
it might be left in your body
during the Divine Activation.
The two powers
in your body
are merging.
If you can't stay undisturbed,
divine power and qi cultivation
will get tangled up
and generate energy
that will seize this chance
to invade your consciousness
and make you lose your sanity.
Divine power can attack its owner?
Yes.
In this world, we know there is divine power,
qi cultivation,
and the soul power of the Demon Clan.
All these powers
may backfire.
The key to cultivation
is to cultivate your mind.
If you don't have a strong mind,
they'll definitely backfire.
In other words,
as long as our minds are strong enough,
we can utilize these powers?
You're right.
We should
strike a balance
with the power in our bodies
instead of owning it.
I understand.
Good.
Wu Geng.
Try to control it.
Wu Geng has entered the city.
[Liusha City]
There's a magical barrier up there.
Looks like it's hard to get out of here.
The whole city has been sealed.
The people in the city
have all become monsters.
During the day, they're trapped inside their houses
by the barrier and can't come out.
No wonder there's no one in the city.
Divine power is consumed very quickly here.
The monsters can't come out.
It should be safe here during the day.
Sir, will you please announce me?
I'm the Plague Immortal
from the six tribes of the Immortal Realm.
My name is Gui Mu.
I have something important
to report to Grand Elder Shen Yan.
Plague Immortal?
Doesn't High Priest Xinyue Kui
oversee all the affairs of the six tribes
of the Immortal Realm?
This is an important matter.
I must
meet Grand Elder Shen Yan
to tell him in person.
Please…
I'll go in to announce you.
Wait here.
Thank you.
Grand Elder.
Gui Mu has something important to report to you.
A deity from the six tribes of the Immortal Realm
has something important to report to me?
That's what Gui Mu said.
[Shen Yan]
Let him wait.
I'll meet him
when I have spare time.
Yes.
Uncle Ziyu.
I didn't know qi cultivation
was so incredible.
It's as amazing as divine power.
After you learn to control your qi,
you can improve
the sensitivity of the eyes of your heart.
Qi cultivation increases the power in your body.
The eyes of your heart
are the switch to control qi cultivation.
When the eyes of your heart are open,
you can change your qi
into the form
you want.
Control the qi in my body
and change qi cultivation
into the form I want?
You mastered the skills
of qi cultivation so quickly.
You're
a rare talent.
Uncle Ziyu.
Where did you learn
this amazing qi cultivation?
Illusion Island.
Illusion Island?
Yes.
It's an island
that doesn't belong to any of the three realms.
I'll take you there
when I have a chance.
Okay.
Stop worrying.
Even though Shi Xing
is a belligerent lunatic,
he's not interested
in a powerless girl
like Bai Cai.
He won't hurt her.
The showdown is tonight.
You need to get your body ready for combat
as soon as possible.
I know, Uncle Ziyu.
Tonight, I'll settle all scores, old and new,
with Shi Xing.
The divine power of the Asura Realm
can conceal the aura of a stranger.
In just one day,
you've become more skilled
than people who have practiced
for ten years.
Looks like you're ready.
You're very gifted.
You succeeded in one go.
Uncle Ziyu.
Let's go meet Shi Xing.
During the battle at the Xin capital,
my qi sword was badly damaged.
Over the years,
I've been trying to fix it,
but I'm not done yet.
Give me some time.
I hope I can make it in time.
Okay.
Uncle Ziyu.
Wait for me to come back.
Wu Geng.
Don't forget
the prisoners here
are all great cultivators
Shi Xing recruited from all over the world.
You want me
to set all of them free?
I didn't ask you to set them free.
I'm just saying
they're all great cultivators.
You mean,
when necessary,
I can use them
to stop Shi Xing.
Boy.
You're still so weak.
You must have come to fight me
with a death wish.
I'll grant your wish.
You're dead!
Lan.
You can cultivate very efficiently here,
but you'll also consume divine power
ten times faster than in the outside world.
You need to get some rest.
I'm just saying
they're all great cultivators.
You were all imprisoned here
by Shi Xing.
You're free now.
What's wrong with them?
Outside this place, there are numerous monsters
controlled by the Seal of the Dead.
They can't leave the city.
The Seal of the Dead
is on Shi Xing.
So the key is that guy?
Qi cultivation?
He's become stronger.
Boy.
It seems
that you've developed new skills.
Great.
Bring it on, then.
Spare no effort.
Try your best to kill me.
Bring it on.
It's time for a showdown.
Let's fight them!
Fight!
Yes. I'd rather die fighting
than keep living like this.
Let's fight them!
Yes. Let's fight!
What's going on?
It seems to be some ancient spell.
We must be careful.
The city governor is getting married today.
What a great day!
Are they under control?
City Governor. City Governor.
Let's go congratulate the city governor.
Let's go.
City Governor.
Congratulations, City Governor.
Congratulations. Congratulations.
Please.
Let's go take a look.
Congratulations, City Governor.
Let's go.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, City Governor.
Mingyue.
It's cold at night.
You don't have to wait for me here.
I…
I'm afraid I may miss the auspicious time.
Don't be afraid.
Although you can't see,
as I told you,
I'll never, ever,
leave you alone.
Bai Cai.
Gou.
Are you okay?
Did Shi Xing hurt you again?
Gou.
Have you seen all this?
They…
It seems they can't see us.
Is this another illusion?
It doesn't look like an illusion.
But we'd better be careful.
Come.
What a perfect match.
It's so lively here.
Shi Xing.
You're getting married today.
Why didn't you invite me and your master
to your wedding?
Xing.
Are we having a new guest?
Mingyue.
The Hell Immortal,
the son of the King of Immortals,
insists on marrying a human.
Is she the reason
why you've become weak?
Tian Kui, kill her.
I dare you!
Shi Xing.
You should thank the King of Immortals
for sparing your life.
Now, you should kill this human
and go back to the Immortal Realm to apologize to the King.
Shi Xing.
Are you going to be a traitor
like Fu Xi?
Humans are humans.
You can toy with them,
but
you can't fall in love with them.
As long as you let her go,
I'll go back to the Immortal Realm with you.
You can do whatever you want with me.
A bane is a bane, no matter what.
You're in no place to negotiate with me.
Xing.
Don't worry about me. Leave.
No, Mingyue.
I won't abandon you.
At worst,
we'll die together.
Mingyue!
Xing.
Xing, what happened?
What happened to you, Xing?
Xing.
Mingyue.
-Xing.
-Mingyue.
What happened to you?
Mingyue, I'm sorry.
Xing.
I'm sorry, Mingyue.
Xing, what happened to you?
Look.
What's that?
What's going on?
Xing.
Say something, Xing.
Xing, Xing.
What's wrong with you, Xing?
Xing.
Shi Xing.
This is the Seal of the Dead.
Grand Elder Shen Yan
gave it to me
to punish you.
The seal holder will lose all his  memories
and never die.
You'll become a beast
who only desires to kill.
Every time the seal opens,
you'll experience
the pain of losing the woman you love again.
There is no better punishment
than this endless cycle of pain.