It's a landslide victory for me.
If you're the real deal,
prove it with your skills.
Not bellowing that you're the best!
It's pathetic.
I haven't lost yet!
Come home early.
Your darling's waiting.
P' Payu!
Who the hell dropped food
bags in front of my house?
What’s going on?
Some idiot dropped food
bags and made such a mess.
And now I’ve got to clean up.
Rain!
Payu, what’s going on?
Rain.
Sky After Rain
What exactly is going on?
Rain’s not here.
What do you mean?
- I told you Rain’s not here!
- Calm down.
I got it.
What I’m saying is,
maybe Rain went home.
You kept him here for days.
Rain, where are you?
P’ Payu, help me! Help…
Remember me?
Stop!
Let me go!
I’m glad you remembered my voice.
If you don’t wanna die,
let my boyfriend go now!
Are you sure you wanna
use that tone with me?
What would you do if I accidentally
slash your boyfriend’s face?
What do you want?
What do I want?
I want you to come crawling to me.
Simple, just come alone.
And if you bring friends with you,
I’ll beat your boyfriend.
And if you fucking call the
police, I’ll beat your boyfriend.
You don’t want things to turn ugly, do you?
Don’t worry, just do as I say.
When all this is over, I guarantee
both you and your boyfriend won’t die.
Isn’t my offer tempting?
Send me the address.
Don’t come, P’ Payu!
I give you half an hour.
And you’d better keep in mind.
Just. You. Alone.
No! P’ Payu, don’t come!
You!
What did he say?
Abandoned building behind racetrack
Dammit!
Calm down.
How can I calm the fuck down?
Don’t you see that Rain’s
fallen into his hands?
Stay out of it.
I won’t waste my time here.
You know it’s a trap.
I know it’s a trap.
But Rain’s with that bastard.
I’ve got to help him.
He’s in this predicament because of me.
Don’t worry, he’s got no guts to kill me.
Just stay here.
Dammit.
- What the hell?
- Stop, you’re going too far!
Yeah, I thought you just
wanted us to beat someone up.
But this is kidnapping.
You think he’ll stay still
and let you beat him?
He humiliated me.
I’m gonna get back at him
You know what?
Leave me out of this.
- You’re chickening out?
- Yeah!
I don’t know if you feel it,
but Payu’s a scary man.
You’re gonna run away like Bas too?
What the fuck are you looking at?
Oh, can’t talk?
P’ Payu won’t lose to someone like you!
Without dirty tricks,
you can’t do anything to him!
Oh, even when you cheated,
you couldn’t even beat him.
Loser!
Hey, you’re gonna kill him!
I wanna see the look on your
face when Payu gets beaten up.
Protect your pretty face well.
When I’m done with Payu,
it’ll be your turn.
Bring it on!
Wanna slash my face?
Go ahead!
Chickenshit!
You...
Let me go!
Don't come alone, P' Payu.
A few cuts on my face won't kill me.
But don't do as he says.
Please don't.
Let me go!
I’m here!
Let my boyfriend go!
If I let him go now...
You won’t do as I say.
It’s okay, Rain.
It’ll be over soon.
We’ll go home together.
Your love makes me laugh my ass off.
But you two won’t be leaving anytime soon.
Kneel.
Don’t.
Hey.
Good!
Obedient like a tame dog.
That’s how I like it.
Next…
Stick you face to the floor.
P’ Payu, don’t!
Not there.
Crawl and kowtow at my feet.
Please stop!
I did as you said.
Now let my boyfriend go.
Don’t be impatient, dude.
Hey, don’t forget to take pictures.
Take a look, the consequence
of challenging me.
You called me a loser, huh?
You’re resisting?
Wanna see your boyfriend get hurt?
If you can’t satisfy me...
I’ll have my men screw
your boyfriend right here.
Good!
That’s more like it!
You arrogant bastard!
What’s wrong?
Why aren't you barking?
Hey, what the fuck!
Let me go!
Hey!
Stop it, don’t hurt him!
I said stop, you fucker!
Don’t you hurt him!
Let me go!
Don’t hurt him, huh?
I dare you to let me go!
A useless scum like you can’t defeat anyone
without cheating or using dirty tricks!
Let go of me, you coward!
- Let go!
- Coward?
Don’t touch my boyfriend.
Don’t touch your boyfriend?
P’ Payu!
P' Payu!
That’s enough.
Stop, don’t do it!
Let go!
Leave him alone!
I said, don’t touch my boyfriend!
Don’t hurt him!
Don’t!
Shut the hell up!
Let go!
That’s enough.
Let go! Let me go!
Let P’ Payu go!
- Let go!
- Leave him alone! Let go!
What the fuck are you standing there for?
Teach him a lesson!
I think you should stop.
P’ Payu.
P’ Payu, I’m sorry.
If I hadn’t been captured,
you wouldn’t have gotten hurt.
Why are you apologizing?
I’m the one who should apologize.
Come on, don’t cry.
I’m the reason you bowed
to him and got beaten up.
You could fight back,
but I was a hindrance to you.
Bowing is nothing...
As long as you're safe.
I’m sorry I was late.
Don’t blame yourself.
You’re just in time.
I should thank you instead.
Where’s Saifha?
Calm down.
How can I calm the fuck down?
Don’t you see that Rain’s
fallen into his hands?
Stay out of it.
I won’t waste my time here.
You know it’s a trap.
I know it’s a trap.
Abandoned building behind racetrack
But Rain’s with that bastard.
I’ve got to help him.
He’s in this predicament because of me.
Don’t worry, he’s got no guts to kill me.
Just stay here.
He’s standing by outside.
Let me go! I said let go!
I’ll tell your boss to fire all of you!
Don’t you know who my father is?
Yes, I know who your father is.
But I guess you don’t know
who Mr. Pakin’s subordinate is.
Payu’s the only one my boss allows
to touch every bike in his private garage.
And if his favorite mechanic
couldn’t work due to injured hands...
How do you think my boss would feel?
- So what? I…
- Oh.
And we also have our golden rule.
My boss will be very upset
if anyone publicizes the race.
One more thing.
I despise underhanded methods the most.
Get up!
I’d like to see how you’re
gonna fight me, a lackey.
Let’s go.
Just a minute.
This is for my boyfriend!
Bear this in mind.
P’ Payu’s the only one who can screw me.
Let’s go.
- Yes, got it.
- Does it hurt?
I’ll tell him.
A little.
P’ Chai said sorry.
He was supposed to deal with
Stop before any of this happened.
But he was busy with work.
And the bastard made a
move faster than he expected.
To be honest, I was terrified
just by hearing P’ Chai’s voice.
I guess he’s pissed
for being called a lackey.
With P’ Pakin’s permission, Stop
will have a much harder time than you.
You should get some rest.
You too, Rain.
Yes, P’ Saifha.
Come closer.
I don’t wanna bump into your wounds.
You should’ve been admitted to
the hospital like the doctor said.
Be careful with your arms.
It’s just a pinky finger fracture.
Rain.
When you kicked him for me
despite your fear of P’ Chai…
You made me fall in love with you again.
You've ever fallen in love with me?
I already confessed.
When?
When I sang for you.
No, that didn’t count.
You’re cheating.
You've never said it.
Neither have you.
Can you hear what my heart’s saying?
I won’t know if you don’t say it.
I love you, Rain.
Me too.
What do you mean?
Don’t cheat.
Then don’t tease me.
I love you too, P’ Payu.
It’s raining again.
Don’t you like it?
I do.
And I like ‘storm’ too.
Because whenever there’s
a storm, there’s always rain.
Guys, my gaming rank went
up a lot during summer break.
So idle.
What’s there to be happy about?
It’ll go down when school starts anyway.
Hey, don’t hurt my feelings.
I spent so much time playing.
As for me, I thought
I finally got a chance to relax.
But P’ Som asked me to
gather data for his thesis.
- That’s expected of P’ Som.
- He did it again.
- What about you, Sky?
- Yeah.
I returned to my home in Lopburi.
I would’ve stayed longer if it hadn’t
been for freshmen orientation meeting.
So I’ll be going home after the meeting
to spend more time with my dad.
'Cause I’ll be busy when school starts.
What about you, Mr. Cloud Jizz?
What did you do during summer break?
My name’s not Cloud Jizz.
My name is R-A-I-N, Rain.
I know you’re smart enough
to know the difference.
Don’t call me Cloud Jizz.
Guess he took extra English course.
His pronunciation’s on point.
Okay, Okay. Nong Fon. Nong Fon.
- Nong Fon, how was your summer break?
- My name’s not Fon.
Stop calling me Fon.
- He’s been clingy to his partner.
- What?
- Sky!
- He found himself a partner?
Someone as annoying as you?
Damn, I wonder who.
Sky, you know who his partner is, right?
- Sky, don’t tell them.
- 500 baht.
Sky.
- If I tell you the name…
- I’ll give you 1,000 baht.
You’ll know who it is.
- Shit.
- Who?
- Sky!
- I’m more curious now.
- Who?
- Stop talking.
Look! Nong Fon’s bangs
shifted from being shy.
His mouth’s droopy too.
So what’s the deal?
- Nong Fon.
- What?
- Spill the beans.
- What do you have to say for yourself?
Who is it, Sky? Tell me.
Oh, who’s calling you?
My mom.
Where are you going, Nong Fon.
Nosy.
- He said we’re nosy.
- It’s our fault?
The heck? We’re just worried.
How come it’s our fault?
He’s acting strange.
That must be his partner.
- Who is it?
- Or maybe a scammer call?
I received one yesterday.
Hello.
Is the meeting over?
Yes.
We’re eating at the restaurant
you recommended me.
Oh, my favorite place.
Yeah.
So why are you calling?
I miss you.
Send me your selfie.
Why?
Just for fun.
Are you feeling shy?
I’m not.
Don’t talk nonsense.
Just a sec.
You’re leaving, Ple?
No, I’m going to P’ Sert’s shop.
Do you want anything?
- You’re going alone?
- Yeah.
- Want me to accompany you?
- It’s okay, keep talking.
Where were we?
I’ll be there in 10 minutes.
See you at the restaurant.
Hey!
Shit, he’s really coming?
What am I gonna do?
- Let’s tease P’ Som.
- Sure.
P’ Som.
You always make Ple help you with work.
Can I help you too?
Shut the hell up, Sig!
- Why?
- I don’t wanna hear your voice.
What’s wrong with my voice?
Do you wanna hear my voice?
- Just shut up.
- P’ Som!
- I told you to shut up.
- No!
Enough, just shut the hell up.
- Don’t tease him.
- Stop teasing him.
- P’ Som’s cute.
- You like him?
A little.
Oh, P’ Payu.
Oh, P’ Payu’s here.
- Hello.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
- How are you?
Why’s he here?
How would I know?
Maybe he's here for you?
So handsome.
I've been doing fine.
You really wanna sit here?
My seat’s here.
Aren’t you gonna claim your ownership?
Why would I do that?
Suit yourself.
Don’t say I didn’t warn you.
'Cause judging from the brother's eyes...
And the sister's...
P' Payu is indeed popular.
Are you really my friend?
What else could I be?
This is also your friend,
your friend, and your friend.
- Your friends are my friends.
- Yeah.
- Guys!
- P’ Payu.
May I sit with you guys?
- Be my guest.
- Please do.
Dust the seat, Rain.
Sawasdee ka, P’ Payu.
Do you remember me?
We met last time when
you came to find Rain.
Of course.
So what are you doing here?
Is it about the freshmen orientation?
No, I’m here to pick up my partner.
What?
You’re in a relationship?
With who?
Shhh, it’s a secret.
- Another secret?
- So many secrets today.
I’m going home.
- What?
- That's so sudden, Rain.
Oh?
Where are you going, P’ Payu?
You haven’t answered my question.
I’m going home.
I told you I’m here to pick up my partner.
- Huh?
- Who?
My boyfriend’s going home,
so I’m leaving too.
- Damn.
- Right, Rain?
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Sig, didn’t you ask who my partner is?
Yes.
Let’s go home, P’ Payu.
Oh my god!!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Is it true?
P’ Payu and Rain are dating?
Impossible!
It’s possible.
It’s already happening.
I can’t believe it.
Our friend’s become cocky after
he’s dating the department’s god.
- Yeah.
- Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Did you see the look on P’ Som’s face?
He was flabbergasted.
Do you still like Ple?
Are you…
Jealous?
Furiously jealous.
Didn’t you see the way she looked at you?
Come on, she doesn’t like me.
I don’t care how that girl looked at me.
All I care about is how
my boyfriend looks at me.
So do you see how your
boyfriend’s looking at you?
For your information.
I never look at other people...
The way I look at you.
Okay.
Then I won’t punish you today.
I won’t cheat on you.
But if you cheat on me, I’ll storm
to the garage to unleash my wrath.
Then there’s no reason for me to be afraid.
'Cause I'll never let you down.
Never.
Let’s go home, P’ Payu.
Let’s…
Do something fun.
After it rained continuously
for the past week…
The sky is clearing up.
While a wind coming from the east…
Good morning, my babies.
Oh, a new shoot.
Let’s hang the laundry.
So much dust.
Has Dad ever cleaned up?
Should I find him a girlfriend?
If he’s got a girlfriend,
I won’t have to clean up.
Tomorrow, you have a meeting at 10 a.m.
And a meeting with
shareholders in the afternoon.
I already sent related
materials to your email.
And this file…
Cancel the 10 a.m. meeting for me.
I just remembered that I’m busy.
But Mr. Pai…
Don’t worry, I’ll be in time
for the afternoon meeting.
It can’t be canceled, Mr. Pai.
I know it’s important.
I can’t afford to have my
father fire me anytime soon.
Thank you.
Sky!
Are you okay?
I told you I’d do it myself.
Look, it's summer break.
You should be resting up.
Come on, Dad.
It’s not a big deal.
I do everything by myself
when I’m at the dorm.
It’s especially because I’m on
summer break that you need to rest up.
Please let me help.
How stubborn.
Alright, I’ll get back to work.
I can’t carry them all.
Help me carry the rest.
I knew it.
Now I can rest easy after
seeing him smile again.
Sky, I’ll make lunch to show
off my great cooking skills.
No, I don’t wanna eat burnt fried eggs!
What are you doing here?
Visiting my friend.
I heard you got beaten up.
It’s been weeks after the incident.
And I’m planning to spend
my leave with my darling.
You’re such a heartless friend.
I went out of my way to visit you.
Now that you’ve seen me, get out.
I’ve just arrived.
Not a single glass of water
to welcome your guest.
- I’ll go get it.
- Stop.
If he’s capable of driving here,
then he can buy himself a drink.
Am I right?
Okay, I’ll get to the point.
Yes?
Last time you were chased by the
guards, you came with a friend, right?
What's his name?
Oh, Sky.
You mean Sky?
Can I have his number?
I got him out of the venue that day.
And he forgot to take his stuff back.
I wanna return it.
That’s why I’m asking you his number.
You can give the thing to me.
I wanna return it myself.
If you don’t give me his number...
I won’t leave.
Sky, I’m sorry. I’ll help you to finish all works
when the semester starts.
Okay.
Thanks for a warm welcome to this guest.
I’m leaving.
P’ Payu, I gave him my friend’s number.
What do I do?
Judging from his expression,
it’s too late to save your friend now.
A cunning expression like yours?
Wanna see that expression on my face?
A water for you.
Here.
- Thanks, son.
- Sure.
- Eat.
- Okay.
Try this, Dad.
Fried Chinese sausages.
Are they burnt?
They’re crispy, Dad. Crispy.
I fried them myself.
- Really?
- Yeah!
You’re not picking up?
I don’t recognize the number.
Maybe it’s a scammer call.
What if I get scammed?
Let’s eat.
By the way, when will
you return to the dorm?
The day after tomorrow.
Pay attention to your studies.
But don’t push yourself too hard.
You don’t need to worry.
Your son is smart.
I can do it, don’t worry.
Showoff.
- Here, try this stewed egg.
- Thank you.
Oh, there’s one left.
This one’s for you.
One for you and one for me.
Here.
You’re trying to please
me to get something?
No!
- Really?
- Yeah.
Let’s eat.
Ignore it, Dad.
He’s not picking up.
It’s okay, there’s still time.
I’m not the type to give up easily anyway.
You’re the one who tampered
with my car at the frat dinner?
Yeah.
I was attracted to the boy
who held an umbrella for me.
So I had to find a way to approach him.
Right?
But your car was due for a checkup too.
You remembered me from the start?
Rather, I like you from the start.
Ever since you held the umbrella for me,
I’d been thinking that if we met again...
I’d make a move on you.
After that, a senior sent
your photo in the group chat.
That's how I found out before the dinner
party that you’re in the same frat group.
But you never pursued me.
That’s my way of pursuing you.
By making me pursue you instead?
So that you’d wanna get to know me better.
Besides…
I enjoy teasing the person I like.
How am I dating someone like you?
You won’t love me after learning the truth?
No.
'Cause I already love you.
What else can I do?
I’ll let you tease me
for the rest of our lives.
Then you’d better be prepared.
English Subtitle by Saowalak K.
- He's my boy.
- I don't have to stay.
At least leave me your number.
They're all assholes.
Hello, P' Pai.
This is P' Pai, P' Payu's best friend.
I'll go back with P' Pai.