Ji Sung
Kim Min Jung
Jin Young
Park Gyu Young
NO JUSTICE
Moon Yu Seok
The Devil Judge
This is a virtual dystopia (imaginary society with great injustice) set in Korea.  All characters, organizations, events, etc. are fictional.
Timing and Subtitles by the Devil's Minions @ viki
♫  I've been seeing all. I've been seeing your soul.  ♫
SEOUL
♫  Give me things that I wanted to know. Tell me things that you've done.  ♫
♫  I've been feeling old. I've been feeling cold.  ♫
♫  You're the heat that I know. See, you are my sun.   ♫
Two years, two years everyone!
While this unprecedented terrible plague that I don't even want to think about
swept the country for two years, businesses were ruined
and people took to the streets.
Out of the blue, due to provocation against the wealthy,
arson, terror were ultimately incited, yes!
The Gwanghwamun Riot!
And the economic crisis. All these are now a thing of the past.
Let's forget all about it now. I will change everything.
We have finally, finally, managed to overcome this plague we're all sick and tired of!
Guarantee my right to live
Social Responsibility Foundation
Incoming Donations
Seo Jeong Hak, Board Chairman of the Social Responsibility Foundation
Cha Gyeong Hui, Minister of Justice
Min Yong Sik
Head of the Inbo Group
Park Du Man, Saram Media Chairman
Utopia
♫  In the sunlight  ♫
I will make new jobs again!
As the person chosen by the beloved people of Korea,
I, Heo Jung Se, will make sure to turn this Republic of Korea
back into the grand country it was before!
President of Korea Heo Jung Se
I swear it on my life!
He can't overcome his habit of overreacting when he is being filmed, Sir.
Where would an out of work clown go?
To restore this country, we need to fix the laws first.
The powerful and revolutionary justice plan I had passed will begin to be applied now.
For the first time in history, the entire country will be on the jury.
The 2lst century's famous Pocheongcheon, ( A judge in the Song Dynasty of China )
Judge Kang Yo Han
will show you all a proper trial here that you wanted so earnestly.
I did it.  I, Heo Jung Se, did it!
Total Change in Korea.
♫  Born in a warped I came here, whoa  ♫
♫  That's when I met you  ♫
Hello.  I am Kang Yo Han.
Live Court Show
Judge Kang, what do you think about the controversy over the constitutionality of this type of trial?
What about the criticism that it is just an anti-civil rights show.
Judge Kang is expected to be too punitive.
We have a concern that you lack consideration toward the socially disadvantaged.
- Who are the socially disadvantaged?
- Pardon?
Which of the defendants I tried was socially disadvantaged?
Umm, there was a juvenile offender. A homeless person. An impoverished mentally ill person.
Are the rapist of a classmate,  happyslapping thief,  and an outrageous murderer, socially disadvantaged?
(Happy slapping-- random assault to film to post on social media)
- Nevertheless, to some degree, weren't they socially disadvantaged—
- They are just defendants.
I have no interest on whether someone is advantaged or disadvantaged.
So  can you punish severely even the defendant in this live court show trial?
Chairman Ju Il Do is notorious for his powerful connections.
JU Chemical chairman Ju Il Do
When the pressure comes down from over that cloud, —
I am the authority.
I, I, I! I am the authority.
As delegated by the people who are the sovereign of this country, the Republic of Korea,
I exercise my jurisdiction.
Who is above the people?
The people, everyone, are the power.
I'll see you in court.
He's good.
I agree.
Congratulations, our star judge.
Shall we have one also?
To sexy power.
Devil Judge
Episode 1
As delegated by the people who are the sovereign of this country, the Republic of Korea,
I exercise my jurisdiction.
Who is above the people? The people, everyone, are the power.
- Wait.
- Wait a moment.
What brings you here?
I am on duty as of today.
Kim Ga On
Oh, you are a judge on the Live Court Show. Go on in.
Yes?
Professor.
I'm sorry, Supreme Court Justice.  I'm still not familiar with addressing you with this title.
Supreme Court Justice? My butt. Cut it out, you kid.
Wow, this is cool.
It's like a temple.
It is a temple.
It's Justice's temple.
Is this the court?
The trials which will be broadcast live.
Why is Judge Kang Yo Han stacking the deck like this?
Judge? You can't call him a judge.
He's the flagbearer of reform to change a corrupt judiciary.
The hope  which has appeared in Joseon's crumbling hell.
They say he is enormously popular.
A monster always appears during a crisis.
The ridiculous laws which he got enacted
were not the brain child of a jurist but that of a politician.
You dislike it so much, yet you appointed me to this court.
Someone needs to be there.
Someone has to be vigilant and keep their eyes wide open even in this insane wind.
There is no one here trying to resist this wind.
Are you ordering me to play the role of Judas Iscariot?
It's a request.  Do you remember what I always said in class?
I do.
Easy justice does not exist in the human world.
Kang Yo Han, Chief Judge of the Live Court Show
It's nice to meet you.
What's wrong?
It's nothing, sorry. You said you were Judge Kim Ga On, correct?
- Yes, please take good care of me—
- Welcome.
For coming to the war zone.
[Restaurant's Owners, Husband and Wife Defrauded By Swindler Were Found Dead
Personal Record
Name: Kim Ga On
They look alike. More than I thought.
Live Court, Associate Judge: Oh Jin Ju
Live Court, Associate Judge Kim Ga On
Oh, Judge Kim Ga On?
Nice to meet you. I'm Oh Jin Ju.
Nice to meet you, Judge.
It's a bit unorganized, isn't it? I came from far away so I have a lot of belongings.
It's all right. But ... are you going to sleep here?
No. Not every day.
It's like ... the basics of working life? Working hard in the beginning and getting noticed.
Right.
- Judge Kim, it's your first working and it's in Seoul, right?
- Yes.
After I became a judge, I was only assigned to work in the countryside, so this is my first time working in Seoul.
Honestly speaking, an opportunity like this doesn't come often.
What's the matter? Are you an introvert?
No, of course not. Please take good care of me.
You seem different when you smile.
Now I get what criteria the trial court used for selecting judges.
When you say criteria, you mean ...
If I had to put it into words, it would be the image.
But is that related to the tasks that a judge has to do?
Of course. Think about it. We are the trial court in front of the citizens of this country.
But people prefer to hear the words of someone they like instead of someone who tells the truth.
Charm is power.
Power?
Don't pay attention to me. Don't take it to heart. I'm just in a good mood right now,
so words emerge without thinking.
Honestly, I'm a fan of Chief Judge Kang Yo Han.
Just my coming here made me hailed with blessings as a fan.
You've succeeded, Oh Jin Ju! Let's work hard.
Did you reconsider choosing JU Chemical Chairman Ju Il Do's case first?
That case is the most suitable.
There are plenty of simple and easy cases, why go through the hassle?
It's not complicated. We'll just do according to the law.
- The best law firms in South Korea will be called in to help.
- Of course.
You know that trust in the judicial system fell to 10%, right?
Yes.
Cases like this where the emotions of the public and the conclusion reached by the court can easily differ,
- are very difficult, so is there a need to do it so publicly—
- Chief Justice.
The Live Court show is not a kangaroo court*.
(unofficial court held by a group of people in order to try someone regarded, especially without good evidence, as guilty)
It's just a transparent court. In front of all the citizens.
I'm satisfied with that.
I'll get going first.
All right, see you tomorrow.
We will cross now. Raise your right hands! That's right, stick to this side.
You bastards!
Be ready to shoot.
A bus is speeding towards the front entrance 200 meters away.
The driver's identity is unknown. Please let me know how we should proceed.
Kids, run quickly!
Are you okay?
The guns were provided in order to be used.
I'm sorry, Judge.
What are you looking at?  Stay back!
Are you all right, sir?
Someone is hurt.  He needs to go to the hospital!  Hospital!
Punish Chairman Ju Il Do!
This morning in front of the Supreme Court, there was an explosion of a preschool bus.
The arrest warrant for Ju Il Do, the chairman of JU Chemical, was rejected.
angering the driver of the preschool bus
- who sped towards the Supreme Court.
- What is this? Was it because Chairman Ju Il Do's warrant was rejected?
It's just a challenge against government authority.
If I may, isn't it a scream of anguish rather than a challenge?
What do you mean by scream?
When you corner and trap a rat and starve it, it will struggles and bang its head on the wall.
Would a human being be any different?
Master Seo,  it's an issue regarding life or death. The foundation needs to help.
We were able to control the epidemic, but there are so many unemployed people that we have nobody to collect tax from.
If the drought lasts for a long time, there will be riots.
- Chairman Park.
- Yes?
Preparations for the live court are going well, right?
Yes, don't worry. It'll be a big day.
You must prepare well.
Our Minister Cha has special interest in the case, due to personal circumstances.
Welfare for the needy
The loan of luck - We guarantee complete confidentiality.
Are you trying to grow a jungle?
Hi.
I heard there was a terrorist attack in front of the Supreme Court.
You already know about this? As expected of Inspector Yun Su Hyeon of the MIU.  (MIU: Metropolitan Investigation Unit)
You didn't get hurt, right? Don't tell me you acted recklessly again.
Stop it. Don't worry. I was so scared I hid far at the back. As a man should.
Good job. You've finally matured. Let's go upstairs now.
Go ahead. I'll finish with this one first.
Come on, stop this and come up.
- Why are you getting angry?
- Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Clink.
Won't you treat me to dinner?
- Why should I?
- I heard you'll be on TV.
But if you become a star like Kang Yo Han, it'll be difficult to see you in the future.
Being a star sounds nice.
Why are you being sarcastic?
Clink. Just drink your beer.
You've got nothing to lose being with a star like Kang Yo Han. He has a story.
The heir to an enormous wealth, and the survivor of a tragic accident...
People go crazy over these things.
True. His story is completely different from mine.
What's wrong with yours?
Hey, now that you've become a judge after all that hard work, you should move to a better neighborhood.
- What's wrong with this place?
- It's changed so much.
Compared to before.
This is the only place now.
For what?
To remember my parents.
- I'll make you food. Eat before you go.
- Food?
You've lost weight. You've been starving yourself again, I'm sure.
If you act this way, I might end up confessing to you again.
Even if I've been rejected five times since I was a kid, I figured it's not over until it's over.
- I don't want to loose my childhood friend. Have dinner before you go. You're done with this, right?
- Yes.
Heartless jerk.
I love you!
The key point is to deny that Chairman Ju Il Do knew anything about the details of the company's discharge.
We argue it was a  force majeure  event.
( an event beyond anyone's control. )
If the people's vote goes toward the panel during the trial, what should our contractors do?
We'll have to emphasize that the sewage treatment facility was damaged because the hill's embankment collapsed.
That it was bound to happen due to the city's negligent management.
Chairman.
Attorney Go, hello.
Look at this. Isn't the public making too much noise?
Ungrateful things.
Thousands of those dregs of society are able to scrounge for food today thanks to me.
Anyway in environmental accidents like this one there can never be indisputable evidence,
How can we expect the business owner to know about his factory's wastewater composition?
We'll plead innocent, and even in the worst case, you'll be charged with death and injury by occupational negligence.
Death and injury by occupational negligence...
What is the sentence for that?
- The maximum penalty is five years.
- Five years?
Well, they did make a special law and other things this time,
but the court is so conservative, they won't be able to increase the sentence like that so suddenly.
Don't you know that I can't sleep if my bed doesn't properly support my back?
Chairman. If you spend just one year reading and meditating,
I'll get you out on parole.
You will even be coming out healthier.
You are sure of that, right?
If you are so anxious about this,
just remember that person is there.
You're right.
Chief.
Thank you for saving me yesterday.
- Don't mention it.
- You shot without hesitation.
Did I?
Were you thinking of killing the driver?
- If there was the need to.
- The need, you say?
It was likely the bus would have kept going straight ahead even if the driver had died instantly.
So you shot to make him turn the steering wheel instinctively.
So that he would be the only one to die if he crashed.
Isn't that basic arithmetic? One is a lesser number than two.
That's right.
How was meeting Kang Yo Han?
I'm not sure.
I survived thanks to you.
You're welcome.
I guess I shouldn't become the lesser number when you are involved, Chief.
Don't do that, then.
Why do you think Kang Yo Han chose Chairman Ju Il Do as his first defendant for the live court?
Isn't it because it's the case that's gaining the most attention from the public lately?
That's true. That's right.
But Chairman Ju Il Do is one of the largest donors of the Social Responsibility Foundation.
And Kang Yo Han's judicial reform
was possible because Minister of Justice Cha Gyeong Hui and the Social Responsibility Foundation supported it.
So he should have avoided that case because it puts him in an awkward position, but instead he insisted on taking it?
I'm wondering if he might have an ulterior motive.
Chief Kang. Regarding the preschool bus driver from yesterday,
what about indicting him without detention for now, and putting him through a trial later?
Why do you want to do so?
The live court is just around the corner.
Is there really a need to receive the public's attention over this shameful matter now?
There's the issue of what you did yesterday as well. First impressions are important, don't you think?
Are you asking me to show compassion toward a terrorist?
It's not about compassion, but about appearance.
In that case, there's nothing bad about it.
The noisier it gets, the more attention it'll garner. We're making noise marketing here.
For a case like this, imprisoning him is the fair thing to do.
Excuse me... May I say something?
The three-year-old daughter of that bus driver is one of the dead victims of the JU Chemical accident.
And her grandmother killed herself over the matter.
So?
I am a little concerned that rejecting Chairman Ju Il Do's arrest warrant while imprisoning the bus driver
might not be fair.
Judge Kim.
Ju Il Do is a defendant whose trial is to decide whether he is guilty or not, while the bus driver was caught in the act.
Don't you know that much?
But shouldn't we take motive into consideration—
Do you think you obtain the right to harm others if you're a victim yourself?
That's not what I mean, but he is injured and—
There is a doctor at the detention center too.
Let's go by the rules.
Yu, the child who had been hospitalized following JU Chemical's waste water discharge accident, died.
In a tragic turn of events, the grandmother took her own life.
With this, the number of deaths due to this accident reaches eleven.
Including the ones undergoing treatment, the total number of victims is no less than forty-seven.
Investigation is underway to uncover the full story of the incident,
and Chairman Ju Il Do's trial will later—
Sorry. It's a bit difficult to watch.
It reminds me of where I used to live. I'm a country girl, you see.
Even though I don't look like it.
And I'm from Seoul. As you can see.
From the slums, right?
- Is that obvious?
- Yes.
I guess people who came from poor backgrounds have a way of recognizing each other.
Like a kind of radar?
Then what do you see from Chief Kang?
Our chief Kang?
I'm not sure...
You can do it! Go for it, Oh Jin Ju!!!
I don't see anything.
Fundamentals of your work life:
useless curiosity toward your superior is forbidden.
- Let's get to work.
- Yes.
We have the trial statute. Have a read through it.
- The trial statute?
- Yes.
The trial statute of our live court.
It might make you a bit angry.
You like to play with numbers very much, don't you?
When the viewers press the smartphone's app button, then let's judge after looking at the numbers.
Do you call it playing with numbers? I call it democracy.
If you're going to do such democratic trials, then why do you need us?
- I think you've read the trial statute.
- Is that a trial?
No matter how many opinions the associate judges give,  you'll make the final decisions based on the number of votes,
so why do you really need us?
It's necessary to have emergency measures during an emergency time.
And ... the pictures won't look good.
Pictures?
If there is nothing at my left and right sides, the pictures will feel empty. It's a broadcast after all.
It's me. I need you to do something.
- What is it?
-  Find me a spare key for the supreme court record storage room.
You punk, do you think it's easy to get that?
If you can't even do such a small thing, I recommend you quit being a supreme court justice.
Hello?
Who dragged me here...?
You'll go to jail if you damage the records.
I won't tell about my accomplice, Supreme Court Justice.
I found it.
The actual case.
You punk chokes me up! So you searched for the 20-year-old records?
Isn't the love even for the first love the most ardent?
The first love?
When Chairman Ju Il Do expanded his business for the first time and got into trouble,
the person who let him off was an élite prosecutor from Seoul, Prosecutor Cha Gyeong Hui.
Whenever the incident was worth forgetting, she let him off the hook, and she did that three times - so he never got a citation.
Of course, she didn't do it for free, did she?
When Cha Gyeong Hui ran for assemblywoman for the first time,
which chairman supported her?
Ju Il Do?
To summarize ...
Ju Il Do was the sponsor of Justice Minister Cha Gyeong Hui at the time when she was a prosecutor.
Cha Gyeong Hui has power and influence and has been supporting Kang Yo Han all this time.
Now Kang Yo Han insists on taking Ju Il Do's trial.
And Cha Gyeong Hui is just watching, without any objection to it.
Is this trial for revealing his crime?
Or the opposite?
The problem is that all these theories are just presumption.
I should dig into it, no matter what.
It seems I'm blocking my future with my own hands,
but it's too late to go back.
It is an ardent first love ...
Is Su Hyeon doing well?
Yes, Ga On. It's okay. Tell me.
Wiretapping device? Why do you need it?
Stay quiet!
Hold on. I'll call you back.
Stop it!
Police!
Stay back!
Save me.
- She is my kid sister.
- Go to the wall.
I told you she is my kid sister.
Are you all right?
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm a policewoman.
Save me.
Minister, Director Jeong Seon Ah from the Social Responsibility Foundation (SRF) is here.
- Let her in.
- Yes.
Hello, Minister. I'm here on an errand from Mr. Seo.
What brings you here?
Excuse me. May I have a seat then tell you?
Thank you.
Both Mr. Seo as well as our foundation supporters
are worried a lot about this trial.
What are they worried about?
I'm sorry for saying it this way but let me be direct.
Let's catch these petty criminals so the citizens can release their anger.
Isn't that the reason we're holding this mock trial?
So?
So is it really necessary to put a businessman on trial?
If even a moderate sentence is the result, it would set a bad precedent for businessmen.
That's what they're worried about.
- Have you ever seen Kang Yo Han make a mistake?
- I haven't,
but they think it might be better if you choose an easier case for the first trial.
Why are you so adamant on this case?
Did you say I'm being adamant?
I'm sorry, I'm just the messenger.
Why are the people in the business of social welfare,
or rather, to be more exact, the alliance of the wealthy,
so invested in how the country is being run?
I'm pretty sure I said I would take care of it.
How arrogant.
I'm sorry, Minister Cha.
I've overstepped my boundaries.
May I dare say one more thing that is beyond my boundary?
Did you know that your chair and the desk you sit behind,
the painting on the wall, and even the car you commute with
were all paid for by our foundation.
That's because the ministry's budget came up short this year.
Right now, there aren't enough prisons, so we might have to build a private one ourselves.
I'm curious, Minister.
Who exactly
is serving this country?
What is it?
Why would a judge need a wiretapper?
Do you have a girlfriend who's cheating on you?
If that's easier for you to believe, then let's go with that.
- I can understand it, but I can't forgive it.
- Even if you can't, let's just go with that.
Quit joking around. What are you going to use it for?
You'll get hurt if you try to know too much.
It's not even one or two times you've been so obstinate.
- Let's test it. Go on the roof.
- The roof?
Wear this before you go.
What are looking at? Don't you know how to do it yourself? Just go.
No police brutality for citizens, Detective.
Can you hear me, Judge Kim?
Will you marry me? No, I'm just joking.
I love you.
She has a nice voice.
Did you hear it well?
- Very clearly.
- What's your answer?
Normally, you're not supposed to show that you heard.
So you're not going to answer?
Fine. Go catch your cheating girlfriend.
Hey, I just got called in. I'll call you later.
Again?
See you later.
Take care.
Will you marry me? No, I'm just joking.
I love you.
Hey.
Thank you.
Judge Kim?
Chief Judge, you're early.
The trial is right around the corner.
So what brought you here?
The library is closed.
Without turning the light on?
I have good night vision.
Then...
What?
- I heard you live alone.
- Yes.
It must be hard.
Your shirt is so wrinkled.
It's hard to find time to iron.
Right.
Keep up the good work.
He is an interesting guy.
Dead: 11/ Injured:36
Associate Judge: Kim Ga On
Yes, Minister of Justice.
Judge Kang. Regarding the trial,
I trust you, Judge Kang.
Don't worry, Minister. Everything will be done according to the law.
I don't think the public is that stupid.
It's me. Everything is ready, right?
You met Doctor, right? So what did you say?
It turned out well. You worked hard.
I'll meet the attorney today.
He's Ju Il Do's attorney.
- What name is your reservation under?
- Kang Yo Han.
Just before the trial, the judge met the defendant's attorney.
He spoke on the phone with the minister of justice who seems to be on his side.
And who is "Doctor"?
He's suspicious,  but we can't prove anything with this.
You know that, right? He could make an excuse that meeting his attorney was to discuss the procedure.
And all he said to the minister of justice was everything would be done according to the law.
The trial will be held just tomorrow.
I'm just going to watch him carefully with eyes wide open in court.
To bring facilities related to new technology such as electricity charging stations into the city,
we need to improve the building structures, use a classification system and share the information of architectural drawings.
We also need to reject the construction of high-rise buildings and promote Building Information Modeling
the building information modeling roadmaps.
By utilizing the construction information through these roadmaps—
Ah yes. Continue please.
I have something I absolutely have to watch today.
Shall we watch our Judge Kang Yo Han's skills?
Father, please forgive them.
They know not what they're doing.
Now 30 seconds left!
- When I say "three, two", get ready.
- Yes.
Now the sound check!
It's very exciting in itself that the general public can participate in the trial.
And I think it's very nice that the public opinions come together as one.
If people commit a crime, getting punished for their crime is a natural course.
They would get voted on equally by the public, regardless of whether they're rich or not.
Now I think we're going to watch proper trials.
- I trust you.
The first trial in the Live Court  show will open today.
Trust in the judiciary is very low, so can the Live Court Show change this current reality?
While the public is waiting for the first trial, full of hope  that everybody is equal before the law,
it's interesting to see whether Judge Kang Yo Han and his  Live Court Show will fulfill these expectations.
Hello, everyone.
This is a live broadcast from the supreme court at this historical moment!
The live court with public participation is waiting for you, for the first time in judicial history.
The method of participation is simple.
As you see, after you install the Goddess of Justice application,
- if you touch Goddess of justice, you can see the progressing trial.
- Mom!
- Yes, Gyu Min. Come here and stay quiet.
-  And you can see two buttons below.
While watching the trial,
if you think the defendant should get punished,
press the red button. But if you don't think so, then press the other one.
Your opinions will be collected, graphed, and brought to this court right away.
The court will judge, seeing the public's opinions in real time.
I introduce the judge who presides at today's trial, Kang Yo Han!
Dear citizens! Now, the Live Court Show begins.
There will no longer be a court held only among the élite, those who turn a blind eye to the public's common sense.
I'll open every step of trial to the public, make it transparent, and listen to your opinions.
I'll render judgment according to the law, but I won't turn a blind eye to the people's will.
The owners of this court are you who are sovereign.
Ready, ready.
Let's meet together the case we are dealing with today.
Prosecutor, please explain it.
There is a village where all young people left.
The population of this village is 47 people. Their average age is 72 years.
Among them, 11 people died and 23 people are still in the intensive care units.
Thirteen people were discharged but are suffering breathing difficulties, neuropathy, and many severe side effects.
One of the dead was only 3 years old and another is her grandmother.
After she lost her precious granddaughter whom her daughter working in Seoul entrusted to her,
she strangled herself.
Her granddaughter was the only child in this village.
The culprit of this tragedy is sitting right there.
JU Chemicals Factory 4, that the defendant operates is only 5 kilometers away from this village.
From such a place, they released untreated toxic chemicals into the river.
The water that the village residents use for drinking, washing themselves and  their clothes, and for farming!
Ladies and Gentlemen!
This is a murder!
- What? Already?  Hey, broadcast! Broadcast!
- Yes.
I listened to the prosecutor's statement carefully.
Speaking exactly, it's not a statement but an inciting speech. I enjoyed hearing that.
Watch what you're saying!
We just saw the riskiness of the media court clearly.
A trial is not a movie. I's not a show either.
A trial is the process where something is proved only with objective evidence.
Just now, he said it's a murder.
What kind of crazy businessman would deliberately murder the residents?
As long as he released the toxic chemicals into the stream even though he knew it could kill people,
it's a murder by willful negligence.
Here, would you look at these?
As you see, the embankment collapsed at the hill behind the factory so the treatment facility got damaged.
Prosecutor, during my studies, I learned that the local government is responsible of managing the embankments.
I'm not sure if my memory is correct.
It's true that some toxic chemicals were discharged.
However, since we immediately stopped running the factory and did emergency repair,
the duration of toxic discharge was less than one hour.
Your Honor.
What could we do more than this?
This was beyond our control.
Hadn't there been discharge due to old equipment before that?
Do you have evidence?
Under the pretext of emergency repair, you replaced or scrapped all the problematic equipment.
Are you asking if I have evidence?
You mean you don't have evidence.  I understand.
The only proven fact is a discharge for a short time due to uncontrollable accident.
There is no evidence regarding the situation before that.
According to the forensic institute's presumption, a tragedy of that size couldn't happen because of a spill for only one hour—
Presumption? I think I heard wrong just now.
Is presumption an objective proof?
It's right!
Without any proof, how can you accuse this patriotic businessman of murder?
Do you know how many people can live in this economic crisis thanks to me?
Our JU Chemicals has as many as 17,400 employees.
If you add their families and affiliates,
it's over 100,000 people who depend on us for their livelihood.
- With this kind of public trial—
- Watch what you say, Defendant!
I also have a right to speak up!
Defendant!
Why doesn't he say anything? Why does he act like that?
Damn it. Broadcasting accident! Hey, get ready for advertisement!
- Defense Attorney, please return to your seat.
- Yes.
Wait! H-Hold on.
Defendant.
- Yes.
- Have a seat, please.
Y-yes.
Defense Attorney, have you finished your statement?
Yes, that's it.
Then, the court is adjourned for a moment and will continue later. You may go to the bathroom.
Judge, may I ask a question?
Go ahead.
The embankment collapse accident you mentioned earlier ---
The collapse happened the very night after the first death occurred.
Is it correct?
Yes, it's correct.
It seems it was quite a coincidence, doesn't it?
As soon as the death occurred,
how could such an accident happen and all evidence be gotten rid of?
I'm sorry, Judge, but the cause of the first death wasn't clear.
So it's our position that it had nothing to do with this incident.
According to the medical report, the victim showed  symptoms such as dizziness, headaches, convulsion, unconsciousness
that aren't different from the symptoms of other victims.
That was just an assumption. An autopsy wasn't even performed on the body.
There is no proof that the toxic chemicals were detected in him at all, Your Honor.
- Your Honor.
- Go ahead.
In order to hear an objective opinion, I would like to call the leading expert in heavy metal poisoning,
Dr. Yu Jung Baek, to the stand.
All right, go ahead.
Everything's ready, right? Did you meet the doctor?
First of all, thank you for making time in your busy schedule to come.
Not at all.
A sample of river water, ah, there it is.
Did you analyze it?  Did you form an opinion as an expert?
Some of the victims have signs of heavy metal poisoning.
There is a lot, but I'm somewhat concerned whether the reason was wastewater runoff.
Although it's easy to think of leaking from heavy metals
used  in a certain environment such as a factory, in reality, it's not so.
It exists in everyday life, wherever we live.
Food ingredients are raised on contaminated land.  Well ...
don't we always encounter chemicals in cosmetics?
Particularly, this region is the very first place
to be affected by fine dust containing heavy metals.
It's an agricultural area, so the impact of chemical herbicides and fertilizers is severe.
Guilty 53% Innocent 47%.
Compared to all that, the concentration of pollutants mixed into the river was very low.
I doubt it.
- Let me ask you a question.
- Yes.
- You just said "this low concentration of pollutants in the river."
What is the specific pollutant?
There was a mixture of chemicals.
Among them, which was the worst you detected?
That would be ... it's called potassium cyanide.
Can you make it easier for me to understand?
What is the common name for potassium cyanide?
Doctor?
Its name is cyanide.
Cyanide!
Seven, seven, seven.
Even though JU Chemical Chairman Ju Il Do knew of the discharge of cyanide, he did nothing.
The word may sound frightening but
isn't the chemical cyanide very common in nature?
Yes, I know. It's very common.
It's in almonds, apple seeds, apricot kernels, cherry pits,  and gingko nuts. It's also in peach stones.
It's not unconditionally dangerous.  It's the concentration.
The concentration is the problem.
There was a village in the immediate vicinity where most of the residents were elderly.
Even so, wouldn't the concentration detected really be zero?
- I am sorry but, your honors—
- Umm. Your Honor.
Although Your Honor knows the law,
don't you think I know this field even better?
Science is facts.  I'm saying it's not a matter of people's sentiment.
- Witness.
- Judge Kim.
That's enough.  Stop.
Thank you, Doctor.
- Yes.
- You may step down.
It must have been difficult to testify for so long. Please have a drink of water.
- Chief Judge.
- Give the witness some water.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.  That water.  Did you change the water from the sample earlier?
What did you do? Seriously.
Your Honor.  It's not so. The evidence is kept here.
They look pretty similar to me too.  I didn't realize and made a mistake.
I'm sorry, Doctor.
He said the water was all right
I'm embarrassed.
If you're done, you may leave, Doctor.
I didn't expect he would do that.
How humiliating.
It's all because of that damned chairman. Really.
What's the matter?
Your Honors, I will proceed with the interrogation of the next witness,
Jang Gi Hyeon, field manager of the wastewater purification facility.
Witness, you've worked at the wastewater purification facility for twelve years.
Prior to the embankment collapse, was there ever any problem there?
January 16th statement. "As far as I know, in the time I continuously managed plant 4 there was never any problem."
Witness? Didn't you already state that to the investigating agency?
Why aren't you answering my question?
Well, that is,
I have a lot on my mind.
- Witness—
- Manager Jeong!
- Defendant.
- Yes.
Please remain seated. Now.
I'm sorry.
- Please continue.
- Yes, Your Honor.
Actually, there's something I want to tell you.
- What is it—
- The wastewater has been leaking for some time now.
I still don't understand why the embankment which was intact for 30 years
suddenly collapsed that night,
but I what I am certain of the fact that wastewater was already leaking before.
It was such an important matter that I reported it to the chairman.
- Manager!
- Defendant.
Please return to you seat.
Witness, please speak comfortably.
The facility's deterioration due to age is serious.
I told the chairman we would have a  major problem if we didn't do something immediately.
But the chairman replied "Why are you making a fuss when we are moving to Southeast Asia next year?"
- "Why are you making a mountain out of a molehill?"
- Manager Jeong!
Yes, what did you say when you heard him say that?
What if something happens to the elderly living in the village?
- If that happens—
The chairman said,
"what does it matter for old people who have lived long enough?"
Manager Jeong, when did I ever say that?
What do you think about  "lived long enough"?
Don't tell me that's what you said.
At the time, I thought,
Isn't that murder?   Is he living disguised as a human being?
No.  I really didn't. Your Honor.
I never said that.
That's murder.
My nickname is "Doctor Safety."
I've worked my whole life taking care of everything according to the safety manuals without a problem,
so I really want to die, Your Honor.
You were prepared, weren't you? You met the doctor.
I'd like to call Dr. Yu Jung Baek as a witness.
My nickname is Doctor Safety.
Guilty 86% Innocent 14%
- Damn!
- Wow!
Look at that S.O.B.  Complete garbage. Don't you agree?
There's nothing more to watch. Sentence him to death.
He's got a lot of nerve.
- Let him off!
- Death penalty. Death penalty. Death Penalty.
Guilty 89%
Your Honor, that's not fair!
It's really, really, not. I never said anything like that.
Why would I say something like "those old people lived long enough"?
- You never said anything like that?  Then what did you say?
- What?
You don't deny meeting the witness.
What did you say when you met the plant manager?
That is ...
Defendant. Please answer.
The whole country is watching.
Guilty 91%
Because I ... I had a lot of work to do,
I can't remember the conversation, Your Honor.
No. Really, no. Your Honor.
I never said that.
No. No.
- Are you treating the public like fools now?
- That's not so.
What does "What does it matter to people who have lived long enough" mean exactly, Defendant?
No.
I'm blinded by my own money.  I don't care if everyone else dies.
Do you know that is willful negligent homicide?
Chairman.
Occupational Negligence
I'm going to urge innocence, but if anything should go wrong,
then I will argue for death and injury by occupational negligence.
Do you understand, Defendant?
Guilty 95%
Occupational negligence negligence.
Guilty 96% Innocent 4%
I am sorry.
It's true I received a briefing.
Do you admit you received a report of the leak?
And that you didn't care if people in the vicinity died?
- That's not true.
- If it is.
What is this? That bastard Kang Yo Han! What the hell is he doing?
Please calm down, Minister. Judge Kang must be thinking of something.
What is he thinking?
I didn't think anything would happen.
At the time the leak wasn't that big.
I really didn't think it would result in this.
What do you mean, "murder"?  That's truly ridiculous.
Then, the defendant denies involuntary manslaughter.
Do you admit negligence in your work?
Ju Il Do was the sponsor of Justice Minister Cha Gyeong Hui.
She has power and influence and has been supporting Kang Yo Han all this time.
Everything's ready, right?  Did you meet the doctor?
-  Meet the lawyer today.
- I am sorry.
It's my fault.  I was stupid.
I did it out of foolishness.
Anyway, you were moving to the new factory soon, weren't you?
I committed a crime deserving of death.
Don't worry, Minister. It will be done according to the law.
I don't think the public is that stupid.
I only trust Kang Yo Han.
You're pushing him into death and injury by occupational negligence?
Chief Judge.
If you plead guilty to murder with one or two lies from a witness,
this trial is a farce.
I ask you to make a decision based solely on the rule of law.
I'll bear what you say in mind.
I'll announce my ruling after a short break.
You said five years for occupational negligence?
Don't worry.  Parole isn't up to the judge.  It's up to the Ministry of Justice.
How dare he say murder?
Why the heck did Jeong Gi Hyeon lie like that?
Judge! It's a big hit! Big!
It had 11.4% average viewing rate and reached the highest 14.7% viewing rate per minute.
Moreover the most important viewing rate for the age between 20 and 49 is over 6%, Judge!
- We're a great success, right?
- Of course yes.
Is a trial an entertainment?
That's not what I meant but I just meant the citizens are very interested in the trial, Judge.
- He's always a little edgy. Please take good care of us.
- Yes.
How much money did we put into this to secure the exclusive right to broadcast?
Our chairman will grin from ear to ear.
Even though you're happy, you shouldn't show it too obviously.
I got it. Have some steak.
Bye.
Treat us to a meal.
I'll buy all the meals in the world.
You gained a lot of money.
Cheers.
I'm going to make a ruling.
I'm seriously accepting the opinion of the citizens who watched this trial.
I contemplated a lot but with the state of the evidence which was admitted
I concluded that it's unreasonable to decide he murdered willfully.
However, the defendant admitted to the indictment charges of death and injury by occupational negligence,
for which I pronounce him guilty.
The maximum penalty for death and injury by occupational negligence is five years.
However, among the judiciary reform bills passed last year,
there is an article which provides that the sentence shall be within the total derived from adding the  punishment for each victim.
No way...
- Kim Sun Ja, Park Myeong Sun,
-  Who are they?
Lee Jeong Ro,
Bae Myeong Jae,
And child Yu So Yeong.
Lee Gab Geun,
Kim Dong Jae,
Park Yong Sun,
Hwang In Chan,
Kang Jeon Il,
Gu Jong Ok,
Kim Yu Chun,
Jeong Gwuin Ah,
Hwang Mal Ja,
Seon Wu Yun Jeong,
Yun Yeong Suk,
- He is really a pro.
-  Lee Seok Gyu,
Won Yeong Seon.
To the defendant who took away the innocent's lives because of his foolish greed
and made the survivors suffer the rest of their lives,
within total of adding the punishments for 47 victims, imprisonment!
I sentence 235 years' imprisonment!
Imprisonment of 235 years
Guilt: 97%, Innocence: 3%
Hey, stop the car.
Imprisonment of 235 years
Guilt: 97%, Innocence: 3%
Is this possible right now?
Live Court Show
Live a long life, please.
Attorney Go, you said five years.
Five years.
Live Court Show
Judge! Judge, thank you.
Judge, thank you. Judge, thank you.
Thank you, Judge. Thank you, Judge.
Thank you, Judge.
Thank you.
I won't have any regrets even if I die now.
Kim Sun Ja who strangled herself after she lost her precious granddaughter is my sister.
I tried to die to follow her a few times.
Since my life string was so durable, I couldn't make it as I wanted.
You deny murder with willful negligence
but you admit  occupational negligence.
If you put each person's picture on the screen, I'll call each person's name.
Yes, I understand.
Bae Myeong Jae, Lee Seok Gyu, and Child Yu So Yeong.
The Devil Judge
Timing and Subtitles by the Devil's Minions @ viki
It was touching. My eyes teared up a little bit.
The rule of law? Is justice the goal of a trial?
That you act as if you're warm-hearted although you're stony-hearted.
It's to sell hope and get it repaid with terror.
What do you want?
A prey?
Someone who only pleases himself has no charm.
nor any usefulness.
Why do you do such things?
You're just a bait. A fresh one.
I think he hasn't been tamed enough.
You crazy bastard!