You will be jealous of me
Strange eyes look at me
I don't have to care about breathing
Go down your own path
Your beauty will soon be frozen
I don't want
I don't want to deceive myself
Miss you, love you, and love you
No matter who is far or far away
At that moment, in the second year
I will be a magical eye
Pass through the loneliness to find you
Put on the most solid gold armor
Hold the weapon in your hand
Use all your strength to fight against the most real you
No matter what the little tricks
No matter what rumors
I will definitely be invincible
I don't care if you are willing
Where is the gold?
In the past, I kept the sweet
No matter where your heart is
My heart is here
Even if the iron armor is invincible
I'm only one you
Episode 2
Jianxi
Tang Fei
Aren't you in the crew?
I'm so worried
What's going on?
What happened?
Where is the wound?
Nothing
I'm not injured
What kind of bad crew are you?
What kind of
I'm sorry, I'm not in a good mood
You were with her in the hospital last night, right?
Where is your phone?
I left it in the crew
I know you are injured
I want to come and see you first
You will definitely feel very happy
But it seems that the reality is not like this
I
I'm fine
I came here
Just to see if you are okay
I'm relieved if you are okay
You are going back?
Thank you
Also came back to see me
It's okay
You don't have to worry about me
Take a good movie
Will
Do not worry
I'll send you
Am I stupid?
I sat on the plane all night to see you
it is good
You stay with another man all night
I tell you, I am your boyfriend
I will do that when I encounter that situation
What do you mean by not worrying about you?
You are my woman
I'm not worried about you, who are you worried about?
What's wrong with you?
I'm fine
Why are you so loud to me?
Say so much at once
You will be short of oxygen, you don't know
Why can't I pretend?
I can't win your sympathy
Silly
Actually
You came back to see me
I am very happy
I'm telling the truth
I didn't see how happy you are at all
That's more like it
Tang Fei
I have something to do
You go first
Talk on the phone
Then you
Go quickly, I'll call you
You take care of yourself
I'm waiting for you to come back
Tang Fei
What's going on?
Why is there a problem with the explosion?
I don't know
You came back with all your might
Didn't you ask clearly?
Could it be
That she doesn't welcome you back?
Tang Fei
Didn't you tell her that you didn't rest for 48 hours?
You came back from the flight of the red eyes
And you still have to rush back to film?
Did you hear that?
Teacher Lu seems to be badly injured this time
I guess the crew will lose a lot of money this time
Yes, I think it's so strange
Didn't you say that the editing department would come out and then pay?
Why did you mention money?
That's right
This team is too unprofessional
It seems that they will lose a lot of money this time
A good crew has such a thing
Really annoying
That's right
Everyone
Miss Shen
Hello Miss Shen
I am sorry for what happened
But
We are in the same team
We should unite
And work together to overcome difficulties
Right?
Yes, yes, yes
Miss Shen is right
We can't be affected by this kind of thing
We should shoot a good show
You don't have to care about that Jianxi
She has a lot of things
She knows to make up rumors all day long
Since she is not injured, she will come to shoot
What big play?
Right?
I think people want to lose money in the crew
So petty
Everyone, cheer up today
Yes, yes
What are you doing?
You have nothing to do, right?
Let's go
Hello director
Shen Yan
Didn't you say that there was a promotion event
That Jianxi would join with you?
Yes
Now it seems that
You can only be the only one who is out of the way
Jianxi is the second daughter
And this kind of thing has happened
It's already pitiful
How can I leave her alone to promote?
This is impossible
I can understand your mood
But think about it
Who else can come after this kind of thing?
If I had this kind of thing
I would have finished the shooting anyway
I didn't expect you to be so careful
You really make me look at you
It was a good thing
How could it become like this?
It's really too hard
Don't be too sad, okay?
You adjust that state
The next promotion
It depends on you
Director, since you said that
I will be reluctant
By the way
Let's take a picture together
Then I put it online
Even if it's for our show
Do a promotion
it is good
One two three
Teacher
Don't worry about it
I will be discharged soon
It's okay
I have nothing to do lately
I can accompany you more
And the teacher was hurt because of me
I should take care of you more
I'm not angry now
How can you be angry?
Anxin and I have been disagreeing
Aren't you always embarrassed?
I know
Actually the teacher has been thinking about me
I was too willful before
So I didn't feel it
Really?
If I hadn't been too anxious to terminate the contract with the company
I wouldn't have been forced to take this show
Anxin is a very good agent
But
She has been with Mei for too long
She is used to being high
Leave Mei to come to your side
She doesn't know how to help you at once
Teacher
Actually it has nothing to do with Anxin
It's my fault
Don't blame her
Jixi
From now on
Can you believe me?
Let me take you
Step by step to the highest place
Okay?
Believe me
Jixi
Anxin
Why are you here?
I have already made an appointment with the production team
We don't need to go to the press conference tomorrow
Why?
It's already like this
Why are you still going?
Why not?
They are all injured
You won't let them go to the show again, right?
Jixi
You don't want to give up halfway, right?
Did I tell you
No matter what happens
You must not give up acting
Teacher, don't worry
I will continue to finish this show
Jixi
Anxin
I believe you
You go back quickly
When she is ready for tomorrow's show
You must remember
Don't be rude in front of the reporters
Teacher
Let Anxin prepare in the afternoon
I can stay here with you
Don't worry
I just got injured and sick
It's okay
You go
But
Go
Go, go
Teacher, take care of yourself
Just blame the temper
I will go
Yes
Time is up
Hello, everyone
Welcome to the TV series
The last princess's press conference
Next, let's welcome actress Shen Yan to the stage
Thank you
Why didn't Miss Jianxi participate in the publicity?
Is it an accident before
Made Jianxi and the crew have a conflict
In fact, this matter
Caused Jianxi great harm
So he can't continue to complete the shooting
I hope everyone can give him more time and space
I believe he can cheer up
Shen Yan, I heard that after the incident
You went to visit
But Jianxi refused to visit
Is this true?
Who told us?
Really?
Is this true?
Dear reporters
In fact, from the beginning
Shen Yan advised him not to shoot these dangerous scenes
But he wanted to take the lead
Have to force shooting
And when it broke down
Obviously, I made a deal with him
He was hurt because he didn't follow the agreement
Yao Yao, don't say it anymore
Must say
To make your reputation fair
Actresses like Jianxi
Is a lonely fish
No responsibility at all
Obviously not hurt
Pretend to be pitiful and sympathize
Such an important publicity today
No one came to participate
Sorry, we are late
Jianxi, didn't you refuse to attend the scene?
Why did you suddenly come to attend the show?
Who said I'm not coming?
Come, Jianhao
I thought you couldn't come
I am explaining to everyone
Sorry
I just went to the hospital to change the medicine
So I'm late
What's the hurry?
Just come
Don't worry if you're fine
We are waiting for the photo
Come on, the actors are all on
Come on, stand up
Smile
Yes, a little closer
Good
Smile
One more
Sorry, sorry
What's going on?
Listen to what he said
I haven't said anything
Sorry, are you Miss Shen Yan?
Yes
We suspect you are related to the explosion case
Please come with us
Explosion case
I think you should have a lesson
How is this possible?
Sorry, please cooperate
Please explain to us
What's going on?
You should have a lesson
This is the scene of the press conference
You should investigate it clearly
Why is there evidence?
Why did the police come to you?
Why did you come?
It's him
You framed me, right?
Zhai Xi
Zhai Xi, what's wrong with you?
You framed you
Zhai Xi, you are too much
I treat you as my best friend
How can you do this to me?
Miss Shen Yan
Please don't talk nonsense
Why am I talking nonsense?
Please believe me
I didn't do it at all
He framed me
I am innocent
Police officer, please deal with it in person
Sure
This is the scene of the press conference
You can't do this
You can't do this to me
Please believe me
Believe me
Police officer
Please believe me
What's going on?
Why did you arrest him?
Sorry, I can't tell you
What's going on?
Please believe me
Why is Shen Yan related to the explosion case?
The assistant of the explosion master has resigned
I don't know who reported him
As a result
When he was caught
He immediately released Shen Yan
So Shen Yan is the mastermind?
Why would the explosion assistant
Do harm to the show without reason?
He was bought
Oh my god, how could this happen?
The competition between the actresses is too terrible
You didn't read the news
The actor who is close to the two actors
Who are not seen by the king and the queen
They all wish that the other party disappears immediately
But who reported him?
It's really strange
Let's go
Yanxi
Don't listen to what others say
Hello
Yes, I am Anxin
Guard station
Shen Yan wants to see you
Yanxi
I just held the last hope
I didn't expect you to come
I'm going back to the studio
Let's talk for a long time
It's all my fault
I just wanted to scare you
I really didn't expect
Such a big accident would happen
And made Lu Zhou hurt
I'm sorry
I'm really sorry
We are the same
Without social background
Climbing from the bottom
The feeling of being hungry
He doesn't understand
But you can feel it
I know
I did too much
I did too many mistakes
It's not worth your forgiveness
But all this
It's life that forces me
I don't believe in everything
Must be famous
Because only when it's famous
I have money to treat my mother
Pay off for my father
I've heard these words
Many times
You come to me
What's the matter
You help me
Please help me
Let me leave this place
You are committing a criminal act
This is all a misunderstanding
It's that assistant
On purpose to drag me down the river
Not to mention
Lu Zhou, he was just hurt
He didn't have any substantial damage
The lawyer told me
As long as you treat it as an accident
We can reconcile
And then withdraw the case
No way
Jianxi
You just look at
Our past relationship
You just help me for the last time
Okay?
Shen Yan
I thought you knew your fault
I didn't expect you to be stubborn
If you want to tell me these words
Then I'll go first
You are so straight-forward
You must be serious
Because you haven't reached
The point of selling yourself for life
I
Every day
It's all through selling yourself
And the bottom line
I was not like this before
I sit in a clean room
And play the piano
I have a grudge for the next meal
Who doesn't want to live
I know
You hate my hypocrisy
Hate my poor things
But all this
Is taught by life
I can't even drink water
I just need to smile at this man
And I can get a chance
It's them
That made me like this
I hate them all
Calm down
Sit down
Don't be too impulsive
No family
No one loves you
You are bullied
Is that the reason for your crime?
Because of poverty
So you go to steal
Because there is no love
So you steal
Because you were bullied
So you turned over
And then you bullied others
Do you think all this
Is right?
You can say it so easily
That's because you don't have my experience
You always say
You are the same as me
But I am not the same as you
Even if I starve to death
I won't steal and steal
And I won't lie and betray my friends
I will only use my own strength
And try to make those who look down on me
Recognize me
Right is right
Wrong is wrong
You should pay for your own behavior
Didn't you take revenge
For your own fault?
What do you mean?
Why did that broken assistant
Give me out?
You should know better
You didn't know
That assistant gave you out
What does it have to do with me?
Forget it
You make it clear
He has already escaped
But why was he caught so easily?
And gave me out so quickly
Don't you think it's weird?
You think about it yourself
Hello, Jianxi
How is the situation over there?
I will go back to the film studio right away
Okay, I'll go over and thank you later
Don't worry
What's wrong?
There is one thing
That's a bit strange
Come in
Lu Zhong
I have something to talk to you
What is it?
I went to the surveillance room
So?
The security said
Your assistant
Lied to the surveillance belt the day before the crime
Yes
My car was towed at the parking lot
Where is it?
I want to find the head of the surveillance
It's like this
What do you think?
The assistant of the security
May have to prepare for the next day's work
So he left very late
But at this time
He just ran into Shen Yan
But I don't understand
If it's Shen Yan
He should be the one on the road
There is only a second possibility
It was when the third person was on the scene
And when the third person left
The surveillance camera happened to be filming me
You mean
I'm the third person
If it's not you
Why did you take the surveillance belt?
But I can't figure it out
Why don't you want everyone to know
You went to the film studio too
Anxin
You can go to be a screenwriter
It's a border
Totally different
Pulled together
You are too good
You say he is not a coincidence
Lu Zhou
So fast
That assistant was caught
And so fast
This assistant
He gave it to Shen Yan
Lu Zhou, you say
What have you done?
You are simply talking nonsense
it is good
Then we will find your assistant to confront
Lu Zhou, I tell you
Don't act in front of me
You know Shen Yan
Bought the assistant of the explosion
You also know he is going to hurt the cut
You know more about the seriousness of the matter
Anxin
You know everything
Why do you still ask?
I just don't understand
Why don't you stop him
How to stop him
One time
Two times
This time it's an explosion
What about next time?
Who can stop it?
We can call the police
How to call the police
There is no evidence
Even if Shen Yan is stopped
He will not be punished
This is not a reason
All are not reasons
If you want to stop him
Today's thing will not happen
You will not live in the hospital
Lu Zhou, I don't understand
You can hide the truth
What do you want to do?
I don't know
You can hide the truth
What do you want to do?
To defeat the opponent
You have to strike hard
I can't give him any chance to turn over
I want him to pay a heavy price for his behavior
Are you really trying to stop Shen Yan?
What else can it be?
For Jansi
You are in the hospital for him
He will definitely be grateful
He will listen to you as before
Lu Zhou
You are not really good for Jansi
You are selfish and hypocritical
You go tell Jansi
Go
What?
If you tell Jansi
What will she think?
Thank you
She can't stand this blow
She is different from others
She is not only good for acting
She doesn't know human feelings
I don't know how the world works
She is strong on the outside
But she is afraid of being abandoned inside
If you tell her
She will definitely be hit
You want to tell her?
Go ahead
Tell her
I won't stop you
Hello, Jansi
I will go out to buy something
I will be back soon
Ok, wait for me
Lu Zhou, I am telling you
I am not doing this for you
I am doing this for Jansi
If you do this again
I will tell Jansi
I will go out to buy something
Why don't you explain it clearly?
Because she is telling the truth
I know the whole truth
But I chose to hide it
No
You protected Jansi
My protection is my purpose
I only know
If it wasn't for you
Jansi would be seriously injured
You know someone hurt her hand
But it's a blast
We can't predict the consequences
You don't know
What kind of damage you will be hurt
I really can't understand
Your feelings for protecting someone
I just want to make a bet with myself
Make a bet?
If I win
Jansi can come back to me
Like before
But what if you lose?
Actually, I just want to exchange one thing
The two most precious words in this world
Trust
If I lose
That's my fate
Can Anxin really keep her secret?
I'm sorry
Let's go
Jansi
Why are you so slow?
I don't know what to say
Hello, Fusheng
Teacher has to leave the hospital
I've sent her back
How can you leave the hospital now?
I said she didn't listen
Or you come back now
Ok, I'll be right there
Anxin, go to teacher's house
Aren't we going to the film studio?
It's too late, go to teacher's house
Jansi
I ask you
If Lu Zhou is not what you imagined
What will you do?
What do you mean?
Nothing
Let's talk later
Why are you here?
Teacher, you should be in the hospital
Why are you back?
I'm fine
Of course I can come out
If the teacher insists on leaving the hospital
Then I'll stay and take care of you
What do you eat for lunch?
I bought all the supplies in the refrigerator
All convenient food
It's convenient to eat like this
You can eat it when it's hot
But it's not nutritious
Jansi, I said she can take care of herself
Let's go
Teacher, your wound has not healed yet
You should eat something light
I'll help you prepare
We have to shoot a play in the afternoon
Anxin
Anxin is right
You should focus on your work
I can take care of myself
You go to shoot
I want to do something for you
Lu Zhou, you are enough
Anxin
You know what's going on
You know the accident will happen
You do this to tie Jansi
Let her listen to you, right?
Anxin, what are you talking about?
Do you forget what Shen Yan said?
He said someone did not care
Just to be a hero in front of you
You believe what Shen Yan said
I know
I will delay a lot of work today
But I will try my best to make up for it
I also ask you not to talk to the patient like this
Jansi
For your plan
I have a disagreement with Anxin
It's inevitable to have a conflict
But I believe
She must be good for you
Lu Zhou, you are really a hero
The play is so good
Enough, Anxin, do you believe her?
I believe her
Lu Zhou, I tell you
The play is the play
There will be a day when it will be over
You choose it yourself
Teacher, I'm sorry
Anxin is in a bad mood
So she said such strange words
Jansi
I think for Anxin
You should give up
She is completely blocking your steps
It's no use
Give up
Teacher, maybe you misunderstood
Actually, Anxin has been helping me
I know her better than you
You want to improve
You have to learn a lot
The first one is to give up
Follow me
Look at these shining trophies
If you want to step by step
You have to give up all the people who are bothering you
What about the second step?
For now
Learn to play
If the scene of this play is changed
Can you explain it clearly?
Tang Fei
You are tired these two days
Why don't you go in and rest
I'll tell you when they're done
The weather is so good
Go
Change, you must change
I'm not saying you can't change now
Can we explain it after the scene is changed?
We discuss it to clarify this point
I will change the script and keep the play going
The most troublesome thing now is to be affected by the weather
Director
How long is this play going to be filmed?
It was filmed for four months
It's been a week now
You must solve this problem these two days
I don't want to
It rains every day
This play is the sunrise
It's a big play
If you don't shoot, everyone will lose
Please
We want to wait
But you know that Tang Fei's play is full
If we have more time
Our loss will be great
Mr. Yue
This play
Must be filmed
Because the importance of the whole play
Hello, it's me
I have something to ask you
It's me
Ji Qin
Tang Fei is resting
If you need it, I can wake him up
No need
Then do you have anything?
I
Nothing special
Then I hang up
Zai Xi
Because Tang Fei's work is really hard recently
If there is nothing special
Don't call me
Xiaoudo
's famous act
Let's go
You didn't tell Jianqi that you're coming back today?
I told her, but she didn't reply.
Don't wait for her.
She has a fan meeting. She can't come.
How about this?
Did she tell you about the fan meeting?
She's too busy. She might not be able to make it.
Tang Fei, your car is here. Let's go.
Let's go.
Stop looking. Let's go.
How is it? Is the shooting going well?
Ji Qing.
Everything is fine.
It's going well. Right, Ji Qing?
It's going well.
I originally planned to let you rest for a while.
But now you have a very good role.
I hope you can go and fight for it.
Jianqi, this is a gift for you.
Thank you, Jianqi.
Jianqi, thank you.
Jianqi, this is a gift for you.
Thank you.
Jianqi, hello.
Hello, this is my gift.
Jianqi, I've liked you for a long time.
Thank you.
Jianqi, I can shake hands with you.
Thank you, Jianqi.
Thank you.
Jianqi, thank you.
Jianqi, drink some tea.
Jianqi, help me to sign here.
Thank you.
Jianqi.
Jianqi, you're in a good mood.
Who is it?
Why is it you?
Why are you here?
Where is Tang Fei?
Jianqi, can I take a picture with you?
Look here.
Thank you.
Jianqi, this is for me.
Jianqi.
Thank you.
Shake hands.
Why are you here?
I told you I would come back today.
You don't go to the school,
you have to tell me if you have a fan meeting.
This is a temporary decision.
Even if it's temporary,
you still have a chance to tell me.
I'm a little upset now.
You have to think about how to make up for me.
I...
Come in.
Teacher.
It's time. We should go.
Where?
I'm going to meet a producer today.
I just came back.
It's time.
We should go.
I'll be right there.
Tang Fei, let's call and contact.
What's going on?
Anxin, Jianqi is going to meet a producer.
You're not going?
I'm a manager now.
What do you mean?
All Jianqi's work
is arranged by Lu Zhou.
If Jianqi didn't protect me,
I would have lost my job.
What do you mean?
Can't you see?
Jianqi listens to Lu Zhou.
I'm really angry.
How can you be a manager?
You're the boss of the class.
You think I'm willing to leave
because of my old temper?
Why didn't you leave?
I just wanted to
get rid of him.
Lu Zhou is a cunning and good actor.
I wanted to get rid of him
but I failed.
What happened
when I left?
A lot of things happened.
Which one do you want to hear?
Teacher, why are we here today?
Are we playing basketball?
Director Xu Ziyu will play tennis here.
You must perform well.
Director Xu Ziyu?
Is he the director of the royal family?
Yes.
He's going to make a new movie
called The Queen.
You must win the first place.
The first place?
Yes. As long as you win the first place,
the best actress of next year
will be yours.
Now you know
why I let you play basketball so hard.
To please a director?
Of course not.
I didn't let you please a director.
I wanted to let everyone know
how good you are.
Lu Zhou.
Director Xu.
Hello.
This is Jianxi, right?
Hello, director.
Nice to meet you.
Lu Zhou sent me the movie you've made
before the exam.
I've seen all your roles.
But,
I need to think about
my role again.
Director Xu, Jianxi
loves playing tennis.
Do you want to play with us?
Sure. Let's play together.
Director Xu.
So lively.
You're late.
Sorry.
So, Miss Ji Qing
is very loyal to this role.
The King of Ice
is the movie you're looking forward to this year.
I want to play the role of the first actress.
But,
the final decision is in the hands of the director.
Let's not talk about this today.
Let's play a game.
Okay?
Come on.
You're here so soon.
What are you doing?
What?
I'm not going to say anything.
You're getting rid of your worries.
What do you want to do?
Get rid of my worries?
Isn't that right?
From the first agent
to the assistant.
You don't even let her participate in such an important event.
I think you've misunderstood.
I'm doing this out of goodwill.
I hope Jianxi
can win the heroine.
Is it that simple?
It's that simple.
Okay.
Tang Fei.
You come.
Come on.
Softens a einem
Look at the bustling city, look at the lonely street
Look at the tide, the cold and the cold, the sky is dark and the sky is bright
There are too many expectations, in the end, there is despair
Look at you coming and going, holding on to the wind and frost, everything is wandering
Too stubborn, but young and crazy
There is absurdity, don't forget me
Looking back, all the grudges will have a return
You and I, gradually lost on the road
Too crazy, don't think about anything
Where is the heart that is still in a trance?
Just like this, waiting for someone to dawn