You will be jealous of me
Strange eyes look at me
I don't have to care about breathing
Go down your own path
Your beauty will soon be frozen
I don't want
I don't want to deceive myself
Miss you, love you, and love you
No matter who is far away
At that moment, the standard age
Transformed into magical eyes
Pass through the loneliness to find you
Put on the most ancient gold armor
Hold the weapon in your hand
Use all your strength to fight for the most real you
No matter what the little tricks
No matter what rumors
I will definitely be invincible
I don't care if you are willing
Where is the gold?
In the past, I kept the sweet
No matter where your heart is
My heart is here
Even if the world is invincible
I only have you
The Love by Hypnotic
Episode 35
Ji Qing
I am the same
I have come all the way
Met a lot of setbacks
Several times
I was leaving
And stayed at last
You may not know
In fact, I cried many times because of you
Because I feel compared to you
I am like a rotten mud
Nothing is
You are prettier than me
More smart than me
And love your father
And the favor of the public
In fact, compared to you
I am the one who should be jealous
But I didn't make this jealousy become painful
I let it become the motivation for me to move forward
I tell myself
One day, I must catch up with Ji Qing
I want to stand on the same stage with him
Ji Qing, thank you
Thank you for the motivation for me to move forward
What do you think we should eat tonight?
How about we go to the cinema first?
But there are no good movies that have been released recently
Jin Xi
Why are you so nervous?
Did you encounter any trouble during the filming?
Quite a bit of trouble
What is it?
Because of me
And because of you
I didn't film your movie
What does it have to do with me?
Ji Qing likes you very much
It seems that because of the fact that we are together
She is quite painful
That can't be because she doesn't like it
We are not together
You don't understand
If I don't reconcile with her
It will be hard to continue filming this movie
Jin Xi, relax a bit
Don't be so anxious
You won't let your boyfriend betray his thoughts
Because of Ji Qing's emotions, right?
That's not what I mean
Then what should I do to make you happy?
I don't know either
Tang Fei
Let me discuss something with you
Go ahead
During this time
Let's not meet first
No
I mean during the filming of this movie
Let's try to meet less
Especially don't come to the scene
I don't want to hurt Ji Qing
I also want to finish this movie well
Okay?
Will you promise me?
I beg you
Let me tell you
My biggest patience is to wait for the day when this movie is finished
I can't wait for another day
I promise you
I call you every day
You have to answer it immediately
I send you WeChat every day
You must come back as soon as you see it
Anything else?
Yes, a lot
I promise you
Recording
27 scenes, 2 scenes, 1 word
Action
Xiaowu
Do you know where this person is?
I don't know this word
This word is Nian Kang
Do you know where he is?
Your Majesty
Let me help you go home and ask my mother and brother
No need
You remember
This matter can only be known by yourself
No one else can know
By the way
You don't know Chinese characters
You have to learn more in the future
I obey
Didn't you say you would teach me to play the zither?
This zither was asked by the person
You try
Cut
Pass
The next scene is
Zhu Yinggong likes Rong Ling
He asked Cixi for a marriage
Cixi agreed
Rong Ling is extremely unwilling
De Ling willingly stood up
On behalf of sister
Married to Zhu Yinggong
Just this scene
I think it's a good scene
To marry to Zhu Yinggong
Just this scene
You two play well
Continue to play the words of Mao He Shen Li
Just play it automatically
OK, get ready
All right
Everybody, get ready
34 scenes 2 scenes 1
Idiot
Where are you going?
I am going to find my ancestors
I don't want to marry Zhu Yinggong
Does it depend on your character?
Doesn't my ancestor like me?
I'll tell him.
Maybe he'll agree.
The Empress Dowager is here.
Greetings, Your Highness.
You may rise.
Xiaowu.
Aren't you going to take a picture today?
That...
You brought that?
I did.
Hurry up.
Hurry up and take a picture for Your Highness.
Your Highness, please wait.
Your Highness, it's not enough.
No need to kneel.
Thank you, Your Highness.
One, two, three, smile.
You're done.
I'm done.
It's so fun.
This Western style is interesting.
Let me take one too.
Your Highness, please wait.
You two go, I'll take a picture for you.
Why is the portrait upside down?
Are you two standing upside down or standing with your feet?
Interesting.
Elderly ancestor, this portrait is upside down.
It's really fun.
Interesting.
Elderly ancestor is so happy now, can I say it now?
No, I can't hold it anymore.
Elderly ancestor, I don't want to marry Zhu Ying.
Take it away.
No rules.
I won't take it.
Next, I, De Ling, for the sake of sisterhood, stand out bravely for the first time.
This is all because of sisterhood.
Normally, you are like a fire treasure.
Now you are so unruly.
Wu, what did you say to me just now?
I...
Elderly ancestor, please take back the order.
Third Miss, what are you doing?
Zhu Ying wants a wife who is good in both the capital and the outside world.
I think this person must be careful.
Rong Ling is young and ignorant, it's easy to cause trouble.
If you marry her, you will definitely ruin the reputation of the palace.
The order has been made.
Tell me, what should I do now?
The order says that the Yu family's daughter should marry.
There is more than one daughter in the Yu family.
Sister.
Elderly ancestor, don't.
You two are really sisterly.
That's good.
But you said that the Zhu Ying Palace's ambassador will not have any opinions.
As long as it is the meaning of the elderly ancestor, there will definitely be no opinion.
All right, thank you.
Thank you, Elderly ancestor.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
You are still not happy?
Thank you, Elderly ancestor.
Cut.
Director, how did we play this scene?
Let's see the next scene.
OK.
Come on, get the knife and put it on.
Jianxi, remember the scene.
This scene is still the same.
I want you to show your sisterly love.
Tang Fei, why are you here?
No, let me see Jianxi.
I'll call her for you.
No, I'm fine here.
Come on, it's not appropriate to see her.
I told her before.
Before this scene was killed, we didn't see each other.
Why?
No reason.
You are angry in this scene.
Don't worry, I saw it.
I'll go back first.
Weird.
Two scenes in twenty-three scenes.
Action.
Sister, you can't marry the Zhu Ying master.
His beard is white.
I'll go to the emperor.
Stop.
Cut.
Ji Qing, you are not in the mood.
Do it again.
OK.
Two, action.
Sister, you can't marry the Zhu Ying master.
His beard is white.
I'll go to the emperor.
Ji Qing is injured.
Why are you holding me?
The director didn't shout.
I've said it many times.
You can't be like this after you enter the palace.
You can't do whatever you want.
You can't mess up at any time.
I...
Even if you suffer a lot, you have to swallow it.
Remember, don't run around without wearing a suit.
If the ancestors see you, they will punish you.
Ji Qing, you like the emperor.
Why did you marry the Zhu Ying master?
But he likes you.
OK.
No matter what happens, I will protect you.
Ji Qing is so good.
Jiang Xi, I will never lose to you.
Sister, let's run away together.
Let's run away from the Forbidden City.
So he also realized it.
What do you mean?
The light of consciousness was taken away by Ji Qing.
So he started to think about the future.
He started to fight for the camera.
Next life?
This is the real actor.
The action is faster than thought.
Sister used to protect me.
But now Xiao Wu has grown up.
I can't let sister suffer alone.
Let's run away together.
Let's escape from this miserable palace.
I want to protect sister.
Cut. Pass.
Next.
Why are you crying?
Who bullied you?
Your Majesty.
My father is sick.
Sister and I are on leave.
We have to leave the palace.
Will you come back after this?
What a pity.
I thought I learned this song.
I can play it for you in person.
Silly girl.
Actually, it's a good thing to leave.
It's better than staying in this huge palace.
But Kang Youwei has left.
Zhen has left.
Now you have to leave too.
Everyone around me has left.
Your Majesty.
Let's go.
The farther the better.
Just like a happy bird.
Never come back.
Your Majesty, goodbye.
Your Majesty.
Cut. Pass.
Cut.
Come on. Drink some water.
Jianxi.
Our competition has just begun.
You are my opponent.
Don't let me down.
I will wait for you at the Phoenix Film Festival next year.
You must work hard.
You too.
Come on.
Director Li.
You are late.
We just finished shooting.
I am late.
Lu Zhou.
When you recommended Jianxi to play Rong Ling.
I thought it was not appropriate.
Because this girl has played many complicated roles.
Let her play a white-fingered Rong Ling.
It's really unacceptable.
But now I know you are right.
She can play any role.
I let her play Rong Ling because I want to expand her career.
And stimulate her fighting spirit.
Fighting spirit?
Didn't you notice?
Every time she meets her lover.
She must be fighting.
But.
But what?
Jianxi.
She values acting too much.
And even gambles on her whole life.
Such a female actor is actually very dangerous.
As her teacher.
You should remind her.
I don't think so.
As an actor.
If you don't play the purest play.
Then what can she play?
It can only prove.
She can't do anything.
But Lu Zhou, have you ever thought.
Jianxi sees her career as her life.
If one day she can't play.
It will be a devastating blow.
She won't.
Because I.
Will help her walk step by step.
Until she can reach the peak.
The peak that an actor can reach.
Director Li.
Thank you for your help to Jianxi.
Goodbye.
Lu Zhou.
Jianxi is not your specialty.
You can't keep acting like this.
It will ruin her.
Next is.
The script discussion of the love of Qingcheng.
The director wants to ask the director's opinion.
You should prepare.
It seems that she is not far from the mountain.
Who?
Jianxi.
Of course.
She is now in the spotlight.
The halo of Tang Fei's girlfriend.
And she shot the big movie of director Li Hong.
Of course, she is popular.
What does it have to do with me?
How can it be?
An actor wants to be popular for a long time.
It can't be based on rumors.
But on strength.
But in two days.
You are going to film in other places.
Did you tell her?
I heard from the company staff.
Her schedule is scheduled until the end of next year.
I'm afraid you can't see each other for a long time.
I'm talking to you.
Can you answer me quickly?
Where are you going to die?
Let me help you.
No need.
What if Zhang Deng breaks the dress?
It's not that exaggerated.
Take it.
No need.
If people see it, they will be surprised.
Sorry.
This is the new shoes released this year.
Is it useful to say sorry?
What shoes do I have?
How much do I have to pay you?
I know.
What do you know?
You must have been looking for trouble on purpose.
You know that my family's situation
is to spend four months with Tang Fei alone.
Or to be in a relationship.
Are you jealous?
Are you angry with me on purpose?
Is this woman's brain as messy as her hair?
You mean, the filming will start by the early morning?
Tang Fei didn't tell you?
You talk really well.
You didn't bite your tongue, did you?
What did you say?
I said, did you bite your tongue?
You were bitten by a cat.
Let's go.
Say it again.
Next time, change your shoes.
Anxin.
Tang Fei.
I'm going to meet you.
I'll see you again.
What are you doing?
Aren't you afraid of death?
How can you come to my house like this?
Are you sick?
Why are you locking the door?
What are you doing?
Are you sick?
Let me go.
What are you doing?
You're wearing a mask.
Don't use my mask.
What?
I'm going to join the event of the Unifan.
I'm going to drink water tonight.
Is the event important or me?
What are you doing?
Let's go.
You haven't answered my call all day.
Do you know how many times I called you?
Why didn't you answer?
What are you doing?
Who made you angry?
Did you encounter any unhappy things?
No.
You won't tell me, right?
What are you doing?
Okay, I'm leaving.
Tang Fei.
What?
Go to hell.
Okay.
I'll show you what I'm made of.
I'll give you one last chance.
Will you say it or not?
Alright.
Later tomorrow,
I don't even know
if you're leaving.
Is that what you want?
Am I your girlfriend or...
I heard this from someone else?
I really don't know how to tell you.
Do you know, Jian Xin?
Whenever I wanted to separate from you,
I feel like we'd be separated by death.
It's like I never ever see you the same.
I'm not happy about this.
How long are you going to be gone?
Four months.
Then I'll see you off tomorrow.
No.
Don't you have a big event tomorrow?
I'm not going.
You can't be willful.
Why?
Be obedient.
I promise you.
I'll be back to see you soon.
I'm leaving.
Be obedient.
Why am I so easy to make up?
Who said that?
Every time you say something, I'm already made up by you.
Enough.
The mission of Yuni House is
to let humans enjoy the beauty of their skin.
Beauty and White Water
is a basic care that star customers like Jianxi
must have every day.
So we selected
Beauty and White Water, and selected mask set.
Okay.
Thank you for your wonderful speech.
Next, let's welcome
our guest of this event
Miss Jianxi
to the stage.
Let's welcome Miss Jianxi.
Jianxi.
I told you to come on stage.
Okay.
Mr. Dai.
May I ask why we invite Miss Jianxi
to be our guest
in this new product launch?
Because Yuni House is an online company
that displays the data of our 10 million
consumers.
Miss Jianxi is our
favorite female star.
So the consumers chose Jianxi.
Okay. Thank you for your speech.
Next, let's welcome
our friends in the media to take a photo with us.
Miss Jianxi, be happy.
Look here.
Look closer.
Jianxi.
Mr. Dai.
Mr. Dai, I have something urgent.
Jianxi.
The event is just half done.
Next, we will have a group dinner.
We will have dinner with sponsors.
Mr. Dai, I'm sorry. I can't go.
Jianxi.
I have to do everything to invite them to the stage.
You can't miss it.
Jianxi, if you have something to do,
you can go first. We will go later.
Thank you.
Goodbye, Mr. Dai.
I'm sorry, friends in the media.
I have to go first.
What are you thinking about?
It's the second time.
What do you mean?
This is the second time she gives up her job for Tang Fei.
Lu Zhuang.
You are so beautiful.
I'm sure every piece of your beauty will be your life.
Secondly, you are the most beautiful girl in the world.
It's been four months since I left.
You are both so busy.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
Why didn't you call her?
She took a very important role.
Today, San'er has a press conference.
Let's have a press conference.
I've already had four cups of coffee.
There's another cup. Don't waste it.
I'm sorry, miss. This is the VIP lounge.
It's okay. We know each other.
Why did you come here in this dress?
What about the event?
Don't tell me
you won't even give me a endorsement in the future.
Because you are more important.
I know.
I'm sorry.
An Jianba.
I'm leaving.
After I go there, make sure
to call me every day.
Only one? Can I call three?
Okay.
Let's call five.
Eight. Ten.
Okay.
How about this?
I'll give you a video when I'm free.
Go back.
Come.
Are you angry?
I'm sorry.
Teacher.
It's okay.
You can go back.
Teacher.
I...I did delay my work.
Because Tang Fei is going to perform abroad.
I want to see him off.
I didn't blame you.
I know you're angry.
Go away.
Don't bother me here.
Let's go.
Teacher. I know you're angry.
I didn't go through your approval.
I left in advance.
Do you think that's why?
You still didn't realize your mistake.
Teacher.
I'm an ordinary person.
I want to have a normal life.
Normal life?
Yes.
I'm an ordinary person.
But you always want me to work.
I'm not a robot.
Are you resisting me?
I didn't mean that.
Since the day you chose this profession,
you're not qualified
to live an ordinary life.
You want to live an ordinary life?
Okay.
Then you want to return the glory to you.
Lu Zhou. Teacher.
Are you too harsh on me?
I think he's not wrong.
You think he's not wrong?
You threw away a lot of fans and reporters.
Even the factory is confused.
You really think you're not wrong?
Look.
Look at yourself in the mirror.
You're beautiful and beautiful.
Is it easy for you to leave today?
Jianxi.
Many people think
you can't climb up anymore.
But you use your own behavior
to prove your ability.
But today,
you forgot your job
and dream for a man.
Okay.
If Tang Fei can do it,
marry him right now.
Go. Marry him.
Teacher, you're too much.
I did everything for your good.
For my good?
You want me to listen to you.
I'm sorry. I can't do it.
Stop.
Enough.
You think he's right, too?
I'm his agent.
I don't think he's wrong.
You're too greedy.
You're too extreme.
One day you'll understand
I do this to make him fly higher.
You'll only push him further.
Jianxi.
I was too impulsive.
Enough.
It's a big deal.
I think you did the right thing.
Although I'm your agent,
I should focus on your career.
But an agent can't be a tool for an actor.
You're human, too.
Anxin.
And,
can you tell me in advance
what you're going to do?
You're so sudden.
Okay, I know.
I'll tell you in advance.
Thank you.
We're family.
You should do your best
to return to the front line.
I'll try.
I'll make you the front line agent.
You're so loud.
I'm scared to death.
Let's go home.
Let's go.
Anxin.
Qin Wensun, what do you mean?
What do you mean?
I'm sorry.
You're the one who should be sorry.
What do you mean?
You broke in so angrily.
What happened?
Why did you push Chen Ai Zhi Meng
who was supposed to find Jian Xi?
This is the company's unified arrangement.
Isn't there a lot of work in Jian Xi's hands?
It doesn't matter if you
make a movie like this.
Nonsense.
Chen Ai Zhi Meng is a famous
international director's work.
It can help Jian Xi quickly.
Why did you push her?
You're just fooling her.
Anxin.
Let me finish.
After playing the role of De Ling and Rong Ling,
you could have received better resources.
But the company pushed you away
and made you take on
those messy commercial performances.
Qi Wen Sen, let me ask you.
Are you deliberately
controlling Jian Xi?
Anxin, what are you joking about?
Jian Xi is an actor from our company.
Why would I do that?
Do you really take Jian Xi
as your own actor?
Why did you make her take on
these messy commercial performances?
She's in her prime.
You're going to hurt her.
I've said it.
This is the company's decision.
Are you done?
Please leave.
But I have to remind you.
If you break in again
without any rules,
don't blame me for being rude.
Get out!
Go.
I'm telling you, Qi Wen Sen.
I won't let you off.
Anxin.
Leave me alone.
Is it really useful to be so impulsive?
I'm really angry.
I finally got you a new agent
and they gave it to someone else.
It's too much.
Forget it.
Forget it?
If I just forget it,
I don't deserve
to be a professional agent.
Then tell me.
What should we do now?
Leave Gong Yu Le.
Forever.
Mr. Cheng, long time no see.
Hello.
How are you?
I'm fine.
I met Miss Jian Xi.
Am I more beautiful than before?
Much more.
Come on, please sit.
Thank you.
Come on, sit.
Miss Jian, this is my business card.
What would you like to order?
Give us two cups of black tea.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Mr. Cheng, we're old friends.
I'll just say it.
Okay.
If Jian Xi
is hired to Hai Yang,
what's the benefit of her career?
We've made a whole plan
for Jian Xi.
We promise to make a big movie every year
and a big TV series.
Are you satisfied with this?
But our contract period
is five years away.
Don't worry about it.
We'll pay
all her contract fees.
What's the point of staying in the public entertainment?
Everyone knows
that Ji Qing is the only one
who is well-respected in the company.
She's the one who gives her the best resources.
Jian Xi is so excellent.
The company hasn't planned for her at all.
Qi Wen Sen
often cusses at the resources
that Jian Xi already has.
I've never heard of
a company that's so biased.
An Xi.
I think
I should wait until the contract is full.
The contract is full?
Are you going to be used by Qi Wen Sen
to get the last bit of the value?
You're a rising actress.
Tell me.
How many years are there left?
Jian Xi.
I think Mr. Cheng is right.
An Xi.
How about this, Mr. Cheng?
Let's go back and think about it
and give you an answer, okay?
No problem.
Okay.
I'll wait for your good news.
Please come here in person.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Take care.
Okay. Goodbye.
An Xi.
I think
we should wait until the contract is full.
The contract is full?
After the contract is full,
the company will only give you
all the resources.
Qi Wen Sen will continue to
give you those useless commercial performances.
What did they do
when they got the bad news?
They only know how to push the waves.
Jian Xi.
If you continue to
follow the waves,
you will ruin your future.
So you mean
to terminate the contract with Qi Wen Sen now?
Yes.
And don't worry about that.
If they can't do it,
I'll prepare a Chinese and Asian company for you.
These are big companies with strength.
They will definitely value you.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Termination of contract?
Termination of contract.
If I remember correctly,
the contract will expire in five years.
I know.
Jian Xi is popular now.
She has a lot of contracts.
But in my company,
only those who are full of contracts will expire.
No actor will quit on time.
Don't worry.
We will pay the termination fee.
What if I don't agree?
Everyone is in this circle.
You can't see it, you can't see it.
It's easy to get rid of it.
Then there will be a chance to cooperate.
That's it.
If you really don't want to agree,
we'll have to meet in court.
Your company doesn't value Jian Xi anyway.
It's meaningless to keep her.
Anxin,
I always thought
you were an experienced agent.
But today I think
your brain seems to have a problem.
You actually will make actors
do such stupid things.
I've been in this business for so long.
I've never seen a boss
who is so stingy like you.
Since you are heartless,
we have to do this.
That means
you have decided
to break up with me?
You can think so.
Jian Xi can terminate the contract.
But she has to pay the termination fee.
She has to complete
the contract on time.
Of course.
If there's nothing else,
I'll leave first, Boss Qi.
Don't worry.
I'll go back and ask
the producers I know.
I'll ask if they have a suitable role for you.
What are you doing?
Teacher.
Why don't you discuss
such a big thing with me?
I'm Jian Xi's agent.
I have the right to deal with all her affairs.
You're not doing this for her.
You're hurting her.
I'm hurting her?
Do you know that
after she finished playing
Deling and Rong Lin,
the company rejected
all her movie activities
and only allowed her to take on
some commercial performances?
You and I both know that.
But you can't do that.
If we continue like this,
we'll only waste
our hard-earned money.
Teacher.
The conflict between Qi Wen Sen and I
is already very deep.
There's really no way to resolve it.
Do you think I don't know?
But you're taking action without permission.
You'll anger the company.
So what?
Look at the newspaper.
Look at what the newspaper said today.
The company has officially issued a statement.
It has never suppressed Jian Xi.
And it has arranged
all important jobs for her.
It's just because
it's involved in the confidentiality agreement.
It has never been released.
This time,
it's because Jian Xi's extreme lack of cooperation
has caused serious losses.
So,
the company has made a single-use agreement
to pursue the violation of the contract and compensation.
Of course I know that I have to compensate.
So I've already found the Xia family.
Xia family?
How can a company that has no strength
take on this matter?
Anxin.
I advise you not to play with yourself.
They are not easy to mess with.
I've been an agent for so long.
I don't need you to tell me
what I should do.
Fine.
From now on,
you are not Jian Xi's agent.
Why do you always
influence other people's thoughts?
Because you are invited by me.
Then you have to ask Jian Xi
if she is willing to do it.
Jian Xi.
You choose.
You can't stay there.
If you stay there,
it's a waste of youth.
Do you know that?
Jian Xi.
All the decisions I made
are for your own good.
I'm sorry.