You will be jealous of me
Strange eyes look at me
I don't have to care about breathing
Go down this road
Your beauty will soon be frozen
I don't want
I don't want to deceive myself
Miss you
Love you
No matter who you are
At that moment
A long age
Turned into a magical eye
Pass through the loneliness to find you
Wear the most solid gold armor
Hold the weapon in your hand
Use all your strength to fight for the most real self
No matter what the little tricks
No matter what rumors
I will definitely be invincible
I don't want you to be willing
Where is the gold?
In the past, I kept this sweet
No matter where your heart is
My heart is here
Even if the world is invincible
It's just one
Episode 16
Ji Qin, please have afternoon tea
Here, Tang Fei
Thank you
Here, Ji Qin, please have afternoon tea
Thank you, Ji Qin
Why are you here so early today?
I came to see how you are doing
Didn't you shoot the last farewell today?
Xiaoxiao, script
You give this to Jansi
Tang Fei, I want to ask
Look at this place
Will the old woman's uncle be more reasonable?
You two
Thank you
I think it's okay
Thank you for what?
Not bad
It's a good thing
Do you have to make others unhappy?
Did I say something wrong?
Lan Xi
Don't worry, I won't fight with a thick-skinned person
Thick-skinned? Who are you talking about?
I've heard of saving money
I haven't heard of saving money
You don't drink?
If you don't drink, you don't drink
You sent it yourself
Who likes to drink?
Lan Xi
I'm not angry with her
What is it?
Just an assistant of a thick-skinned person
She is just a mouthful
Not bad
It's okay, it's okay
It's okay
What's wrong with you?
Are you uncomfortable?
I also suddenly have a little pain
Do I want to buy you some medicine?
It's okay
It's an old problem
Just take a break
You have to shoot the rain scene later
How can I hold on?
Everyone is ready
Don't bother everyone
Finish this scene first
How about this? I'll pour you some hot water to drink
Okay?
Ready
Action
Baojun
I know you can hear
Open the door for me, okay?
Baojun
I know I wasn't brave enough before
I'm not persistent enough
Give me another chance
Can you give me another chance?
Baojun
What's wrong with you?
Are you uncomfortable?
You are sick
It's the cut-off
The cut-off is uncomfortable
Wasn't he fine just now?
What's wrong with him?
I have a stomachache
This kid is very stubborn
It's okay, you don't have to worry about it
Actors are busy shooting the day and night
Can't afford three meals
Stomachache
It's a very common thing
I'm worried he can't stand it
Anyway, as long as he thinks it's okay
There must be no problem
Don't worry, okay?
What do you know?
Don't guess what the girl is thinking
Baojun
Open the door, Baojun
Go out and see him
I've said everything I should say
Nothing to say
Baojun
If you don't go to see him
Please
He will stay until dawn tomorrow
Open the door
Even if you don't see him
Tomorrow's disaster relief meeting will also meet
Don't treat me like this
No
I will never see you again in my life
Baojun
Leave here with me
Leave with you
Yes, with me
Since the first day I saw you
I fell in love with you
I also swore on the case
I must pull you into my arms
Otherwise, I'm not Gu Yunsheng
I've been waiting for four years
Baojun
This vow has finally been fulfilled
I will not marry you
Baojun
Okay, cut
What are you two acting?
Can you do it?
I said, Jianxi
You are too cold-hearted
Yu Yaojun doesn't dislike Shen Lan
He loves her too much
It's all because of despair, you know
So I need you to show extremely
The feeling of suppressing your excitement
Just that kind
You think about it
Despair, you know
That kind of excitement
You know
I'm sorry
Despair, you know
That kind of excitement
What are you doing?
He is sick, he can't be in the hospital
Don't worry, director
You are his agent
You should respect his opinion
I am his agent
I am his friend
Don't be emotional, okay?
Then I am such a person
If you really know him
You should know that you can't stop him
Let's do it again
Okay, do it again
Okay
Jianxi
What's going on?
Go drive, take him to the hospital
Okay
Hurry, go
Tang Fei
What's going on?
Yes
Tang Fei
Tang Jian
You know you are sick
And you need to be on standby
Do you know that
This will delay
The progress of the whole crew
If you are sick
Just stay at home
And let me take care of you
You are strong
But people will hate you more
I'm sorry
Until you get it wrong
You have to change next time
You don't want everyone to worry about you
Why do you look at me like this?
Here
What do you want to say to me?
For taking care of princess Qingyi!
But why
Are you leaving now?
I'll go.
You see?
Your girlfriend is in the relationship
between you and this man…
Yuan activists suffer!
I know you're not asleep.
Listen to me carefully.
Listen to what I'm saying.
Love is like stomachache.
The more you endure it,
the more it hurts.
No matter how good the air is,
you can't hide it.
So don't listen to others.
Respect your heart.
You will know that you should leave.
Yanxi.
Director.
How are you feeling?
Much better.
Great.
We care about you.
By the way,
today is the last scene of our play.
It's also Yu Yaojun's solo play.
Look, you left Shanghai with Gu Yingsheng.
But you didn't stay with him.
You chose to sing alone.
You didn't get married.
After the plot developed for many years,
Shen Lan asked to see you again.
After you heard the news from the servants,
you cried with sadness.
I cried with sadness?
You want to show the character's
indecision and sorrowful mood.
Director.
Can I play this scene by myself?
Play by yourself?
Yes.
I want to try.
Okay.
You can do it.
Thank you, director.
Okay.
All the parts are ready.
Ready.
Action.
Director.
He didn't play the role.
Let him play by himself.
Okay.
Madam.
Mr. Shen insists on seeing you.
He said
he wants to see you.
He said he wants to see you.
He said he is old.
Maybe it's the last time we meet.
Let him go back.
Madam.
Do you want to sing another song?
Where is the zither?
Isn't the zither there?
How can I sing without the zither?
Madam.
The zither is there.
The zither
is gone.
Okay.
Cut.
Let's go.
Jianxi.
Director.
I think we should discuss this part.
Your performance and the plot are too big.
Director.
But I think Jianxi played it right.
Why?
Because I think
the plot of the play is too big.
I think the plot of the play is too big.
Jianxi,
how do you feel now because What kind of management you are holding?
I'm an adult.
What kind of management are you having?
Sheng Zhenyu said you work fast.
Yes.
replicate after you упyette.
How do you feel now?
I feel happy now.
Even if the zither is deep, I must be able to cut it off.
Even if people say it's delicious, I must keep my dignity.
I think this is the real Yu'ao Jun.
But don't forget,
your family still has Shen Lan's photo.
In the vending machine, there is the farewell of the king.
Have you really forgotten it?
Yes.
I will never forget it.
When I look back,
there is only a heart-full of sorrow.
I won't cry anymore.
Because the zither has been broken,
and the tears have dried up.
Let me think about it.
It makes sense for you to say that.
Director,
if that's the case,
can we finish it?
Okay.
Thank you all for your hard work.
Everyone, finish it.
That's great.
Thank you.
Thank you, director.
Yanxi.
That's great.
Thank you, everyone.
There are people over here.
Come on.
Good.
Yanxi.
There is a wedding banquet tonight.
Don't be late.
Don't worry.
We will be there on time.
Okay.
Yanxi.
Let's go home and rest.
What's wrong with you?
You should rest when you should.
You shouldn't rest when you shouldn't.
Why?
I don't like that kind of occasion.
You can't say that.
You are a girl.
Can you not show up?
But...
No buts.
Don't say that.
It will be bad if it gets out.
You must go.
Then I will ask my teacher.
Don't ask him.
He doesn't like that kind of place.
It's like you didn't ask him.
You can have fun tonight.
Be happy.
That's it.
Clean up.
Make yourself pretty.
Come on.
Take a picture.
Cheers.
Good wine.
Thank you, Meidao.
Come on.
Congratulations, Meidao.
Thank you, Meidao.
Meidao, you have worked hard.
We are also working hard.
We are working hard.
Come on.
Let's walk a little.
There are so many people.
Over there.
Let's go.
Come on.
I heard that
there are more and more people coming to your place.
Is it okay?
Yes.
I'm lying here.
The board of the tour is not bad.
What are you doing?
Let's sit here.
They are all sitting over there.
Why are we sitting here?
There are too many people over there.
It's too noisy.
I think we should sit here.
They are all sitting over there.
You forgot what we are doing.
Let's go.
Listen to me.
I don't want to go.
Finish what you should do.
Come on.
I...
Listen to me.
I really don't want to go.
I mean it.
I think this school is not bad.
We can develop our own
in the future.
Director Mei.
We are here.
Let's sit here.
Jianshi.
Come on.
Is Jianshi a good person in the drama?
Of course.
We should use her next time.
We will.
Definitely.
Come on.
I toast to you, Director Mei.
Happy cooperation.
Cheers.
Fei.
When will the next play begin?
Our Fei's next play
is to make a movie with our Ji Qin He.
It's called The Love of Qingcheng.
The Love of Qingcheng.
Why is the name so vulgar?
What did you say?
I said why is the name so vulgar?
Are you filming a story about the countryside?
Take a break.
Anxin.
We are a big production.
Some people can't make it if they want to.
You are jealous again.
Can you stop
looking at your eyes?
Your eyeballs are almost on the ground.
I envy you.
I don't want to make a movie
that makes me tired.
Fei.
When will you and Ji Qin
send sugar to the others?
Yes.
What do you know?
They must have been engaged.
You know,
Ji loves his daughter so much.
How could he get married so easily?
Right.
Last time,
I saw Fei at the jewelry store.
He must have gone to buy diamond rings.
So sweet.
Yes.
And he even goes to the hospital to see Ji Qin every day.
You said it's okay.
Yes.
If you are good friends,
how can you be so close?
Ji Qin.
Ji Qin, tell me.
Then, don't be a celebrity.
Be a reporter, okay?
Don't be so stingy.
Yes.
I'm just kidding.
Don't be stingy.
I'm a little tired today.
I'll go first.
He's leaving again.
Ji Xin.
So boring.
Right.
Why does he always
stay out of the show?
What's wrong with him?
Mei.
He's so lucky.
Jian Xu is too tired recently.
Let him go back and rest.
I'll drink with you.
It's really hard.
Let's go.
Come on.
Let's drink.
Cheers.
He's going home
after the hot pot party.
Yes.
He's playing hard to get.
Why is Jian Xu like this?
So many rumors.
He should be more open.
He's a weirdo.
Come on.
Let's drink.
Right.
It's okay.
Come on.
Let's drink.
Cheers.
Miss, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Anxin asked me to bring you this.
Actually, I've thought about it these days.
Let's be friends.
But this circle is really small.
We can't meet face to face.
What if we work together again?
You said we can't talk when we meet.
We should be more open.
Right?
Right.
For sweetie pie.
Was I 50?
I don't need to be 50.
I'm really well-off.
What about Yuwen Lin?
Is he still in the Ji 막ia guys?
How can you say so?
Those areUNKNOWN.
I think what you mean
is we don't have to talk all the time.
You know that.
I don't understand.
We don't stand home and do nothing.
We act this way.
I have something important to tell you.
Is that really the case?
Are you crying?
I'm not crying.
Yes, I'm not a mature person.
I'm the kind of person who can write whatever she wants on her face.
I've already worked very hard,
I've already worked very hard to pretend that I have nothing to do with you.
They're right.
Ji Qin is the most suitable person for you.
She's pretty and gentle.
What about me? I'm stupid, stupid and ridiculous.
I'm nothing compared to her.
And...
I'm not going to be your friend.
Why?
Because...
I...
I still like you.
What are you meidän is...?
You're in my heart?
I couldn't believe that you were Eagle Plus,
why do you...
You only bicycles,
What I said just now,
is not true.
What you said just now,
you won't take it back, right?
What did you say?
You said you like me.
I won't take it.
Then I'll ask you,
why did you run away?
They said you already bought the ring.
You already bought it for Ji Qing.
Did you see it?
I went to that kind of place
to buy this necklace.
The only person I love in my heart
is you.
I've never loved anyone else.
You won't take it off again, right?
It depends on your performance.
Does it still hurt?
It hurts.
It still hurts?
Then drink some medicine.
I don't want to drink today.
Drink some.
If you're so painful, I'll really worry about you.
I don't want to drink today.
Your health is important.
Then you give me a bath.
Okay.
Good morning.
You look in a good mood.
What kind of script do you want to see in the future?
Am I qualified to choose?
Usually, the characters come to pick me.
Come, come, come, look.
What?
You're in love?
You introduced it.
Then this is for you.
For me?
Yes.
You are my only one.
You won the global movie
public welfare love award.
These are all gifts from fans.
Are you happy?
Really? Of course it's real.
Do you know?
When the movie was released,
I got a lot of ads.
But I've already paid for it.
Do you know why?
Because now, it's not others picking us,
it's us picking others.
Really? Of course.
Let's go to battle.
Where to battle?
Qi Wen Sen later
doesn't know what to ask you for.
But no matter what he sends you,
you have to return it all.
Why? Because you have to give him some color.
You can be a good actress.
That's not good.
Nothing is bad.
Remember what I said.
All of it.
No more.
Let's go.
Mr. Qi, today's audition is still in the process.
We don't have much time.
I know he's busy.
You have to see him.
Let me introduce.
This is Director Li.
Director Li.
I really like your movie.
Jian Xi, let me introduce.
This is the famous director Li Hong.
His movie is in the Venice International Film Festival.
He won the best director and the best screenwriter.
He's the director of the movie.
Director Li.
Hello.
Let's sit down and talk.
Please.
Miss Jian.
I want to invite you to act in my movie.
Me?
But...
Director Li, you have a good taste.
Our film is great.
Do you want to see the script?
We'll take any role.
Director Li.
Thank you for giving us this opportunity.
We will do our best to play this role.
Thank you.
Why are you laughing like this?
Who made you laugh?
It's a matter of life and death.
Li Hong.
Did you see Qin Wen Sen's expression?
So happy.
I've never seen you so excited.
Do you know?
Many people want to go to Li Hong's movie.
But he chose us.
I'm so happy.
Drive carefully.
You're so excited that your eyes are closed.
You're the one who's holding me.
So I'm in a good mood.
I mean it.
You must believe me.
After you play Li Hong's movie,
you will be famous.
I don't know what role it is.
It doesn't matter.
We'll play it well.
De Lin.
He was born in the capital.
He came from abroad.
He came back to the country at the age of 17.
He speaks many languages.
He was recruited by Zi Xi.
He became a pre-eminent official.
Here you are.
Let me introduce.
This is the film writer, Mu Ge.
This is...
Leader, we're old friends.
Leader, come in.
Sit down.
Why is he here?
Zuo Zuo.
I don't want to play with him.
Did you forget what I told you?
Actors need to cooperate with anyone.
I don't care if you're so willful.
Zuo.
Zuo Zuo.
Can we start?
One more is not here.
Who?
Director Li.
Aren't you shooting the movie, The Love of My Life?
Yes.
But he had a car accident.
So he was delayed for three months.
So he came here.
Since everyone is here,
let's talk about the script.
The leading actress is De Lin and Rong Lin.
Please introduce the screenplay.
Okay.
The story happened in the time of Lie Qiang's pregnancy.
Empress Dowager Zi Xi knew Yu Geng's daughter
was pregnant.
So she asked De Lin and Rong Lin to join the palace.
She was a translator.
They lived in the old Qinghuang Palace
in a fashionable suit.
It was the first time they introduced modern dance and ballet to China.
It was the first time they taught porcelain painting and portrait painting.
It was also the first time
they used the female identity to win the favor of the strong.
It brought a fresh atmosphere
to the old Qinghuang Palace.
So it's a wonderful story
that's different from the old times.
So, Director Li,
is our Jansi not De Lin's?
De Lin's role
is played by Ji Qing.
I play De Lin.
Rong Lin's role is played by Jansi.
Director Li, are you kidding me?
I said before that
Jansi is De Lin's role.
And Ji Qing is Rong Lin's role.
Yes. De Lin's play is very complicated.
I'm suitable for this role.
And when Director Qi talked to me before,
he asked me to play Rong Lin.
So I play Rong Lin.
This is my decision.
But, Director,
as an actress, you should play various roles easily.
Right?
Zuo Zuo plays the empress of Guangxu, Jin Fen.
Director Li, what about me?
You play Zhen Fei.
Zhen Fei?
Zhen Fei only exists in Guangxu's memory.
There are only a few scenes.
I'm not a director who lets investors do nothing.
If you don't want to,
you can't.
I'm not a director.
I can only help you.
If you want to play Rong Lin,
you can play him.
I'll help you.
You can't play him.
You must play him.
I won't play him.
Zuo Zuo is not my character.
I'm not a director.
I'm a good actor.
I'm not a good actress.
Zuo Zuo is not my character.
I just don't understand.
What don't you understand?
What do you think about Director Li?
He totally messed up our plan.
Jian Xi is always good at creating complicated characters.
What's the point of this silly girl?
What's silly?
It's called being naive and romantic, okay?
That's silly.
I'm not silly.
I'm just convinced.
Jian Xi.
I think Ji Qin is more suitable for this role.
How about we change with him?
Didn't Director Li say that he has made up his mind?
But I don't think you're suitable for this role.
Rong Lin is naive and romantic.
He's passionate.
Jian Xi has never played a similar role.
This role is like a blank paper.
I don't know how to draw it.
Look.
The light of the night.
I hope you can integrate into Rong Lin's life.
Only then can you understand her.
Integrate into Rong Lin's life?
Or what do you want to change?
We live in the same environment.
But Rong Lin and De Ling are different.
Rong Lin is younger than her.
So she's been favored by her parents.
She's not like De Ling.
De Ling is strict with her.
She's gentle and introverted.
I've never been favored.
How do I know what it feels to be favored?
Are you trying to tell me something?
Of course.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
Are you trying to trick me?
Little beauty.
This girl.
Here.
You two try it first.
Take me as a magnet.
Walk two steps in front of me.
From here to there?
Yes.
Don't forget to match the identities of the two sisters.
Stop dawdling.
Hurry up.
You go first.
She's so elegant.
Yes.
Look at her walking in shoes.
She's so professional.
She knew it was a mistake at first sight.
Yes.
You go to the side first.
Jinahi, there you are.
This is wrong.
Jinahi, although you've done Yokohama Riki,
the fear is covered in it in your eyes.
What is it like?
I...
What's the use of the bow?
It's empty, dull and dull.
There's no smell.
This is not the De Ling and Rong Ling.
At least, it's not what I want.
Come on.
You two try again.
Jian Xi, you go first.
I...
No.
I've told you many times.
I can't feel your happiness at all.
Rong Ling is not like that.
Forget it.
You stay here.
Ji Qing, you go first.
Your Highness.
Rong Ling is naive and romantic.
She's as beautiful as spring.
If she offended you,
please forgive her.
What did you call me?
Your Highness.
You must be confused by those shallow and light tools.
Your Highness is indeed a name.
But this is the teaching behind eunuchs and officials.
Behind?
Have you ever seen a student from the Imperial School
call Jiang Jie as an old man in person?
You two are not good at all.
This is not De Ling and Rong Ling at all.
You two are like a bunch of fools.
I'm really crazy.
I thought your eyes could overcome the difficulties.
You two go back.
Director.
I'll tell Qi Wen Sen to change you two.
Calm down.
If you need anything,
tell them they can do it.
I can't understand the role.
I can't act well.
I don't accept a professional actor.
Director.
Give us more time.
Let's think about the script.
Yes, director.
Give us another chance.
Three days.
I'll give you three days.
If you still can't catch the character in three days,
just give up.
Shen Yan.
Director.
Let's shoot your scene today.
I've already prepared it.
You two really let me down.
Qi Qing.
I think you're doing a great job.
You're acting well.
You're gentle, modest, noble and generous.
I wonder what kind of mother Li Dao has.
What does the real De Ling look like?
What else do you want?
To play De Ling,
you hired a teacher to learn etiquette.
You also learned French.
What else do you want?
Not enough.
That's not enough.
Qi Qing.
Red light.
What are you doing?
Qi Qing, what's wrong with you?
You seem to be living in another world.
There are so many cars on the road.
If one of them is not careful...
What did you say?
There are so many cars on the road.
If one of them is not careful...
Not that sentence.
I said...
I said you seem to be living in another world.
Yes.
Another world.
Qi Qing.
What's wrong with you?
De Ling knows the language of the five countries.
He can draw, plant flowers,
dance the Western dance, and take pictures.
He has a Western life experience.
But he is quiet and gentle.
So he is different from Rong Lin who is carefree.
It's hard for him to understand his inner heart.
If you want to understand this person,
you have to understand his inner world first.
In his own world,
he is silently in love with Guang Xu.
But in real life,
he has buried his love.
He never showed it to anyone.
Right?
Yes. Yes.
I understand. Let's go.
Rong Lin.
Jian Xi.
Jian Xi, come out for dinner.
It's really Rong Lin.
What's wrong?
Shouldn't he be practicing?
When he first got the script,
he learned Japanese and French,
practiced etiquette every day,
and danced in Western clothes.
But now,
he has let it all go.
Let it all go?
These three days,
he played the zither and planted flowers.
Even the script is not good enough.
He has to practice.
He even stopped reading the script.
But Li Hong is going to face him tomorrow.
What does he think?
Will he give up completely?
You go with him.
I'm leaving.
Bye, boss.
Love is blind.
Jian Xi.
As a result of their other commonción,
這個是運 身 生 的 了!
Disneyland Beautiful Lesbians
Vijayities of innocent and everything else
I can make you happy
Okay.
Ji Qing! Ji Qing!
Why are you still drawing? We're leaving soon.
Ji Qing!
De Ling.
People in the palace won't call her De Ling.
What is it then?
Third Miss.
Because she ranks third,
that's why they call her Third Miss.
Third Miss?
Director, have some tea.
Okay, thank you. Leave it there.
Director, we're here.
Then let's start the performance.
Let me see your results.
What is she doing? Isn't it a performance?
Quiet.
The more I think of you, the more I feel lost
I'm too crazy to think about anything
Where should I put the red heart?
Just like this, I wait for someone until dawn