You will be jealous of me
Strange eyes look at me
I don't have to care about breathing
Go down this road
Your beauty will soon be frozen
I don't want
I don't want to deceive myself
Miss you
Love you
No matter who is far away
At that moment
The old age
Turned into a magical eye
Pass through the loneliness to find you
Put on the most solid gold armor
Hold the weapon in your hand
Use all your strength to fight for the most real self
No matter what the little tricks
No matter what rumors
I will definitely be invincible
I don't want you to be willing
Where is the gold?
In the past, I kept this sweet
No matter where your heart is
My heart is here
Even if the world is invincible
I'm only one you
The Long Ballad
Good evening, guests
Tonight, Gongyule donated 200,000 yuan
To buy a piano song by Miss Shen Yan
200,000 yuan
Thank you
I hope to do a great job for charity
So next, we will give the time to Shen Yan
I'm sorry
Good evening, everyone
In the center, if you want to study,
You can follow myasa Yihong
Seems like once you know this,
You will get your nous
Know it?
What?
Taylor Learner
Mr. Lu,
we can put the things I told you to do so.
All right. I'll do it right now.
Don't light the fire.
Quick, quick, chamberlain.
Yes, over here.
Take a picture.
A photo.
Stop doing this,性ish.
Please take a picture.
Come on, miss.
One more.
Miss.
Is this fake?
Yes.
What's going on, Miss Qin?
This is so ridiculous.
When did this happen, Miss Qin?
Are these all fake?
Who made these bad plays?
These photos are all fake.
This is too much.
So many.
This is not me.
Stop taking photos.
This is too much.
This is not me.
Where are you going?
I just saw the teacher.
You mean Lu Zhu?
Yes. He's at the door.
Why didn't I see him?
This...
He wouldn't come to this kind of place.
I think he came
only for one reason.
Tang Fei, you said...
What do you want to say?
Nothing.
Actually, Shen Yan
saved herself this time.
I think you should be happy.
I just think this is very strange.
I don't know who
prepared these photos
and posted them on today's party.
Actually, it doesn't matter who prepared them.
I think the most important thing now
is that you play this role well.
I'm going to the hospital.
Be careful.
Okay.
Thank you.
Bye.
Good night.
Today I asked you all over here.
Why? Tell me the reason.
Director Li, haven't you always not found a suitable candidate?
In the end, you even asked Shen Yan to play the role of Rong Ling.
This... Shen Yan can't do a duet with Jian Xi.
Rong Ling also has no charm to play.
This will drag the whole movie down.
Ji Qing, I don't need to do a duet with Jian Xi.
Also, I can work hard.
Yes, you can work hard, but this has nothing to do with me.
Director, please give me a little more time.
I will definitely play the role well.
I'm sorry.
I acknowledge every hardworking actor,
but I will never accept a low-class partner like you.
Ji Qing, what do you mean?
Didn't what happened yesterday prove everything?
You've been lying.
In order to defeat your opponent, you got the role of Rong Ling.
You created such a big scandal,
and you even completely ruined your opponent's future.
Ji Qing.
Today is Jian Xi, who will be next?
I feel scared to work with someone like him.
Ji Qing, you don't have the right to be the role.
Moreover, Director and President Qi are both here.
You can't be so unprofessional.
If you don't leave, I will.
Director, thank you for your care and guidance.
Please contact us for further information.
I won't let the crew suffer any loss.
Wait.
Ji Qing is right.
I can't accept you anymore.
Director Li.
You're fired.
No.
Director Li, President Ji has an investment.
He promised me that he would give me an important role.
Stop talking to my father.
As long as I say something,
he will never stand on your side.
Director Li, give me another chance. I will work hard.
Even if I don't play Rong Ling, I can play Zhen Fei.
Your behavior is too evil.
Our crew can't let you do this.
How could this happen?
Those are all conspiracy.
How could you believe the rumors?
I am innocent. I am innocent.
You will regret it.
President Ji. President Ji.
Let me go.
President Ji, you must help me.
Miss Shen, this is the office. Please don't do anything to your identity.
Let go.
President Ji, those photos are all fake.
Someone framed me on purpose.
Director Li wants me to leave the crew.
I don't want to lose this role.
Miss Shen.
Get up.
This matter was already known to everyone.
Even my daughter knew about it.
I think you are asking for it.
I am not capable.
So from today,
please don't come to me again.
Please go home.
Miss Shen, let's go out.
Let go.
I will go by myself.
I'll go by myself.
Oh, right. Did you hear?
Last night, something big happened.
What happened?
I heard that Shen Yan
was dancing in the basement bar.
Really?
Really. I saw the picture.
I saw the pores on his face clearly.
Oh my god.
Really?
He looked so pure.
I didn't expect that he was like that.
That's why
he's a dog that can't be bitten.
Right.
Stop talking. Let's go.
It's you!
You put the picture on purpose, right?
You've already calculated it.
You didn't announce it early or late.
You just went to the charity party.
I didn't see it.
You pretend to know nothing.
But you're so cruel.
This has nothing to do with me.
Who else would it be if it wasn't you?
Do you think everyone is as despicable as you?
Don't pretend in front of me.
I have nothing to pretend.
Why should I admit to something I've never done?
Oh, right.
What do you think those pictures are?
They're from He Cheng.
Why are you so nervous now?
It's my reputation.
I'll...
Since you suspect me,
you can call the media now.
We'll confront them face to face.
And check the pictures.
Are they real or fake?
You...
Anxin, let's go.
You can't live on your own.
This is...
I won't lose to you like this.
I definitely won't.
Teacher.
Jianxi?
Why are you here?
Teacher, I have something to tell you.
Teacher is going to class soon.
You can go out.
But...
Go out.
You go out first.
Then you talk to him.
I'll go.
Do you want to ask me
if I arranged what happened last night?
Yes.
Because I saw it at the concert.
I want to know if you put that picture.
I arranged it.
Jianxi.
Only by exposing Shen Yan's fake mask
will people suspect him.
Don't forget.
What he did to you before.
And now.
Everything I did.
I didn't make any lies.
Including this picture.
It's real.
Is there anything wrong?
These pictures are real.
I admit I used some means.
But I never make falsehood.
In your heart.
Am I so shameless?
I didn't mean that.
That's good.
You just need to remember.
Everything I did.
It's for your own good.
I hope you can stand in front of the spotlight.
Because of the pressure of society.
The company has already helped you.
Don't do anything.
Wait for a few days.
Keluo.
What?
I just want to say something.
You go first.
I'll be back in a minute.
Keluo.
I've lost my way.
I really don't know who is so cruel.
Fake photos.
Now because of this.
Rumors are everywhere.
The director wants to change me.
How much did I pay to have today?
But now.
But now everything is over.
I know.
I shouldn't have done that to you.
I'm just jealous of Jianxin.
Jealous of her love for you.
I really regret it later.
Why?
Why did you hurt her?
What do you want me to do?
As long as you admit your relationship with Jianxin.
The direction will change.
Even if they don't believe.
They won't put all the attention on me.
Keluo.
I know.
I know you don't want to hurt Jianxin.
But if you don't do that.
I will die.
I really will die.
You still don't give up?
Jianxin doesn't have this stage.
She still has Tang Fei.
If I don't have the chance to perform.
I will lose everything.
I don't want to go back to the day of the bar.
I can't stand it at all.
Don't be so cruel to me.
Please help me.
Please help me for the last time.
Shen Yan.
Put it down.
Stop acting.
Even if you go back to acting.
You can't act forever.
You will be exposed sooner or later.
Give up this opportunity.
Learn to face yourself honestly.
Face others.
Give up this fake life.
No.
I can't give up.
I can't.
I tried so hard to get everything.
How can I give it to others?
Ke Lu.
If you don't help me.
I will jump off from here today.
If you use all these acting skills in the movie.
You would have been generous.
It's a pity.
I'm leaving.
Where are you going?
To learn how to be pregnant.
You can do it yourself.
You don't want to help me.
You all don't want to help me.
Okay.
I will stand up myself.
Even if the whole world doesn't care.
Ke Lu.
Yanxi.
I'm going to leave here.
Where?
I don't want to go.
I don't like acting.
I'm not suitable for acting.
I really like singing.
Seeing you work so hard for your dream.
I'm actually ashamed.
For the so-called interests.
I gave up my original dream.
So I'm going abroad to study.
I'm going to dream.
Ke Lu.
Before you leave.
I came to see you.
I have something to tell you.
No matter what happens in the future.
Don't give up acting.
Even if I'm far away.
I will always be concerned about you.
I...
I hope you and Tang Fei can continue to be happy.
As expected.
Do everything to the end.
I'm sorry.
I didn't go to the end.
I'm leaving.
Ke Lu.
What time is your flight?
I'll send you.
No need.
Just send me here.
Why?
I've been deceived by the illusion.
I did a lot of wrong things.
I'm sorry.
But even if I did wrong.
I regret it.
I can only move forward.
There is no way to turn back.
So give me a reason to give up.
Just send it here.
Ke Lu.
You have to keep going.
Shen Yan.
Don't accept the interview if this happens.
No.
I have to go.
If you go.
It will only make it worse.
If I don't go.
They will think I'm guilty.
Shen Yan.
Get off.
But.
I want you to get off. Did you hear me?
Okay.
Shen Yan.
Are you okay?
Say something.
Shen Yan.
Where are you hurt?
Say something.
Are you okay?
Call an ambulance.
The ambulance will be here soon.
It's okay.
Hello.
Say something.
What's wrong with you?
Shen Yan.
Who allowed him to hold the press conference?
He insisted.
I just got the news.
He didn't decide it by himself.
He doesn't want to do it.
Are you Zhao Tian Li?
Yes.
I think.
I can't lie to the audience.
At that time.
I had to work three shifts a day.
The money I earned.
Was not enough.
Mom was still in the hospital.
Waiting for the medical fee.
When I was the poorest.
I could only drink water.
I knew a bar owner.
He said.
He could let me dance and make money.
At that time.
I really needed the money.
So I agreed.
I think.
As long as I can make money for mom.
To cure.
I can sell shoes.
Not to mention dancing.
I think.
I'm very lucky.
Why?
Why would someone.
Publish such a photo?
The company thinks.
These photos.
Will ruin my future.
They suggest me to deny.
But I can't lie.
I can't do it.
Actually.
Shen Yan is really hard.
He has to face the hardships of life.
And the impact of the scandal.
After the incident.
Shen Yan.
He didn't sleep all night.
After a fierce fight.
He decided to stand out.
To tell everyone.
What he has been through.
But on the way here.
Shen Yan had a car accident.
He was hurt in many places.
He should have been hospitalized.
But he insisted.
To explain to everyone.
Now.
It's all my fault.
I'm causing trouble.
And let my fans down.
I'm disappointed.
I'm sorry.
Really.
Shen Yan.
It's wonderful.
I really underestimated you.
Don't say that.
When I came.
I wanted to deny it.
Thanks to this accident.
I changed my mind.
Really?
After the accident.
Many people came to care about me.
This makes me feel.
A single denial.
Doesn't work at all.
It will make everyone more curious.
At this time.
I'd rather admit it.
I'll get everyone's forgiveness.
Think about it.
A poor girl.
For the sake of raising a family.
She made the wrong decision.
Everyone will understand.
And.
Will think.
I have the courage to admit my mistake.
You're right.
As long as you admit the past.
Can win the sympathy of the public.
Isn't it?
I really didn't expect.
You solved this problem so quickly.
And you did it so perfectly.
All this.
It's all because of Jian Xi.
I will never.
Forgive him.
Jian Xi.
What's wrong?
The punishment is cancelled.
You can act again.
Really.
Hello, director.
Jian Xi.
What are you doing at home?
Come to the set.
Because of your reason.
The shooting has been delayed for too long.
Come on.
I'll go right away.
Good.
Goodbye, director.
My chin.
Great.
Sorry, everyone.
Because I'm late.
It's okay.
Don't be surrounded.
We have to hurry up.
Get ready.
Director.
Jian Xi, welcome back.
Thank you, director.
Get ready.
I'll go and say hello to Ji Qing.
No, don't go.
Why are you looking for him?
Are you friends with him?
Remember, you are rivals.
I think.
Did he talk to you?
Let's go. Hurry up and put on makeup.
Ji Qing, what's wrong with you?
Nothing.
You always hate Shen Yan.
What about Jian Xi?
No.
I'm thinking for myself.
Shen Yan has a good reputation.
No strength.
Not worthy to stand with me.
What I need is not a embroidery pillow.
But a strong opponent.
So I can become stronger.
So you're talking about Jian Xi?
He's back.
The real war
has just begun.
Jian Xi,
we'll shoot the scene of the New Year.
We'll put money in the dumplings.
Whoever eats it will be lucky.
So Rong Ling will eat it.
I see.
Jian Xi, you just went back to the crew.
Get used to it.
Thank you, director.
Get ready.
Still alive?
Not so easy to die.
Then you should cheer up.
Don't look so down.
I don't want to
shoot with you again.
Can you say something nice?
It hurts.
What?
What? I'll eat it.
Or I'll grind your teeth.
Silly.
You curse me?
I won't eat it.
I have to eat something.
You're not smart.
Sorry.
That's the way he treats others.
Treats?
Zuo Zuo has no friends since childhood.
He doesn't know how to interact with others.
That's the way he treats others.
Don't mind it.
23 scenes, one shot, one kill.
Action.
What are you doing?
Eating dumplings.
Why are you eating so fast?
It's the new year.
They say if you eat the whole piece
of dumplings, you'll be rich.
You're a little fortune-teller.
Don't eat too fast.
It's bad for your health.
What's wrong?
Did you choke?
I ate the whole piece.
You're so lucky.
I can get pregnant.
Yes.
Sister, look at me.
I ate the whole piece.
Don't eat too much.
Cut.
What's wrong?
De Ling and Rong Ling are sisters.
I can't see the taste of
being intimate with you two.
Ji Qing, the line you just said
you don't care about your sister.
It's like being jealous.
And you, Jin Xi.
You're too immersed in your performance.
Before the shooting,
you should care about yourself
and not the play.
You should be smart.
You should know how to interact with others.
You must act in the play.
It's not your play.
I understand.
Okay.
Let's do it again.
Come on.
Ready.
Action.
I'm so talented.
Sister, look at me.
I ate the whole piece.
Don't eat too much.
Cut.
What's wrong with you two?
I can't see the taste of being intimate with you two.
It's not right.
If you two act awkwardly,
the audience will also be awkward.
Forget it.
Let's not shoot today.
Think about it.
Next scene.
Okay.
Don't move the track.
Come here.
What's wrong with him?
Enmity.
Enmity?
Jin Xi has enmity with me.
It's very strong.
So I can't be intimate with him.
It's too rare.
He can have enmity.
Come on. Ready.
Action.
30 scenes. One shot. One shot.
Sister.
Jin Xi.
Hold her warmly.
Hurry up.
What are you hesitating about?
Cut.
What's wrong with you two?
You can't cooperate at all?
Director. Today...
Forget it. Let's not shoot today.
Give me another chance.
Don't waste time.
You two don't have any tacit understanding.
Cut.
Director.
The scene is over.
Listen to me.
Take it.
Be careful.
Give me the camera.
Go now.
CDC, you are a thunder that stirs things.
Hardships.
Long harvest.
The
I mean teammates.
Dear contexts.
Dear enrollments.
Alright.
Why are you drinking?
Ji Qing.
Ji Qing, what's wrong with you?
He has outstanding performance skills.
And the spirit of living together.
I don't have all of these.
No matter he is beaten or beaten to pieces.
He can always come back.
It's not him who chooses to perform.
It's the performance that chooses him.
Ji Qing, don't be like this.
I will be surpassed soon.
What are you talking about?
Such spirit and talent.
I want it too.
Ji Qing.
I'm so jealous of him.
I'm really jealous of him.
I've never been so jealous of someone.
I...
Stand up.
Boss.
Stand up and follow me.
Cheer up.
Let me go.
Boss, Ji Qing is not feeling well today.
If you're not feeling well, then follow me.
Let me go.
What are you doing? Let me go.
What am I doing?
I want to ask you what you want to do.
What's wrong with me?
You can't act anymore, right?
You can't face the test.
You can't act out your sister's love, right?
I will be fine.
I will be fine tomorrow.
No, I will be fine soon.
You don't even have the most basic confidence.
How will you perform in the future?
I'm fine.
You're like this.
You still say you're fine.
A cold-hearted and ruthless businessman.
What do you know?
I know you.
You risked your life to suppress the test.
You completely forgot that you were acting as sisters.
Ji Qing, what's wrong with you?
You used to be so confident.
Now you're beaten by him.
I'm really scared.
As long as he's by my side,
I don't have any confidence.
I've never met a opponent like this.
Never.
Ji Qing, look at me.
No one will take anything away from you.
I won't allow it.
I said it has nothing to do with you.
Ji Qing.
As long as it's your business,
I can't just sit around and do nothing.
Don't force me anymore.
Let me help you, okay?
So?
Are you going to let the best actress perform this night?
Qi Wen Sen,
I'm telling you.
If you really want to do this,
I won't thank you.
And I will hate you even more.
Let's go.
No need to see me off.
Let's go back.
It's okay.
I want to spend more time with you.
Ji Qing.
Ji Qing saw me.
So what?
I sent my girlfriend to the scene.
Who cares?
That's not what I meant.
So what?
It's weird.
I'm not going to let you go.
It's nothing.
I'm going to work.
I'll be back early.
Okay.
Chang Wu, bring the ladder.
The actors will need it later.
Okay.
We're going to shoot a play
where the two sisters are talking.
Act well.
Don't mess up again.
Get ready.
Director,
do we need to add a little bit of sound?
The investigation is not coming.
Don't worry.
There won't be any problems.
Hurry up and get ready.
Can you do it so high?
It's okay.
I can get up easily.
You're a little flying blind.
Little swallow.
Let's go.
It's so beautiful here.
When I was in France,
I used to like to play in the trees.
Life here is too boring.
Just like the old man, the parrot.
It seems to be very happy every day.
Actually,
I was locked in that cage all day.
You,
be careful of the goods coming out of the mouth.
Sister,
look.
The sparrow.
Sister.
Why do you exist?
I hate you, Jixi.
If it weren't for you,
Tang Fei would definitely have been mine.
Be careful.
Jixi.
Hurry up.
Go and save her.
Jixi, are you okay?
Are you okay, Jixi?
Who?
Sister.
Thank you for saving me today.
Don't think of me too kind.
Shen Yan said,
I envy you.
I didn't admit it before.
But now I found out,
what he said is true.
What do you mean?
Just now,
the moment you almost fell,
I even thought,
if you weren't in the world,
it would be fine.
Do you know why?
Before,
I always thought,
I was talented in acting.
But I found out,
you are more talented than me,
and you work harder.
Gradually,
I am going to be surpassed by you.
It's not like that.
I...
Let me finish.
If I don't finish,
I'm afraid,
I won't have the courage to say it.
This time,
I will not be able to say it.
The best actress,
I did win you.
But,
it's not that glorious.
I really,
I really regret it.
So I made up my mind,
I must win you once.
But,
I didn't expect,
it's not that easy.
And,
the worst thing is,
I like Tang Fei so much,
the person he loves,
is you.
This thing,
I only realized this time,
the feeling of jealousy.
The first time I realized,
the person I love the most,
the feeling of being taken away.
I really, really like acting.
And,
I really love Tang Fei.
But,
I lost everything.
I lost everything,
because of you.
I can't act well.
Now,
I'm full of jealousy.
I really don't know why,
I became like this.
Ji Qing,
I'm the same.
I've been walking,
I've encountered many setbacks.
Several times,
I was about to leave,
and stayed at last.
You may not know,
I cried many times,
because of you.
Because I feel that,
I'm nothing compared to you.
I still can't forget the fantasy.
The rain in the fall,
it's like a scar.
The moonlight shines tonight,
it's a little bit bright.
With this loneliness,
it's like a long story.
Watching the prosperity and prosperity,
watching loneliness turn into frost.
Watching the tide rise and fall,
the people are warm,
the sky is dark and the sky is bright.
Too many expectations,
in the end, you become desperate.
Watching you come and go,
holding on tightly to the wind and frost,
everything is in a trance.
Too stubborn,
I have to be young and crazy.
There is a lie,
I don't forget the fire.
Looking back,
there will be regrets.
You and I,
we are lost on the road.
The sea is crazy,
don't think about anything.
The heart is crazy,
where is the sea?
It's like this,
waiting for a day,
it's like this,
waiting for a day.