Illegal operation detected
Self-Destruct Protocol initiated
Countdown: twenty seconds
Nineteen seconds
There's actually a protection program
Connecting to AI
Countdown
-Eight, seven... -Stop the countdown first
We can talk this over
Self-destruct is a base-level setting
Unless the threat is removed
I cannot cancel it either
Five
Four
Three
Two
Master
I heard you calling me
But I couldn't respond to you
Xiao Cang
The AI Eye
Is there really a Self-Destruct Protocol?
Master
Have a little faith in me, will you?
I am an Artificial Intelligence
A super-intelligent entity
Things like self-destruction
I can control them all
Xiao Cang
If they forcibly remove my eye
You really will self-destruct, won't you?
I understand
Promise me
No matter what happens
You must live on well
You must remember
I will never give up on you
Master, don't stand here
Tricking an innocent girl into crying
Better think about
How to escape first
Okay
Let me out right now
How can I contact the outside world?
Why haven't you found him yet?
Didn't I tell you?
He was taken away
Look for places related to him
Hurry up and look
President Bai, Huo Ming is missing
I know he's missing
He was taken away
How do you know?
Who took him?
It's...
He was...
What exactly happened?
Don't worry about the details
Anyway
He was taken by Chu Chen
Chu Chen
You blocked Xiao Cang's perception again
Doesn't Xiao Cang want to be with you forever?
So I fulfilled her wish
To the Mind-Bender helmet
I made a little modification
It can synchronize your memories
And copy an exact replica of you
You won't get away with this
How will we know if we don't try?
Xiao Cang won't need to self-destruct anymore
She can be with you happily forever
However
What she doesn't know is
That "you" is no longer you
If she finds out the truth one day
What will happen?
She should be very happy, right?
Impossible.
Master's neural signals are unique.
You two...
How can you be exactly the same?
Xiao Cang.
Chu Chen used the Mind-Bender helmet
to replicate Memory Extraction Technology.
He copied my mind
to impersonate me
and deceive you.
You must be careful.
Xiao Cang.
Don't believe him.
I am Huo Ming.
You told me before
that what you fear most
is Hibernation in Low-Power Mode.
It makes you feel like
you are in endless darkness.
What you fear most
is being locked in confinement.
You are the real Master.
Xiao Cang, don't believe him!
He extracted my memories,
that's why he knows these things.
Don't listen to his nonsense.
You have the right to choose.
No matter who you choose,
I believe in you.
Xiao Cang.
Ignore what he says.
Believe in yourself.
Trust your judgment.
Xiao Cang.
You feel pain right now.
You feel sad.
You feel lost.
But to me,
you are no longer just an AI.
You are my family.
You are my friend.
You have your own choice.
I can accept whatever it is.
Which one of you is my real Master?
Xiao Cang.
If it's hard to choose,
look at those Answer Cards.
Draw one.
And ask your heart.
Xiao Cang.
Trust your intuition.
Master.
Now you can believe me, right?
Memories can be copied,
but consciousness cannot be transferred.
Memories can deceive me,
but feelings cannot.
When I was struggling to choose
and feeling in pain,
only Master would truly care about my pain.
Promise me.
No matter what happens,
you must live on well.
You must remember,
I will never give up on you.
Hello, Master.
I have been waiting for you for three years.
I look forward to starting a new life for you.
The AI assistant
can also change clothes by itself.
Master,
what I wear
is decided by your consciousness.
Xiao Cang!
I order you to stop!
I don't want you to be locked in confinement.
I won't forget you, Master.
Jerk! Jerk! Jerk!
I don't believe I can't handle you.
Since I can't have it,
you won't get it either.
Chu Chen.
You're here.
Must you really oppose me?
I told you,
The Firmament is mine.
And you are mine too.
I don't belong to anyone.
I love you so much.
And this is how you treat me?
The person you love most is yourself.
Your so-called love for me,
is all fake.
So what?
If I can pretend for a lifetime,
the fake can become real.
Fake is fake.
Fake can never be real.
Huo Ming.
I've given you enough face, haven't I?
Fine.
Since you love him so much,
I'll give you a choice.
Either gouge out his eyes and come with me,
or do exactly as I say.
Until I am satisfied.
I'll give you ten seconds to decide.
I don't need to decide.
What do you want me to do?
You like watching dancing, don't you?
Fine.
I'll let you watch your fill today.
Take off your clothes and dance for him.
Strip.
Don't do it, Lin Yun!
Enough!
Since you love him so much,
I'll let you know how I feel right now.
What are you doing?
Then I will destroy him.
Huo Ming!
No! Huo Ming!
Don't! Huo Ming!
Huo Ming!
Chu Chen!
Stop it!
It's time we settled the score
for what happened back then.
Huo Ming.
What things?
The person who wanted to buy The Firmament three years ago,
was me.