MISSION NATION CHURCH
♪ The Lord's great grace has taught me ♪
♪ The Lord has bestowed on us his grace ♪
♪ When I feel the Lord's miraculous love ♪
♪ The Lord's boundless grace ♪
♪ When I follow the Lord ♪
♪ He answers my prayers ♪
♪ He gives me peace ♪
♪ When I follow the Lord ♪
♪ He answers my prayers ♪
♪ He gives me peace ♪
REVELATIONS
Hello, sir.
Glad you came.
-Let's go get something to eat.
-Sure.
-That man followed you?
-Don't look at him. Don't look.
You're popular, A-yeong.
That old guy followed you? Huh?
Want me to kill you? Shut up.
It's much better now. Yeah.
Oh, right, I see.
Sorry, excuse me.
Hello there.
Ah, you haven't come to visit us before.
I'd like to introduce myself.
I'm Pastor Sung Min-chan.
I was just, uh, passing by
and saw this church…
Ah.
Would you like some coffee?
I'll get it started.
I'm busy.
I need to get going.
Wait.
One cup won't take long.
-I swear he followed me.
-You're imagining things again.
-Sorry about that.
-Sorry, ma'am.
Oh. Are you okay?
Uh, are you feeling sick?
Do you want me to call 911?
I'm okay. Don't worry.
Let's go.
-Okay, bye.
-Bye. See you next week.
Watch your step, it's slippery. Slow down.
I think
the large will fit you well.
You stopped by on a whim,
but I hope you join us here again.
Do you live in the area?
Yeah, kinda.
Then we'd love to have you.
It would be great if you became a regular.
Are you a churchgoer?
Yeah, somewhat. A long time ago, as a kid.
Oh. That happens a lot.
People who attend church regularly
when they are young
can drift away as they grow up.
Only to return to God eventually.
In that process, you receive revelations
and you come to accept
God's place in your life.
Oh, right.
I just realized that
I forgot to ask what your name was.
What is your name?
Kwon Yang-rae.
What's that for?
This is just…
REGISTRATION FORM
This… This is for new member registration.
We never used to
need to get all this information before,
but everything's become digitized
these days,
so the manual forms come in handy
from time to time.
We're a… We're a church plant,
and I'm embarrassed to say…
-…I'm not used to this.
-Look.
Like I said, I was just in the area.
This isn't some complicated form.
It's just, uh…
It's easy and simple to fill out.
Name and phone number
so we can contact you.
Yeah, it's not much.
What else? Right. One second.
A photo would certainly help us out
as well.
This is great. I'll print it right now
and once it prints, I'll delete this.
See? Look. Your photo's been deleted.
Oh, no. Um…
Excuse me, sir,
I have to make an urgent call.
I'll be right back.
Yeah, so this, it's just a simple form,
so if you could please fill it out.
I'll only be gone for a moment.
I'll be right back.
Hey, Mr. Sung.
Yes, what's going on?
Well, your hunch was right.
I think your wife's been seeing
her personal trainer for quite some time.
They meet about three times a week.
I'll send you some photos now.
Take a look.
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate it.
Not at all. You've been extremely helpful.
What do you think?
Should I collect more evidence?
It depends.
What do you mean by "more evidence"?
They meet pretty often,
so the next time they go into a motel,
I can take pictures and videos
of them making out, having sex,
and also look for stuff
like condoms or tissues with semen.
If they don't use condoms,
my boys can find and collect traces
of semen on your wife's body.
So no worries there.
So do you want me to try
to gather more evidence or not?
Hello? Mr. Sung?
Wait, sir, don't go yet.
We haven't had time to talk.
Um, I have business I need to get to.
I've filled out your form.
Where's my shoes?
These?
You shouldn't fold the back of your shoes.
You'll ruin them.
Here, put them on.
You are welcome.
Church is a place for sinners.
You're always welcomed here.
God loves us all.
A new member?
Did that man register?
Well… kind of.
Honey, aren't you gonna be late?
-Yeah. I'll meet you outside, all right?
-Sure.
What's up, Dad?
Now?
Nothing. I'll be home soon.
We can eat together.
Hey, honey,
just drop me off at the subway.
What reunion is this?
A college reunion.
Did you forget?
I might be home late.
You'll pick up Yeon-u, right?
Oh. Why do they have to work
on weekends too?
Never mind.
It's better
they finish this new building soon,
so we can get some more parishioners
in this area.
What is that?
Can you pull over here? Pull over.
HEAVENSFOLK CHURCH
Oh, my gosh.
They're building a new church here.
Hold on. It's Pastor Jung's church!
OWNER: JUNG GUK-HWAN
Wow! Maybe he'll ask you
to come be the pastor.
He brought you here
to grow that tiny church.
This must be his plan.
You picked up everybody that came
to his morning prayer service for years.
It's paying off.
You should go pay him a visit today.
Right? Don't you think?
I'm home.
No construction site work today?
It stopped raining.
Yeah, it's supposed to rain a lot later,
so they sent us home.
The assistant manager'll wrap things up.
Come on. Time to eat.
What's all this?
You cooked up a feast.
Tomorrow's your first day on the new team.
You should eat some meat.
It's no big deal.
How's the construction? Almost done?
We'll remove the scaffolding in two days.
Nice. So it's almost done.
Anyway, you were on a good team,
but you picked a hard route
to a promotion.
Did you have to volunteer
to join the Violent Crimes Unit?
It's great.
I'm closer to home
and my commute was stressful.
Kwon Yang-rae, that shithead.
He's been released in this area.
Really?
You already knew that.
This tastes great.
Did you buy the yangnyeom sauce?
No, stop trying to change the subject.
Hey. You're not tailing him, are you?
Let it slide. Hmm?
Live your life and move on.
Show me the building
after the scaffolding comes off.
I'm curious what it'll look like.
Yeon-hui, you're all I have now,
you know that.
If something bad happens to you too…
You do the dishes.
SKY PEACE CHURCH
Come in.
Pastor.
Look who it is, hello.
Oh. Are you all right?
Sit down.
Make sure you take care of yourself.
You always work so hard.
No, I'm fine. It's not that bad.
I know you've been
working pretty hard yourself.
How's the church been doing?
I don't work as hard as you.
I did want to mention that,
just before I came,
I managed to register a new member.
Don't be so obsessed
with registering new members.
All right? Just remember that
you're a messenger of God,
spreading his good word
on this world's barren land.
That's all the purpose
we need to keep going.
I'll be sure to remember that.
I saw… Was it "Heavensfolk Church"?
-Hmm, you saw the poster.
-Yes.
I think… that my wife
was more surprised than I was.
Why didn't you mention it to me?
Sorry. I've been so scattered.
Who would you recommend for that church?
Recommend?
Yes, for the Heavensfolk Church.
I'm curious about who you'd recommend.
You've been in that area for a long time,
and I thought I should ask you.
Who do you think would be a good candidate
as the pastor in charge there? Huh?
Ah, hmm. As the pastor…
Is there anyone who comes to mind at all?
Not yet, um…
I'll get back to you
once I think about it a bit.
All right, sounds good.
Let's put our heads together.
God will reveal to us
the right person for the job.
Hurry. Hurry!
I told you to bring your umbrella.
Let's head inside.
Quick, so we don't get soaked.
Oh, Min-chan.
Oh, Hwan-su.
One minute.
Oh. Why'd you stop by? It's been a while.
Ah, I'm headed out.
I came to see Pastor Jung.
Ah, you came to see my father.
Oh. My dad's building a new church.
Did you know? It's in your neighborhood.
Uh, yeah, I mean… I've heard about it.
The church elders keep saying
they want me to lead that church,
but I'm under so much pressure.
Well, actually, during our meeting,
your, um, your father said
he was still looking for the right person
and asked for my opinion, so…
Why would he ask you for your opinion?
Why would he ask you that?
Why did my father ask for your opinion?
Ugh, he's out of his mind
and putting me in a tough spot.
No, you're obviously
the one who should do it.
You've been growing your church for years.
Let's be honest.
What do I know about leading a church?
I'm definitely underqualified.
Hey, I'll talk to my father for you.
No, it's all right. Don't bother.
You and I both know
that it's not our call.
And our Almighty God
will show us the right person.
-We have to have faith.
-We're heading in now.
Hold on. I have to get going
but I'll call you. We'll talk again.
-Sure.
-You got this, okay?
-Oh, okay. Thanks.
-You got this!
-Have a good day.
-Sorry 'bout that. Let's go.
Dear Heavenly Father,
please watch over me,
so that my pure faith in you,
my Lord, who's carrying all my burdens,
is no longer shaken or swayed
by worldly temptations.
I ask that…
I ask that
if my leading the new church happens to be
in alignment with what you have planned,
I am available
and more than happy to abide.
Please enlighten us all, as we are--
WIFE
LEE SI-YEONG
-Hello?
-Honey, where are you?
Is Yeon-u with you?
Yeon-u? Why would he be with me?
I asked you to pick up Yeon-u
because I had my college reunion.
Right. Well, uh, I had something to do.
What did you have to do?
The service ended hours ago!
What are we going to do?
What do we do?
Calm down.
What did the daycare teacher say?
She said that some man came
and took Yeon-u!
I assumed it was you.
What do we do? What are we going to do?
Yeon-u's been kidnapped!
Honey, go to the daycare center
and ask the description
of the man who picked him up.
I swear, if Yeon-u is hurt,
it's all on you.
Do you hear me?
SEX OFFENDER REGISTRY
KWON YANG-RAE
9, 8-GIL, MYEONGHWA-RO, MUSAN CITY
Hey, Yeon-ju.
Are you still not talking to Dad?
You should really call him.
Mmm, okay, okay, I will.
Why do you sound like that?
Are you sick?
Yeon-ju?
It's not that.
I just woke up.
You just woke up?
Do you know what time it is?
You moved to the new place
so you could commute less and study more.
You are studying hard, right?
Yeah.
I'll call you later, okay?
All right. Call me if you need anything.
Yeon-hui.
Do you remember?
Remember the day I moved
into my own apartment?
We said it was like a housewarming party…
and took this photo.
You look great in this picture.
But you know what?
I regret getting my own place.
Do you know what I kept telling myself
when I was with him?
"Someone will rescue me eventually."
You graduated
from the National Police University.
You're so smart,
you must have known something was off.
But instead of you,
the person walking through that door…
was always him.
Yeon-hui.
I was waiting.
Why?
Why didn't you even try to come save me?
Where were you?
In ten meters,
you will arrive at your destination.
911. What is your emergency?
Yes, hello, uh…
My… My kid…
My child, uh, my child has gone missing.
You're reporting that
your child is missing?
Kwon… Kwon Yang-rae, Kwon Yang-rae.
The, uh, the rapist
that lives in the area.
He's here.
Uh, I mean, I'm in front of his house.
Sir, all right, please calm down.
Explain to me what's going on.
He's planning to…
He's going to bury something.
He's got a shovel.
I see him with a shovel.
Sir, are you saying that
you witnessed a crime?
No, I said my child has gone missing,
but right now--
When was your child last seen?
I said Kwon Yang-rae,
the rapist in our neighborhood.
Look him up and see!
Well, sir,
have you reported your child missing?
Send some officers to meet me
in front of Kwon Yang-rae's house.
Right now I'm in front of--
Are you there?
FOXHILL PASS, 1.5 KM
Pastor, I'm surprised to see you.
You haven't been following me, have you?
Is everything all right?
I'm gonna head home now.
I hope you have a good night.
Yeon-u.
Pastor.
What do you think you're doing?
Please move.
WIFE
LEE SI-YEONG
I found Yeon-u.
You know Yeon-u's friend, No-el?
No-el invited Yeon-u over,
so No-el's dad picked them up.
He said he told the teacher.
I guess the message was lost
during the school shift change.
Anyway, the responsible thing
would have been for No-el's parents
to have called us to let us know.
If I told you,
you would tell me
not to play with No-el again.
Hey!
I told you I'm talking to your father!
Stop your crying!
Where are you? Why aren't you home?
Are you Inspector Lee Yeon-hui?
Hello, ma'am.
I'm your teammate
in Violent Crimes Unit 4, So Eun-gyu.
It's a pleasure.
Ah, hi.
You're already being requested
by the captain.
There's a briefing for a new case,
so, uh, are you ready to go?
Sure.
It's not
a simple disappearance case.
Oh, here they are.
Before we begin the briefing,
meet Inspector Lee Yeon-hui,
a new member of Violent Crimes Unit 4.
Say hello.
A big case broke out last night,
so it's a bit hectic.
Let's get back to it.
At 10:30 p.m. last night,
Sung Min-chan,
the head of Mission Nation Church,
called the police.
He said Kwon Yang-rae,
a two-time convicted sex offender,
seemed like he might be up to something.
Kwon Yang-rae wears an ankle monitor
and lives in the area.
Last night, he cut off his ankle monitor
and has disappeared.
And a middle school girl
has been reported missing.
Her name is Shin A-yeong.
She attends Mission Nation Church.
After the service,
she and her friends left to sing karaoke
and went home.
But Shin A-yeong never arrived.
Unit 1, I want you to start
interviewing Shin A-yeong's friends.
Yes, sir.
Unit 4, interview the man
who called this in last night.
Yes, sir.
All right. Get moving.
Crime Scene Team
will be here within five minutes.
-Ah, you're here.
-Hey.
Oh, man.
I think Kwon Yang-rae
really did live here.
I don't know how he did.
What? There's no power?
No. His electricity's cut off.
Hey, try moving all the furniture out.
Yes, sir. Give me a hand.
Huh.
I found something.
Whoa.
This bastard…
is some kinda psychopath.
CHARGE FOR INVOLUNTARY MANSLAUGHTER
TURNING YOURSELF IN
FOR INVOLUNTARY MANSLAUGHTER
Hello?
Yes?
Uh, Pastor Sung Min-chan, correct?
That's right. How may I…
We're from the police department.
We're following up on your call to us
reporting Kwon Yang-rae last night.
You said it looked like
he was going to bury a dead body.
I did.
Kwon Yang-rae, uh, um…
He, uh, he came to my church yesterday.
When he was here,
he seemed a little suspicious.
I noticed he had on an electronic anklet.
I was surprised to see that.
Then I got a call from my wife
that my ch… child was missing.
I suspected Kwon Yang-rae,
which is why I went to his house but…
But what?
Um, I saw him holding a shovel.
I assumed he was about to bury a body,
so I called the police and told them that.
What about your child?
Oh, uh…
We were mistaken.
He ended up being all right.
We found out that…
he was at a friend's house.
Ah, I see.
Hmm. Well, there's also
the case of a missing middle school girl.
Shin A-yeong.
A-- A-yeong from our church?
Yes.
What-- What happened to A-yeong?
May I look in here?
Yes, of course.
Sure.
Kwon Yang-rae,
how long was he here?
Uh, I asked him to fill out
our new member registration form,
but he left
while I stepped out to take a call.
Tell me, Pastor,
what did you do
after you called the police?
I headed straight home after that.
Mind you, we have no evidence
of him abducting Shin A-yeong yet.
We're still
in the investigating stages right now.
So please give us a call
if you happen to remember anything else.
Here's my card.
Will do.
PASTOR, I HAVE A CONFESSION TO MAKE
YESTERDAY, I
MIN-CHAN… LET'S TALK IN PERSON,
COME TO MY CHURCH NOW…
Pastor Jung.
I've got a big problem.
I guess you already heard…
the news about my son.
I taught him to never do anyone wrong.
What was he thinking?
I can't believe he's having an affair
with a church member.
Um, he just… He only got married recently.
Well, and…
…you know how tender-hearted Hwan-su is.
He is too tender-hearted for his own good.
That's why he let her seduce him.
I told him to end it.
I told him to end things with her
as soon as possible.
I said he should go back to his wife
and repent.
But that girl…
The girl he had an affair with…
she posted their relationship details
on the church's website.
Here, look wh… what she wrote.
I'm telling you.
She approached him on purpose! Right?
Goodness.
He's going away.
I'm sending Hwan-su abroad for a few years
to do missionary work.
He needs to get away from this.
This is insane.
How could he let lust blind him
when his duty is to serve God?
I've… always told him to live his life
for God and nothing else.
Min-chan.
Maybe this…
was all a part of God's larger plan.
Pastor Jung…
does it… smell like… something sweet?
About the Heavensfolk Church,
that I'm building…
I was hoping…
that you could be the pastor in charge.
I suppose that this is God's will.
And we must always follow His will,
as you know.
Min-chan.
Lead Heavensfolk Church.
Do your very best.
Expand it into something amazing.
Thy will be done.
God's will…
thy will be done.
Kwon Yang-rae's probation officer
said he showed no strange signs at all.
And he worked hard
at the demolition company.
He also hasn't missed
a single session with me.
His condition, to my knowledge,
had improved quite significantly.
Do you know when he drew this?
Our forensic team's working on it,
but it looked like it was drawn recently.
Recently?
He showed absolutely no signs…
but committed a crime?
That must be
Kwon Yang-rae's psychiatrist.
Mental illness can be
caused by many things,
including genetics.
It's hard to narrow it down
to one specific cause.
Being abused by his stepfather as a child
must've played a key role.
How was he abused?
His stepfather beat him to the point that
he ended up with a dent in his skull.
He also dunked his hand in boiling water.
He was waterboarded,
lying face up on the bathroom floor.
As well as being sexually abused.
Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
Mr. Kwon Yang-rae…
…has over a hundred scars
remaining on his body.
These scars are from the abuse
he suffered for ten years.
Doctor, in your opinion,
could he develop
into a well-adjusted adult?
Yes, not everyone
with these traumatic experiences
develop into criminals.
In this particular case,
things could've been different,
had he been treated in time.
Mr. Kwon Yang-rae
was abused for ten years.
It was only at the age of sixteen,
after he was sent
to juvenile hall for assault,
that he was able to escape his stepfather.
When he was quite young, he--
No, wait. What are you doing?
Yeon-hui.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you giving him an excuse
to escape punishment?
You laughed?
Please calm down.
-Get off of me!
-Come with us, ma'am.
-Yeon-hui!
-He's pure evil!
You need to leave.
Whose side are you even on?
Let go! I said let go of me!
Hey!
Dr. Lee Nak-seong.
It's been a while.
Lee Yeon-hui, Violent Crimes Unit.
Have we… Have you and I met?
We've met before.
Kwon Yang-rae's case from five years ago.
The victim was abused
and held against her will.
She managed to escape
and called the police.
Her name was Lee Yeon-ju.
I'm her sister.
I've always wanted to ask you a question.
What were you thinking?
Why did you create a reason
for Kwon Yang-rae to get away with it?
At that time…
I was testifying as an expert witness.
You're aware I'm a psychiatrist?
Well, I study and treat mental illnesses
for a living.
You "treat" them?
How long have you been treating that guy?
Where is Shin A-yeong?
This is all your fault.
All this happened because
you created an excuse for that devil.
It's repeating again,
just after a few years, because of you.
He's not the devil.
He's just a human being. A broken one.
Do you want to save Shin A-yeong?
I suggest that you learn
more about Kwon Yang-rae.
Don't get me wrong,
I understand you feeling that way,
being the victim's family.
But as a detective…
I should get going.
His story went viral after that trial.
Everyone talked about him
as though he deserved pity.
As if he had no choice…
SYMPATHY FOR THE OFFENDER, WHY?
…but to turn out the way he did.
Shortly after that…
my sister, Yeon-ju, took her own life.
She had survived horrific torture
and managed to escape,
but you…
You killed her.
Pastor.
Pastor. Pastor Sung, right?
-Yes, uh…
-I'm… A-yeong's mother.
A-yeong's mother!
Uh, what brings you here?
My daughter, A-yeong…
Wh… Why is my daughter…
Why don't we-- Le… Let's go…
Let's go inside and talk.
Come with me. Okay?
What happened to my…
Here you go. We'll find A-yeong.
We'll do everything we can.
I have to find her.
Um, but, Pastor…
Hypothetically…
speaking…
What if s… something
already happened to A-yeong?
Don't speak like that.
How could you even think about that?
I know, but if…
What if I…
If the police suddenly call and…
…tell me that something happened to her
and everyone says I have to confirm--
Ma'am, please. You must stay strong.
A-yeong must be alive.
Right, Pastor? She must be, right?
My daughter has to be alive.
Yes. Of course, she is.
Let us pray.
Almighty God, our dear Lord, our shepherd.
You guide us and you protect us
every single step of the way,
so you must know where A-yeong is
and what kind of situation
she is in right now.
Even if your little lamb, A-yeong,
is in a dark place,
we believe that she is alive
and that you are with her.
Lord, please be with us
in this distressing situation.
We desperately need your help.
This is camera footage
near Kwon Yang-rae's place
a day before his disappearance.
Looks like he deliberately damaged
four security cameras near his home
over the weekend.
He seems to have come up
with a thorough plan a few days prior.
What was the control center doing
while he was breaking all those cameras?
A lot of cameras broke
due to lightning and heavy rain,
so they thought that was the case.
Any home security or dashcams
in the vicinity?
We checked but because of the rain,
couldn't secure a visual.
That's frustrating.
Yes.
Ah, okay, got it.
-Captain, they found Kwon's car.
-Where?
-Near Foxhill Pass on Cheonil Mountain.
-Come on, everyone, get moving.
-What're you waiting for? Go!
-Yes, sir.
I can just take the bus, Pastor.
It's better if I drive you.
You have to keep thinking positive.
I have an idea. How about
we all get together and pray?
I'll assemble a community prayer vigil
and everybody that loves A-yeong
will be there.
-We can be sure--
-Hello?
Um, what about A-yeong?
No, I… I want to be there.
No, I have to be there! I'm her mother!
Send me the address.
Okay.
What is it? What happened?
They found that asshole's car.
What do I do?
Where is it? I'll take you.
We will
begin searching Areas 1-3.
The Forensic team is on it now.
Copy.
There has to be something.
We need to find it.
Requesting additional support
for Areas 1-4.
That bastard.
I wonder why he came here.
Looks like he abandoned his car.
Where is he?
Do you think A-yeong escaped
on their way here?
Possible.
What is all this?
Find something?
Forensics!
Hey! Try to search over there.
-Find anything?
-No, sir. There's nothing here.
-Why are you being like this?
-Sir, please…
Okay, okay, I know.
I'm her dad, so let me in.
Why are you being like this?
Ugh! Hey! Let me in, just for a minute.
Get out of my way!
-Honey!
-You can't go in!
Please calm down!
-Where's A-yeong?
-Honey! They're still searching for her.
-Let's go that way.
-A-yeong!
You can't go in.
We are A-yeong's parents!
You need to tell us what's going on!
-A-yeong!
-Barricades…
What's going on?
Shin A-yeong's parents.
-A-yeong!
-Let us look for her.
Guys, it's okay. It's okay.
You must be A-yeong's parents.
Have you found her?
No, not yet.
We haven't found any clues yet.
You found his car though.
Right, we did,
but we're still investigating.
Did you not find a body?
"Body"?
"Body"? Do you mean…
Is my daughter…
Is my A-yeong…
No, ma'am.
-My A-yeong!
-Oh, no.
-Careful.
-Medics.
-Come help us!
-Here! Over here!
Honey, are you okay?
Honey, honey! Are you okay?
What are we going to do with this?
This guy breaks all the security cameras.
We can't get any clues from them.
Hey. Was there no dashcam in his car?
No, no dashcam.
So we found no evidence?
Nothing.
It rained a lot yesterday,
so I'd be surprised if we found anything.
Seems like
the universe is helping this asshole.
What's gotten into you?
You never liked
to volunteer at the care center
because of the ladies and their politics.
Aren't you holding
a prayer service for A-yeong?
Shouldn't you be getting ready?
Si-yeong.
Don't you have something to tell me?
Huh?
You can say it. You can confess to me.
What do you mean?
Si-yeong.
I know it's my fault.
We're in this mess because of me.
But…
But I've repented for everything.
It's your turn.
Do you have anything to tell me?
What are you saying?
Come on!
Listen carefully.
Remember that new church that we saw?
Pastor Jung asked me
to be the pastor in charge.
You know, I looked into it.
Hwan-su's getting that church,
everyone knows that.
You said
Jung Guk-hwan was your spiritual father?
-You're always so ridiculously gullible--
-Si-yeong.
Watch what you say to me.
Hwan-su… is doing mission work abroad.
You know why?
It's because he sinned.
He committed adultery.
I'm sorry. Hey, I'm sorry.
This is God's revelation.
We must become sinless before God.
In order for us to receive
God's revelation,
we must be completely sinless.
Si-yeong.
Come on, confess.
I… I…
I'm gonna be late.
God knows everything though.
You can't hide from Him.
Confess.
I have committed
the mortal sin of adultery.
Louder.
Heavenly Almighty.
I've sinned
and committed adultery with another man.
Louder!
This confession must reach
the ears of God. Louder!
Almighty God,
I committed adultery with another man!
-Amen!
-Amen.
Amen! Amen!
-Amen…
-Almighty God.
-Amen.
-This lost sheep repents for her sins.
We have sinned many times.
Please listen to us
as we sincerely repent to you
and before you.
Your boundless love…
Sir, this is completely…
It's definitely stuck.
Hello, do you… Do you need a hand?
No, it's okay.
The tow truck will be here any minute.
But we appreciate it.
-All right.
-Be careful. The road is narrow.
YEONGJIN ASSISTED LIVING CENTER
-My gosh. Look at this.
-Mrs. Lee.
Oh.
-Hi.
-Oh, you're early.
Oh, wow.
Pastor Sung, what brings you here?
Did you just come to drop her off?
You two are still so in love.
-It's all thanks to their faith.
-Amen.
You're filled with God's grace.
I wish I could've been here earlier
to help you all get ready.
The caterer will be taking care
of everything.
We'll just watch them cook, while we chat.
There's so much evil in the world
we must discuss.
My dear Lord.
What is it? What's wrong?
Oh. No. I'm just waiting on the ambulance.
Oh. We saw an ambulance
waiting for a tow truck.
I can't believe this.
What's wrong? Is someone hurt?
Well, a man showed up earlier
covered in dirt and blood.
He crawled here and passed out.
I think he's badly hurt.
I think he should be taken
to a proper hospital.
I wonder what happened to him.
He must have crawled here
from that mountain up there.
My goodness. That sounds serious.
Where is he now? Do you have room for him?
Oh, we moved him to the ward upstairs
so he could lie down.
But if the ambulance doesn't come…
When my husband asked
the ambulance drivers if they needed help,
they said a tow truck was on the way.
I'm glad.
Ah, everyone! Don't you need
to oversee them set up the cafeteria?
-Yes, let's do that.
-Yes.
We should get changed,
and we need to take photos.
Yes! You're right.
You ladies are busy.
I should be on my way.
Pastor, you should stay and eat with us.
I'm holding a prayer service this evening.
-Ah.
-I should get ready.
All right.
Shall we?
I'll take you to the room
next to the cafeteria.
-Okay.
-This way please.
-Let's go in.
-Watch your step.
-Go on inside.
-Yeah.
A pastor…
A pastor tried to…
A pastor… A pastor tried to…
…kill me.
This isn't what I want to do.
God's will must be done.
You took so long!
-Where's the patient?
-Upstairs.
This way!
It was this man, correct?
Yes, it was him.
We had no idea that man was a criminal,
so we just took him in and helped him.
That must be why he fled.
-Can we see the room you put him in?
-Of course.
It's this way.
Can we check the footage
from that camera up there?
Oh. Um, that camera is very old.
It actually doesn't work.
Could we get in trouble for that?
We're really struggling
to make ends meet here.
Uh, we don't handle
that type of thing.
He was here.
He took him.
Someone took him?
Who was it?
It was the Almighty. Our Heavenly God.
Amen.
Dad, did you just say "amen"?
You hated the church.
What a surprise.
Well, I… I have to believe in God…
This man's had dementia for over 20 years.
Yeah, that's right.
I believe you. I believe you, Dad.
-How many entrances and exits are there?
-Oh.
Is there a back door?
There's one over here
and there's an exit by the kitchen.
Oh. May I see?
Who are they?
Oh! Uh, they are pastors' wives
who come here to volunteer
on a regular basis.
Do you think we could possibly
get a list of the churches they're from?
Yeah. Absolutely. Yes.
♪ Giver of immortal gladness ♪
♪ Fill us with the light of day ♪
Surprised?
You managed to survive, but here I am.
You asshole…
why are you doing this to me?
Good question.
That's what I'm really curious about.
Why does the Lord
always keep leading me back to you?
Why?
Like with that care home.
I hadn't been there in so long.
When I woke up this morning,
I, all of a sudden, had to go there.
Why?
Out of nowhere?
The day of Pentecost.
The anointing of the Holy Spirit!
The Holy Spirit was sent to me by God
and led me straight there.
Holy Spirit?
You're just trying to hide the fact
that you tried to kill me.
Wait, hold on.
It's all clear to me now.
Now I know why God keeps leading…
leading me to a child of Satan.
I get it.
He wants to see just how much
I'm willing to obey his commandment.
I mean, look around us.
This hotel was built because of rumors
about a new golf course in the area.
The developer went bankrupt.
And it's been abandoned
for over three years.
Who knew this creepy, derelict building
would be useful.
It was prepared by Him.
It's God's providence!
This is truly a miracle.
You're crazy. You completely lost it.
So what now?
You gonna kill me?
I don't know.
I'm waiting for God.
We are all just God's servants
who obey his orders.
If you kill me, you know,
you won't ever find that girl.
That little girl…
What?
The girl who goes to your church.
She's still alive.
Where is A-yeong?
Call the police,
and I'll confess everything.
Where is A-yeong?
Kill me now, Pastor,
that girl dies as well.
Where is she? Tell me!
Call the police.
What? You scared?
♪ Glory be to Jesus ♪
♪ Who died on the cross for me ♪
♪ The cross that you carried ♪
♪ I carry it now for Thee ♪
Amen!
♪ His cross-- ♪
Where's A-yeong? Tell me!
Just call the police, satanic bastard.
Do we have their dashcam footage?
Yeah, everyone parked here
gave us consent.
Go through the footage
as soon as you get to the office.
Lee Yeon-hui.
-Call it a day, Inspector.
-What?
We can't throw a welcome party for you,
but we can at least make sure
you don't work late on day one.
There's only a few files.
Head home, rest up.
See you.
How long has it been
since she was last seen?
It's been 24 hours, sir.
Gotta say, the chances
of her still being alive are slim.
DETECTIVE SO EUN-GYU
HERE'S THE LIST OF CHURCHES
MISSION NATION CHURCH
♪ Giver of immortal gladness ♪
♪ Fill us with the light of day ♪
It was the Almighty,
our Heavenly God.
Did you not find a body?
Pastor. A-yeong is okay, right?
She's gonna be fine?
Thank you, Pastor.
Let's go upstairs.
MULBERRY FARMS
MUSAN ORGANIC MULBERRY FARM
Today, we will be reading from the passage
Deuteronomy 24:7.
I'll begin.
"If someone is caught
kidnapping a fellow Israelite
and treating that person as a slave,
or selling their fellow person
into bondage,
the kidnapper, then,
must die."
"You must purge the evil
that lies amongst you all."
Amen.
Let us now pray.
Dear Heavenly Father.
Everyone who loves
your little, precious lamb, Shin A-yeong,
is here now.
We know that A-yeong
is watching over us from heaven.
A-yeong's mother is utterly devastated.
Please allow her to feel
the sense of peace A-yeong is able to now.
Amen!
We know that you never ignore
or keep a deaf ear,
but listen to our prayers
and cries for help.
Amen!
Punishments to all whom are evil,
purging all
that are here to go against us.
God, all of your precious children
remember your wrath, your fairness,
and your righteousness!
Amen!
You love those who are righteous,
but you hate those that sin,
punishing them.
In Sodom and Gomorrah,
you punished
by raining sulfur and fire upon them.
Now, with your right hand
majestic in power,
judge all that is evil
with your righteous fire!
Consume them all!
Annihilate them all in your name!
May your will be done!
All of you now shout "Lord"
with me three times
and pray together. Amen.
-Lord!
…our heartfelt prayers, dear Lord…
Amen. Amen.
MUSAN ORGANIC MULBERRY FARM
DETECTIVE SO EUN-GYU
Yeon-hui.
He should die.
Now's your chance to kill him, Yeon-hui.
Kill him.
This is the moment
you've been waiting for.
Do it now!
Don't you feel bad for me, Yeon-hui?
I thought
you wanted to avenge me!
Do it! Avenge me!
He's pure evil!
He'll hurt more people.
He'll hurt more people
if you don't kill him.
Do it now!
If you kill me, that girl will die.
Police. Call the police.
She's still alive for now.
He's lying!
Yeon-hui,
he's the devil.
Don't side with the devil.
I am a police officer.
Where is Shin A-yeong?
Hospital.
Take me to a hospital first. Please.
Just tell me where A-yeong is.
You'll kill me once I tell you.
I won't kill you. I won't kill you.
Listen to me. Stop the bullshit,
and tell me where A-yeong is.
You're a crazy bitch, aren't you?
Think I'll believe you
when you're glaring at me like that?
Fuck.
There are so many lunatics
in this neighborhood, aren't there.
Tell me, asshole.
Where the hell have you been hiding her?
Just tell me or die!
Pastor! What… What are you doing?
You think it's a coincidence?
There are no coincidences.
He led us all here.
Come to your senses.
Untie me! Untie me!
You see, God's will…
isn't something
we mere humans can understand.
I had the biggest headache earlier.
"What am I going to do with the body
once I kill that devil?"
"Should I just……burn it?"
"Or should I chop it into pieces
and dump it somewhere?"
But God sent you to me, Detective.
A-yeong! Do you know where she is?
A-yeong has perished.
She's lying dead somewhere.
Let's not think about her.
It's time to follow God's will.
It's time to punish this evil bastard
for what he did to A-yeong.
Pastor, turn yourself in.
It's not too late.
I'll tell them that
you were accidentally shot.
He pulled the trigger
while fighting with you.
Then he tripped and fell to his death.
Wake up, Pastor, please.
If you kill him, we'll never find A-yeong!
Didn't you hear me?
I told you that she's dead.
That evil monster killed her.
Oh, yeah! It's you.
You're Yeon-ju's sister.
I wondered why you followed me
and stared like that.
But let's be honest with ourselves.
Did I actually kill her?
-Huh?
-What?
She jumped to her death
all on her very own.
-Am I wrong?
-What the fuck did you just say?!
If everyone killed themselves
over a few days of suffering,
I would've died 10,000 times by now. Fuck!
Every night, the one-eyed monster
came knocking on my door.
Every night, he tied me up and hit me--
Shut up, devil!
Don't you dare flick your forked tongue.
Stop it!
We have to find A-yeong.
I told you she's dead. She's already dead!
Otherwise,
I never would've received the revelation
to kill him like this!
God is perfect, understand?
The Lord does things for a reason!
Please, please do something
about this crazy pastor.
Don't you want
to save A-yeong? A-yeong will--
Shut up, devil!
How dare you.
You're lying to get out of here alive.
-He said she isn't dead.
-I won't fall for your lies!
He said A-yeong is alive.
A-yeong isn't dead. A-yeong is alive!
Why would you let the devil deceive you?
Can't you tell that he's lying?
If we don't kill him now,
there will be more innocent victims
just like A-yeong.
♪ Glory be to Jesus ♪
♪ Who died on the cross for me, oh, Lord ♪
♪ The cross that you carry… ♪
Look at that man.
He's clearly insane.
♪ I will carry it now for Thee ♪
He is the spawn of Satan.
He's a monster.
Because of people like you
who comfort devils like that
the whole world is becoming more evil.
♪ To take away my sins ♪
♪ Now Heaven is in store… ♪
That girl…
The one-eyed monster ate her.
The one-eyed monster.
-Inspector Lee!
-Medics!
Hey, you two!
Go, quick. Examine him.
-Hey, everyone, move in!
-Say it. Tell me.
Tell me before you die!
Enough. Come on.
Come with us.
Not getting a pulse.
Transport him.
Go inside and check!
He says he received God's revelation
to kill Kwon Yang-rae.
I don't think he has any idea
as to where Shin A-yeong might be.
Ugh, that crazy asshole.
Captain, Kwon Yang-rae's car
was found near Foxhill Pass,
I think because he was headed
to Redevelopment Zone Four
in Myeonbuk-dong.
He had been working there
and knew the area well.
He took her there, that's my bet.
It's the perfect place to hide her.
How much time do you need
to comb through that area?
I'd say probably at least three days.
Three-- Then it'll be day five. Shit.
The chances of her being alive
after five days are slim.
♪ The Lord's great grace has taught me ♪
♪ I feel the Lord's boundless grace ♪
♪ The Lord's boundless grace ♪
♪ When I follow the Lord… ♪
Hey.
Get moving. What are you waiting for?
Yes, sir!
Inspector, please go home.
Don't worry, we got this.
I'll call you if we find her.
Hey.
Mr. Kwon.
Hey, Mr. Kwon! Mr. Kwon!
Yeah?
Demolish it all. All of this has to go
by the end of the day, okay?
-Yeah, I got it.
-Right.
Oh, please come in.
I was surprised to get your call
so early in the morning.
DAD
IMAGE
SCAFFOLDING REMOVED
So, about that pastor,
I reviewed everything you sent.
Seems like a case of apophenia.
Apophenia?
It refers to the tendency to perceive
meaningful rules, patterns, or connections
between unrelated things.
What you're seeing now…
is called pareidolia.
They're natural phenomena,
but some people believe
they see specific images.
People like him attach profound meanings.
Nothing is by chance to them.
Dr. Lee…
I…
I wanna learn more about Kwon Yang-rae.
Can you tell me about his life?
Horrible, right?
He was abused every single day.
Every time it happened,
his mother sang hymns outside his room.
She sang and prayed.
The one-eyed monster.
He talked about this before he died.
What do you think
this one-eyed monster means?
It could symbolize his stepfather,
or it could represent himself.
Do you see the people in its mouth?
I'm not sure if it means
he's in the monster's head
or if he is the monster.
A monster who swallowed his victims?
It's all speculation.
Like a puzzle, but one thing's for sure.
That monster is deeply connected
to his traumatic memories from childhood.
Are you having visions?
My sister.
Sometimes I see her.
What happens?
Does she say something?
That she waited for me to rescue her.
But…
he was always the one
coming through that door.
You know it's not your sister.
That's not her.
Inspector Lee,
your visions are illusions
crafted from guilt.
I know.
I know it's not real.
But I can't shake it off.
A-yeong must be waiting
for someone to rescue her.
She's probably waiting to see someone
walk through the door and save her.
But again,
there's nothing that I can do.
What if we can't find A-yeong?
If something bad already happened to her…
It's all my fault.
This is all my fault.
Right.
You think it's all your fault.
Kwon Yang-rae blamed his tragedy
on the monster.
Sung Min-chan, God's revelation.
You blame yourself.
You think that it's all your fault.
These sound different,
but they're actually the same.
You all fixated on one thing
as the cause of a situation.
It's what a lot of people do.
Most tragedies are caused
by a combination of circumstances
we can't control.
Devils, monsters and the like,
they're created
by people seeking justification.
Then what should I do now?
I need to get to A-yeong.
I agree.
Think about what you can actually see.
Kwon Yang-rae was getting better,
so what triggered him to re-offend, huh?
We have to find out
what awakened his monster.
I'm sure there's something
we happened to have missed.
Professor,
the dean would like to meet with you.
Ah, I'll be right back.
Come all the way!
To the right, to the right!
More, more, more, more!
Stop!
I would've died 10,000 times by now. Fuck!
Every night, the one-eyed monster
came knocking on my door.
Every night, he tied me up and hit me--
DAD
What's up, Dad?
What's going on with you?
You're not responding to my texts.
You didn't even come home last night.
I know. I've been super busy. Sorry.
I've been working on a case.
Why'd you call?
Did you see the picture I sent?
We finally removed the scaffolding.
You said you wanted to see it.
Oh, right.
Let me look.
The exterior is done,
but we'll probably need another month
to finish the interior.
There's a lot of big remodeling jobs
like this in this area.
They want to fix up all the old houses.
-Wait, Dad--
-My goodness.
This one was stressful.
The client wanted to highlight
the one-eyed thing.
"One-eyed thing"?
Yeah. Do you see the round window
right under the roof?
That's what's called an oculus window.
Some people call it a one-eyed window.
Back in the day,
they built a lot of houses like that.
They're a rare sight these days though.
Are you listening?
Argh! What's wrong with this phone?
Ta-da!
-Isn't it great? Come here, come here.
-Hmm?
Let's take a selfie.
One, two and three.
Kwon Yang-rae
was getting better,
so what triggered him to re-offend, huh?
We have to find out
what awakened his monster.
Kwon Yang-rae's trigger.
Yes, Inspector Lee.
-Did you see the photo I sent?
-A photo?
Kwon Yang-rae's "one-eyed monster,"
it's a house with a circular window.
Check the street view
of Redevelopment Zone Four
and find a house with a window like that.
That's where A-yeong is.
Got it.
Find a building
with a circular window like this
in Redevelopment Zone Four. ASAP.
-Roger that!
-On it. Send us the photo.
This is it.
DETECTIVE SO EUN-GYU:
23-7 MINDEULRE-GIL
Hey! What's your problem?
Wait, hold on.
Hang in there, okay?
I kept telling myself
that someone would come and save me.
It's all right.
You're safe, you're all right.
You're okay.
Mr. Sung Min-chan.
We found her. We found Shin A-yeong.
You found… her remains, you mean?
Actually,
we found her alive.
She's being treated in the hospital.
She's still traumatized by everything…
but there is hope.
Her doctor said she'll be okay.
That can't be right.
I swear I was told that she died.
Who told you that?
Pardon me?
You just said that
you were told that she died.
Who told you?