Let's go.
These are your medications.
Take them after half an hour.
Half an hour?
That's a long time.
[Deluxe Suite No. 3]
[Holy Bible]
Let go of me.
Alright.
You have some strength.
Stop it.
Let go of me.
Beg me.
Help!
Get off me!
[Justice Is Mine]
[Episode 13]
[Hokong Prison]
Dad.
You look good.
How's there?
They know you are my son,
so they don't really talk to me.
That's better.
Less contact, less trouble.
Remember,
if anything happens,
let the guard know.
You are a grown-up now.
You need to know
how to protect yourself.
Dad,
if people get punished
for making mistakes,
how could some people get away with it?
No.
They have to pay for their mistakes.
So do I.
[Coffee Alley]
Coffee with less sugar.
Thank you.
Mr. Fei.
Whenever I think of you,
you are here.
Well, it's 1:15.
Your coffee is ready.
I will give it to you now.
Mr. Chun,
your coffee.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I should be the one to apologize.
Take off your ring.
I will clean it for you.
Thank you.
Alright.
It's all wet.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Forgive me, Your Honor.
Please don't say that.
Thank you so much.
Alright.
Thank you. See you tomorrow.
Can you walk on your own already?
That's right.
I can do that now.
What's wrong with your face?
It's okay.
It was...
Got it?
He raped a nurse.
Is it taken care of?
We gave her money.
She shouldn't dare to speak up.
Is he still having seizures?
Once in a while,
but it is not as bad as before.
Hey,
are you seriously considering me deaf?
Anyway, after
seeing the priest tomorrow,
I won't need to take any pills,
and I can even kill some tigers.
It's all set.
It'll be in the church close by.
Lit.
Slow down.
You are not fully recovered.
I was going very slowly.
Where does it hurt?
Have a guess.
Here.
It really hurts!
Thank you.
Gong,
do you really believe in the exorcism?
I don't think we are even
in line to go to heaven.
Hey, do you remember
that once I almost died?
A priest gave me a bracelet,
and then I was all fine.
This time is the same.
I will get well soon.
Lit,
our father
is in prison.
If I die...
Stop it.
Spit it out.
Then you will be in charge
of the business of the Hon family.
Both Father
and I know
that it is not a business
that you want to run,
right?
We are a family.
I will do it no matter what.
Anyway, as long as I'm around,
I will have your back.
You can do whatever you want.
Okay?
So what are you doing now?
Stop looking.
Help me take off the bracelet.
Alright. Keep it.
Why are you giving me your bracelet?
I just told you.
Father and I
will always support you and protect you.
You really don't like me?
Are you taking the night shift
to avoid me?
As a nurse, rotating shifts
is part of the job.
Mr. Hon doesn't want anyone else here.
I will donate some money to the church
as compensation.
I understood.
No problem.
Is it ready?
Almost.
Oh, this woman.
Look at her.
How can he accept her?
Mr. Hon Gong,
it's ready.
You can come in.
Mr. Hon Gong.
Don't touch me.
It will be fine.
Go.
Do you think the priest
is going to eat me alive?
Go. It's okay.
Close the door.
Take the wheelchair away.
Let's go.
Hi, priest.
Hello.
I'm Hon Gong.
So this is the thing.
Lately, I've been having some hard luck.
I had a car accident and hurt my leg,
so I want you
to do an exorcism.
Take it easy.
I'm not in a hurry,
but let's do it fast.
I can have a chat
with your boss first.
Chun Yue?
Kneel.
Alright.
We can talk it through.
Close your eyes.
[Chun Yue, Judge]
Jenny.
What's wrong, Mr. Chun?
I just accidentally stained
the statement of B04.
Could you print another one out for me?
Sure.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Could you give it to me
before the trial at 2 pm?
No problem. I'll give it to you soon.
[Herbal Tea]
Thank you.
Madam,
Hon Gong was shot in the head.
He is dead.
There is no witness at the moment.
We found the priest in the prayer room.
He was drugged
and sent to the hospital.
We will take his statement
when he wakes up.
That's it for now.
Are you the family of the deceased?
He is his brother.
Take a look.
Is this your brother, Hon Gong?
The priest probably took something
like a sedative
and lost consciousness.
Luckily, it doesn't do
serious damage to his body.
After the IV,
he should wake up soon.
A few weeks ago,
the Drug Enforcement Unit found
that someone used underage students
for drug trafficking.
At around 8:20 in the morning,
2nd of October,
the Drug Enforcement Unit
followed a student
after receiving a report
from the school
and got to the trading location.
[Hokong Maximum Security Prison]
What did you say?
He was shot in the church.
He...
Dad?
Dad, how are you?
Dad!
Doctor!
Get someone here!
[Eastern District Police Station]
Who do you think
killed Hon Gong?
Madam,
someone like him
did a lot of horrible things.
He deserves it.
Consider it's his karma.
It's actually good.
He wanted to be exorcised,
but only he was the target.
What are you talking about?
It's not an exorcist.
It's payback that might be delayed,
but never denied.
Right.
So it's done.
Yes, it's done.
The murderer didn't kill the priest.
It doesn't seem to be someone
from a gang or a hit-man.
What if we consider it
as a revenge?
It makes sense if the murderer
knows Hon Gong.
I agree.
He knew Hon Gong's moves very well.
He should have observed
and made a plan before he did it.
Get the surveillance tapes
of the hospital, the church,
and of the surrounding streets
from last week.
Check every detail.
Perhaps the murderer is on tape.
- Yes, Madam.
[Coffee Alley]
Mr. Fei.
Mr. Chun, what brings you here?
Do you miss my coffee?
Not really.
I don't know when or where
I lost my ring today.
I searched for a long time,
but I couldn't find it. So, I thought,
perhaps it's here.
Today?
Did you come by today?
I'm here every day at 1:15.
That's right. It's your habit.
1:15.
You can take a look.
Alright.
So
I get my coffee here.
That's right.
After the coffee, I usually
will not touch anything.
Okay.
When I walk here,
I will get the sugar.
Could it be in the sugar jar?
Let's check.
Let me take everything out.
It's here!
Is this yours?
It is!
I'm so careless.
Luckily, it's in the sugar jar.
You have to
keep the ring well from now on.
I will. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Alright. Bye.
See you at 1:15.
- Sure.
- Bye.
Hi, Priest.
I'm Tong Huen, a Senior Inspector
from Eastern District Police Station.
Ms. Tong,
hello.
May I talk to you about something?
Yes.
We found a bottle
at the scene.
In the bottle, it's herbal tea
and some trace of sedative.
Do you remember
who gave you
the herbal tea?
I brought it there myself.
Then do you remember
if anyone touched it?
Not really.
There were
a lot of believers at the time.
Before you passed out,
who took you to the prayer room?
I remember that.
It was a man.
He was holding me,
and I had a look at him.
Could you help us with the portraiture?
I can try.
Thank you.
[Eastern District Police Station]
Come in.
Madam,
it's the portraiture,
according to the priest.
[Herbal Tea]
[Hokong Courts of Final Appeal
and Second Instance Building]
Congratulations, Mr. Lo.
You deserve it.
We know it's going to be you.
Thank you, everyone.
Cheers.
I still need your support
in the future.
- Let's have a toast to Mr. Lo.
- Cheers.
Congratulations!
Ms. Tong,
I would like to file a report
about someone
abusing their power,
stalking me and invading my privacy.
Perhaps there's some misunderstanding.
My colleague wanted to invite you
to the station
to give us some clarification.
Maybe you just took the same route.
I'm here now.
What do you want to ask?
What is this?
This is
a portrait of the murderer
who killed Hon Gong.
Mr. Chun, any thought?
It looks familiar,
but I can't recall where I saw it.
Don't you think these eyes
look similar to yours?
They look similar
to yours, I think.
The time of Hon Gong's death
was between one and two
in the afternoon.
Mr. Chun,
where were you at that time?
Is it an official investigation?
Shall we go to the investigation room?
Tell me where you were.
Isn't it the easiest way
to clear your suspicion?
We don't need to make it complicated.
For a criminal trial,
the burden of proof
lies with the prosecution,
and it must meet the standard
of beyond a reasonable doubt.
The defendant
is under no obligation
to prove his own innocence.
Are you now refusing to answer?
Assisting the police
in their investigation
is the duty of every citizen,
but if certain procedures
were to be omitted
merely because of our acquaintance,
that would be inappropriate.
[Coffee Alley]
Mr. Fei?
Are you Mr. Fei?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
The cafe is closed.
You can come by tomorrow.
I'm Tong Huen, a Senior Inspector
from Eastern District Police Station.
What can I do for you?
May I ask
if you can recognize
most of your customers?
Most of them are regulars,
and I recognize most of them.
This is near the court.
Are there a lot of customers
from there?
Yes,
like Mr. Chun.
He comes here every day.
He orders a coffee
after lunch in the afternoon.
He is always on time,
1:15 every day.
After all, he is a judge.
Do you remember
if he was on time as well
last Friday?
Last Friday?
Yes.
I remember that last Friday,
there were a lot of customers.
I almost couldn't cope.
Then,
when I was about to close,
he came here and told me
that he had lost his ring here.
We found it
in the sugar jar.
That's why
I remember it very well.
I also know Mr. Chun,
but I don't remember
seeing him wearing a ring.
He does.
One time,
he accidentally spilled the coffee
and hurt himself.
I cleaned it for him,
including the ring he took off.
Madam,
what is this about?
It's okay.
Thank you for your help.
Thank you.
See you next time.
Bye.
Alright.
Mr. Chun has an alibi now.
I also asked his secretary.
She also said
that Mr. Chun had some coffee back.
Later,
he spilled it on a document
and asked her to print it again.
What's your thought, Madam?
Everything checks out too perfectly
to be real.
Let's talk about it later.
[Hokong Prison]
Dad,
did you get back
what they owe us?
Leave these to me.
Don't worry.
Take care of yourself
in there,
alright?
[Hokong Prison]
Priest,
didn't you do a portrait for the police?
Do one for us, too.
Life for a life.
I'm sure God
will agree.
[Hokong Courts of Final Appeal
and Second Instance Building]
Someone smashed Mr. Chun's car.
I wonder who did it. Here he is.
Mr. Chun.
- Mr. Chun.
Your car was vandalized last night.
Do you know who did it?
Mr. Chun,
do you think it is a signal
that security is getting worse
in Hokong?
It's nothing new
that Hokong's security is getting worse.
If the police overlook the problem
that the rule of law
is being threatened by violence,
similar incidents will happen again,
and
it will get worse.
I'm not afraid of the criminal,
and I'm willing to sacrifice anytime
for the rule of law.
Mr. Chun,
[Self-Discipline and Impartiality]
there is a council member
called Ong Siu who wants to meet you.
Bring him in.
Mr. Ong, please come in.
Hello, Mr. Ong.
Hello, Mr. Chun.
Because of what happened last night,
I'm here in particular
to see how you are doing.
Thank you.
Take a seat.
Sure.
As a council member,
Other than the public,
I also care a lot
about the core values of Hokong.
Economic development and the rule of law
are closely connected.
If the rule of law is trampled,
I'm afraid that investors
will lose confidence in us.
Therefore, I have zero tolerance
in terms of violence against you.
Ever since my son was sentenced to jail,
I have suffered
from a lot of verbal violence.
Lately,
it has escalated to real damage.
Yet, my biggest concern
is the safety of my son in prison.
I definitely understand your concern.
Mr. Chun,
in fact, I'm a member
of the oversight committee
of the Correctional Services Department
Maybe I can directly tell the warden
to pay attention
to your son's safety in particular?
Is that okay?
No problem.
Alright.
Hello, warden.
I'm Mr. Ong Siu.
Hi, Mr. Ong.
Mr. Chun's car was vandalized
last night.
I'm sure you read the news, too.
I do.
I think this is definitely
a targeted violent behavior.
I'm worried that Chun Yat-wai,
Mr. Chun's son,
will be the next target.
Could you please take measures
to guarantee the safety of his son?
Don't worry, Mr. Ong.
I know what to do.
I will make sure Chun Yat-wai
won't get even a scratch.
Thank you, warden.
Stay in touch. Goodbye.
Mr. Chun.
The warden gives his word.
You can rest assured.
Thank you very much, Mr. Ong.
It's okay.
If there's any problem in the future,
you can contact me anytime.
I can see that we have many chances
to work together in the future.
Alright. I should leave.
Alright. This way.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Mr. Chun,
is there a problem with your car?
Yes.
The tire is flat.
It's difficult
to get a taxi at this hour.
If you don't mind,
you can take my car.
Thank you.
What's your name?
Which department are you from?
[Aspirations unmet, Rest in Heaven]
I got you here today
as a sacrifice to my brother's death.
Do you know that the maximum sentence
for kidnapping is 15 years?
You are such a good son.
Do you want to
be in prison with your father?
15 years for kidnapping,
then how about murder?
What do you say you killed my brother?
What do you want?
Why did you kill my brother?
Do you really want an answer?
I will ask you one more time.
Why did you kill my brother?
Because he is a scumbag.
Your entire family is scumbags!
Why?
Why did you kill my brother?
Why did you kill my brother? Why?
Tell me.
Not speaking?
Then I will kill you,
and I will kill your son!
[Aspirations unmet, Rest in Heaven]
Get up!
If I get to walk out this door alive,
I will kill you as well.
You are a noble man, huh?
You are nothing
without that court dress.
Don't shoot.
I will tell you.
I will.
Because you all deserve to die.
I will kill you
in revenge for my brother.
Okay.
If you have the guts,
shoot.
Do it!
Mr. Hon Lit,
what's the matter?
Someone is here.
You have to see him.
Watch him.
Got it.
Mr. Hon Lit,
this is
Mr. Ong Siu.
Mr. Ong,
I don't think we know each other.
What's the matter?
I'm sorry for the death of your brother.
I'm here to see how you are holding up.
Thank you for that.
Perhaps we can have a chat?
Now?
I'm kind of occupied.
Mr. Ong,
this way.
I guess you are not here
to offer your consolation.
Maybe
you can cut to the chase.
I like to talk to smart people like you.
It saves a lot of time.
I want you to spare Mr. Chun.
Hokong needs this judge
to uphold justice.
Justice?
What if I don't?
Even if Mr. Chun dies,
your brother will not come back to life.
It's better for you
to do something meaningful.
There are some signs.
Whenever you see them, be alarmed.
Diamonds,
hearts,
and spades
are the businessmen,
police,
and politicians.
When you see them,
be careful.
They are all about interest.
I don't think
we can convince each other.
Let's not waste each other's time.
Mr. Hon Lit,
what we are wasting
is your father's time in jail.
What do you mean?
It's like a chess game.
Each piece has its own purpose.
You cannot move it at will,
or it will
mess up the overall strategy.
It then affects the result of the game,
and finally,
the interest behind it.
You should understand, right?
Who's the one pulling the strings
in this game?
You?
I'm only a messenger.
You are saying
that my father
is only a chess piece.
That's right.
So is that judge.
He will be.
How do you know
that he will listen to you?
Everyone has a soft spot.
I'm not trying to make him obey.
It's for the greater good.
The interest of the greater
is the interest of your father
in the future.
I know my father too well.
Nothing
can compare to my brother.
Same for me.
It's a pity, then.
A useless piece
has no value.
Just you try.
I'm only a messenger.
I've delivered the word.
It's your choice.
Mr. Chun,
Mr. Ong wants to give you a ride.
Mr. Chun.
Mr. Ong.
Get in the car.
Thank you.
How do you know where I am?
I got a message
that you were in trouble,
so I came to take a look.
After all, you are
an important figure in Hokong.
As a council member,
I'm like a bridge for communication.
I know exactly
what happened.
Mr. Chun,
let's pretend nothing happened tonight.
I'm sure
it won't happen again, too.
I'll send you home,
and you can take a rest.
Thank you.
Why didn't you kill the judge?
Mr. Ong came,
and he asked me to let him go
for the sake of Hokong.
Did you back down just because of that?
Dad,
you said it yourself.
They are all about interest,
and interest is the biggest weapon.
Your brother...
Your brother was the only interest.
The rest is nothing!
A useless piece
has no value.
Just you try.
I've delivered the word.
It's your choice.
Dad,
the judge will not leave
without his son.
We can kill him anytime we want,
but I won't let them
have any excuse to hurt you.
I'm not scared of them.
I don't believe they dare to harm me!
I can help them,
so I can ruin them!
Let's see who the winner is.
Father...
Alright, Lit. Stop it.
You should go.
I will definitely take revenge for Gong.
I won't let you down.
Don't get so angry.
I remember you told me
that no one is harder to catch
than a police officer
who breaks the law.
In that case,
it is even harder
to catch a judge
who breaks the law,
because no one
knows the legal system better
or makes better use
of the legal loopholes than him.
He will be harder to catch
than the police.
If that is the case,
you are facing
a huge challenge.
His alibi
is way too perfect.
I've thought about it.
He could
put his ring there in advance.
He could also
prepare everything else in advance.
How about the witness?
You said Mr. Fei
was his alibi witness, right?
How could he kill someone
while getting a coffee?
This is where I can't figure it out.
I'm sorry. I'm talking about work again.
Let's watch a movie.
I'm the one who should apologize.
I need to visit Lau Mao after this.
To Tuen Shing?
No.
After he agreed to having the operation,
I had him transferred.
As long as there is a slight chance,
no one is willing to wait for death.
I hope he can truly
give you a new lead.
I hope so.
Let's see when I'll be back.
If we have time,
we can watch a movie.
Sure.
After the medication, the patient
will fall asleep very soon.
Keep it brief.
Got it.
How are you, Mao?
I took some pills. It's okay.
Thanks for asking.
Mao,
do you remember
who Lum Chin is?
She is also in Hokong.
She said she would pay a visit later.
I know.
God is punishing me.
I owe it to the Shantytown.
Sektau,
I know why you are here.
It's for your families.
The person who pleaded guilty back then
was not the one who did it.
Do you know who did it?
I saw him from behind.
He was tall.
The one who took the fall now
is short
and malnourished.
[Archives]
Mr. Sek,
this is the court file
for the Fu-Ngam Shantytown
arson case in 1978.
So all the evidence is here.
That's right. It's all on record.
[Criminal Case File Index]
Thank you.
You are welcome.
[Indictment]
[Hokong Judiciary]
[Defendant's Information]
[Basic Information. Height: 160 cm]
He was only 1.6 meters tall.
It was a totally different shape.
No wonder Lau Mao insisted
that he was a scapegoat.
[Attendants: prosecutor:  Chun Yue,
on behalf of Hokong Police]
You are back.
I can see
that you've decided to move your office
to my place.
That's right.
What?
You have a problem?
Not at all.
I love it.
Have you eaten?
No. I'm waiting for you.
Alright. I will cook.
What do you want?
How about
I cook for you today?
Ever since the rice soup
with diced melon I made last time,
I haven't cooked for you anymore.
Wait a second.
You sure the yellow thing
you made last time
was rice soup with diced melon?
What's the problem?
Pumpkin is also a melon.
Get back to your case.
I will cook.
It's okay, alright?
Wait.
I want to make
the seafood chowder
with puff pastry for you.
With puff pastry? Really?
Here you go.
Take a look at the real rice soup
with diced melon.
So it should be like this.
How's everything?
Did you
get any new leads
after visiting Lau Mao?
Based on what Lau Mao said
and the statements
from the court file,
this 1.6-meter-tall guy
is definitely a scapegoat.
Because Lau Mao said
the arsonist he saw
was a tall man.
That's it?
How can that help?
There is someone who might help.
It is
the prosecutor
of the first trial of the case.
Chun Yue?
The prosecutor of the first trial
knows the most complete statements
of the case from the very beginning.
Those can be
the most valid evidence and statements
before any framing or falsification.
So it is indeed Chun Yue.
Hey,
I'm asking
the major suspect in your case
for help.
Are you going to be mad?
They are two separate things.
I'm just worried
that he is not
who he used to be anymore.
He might not help you.
I have to try.
Good morning, Mr. Chun.
Good morning.
I know it's a sudden visit,
but
if it's possible,
may I have a word with you?
Mr. Chun,
could you please
have a look at this copy?
Fu-Ngam Shantytown arson case?
That's right.
You were the prosecutor
of the first trial of this case.
I know
you were suddenly replaced
right before the trial,
but you should have read
the documents of the first trial, right?
That's right.
Back then,
I briefly studied this case.
Did you find
anything off?
It's a case from 1978.
I don't really remember much.
Mr. Chun,
you said you don't remember much,
but
you got it perfectly right
that it's a case from 1978.
Alright.
Well,
thank you, Mr. Chun.
Sorry for bothering you.
Come in.
Mr. Tat, you want to see me?
I think this coffee from Panama
is great.
Take a seat. Try it.
Sure.
Thank you.
I heard
that you are
interested in some old cases recently.
I'm just trying
to learn from the old ones.
Back then, technology was less advanced,
but instead,
it was more sophisticated
when it came to investigation.
The closed cases
have nothing to learn from.
It's a new era.
Surely, we deal with cases
differently now.
There is hardly right or wrong.
It's better to let it pass and move on.
There is a Chinese saying:
Have a definitive conclusion
on the coffin lid.
If someone keeps digging,
there will be some bad luck.
Back then,
I didn't tell you the truth
because
I received a payment.
Well,
who did you get it from?
I didn't know him.
He said
he was only a messenger.
After I got the money,
I took a look outside.
He was standing by the car,
having a chat
with
a tall foreigner.
The foreigner was smoking a cigar.
I guess he was some businessman.
You've been a police officer
for so many years
with a lot of achievements.
I'm going to recommend you
for promotion to Deputy Superintendent
by the end of the year.
What do you think?
In that case, Mr. Tat,
I have to say thank you.
Skip the pleasantries.
From now on,
think about the bigger picture.
You should
leave the complicated,
meaningless cases alone,
and I will surely
save the spot
of Deputy Superintendent for you.
I won't disappoint you.
I used to suspect
that Tat Ga-ma is a bad cop.
Now I've got the answer.
Tat Ga-ma is always
going easy on Hon Fui-lung.
Is it possible that he is collaborating
with Hon Fui-lung?
I think it is more than Hon Fui-lung.
There should be someone
higher up than Tat Ga-ma.
What are you going to do now?
Of course it's to do
what a cop should do.
Tat Ga-ma knows
that you are working
on the arson case again.
Did he send someone
to spy on you?
He is still trying to buy me off,
which means he doesn't know
that I'm going to
investigate him next.
Then Lau Mao
will be your most powerful witness.
For the sake of interest,
how many innocent lives
have become their victims?
Why is it a cause?
Like flames
scorching every possibility
No strength remains
to question the effect
A crack grew in my heart
Trapped by karmic flames
Blinded by the fire,
I can't tell effect from cause
When right and wrong
are buried, I can't bear
To see hearts and eyes
blurred by smoke
Tangled in the struggle
between light and dark
I sense something near,
veiling truth in shadow
Confronted by my own conscience
Who decides punishment and justice?
How ironic it is to regret
I asked myself,
but grasped no hidden meaning
Keep judging morals
Yet my reason is eroded
Beneath my feet, the abyss awaits
Why can't silence be an answer?
The path back slips beyond my reach
Falling into fate's hollow mystery
On this long road to better days
I forget the heart's
still bleeding within
Who decides punishment and justice?
How ironic it is to regret
I asked myself,
but grasped no hidden meaning
Keep judging morals
Yet my reason is eroded
Beneath my feet, the abyss awaits
Why can't silence be an answer?
The path back slips beyond my reach
Falling into fate's hollow mystery
On this long road to better days
I forget the heart's
still bleeding within