Doctor?
Anything wrong?
Hey!
Gong!
Gong.
What's wrong?
Gong's awake!
Gong.
[Justice Is Mine]
[Episode 8]
Who is it?
Me.
What do you want?
Po is your nephew
and my buddy.
Isn't that worth
a proper talk between us?
Come in alone.
Wait for me here.
Po was young
and didn't know
how cruel the world could be.
That's why he was tricked.
What are you getting at?
You don't want to talk about Po?
Then let's talk about business.
I've got no business
to discuss with you.
The 200,000 you gave to Po's family
was a payment for his life.
Wai,
even Sa knows how rotten you are.
Why else would she walk out on you
with the kids?
Sa is such a great woman.
Everyone adores her.
Shut up.
So many men wanted to marry her,
but she chose you.
Do you think
she regrets it now?
I'll need to have a nice chat
with her someday.
Don't you dare.
You gave Po's mother 200,000
to make her son plead guilty,
but that turned out
to cost him his life.
But you won't go to the cops
because they kicked you out.
You hate them.
But I don't care.
I can tip them off
and even get a reward.
Sa is from the old town.
You married her,
that makes you one of us.
Family
always looks out for each other.
Even you should get that.
I'm planning
to give Hon Fui-lung a big gift.
You'd better act quickly.
When I lose my patience,
there's no telling what I'll do.
Gong.
Doctor,
can he hear us?
He can,
but right now,
he may not understand.
Gong.
It's me, Lit.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Dad's been worried about you.
Do you remember what happened?
You were riding your motorcycle
when someone tried to ram you.
Do you remember it?
Do you have something to say?
Gong,
answer me.
you've been in a coma for half a month.
Take a step back.
He's just woken up.
Full recovery will take time.
Ms. Tong is right.
We can't rush the patient.
Please give him some time.
Let's take it slowly.
Sorry.
I got too emotional.
A parent's love for a child
is beyond question.
But that love
led the defendant to ignore the law,
encouraging her son
to bully classmates at school,
which caused an innocent death.
Afterwards,
she tried not only to destroy evidence,
but also to frame others
to evade justice.
Even if she cooperates
with the investigation
and compensates the victim's family,
the harm
cannot be undone.
The Court believes
that although the defendant's actions
as a mother
may be understood,
they cannot be forgiven.
You must pay the price
for what you have done.
The sentence
is not only punishment
for the defendant,
but also a hope
that such tragedies
will not recur.
It is so ordered
that the defendant Ong Kuen
is guilty on all four counts
and is sentenced
to five years' imprisonment.
[Hokong Maximum Security Prison]
Gong's woken up.
Aren't you happy?
He's only regained consciousness.
He can't do anything yet.
The doctor said
he'll definitely recover.
It's only a matter of time.
Time is the real problem.
Why did I
just let them
lock me up in here this time?
Because if I stepped away,
the foundation
I built for decades would all be lost.
Even worse,
that lunatic Chi Cheung-wing
would take advantage.
I agreed to serve time
so someone could take the credit
and someone else could pocket benefits.
That way,
they and I are in the same boat.
It's all deals.
Deals aren't about fairness.
To win,
it's not about how strong you are.
It depends on
how far one's bottom line can be pushed.
You may be a wolf.
But your brother
is more ruthless and shameless than you.
You two
can help each other.
But when it comes to dirty work,
let Gong do it.
As long as he recovers,
I don't mind what I do.
Targeting Gong
means going against our family.
You killed that car thief.
That gave the lunatic an excuse
to stir up trouble.
While Gong
is stuck in the hospital,
that lunatic is bound to cause trouble.
We must hold the fort.
But we can't afford
to lose our strength.
Understood.
Take good care of your brother.
I will.
Have a look.
Hello.
They're so cute.
Which one do you like?
Right?
Do you like this one?
Thanks.
Here you are.
[Eastern District Police Station]
Tell me about Ma San-po.
That poor kid.
He was only 18 years old.
I've known his mom for a long time.
I saw her this morning.
Her eyes were swollen shut from crying.
Who did it?
If I knew who it was,
they'd already be in the grave with Po.
He was one of your old town gang.
My gang?
I don't have a gang.
Everyone living in the old town
is family.
I take special care
to protect kids.
It's cute.
Chun.
Chun?
Mom!
Chun!
Give me back my child!
Stop!
Chun!
Don't go! Chun...
Do you have kids?
It's Madam questioning you.
You don't question her.
At 7 AM on the day of the incident,
where were you?
At home.
In bed with my girlfriend.
Do you want me to describe the details?
Do you want me
to detain you for 48 hours?
You know how many cases
you have on your back.
I could pick any of them
and arrest you with it.
You should know
who killed Po.
If I knew, I wouldn't
have called you here.
You caught Po
because he hit Hon Gong.
Do you think he'd let Po go?
So you mean
Ma San-po hit Hon Gong?
Don't play dumb!
You cops always pretend to be righteous.
But you do all sorts of vile deeds
behind the scenes.
You know who did it
better than I do.
What a wretch.
Mind your language.
Chi Cheung-wing.
What?
Are you going to arrest me?
If not,
I'm leaving.
Madam allows you to go.
Go.
Get up.
Move.
Mr. Hon,
a stepmother isn't enough for you,
so you came here
looking for another one, huh?
Did you ever think about
how your mother would feel?
I'm afraid she can't rest easy
in her coffin.
If you care so much,
why not go down
and keep your mother company?
Careful not to trip.
I'm not done
with you on this.
Hey.
Chi Cheung-wing,
don't cause trouble.
Hello?
Wai,
they took Chun away.
What?
It was Chi Cheung-wing.
I recognized his men's car.
Sa, don't panic.
Go home now. Lock the door
and look after our daughter.
Chun will be fine.
I will bring him back.
Wai...
Wait for me.
[Eastern District Police Station]
Chi Cheung-wing,
come at me if you've got guts.
Keep away from my family.
Wai, didn't I tell you
my patience is limited?
And I hate babying kids.
As I do more,
I'll just want to slap him.
I'll do anything for you.
Just let my son go.
See?
Why did you think we had
no business to discuss?
Here it is.
Madam will be here shortly.
Any paper?
Chun!
Chun.
It's okay.
Mom's here.
It's okay. Don't cry.
It's over now.
It's over.
Don't cry.
I haven't asked,
and you're writing your confession?
I saw Chi Cheung-wing leave.
What,
are the cells too full
to hold him?
Give me some useful leads,
and I'll free up a cell for him.
Didn't you move the suspect
who hit my brother to another cell?
The suspect's name is Ma San-po.
No,
more accurately,
the shooting victim.
For your brother Hon Gong,
you had every reason to kill him.
Madam,
if you had evidence,
you wouldn't just call me in
to question me.
You'd have deployed the SDU
to haul me in
in the middle of the night.
No need to wait till late.
If you're so keen to go to jail,
I can put you in anytime.
I warn you,
don't blow this up.
You're not your brother or your father.
Don't make a fool of yourself.
I want all the bloodshed to stop.
Are you sure
Ma San-po was the one
who hit my brother?
If it wasn't him,
why would someone want
to kill him for revenge?
If you cops are so capable,
why did you
let this man
break into my brother's ward last night?
Is this Chi's man?
No.
Are you sure?
You can smell
the old town gang members
from a mile off.
Madam.
You were looking for me?
Chun Yat-wai.
I was going to leave quietly.
There's no point in saying goodbye.
About your problem
and your family's problem,
I'm not able to solve them.
I don't want them to end up being on me.
Get help from experts.
I'm off.
No need for goodbyes.
Why didn't you turn on all the lights?
Be quiet.
Close your eyes.
Give me your hand, darling.
I'm here.
Come with me.
Okay, sit down.
Right. Don't open your eyes yet.
So pretty.
Wait a moment.
Just a second...
and you can open your eyes.
Happy birthday.
♪Happy birthday to you♪
♪Happy birthday to Ms. Tong♪
Come on, make a wish
and blow out the candle.
Thank you.
Hey, what is it?
Okay, watch him for me.
I'll be right there.
What is it?
You know
I've been investigating
the Fu-Ngam Shantytown arson.
I suspect the prisoner
who died in custody was a scapegoat.
There should be someone behind it.
What's the situation now?
I know someone called Lau Mao.
We used to play together as kids.
Lum Chin said
she'd heard him brag
he'd seen the real arsonist.
Then
he left Hokong
and disappeared.
The call tip said
someone saw him in Tuen Shing.
Then move,
go to Tuen Shing District now.
Go.
It's your birthday today.
It can be celebrated at any other time.
Just go.
Then you must wait for me to come back
before cutting the cake.
Why?
Because if you cut it without me,
it'll explode.
Okay.
Sorry.
All right.
Just go.
Sorry.
Wait for me, I'll be right back.
[Eastern District Police Station]
So this is the guy
who got into Hon Gong's room?
Who is he?
Watch the next clip.
That's the same guy.
Didn't expect Hon Lit's drawing
to be pretty decent.
Who is he?
He doesn't look like a gang member.
Of course not.
You know him?
[Self-Discipline and Impartiality]
Mr. Chun, Ms. Tong is here.
Ms. Tong.
Do you have a minute?
Please sit.
Aren't you investigating
Ma San-po's case?
Any leads?
The Special Investigation Unit
is following up on it.
I came
for something else.
How are you and your son
doing lately?
Still arguing?
We're okay.
Why?
The night before last,
he went to the hospital.
He didn't say he felt unwell.
How did you know?
While taking Han Lit's statement
on the Ma San-po case,
he told me
someone had broken
into his brother's ward.
So I went to the hospital
to check the CCTV,
and
this is what I saw.
Just looking at this photo...
And this one as well.
Mr. Chun,
I want to know
why your son
went into Hon Gong's ward
wearing a lab coat.
This photo
looks odd.
I'll go back and ask him.
This is
Hon Gong's ward.
The car that hit Hon Gong
was yours.
Your son
went to check him
in a lab coat.
Do you really think
there's no connection?
I can't answer that.
I'll go ask him first.
And my advice is
you should bring him
to the station immediately
so we can question him.
You can be present.
It's your right.
That is
the best way to clear his name.
What's there to clear?
You know what I'm investigating.
Okay.
I'll arrange it
and let you know.
Okay.
Yat-wai,
where are you?
What is it?
Have you finished class?
I'll pick you up.
[Eastern District Police Station]
Dad,
do you remember
the ice-cream shop by the post office?
Yes.
We used to go every week.
I remember
Mom loved the lemon slushie there.
She said no sugar and milk
made it healthier.
But I didn't like it.
I love sweets.
Still, I just bought a lemon slushie.
Is it good?
It's awful.
I passed by that shop last week.
It was closed down.
Where are you?
What were you doing at the hospital?
The night before last,
why did you go into Hon Gong's ward?
Someone saw you.
You were spotted.
I wanted them to see me.
I'm so tired.
I can't hold on much longer.
You haven't answered
why you were there.
Mom would never act like you.
I'm not your criminal.
I won't answer your question.
[Eastern District Police Station]
Are you looking for Tong Ka?
She finished early
and just left.
Tong Ka.
What's the matter?
Thanks for taking care of my brother.
This is for you.
That's unnecessary.
This is my job.
I said,
it's for you.
Hey, wait,
I can't accept it.
Why did your son
go into Hon Gong's ward
wearing a lab coat?
I can't answer that.
I'll go ask him first.
You should bring him
to the station immediately
so we can question him.
That is
the best way to clear his name.
What's there to clear?
You're back.
Why are you sitting there like that?
You could turn on the TV.
I was thinking.
Thinking?
About what?
I was thinking...
if what I suspect is true,
it'll be hard for me
to accept the truth.
Okay,
let's not talk about work.
So,
what's the plan for today?
I've got it all planned.
First,
we'll go to the buffet
I've been craving for ages.
Then, we'll go
sing karaoke.
So, on my birthday, we're going
to the buffet you've been craving for...
No, it's we!
And the singing
you've been waiting for, right?
Hey,
it wasn't my idea.
Sek asked me to.
He told me to keep you company
for one crazy night.
He didn't want you
to be stuck
with nothing but work and worries.
All right, you're right.
Go get changed.
I'll be ready with my hands washed.
Oh, okay.
Your birthday gift is in the bag.
Open it yourself.
Thank you.
My birthday gift?
That's my breakfast for tomorrow.
Ka,
isn't this too costly
for you as a nurse?
Is this a fake?
That's against customs regulations.
No.
This one
is your birthday gift.
This is...
This is what Hon Lit...
gave me today.
Hon Lit, Hon Fui-lung's son?
His brother is in the ICU.
He thanked me
for taking care of his brother.
He's grateful to you
for taking care of his brother,
so he gave you a watch
worth over a hundred thousand.
I had no idea.
I just saw it
when you opened it.
I warned you not to get involved
with such people.
I didn't.
He forced it on me at the elevator
when I was leaving work today.
Say no more.
Let's go then.
You go get changed.
[Good Fortune]
[Mon Jai Cafe]
This is Hon Lit.
This is Tong Huen.
Madam?
What's the matter?
Can you be at the square in Hung Wa Wai
in 15 minutes?
Okay.
All right.
Hello?
Hello, Ms. Tong.
This is Chun Yue.
I'd like to talk with you again.
Okay.
I'm near your place now.
Can we meet?
Just a bit later.
I'm out right now.
All right.
So, Madam,
did you find who went
into my brother's ward?
Tong Huen.
Here's your watch back.
It wasn't for you.
I don't care what your motive is.
From now on,
stay away from her.
Why?
I don't want my family
tied to any gangs.
What's the big deal about gangs?
[Eastern District Police Station]
Dad.
Where are you?
I'm outside the police station.
What are you doing there?
Can you come pick me up?
Okay.
Stay there, I'll be right over.
Mr. Chun, I've gone home.
You can come anytime.
It's too late today.
Let's meet another day.
Your son
went to check him
in a lab coat.
Do you really think
there's no connection?
You should bring him
to the station immediately
so we can question him.
That is
the best way to clear his name.
Dad.
Don't say anything.
Have some food first.
Yat-wai.
Staying here
only leaves us
with unhappy memories.
If I want to leave,
will you go with me?
Is it because of me?
It's because of us.
I won't get away
if something happens to you.
I already gave false statements.
If we really have to leave,
we'll go together.
Okay.
Good.
We're not there yet.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Get some for your son.
Is it good?
Yes.
Here.
Have more.
Eat some vegetables.
Thanks, Dad.
Here.
It's good you're back.
This is always your home.
Be happy.
Okay.
Eat.
Don't worry about me.
Let me get you some.
Is it good?
Have more if you like it.
Wai.
Hey.
So, can you?
Wai.
I won't make things hard for you.
I don't need you to do it.
I'll take care of it.
Yes or no?
Just say it.
After today,
I don't owe you anymore.
[Hokong Poon Dou District
Evidence Storage Warehouse No. 1]
[Government Property,
No Unauthorised Entry]
It's all weapons.
Please be careful.
Okay.
Take care,
Sir!
What's wrong, Bun?
Got the runs.
I can't hold it.
Need to go to the toilet.
Give me five minutes. I'll be quick.
Sir!
Didn't you notice your tyre's leaking?
Leaking?
You don't ask why I showed up?
You'll tell me if you want to.
I think
there's something you'd want to know.
Is that so?
Last night, around 7 or 8,
I drove past a square
near Ms. Tong's house,
and I saw her
meeting Hon Lit.
Tong Huen and Hon Lit?
Yes.
Ms. Tong was holding
a luxury watch box.
What do you mean?
Hon Lit seemed
to be thanking Ms. Tong for something.
Actually,
that makes it quite clear.
Ms. Tong
has covered up Ma San-po's alibi.
Because she knew Hon Fui-lung
would seek revenge on the old town gang.
To prevent a bloodshed,
she leaked the news
to Hon Lit.
She chose
to sacrifice Ma San-po.
She is a police officer.
How can she disregard
civilian lives?
You said you saw them
meeting in private.
And you saw Tong Huen taking a bribe.
They were just meeting each other.
Ms. Tong might say
she was collecting evidence
from Hon Lit.
And
holding a watch box
doesn't mean she accepted it.
As a judge,
I'd rule
there isn't sufficient evidence.
Then why are you
telling me this?
The police could follow this lead,
check CCTV nearby,
and find the truth.
May I tell you
what I think?
Two weeks ago,
you introduced a client to me.
But you didn't tell me
my client stole your car.
Later,
my client got involved
in Hon Gong's case.
And you knew this all along.
But again,
you told me nothing.
Yes,
you told me eventually
and pointed me to a way
to bail my client.
But how did that turn out?
You saw it.
And today,
you suddenly came telling me all this.
Do you want to twist
this dead story
into something else?
Or do you want
to instruct me again on what to do?
Yes.
You guessed right.
This case
is tied to me.
Thanks, Bun.
You have half an hour.
That's enough.
Wai,
sorry.
I'll repay you
in the next life.
SP650 requesting backup.
We were ambushed at Sum Sek Street.
That's right.
This matter
is closely tied to me.
Because
the one who hit Hon Gong
was my son,
Chun Yat-wai.
I never meant to drag you in.
I only wanted you to help Ma San-po.
But what followed
went completely out of control.
Mr. Chun Yue,
you were my professor in law school.
You taught me what law is,
what justice is,
and that the law
must never bow to the unlawful.
I've always respected you.
Scum, you said half an hour.
Freeze!
Don't shoot!
Hands up!
Don't move!
Don't shoot.
Don't shoot!
Hands up!
Don't move!
Don't shoot.
I don't want to force you.
You can choose not to help me
or act as if this never happened.
And if you think I'm the villain,
you can report me.
I won't help you,
but I won't run away either.
You want to know if I'll report you,
right?
You're the judge.
Guilty or not guilty,
you decide.
But I don't want to hear
your guidance anymore.
I'll clear Ma San-po's name
in my own way.
Lok-man.
I'm sorry.
♪Why is it a cause?♪
♪Like flames
scorching every possibility♪
♪No strength remains
to question the effect♪
♪A crack grew in my heart♪
♪Trapped by karmic flames♪
♪Blinded by the fire,
I can't tell effect from cause♪
♪When right and wrong
are buried, I can't bear♪
♪To see hearts and eyes
blurred by smoke♪
♪Tangled in the struggle
between light and dark♪
♪I sense something near,
veiling truth in shadow♪
♪Confronted by my own conscience♪
♪Who decides punishment and justice?♪
♪How ironic it is to regret♪
♪I asked myself,
but grasped no hidden meaning♪
♪Keep judging morals♪
♪Yet my reason is eroded♪
♪Beneath my feet, the abyss awaits♪
♪Why can't silence be an answer?♪
♪The path back slips beyond my reach♪
♪Falling into fate's hollow mystery♪
♪On this long road to better days♪
♪I forget the heart's
still bleeding within♪
♪Who decides punishment and justice?♪
♪How ironic it is to regret♪
♪I asked myself,
but grasped no hidden meaning♪
♪Keep judging morals♪
♪Yet my reason is eroded♪
♪Beneath my feet, the abyss awaits♪
♪Why can't silence be an answer?♪
♪The path back slips beyond my reach♪
♪Falling into fate's hollow mystery♪
♪On this long road to better days♪
♪I forget the heart's
still bleeding within♪