[English subtitles are available]
[Lost Identity]
[Episode 19]
This is the first time in his life
that he wanted to leave the mines
and go out to fight
for the Communist ideal.
It was that record
of the Chopin piano piece, right?
Later,
I made a joke with him.
We made a bet.
I said,
if you can quit smoking,
I'll give you the record.
I thought, he was a kid
who smoked so much
so it would be impossible.
But after that,
he never smoked again.
So I gave
the phonograph and record
to him.
Later,
I took him out of the mines
and sent him to school.
I asked him the same question.
What question?
Why did he
quit smoking
for a record?
If you see a ray of light
coming through from a distance
in a suffocating, dark night,
you would crawl
as hard as you could
towards that light.
Even if
there were a thousand ravines and obstacles along the way,
you'd do it
because you know
this is
the only way
you'll ever be able to tear the night apart.
That's faith.
That's what
that light and record
did for Lou Mingyuan at the time.
After that,
I cultivated him
and joined the Communist Party.
You are also a candidate
that Lou Mingyuan wants to cultivate.
But...
Come out!
Hurry up!
Hurry up.
Go!
[Greater East Asia Co-Prosperity]
No need to look around.
We've been observing for a long time.
There's no chance.
If they have shifts,
and there are blind spots,
there must be a chance.
Let me remind you.
Here,
one person's power
is very small.
Given the condition of the rock
and the humidity of the ground,
I don't think this is a cave.
I think this is
a subterranean fortification deep underground.
If we want to figure this out,
we need more time
to observe these people.
We have a plan
that needs your cooperation.
Why do you trust me,
a NBIS guy?
We are all Chinese.
What plan?
I can't tell you yet.
But please trust me.
We will make it.
[1945 NBIS Chongqing Station]
What about the body?
Even if the prison was blown up,
there were so many criminals. There can't be
no trace of the body, right?
We found two huge incinerators
in the above-ground incinerator room,
and tons of ashes.
I guess the Japanese
disposed of all the prisoners' bodies before they left.
Ohashi's top priority
was to evacuate immediately,
so these prisoners
became the biggest burden.
That was
the fastest way to handle it.
What's wrong with you guys today?
Picking...
Picking rats.
Picking what?
In 810.
All the prisoners
are lab rats for the Japanese.
They do this twice a week.
Those who've been chosen
will become their virus test subject.
How do they test it?
Fall out!
Hurry up.
Come out!
Hurry up!
-Hurry up!
-Come out!
Hurry up!
Go on.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
Go.
Hurry up!
Hurry up.
Go.
[Greater East Asia Co-Prosperity]
Dr. Mitsui, everyone's here.
That man
is Ichiro Mitsui.
He'll choose one person
to conduct virus experiments on.
And he'll also...
also pick a subject
to study for a cure
for the Ohashi's daughter's disease.
Thank you.
This guy.
That cripple following him is called Liao Zhijing.
He's from NBIS.
[Liao Zhijing, former NBIS Vice Captain of Nanchang Station]
Why did they release him?
These people
gave all their assets
to Liao Zhijing.
This guy is good.
Officer Liao, save me.
Officer Liao.
I'll serve you for the rest of my life.
Officer Liao, save me!
Officer Liao.
I'll do anything for you, Officer Liao!
Officer Liao, save me.
I'll serve you forever.
Officer Liao.
No!
Officer Liao, save me.
Officer Liao.
We are all from NBIS.
You can't just stand by and watch, Officer Liao.
Officer Liao, save me!
Officer Liao, I don't want to die!
Officer Liao, save me! Officer Liao.
Ou Xiao'an.
Officer Liao.
The ace of Chongqing Operations Department,
Captain Wen Yishan's favorite.
Officer Liao.
Mr. Mitsui, that's him.
Take him.
Officer Liao.
Ou Xiao'an.
If you have anything valuable,
just give it to Officer Liao.
At the very least,
you can stay alive, Ou Xiao'an.
Ou Xiao'an.
Take out your valuables.
Since those prisoners were taken to be experimented on,
there's a good chance that
their corpses have terrifying viruses on them.
Do you remember
the drugs they were injecting in this picture?
KW30.
KW30?
KW30
is the latest virus the Japanese are working on.
They are using prisoners from 810
to conduct living experiments.
Every prisoner who was injected with the virus
died very painful deaths.
You remember everything now?
No.
I have
some images in my mind.
Long time no see,
Mr. Ou.
This is where
you torture us, right?
What do you think?
If that's heaven,
then this is hell.
We transported everything
from Shanghai to Burma.
But I felt like
something was missing.
You're what's missing.
Besides,
you still have what I want in your head.
What you want
is not in my mind anymore.
As long as you cooperate with us
and write out the Cherry Blossom Project,
you'll still be my distinguished friend.
I...
I really want to cooperate with you and write it out.
But I can't remember it anymore.
I have no choice then.
Mr. Ando.
He's yours.
Yes.
Mr. Ou.
Please.
After we parted in Shanghai,
I really missed you.
Mr. Ou.
Do you remember
all the data and information
about the virus experiments
in the Cherry Blossom Project  information booklet now?
I...I can't remember.
Mr. Ou,
I'm starting.
This medicine
will amplify the sensations of your tactile nerves.
Here, relax.
The more tense you are,
the more painful it'll be.
Let's start the countdown.
About two minutes.
Now,
you'll feel pressure in your lungs
slowly building up.
Your throat
is filling up.
Your eyes
are swelling up.
Yes.
The pain you feel now
is ten times what you feel in reality,
maybe even a hundred times.
Yes.
Time's up.
Let's move on to the first item.
Here, follow my command.
Stretch your fingers slowly.
Yes.
Slowly.
Open
your hand, yes.
Do you feel like
someone is
trying to break your fingers?
Now, your finger is broken.
Yes.
Is it different from that time in Shanghai?
Mr. Ou.
Now,
we are going to
the second item.
Do you feel
the pressure
on your throat getting worse?
Yeah.
Like you're
suffocating.
Yes.
Suffocate. You can't breathe.
Now follow me,
follow my command.
Yes.
You can only stop when I say stop.
Suffocate.
Stop.
No.
How is it, Mr. Ou?
Do you remember now?
Don't.
Then I can only
continue.
Don't.
No!
♫Find a reason for myself♫
♫I bow my head in times of trouble♫
♫Whenever I raise my head♫
♫And hold on with all my might♫
♫Reaching out to the future♫
♫What's there to worry about?♫
♫Standing hesitantly at the crossroads♫
♫Can't see through♫
♫Let time take care of what I can't bear♫
♫Looking back♫
♫How many worries♫
♫Have long disappeared♫
♫Please remember those clear eyes♫
♫Who's in the turbulent waves♫
♫Who embraced each other in the years♫
♫Who sings every spring, summer, fall and winter♫
♫Who can be manipulated by whom?♫
♫Every face is unique♫
♫Who's in the turbulent waves♫
♫Who holds up the sky♫
♫The ending may not be written in the stars♫
♫In that sky, it will appear♫
♫That rainbow♫
♫Who's in the turbulent waves♫
♫Who holds up the sky♫
♫The ending may not be written in the stars♫
♫In that sky, it will appear♫
♫That rainbow♫
Help! Help!
Someone died!
Help!
Someone died! Help!
Help! Someone died!
Help!
Help! Help!
Drag him out.
Yes.
Help! Someone died!
Someone died! Help!
Is he still alive?
Didn't you say the KW30 vaccine trial
had shown
some preliminary success on him?
No matter what it takes,
bring him back to life.
It's too late.
He's dead.
Bastard!
Yes.
We have to start over again.
Take the body away.
Stop knocking!
Stop knocking.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
What do you want?
Dignity.
It's you again.
We want dignity.
We want food that's fit for humans.
We want longer
out of cell time.
Who are you to negotiate with me?
All of us here today
can guarantee that
any experimental subject you choose
will end up committing suicide.
We'll make sure that
your experiment
never succeeds.
Can we do it?
We Chinese are not afraid of death!
Okay.
Name your terms.
Increase out of cell time by 30 minutes.
Above ground.
We want to see the sun.
Ye Xuanmin.
I could just kill you now.
But it's not the time yet.
Okay.
I can agree to your terms.
But
only here.
Great!
Sir.
Great! Great!
Threatening suicide
in exchange for your rights.
That's how you guys do things, huh?
There's no other way.
The dead comrade
is Shangguan Haifeng.
This was his idea.
I tried to talk to him,
but he felt that, as a
test subject for the Japanese,
if the experiment succeeded,
he wouldn't be able to face
his faith.
So he decided
to end his life
in this way.
Then
are you going to keep doing this?
This is Ou Xiao'an.
He used to be in NBIS.
I hope we can work together against our common enemy.
I want to tell him
our plan.
[Communist Party member Li Manqiu]
Secretary Chen.
I know this agent.
When I was still in Shanghai,
he was already working for the Japanese
and even appeared on the Japanese newspaper.
Traitor.
I think he just wants to be rich and comfortable.
[Communist Party member Li Zhijun]
Who could've forced him if he wasn't willing?
He just wants to live a cushy life.
Alright, stop it.
-Chen…
- Let me repeat myself.
He was undercover for NBIS, not a traitor.
Secretary Chen.
Alright, laugh.
Well...
In 810,
there's no Kuomintang and Communist Party.
We are all Chinese.
We must unite
everyone who can be united
to fight against the Japanese.
Ou Xiao'an.
You've been
studying and observing
the terrain and structure of 810 for the past two days.
Have you ever wondered
why Ohashi built it underground?
It's such a big project
and there are so many prisoners.
Only by building it underground
would it be easier to hide
and escape detection.
Another thing.
We can't distinguish day and night,
so we lose our concept of time.
None of us know
how long we've been locked up.
More importantly,
it's easier to destroy.
Look.
One only needs to blow up
those critical load-bearing walls
[Greater East Asia Co-Prosperity]
and the whole 810
will completely collapse.
After all the projects
under Ohashi's Cherry Blossom Project are successful,
he will quickly
wipe this place clean
and leave no trace.
So the people in here
will never get out alive.
You've come across the Cherry Blossom Project.
You know how scary those viruses are.
There is now a very potent virus
that has been brutally tested on
human beings here
and has been officially named
KW30.
Ohashi has started to
develop the vaccine for this virus.
Once he succeeds,
there will be
controlled mass use in the war.
And all of us
are just Ohashi‘s
lab rats.
We've already reached
the most dangerous moment.
We have to fight.
We are organizing
the comrades who survived the vaccine experiment
to fight against Ohashi
and force him to make some concessions.
For example,
extending the out of cell time
and expanding the out of cell area
so that we can find out
where 810 is
and prepare for a prison breakout.
With this structure,
breaking out of here with a riot
is unlikely.
As long as someone gets out,
we won.
Now,
we need to learn more about what's going on inside.
So we desperately need a comrade
to get close to Ohashi.
I have individual access to the Ohashi.
He needs me to
write out a document for him.
That's exactly what we want you to do.
Try to cooperate with him
to
gain his trust.
Laugh.
[1941, Burma, 810 Laboratory]
How is it, Mr. Ou?
Do you remember now?
Prepare the next set of tests.
Double the scopolamine.
One more unit of pentobarbital.
You shouldn't be so stubborn, Mr. Ou.
You're different from them.
You have choices.
I planted many people in Chongqing.
Just like you,
they always bring me surprises.
D-D-Don't touch her.
Don't touch her.
Okay?
Okay, I promise you.
But the choice
is in your hands.
I'll write.
Smart.
♫Standing hesitantly at the crossroads♫
Make sure you memorize every number
♫Can't see through♫
and every equation.
Ensure that you, Sundial,
and the information in your head
♫Let time take care of what I can't bear♫
leave Shanghai safely.
That's my top priority.
♫Looking back♫
♫How many worries♫
♫Have long disappeared♫
♫Please remember those clear eyes♫
♫Who's in the turbulent waves♫
♫Who embraced each other in the years♫
♫Who sings every spring, summer, fall and winter♫
♫Who can be manipulated by whom?♫
♫Every face is unique♫
♫Who's in the turbulent waves♫
♫Who holds up the sky♫
♫The ending may not be written in the stars♫
♫In that sky, it will appear♫
♫That rainbow♫
I've double-checked it.
There's no problem.
But the Cherry Blossom Project
is way more than this.
Mr. Ou.
You can write out the entire
Cherry Blossom Project.
Yes.
You're amazing.
You can remember
hundreds of pages of information.
From now on,
you have to give me at least 10 pages a day.
Then, I'll put you
in the experimental team of Cherry Blossom Project
to conduct experiments with Dr. Mitsui.
I believe,
with you on board,
the plan will move faster.
10 pages.
Too many.
I can't get that much out in a day.
Chief Ohashi.
Can you get Ando
to stop doing experiments on me?
My head's been all messed up
because of him.
Also,
can I
go out everyday
to get some sun?
Just for a little while.
Let me...
Let me sober up.
Who are you to bargain with me?
10 pages
a day.
I'll help you
write 10 pages a day.
Let me have some sun.
Okay.
I promise you.
I'll let you go up twice a day.
10 minutes each, in the morning and afternoon.
But you must
give me 10 pages.
Okay.
[Military Area]
♫The baptism of blood and fire makes my waiting not in vain♫
♫I still believe you despite my vague memories♫
♫With faith, I saw you and overcame obstacles♫
♫Carry me in your arms♫
♫There will be blossoms in my heart when the sun goes up♫
♫You are exactly as I remember you♫
♫Let the truth in our hearts♫
♫Guide the future♫
♫There will be blossoms in my dreams when the sun goes up♫
♫You and I have never left♫
♫The dawn♫
♫The dazzling sea of flowers♫
♫Is a new era♫
♫How many identities♫
♫Covered by the rainbow, shuttling through the crowds♫
♫Carrying a secret, stuck between a rock and a hard place♫
♫Just for justice♫
♫How quickly things change♫
♫Long-hidden stories, silent soliloquies♫
♫A lonely battle is still exciting♫
♫There will be blossoms in my heart when the sun goes up♫
♫You are exactly as I remember you♫
♫Let the truth in our hearts♫
♫Guide the future♫
♫There will be blossoms in my dreams when the sun goes up♫
♫It turns out we never left♫
♫The dawn♫
♫The dazzling sea of flowers♫
♫The new era♫
What you have so far
is all partial.
I can only go to these areas now.
I can't go anywhere else.
Where is the guard post?
Not counting the prison area,
in the out of cell area alone,
there are four guards
and three more patrols below.
Four shifts a day.
The two shifts after our out of cell time
is the most relaxed.
They often go out for breaks and to chat.
I also heard
that there's...
Ou Xiao'an.
What's up?
I know what you're planning with those guys.
Count me in.
I can give you information.
Which department are you from?
Count you in?
What are you doing?
You guys want to escape,
right?
Have you eaten too much?
Do you think I’ve been in 810
working against my conscience with the Japanese
for nothing?
Let me tell you.
You're not the first person
to try to get out of here.
Plus, you know that
even if you guys manage to escape,
first, you don't know the environment.
Second, you don't know the route.
The Japanese will catch you again really quickly.
I know the coordinates of 810.
The precise coordinates.
Trust me.
You will need my help.
If you know so much,
run away yourself then.
Are you too used to being a traitor
so you're talking to me on behalf of Ohashi?
Do you think I really want to stay here
and be a traitor for the Japanese forever?
I really want to get out.
Ou Xiao'an.
Take me with you.
Or I'll report you to the Japanese immediately.
Hurry up then.
97°26′ E.
What?
The position of longitude of this place.
You're a special agent.
You can do the math based on how you came
and check
if I lied to you.
Think about it carefully.
When you've decided,
come to me with your plan.
I'll give you the exact latitude then.
Take me with you
and you'll have a better chance of getting out of here.