[English subtitles are available]
[Lost Identity]
[Episode 26]
Sir,
now that Zeng Jiwu knows
so much about Ohashi,
could he know
about Li Shaotang's identity, too?
Even if he knows, he won't tell.
Why do you think he's here?
He came to Captain Wei to save his life.
He'll reveal all that he knows
little by little.
That jerk
just wants
to show his loyalty
to Wei Qingming.
But why is he transfered here
to be interrogated?
I guess they want to hide it
from Feng Yunian and Li Shaotang.
Sir, be careful.
All right, don't worry about me.
Does Zeng Jiwu know
your relationship with Lou Mingyuan?
I'm afraid he'll tell Captain Wei.
Don't worry.
I think he knows you.
We met once years ago.
Shanghai is so big.
It's only normal to run into unpleasant people.
I see.
This is the coordinate of the takeoff point.
[106.1 degrees east longitude, 27 degrees north latitude]
Four days later,
he'll go there as promised.
You'll decide who to go and how to do it.
It's all up to you.
I told them to go out just now
because I was afraid others would steal your credit.
Your pledge of loyalty
is quite important.
If you have a secret position in Chongqing Station,
I'll secure my job, too.
Why me?
To be honest,
before I came to Chongqing,
I've conducted thorough research.
At NBIS and the Inspection Office,
you're No. 1.
Captain Wei,
the Japanese can't stir up any waves anymore.
Next,
the mission of the Kuomintang is to annihilate the Communist Party.
That is our strength.
Do you have more important information
to tell me?
I knew I followed the right person.
Among the people Ohashi taken away
from 810,
there's a person in charge of
of a communist underground organization in Shanghai.
Who?
Chen Ke.
Chen Ke?
Yes.
Why don't I remember such a person?
[Talking about Co-prosperity with Japanese Official Ohashi Kazuya]
Ye Xuanmin?
His alias is Ye Xuanmin.
If we didn't run into
Captain Ou today,
I almost forgot
there's an acquaintance next to him.
[Talking about Co-prosperity with Japanese Official Ohashi Kazuya]
Captain Wei,
Ou Xiao'an must have something to do with that.
As long as you know it.
-Wei.
-Wen.
You want to see me?
These are Ohashi Kazuya's coordinates
Zeng Jiwu confessed.
OK.
I'll send someone from the Operations Department over.
You can't do that.
Think about it.
Once the Operations Department makes a move,
Li Shaotang
and Feng Yunian will find out immediately.
So I arranged some peripheral people
for this operation.
All of them are peripheral?
Yes.
I don't think it's appropriate.
How about this? I'll go there myself.
Ask Moqing and Xiao'an to go with me.
If Li Shaotang and the others ask about it,
just tell them
we went to search for the whereabouts of the gas bombs.
Wen, you're so thoughtful.
That's why I invited you here.
But…
you can just take Qin Moqing there.
Leave Ou Xiao'an to me.
I need someone for the case of the gas bombs.
Wei,
are you...
Don't think too much.
I kept Ou Xiao'an
because he's familiar with gas bombs.
Understand?
OK.
I'll do as you say.
Please. Please.
You're welcome.
It's all for the work in the station.
Yes, it's all for the Kuomintang.
I heard that their clothes are quite nice.
Is it silk?
Yes.
Take a look.
This fabric is silk.
This one.
OK. This one. This color is a bit…
-Boss.
Boss.
Come here.
Coming.
Hello.
How much is it?
That one is 216 yuan.
How about this one?
Same price.
Boss.
OK, wait a moment.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
This one.
Is there a big size? For her.
[106.1 degrees east longitude, 27 degrees north latitude]
These are the coordinates
of the plane to pick up Ohashi in three days.
He should be hiding nearby.
Is the news of Zeng Jiwu
reliable?
If he doesn't have any accurate information,
he wouldn't dare to submit to Wei Qingming.
I've dealt with him once before
in Shanghai.
He's been working under Ohashi.
All these years,
he was in the core division of
the Japanese Expeditionary Forces Headquarters.
I don't think his information is wrong.
You dealt with him when you were in Shanghai?
Do you remember that time
when our party needed a passage permit urgently?
When Li made the report, he said
a spy had been watching you all the time.
It was him.
Will he recognize you?
He didn't notice anything at that time.
He only knew that I'm Qin Jiru's sister.
Besides, a selfish person like him
will only do things
good for himself in this kind of situation.
He won't bring up his past experience
as a traitor.
This kind of person has no bottom line.
You should be careful anyway.
Understood.
Our priority now
is to save our comrades ASAP
before the NBIS.
Wei Qingming wants to
achieved a great feat before Dai Li with this.
It's such important information,
yet he didn't even inform
the National Revolutionary Army in Guizhou.
So, I think we still have a chance.
Do you know
Wei Qingming's detailed deployment plan?
He made the decision about the participants
and the plans himself.
I only know that the people and the motorcade of the NBIS
will leave tomorrow morning.
Then, our men
must hurry.
Understood.
Is there any other color for this?
We want two.
Yes.
-Boss.
-It's of the new style.
-Hurry up.
-Boss, go get it.
OK.
Shopkeeper,
We're too busy today.
Come out and help.
The NBIS will take action tomorrow.
You can't be out for too long.
Go back.
I'll get going then.
We won the War of Resistance Against Japanese Aggression!
We won!
We won the war!
We won what?
The War of Resistance Against Japanese Aggression. The Japanese surrendered!
♫Who are you♫
♫An undercover agent♫
♫Working with the enemy♫
♫Who's to judge whether it's good or evil♫
Next, I'm announcing
the latest news.
♫Who am I♫
Emperor Hirohito of Japan announced
♫Fate has twisted and turned♫
that he'd accept the Potsdam Declaration
♫The lone warrior is fearless and persistent♫
and surrender to the Allies unconditionally.
♫Eyes filled with tears♫
♫Because of his ideal♫
♫Carrying old wounds♫
♫Threatened by crises on the battlefield♫
♫Look into the distance♫
♫Far away, yet so close♫
♫Emotions surging♫
♫Hot blood boiling♫
♫The truth and lies buried in the long night♫
♫The more you try to hide it, the more rampant it is♫
[Open]
♫All is not lost♫
♫Never give in♫
♫Who are you♫
♫An undercover agent♫
♫Working with the enemy♫
♫Who's to judge whether it's good or evil♫
♫Who am I♫
♫Fate has twisted and turned♫
[Open]
♫The lone warrior is fearless and persistent♫
♫Eyes filled with tears♫
♫Because of his ideal♫
♫Carrying old wounds♫
♫Threatened by crises on the battlefield♫
♫Look into the distance♫
♫Far away, yet so close♫
♫Emotions surging♫
♫Hot blood boiling♫
♫The truth and lies buried in the long night♫
♫The more you try to hide it, the more rampant it is♫
♫All is not lost♫
[Xiuyuan Grocery]
♫Never give in♫
Shaotang.
The Japanese surrendered.
The Japanese surrendered!
We won!
We've defeated the Japanese!
Breaking news of Xinhua News Agency from Yan'an
[August 1945, Guizhou, Sichuan-Yunnan-Guizhou Area]
Japan announced its surrender
and notified
the governments of America, Britain, the Soviet Union,
and China.
It announced that it'd officially accept the Potsdam Declaration
and promised to sign the unconditional surrender document.
[Wu Guangxian, the detachment leader of the Guizhou Detachment, Sichuan-Yunnan-Guizhou Guerrilla of the Communist Party]
The Japanese Emperor, the Japanese government,
[Yan Dawei, Political Commissar of the Guizhou Detachment, Sichuan-Yunnan-Guizhou Guerrilla of the Communist Party]
and their successors will carry it out faithfully.
Great.
Captain Wu!
Captain, the higher-ups have assigned an urgent task.
What is it?
There's news about Secretary Chen.
[Map of Guizhou Province]
Political Commissar Yan.
This is our base.
This is the Japanese's scheduled takeoff point.
[Bijie] [Shuicheng]
Let's follow this route
and walk to the destination.
The comrades we need to rescue
should be near this point.
I believe Comrade Chen Ke
should be among them.
Because to the east of this area
are the elite forces of the 20th Army of the CNP.
To the west of it is our guerrilla area.
Even Japanese
dare not hide there.
It will take about five or six hours
to walk there from here.
Let's set off now
and get there before Chongqing's NBIS.
As long as we keep quiet, move fast,
and don't draw the 20th Army's attention,
we'll have a chance of success to rescue our men
before the CNP.
Sergeant of the 1st Platoon!
Yes!
Notify all the people in the 1st Platoon. Emergency muster!
Wait, Sergeant.
Inform Doctor Ding
to bring more medicine and bandages.
The comrades we need to rescue
may all be suffering from serious injuries.
Yes!
Political Commissar Yan, you are so thoughtful.
I think you must go together.
Yes.
I must rescue Secretary Chen
in person.
Emergency muster!
Comrades,
this operation is in the CNP-Ruled Area.
The Party asked us
to make it clear that our priority is to save people
and get out of here whole.
We just won the War of Resistance Against Japanese Aggression.
Our area is sensitive.
Remember,
don't easily fight with the National Revolutionary Army.
We can't give them any excuses
at this critical moment.
Do you understand?
Yes!
Let's go!
Turn left.
Run!
Who is it?
Secretary Miao, Captain Wei is looking for you.
Tell him I'll be there soon.
Come in.
Captain.
You want to see me?
Let's have a drink today.
This wine
is to celebrate
and to take an oath.
After fighting for so many years,
we've finally driven away the Japanese invaders.
Now we can
focus on dealing with the Communist Party.
Captain,
do you still want me
go on investigating the case of 810?
As you said,
find those gas bombs and biochemical weapons
and catch all the communists.
You don't have to
worry about this.
Let them investigate.
Miao,
all these years,
you've followed me from Beijing to Chongqing
and helped me a lot.
You also saved me many times.
Especially these years.
Thank you.
It's time to rest.
Actually, I asked you here
to tell you something.
I knew long ago
that Mao Renxing
is not a Japanese spy in our station.
Then tell me.
Who on earth
is this spy?
This time,
his Japanese master has left.
He should give himself away.
What do you think, Miao?
Miao?
In my view,
it should be soon.
I think so, too.
Soon.
We won.
Yes, we won.
Why are you alone?
They all went out to celebrate.
Why didn't you go?
I'm saving my celebration wine
to drink with my comrades.
Me?
Do you know anyone else?
You have to wait until
after my operation this time.
Then, I'll just wait. No hurry.
Your goal this time
is not only Ohashi Kazuya, right?
The prisoners of 810 are included, too.
What do you mean?
Let me remind you.
Our teacher has always been sharp-sighted,
but his eyes are
not only staring at the Japanese.
Don't worry about me.
We've won the war.
I will bring back
whoever needs to be captured or saved.
But, then again,
the Elk is still threatening
the safety of Chongqing.
That's what we should worry about.
I'll keep an eye on Miao Jiang.
She's just like Li Shaotang now.
We can't find evidence about them.
So what there's no evidence?
Wei Qingming trusted her so much before.
But now,
he didn't inform her about the operation.
It means Wei Qingming is also suspicious of her.
Sir.
We finally won.
Finally.
Moqing,
come with me.
Where?
Guizhou.
The latest news from the Central News Agency:
our country is going to celebrate the victory
after Japan signs the surrender document.
The celebration is scheduled to last for three days.
Every organisation will have a day off.
The central government has made every decision.
And it will be carried out after all provinces and cities get the news.
After hearing the news of Japan's surrender,
the streets of Chongqing are full of people celebrating.
Excuse me.
What's going on?
Officer,
I just received a secret telegram from Shanghai.
The Emperor has indeed made an announcement to end the war.
People from Shanghai have arranged a flight for us.
We can leave tomorrow.
Inform Chongqing
to take action.
Yes.
Get ready.
Set off as soon as the plane arrives.
Yes.
What about these people?
You wait for my order
with the main force here.
Get Mitsui and the files on the plane first.
Get rid of what can't be taken away.
Transfer the rest to the cellar.
I'll arrange a car to pick you up.
Yes.
Why are you here again?
You are in such a hurry to leave Chongqing.
You haven't said goodbye.
Qin Moqing has started to suspect me.
She just doesn't have any evidence yet.
That's easy.
We can help you get rid of Qin Moqing.
Get rid of her?
How?
Can you get rid of everyone in the Chongqing Station?
The war is over now.
I can't help you even if I stay in Chongqing.
The holy war of Empire of Japan is not over yet.
Haven't you heard?
His Imperial Majesty has surrendered.
His Imperial Majesty won't surrender!
Tanaka Koji,
wake up.
Now, you are
a loser.
I'm a loser.
What about you?
You poisoned Ando Motoyoshi
and stole Wei Qingming's approval letter.
You betrayed special agents and framed Mao Renxing.
If Wei Qingming
finds out about these things,
you think you can live?
Besides,
if you run away now,
I can shoot you immediately.
Be good
and cooperate with us.
One day,
you'll be of no use.
-Miao Jiang!
-So?
I should just wait for you to kill me?
C-Calm down.
Miao Jiang.
Listen.
Even if I'll die,
I'll kill you first.
Miao Jiang!
Secretary Chen.
Hurry up.
Hurry up!
Take these two weak men out
and throw them into the river.
Yes.
Secretary Chen.
S-Secretary Chen!
Secretary Chen!
Manqiu.
Is that you?
Secretary Chen.
You're awake.
I'm dying.
Leave me here.
Go now.
F-Find our members.
Reveal the Japanese people's sins
to the world.
Secretary Chen!
Secretary Chen.
Don't worry.
I'll save you and take you back.
Captain,
we found traces of the Japanese people's trucks ahead.
They're new. They went southeast.
How many trucks?
Two.
Looks like there are not many of them.
I think we can take care of them.
Yan,
let's split up.
Okay. Move now.
Thank you.
What's the situation now?
You guys guard here, understand?
Yes.
You stay here.
Okay.
Save them!
Gonglai.
You finally came.
Are you okay?
Where is Chen Ke?
Secretary Chen hasn't been feeling well
and has been having a high fever.
Manqiu also got sick later.
The Japanese saw they were dying,
so they asked someone to take them away.
Looks like we are still late.
Right,
Ohashi... Ohashi has run away.
He's at the nearby airport.
Ohashi!
Who is he?
He's a member of CNP.
Sir!
Please save me.
If you save me, I'll leave CNP
and join the Communist Party.
I'll join the Communist Party.
We came back together.
We are all brothers who have faced life and death together,
you can't just watch and do nothing.
Sir.
Sir, I beg you.
Please save me.
Get up.
Listen carefully,
I don't care if you're from the Chinese Nationalist Party or the Communist Party,
we are all Chinese,
and we must not fall into the hands of the Japanese.
Stay close.
Captain,
the Japanese are back again.
Captain Wu, what should we do now?
Retreat quickly.
Run!
Go!
Get up. Hurry.
Yan,
you take the wounded and retreat first.
What about you?
I'll cover you,
otherwise no one will be able to leave.
Mr. Cang.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Major, there are enemies over there!
Go!
It's too late. Take care of the wounded.
Wu.
Gun.
You just barely escaped death,
do you want to die again?
Run!
Didn't I tell you to retreat first?
I also want to kill Ohashi
and avenge our fallen compatriots.
Well done!
Fire!
Wu, what's wrong?
Where is he?
Oh no! It's the Japanese's gas bombs.
Retreat!
Hurry up! Go!
Hurry up!
This way.
Don't go over there.
There is also gas over here.
Everyone, cover your mouth and nose tightly,
and get down on the ground.
Lu Ziming.
I'm late.
Everyone, put on your gas mask quickly.
-Gas masks.
-Hurry up!
-Give me one.
Give me one.
Alert!
Chief Ohashi.
What's going on?
There are trees blocking the road.
We can't pass.
Getting someone to clean it up immediately.
Yes.
Group one, clear the roadblocks.
Group two, stay on alert.
Sir, slow down.
The airport is right ahead.
The road is destroyed,
Ohashi will definitely stop the vehicle here
and have people unload the goods
to send them over.
Got it. I'll arrange an ambush.
We still need to wait for someone.
Who?
He should be here soon.
Zeng Jiwu?
Have Zeng Jiwu follow the original plan to meet Ohashi,
and then get him on the plane.
This way, Ohashi won't be suspicious,
and we'll have a chance to act.
Got it.
Vice Captain Wen, Section Chief Qin.
Wei has told you what to do, right?
Don't worry.
I've been with Ohashi for so many years,
he definitely won't be suspicious of me.
Section Chief Qin,
I actually recognized you the last time
we met at the Huajiang Villa,
but I was too embarrassed to say anything.
I apologize for any offenses I may have caused before.
Please forgive me.
It's nothing.
Don't mention it.
I'm now wholeheartedly serving the Kuomintang.
Enough.
Saving those words for after we capture Ohashi
and expressing loyalty upon returning to Chongqing.
Okay.
Communicator.
Yes.
Send a telegram to Captain Wei,
and tell him everything is proceeding according to the original plan.
Yes.
Driver, drive the car away.
The rest of you, follow me to the mountain to ambush.
Yes.
Come in.
Secretary Miao,
this telegram is sent to Captain Wei from Guizhou.
[Confidential case]
Wait.
Guizhou?
Don't you know?
I heard that Ohashi Kazuya
is hidden in Guizhou.
See you.
Okay. Got it.
Secretary Miao.
Captain, this is a confidential report from Guizhou.
Take a look.
[Confidential case]
[Guizhou Operation Report]
The brigade has arrived in Guizhou,
deployed according to plan,
and has reached the airport route.