[English subtitles are available]
[Love is an Accident]
[Episode 5]
Zhao.
Chuyue.
Come over here quickly.
Sit down.
Hottie,
where should I sit?
You...
Look what we've got today.
Chongyue Pavilion is under renovation,
and only this bench is available for now.
How about you sit with Zhao?
Come on.
Here.
I'm sorry.
No worries.
Let me help you with it.
Thank you.
I was too careless.
Never mind.
Here, take it.
Greetings, Madam.
Jingzhao.
Chuyue.
Bai Zhi.
Today, we're having a family feast to savour springtime and pray for blessings.
It's inconvenient for an outsider to join us.
Madam.
I didn't mean to interrupt you.
It's just that I was so willful back then
that I took the liberty of fighting a duel with Chuyue
and frightened her.
I feel guilty about it.
So I came here today
to apologize to Chuyue.
Chuyue,
it was my fault that day.
I shouldn't have fought with you
and startled you.
I'll now make a toast to you as a token of apology.
Here.
Come with me.
Miss,
do you take a liking to An Jingzhao?
Don't deny it.
Girls feel girls.
To be honest,
I don't like An Jingzhao at all.
Soon,
I will leave here.
So you don't have to pick on me.
I can even set you up.
Really?
Yes.
I, Li Chuyue, am a man of my word.
With me being here,
An Jingzhao will fall in love with you soon.
Then you will get married shortly.
And you will soon become Young Madam.
How about this?
You take a sip of the wine,
and I'll make a toast to An Jingzhao later.
In this way, you'll be kissing indirectly.
Wait here.
Young Lord,
thank you for helping me draw the Talisman of Cure today.
Here's to you.
I don't drink from the same cup as her.
Oh no.
Jingzhao drank the wrong cup.
Jingzhao,
may I have a word with you?
There's no outsiders here.
Just talk here.
Zhao.
Follow me.
[Black Eagle Hall]
Master.
We can't wait any longer.
In a few days,
the wedding will be held.
It's the finest hour for us to take action.
What's your plan?
Master,
how about this?
In a few days, the wedding will be held.
Many people will attend, and the scene will be chaotic.
We can send some assassins
to disguise as people from the Beiming Sect
to assassinate An Jingzhao.
Firstly,
it's easier for us to take cover in a crowd.
Secondly,
An Jingzhao will surely be defenceless.
By then,
we can get rid of him
and that woman.
Assassins?
They can't defeat An Jingzhao.
To deal with him,
we have to take him unawares
and strike a deadly blow.
Oh no.
The two cups of wine were swapped by mistake.
I am the one who got poisoned.
I have to go back immediately and take the antidote.
Jingzhao,
I'm not feeling well.
Let's talk another day.
Dongyue.
They are having a private conversation.
Yet Hottie asked me to join in.
An Jingzhao.
Li Chuyue, what are you doing here?
Get out.
What's wrong with you?
Where's Bai Zhi?
What's going on?
Stand right there.
Don't come over.
Don't come near me.
An Jingzhao?
An Jingzhao.
An Jingzhao, what's wrong?
Based on my experience in watching dramas...
You took something, didn't you?
Did you take the wrong medicine?
Stop talking nonsense.
I said get out!
Leave now!
You're getting hot under the collar.
Don't tell me you took that one!
Stay away from me. Don't come nearer.
An Jingzhao.
I told you to get out.
Go!
Fine...
Based on my experience in watching dramas,
you did take the wrong medicine.
Why is the door locked?
Is anyone outside?
What's going on?
I can't.
Bro!
Put me down!
Master.
Bingqin is back.
Bingqin has cultivated the 10th-level inner power of the Tianxuan Heart Sutra.
With her around,
An Jingzhao will surely be killed with one fatal move.
No.
An Jingzhao made a diversion
to fool me.
I will also
give him a taste of his own medicine.
Master is wise.
Dying in the bridal chamber
will be a big gift
I prepare for An Jingzhao.
Master,
I have something that came to my mind.
An Jingzhao's bridal chamber is not in Lingxiao Yard
but
where his mother prepared for him,
Hese Pavilion.
Hese Pavilion?
[Yunwei Villa]
On such an auspicious occasion,
the wind is mild and the sun is bright.
The happily married couple
is a perfect match.
May happiness be with you today and always,
like lovebirds in the sky.
On the wedding night,
pleasure permeates the entire household.
Okay.
How could the prestigious Yunwei Villa
take such a rude woman as the bride?
It's my fault.
I was negligent in my daily life
and failed to teach her manners.
You are a little mean
but full of masculine charms.
If a girl marries you in the future, that's not bad.
What's your standard for choosing a partner?
In other words,
what kind of wife do you want to marry?
She should be a short one,
right up to my shoulder.
In terms of appearance,
she's not even close to being beautiful.
They're married now.
She's not a gentlewoman.
And she has no manners.
Your criteria for choosing a partner is so odd.
Are you blind?
Yes.
I'm blind.
The red decorations cast a glow in the hall,
and we send our best wishes through the wedding song.
The auspicious time has come.
-Could you please behave yourself?
-Bow.
First, bow to heaven and earth.
Come here.
Second, bow to your parents.
Bow.
The bride and groom bow to each other.
Can you be serious?
It's just a show.
What are you so serious about?
Protect Young Lord.
Don't be afraid.
Just a few small potatoes.
Everyone,
don't panic.
It's just a few remnants from Beiming.
The wedding continues.
Please return to your seats.
How could you lift it up
before you're in the bridal chamber?
I'm sure I can go back this time.
I surely can make it to registration in time.
Go back.
Oh no.
It's all over this time.
Li Chuyue.
Keep your chin up.
There must be a way to go back.
Don't be so discouraged.
Thank you.
Enjoy yourselves.
I wish you live happily ever after
and have a baby soon.
Ling.
Chiefs.
Here.
Thank you.
[Hese Pavilion]
You...
Father.
Grandmother.
Today is my wedding day.
Let me propose a toast to you.
Sure.
Pour me more.
Young Lord.
Congratulations on your marriage, Young Lord.
Although
it's Thousand Cups from Fengnuan Pavilion,
I think there's also
Cold Lake from Yunwei Villa in the wine pot.
No amount of masking
can hide the rich aroma of Cold Lake.
Am I right?
Second Lord.
Young Lord.
Whether it's Thousand Cups or Cold Lake,
they're both great wines.
A fine wine should be toasted to a perfect match.
Right?
Yes.
Everyone, please have a seat
and continue drinking.
Sure.
Sit.
Everyone, please continue drinking.
Sure.
Here.
There is also Bamboo-leaf Green in the wine.
I'm afraid you'll only taste it after a while.
Why are you here?
The guards have besieged here.
You can hardly escape now.
If you reveal the conspiracy to the Lord,
the Young Lord will surely spare your life.
Tianxuan Heart Sutra?
How do you know how to use it?
Do... Do you want to get to bed early?
Young Lord.
You are hurt?
Bingqin...
has cultivated the Tianxuan Heart Sutra.
It seems that when we wiped out the evil sect,
Yuan Shu had already copied the Heart Sutra.
We must find out
what else Yuan Shu has done.
Yes.
I can't believe she cultivated the 10th level directly.
That's reckless.
It seems that Zhou Wei has taken another action.
Do you still remember the mantra I taught you?
Go back and cultivate it.
It can help with your recovery.
I remember.
Don't worry, Young Lord.
I'll heal myself.
I wonder how Li Qing is doing.
I've taken care of it.
I sprinkled enough powder on my body.
The assassins' feet
must have got a lot of it on them.
According to the traces of the powder,
Li Qing should be able to find their base.
Young Lord's plan
will surely catch Zhou Wei off guard.
Master.
All the men we sent are dead.
No one survived.
I knew it. You're just a bunch of losers.
Search carefully
and see if they have any clues on them.
Yes.
How is it?
It's neat,
leaving no traces.
Let's go.
A wound caused by a sword?
The swordsmanship is amazing.
Only Li Qing in the Yuwei Hall
can do this.
Find out the source of this fabric.
Don't let any clues go.
Yes.
How are you?
Are you okay?
I-I think we haven't had...
the Hejin wine?
What other customs do you have?
I want to try them all.
When I go back,
I can brag to my parents and Yang.
Fine.
Since you want to experience everything,
I'll let you try everything.
The consummation is also included.
No way.
You can't do this.
We're having a fake marriage.
Besides,
I'm into my Prince Charming, Gu Qingfeng.
I can't let my Prince Charming down.
Right?
What's so good about him?
He is the Prince Charming of our Design Department.
He's well-built
and handsome.
Above all, he is talented at designing clothes.
Don't you want to drink the Hejin wine?
I'm back.
I'm finally back.
I told you
I'm from another world.
I'm not an assassin.
Now you know that it's true.
Where are we?
This is my hometown.
So I can hear the sound coming from here.
Things from your bedroom
fall into mine.
So I actually heard you talk.
It was not from the game at all.
Could it be...
we can talk to each other in different rooms?
In that case,
I don't know why
there's a passage
between your bedroom
and mine.
Moreover, the bed
may be the passage.
Then why is there a passage?
Why would it connect the two worlds?
What's the mechanism?
How could I have forgotten the computer?
Wormhole?
Is it really because of the wormhole?
Multiverse?
Multiverse usually refers to the idea
that beyond the observable universe,
other universes that are similar to it
may exist as well.
Perhaps it's the wormhole
that opens the passageway between the two worlds.
I can't clarify it
with my flimsy scientific theory.
But
when we kissed,
we travelled from your bedroom to mine.
Don't tell me kissing can open
the passageway between the two worlds.
That's not right.
The first time I went there,
I was sleeping well alone.
Oh yeah.
The registration.
Sign-up...
[Emerging Fashion Design Competition]
[Sorry, the registration is over]
It's been seven days in Shangyu.
Seven days have passed here as well.
So the two worlds have the same time.
We can only think of another way.
Dad.
Mum.
Go and cook.
I'm hungry.
Yang.
What are you doing? Sit down.
-Sit properly.
-What are you doing?
Don't come out.
Cover yourself.
Li Chuyue, did you purposely...
-W-What happened to you?
-Yang!
I miss you so much, Yang.
Yang,
I thought I would never see you again.
What's wrong with you?
You always say you get annoyed when you see me.
We haven't seen each other for a few days.
Yet you are cuddling me now.
Let go of me first.
Let go.
But I can also ask for money for the cuddle.
No problem.
By the way,
why did you send me a message on WeChat?
I just want some pocket money from you.
No problem.
Here.
Take it.
Y-You're dressed like this too?
Don't tell me you two...
Him?
He's an extra for a commercial
for our company.
Advertise.
An extra?
Dad!
Mum!
My sister brought a man home.
Dad and Mum are here too?
A love rat?
What? What love rat?
Where is the love rat?
Love rat! Move!
Dad, Mum.
-You brat.
-I miss you so much.
What are you wearing?
Wait.
The love rat.
The...
Young man,
what's your name?
Where are you from?
What do you do?
I am...
Shut up.
Him?
We were discussing work.
He is a model hired by our company
for a commercial.
Don't listen to Chuyang's nonsense.
Model?
Dad, Mum.
Why are you here?
Are you going back today?
We haven't seen her for days.
Is she in a relationship?
We have to size him up.
No.
We'll stay for the night.
Okay.
This model,
I'm in the middle of cooking.
Tell me what you'd like to eat.
Yes.
Whether it's Sichuan, Hunan, Shandong or Cantonese cuisine, choose whatever you like.
Dad, Mum.
He's a guest. Don't scare him away.
Let's talk outside.
Come on.
You're right.
Let's cook first.
Help yourselves.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
Go. Hold on.
Hurry up.
Are you going to leave him here just like that?
What love rat?
Hurry up. Let's go.
A love rat.
I don't have any nice clothes for you.
Where's my phone?
Where is it?
What kind of sleeping gas is this?
Oh no.
If Zhou Meizi knew I was absent,
she would kill me.
Answer me.
Yes.
It's sleeping gas.
But I
took the antidote in advance.
It's very effective.
The inhaler will lose his consciousness immediately.
Why are you doing this to me?
What do you want?
What else could it be?
You're so young and good-looking.
So I want to do something bad.
Just kidding.
You took it seriously?
That's called a humidifier.
If you put water inside,
water will become steam
and make the air less dry.
How should I put it?
Our technology
is more advanced.
Many things don't involve manual labour anymore.
For example, music doesn't need live accompaniments.
You can play it after recording.
Xiaodu.
Play "Baby" by Justin Bieber.
Do you hear it?
This is the song I sang that day.
Xiaodu.
Play "The Ordinary Road."
This is my Prince Charming's favourite song.
Play another one.
This song is not bad.
It does suit your temperament.
Then what is this?
This
is called a computer.
It connects to the Internet to look up information.
You can browse websites
and read information around the world.
It's the same as spreading the news
about what happened to the sects
immediately to the others in your world.
You can also watch movies and dramas.
Look.
Be careful.
That's fake.
Don't worry.
That's the screen.
Time to eat.
Go on.
Li Chuyang.
Hurry up and get changed.
I won't change into
these fancy clothes.
You are the Young Lord.
It's your call.
Remember to tie your hair.
It's a drama.
It's to film the story with equipment
and air it on TV.
This is our mode of transport,
the car.