[English subtitles are available]
[Love is an Accident]
[Episode 16]
An Jingzhao.
How are you?
-Brother-in-law. -Young Lord.
Young Lord.
An Jingzhao, stop pretending.
Do you think I'll be fooled
just because you're handsome?
Let me tell you. I've quit the desire.
An Jingzhao, are you really not okay?
I was just saying it.
Quitting the desire for men is more difficult than quitting meat.
I'm not able to do it.
Wake up, An Jingzhao.
An Jingzhao.
Don't worry about me.
Just now, I gave treatment to myself with the spell
which my grandmother told me about.
I'm fine now.
But I feel a bit cold now.
Can you help me?
Let's leave at once.
Sister, we have to go.
My brother-in-law's health is the most important thing.
You should do whatever he says.
Let's go.
Forget it.
I should wait until he recovers.
So warm.
How are you? Are you feeling better?
Much better. Don't worry.
After you fully recover,
you should go back to your world at once.
We should go back together.
We are from two different worlds.
Who wants to go back with you?
Li Chuyang, come here.
Sister.
Come on. Take this
to An Jingzhao.
Sister.
My brother-in-law is still very weak now.
Besides soup,
what he needs most
is your love, care and company.
Then he can recover faster.
If this is helpful for the young lord's recovery,
Young Madam,
I can share your burden.
I can give him love.
This is not something you can help with.
Don't make trouble.
Don't look down on me.
I'm the strongest man in the Yunwei Villa.
From now on, you should shut up.
You...
Sister.
My brother-in-law has been depressed because you ignored him.
If this continues,
not only will his health not recover,
but his condition will also get worse.
Sister, please save this kid at once.
How can you describe our young lord as a kid?
Young Madam.
Our young lord is the manliest man
in the martial arts world.
He's not a kid.
What a stupid teammate.
You want me to leave?
Yes.
I want you to look me in the eyes and say it.
An Jingzhao.
-Young Lord! -An Jingzhao!
-What's wrong? -Young Lord!
What’s wrong?
Sister,
we'll go buy some supplements for my brother-in-law.
Let's go.
Come on.
You haven't fully recovered yet.
Come on. Lie down.
Just lie there and don't move.
I'll bring you the soup.
Chuyue, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have kept it from you.
Just take a rest to recuperate first.
I don't want to hear anything now.
My internal force hasn't recovered yet.
Chuyue.
Considering that I'm a patient,
don't be angry. Okay?
What did you say? I couldn't hear you.
Drink the soup and get some rest.
I don't want to drink it.
Take a rest if you don't want to drink it.
I want to eat fruits.
[How to ask your girlfriend for forgiveness? Articles About Romantic Relationships]
You can take a rest now, right?
Chuyue.
After I kill Zhou Wei,
I'll finish all the things
on your wishing list with you, okay?
No.
I'm sorry, Chuyue.
I know I shouldn't have kept it from you.
But I didn't tell you
because I was really afraid that you would be worried.
I promise that from now on,
I will protect myself well.
Okay?
Don't be angry.
An Jingzhao, you know nothing.
I...
I don't want to see you anymore.
[To Chief of Beiming Sect]
Give this letter to the people of the Beiming Sect.
Tell them
as long as they follow our arrangement
and act in the show of eliminating the evil sect for me
in order to help me become Chief of Yunwei Villa,
from now on,
I won't stop them from doing anything,
and half of the Yunwei Villa will be theirs.
Master,
are you really going to share the Yunwei Villa with them?
Are you really stupid?
If I want to use them as pawns,
I must make the bait sound very attractive, right?
As long as I become Chief of Yunwei Villa,
we can turn this fake show of eliminating the evil sect
into reality, and it'll be fine, right?
Master, you're wise.
Have you found out where An Jingzhao is?
I've dispatched half of the men in the villa to look for him,
but they didn't find An Jingzhao's trace under the cliff.
I think he must be dead.
What about An Jingling?
Master Jingling was hit by the Cold Ice Palm.
He has been sick in bed lately.
Let's go.
Let's go visit Master Jingling.
Chuyue.
Where on earth are you?
Are you safe?
When can I see you?
Master Jingling, the second lord is here.
Why is he here?
Master Jingling.
Second Lord.
Are you feeling better now?
Much better.
Thank you for your concern.
I should have come to visit you earlier.
This is too absurd.
Bingqin should be blamed for being too reckless that day.
She wanted to kill the assassin who broke into the villa,
but she hurt you accidentally.
It's all right.
Bingqin acted like this because she wanted to
protect the villa.
Come on.
Let me see how well you've recovered.
Don't bother, Second Lord.
It's okay.
Fortunately, my elder brother taught me in advance
how to disrupt my heartbeat with a spell.
How about this?
I'll exert my inner force to help you heal your wound.
Don't bother, Second Lord.
The disciples of our villa give treatment to me every day.
That's good.
I won't disturb you any longer.
An Jingling won't live long.
The next one is that old woman.
We must kill her at once.
Otherwise, there will be more trouble.
Tell the disciples of my hall
to surround the Chongyue Pavilion.
Don't let even a fly come out.
Yes.
Because of the young lord's death, the old madam
is heartbroken and is critically ill.
I'm afraid she won't be able to survive these one or two days.
Spread this news.
If she dies, she will die of illness.
I won't be blamed.
I'll do it right away.
There's one more thing.
Although An Jingzhao is dead,
we still haven't seen his corpse yet.
It's still a hidden danger after all.
We can take this opportunity
to verify it again.
If he is still alive,
when he hears that the old madam is critically ill,
he'll surely understand that the old madam is my hostage.
He'll definitely come back to rescue her.
Master, you're wise.
Chuyue.
Ms. Qiao.
Why do you look so sad?
Nothing.
Give me the notice.
You passed the second test.
This is the notice.
[Notice]
[Li Chuyue: You've passed the second round of the New Apparel Designer Competition]
[Now you're officially invited to participate in the final of the competition]
-Thank you, Ms. Qiao. -Don't be happy so soon.
This is just the second round.
You still need to participate in the final.
In the final,
competitors need to present their own design drafts.
That's the final test.
I will work hard
to get a prize.
There's still half a month before the competition.
With your current level,
you can only focus on one thing.
So, you don't need to
come to work in the next half month.
You should go prepare for the clothes.
But that's the maximum amount of time I can give you.
You should work hard after you come back.
Okay, okay, okay.
Ms. Qiao.
Bring me the fragment
on my desk.
Okay.
In your design,
you've used a lot of extremely soft and exquisite fabric
and the elements of embroidery.
Normally, when embroidery is used on this kind of fabric,
it'll deform.
So,
we must find
very good embroidery techniques.
I've found this piece of
embroidery which may suit your clothes.
Although it was made many years ago,
this technique is very rare.
You can take it to look for this technique.
Ms. Qiao, please accept my bow.
Your cutest brother will treat you to dinner tonight.
Okay.
Give me a few minutes.
Let me finish.
If you want to leave after that, I won't force you to stay.
Ten minutes. I still have work to do.
I didn't let you go back with me that day
because I received the news that
Zhou Wei was going to kill Ling.
Although the plan of fake death
has made Zhou Wei relax his vigilance,
he still won't believe it easily.
Are Hottie and Jingling all right?
They're fine.
Don't be angry, okay?
Do you know why I'm angry?
We agreed to be together.
At a dangerous moment like that,
we should face it together,
instead of letting me hide away to avoid danger.
Right. It's my fault.
But I did this because
you are the most important person to me in the world.
I can't put you in danger.
I know you did this for my own good.
But you didn't tell me anything.
I didn't know
what kind of danger you would encounter.
I didn't even know that you almost lost your life.
It's my fault.
It's my fault. I made you worry.
What I need is that
no matter what happens,
we should face it and solve the problem together.
Okay?
Okay.
No matter what happens in the future,
we'll face it together
and solve the problem together.
Have you recovered from the injury caused by the Cold Ice Palm?
Don't worry about me.
I have practiced
according to the spell which my grandmother told me about.
I'm feeling much better today.
Who's worried about you?
I haven't forgiven you yet.
There's one more thing I want to tell you.
There will be thunder and rain tomorrow.
I need to go back to the Yunwei Villa again.
Everything is going according to plan.
I will save Ling and my grandmother from the villa
so that they can get away safely.
Now I have nothing to hide from you.
I won't hide anything from you anymore.
Can we make up with each other?
You promise?
I promise.
Young Madam.
I have something to say.
Since our young lord met you,
he has always cared about you.
He has changed from a pure young man
to someone who loves his wife so affectionately.
Everyone is jealous about
his love for you.
Just don't be angry.
Young Madam,
please forgive our young lord
so that the fans of
loving couples like us
can smile like an aunt.
Is the statement online wrong?
I'm a man.
It should be smiling like an uncle, right?
Alright. I forgive you.
You haven't seen what I prepared for you.
This is a photo of you when you were five, right?
At that time, your dream was to
eat all the snacks, right?
So I've brought some snacks.
I made these snacks myself.
They're snacks from the Yunwei Villa.
I hope it's not too late to bring them here.
In that case,
it seems we once went to school together.
When you studied, I practiced martial arts skills.
We both worked hard for our career.
So,
it's not a big deal to belong to two different worlds.
As long as we are together,
there's nothing we can't overcome.
How come there's no other content after that page?
From now on,
we'll be together forever.
We will never be apart from each other.
Let's fill it up little by little.
[Yunwei Villa]
This letter must be sent to the Qixia Mountain.
[To Master Xuanfeng]
Madam, don’t worry.
Madam, since you will hold a ritual for the young lord tomorrow,
I'll ask someone to send the letter out with the excuse of
going out to buy incense.
There are Zhou Wei's spies everywhere outside.
Tell the messenger to be very careful.
Don't let them find out.
Don't worry, Madam.
Madam.
Zhou Wei.
What do you want to do?
At this point,
there's no need to pretend between us.
You can choose one of these two things.
Before I die,
I want to see Chenghu.
It's natural for you to feel like seeing him.
Sure.
I...
I want to go closer and see how Chenghu is.
Go.
Chenghu!
My son!
What happened to you, my son?
Chenghu!
Don't listen to Zhou Wei anymore.
-He wants to take the villa away! -Madam.
He's just a treacherous man!
-Madam. -He's just a treacherous man!
It's almost time for you to leave.
We should go.
My lord.
The old madam has been feeling unwell recently,
and she has many misunderstandings towards me.
Madam.
His Lordship needs to rest quietly.
Let’s go.
Chenghu.
Chenghu!
My son!
Madam.
I think you should give up.
Zhou Wei,
I have one last request.
What is it now?
Tomorrow is the seventh day after Zhao's death.
I want to hold a ritual for Zhao.
Sure.
Find a way
to replace Zhou Wei's men in the Lingxiao Yard.
The priest will send disciples
to pray in the Lingxiao Yard.
I've replaced the disciples
with our men who are very reliable.
By then,
they will find a way to replace Zhou Wei's guards.
Okay.
Don't let Zhou Wei find Zhao's trace.
Master.
The old madam asked someone to send a letter, and it was intercepted at the Qixia Temple.
The letter says that she wants to have a get-together with Master Xuanfeng at the Chongyue Pavilion.
Xuanfeng?
The old madam wants to get reinforcements.
It's not that easy.
Amitabha.
Madam, the young lord will surely ascend to the paradise soon.
My condolences, Madam.
-Madam. -Madam.
I've sent my disciples to the Lingxiao Yard
to see the young lord off.
Thank you, Master.
Amitabha.
Follow them. Keep an eye on them.
Don't let them play any tricks.
Yes.
As you expected,
there's something fishy about these people.
There must be a secret in the Lingxiao Yard.
Maybe An Jingzhao is still alive.
Madam.
Since the ritual is over,
please go back.
Madam.
That's the wrong direction.
Where do you want me to go?
Lingxiao Yard.
Be careful when you go back.
Don't worry.
I'm ready.
Why don't you let Donghua go back with you?
You can take care of each other if there's any problem.
It's easy to attract attention if there are many people.
No need.
According to the weather forecast,
there will be strong thunder and lightning in six hours.
Can you come back tonight?
Don't worry.
I'll be back as soon as possible.
Okay. I'll wait for you.
It's the first time that I’ve come to the young lord's bedroom.
The decoration is really elegant.
[Lingxiao Yard is full of Zhou Wei's spies. Zhao, be careful when you come back.]
Grandmother.
There will be thunder and rain at 3 p.m. in three days.
You must delay the time of my father regaining consciousness.
Besides,
since Zhou Wei has strengthened his defense in the Lingxiao Yard,
let's change our plan.
When you send the letter to Master Xuanfeng,
Zhou Wei will definitely send someone to follow the messenger.
Just purposely let Zhou Wei's man
intercepte the letter.
Then send the letter to Master Xuanfeng secretly.
This is the first step.
Secondly,
when the priest goes to the Lingxiao Yard to deliver the joss paper,
ask our men to mingle with the crowds
and deliberately give away the hidden information.
This matter will definitely make Zhou Wei suspicious.
He'll suspect that I'm still alive,
and will be sure that I might appear in the Lingxiao Yard.
[Chongyue Pavilion]
Is An Jingzhao really dead?
Madam.
It's time to make a choice.
An Jingzhao
hasn't shown up till now.
That means he's really dead.
Madam.
Second Lord.
Xuanfeng wants to see the old madam.
Xuanfeng?
Yes.
Zhao once saved Master Xuanfeng.
So,
Master Xuanfeng has come to attend Zhao's ritual.
Madam, what a good tactic you've used.
You deliberately let me intercept the secret letter,
and then sent
the real letter stealthily.
Send my message.
The old madam is seriously ill. She can't see any visitors.
Yes.
Second Lord, Master Xuanfeng has barged in.
We couldn't stop him.
If he knows that the old mandam is killed by me.
it'll be unjustified for me to become Lord of Yunwei Villa.
Put away the things.
Yes.
Madam.
Master Yunwei.
Second Lord.
How are you, Madam?
People outside have been saying that you are seriously ill.
I'm fine.
I'm feeling much better after resting for a few days.
That's good.
I've been dealing with some chores near the villa.
I've come to the villa to talk to you.
Second Lord, sorry to bother you.
Don't say that, Master Xuanfeng.
The old madam has been in a low mood recently.
Please help to ease her anxiety.
Amitabha.
Madam, enjoy your chat with Master Xuanfeng.
I'm leaving.
Second Lord.
There's something unusual in His Lordship's residence.
Let's go have a look.
Father.
-Zhao. -It’s me.
How come it's you? Well...
What's going on?
Why is there a chain?
Help me up.
Zhao.
How come it seems that I have forgotten many things?
Father, you've finally recovered.
Father, Zhou Wei has been lying to you.
He fed you with the medicine that made you lose your mind,
and asked you to do everything according to his intention.
Nonsense!
Zhou Wei is my buddy who has gone through many kinds of danger with me.
He was the one who saved my life.
That's why I was able to establish the Yunwei Villa.
He would never do such a thing.
Father, I'm telling the truth.
Zhou Wei was once a member of the evil sect.
He disguised himself as someone with a decent background and entered the Yunwei Villa.
His purpose is to take over the Yunwei Villa.
He has always had this ambition.
He repeatedly hurt me.
He sent people to guard the Yiju Hall day and night
and fed you with the medicine that made you lose your mind.
If it weren't for Dr. Luo who gave you treatment...
An Jingzhao?
Are you a human or a ghost?
Surround the house.
Don't let even a fly out.
Yes!
Surround the house!
Father.
Anyway, you must believe in what I said.
Zhou Wei sent someone to kill me.
Fortunately, I took precautions in advance
and jumped off the cliff to escape.
All these years, he has been obedient to me.
I didn't expect that
he was actually so ambitious.
There's no time to lose. Let's leave now.
Okay.
Father.
Leave at once!
Father!
-Leave at once! -Why are you doing this?
Leave at once!
Zhao. Zhao.
There is a secret tunnel here.
You should leave at once.
Let's leave together.
With my condition like this,
neither of us will be able to leave by that time.
Don't worry. I'll protect myself.
After you arrange everything,
you can come and save me, and it won't be too late.
Be good. Go.
Go!
Go! Go!
How is it?
Things have changed. The young lord has been discovered.
Don't worry, Madam.
I'll protect the young lord.
Okay.
An Jingzhao,
You must come back safely.