Xingrou?
Is it you?
Cheng Xun?
Thank goodness. You're alive.
It's been 5 years.
Where have you been?
[Blazing Elegance]
[Episode 18]
So that's how it is.
So you're Eldest Miss Huo now?
But I hope you
can keep this a secret for me.
Especially...
Especially from Yi Qiuting.
Don't worry, I won't say a word.
Thank you.
Don't be so polite.
I really didn't expect
that the legendary Eldest Miss Huo
everyone talks about
is actually you.
Xingrou,
you've really changed a lot.
Circumstances forced me to.
So,
was what happened to the Duan family orchestrated by you?
That's right.
But actually, I wasn't the only one targeting the Duan family.
Dad, don't go.
I won't leave.
I'll stay here with you.
Go to sleep.
Yi Nian's fever has gone down.
Prepare some light food for him.
Yes, Grand Marshal.
You're just leaving like this?
Are you planning to spend the rest of your life
only looking after this child?
Mom, Yi Nian had a fever all night yesterday.
We're not even sure if he's really yours.
Mom,
I don't want to hear this again.
And I don't want Yi Nian to hear it either.
Yi Nian is my child.
So you don't plan to marry in the future?
I am married.
My wife has passed away.
How much longer are you going to stay this stubborn?
It has been so many years, and you're still alone.
Look at how others are living.
Do you even know what people are saying about you?
Mom!
This is my personal matter.
If you can't accept it,
just forget it.
You...
Grand Marshal.
I asked the teacher from the kindergarten
and the candied haw vendor.
Based on their descriptions,
we drew this portrait.
Nian.
Did the lady you saw look like this?
She's much prettier than this.
How about this one?
No wonder when I first met her,
I felt like I'd seen her somewhere before.
Dad, is that lady my mom?
But isn't Mom in the cemetery?
How did she come out?
I can't explain it either.
Then go find her and bring her back quickly.
Grand Marshal, we need to be cautious about this matter.
People can look similar.
What if she's just a woman
who looks like Madam?
She approached Nian twice,
which shows she has intentions toward him.
No matter what,
let's find her first.
Let's use Nian as bait
to lure her out.
But...
What if she really isn't a good person?
Will the Young Master be in danger?
I'm not afraid. I'm willing to do it.
[Hangcheng Nanhe Kindergarten]
Don't get out of the car.
There are people watching nearby.
But I just feel like
that child is waiting for someone.
Maybe he's waiting for me.
Didn't you say
you've confirmed he's not related to you?
But I don't know why,
I just can't help but want to come and check on him.
From the surveillance around,
it looks like that child is being used as bait by Yi Qiuting.
Does he already suspect that you're not dead
and have returned to Hangcheng?
Very likely.
Yesterday, when I was with the child,
someone saw me.
Let's go.
Okay.
[Hangcheng Nanhe Kindergarten]
Nian, why haven't you left yet?
Here, you can play with this.
Be careful.
Come on. Let's go.
Why hasn't Mom come yet?
Mom...
I've been waiting for so long.
Dad, why hasn't Mom come yet?
Let's not wait anymore.
Let's go home.
That person may not be your mom.
Mom has passed away.
I shouldn't mistake others for my mom.
Let's go.
When we get back, I'll give you your favorite chocolate,
okay?
Come on.
Miss Huo,
have you made a decision about the meeting
with Yi Qiuting?
Building the military supply factory is urgent.
I should meet him in person.
This matter is indeed very urgent.
But aren't you afraid Yi Qiuting might recognize you?
From how he's had surveillance around Yi Nian,
it seems he's already started to suspect.
It's alright.
I have a plan.
Grand Marshal,
We've investigated the area near the kindergarten several times,
but still haven't found
a woman matching the description in the portrait.
Should we issue a wanted notice?
She hates me so much.
Even if she really is alive,
she probably wouldn't come to see me.
Grand Marshal.
No need for a wanted notice.
Just continue to strengthen
the protection around Yi Nian.
Yes.
Now, let's talk about the Huo family.
The Huo family is building a military supply factory in Hangcheng
with the purpose of supporting the resistance against Japan.
They want the government office to provide strong support.
The one coming for the meeting this time
is Eldest Miss Huo herself.
Miss Huo has been stirring things up outside.
I thought she would be like those opportunistic politicians,
doing some superficial work.
I didn't expect her
to actually be doing something substantial.
However, up to now, there hasn't been a single photo
of this Eldest Miss Huo published in the newspapers.
And we haven't figured out her background either.
As long as it's beneficial to the war,
no matter how big a trap she has set for us,
it's worth trying.
Marshal Yi, please stop.
Miss Huo, you invited me for a talk,
but you're avoiding me.
Why?
I am unsightly
and not suitable to be seen.
That's why I can only meet with you
in this way.
I hope you understand.
Alright.
Since you have your reasons,
I won't force you.
Thank you.
Let me get straight to the point.
We still need the government office's
strong support for water, electricity, logistics, and land
for the factory we're building in Hangcheng.
This voice...
Why does it sound more and more familiar?
Marshal Yi,
are you listening to me?
Miss Huo, did you grow up in Gangcheng?
Why do you ask?
I can hear a bit of
the Hangcheng accent in your speech.
My nanny is from Hangcheng.
I grew up with her,
so I picked up some of the accent.
I see.
Sorry for interrupting you, Miss Huo.
It's just that hearing you speak
reminded me of an old friend.
To be precise,
it reminded me of my late wife.
It's a business meeting,
but I unintentionally started talking about personal matters.
Miss Huo, what you mentioned
about building a military supply factory
is a great thing
for the country and the people.
I will naturally give my full support.
That's good.
But there's one more thing that requires your decision.
Please, go ahead.
The war is in a critical state,
and there aren't many available places.
So,
the location we are considering for the factory
overlaps with the Yi family's ancestral burial ground.
What do you mean?
Are you planning to dig up my Yi family's ancestral graves?
If I wanted to,
I would have done it long ago.
Miss Huo,
you have quite the bold tone.
I don't wish to fall out with you either.
Why don't you take the initiative to relocate the graves
and make things easier for everyone?
Make things easier for everyone?
It seems more like you're taking advantage of the situation to force me.
Marshal Yi, don't be hasty.
You can take some more time to think about it.
But the war won't wait.
The sooner the military supply factory is built,
the sooner it can serve the soldiers.
I've never heard that
the factory site would take over the Yi family's ancestral burial ground.
I made it up.
He kept bringing up the past.
Grand Marshal.
Did the negotiations not go well?
This Eldest Miss Huo
certainly lives up to her reputation.
Grand Marshal, are you praising her?
Praise her?
She's about to dig up my Yi family's ancestral graves.
Am I supposed to praise her?
This Eldest Miss Huo
was truly aggressive.
But we've never had any dealings with her.
Why did she force you like this?
Maybe she wants me to prove my sincerity.
Or maybe she just has a peculiar temperament
and was using me for amusement.
What should we do then?
What else can we do?
Relocate the graves.
Wouldn't that be giving in to her?
The military supply factory
is a matter of national importance.
My personal pride is insignificant in comparison.
Let's go.
I never expected Yi Qiuting
would actually relocate his ancestral graves so obediently.
But to be fair,
although Yi Qiuting has done many things
that wronged you,
he's competent in his official duties.
I know what I'm doing.
That's good.
Oh, by the way,
I'll be leaving Hangcheng in a while.
The world is in such chaos now.
Where are you going?
Abroad again?
No.
No. I'm going to Northern Shaanxi.
Northern Shaanxi?
I've made up my mind.
"A man should take up his weapon
and reclaim the lost land of his homeland."
I believe only there
lies the hope for the future.
When are you leaving?
I can prepare several carts of medicine
and go with you.
That would be great.
But right now, the checkpoints are strict.
It may not be easy to get the medicine out of the city.
I can talk to Yi Qiuting.
Well...
Wouldn't that be too risky?
Isn't that the Grand Marshal?
The Grand Marshal has never been interested in women.
Why did he come to a pleasure house today?
He's been single for too long.
I guess he couldn't bear the loneliness anymore.
Young Marshal?
Oh, right. Grand Marshal.
I apologize for not welcoming you from afar.
I didn't expect you would really come here to find me.
What's wrong with this place?
You've been saving yourself all these years.
Now, you suddenly stepped into this place of pleasure.
I'm sure the gossip outside is spreading like wildfire.
Isn't this exactly what you want?
Please forgive me, Grand Marshal.
Life is long,
and I'm bored.
So I had to
find some entertainment
to pass the time.
You're treating me as entertainment?
You really aren't afraid of dying.
That's because I know
you have a reason that you must see me.