Stop pretending.
What are you doing?
Yi Qiuting has gone missing.
At a time like this?
And his subordinate, Division Commander Chen Peng,
has already defected to the Japanese army.
That old bastard Chen Peng.
What did you say?
I said Chen Peng knows how to read the situation.
Now is our best opportunity.
Stop hiding here.
Get discharged from the hospital quickly.
Why?
Haven't you always wanted the Yi family's military power?
I'll give it to you.
So what do you want to do?
Occupy the government office,
kill all the anti-Japanese leaders,
and incorporate the Zhejiang Army.
Jinyao,
can we stop doing things
for those Japanese?
Those Japanese are all beasts.
They...
You're beyond help.
I just not want it anymore.
[Blazing Elegance]
[Episode 22]
I'll have to personally
transport your batch of medicine,
so I might be gone for a few days.
To Lianyungang?
No, I'm taking it directly to Datong.
Once I get there,
I can't continue by rail anymore.
I'll have to use a horse caravan to get it in.
There's a Huo family trading house in Taiyuan.
I can send someone to assist.
Alright.
I've already spoken to the Shanxi Army.
They'll at least do me this small favor.
Aren't you afraid of crossing the precinct?
Are you...
worried about me?
What are you thinking about?
Mom,
why hasn't Dad come for several days?
Dad's on a business trip.
He'll be back soon.
Nian,
if I take you to live in Gangcheng,
would you like that?
Will Dad come with us?
Just the two of us.
I don't know which to choose.
I love Dad,
and I love you too, Mom.
I like it when the three of us are together.
Come here.
It would be easier if Dad were a bad dad,
then I wouldn't miss him.
Yi Nian.
Mr. Wu, how is it going?
Yi Qiuting has already come back.
The Huo family's trading house in Taiyuan has received the goods.
They've switched to a horse caravan
and should be delivered soon.
We owe him a lot this time.
Are you planning to forgive him?
I can't do that yet.
What is Marshal Yi doing?
I don't know.
Why is he kneeling in front of the Huo Mansion?
He offended Eldest Miss Huo?
Who is this Eldest Miss Huo anyway
that she can make Marshal Yi kneel?
Dad.
Dad, why are you kneeling?
Isn't that the young master of the Yi family?
Why is he staying at the Huo Mansion?
Yes, indeed.
I miss your mom.
Mom, please let Dad come in.
Turns out they're a family.
The Yi family's young master's birth mother is always a mystery.
Turns out it's Eldest Miss Huo.
What exactly do you want?
I want to live with you and Nian.
You've brought this upon yourself.
Don't blame me.
Xingrou, where is this?
This is a room specially prepared for you.
For me?
I'm not used to you being so proactive
all of a sudden.
Don't speak.
Xingrou, what are you--
Just wait here for me.
Xingrou.
Xingrou!
I want to see Zhao Xingrou.
I want to see Zhao Xingrou!
Have her come see me!
Madam.
No.
Miss Huo.
I understand
you have many personal grievances with the Grand Marshal,
but please understand the current situation.
If the Grand Marshal doesn't return soon,
the morale of the troops will be in chaos.
Alright.
I will let him go back tomorrow.
Thank you.
How does it feel to be imprisoned?
Xingrou,
you've finally come to see me.
When you imprisoned me in the Small Mansion,
you weren't as delicate as you are now.
As long as it makes you feel better,
you can imprison me
or torture me
as you like.
Really?
Really.
If you truly love me,
then try to preserve your chastity.
Xingrou,
what are you doing?
Make them leave.
Xingrou!
Don't come near me.
Don't come any closer!
Let go of me!
♫Love, as it should be, your silhouette♫
♫Flutters with the glow of a heartbeat♫
♫Under the vast starry sky, glancing back♫
♫Love, as it should be, paints my essence♫
♫You let me live more like myself♫
♫Memories like endless fireworks♫
♫Love, as it should be, your silhouette♫
♫Flutters with the glow of a heartbeat♫
♫Under the vast starry sky, glancing back♫
♫Love, as it should be, paints my essence♫
♫You let me live more like myself♫
♫I remember it all♫
Your inner conflict has been resolved?
After all, he is the Governor.
You can't really hurt him.
You're awake.
Xingrou.
I have some bad news to tell you.
Your training has failed.
Impossible.
I don't believe it.
Take a good look at yourself.
You didn't pass the test.
Leave.
Impossible.
How could this happen? No way.
No way.
Grand Marshal, stop drinking.
Get out!
Get out now!
Go get some hangover medicine.
Xingrou.
Who is he?
You go in first.
Who is he really?
He is my husband.
What did you say?
I forgot to tell you.
I got married in Gangcheng.
Impossible. I don't believe it.
Believe it or not.
Xingrou.
Let go.
Can you not treat me like this?
Who do you think you are to say such things?
Miss Huo,
dressed like this,
I hope I'm not causing you any trouble.
Of course not.
In fact, you've done me a favor.
What did you just say?
Grand Marshal looked very upset.
I said I got married in Gangcheng
and you're my husband.
Grand Marshal must hate me now.
But this way,
he should give up
and stop looking for me.
What about your child?
I'll take Nian back to Gangcheng.
Will he agree?
I'll see whether Yi Qiuting has the ability
to take Nian away from me.
By the way, Miss Huo,
the real reason
I came this time is to ask you
for a favor.
Go ahead.
Several professors from Central University
have some collections,
like antiques, rare books, and manuscripts.
They're worried these items will be destroyed in the war,
so they want to have them transported to Gangcheng for safekeeping.
Do you think you could help
transport these items out?
That's easy.
We've rescued a batch of cultural relics
in Beiping before,
so we have some experience.
That's great.
Don't worry.
Get in the car first.
It's rude to stare at my husband
like that.
The marriage of the Huo family's young lady is such a big event.
How could there be no news at all?
Our family was in chaos back then.
So we got married in secret.
But you're already married to me.
How could you remarry someone else?
The one who married you was Zhao Xingrou.
She's already dead.
And I am Huo Xingrou.
I'll do anything you say.
I'll take any beating or scolding.
I won't argue or make a fuss.
Just think of me as a little cat or dog
you keep.
Will you please consider it?
Okay.
I'll think about it.
Then please consider it quickly.
I can't wait.
Xingrou.
You can stay here.
But I don't want to see any servants.
I don't want others to know about our relationship.
Okay.
I want you to be here every day,
so I can see you whenever I come by.
Okay.
Lastly,
and most importantly,
I don't want my husband
to know about our relationship.
Okay.