Who are you exactly, sir?
[Huo Shaoying]
You're...
Miss Duan,
I know you want the position of the head of the Duan family.
But your lover, Yu Junren, has failed
and was sentenced to five years in prison.
What are your plans next?
What do you mean?
I can help you.
There's only one condition.
Kill Zhao Xingrou for me.
She's protected by Yi Qiuting
and a martial arts expert.
It won't be easy.
If you can do it,
I can offer you very favorable business resources.
You should know
what it means to be a business partner
with our family.
Alright,
I agree.
[Blazing Elegance]
[Episode 14]
[Keep quiet]
Xingrou.
Didn't we agree to come for the prenatal checkup together?
Thanks, doctor.
Why didn't you wait for me?
I can manage on my own.
Why would a woman come for a prenatal checkup alone?
What if you get hurt?
[Keep quiet]
Don't worry.
I'm accompanying Miss Zhao.
For something like a prenatal checkup,
you must be here too?
My duty is to protect Miss Zhao.
[Clinic Room]
Take it slow.
Xingrou, I'll go pay the fees first.
You sit here for a while.
How is it? Is the baby doing alright?
I'll be able to see him in just two more months.
[Clinic Room]
Ma'am, are you alright?
Mr. Wu,
why don't you help this lady to see a doctor first?
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Alright.
[Clinic Room]
Careful.
Someone come here!
Hurry, hurry!
Xingrou.
[Clinic Room]
Xingrou!
Quick, block all the exits!
Hurry, don't let anyone leave!
Yes, sir.
Hurry!
Young Marshal.
How is she?
Madam has lost too much blood.
She's still unconscious.
Due to lack of oxygen,
I'm afraid we can't save the baby.
Please prepare yourself for the worst, Young Marshal.
I'm telling you,
I don't care what methods you use,
you must save them both!
Do you understand?
Go now!
[Operating]
Yes, sir.
Weren't you responsible for protecting her?
Why was she shot?
It was my negligence.
Who is it this time?
[Operating]
Yu Junren?
Duan Jinyao?
Or my parents?
It could be another group of people.
You still won't tell me the truth even now.
Who hired you?
Who wants to harm her?
Senior, please tell us.
I really can't say.
I don't care who it is.
I will make them pay for this.
Xingrou.
Where's the baby? The baby?
The baby...
The baby is fine,
just a bit weak,
and needs to be in the delivery room for a while.
Is it a boy or a girl?
A boy.
He looks a lot like you.
You've suffered a lot.
[Delivery Room]
[Ward One]
Young Marshal, the child is not going to make it.
Continue the rescue efforts.
Don't tell Xingrou.
[Delivery Room]
Alright.
Okay.
Yes, that's right.
I haven't fulfilled my responsibilities.
I will explain to the employer.
Okay, I understand.
I'll make the arrangements.
Yi Bingyao!
Grand Marshal!
Chase!
What are you burning?
Bricks again?
Where did you get them?
I've been wandering the world for so many years.
I have saved up some money.
Didn't you say you wanted to start a family?
Consider this as my wedding gift to you.
I don't want it.
Keep it for yourself.
You don't want it?
Then throw it into the river.
Are you planning to run away?
Young Marshal and Madam were assassinated.
Your employer wants to cause you trouble.
So you're running away, aren't you?
You got half of it right.
What about the other half?
The other half...
I can't tell you.
Wu Chongmo, what do you take me for?
You play with me when you're happy,
and toss me aside when you're not.
What can't you tell me?
We can solve it together.
I'm staying at Ningshuang's place tonight.
Do as you please.
Bingyao.
Murder.
Arson.
You insisted on giving her fertility drugs back then,
forcibly altering the balance of yin and yang in her body,
resulting in damage to her internal organs
and a disruption of her vital energy.
She probably won't be able to get pregnant again.
[Delivery Room]
Is there no other way?
Young Marshal, I've told you before,
those fertility drugs would...
You gave me fertility drugs?
[Ward One]
Xingrou, let me explain.
Yi Qiuting.
You're terrifying.
Do you even see me as a human being?
I just wanted to get you into the Yi family.
You keep saying it's for our love,
but it's clearly just for yourself.
You're selfish
and cold-hearted.
You'll do anything to achieve your goals.
That's not true, Xingrou.
Don't come any closer.
Maybe we were wrong from the very beginning.
You have your mission,
and I have my own life.
If you hadn't forced me to stay by your side,
we wouldn't have
ended up like this.
Without you, I could have had a better life.
[Delivery Room]
Xingrou,
let's start over,
okay?
Yi Qiuting,
if you truly realize your mistakes,
then let me and the child leave.
Let us live our own lives.
Can you do that?
[Delivery Room]
This poor child.
So beautiful, yet didn't live for even a day.
Young Marshal's wife was shot in the chest
and lost so much blood.
It's a miracle she survived.
The baby...
Baby.
My baby.
[Operating]
The baby's awake. The baby's alive!
Young Marshal, it's a miracle!
My whole life
has been like a joke.
No parents,
hurt by my lover,
even lost my child.
This poor child.
So beautiful, yet didn't live for even a day.
Should I resent the unfairness of fate?
Or blame someone?
If I hadn't been with Yi Qiuting,
would I not be so miserable?
Yi Qiuting,
don't make me hate you!
Qiuting.
Then hate me.
He did make some mistakes.
You insisted on giving her fertility drugs back then,
forcibly altering the imbalance of yin and yang in her body,
resulting in damage to her internal organs
and a disruption of her vital energy.
She probably won't be able to get pregnant again.
But he has already done enough for me.
It's this world that can't tolerate us.
If I continue to stay by his side,
neither of us will be happy for the rest of our lives.
It's better...
to be free.
Oh no! Someone jumped into the river!
Hurry. Go save her!
Young Marshal.