[Kang So Ra]
[Jang Seung Jo]
[Strangers Again]
[Locales, organizations, characters, agencies, and incidents in this drama are not real. This is a work of fiction.]
[Episode 12]
It's because of Ha Ra, isn't it?
Think whatever you want.
Fine, I'll ask Ha Ra.
Don't ask her!
Fine, I'm the one who ended things.
I dumped Ha Ra, not the other way around. Happy?
And you know... technically speaking,
I never came here with impure intentions from the beginning.
It just ended up that way.
Oh, you dumped her?
Why?
Why are you so interested in your employees' dating lives?
Hey, you should get some therapy, at least.
There's a place I go to, so try paying a visit.
And why should I do that?
Hey! Whenever I see you, I—
You don't even know what you really want and
just keep going around, twisting your life.
You can't keep playing around with your life
like that, twisting it around.
You'll only get hurt by whomever you meet.
Eun Beom, there's no paradise on the run.
You need to keep that in mind, punk.
[Complaint]
[Claim for Disconnection of Parental Relations]
[Episode 12: Give Me a Big Hug]
Why did you guys break up this time?
- S-Sorry?
- I heard from Goo.
I heard you two dated again.
Why did you break up this time?
I heard you got dumped again.
What excuse did that bastard use this time?
You should've heard the whole story from him.
Why are you asking me after only listening to half the story?
Must I say everything with my own mouth?
Well, he says he dumped you, but he's acting like it was the other way around.
And you... seem to be doing better than he is.
Is he even playing the victim now?
Who would be okay?
It's not like it was just a fling.
I'm doing my best to look okay.
But I'm not... exactly doing well, either.
He says he'll leave our firm.
Why are you two doing this when you like each other?
Why did you break up again this time?
I don't think liking each other alone...
is enough for it to work.
Between him and me.
Our personalities are too different and...
Different and?
He doesn't want kids...
and I do.
Our outlooks in life are different.
[Paradise]
[Goo Eun Beom]
- Hello?
- Mom, are you nuts?
You must be very bored.
Why are you putting effort into doing such a meaningless thing?
What? A meaningless thing?
That's my last warning to you.
If you don't listen to me again this time,
I'm going to completely disown you.
- You know Ji Yoon, don't you?
- Who?
She's Mrs. Hwang's daughter.
Gong Ji Yoon.
She got divorced this spring.
Her husband screwed up.
Go on a blind date with her and marry her.
She said she's all right with it.
Mrs. Hwang's okay with it, too.
Mom... is marriage a joke?
Did you tell her and Mrs. Hwang that I don't want to have kids?
Why won't you have any kids?
Stop talking back and marry her.
Then have just two kids.
I'll do everything you want me to do after.
Instead, if you refuse...
I also don't need a son...
who wants to live as he pleases...
in such an ungrateful manner.
So I'm going to file a suit and
disown you from the family register!
Money spent on raising you...
your college expenses...
all of the money I spent on you!
I'll get all of it back.
I'm not joking, all right?
Go ahead and file the suit.
Go ahead and do whatever you please.
I'm the one who wanted to completely cut ties, to begin with.
I'm also—
I also held back a lot!
Did he go to the restroom?
What's this?
[Complaint]
[Claim for Disconnection of Parental Relations]
[Calculation of Requested Reimbursement]
What are you doing with someone else's stuff?
Hey...
What the heck is that?
I don't know.
Didn't you make up with your mother last time?
How the heck did it come down to this?
I don't know, either!
About why she keeps harassing me after giving birth to me.
So what will you do?
What else? I'll have to go with it since she wants a suit.
In my opinion...
it's a luxurious expression of...
something like...
a threat, honestly.
This is luxurious?
I've never seen such a lowly threat in my life.
Should we help him at the office level?
I saw that the other party...
had hired five or six lawyers.
He told you not to care about it, didn't he?
Saying he'll take care of it.
Then just let him be.
Would he want the whole office to know about his family business?
It's Attorney Goo we're talking about.
Even so... it's because he might pull some weird shit off by himself out of anger.
Keep an eye on him, you know?
Why are you so caring about Attorney Goo, though?
People would think he's your son.
Not an employee.
I feel like I'm looking at myself.
When I broke up with Mi Ok...
So, because you feel his pain as yours,
you want to hold his hand?
I do want to.
Just like how you held my hands, CEO Hong.
In my case...you helped me first when I was bumming around after getting a divorce
since my career was on a break, CEO Seo.
However... don't you think I'm paying back that debt for too long?
What do you think?
I hope Goo Eun Beom, that punk, will understand my feelings.
Gosh, why do I even bother arguing?
Yes, Mom.
Oh, you're already there?
I'm almost there. Very close.
Yes. Yes, see you later. Okay.
Oh, hello. I'm here for a reservation under Im Sook Jeong.
Oh, come this way, please.
This is the table.
- Wait, excuse—
- Hello.
My name is Joo Sung Yoon.
O-Oh, I think he brought me to the wrong table.
N-No, he didn't.
This is the right table, Ha Ra.
Well, yes.
It's a blind date our mothers scheduled behind our backs.
I also didn't know and found out after coming here.
Wait...
You already parted ways with him?
Mom, what are you trying to do? It's so tacky.
Do you know how flustered I was?
It's because you wouldn't go unless I do that.
I told you I'm seeing someone right now!
- Why on Earth—
- But that's Eun Beom.
I don't like him.
I absolutely don't want Eun Beom!
I called him over to tell him I don't like him and to break up with you.
Didn't he tell you about it?
What?
You called him over?
I heard from my church's deacon that you two seem to be dating again.
What can I do?
I knew you'd never tell me the truth, so...
I called him over and confirmed it.
He said I was right.
In the meantime, your mother is telling you to break up with me.
When?
When was it?
It was last week or the week before that.
Mom, how could you—
You should've called me over and talked to me.
Why would you call him and—
For not letting me get held up by a nutcase like you...
I'm really way too thankful.
I didn't even know that and...
What did you say to him, exactly?
What could I possibly say?
I just told him to break up with you.
I didn't even beat around the bush.
I was watching him sitting in front of me and it made me so furious, so—
Mom, please!
This is really unbelievable.
I'm really disappointed in you today, Mom.
For the first time in my life, I'm seriously disappointed in you, Mom!
Ha Ra...
Ha Ra... Ha Ra...
Ha Ra!
It's my fault.
Ha Ra...
H-How can you leave like this?
Well, he says he dumped you, but he's acting like it was the other way around.
[Goo Eun Beom]
[Bi Chwi]
If you've something to say to them, just say it!
I'll take care of things after.
- One second.
- Sure.
Yes, Ha Ra.
What's wrong with your voice?
I-I'm at the family meet-and-greet right now.
Oh, that's right. Your families were meeting today.
I-I don't think I can talk for too long.
They're almost here...
Yes, let's talk tomorrow.
Yes. Bye.
What are you doing in a room without its owner so early in the morning?
You were summoned by mom and told to break up with me, weren't you?
Why... didn't you tell me?
What's the use? Nothing good will come out of it.
Are you a mama's boy for your mother-in-law?
Just because my mom told you to break up with me, you do it right away?
I didn't break up because of your mother.
- Don't be mistaken.
- I'm mistaken?
You wanted to break up with me.
It's because of that, not your mother.
If we didn't have a problem, I would've convinced...
your mother, no matter what.
I wanted to break up with you?
What the heck are you saying?
I mean...
Anyhow, it's all said and done.
Do we have to replay it again?
Forget it.
Then just tell me this.
What's your basis for saying that I wanted to break up with you?
[Sister]
I...
Hurry up and call me.
Mom's going to submit the complaint to the court right now.
You should know when to stop, too!
What's up? Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Then finish what you were saying.
What were you about to say about yourself?
I...
I felt it wholeheartedly.
After seeing that shit between my mom and me...
I told you so many times, Mom. Whenever you do this, I get so sick of you!
How dare you say you get sick of your own mom in front of her.
Is that something you should say?
It's too scary that a family you can't cut ties with will be created.
After I told you everything about my family honestly, you wanted to end things with me.
Hey... h-how could you know my feelings even I don't know—
After chasing after a person so crazily,
you started thinking about how to back out after a certain point.
How do you think...
I felt watching that happen?
Chasing after so crazily?
On top of that, I thought about backing out?
I did?
You didn't?
In the end, you got back together with me because...
I chased after you crazily and broke up with me because...
of my fault only, huh?
You're really—
Forget it. Never mind.
What you said is right. It's a replay.
Let's quit it.
What was I hoping to gain?
What are you doing?
I-I was just curious about what you were talking about.
Let's get a meal together later.
[HeadacheN.]
A Claim for Disconnection of Parental Relations?
Such a claim exists?
Apparently, there is.
Although they were all rejected due to lack of eligibility.
In that case, the one Mother filed against Eun Beom would also be rejected.
We don't know about that.
We can't guarantee anything, you know?
She had a lot of lawyers on it, too.
Why would Mother go that far against Eun Beom?
That's exactly what I'm saying!
[Compensation]
Why are they so aggressive against each other?
[Countercomplaint]
After his younger sister died,
Eun Beom has always lived with a sense of guilt and
Mother seems to have been trying to raise Eun Beom with
a strong control, rather than treating him kindly.
Against his personality, that must've been the worst.
Exactly.
Their mother-son compatibility was the worst.
He and his mother should both try getting some counseling, at least.
It wouldn't be easy to make them get it, right?
Probably.
If he was still dating you,
he would've listened to you, at least a little.
I'm also not confident, CEO Seo.
To support and embrace him...
I'm too weak and shabby.
I don't think I can do it.
All right.
You two must've broken up because that wasn't possible.
- I'm sorry.
- Gosh.
No need to be sorry about that.
You don't need to be sorry for such things.
Well... you know...
I actually have another favor to ask of you.
Ha Ra...
Why don't you... leave the firm instead of Eun Beom?
To be honest, our firm is too small for you.
It's about time... for you to go play...
in the deep waters now.
If you don't intend to get back together with Eun Beom anyway,
that's the more constructive way in many ways.
So give it some thought.
I've been to the otolaryngologist, internal medicine, and neurosurgeon.
But they all said I was fine, more or less.
Does psychological stress cause a symptom like this, too?
Of course. Your body and mind are connected.
This is also known as physicalization.
It's common for cerebral reaction to stress
and appear as a physical symptom.
Have you experienced severe stress lately?
Stop standing there and go.
I said, get lost!
Eun Beom... thank you.
Let's live happily. Both of us.
I'm going to hang up first.
Goodbye.
I did... experience one.
Mr. Goo?
Y-Yes. The thing is...
I'm being sued by my own mother.
That is giving me a lot of stress.
Gosh, you must've been stressed severely.
Will the symptom get better if I take medicine?
That's possible.
Should I prescribe you some tranquilizers?
Yes, and also, regarding that...
I'd like to get a letter of opinion.
What? A countercomplaint?
I filed for five billion won, and he filed for ten billion won?
Mom, I left something at home.
- Please look after Woo Joo for a second.
- Okay.
Compensation for mental damage?
Attorney Song, change our complaint, too.
No, this won't do.
Raise it to 20 billion won.
I'm saying... it doesn't matter how you do it.
So just get it done!
Woo Joo!
No, Woo Joo!
[Hyungnim]
Yes, Unni.
Oh, Ha Ra...
Long time no see.
Yes, long time no see.
The thing is, my mom got into an accident, so...
Sorry? Mother did?
So she's getting diagnosed right now, but...
Eun Beom, that punk, must've blocked off mom's number and mine.
He can't be reached!
Could you please tell Eun Beom to come to Onyoo Hospital right away?
Yes. Okay, I got it.
Okay.
- What's up?
- Hurry up and get up.
You have to go to the hospital right now.
What?
They said your mother collapsed!
I just got a call from Unni.
Give it.
You can't drive right now.
Go in my car.
Ms. Seon Myeong Hwa, please.
Please go to General Ward.
They said her brain was fine, according to the CT.
But it looks like some people don't recover consciousness for a long time.
So, if she doesn't wake up after six hours...
they need to do another MRI and
see if she has diffuse axonal damage...
or whatever it is they said.
- What's that?
- I don't know, either.
If she has it, they said it might be more serious.
After six hours... When will that be?
10:00.
She collapsed around 4:00.
She'll be okay. Don't worry.
She'll come to.
[Wonyul Hospital]
You should head back now, too. I can stay here by myself.
It's okay. I want to stay with you.
Why are you so good to me?
I always treat you like a mess every day.
Still... we were family once.
You would've done the same.
No...
You did do the same, too.
Also, to tell you one more thing...
it's because I don't want to regret it.
Regretting is a really terrible thing.
After divorcing you like that,
I had so many kinds of regrets.
You wouldn't ever know.
So I did my best this time not to regret.
Not to leave even a speck of regret.
Since I did that...
it felt a lot better...
even after breaking up.
I don't have any regrets.
Of course, when I thought it happened because of my mom,
I did get stuck for a moment.
Eun Beom...
for that reason... don't regret it
and say everything you want to say to your mother right now.
I don't want to watch you regret it.
You do resent your mom but in fact... you love her a lot.
Go to Mother and tell her you love her a lot,
to hurry and wake up,
and that you'll do better from now on.
Okay?
Okay. I'll do it once you leave.
Will you really be okay by yourself?
I'll be fine.
I really just want to talk to Mom alone.
Oh, right. Let me know when Mother wakes up.
I'll be waiting.
Okay.
Ha Ra...
You're thankful?
I'm going.
[Calling: Madam Im Sook Jeong ♡]
[Call Ended: Madam Im Sook Jeong ♡]
Mom! Mom!
Why aren't you answering your phone?
You called me?
My phone's acting weird nowadays.
It must be broken. It doesn't really ring.
You should've told me sooner, then. To get it fixed or replaced.
You got me spooked.
What's up all of a sudden?
You haven't called once after leaving like that.
I was busy. Just so busy.
I happened to have time, so I was going to ask you out to dinner.
Why are you eating such a shabby meal alone?
I told you to eat a proper meal, even if you're eating alone.
This is enough for me.
You should've let me know you were coming.
So I can shop for groceries in advance.
I can't let you know if you don't pick up your phone.
Is that so?
Since you're also at that age now, Mom...
my heart skips a beat when you're not picking up your phone.
So make sure to pick up your phone from now on. Okay?
Such needless worries. Gosh, seriously.
You mind your own business, please.
I'm always worrying about you, day and night.
I'm doing well.
- So don't worry.
- Goodness.
You're doing well? Really?
To be honest... I broke up with Eun Beom.
I'm saying we broke up a long time ago.
Are you happy now?
It's not because of you, though.
We're just too different.
Eat up. Take big bites.
I'm not the only one. You need to eat, too.
My belly is out of control.
You! H-How could you...
I missed you so much, Mom.
I couldn't hold it in anymore.
You missed the money, not your mom.
That's an option.
How great is it for your son to come with you to the hospital?
Or you'd have to go alone.
You need to get an endoscopy, too.
Did I tell you to come? You came on your own.
Mom, let's...
Let's get up and have just one...
more conversation, please. Okay?
You only worked your whole life because of us.
You can't go like this. It's unfair.
Given your personality.
Mom... Mom, is Eun Byeol telling you to come, perhaps?
Saying she's lonely?
You still can't go, okay?
Not yet...
You can meet... Eun Byeol again later, right?
I'm sorry for making you...
let go of Eun Byeol early, Mom.
I'm really...
I'm really sorry about that, Mom.
I thought you'd know even if I didn't tell you.
But you didn't seem to know...
I'm sorry.
Eun Byeol... wasn't...
Mom! Mom...
It's not your fault...
that Eun Byeol... left this world early.
You idiot.
Why would you... think it's... your fault, like an idiot?
Mom, are you okay?
Mom, how many fingers am I holding up?
I thought... you wouldn't come even if I died.
What the heck are you saying?
Come here.
Mom...
Mom, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Senior, I have the proposal ready. I'll send it to you.
I'll look at it later.
My daughter... withered a little.
I'll use expensive products.
Are you busy? Why do you keep looking?
A client is supposed to send me something.
[Goo Eun Beom]
My mom woke up.
Thank you so much for earlier.
[Oh Ha Ra]
Thank you for letting me know.
I'm so glad.
Have you practiced a little?
Hey, what about your mother?
She was discharged yesterday. She's fine now.
Did she withdraw her complaint? The disowning complaint.
Well, she'll need to submit the withdrawal soon.
Hurry up and get it done.
The fight between you and your mother is meaningless.
What I mean is...
Anyhow, you don't know what will happen tomorrow.
So I think it'd be better to get it done quickly.
I got it. I'll have it withdrawn today right away.
Thank you for... taking care of me in this way and that, CEO Seo.
I mean it.
Gosh... Seriously...
You make me... age faster than I should.
- I have one more request to make, CEO Seo.
- What is it?
Let me postpone indefinitely my quitting the firm.
I think I was a little... carried away
by emotion when I told you back then.
- You don't need to leave the firm.
- Sorry?
Didn't you hear?
Ha Ra will be leaving the firm.
What are you doing? Get changed and ready for a game.
- All right, you can see here, right?
- Yes.
- Feet...
- Feet.
- These are calves.
- Yes, right above.
- And thighs right above.
- Th-The thighs are there, too.
- In between them...
- In between?
You can see, right?
Whoa... Yes!
Noona, what did I tell you? Huh?
I told you it's a son, didn't I? I'm right, am I not?
- You're so lovely! Come here—
- Why are you doing this?
What the heck? O-Oh, my, he's gone mad.
- Oh, my goodness!
- It's a son.
What are you doing in the office?
Was that too much? Chan Young and Ye Seul,
starting today, Korea is an island, not a peninsula.
Why? Because there are four seas.
East Sea, West Sea, South Sea, and Kang Bi Chwi I love you.
(Hae also means sea, saranghae means "I love you")
Kang Bi Chwi, I love you! Kang Bi Chwi, I love you!
Where did she go?
Where did my baby go?
He's completely in love, hopelessly.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Oh, you're here?
How are you so lovely even when you're drinking juice?
You hit a new high every single day.
Is it your goal to become a better you each and every day?
Please cut it out.
This is no joke.
Congrats, Unni.
Sunny really happens to be a son, huh?
Your parents are overjoyed, too, aren't they?
Hey, don't even mention it.
My mother was making a scene, saying they needed to
have an ambulance ready since my father might collapse from happiness—
It's crazy— What's this now?
My father is calling me again.
Hello?
Herbal medicine? Can she just take them?
I'm so jealous of you.
A beloved wife, right?
A beloved daughter-in-law!
Everything is sailing smoothly.
How do you always fall onto a flower field every time?
You're not one to say. You're the one in a flower field.
Going to Moon and Jin with that groundbreaking salary—
Whoa, I'm seriously jealous of you.
I'm on my way to the thorn field, getting paid more money.
I'm in a thorn field, all right?
With a man whose head is full of flowers...
I need to give birth and raise the child.
You don't need to be like that.
Just say you're happy if you are.
All of this might look great to you since you want to marry...
but well? I'm not really sure.
Sometimes, I keep thinking
if it's okay for me to go this way
or if this is right.
Huh?
Ha Ra, can we talk for a minute?
I heard... you're going to leave the firm.
Oh, y-yes.
You heard?
It was decided yesterday.
Can I ask you why you're leaving?
Because you said, you'll leave.
CEO Seo said since you don't really have a place to go to,
why don't I think about leaving instead?
I already had an offer at the time, so I just went in for the interview.
Luckily, things worked out well.
That man is really no help at all.
- What?
- No, nothing.
If, by any chance,
it's entirely because of me, you don't need to leave.
I thought about leaving for only a moment
because you might be uncomfortable.
But you didn't really seem that way,
so I decided again not to leave.
So, if you're doing this because of me,
we can just keep working together like now.
I-If you want to.
Well...
But when I think about it,
it's a little awkward for you and I to be working together like this indefinitely.
I don't know when, but
we'll both start dating again, probably.
If I say I work in the same office as my ex-husband, who'd be happy about it?
Isn't that true?
That's true. You have a point.
Also, I do want to tread... the deeper waters now.
My world has been too small so far.
- You'll root for me, right?
- Huh? Yes.
Of course. I will.
Fighting.
Thank you.
[Seocho-gu Counseling Centers]
[Practicing admittance for people who tend to avoid.]
[Therefore, people who fear rejection due to suffering from evasive personality disorder]
[tend to avoid situations that might cause rejection entirely.]
Yes?
Oh, what's up now?
What are you doing this evening?
This evening... Why do you ask?
I owe you from this time and
I also have something to say.
So I want to treat you to a meal. An expensive one.
I have plans today. I'm sorry.
Really?
What about tomorrow, then?
Tomorrow...
Gosh, I also have plans tomorrow.
What about the day after tomorrow?
♫ Still filling my day to its fullest ♫
♫ I keep repeating your name ♫
♫ On the street where we walked hand in hand ♫
♫ I stay alone and think of you ♫
♫ Can't have it ♫
♫ The warmth of that day ♫
♫ Close your eyes and look through them ♫
♫ and put it in them ♫
♫ Dazzlingly shining ♫
♫ I see you and me ♫
♫ When the morning comes ♫
♫ I know it's a dream that will disappear ♫
♫ Then we say goodbye ♫
- You came early.
- You, too, Mom.
Thinking about a date with my daughter at a good place,
I got ready quickly out of excitement.
What's this?
Your pickup lines are getting better after you started dating.
- Let's eat delicious stuff.
- Okay, okay.
[Nakwon Counseling Center]
Welcome. Did you make an appointment?
Yes. It's Goo Eun Beom.
Eun Beom, one second, please.
But why are you suddenly buying me an expensive meal
at a place like this when there's no occasion?
Well, I don't know. What could it be?
Anything come to mind?
Is this your first time getting counseling?
Y-Yes.
What made you come?
Because my heart was in distress.
What could have made you distressed?
There's a woman...
I broke up with more than about five times...
and she is now really trying to become
strangers with me.
It's my ex-wife, whom I divorced.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I can't go on blind dates.
I gave it a lot of thought...
I've lost a lot of hair because of Eun Beom
I still...
think I'll break up with him.
Who could I date with such feelings?
Perhaps...
it might be that I... just want to love...
not... marry or date.
But I still can't figure out what love is.
Although I might just... wander around aimlessly and confused
about everything in life,
ending up unmarried without any children...
and eventually, die a lonely death alone...
I can't help it.
I can't do it anymore when I don't know what love is.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's okay, Ha Ra.
I must've given you a really hard time, Ha Ra.
Because... I had a lot of hopes and wishes...
Regardless of... what kind of life you live,
I'm going to trust you and cheer for you.
So, Ha Ra... it's okay.
Wander around a little more...
until you find the answer.
You can do that.
What you need to know clearly is that...
my heart, when I say that, is trembling in fear.
Still, since I love you... I know I have to...
say this as your mother.
I'm sorry for telling you this too late, Honey.
Although I don't really know, either,
if love means these things that I do for you...
love is a really hard thing.
So do it when... you're ready.
[Law Firm of the Year, Law Firm Doohwang]
[Attorney Oh Ha Ra]
~Thank you to our Channel Manager: jiminnie_347~
~Thank you to our English Team and Seggers~
~Thank you to all the Other Languages Moderators~
What's the big deal now? Telling me to wear a bow tie.
Don't open your eyes.
- D-Do I go this way?
- Wait, I'm scared.
- I'm scared.
- Are we there?
Where is it?
- All done?
- What's this?
Open your eyes!
Congratulations!
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Gosh, preparing all this...
- My goodness.
As you live together,
you'll find yourself getting sick of each other, disappointed in each other,
and things you just can't understand about each other constantly.
Just like our clients.
However, if you keep trying to avoid
and evade those things,
your married life gets rocky.
Just like our clients.
As you two probably know already,
what I particularly want to tell two divorce lawyers
facing marriage is...
a quote from the literary giant Shakespeare,
who's way smarter than I am.
If you can't avoid it,
you might as well embrace it.
If you do that, you'll probably have to hug each other quite often.
And in the end, you'll have to love each other.
Since you two are doing this marriage thing,
which is a hard and complicated choice to make,
in this day and age where one
can be happy even without marrying.
I sincerely congratulate you two on becoming a married couple,
Bi Chwi and Si Wook.
Thank you!
- Cheers.
- Congratulations!
Gosh, CEO Hong, when did you prepare all this?
Goodness, what can't I do for a Doohwang family?
You're still having a proper wedding after giving birth to Sunny, right?
Not sure. If we're still living together, then, maybe?
Gosh, after all the things I said!
When did you meet Jay? Tell me about it.
Wasn't this expensive?
I'm sorry. This is the best I can do.
CEO Hong did all of it. CEO Seo doesn't know anything.
I'm sorry.
- Seriously.
- I love it so much.
- You have to do well.
- Does it look good on me?
How did you know my size to prepare this?
Those two did all the work.
I'm going to defend myself.
It looks great on you.
How did you know my size to prepare this?
- Those two did all the work.
- Gosh, it's tiring.
It's a battlefield. A war.
Gosh, I think I need to go now. I have a filming schedule.
Ha Ra, thank you.
- Be happy, Unni.
- Okay.
- I'll call you.
- Please look this way!
All right, make sure to show them what you got at Moon and Jin, too.
- I'll do my best.
- Good.
I got it.
- Let us not meet at the court.
- Let's not do that.
- I'll be on my way now.
- Okay, take care.
He's boasting, saying he did it.
All right, I brought you your beautiful bride.
Gosh, not at all.
It's nice, even if it's
just us gathering to do this. Right?
- You're leaving?
- Yes.
I'll take off first.
Are you doing well?
You seem to be.
Of course, I'm doing well.
What's a reason not to be?
Where are you going?
O-Oh, I have a filming schedule today. What about you?
I'm babysitting my niece and nephew these days. Woo Sung and Woo Joo.
To go play with them.
They must love you.
They're so cute.
It's here.
~Thank you to all the subbers~
~Thank you for watching~
~Hope you enjoyed~
~The Sparks of Love & Hate 👰⚡🤵 Team~
I'll be off now.
See you next time.
When?
Not sure.
At court?
Can I ask you one thing?
What I really want to ask is...
- Can we really...
- ...become strangers again?
That's what I want to know, too.
♫ At the sound of dawn coming ♫
♫ I finally had realized ♫
♫ Among my hidden pains ♫
♫ Another me was in there ♫
[Thank you for watching Strangers Again.]
♫ The light from the window ♫
♫ My heart that was in darkness ♫
♫ Shines a new hope into it ♫
♫ Everything is so radiant ♫
♫ All the times we spent together ♫
♫ Becomes a strength for me ♫
♫ All of the happy memories ♫
♫ My way, at the same place ♫
♫ Able to smile brightly ♫
♫ My way ♫
[Strangers Again]