When will you come back?
Where are you going?
To the convenience store
Let's go together
I will be back soon
Please wait for me at home obediently
Where did Jungwoo go?
He said he was going to the convenience store
I want to follow him
Just sit down
Just wait quietly!
ðŸ‘¦ Ko Hojung ðŸ‘¦
ðŸ¶ Lee Jaebin ðŸ¶
ðŸ± Kim Seonghyeok ðŸ±
ðŸ§‘ Park Seungbin ðŸ§‘
Chapter 3 The truth about Choco and Milk
Hey, Jungwoo!
I told you to wait at home
I've told you to wait at home obediently!
What will we do if an accident happens?
I am sorry
You are worried because of me?
Why did it take too long?
You are hungry, right?
Just wait a little
What happened to Choco?
Huh?
Nothing
So why Choco looks so dispirited?
Milk
Yes?
Have you ever felt any resentment at me?
What are you talking about? Why should I resent you?
Because, it was me
It was too late when I noticed that you were sick
Are you stupid?
Do you still thinking that it was your fault?
You think that we died because of you?
We don't think like that
Do you know what was our biggest worry
Even when we were about to die?
That it would be difficult for you
That you would be sad for a long time
That was our biggest worry
Really?
We
Don't have any resentment at you
Hey, Milk
Why are you hugging Junwoo?
I also want to hug him
- Let's do the cleaning
- Ok
- Let's go, let's go
Are you sleepy?
Do you want to drink some coffee?
Sounds good
A cup go milk for me, please
Aha, okay
A cup of milk tea for me
Cold
Excuse me
Choco
Yes?
About that burdensome stare
How can we fix it?
Stare?
What's wrong with the way I look at you?
Uhm...
You are too cheesy when you stare at him
- What?
- You should do it like me
Look carefully
When your eyes met like this
Ehem
Pretend that you are not looking at
- Like this
- Mmmm
When Jungwoo looks to another place, look at him again
Not burdensome
Got it
Exactly, like that
Right
Good job
- Right?
- Right
Ah...
- Not bright gaze
- How do you open your eyes with such a beautiful gaze?
But, why Jungwoo haven't said anything?
Because you look at him like this
- What are you looking at, look again
- Huh? Got it,  practice again? Just wait a little
Okay, last time, focus all your energy for the last time
- Open your eyes just a little and a little more
- Hey, just try it
- Why do you look so excited?
- No, it is nothing
What? Do I have something in my face?
No
It's been a long time since I've seen you looking this comfortable
Me?
- Me?
- Yes, you
It is because of them?
Excuse me?
Of course not
Hey, if you're bored, go ahead and clean some tables
Gosh...
Do it fast
- Hey, Choco
- Yes?
Shouldn't we tell to Jungwoo now?
Yes
We have tell to him
We should tell him that we have to leave
Let's talk  before it is too late