Je-sun.
Wait a minute.
- Je-sun.
- I'll pretend I didn't hear you.
Just go. Please.
You must get the package before he does.
Je-sun!
EPISODE 9
Are you okay? You're not hurt?
What... what are you doing here?
How... how did you get here?
Director.
Director, please open your eyes!
Oh, Director!
Director!
- She's not badly hurt.
- All right.
- Let's get her out of here.
- Okay.
Look how smoothly this car is going.
Darn, this is fun to drive.
What the... Gang Beom-ryong?
His face looks kind of familiar.
Hey, what's going on?
Hey, Kkot-nim, are you okay? Hey.
Hey, what happened?
- We were attacked, Boss.
- Attacked? Who attacked you?
- Gang Beom-ryong?
- No.
- It was some other guy.
- Another guy?
He showed up out of nowhere
and grabbed Kim Seon-jung's wife
and the woman we saw at the house.
- Yes, that woman.
- He took them and disappeared.
He took them and...
Darn it! Seriously. Gosh, my leg.
Hey, you idiots! What are you doing?
- Get out here, now!
- Boss, what about Kkot-nim?
Just leave that idiot.
Get out here, quick.
Darn it.
They say it's a mild concussion.
I think she'll have to be admitted
to the hospital for observation.
How do you two know each other?
She's the wife
of one of my high school teachers.
A teacher?
What kind of teacher
has gangsters looking for him?
What are you trying to imply?
It's not what you think.
Stay away from him for a while.
Don't get mixed up in this.
- What do you know to be saying this?
- Because I'm worried.
My wife almost got dragged away by thugs.
As her husband,
I'm not allowed to say that?
No, you're not.
About how you showed up there earlier
or what that whole fight was about...
Have you ever once given me
a proper explanation?
No, that's...
- What's that got to do with this?
- How could it not?
You...
You've been acting so suspiciously lately
and you haven't even given me
a proper explanation for what's going on.
What wife in the world
would listen to a husband like that?
What reason do I have to trust you?
Honey.
Are you, by any chance...
keeping a secret
that I'm not supposed to know?
Is that it?
O-ran!
Oh, Mr. Kim!
How is my wife?
She's all right. This way, please.
Get lost, you idiots.
Get out. What are you looking at?
Get back to work. Now.
So you're saying
you failed to tie up the loose ends?
I'm sorry. It's just that
some guy showed up out of nowhere--
And this guy who showed up out of nowhere
was with Gang Beom-ryong,
Hwasan Sect's number two?
So why?
You had no idea who this guy was?
Well, that's the thing.
He definitely looked familiar, but...
- I just can't place him--
- If you say you can't remember
then what am I supposed to do?
It wasn't that so-called
Martial Arts Master, was it?
No, it was someone else.
Mr. Nam, the owner
of the van that appeared
in front of Kim Seon-jung's house
and at the port.
Have you identified him?
We ran a check, but it was a ghost car.
A ghost car?
My goodness.
Now things are starting to become clear.
- What?
- The masked guys Yoo was chasing.
This mysterious man and Gang Beom-ryong.
It fits perfectly, doesn't it?
Oh, right.
Now that you mention it... I see.
Gang Beom-ryong,
number two of the Hwasan Sect
the martial arts master,
and the mystery man.
For skilled fighters like them
to just pop up
and interfere with our business
at every turn.
This can't be a coincidence.
I have a feeling
they're specifically targeting one of us
and this is all part of a plan,
don't you think?
Darn it, but why the hell would they?
If we just find one more puzzle piece,
we'll have our answer.
- Chairman Do, should I handle this?
- Handle it?
How?
If we grab Gang Beom-ryong
and beat it out of him
we'll get our answer, won't we?
- Beat it out of him?
- Yes.
- Gang Beom-ryong.
Well, I don't know about that.
Mr. Geum, back when you were
just shining shoes for the Hwasan Sect
wasn't Gang Beom-ryong already
their second-in-command?
Even if you do catch a guy like that
and try to beat him
do you really think he'd talk to you
who's so far beneath him?
I mean, a man has his pride.
- Am I wrong?
- Well...
Chairman Do, actually,
I wasn't that low on the totem pole.
- In the Hwasan Sect, I was--
- For now
Mr. Geum, just focus
on managing Heaven Capital.
- But, Chairman--
- Do you understand?
Chairman...
I asked if you got it.
Yes, I understand.
Let's go.
Darn it.
As if he could beat it out of him.
Mr. Nam, do you have anyone competent?
I need someone who can handle
this job cleanly, with no fuss.
- There are some very skilled hitmen.
- Hitmen?
Okay. Hitmen. I like it.
Set them up right away.
And Mr. Nam,
you should get warmed up, too.
Man, you must have been feeling
cooped up, stuck behind a desk.
It's about time
you got out in the field again.
Yes, sir.
What's with all this drama?
Are you sure about this?
I'm going to come clean.
I have to.
O-ran.
Her family.
And the people of Yeongseon Island.
Before they're in even more danger.
From now on
I have to be more aggressive.
All right.
Then I guess I'll take this chance
to properly introduce myself to your wife.
So after you tell her everything
what happens next?
First, I'm going to meet
with Candidate Kim Seon-jung
and hear what he has to say.
MY LITTLE BROTHER
Jeez, you scared me.
Hey, why aren't you answering my calls?
I was busy.
For a guy who never answers his phone
to be looking for me
means you got your butt kicked again.
No, it's not like that.
What do you mean it's not like that?
I can tell just from your voice.
So who was it this time?
- This fake Yankee jerk.
- Yankee? A foreigner?
I'll explain the details when we meet,
so can you come to where I am now?
All right.
- I'll go once I wrap things up here.
- Hey!
The kimchi stew is ready.
Why aren't you coming? Jeez.
I was on the phone with In-gu.
For crying out loud. Geez.
In-gu? He got beat up again?
- That's just In-gu for you.
- What an idiot.
So where is he now?
Yes, Mi-kyung, it's me.
I'm at the hospital right now.
No, not me. Je-sun got a little hurt.
Yes. I'm sorry to ask
but could you tell Nam-il
to come to the hospital?
Hey.
Who's there?
I'm sorry.
- Who are you?
- I couldn't ring the doorbell
because there were too many prying eyes.
O-ran!
Oh, Mr. Kim!
So the reason you dropped out of the race
was because of Han Gyeong-wook's scheme.
I was too naive.
I never imagined
that he'd attack me like this.
You don't need to blame yourself.
About Han Gyeong-wook...
Ever since his days
at the National Intelligence Service
he has specialized in plots,
threats, and things like that.
Since I couldn't stop
Candidate Han Gyeong-wook
I'm worried there will be more victims
like with the orphanage
and the Heaven Capital debtors.
- We have to stop him somehow.
- Alone?
Do you think that's possible?
Those scumbags...
They are a force to be reckoned with.
I know exactly what they are like.
I'll deal with them.
You just focus on what you have to do
- for the people of Yeongseon Island.
- Okay.
I understand.
I can't take back my withdrawal.
But if there's anything I can do to help
- just let me know.
- Thank you.
Oh, and...
About the place
where my wife is helping the victims.
Is it possible to know where that is?
JEONGSEOK BOARDING HOUSE
WE CAN'T BACK DOWN FROM REDEVELOPMENT
THAT KILLS THE COMMON PEOPLE!
JEONGSEOK BOARDING HOUSE
HANMAEUM SOCIAL DANCE
- Where's Ji-woo's mom?
- She said
she had a dance club meeting
and left suddenly.
Again?
Has she gone crazy for dancing?
What's with her lately?
HANMAEUM SOCIAL DANCE
Bulgae's nephew?
YEONGSON MEDICAL CENTER
Uncle!
What happened?
How can someone who went on a date
become a hit-and-run victim?
- Is he badly hurt?
- There are no external injuries
so don't worry too much.
He'll wake up soon.
Darn it.
I've explained the schedule
for his checkups.
So, who will be staying with him?
- I'll stay.
- All right.
- You?
- Je-sun got hurt because of me
so I think it's only right that I stay.
No, even so, his nephew should stay.
Please give me a chance to repay him.
When I fell into the sea,
Je-sun was the one who took care of me.
Can I ask you something?
What do you think of my uncle?
- What do you mean?
- What?
- Excuse me?
- No, I mean...
Do you find my uncle...
Never mind.
Don't worry about it. Okay.
I should... I should get going.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Hey.
- Have a good time.
- What?
With my uncle.
Prosecutor Gang Yeong-ae?
Who might you be?
So we finally meet.
So Yoo In-gu has already been cut loose?
Yes. What's more, a man named Chairman Do
took over everything Yoo In-gu was doing.
So Han Gyeong-wook
won't be affected at all.
Instead, why not focus
on what you mentioned earlier?
The package containing
Han Gyeong-wook's weakness
- and try looking for that?
- The package?
I mean, you said you have
the radio receiver.
So is there really no way to find it?
The receiver is supposed to go off
when I get within 10m of the package
but I've searched all over
Yeongseon Island for the past ten years
and the receiver has never gone off.
I even went to Bulgae's house,
but there was no signal there either.
It seems Bulgae
likely hid it in a secret place
only he knows.
Je-sun probably doesn't know
about the package.
Right now
you seem to think
Bong Je-sun is faking his amnesia.
But no.
The Je-sun I saw wasn't faking it.
Since we have no leads on that package,
we need to find another way, and fast.
I heard Han Gyeong-wook is deeply involved
in the recent redevelopment project
on Yeongseon Island.
- Yes.
- Seeing how he's pushing to become mayor
and even mobilizing Heaven Capital
this can't be just an ordinary project.
Please look into what's going on
behind the scenes of that project.
Here on Yeongseon Island
we'll dig into the activities of that guy
Chairman Do and Han Gyeong-wook.
All right. I'll investigate
as soon as I get back to the office.
And you have to get the dance club members
to back off from this.
- They could be in danger.
- Well...
They're Yeongseon Island natives
who are directly tied to this issue
- so it won't be easy to persuade them.
- I'll try to persuade them myself.
- You will?
- It's about my wife, after all.
That's true.
All right. Let's proceed that way, then.
Okay.
What is it, so late?
About your wife...
Did things get resolved?
Before I go and take care of it,
there's something I need to tell you.
Why Officer Park Mi-kyung was there
and what her relationship is with Bulgae.
I've figured it all out.
But Mi-kyung is just a patrol officer.
What can she do?
I mean, does she even know
who she's up against?
She doesn't know what it's like
because she hasn't been through it.
Hey. If you were me
what would you do?
- You tell her to quit right now.
- Hey, it's easier said than done.
If I bring up my past
and tell Mi-kyung to quit what she's doing
you think I don't know how she'd react?
Would the words come easily
if you were me?
So you know she's walking into danger
and you're just going to stand by
and watch?
Because you're scared
of what she'll think of you
- you'll just sit back and do nothing?
- Who said I would do nothing?
Think about what's really important.
Your pride or her safety.
- Where's Ji-woo?
- At the restaurant.
I left him with my dad for a little while.
I couldn't let Ji-woo see us fight.
I thought you'd be here yesterday
but you're just showing up now?
That's just like you.
I needed to clear my head.
Not because you were busy
thinking up an excuse?
I was so buried in my own work
that I didn't even realize
what you were going through
or what you were getting into.
I wasn't paying attention
like I should have.
The K-Pop dance club.
You don't go there just to dance, do you?
- What?
- I met with Kim Seon-jung.
He asked me to make you quit
what you're doing.
You were looking into me.
Helping the victims of Heaven Capital.
I get what you're trying to do,
but you need to stop.
They aren't just gangsters.
What do you know that gives you the right
to tell me to stop?
I know them very well.
They're the ones who made me this way.
What?
Do you remember what I told you?
About why I came to Yeongseon Island.
You said that
you were at a trading company
and you were framed for embezzlement
and kicked out.
- You came here to clear your head.
- That was a lie.
The place I worked...
It was the National Intelligence Service.
I was a black ops agent for the NIS.
A black ops agent?
You mean like in the movies,
shooting guns and breaking in?
- Is that what you're talking about?
- Yes, something like that.
Well, do you by any chance...
Do you have a criminal record?
Is that why you're telling
this ridiculous lie...
I know it's hard to believe.
I was framed during an operation
and had to go on the run.
I came to Yeongseon Island
to find a clue that would clear my name.
Well, I didn't think ten years would go by
but the person who framed me
and forced me on the run
is now using Heaven Capital
to plot something on Yeongseon Island.
He's extremely dangerous.
So, just for a little while
close the restaurant
- and leave Yeongseon Island.
- So then...
From the very beginning,
you've been lying to me for ten years.
I'm sorry.
Once I cleared my name
and was reinstated at the NIS
I planned to tell you in a grand way.
So I could proudly face you
and our Ji-woo.
Clear your name?
Is that why
you were always out
running around like that?
I mean, how...
How could you do something like that
without even consulting me?
And who are you to tell me
to leave Yeongseon Island?
I mean, right now
where would I even go?
I have nowhere to go.
Oh, the dance club. Go stay there for now.
There are no security cameras there,
and it seems safe.
Since they know your face,
they'll use security cameras to track
you, your father, and our Ji-woo.
There's no telling what they'll do.
Our Ji-woo?
The fact that up until now
I couldn't be honest with you...
I'm truly sorry.
I know that you're angry
and it's hard to accept the situation.
I'd feel the same way
if I were in your shoes.
But, just this once
for our family
and for our Ji-woo's sake,
please do as I say.
Please trust me
and just for a little while
go somewhere safe.
I'm begging you, O-ran.
Leave.
You're a husband
who lied to me for ten years.
I don't know how
I'm supposed to trust you.
Give me some time to think.
All right.
Let me know when you're ready.
Hey, you.
- Never mind.
- Geez, come on.
You can't even ask him one thing?
Ho-myeong.
Are you really
an NIS agent or whatever it's called?
It's just that we overheard
you and O-ran fighting.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you all sooner.
So it's true. It is.
- Mi-kyung.
- My goodness.
You startled me.
What are you doing here?
Could you spare
a moment to talk with me?
It's so late
that my convenience store
is the only place still open.
It's fine.
We don't need to talk for long anyway.
You don't have much time, do you?
- Excuse me?
- That's what your employee told me.
That you're someone with big plans
so you don't have time
for someone like me.
That's absolutely not true.
- I apologize on his behalf.
- It's fine.
It went in one ear and out the other.
So, what did you want to say?
The reason
I couldn't make it to our meeting that day
was because I didn't want to tell you
about my past.
Your past?
Yes, I...
Before I became the owner
of this convenience store
I was in a gang.
A gang?
Wait.
You're not talking about
being a gangster, are you?
That's right. A gangster.
The kind that uses his fists
and beats people up.
That's the kind of gangster I was.
Is that why you came looking for me?
To tell me this?
Mi-kyung.
It's because I found out
what you've been up to recently.
What you're doing right now
and the stuff related to Heaven Capital.
You need to stop.
Those guys at Heaven Capital.
They're not the kind of people
a patrol officer like you can handle.
If they think you're in their way,
they'll get rid of you
without a second thought.
So all this stuff you're doing,
just stop all of it.
If you get caught,
you'll be in big trouble.
What right do you have
to suddenly show up
and tell me what to do?
I mean, it's not like
we've even been on a date.
You have no right to tell me what to do.
And...
in case you forgot, I'm a police officer.
The kind that arrests gangsters
and throws them in jail.
And yet you're telling me
to quit because you know better
as an ex-gangster?
- How could you say that?
- I know.
I knew how you'd see me
if I told you this.
But I couldn't stand by
when it's so obvious
you're walking into danger.
- I couldn't pretend not to know.
- Why?
You should have just pretended
you didn't know.
Then we could have just stayed
as the store owner and a customer.
That's all we could have been,
couldn't we?
I don't care how you see me.
In any case, for your own safety
I hope you'll give my words
one more serious thought.
I should get going.
MY DAD
For our family
and for our Ji-woo's sake,
please do as I say.
Please trust me
and just for a little while
go somewhere safe.
I'm begging you, O-ran.
Yeongseon Steel.
My savior.
Family.
Je-sun, in the field...
The doll.
Darn it.
The receiver is supposed to go off
when I get within 10m of the package.
You're here? Boss, hold on.
What's with your eyes?
Are you sick or something?
- They're really red.
- Let's hurry. We'll be late.
Seriously, what kind
of K-pop dance team is this?
They've got Prosecutor Gang,
Bulgae, and the cop.
And on top of that, even Mr. Jeong's wife.
Hey, Ho-myeong. How did your wife take it?
Of course she's very disappointed.
So, as soon as I crush Yoo In-gu,
Chairman Do, and Han Gyeong-wook
and we talk again...
I hope she'll understand then.
Right.
We just have to finish
before it's too late. Then...
That angry look in her eyes
will probably die down a bit.
So, based on your talk
with Prosecutor Gang yesterday
what we need to do at this point
is to dig into what this
redevelopment project is all about, right?
There's definitely
something shady about it.
Han Gyeong-wook must have bribed
someone at the Imcheon city hall.
You should head over there
and find out everything about the project.
We'll go meet Prosecutor Gang
and wrap things up.
Okay. I'll hurry.
- Let's go.
- Yes, let's go.
- Hey, Gong-bok.
- Yes?
Well... About Mi-kyung.
- Never mind.
- It's nothing, right?
Darn it.
What is it? What?
What about that police officer?
Well... No matter how much
I think about it
spying on the Heaven Capital guys
is just too dangerous.
So, I want you to go and...
You want me to what?
- You want me to watch over her?
- I mean...
It is related to our work, after all.
And that area is your specialty.
Why should I use my specialty for that?
She's a cop. She can take care of herself.
Come on, how can you be so heartless?
I mean, she's a long-time customer.
Think of it as customer service.
Just go and support her
if she needs anything.
We closed down the convenience store.
What damn customer service
are you talking about?
Fine. Just forget it.
- I just have to watch her, right?
- Yes.
You know me, right? I'm allergic to cops.
- This is the last time.
- I know, Gong-bok. Let's go.
Gosh, seriously.
We've located their base.
Excuse me.
Have you seen Bong Je-sun from room 1301?
- Bong Je-sun?
- Yes.
He was here when I checked
his blood pressure last night.
- He's not in his room?
- Oh, okay. I understand.
Bong Je-sun is gone.
- When? When did he disappear?
- I don't know.
He was gone when I woke up this morning.
His clothes are gone too
and he hasn't been officially discharged.
Where did he go? Are we going to lose him?
I knew this would happen,
so I put a tracker on him yesterday.
Look at you.
There's that old NIS training.
So, where is that guy now?
What? What's wrong with this thing?
What? It says he's still in the hospital.
But I already searched
the entire hospital.
What?
Look at this guy.
So, what happened?
Did we lose him, or what?
I think he figured it out.
Figured what out?
I told you. Bulgae is not an amnesiac.
He was afraid his act would be blown
after seeing me yesterday
so he must have run away.
What? Prosecutor Gang, what are you doing?
Je-sun.
I heard the chicken soup here
is delicious.
- My gosh.
- Just look at this place. Darn it.
It's cozy.
My goodness.
HWANG HWA-SAN SENTENCED TO LIFE
FOR MURDERING KWON SOON-BOK
- These darn stalkers. Darn it.
- What?
Mr. Geum, you are quite photogenic.
THE DEATH OF NATIONAL SECURITY DIRECTOR
KWON SOON-BOK
REPUBLIC OF KOREA PASSPORT
What?
Chairman.
I think we came to the right place.
Man, I really don't get it.
It doesn't seem to be about money.
So why are they pulling this crap?
Take a look at this photo.
SEPTEMBER 2010, FEBRUARY 2010, MAY 2010
ORAN CHINESE RESTAURANT
If you don't pay next time,
I won't be making any more deliveries.
ORAN CHINESE RESTAURANT
- Oh, right!
- Gosh, you scared me.
The Chinese food delivery guy.
Chairman, that guy...
- He was with Gang Beom-ryong
- The day before yesterday?
- The delivery guy?
- Yes.
So this is how it all connects.
You put the camper van back
to how it was, right?
Yes. I even planted a bug, as instructed.
Okay, good job.
We absolutely cannot leave
a single trace that we were there.
And for now, tell the hitmen
to just tail them.
Wouldn't it be better to eliminate them?
No. Absolutely not.
The way I see it, these guys
and Deputy Director Han have a past
and I'm sure there's
some spectacular drama involved.
Didn't you see the news clippings
about the ferry incident
from ten years ago and the Hwasan Sect?
You take one look
and the answer is obvious.
If their target was Han from the start,
that means I'm holding a hand
with far more to gain than lose, right?
I can't just throw away a lucky hand
that fell into my lap.
What are you planning to do?
To be the winner in this game
you need to hold a few jokers
to shake up the board.
For now, maybe I'll poke
at Deputy Director Han first?
Gosh, this will be fun.
I'm curious
how he'll react.
Yes, I confirmed he left the hospital
and hailed a taxi.
YEONGSON MEDICAL CENTER
And...
He returned to the hospital
exactly five hours later.
Got it. Send me the video.
Like I said
I just went out to get something to eat.
At that hour? After pulling out your IV?
Yes.
Prosecutor Gang was having a hard time
because of me
sleeping in a chair at the hospital.
So I wanted to repay her somehow.
Why would you say that's on you, Je-sun?
You were injured trying to save me.
Then what about this tracking device
that was on your hoodie?
Why did you deliberately remove it
before you left?
Tracking...
I had this on me?
Why?
Playing dumb, are you?
No, I'm not playing dumb.
I really didn't know it was there.
Maybe it fell off
when I put the hoodie on?
To be honest...
About what you two and Prosecutor Gang
told me about my past...
I still can't believe it.
I'm just an ordinary office worker.
The idea that I was
such a strong and ruthless agent...
But since you all say so, it must be true.
Even though I don't remember
if I did something wrong
to you two in the past
I want to apologize now.
Yes, I'm truly sorry.
Oh my, Je-sun.
My goodness, what are you doing?
Ho-myeong, what was that for?
He took the hit on purpose.
Can't you see that?
- Oh my, Je-sun.
- Hey.
- Drop the act, you goddamn spy.
- It hurts so much.
Geez, don't you think that's too much?
He's a patient who hasn't fully recovered.
Yes, even I couldn't have dodged that.
Did you have to throw it that hard?
Look, Prosecutor,
you don't seem to get it.
This guy is Bulgae, the most elite agent
of the Ministry of People's Armed Forces.
In the middle of Washington, D.C.,
he evaded the CIA
and helped
all the North Korean hackers escape.
In Sichuan province,
he beat 20 Triad men to a pulp.
He's Bulgae, a human weapon
trained by North Korea.
- He's not a pushover.
- I think you've got it wrong.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Look how frail he is.
How's he supposed to take on the CIA?
Get real. You need to make sense.
Yes.
I...
I must have been a really terrible person.
Seeing how you're still this angry
at me after ten years...
I really...
I really don't remember anything.
But I sincerely apologize. I am so sorry.
What's with the sudden apology?
- Exactly.
- Are you okay?
This is not a situation
where you need to apologize.
I'm telling you, it's an act!
Hey, you're a hell of an actor.
Where did you learn to act?
Do they teach that in North Korea now?
- Hey, wait.
- Okay.
I can't atone for my past mistakes,
but perhaps...
Is there a way I can help you two?
- Help us?
- Yes.
- What the hell are you plotting?
- Hey, what's wrong with you?
I'm not plotting anything.
I'm doing this for me. For myself.
That package
I supposedly disappeared with.
If I just have that package,
you said you could stop
what the Heaven Capital guys
are planning, right?
I have a score to settle
with those guys, too.
I just figured if I stick with you two,
the ones who know my past
maybe I'll start to remember something.
Hey, listen to him. It all makes sense.
If he gets his memory back
and we find the package
isn't that the best
we can hope for right now?
I'll go get you another one
of those drinks you were drinking.
- No, it's fine. Are you okay?
- Yes.
Gosh, it hurts so much.
Oh, dear.
That's definitely not an act. My goodness.
That darn scumbag.
- This woman.
- That's Prosecutor Gang Yeong-ae.
I think Yoo must have botched the job.
Gosh, but still...
A Chinese restaurant owner,
a convenience store owner
and an office worker.
They may look like nobodies on the outside
but there's something
suspiciously professional
about the way they operate.
I mean, starting from
when they hit Capital
and then the whole thing with
ruining President Yoo's drug shipment.
Seriously, what's their motive?
Why do they keep interfering
with our business at every turn?
I just don't get it.
By any chance
I was just wondering
if you might have any hunches, sir.
Chairman Do, you must have
a lot of time on your hands.
Pardon?
Worrying about such useless things.
Oh, no, sir. Of course not.
With preparing
for the Yeongseon Island Project
I'm already stretched thin as it is.
Right, so I'll just stop looking into this
- and I'll wrap it up on my end.
- No, wait a minute.
There's something I need to check.
Understood.
The owner of a Chinese restaurant.
He's really moved up in the world.
I'm heading back to my office.
I've got work to do.
Prosecutor, I know
it's not my place to say
but are you sure you should be
getting involved in this?
Han Gyeong-wook has connections
in the Prosecutors' Office too.
You could face pressure
from unexpected places.
I came all the way to Yeongseon Island
and even had my life threatened.
I even found out exactly
what those jerks are really like.
You think I'm going to back down
over a little pressure?
I'll risk my career to expose everything
Han Gyeong-wook has done
and plans to do in the future.
I will make him pay for his crimes.
- What about Chairman Hwang's case?
- Right. I need to figure out
how to properly reinvestigate
that case as well.
- Thank you, Prosecutor.
- Of course.
Hey. Can I talk to you?
What?
Well...
About the hit-and-run driver
who hit you...
I will catch them no matter what,
so don't you worry.
Oh, okay.
Is that what you wanted to talk about?
Yes, that's part of it.
I realized I never got the chance
to properly thank you.
- Thank me for what?
- You saved my life. Twice.
- I'm truly grateful.
- Oh, it was nothing.
As long as you're okay, Prosecutor,
that's all that matters.
I think you're a really good person.
Me?
The Bong Je-sun I've seen
is someone who truly looks out for others.
A good person.
Even if you happen to go back
to your old self
my gratitude toward you will never change.
- Let me see your phone for a second.
- Oh, my phone?
It's my number.
It's not my work number.
It's my personal one.
I don't give this number to anyone,
but I'm making an exception for you.
But why are you giving this to me...
Because I owe you.
Save that number,
and call me if you ever need my help.
Anytime. For anything. Just once.
I'll help you out, no questions asked.
Are you really going to keep him around?
Why? You have a problem with it?
No. To me, it seemed like
he really didn't remember anything.
So I'm just wondering
if we really need to keep him with us.
He also said he can't control
when his skills come back, right?
Then he's just dead weight.
Don't tell me you actually believe
Bulgae lost his memory.
Don't you?
Look. This is the CCTV footage
from near the hospital Gong-bok sent over.
He said he went out
for chicken soup earlier, right?
But there's a chicken soup place
right in front of the hospital.
Why would he need to take a cab to go out?
Maybe he just went to find
a better chicken soup place or something.
That's ridiculous. Hey!
He took a taxi to escape
and then decided to come back.
Then he just shows up out of nowhere
saying he wants to help us?
He's definitely up to something.
But he seemed pretty clueless.
You really think he could plan all this?
He's Bulgae, not Bong Jae-sun.
The master of disguise, Bulgae,
who can even change his voice.
He's the kind of guy who'll stop
at nothing to complete his mission.
Did you forget ten years ago
when he showed up
on that ferry dressed as a woman?
Him, acting all innocent
like this right now...
It's nothing for a guy like him.
So don't you let your guard down either.
Okay, then if you knew
all that about Bulgae
why did you agree to take him in?
Mi-kyung and your wife
are at that K-Pop place or something.
What if he shows his true colors
and does something to them?
It would be better to just
get rid of him right now.
Didn't you see
Prosecutor Gang's reaction earlier?
Besides, everyone else
is completely convinced
he's the naive Bong Je-sun.
And he's putting on such a convincing act
so it's useless for me
to go around saying he's Bulgae.
It's better if I keep him close
and watch him.
That way, we can figure out
what he's after.
And then we can use it against him.
So you keep your eyes peeled
and watch him closely.
- He's coming.
- So he is, that jerk.
Oh, sorry about that.
I got caught up talking.
At least you know that. You drive.
JEONGSEOK BOARDING HOUSE
- Nam-il.
- Oh, Uncle!
Are you okay, Uncle?
What happened?
Are you allowed to leave
the hospital already?
- I'm much better now. I'm fine.
- I know, but still.
It's not like you're the Hulk. Jeez.
Who... who are they?
They're just some people I know.
- Why are you alone? Where's everyone?
- What?
The lady from the Chinese restaurant
came by with her kid earlier.
- Daddy!
- Oh, Ji-woo, you're here.
You came?
- Thank you.
- I still don't trust you 100%.
I only came because of Ji-woo,
so don't get the wrong idea.
I know.
You did well.
But where's your father?
I don't know. He said he was going
to close up the shop and come
but then he said
a large group of customers showed up
so he isn't coming.
Still, you should have
brought him with you.
He said he wouldn't come.
What was I supposed to do?
My dad's mad because of you,
so you go deal with him yourself.
Jeez.
All right. I'll go get him.
- Ji-woo, stay here for a minute.
- Okay.
You explain the situation to people
when they get here.
And...
- Keep a close eye on Bulgae.
- Yes, got it.
IMCHEON DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
Prosecutor Gang? Long time no see.
Are you back from your leave today?
I'm sorry, Chief Prosecutor.
I'm sorry I didn't answer your calls
and missed my return date.
I truly have no excuse.
Hey, that's not like you.
No need to apologize.
Judging by how well you look
you must have had a good time off.
I am so sorry. I'll accept any punishment.
You can go.
- Sir?
- Isn't your return report finished?
- I said, you can go.
- But Mr. Kim said
that you were desperately looking for me.
That was then, and this is now.
Or what? You want to stay
and write a formal apology?
No, sir. Really.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you so much. Take care, sir.
Yes.
Just as you said,
Gang Yeong-ae came to work.
I'll put my people on her.
We won't lose her like last time.
Hey, why are you here?
O-ran's already there.
I told you yesterday.
It's dangerous right now.
You need to close
the restaurant for a while.
You said you understood yesterday.
I said I'd convince O-ran.
When did I say I would leave?
And who are you
to decide to close the business?
Come on, you've been wanting a break.
Just think of this as a vacation.
But how can I think of it as a vacation
when it's not?
To you, this may just be a restaurant
you worked at reluctantly
but O-ran's mother and I
poured our youth into building this place.
Does it make any sense to close down
because of some thugs?
- Father.
- You go and take care of O-ran.
I can handle this restaurant
just fine on my own.
Go on upstairs and get some rest.
I'll close up.
I haven't been able to come
to the restaurant much lately.
All right, then.
Finish up and come upstairs.
We're closed.
Long time no see, Ho-myeong.
SPECIAL THANKS
TO KIM SANG-KYUNG AND KWON YUL
Do you and everyone around you
have to be destroyed
before you learn your lesson?
Is it okay for you to go up
against someone that dangerous?
- Take care of that woman.
- I'll have to get some blood on my hands.
That USB drive
with Han Gyeong-wook's weakness.
It means that the package has surfaced.
Those two have the missing package.
We just have to make Bulgae talk
and get the package.
Agent Bulgae of the Ministry
of People's Armed Forces.
A human weapon trained in North Korea.
- What?
I think you've got it wrong.
I'm telling you,
I really don't remember a thing.
He says he can't remember anything.
How are you supposed to make him talk?
Tie him up.
- You've really gone too far.
- Stop.
- Everyone will be in danger.
- We're not far from the finish line.
We need to strike first.
Hey, Bulgae. Now make your choice.