Min-ju is at peace now.
What do you mean by that?
Nam Si-heon.
I killed her.
You're telling me In-gyu killed Min-ju?
In-gyu would never do something like that.
And he also killed himself?
Something is completely off here.
Ever since what happened to In-gyu…
I've been trying to figure out…
where things went wrong.
This
started on the day Min-ju died.
Shouldn't we change
what happened that night, then?
To be honest,
a part of me…
wanted to ignore
what had already happened…
and just continue living with you.
But…
But you probably
couldn't bring yourself to do that.
I would've felt the same if I were you.
If you could only go back,
you would've done it over and over again.
Because Nam Si-heon
and Koo Yeon-jun
are that kind of people.
Even though you knew you would die,
you got on that plane
so you could see me again.
Now,
it's my turn to do something.
I'll go back to 1998.
What should I do when I get there?
The day Min-ju dies.
We must get through it safe and sound.
When you wake up in Min-ju's body,
you have to do whatever it takes
for Min-ju to make it out alive…
on October 13, 1998.
Okay.
I'll do that.
I'll try.
A TIME CALLED YOU
I want to ask you something.
What is it?
"Whenever your heart calls me."
What does it mean?
"I will come to you."
Give me your hand.
When I get back from 1998…
you still have to stay by my side.
Promise me.
I promise.
When the lights outside the window
Start dimming one by one
I write a letter to the sky
You left me for someone else…
Jun-hee.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Are you back from 1998?
No.
You weren't there when I woke up,
so I was surprised.
I thought everything that happened
last night was a dream.
Look at me. It's not a dream, is it?
Right.
From now on, you can never leave me, okay?
Okay.
You promised.
Sure, it's a promise.
I'll always be by your side.
Then last night,
you couldn't go back to the past
even though you listened to that song.
It was the first time you failed, right?
What could be the reason?
I've been doing some thinking.
If we compare
the situations
when Jun-hee and I traveled through time,
we might find a clue.
So what they have in common is
this cassette player and listening
to that song on this cassette.
Then, whether it be in the past or future,
you wake up in the body of someone
who resembles you.
You did that last night.
So, why couldn't you go back?
Perhaps there are other conditions
that we don't know about.
Also, there is something odd.
In 1998, the attacker
had already killed two people.
Byeon Da-hyeon and Min-ju.
If the attacker killed two people
just a few months apart,
it means they're a serial killer
who can't control themselves.
Why weren't there
any more killings after that?
You're right.
I also searched for more,
but I couldn't find anything.
Usually, serial killers only stop killing
when they're in prison, seriously injured,
or something like that.
Perhaps after killing Min-ju,
he was placed in a situation
where he couldn't commit murder again.
I'll go to the school and find out.
Something else must have happened
around that time.
I'll search for articles from 1998, then.
Maybe there were other incidents in Noksan
we didn't know about then.
Sir.
My goodness. Look who we have here.
You remember me?
Of course I do. You're Nam Si-heon.
Girls from other schools lined up
at the school gate to see you.
Hey, it's good to see you.
Come on. Come take a seat.
Here. Be careful.
Be careful.
I heard you were in an accident.
Is that when you hurt your leg?
It's a lot better now.
Have you been well, sir?
Of course. I'm old enough to retire soon.
Anyway, what brought you here today?
I have something to ask you.
Do you remember Kwon Min-ju,
a girl from our class?
Yes.
I was wondering if anything else happened
around the time of that incident.
That was back in 1998, wasn't it?
I'm not sure.
You know, perhaps someone was injured
or suddenly transferred schools.
Even something trivial.
I'm just curious
if there was anything you found strange.
Well, you probably already know
about Byeon Da-hyeon.
I don't remember
anything major happening since then.
By any chance,
are there still copies
of the school newsletter from back then?
There's something I want to check.
Well, I suppose
there should be copies in the library.
1998 NOKSAN MURDER CASE
NOKSAN HIGH SCHOOL GIRLS
MURDERED MONTHS APART
MURDER SUSPECT, JUNG, 18, ARRESTED
VICTIM, BYEON DA-HYEON (18)
VICTIM, KWON MIN-JU (18)
MURDER SUSPECT OF KWON MIN-JU
MR. JUNG (AGE 18)
Did you find anything?
No.
Why are you curious
about what happened back then?
It's because you can't accept
that In-gyu did it, isn't it?
Yes.
Since he confessed,
there wasn't much I could do.
But I kept thinking it was strange.
Why would In-gyu do something like that?
I was actually thinking
about what you said.
Something strange did happen.
It wasn't a kid from our class
but from another class.
He took a leave of absence
due to health issues
and was admitted to the hospital.
I just assumed he was sick or something.
But I found out later
that he was admitted to a locked ward
at a psychiatric hospital.
When was that?
It was in 1998.
It wasn't long
after what happened to Min-ju.
The whole school was unsettled
by what happened to Min-ju and Da-hyeon,
glossing over what happened to him.
Do you remember who that kid was?
Yes, of course.
I was his homeroom teacher
in his first year.
Give me a moment.
His name was
Chu…
I believe it was Cheol, Chung,
or something like that.
Okay, where should I put it?
You can put it down there.
Jeez, I told you I'd go get it.
No need for such trouble.
I had some free time today.
Thanks. Do you want a cup of coffee?
-Sounds good.
-Have a seat.
Gosh, why is she reading such scary stuff?
NOKSAN HIGH SCHOOL GIRLS
MURDERED MONTHS APART
VICTIM, BYEON DA-HYEON (18)
VICTIM, KWON MIN-JU (18)
-Jun-hee.
-Yes?
What's all this?
Oh. That…
Just looking something up.
They're all old murder cases.
Yeah.
I mean, you said
your insomnia has been bad,
along with bad dreams.
Doesn't reading this kind of thing
make it worse?
Chan-yeong.
Do you remember the dream
I told you about the other day?
Yeah.
It wasn't a dream.
What?
I…
met Yeon-jun again.
STUDENT RECORDS
-See you tomorrow.
-Good job today.
Oh, here it is. It's him.
This guy.
Oh Chan-hui.
You're telling me
you time-traveled back to 1998
and woke up in the body of the girl
who wrote this diary, Kwon Min-ju?
And everything that happened to you
since 1998 was actually real.
Right?
Yeah.
And you met Yeon-jun again.
But Yeon-jun is actually the same person
you met in 1998
called Nam Si-heon?
I'm not sure how all of this is possible.
Just how did you go back to 1998?
Using this.
I went back by listening
to Seo Ji-won's song with this.
I fell asleep listening to music on this.
And I was in 1998 when I woke up.
Kwon Min-ju and I had the same face,
as did Yeon-jun and Si-heon.
I think that's how it was possible.
As long as there is someone
who looks just like you
in the time you're trying to go to,
you can listen to this song,
travel through time,
and wake up in that person's body.
Is that what you're saying?
That's what we think.
I know it's hard to believe.
I thought it was a dream
in the beginning too.
No.
I believe you.
Really?
But why are you interested
in the Byeon Da-hyeon murder case?
Actually,
I think the culprit in that case
and whoever murdered Kwon Min-ju in 1998
might be the same person.
What?
Kwon Min-ju was murdered in 1998.
At the time, the culprit
confessed to killing Min-ju,
so he was immediately arrested.
But I have a feeling
the real culprit was someone else.
I'm sure the murderer of Byeon Da-hyeon
killed Kwon Min-Ju as well.
Chan-yeong.
Yeah?
Weren't you getting me some coffee?
I'd really love a cup.
Sure. Give me a minute.
Who is this?
Do you like her?
Chan-yeong, you can't be going through
my drawers like that.
Give it now.
You like her, don't you?
No, it's just…
that she doesn't have any friends
and doesn't talk much.
She's like me.
So I've just taken an interest in her.
That's liking someone.
If you like her that much,
you can just have her.
Have her? How?
If you make her into a specimen,
you can have her completely.
Like when you're collecting butterflies.
If you make her into a specimen
when she's at her most beautiful,
she'll be yours forever.
Chan-yeong, what are you talking about?
People are not insects.
If you like someone,
you must cherish them, not hurt them.
Cherish them?
Of course.
You must never hurt them
or do anything like that.
Huh? Where's the fun in that?
Anyway, this girl's eyes
look just like the eyes
of our puppy, Happy.
Is that how it was?
The person who killed Byeon Da-hyeon
also killed Kwon Min-ju?
YEON-JUN
SLIDE TO POWER OFF
The phone has been turned off.
You will be forwarded to voice mail.
After the tone…
From what I can remember,
Chan-hui was introverted and quiet.
SIBLINGS: OH CHAN-YEONG
Oh Chan-yeong.
Oh Chan-yeong?
Oh, I see he had a younger brother.
If he was born in 1988,
he must've been 11 in 1998.
Sir.
I think I know who the culprit is.
It's someone called Oh Chan-hui.
He went to Noksan High School in 1998.
Yes.
It also explains why the crimes stopped
after Min-ju's murder.
Apparently, he's been locked up
in a psychiatric facility since 1998.
No, I'm heading
to Jun-hee's home right now.
I will send you
Oh Chan-hui's school records first.
Okay.
Chan-yeong.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You said listening to this
took you to the past.
I was curious, so I had a listen.
Did you…
It's a great song.
But I just had a nice nap.
Yeah.
Jun-hee, I'm hungry.
Got anything to eat?
Yeah, I have fruit. Do you want some?
-But, Jun-hee.
-Yeah?
The murder of Kwon Min-ju in 1998.
Any clues on who the real culprit is?
Yeah. When Kwon Min-Ju was attacked
for the first time,
her attacker was wearing
a Noksan High School uniform.
The real culprit must be a male student
who attended Noksan High School back then.
I see.
I know I must have sounded crazy.
Thank you for taking me seriously.
No, I'm the one who should be grateful.
What are you grateful for?
Thanks to you, I just found out
what happened
to my brother and me back then.
Did I ever tell you?
I used to live in Noksan when I was young.
You shouldn't have disturbed me earlier.
Dear, I'm going to wait…
Hey.
Wake up.
Hey, wake up.
Are you awake?
Oh, taxi!
Taxi!
OH CHAN-HUI
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay. I'm absolutely fine.
Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
Something terrible could've happened.
No.
Something terrible almost happened to you.
Are you okay?
What were you doing here?
If you're not hurt, I'll be on my way.
Thank you so much for that.
Where are you going alone at this hour?
I think it'd be dangerous
for you to go alone.
I'll come with you.
No, you don't have to.
I just saved--
I just saved you.
What if something happens to you now?
May I ask where you're headed?
My mom's shop at the big intersection.
I know a shortcut to the intersection.
Let's take it.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Stop. Let go of me!
Why are you doing this?
Somebody help--
Stop.
Get away from me.
Get away.
Chan-yeong.
You don't know how disappointed I am
that you're not Kwon Min-ju.
Can I help you with your order?
What the hell?
What?
What could this be?
Who is this?
So, what would you like to order?
Female customers usually enjoy Set A or B.
As for guys…
At first, I was excited
because I thought you were Kwon Min-ju.
But the moment
I saw you looking right at me, I realized
that you were not the Kwon Min-ju I saw
in that photo back then.
You didn't shrink back or cower
like Min-ju used to.
I didn't feel an inkling of excitement
when I saw you.
Jun-hee.
Jun-hee!
Hello? Somebody's collapsed.
It's Apartment 805, 45 Yeoksam-dong.
Please hurry.
Jun-hee.
Jun-hee!
Koo Yeon-jun?
Oh Chan-yeong.
What are you doing here?
Was it you?
No.
She was like that when I got here.
Then why were you in there?
I thought whoever did this had come back.
I was hiding because I was scared.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Did you happen to know
what your brother had done?
Did you do this because Jun-hee found out?
What are you talking about? My brother?
I had something to give Jun-hee.
See? That chair.
I just dropped by to give her that chair.
Yeon-jun.
I'm the one
who should be scared out of my skin.
Do you know how shocked I was
when Jun-hee told me
you'd come back to life?
Didn't you say…
she was like this when you got here?
It was you.
It wasn't Oh Chan-hui.
You killed Kwon Min-ju and Byeon Da-hyeon.
Didn't you?
It was you.
It was you all along.
Why did you kill her?
Why did you kill Kwon Min-Ju?
Yeah.
Apparently, it was me.
But the funny thing is,
the things my older brother told me
when I was little…
Today, I finally figured out the answer
to that puzzle.
Finding a way
to get into my brother's body in 1998,
I guess that's just a bonus.
Yeon-jun.
All of this
is thanks to your girlfriend, Jun-hee.
Thank you.
No, Chan-hui.
You were wrong.
WHAT WOULD NAM SI-HEON SAY
IF HE FOUND OUT I LIKE HIM?
I'll lower myself to lie next to you
And I'll tell you
That because I cannot forget you
I'll just continue to love you
Dear, I'm going to wait…
She's damaged because of you.
It's fine.
I still have plenty of time.
Come on. Let's go, okay?
-Taking a shower?
-Stop it.
-Hey.
-Okay!
-Hey, get back here.
-I told you to get a move on.
Oh no.
Si-heon, open your eyes.
No, Si-heon. Oh no.
Oh, please.
Oh no.
What am I supposed to do now, Si-heon?
Si-heon. How did you end up here?
What am I going to do?
Si-heon.
Oh no.
Oh Chan-yeong.
We must find Oh Chan-yeong.
I'm going to find the cassette player
that he took…
and bring Si-heon back to life,
no matter what.
This is CCTV of Chan-yeong
caught after the crime.
Where is he now?
We went to his home and studio,
but he wasn't there.
We're using the CCTV footage
to trace his whereabouts.
But the items that he stole.
Do you know what they are?
My cassette player and my diary.
Those two things disappeared
after he left.
They wouldn't be particularly valuable.
Why would he have stolen them?
Do you have any idea why?
Or are those items somehow special?
Chan-yeong.
By the time
I woke Oh Chan-yeong up last night,
he might have already gone back
to 1998 once.
But if he went back to 1998,
whose body would he have woken up in?
There has to be someone
who looks like him.
His older brother, Oh Chan-hui.
Si-heon sent me this last night.
No, she's not Kwon Min-ju.
Right, Han Jun-hee?
Chan-hui.
I'm back from school.
Well.
I heard the dog whimpering for ages.
I thought he was playing with Happy.
But even after killing the dog,
he didn't even bat an eye.
Honestly. Did I really give birth to him?
He makes my skin crawl,
and I'm also worried.
It's driving me nuts, Chan-hui.
Where's Chan-yeong?
Oh Chan-yeong.
Are you sleeping?
Okay.
I guess you're not in the mood to talk
right now, are you?
Then I'll leave you to yourself.
Mom's mad at me, isn't she?
Because of what I did to Happy.
Are you mad at me too?
No? Why would I be?
You also said that if we like something,
we shouldn't hurt it.
Sorry.
Back then, I didn't know much better.
Chan-yeong.
You were right.
If you really like something,
you have to make it into a specimen
and make it yours.
-Really?
-Of course.
Because our little Chan-yeong
is a special person, just like me.
Normal people like Mom
will never understand people
like you and me.
Shall I let you in on a secret?
I'm actually
you from the future.
You don't get what I'm saying, do you?
Later, much later,
you'll get what I'm saying one day.
The most important thing
is to hide yourself
for that day.
Hide myself?
From now on,
you can't let anyone find out
just how special you are.
Be as nice and indifferent as possible.
Put on a mask that won't make others wary,
and show them it.
That'll make things easier for you.
Keep that in mind.
Next time I go to make specimens,
come with me.
I'm going to make
a very big and very pretty specimen.
SAEMMUL CONVALESCENT HOSPITAL
His condition improves on some days
and worsens on others.
On a good day,
we can have some light conversations.
But on a bad day, he spouts gibberish
and even has seizures.
Just a moment.
Hello, Mr. Oh Chan-hui.
My name is Han Jun-hee.
I am here
because I need to ask you something.
In 1998,
do you remember what happened back then?
a student from Noksan High School
named Kwon Min-ju died.
You remember, don't you?
If you heard me, please answer.
This is really important.
Please answer me!
Surely you know whether it was you
or your little brother who killed Min-ju?
I can…
hear everything.
Everything that is happening…
I can see and hear it all.
But that's all.
All I can do is watch.
I can't do anything.
Yeah? Yeah.
I promised you last time, didn't I?
That when I went to make
a bigger and prettier specimen,
I'd take you along.
What do you think? Do you like it?
Keep shining the light on her.
Be careful, or you might get hurt.
It'll be over soon if you listen to me.
Then we'll let you go, okay?
No.
It…
It wasn't me.
I didn't do it!
I didn't want to do it.
If it wasn't you who did it,
then your younger brother did it, right?
It was Oh Chan-yeong's doing…
right?
Kwon Min-Ju.
How…
How are you…
I didn't do it.
Min-ju.
It wasn't me. I didn't do it.
They made me do it.
They forced me to do it, Min-ju.
I never wanted anything like that, Min-ju.
-It wasn't me, Min-ju!
-All right, Mr. Oh Chan-hui.
-If there's someone precious to you…
-Mr. Oh. It's okay.
It's okay.
It was Oh Chan-yeong who killed Min-ju,
not Oh Chan-hui.
Oh Chan-hui went insane
watching what his brother did.
Who are the "they" he was talking about?
Other than Oh Chan-yeong,
who could've told him to do such a thing?
What is it?
Thanks to you, I just found out
what happened
to my brother and me back then.
The fact that the murders in 1998
were committed by Oh Chan-yeong,
not Oh Chan-hui.
Oh Chan-yeong only realized that
after what I said yesterday.
What have I done?
I was the one who told him everything.
So both Si-heon and Min-ju are dead
because I…
Min-ju and Si-heon died
because of Oh Chan-yeong, not you.
It's all Oh Chan-yeong's doing.
We have to catch him.
We have to catch him
and find the cassette player.
That's how we can bring back Si-heon.
Hello?
What?
You said you've caught Oh Chan-yeong?
Yes.
We arrested him, hiding in a motel.
What was he doing
at the time of his arrest?
Was he listening to music?
How did you know that?
Where is that cassette player right now?
Could we get it back right away?
Returning it to you won't be an issue
once the National Forensic Service
is done collecting evidence.
However, the cassette player
isn't intact right now.
Oh Chan-yeong.
Oh Chan-yeong!
Come on! Grab him quickly!
No, it's not time yet.
Why did it have to be now? Why?
EVIDENCE NUMBER 23-01
-Hey! It was you!
-Oh, hang on.
It was you from the very beginning, huh?
You were the killer! Bring Si-heon back!
You can't be doing this.
Bring Si-heon back!
Why did you do it?
No, Han Jun-hee!
You've got things in the wrong order.
First, you need to ask yourself.
"What did I, Han Jun-hee,
possibly do to Kwon Min-Ju"?
Hey, let's go.
You don't understand?
I wasn't the one who killed Kwon Min-ju.
It was you, Han Jun-hee.
Subtitle translation by: Sung In Jang