(The drama was shot in the presence of the child actress' guardian.)
Hello?
Detective Choi!
(Final Episode)
Hello?
(Geumsung Realty)
Detective Choi!
Hello?
What's wrong?
Dae Sung's not back yet.
You're right.
If that darn detective made some excuse...
to take him to the station...
A Hee.
Dae Sung left with Detective Choi.
They've been gone for hours.
What? Where did they go?
I don't know where they went,
but are they at the...
Wait!
What did she say?
We'll hear soon enough if they're at the station.
Okay.
Then you come with me to check on Yul.
She'll be alone at home.
It bothers me.
Let's go. Bring that with you.
(Police)
Choi Ji Woong!
Where is he?
Officer Do. The sergeant is not your friend.
How dare you yell his name?
If all a cop does is bother the innocent,
I might as well just quit.
I'll drop rank...
and take him on as a citizen.
Where is he?
He took Dae Sung again, didn't he?
He isn't here. Shall I call him for you?
(Police)
I wonder if he has a thing for An Dae Sung now.
He's not picking up.
Shall I leave a message...
Officer Do!
My goodness.
Will you make it...
or will you not?
Detective Choi!
You said he left to find proof that Yul was abused.
No one's at home?
I don't think he was here at all.
No one's home.
Give me the phone.
A Hee.
Something's not right. I have a bad feeling about this.
What do you mean?
Yul left the store a long time ago,
but she's not at home.
And the smell coming through the window...
- It's... - Isn't it that drain cleaner?
Yes, that's it! Pine scented Quick Drain Cleaner.
I see the bottles.
I smelled it when I was here last time,
and I smell it now too.
You heard what Products told Dae Sung, didn't you?
Captain, I need backup!
Come to Geumsung Realty.
Dae Sung and Yul might be in danger!
(Geumsung Realty)
Stay away!
He's alive.
He's still alive.
This is Nawoo Two. Stab victim found at Geumsung Realty.
Send paramedics right away.
Captain.
An Dae Sung, you have the right to an attorney...
What are you doing?
You should hear what happened first!
Did you do it?
Yes.
What are you saying?
It wasn't you. It was Seo Cheon Kyu!
Again,
I couldn't help.
Yet again,
I caused a situation...
Dae Sung! Pull yourself together!
Yul.
Is she still at the store?
They said she left a while ago.
But she wasn't at home.
- An Dae Sung! - Captain!
Please.
If you suspect Dae Sung now,
we might never get to save Yul.
I might...
do something else I'll regret.
Thank you. I promise I'll save Yul.
I let him go because I trust you.
We can't let anyone else get hurt.
Okay.
(Geumsung Realty)
It wasn't me.
- I know. - It really wasn't me.
I was locked in the room in the back.
- I broke out... - I know.
I know.
Yul.
If her dad took her...
Let's get him.
Detective Choi might wake up by then.
Even if he doesn't, we'll catch him.
But they'll suspect you until then.
Will you still do it?
(Quick Drain Cleaner)
You know that man, right?
You need to answer me properly.
I do.
Did you follow me?
You need to keep a close eye on your girl.
What if she roams around the streets at this hour?
What a nuisance.
Won't she develop a bad habit if you don't stop her?
I mean, I happened to come across her cell phone.
I saw some weird photos on her phone.
You're lucky that I saw those photos.
If the cops saw them, things would have gotten very ugly.
What? Why are you doing this?
The thing is,
I also took a photo.
There was a terrible incident...
in the unit next door not too long ago.
I'm sure you know.
That strange lady, Ms. Chairwoman.
She almost died in that unit before the ambulance took her.
I saw her enter the unit next door.
The unit next door was vacant.
I found it odd that she went in, so I secretly followed her inside.
And I secretly took a photo.
My goodness. I was so scared!
I almost peed my pants.
I mean, if this works out,
I thought it would be a win-win situation...
for the both of us.
Well, I can use this...
to destroy that jerk,
the son of the supermarket lady.
And I just need you to keep quiet.
I don't follow you at all.
I can tell the cops that the son of the supermarket lady...
is the culprit.
I can do that for you. Okay?
And when I have to leave this neighborhood,
I just need you to find me a house in a quiet and clean area.
If you buy me a house...
No. You can rent a house for me with a deposit.
It will be clean for both of us.
I'm sure you have a good network with your fellow realtors.
That would be lovely for me.
Gosh.
There are so many weirdos.
Darn it.
So that man was punished.
He saw something he shouldn't.
Do you know who else was punished?
I promised you, didn't I?
I kept my promise.
(Geumsung Realty)
Did you check inside?
What about the alibi?
(KCSI)
(Under Investigation, Do Not Enter)
(Operating Room)
(Police)
Hello, there.
(Surgery in Progress)
(Authorized Personnel Only)
Hey.
Don't you think we should look for the realtor first?
Exactly. According to the other business owners in the building,
he closed his office yesterday to visit his wife.
But why did Detective Choi go there?
He left saying he was going to the supermarket.
He went there to put pressure on the cashier...
because he only had circumstantial evidence.
If he found a lead,
he wouldn't have proceeded without reporting it first.
Right. I'm bringing this up because he's not the type to do so.
What's going on?
Always by our side Happy, happy MS
This doesn't count as hiding.
Don't you think people will find it suspicious?
People always miss what's right in front of them.
I'm not hiding to evade the police.
I just need to figure out where the culprit is.
Finding the culprit is important. But we must find Yul too!
Right. We need to figure out where he is to find her.
You want to find the culprit in that box? How?
With magic?
No.
We tried to find the culprit by looking at our customers...
who bought the items that were used in the crimes.
I can't hear you at all.
Hold on.
Right here. Talk to me through here.
We need to figure out the location of the culprit...
from the items the culprit bought.
He knew that I was suspecting him for abusing Yul.
But he must have stopped by here to buy some stuff...
for a reason before he ran away.
Is that so?
- As for the things he bought... - What did he buy?
He didn't buy a lot.
He only bought instant food and so on.
My goodness. It's been a while.
It's been a week, right?
Hold on.
You buy all of your groceries for the week,
so you never have to leave the house?
My goodness. You should go outside, exercise,
and meet your friends.
You play computer games, right?
- What? - Nothing.
Right.
Right!
We have a buy-1-get-1-free deal for these dumplings.
You must have forgotten to take an extra bag.
Part Timer! Bring us an extra bag of dumplings.
The one with the buy-1-get-1-free deal!
No. Bring me five bags!
Forget it!
Take the dumplings!
(Chaechae Stationery Store)
The hairtail is on sale today.
- It is? - Yes.
We just received our beef today.
This isn't the only place where people won't check.
What are you talking about?
Seo Cheon Kyu came back to his office yesterday.
As soon as the incident took place, he took Yul.
He never went far.
He's hiding in this neighborhood.
Don't you think he's hiding somewhere with the instant food?
(Chaechae Stationery Store)
They move in a pack.
They never know what can end them.
(Soju)
Yul, why won't you eat?
I'm not hungry.
Once the hunting is successful,
they drag their prey someplace deep and drown it.
But you didn't eat anything today.
What if you get sick?
You'll die...
because you can't go to the hospital.
And I'm not a doctor.
Do you want to finish this or get punished for an hour?
If he's the only one who saw what he shouldn't have seen,
I'd be relieved.
What did you take with Mom's phone?
Videos and photos.
Of whom?
Where is it now?
If someone else sees it, he'll also be dead.
Yul. If the police see it,
I'll go to prison, and you'll go to the orphanage.
Then what do you think will happen to you?
Darn it.
Gosh.
Did you hide it in the supermarket?
If you don't tell me the truth,
everyone who works there will end up like him.
What? I can't order soju?
Darn it.
(No alcoholic beverages and cigarettes sold online)
(Except for traditional liquor)
(Pears for 3.5 dollars)
Look.
This is like searching for a needle in a haystack.
We can never go through all these.
It was so hard to get it from the redevelopment committee manager.
Look carefully.
She's right. Look carefully.
(Delivery order)
(Jinsong Apartment Building 1, Unit 406)
Okay.
Hey. I'm off for delivery.
(Traditional Liquor)
Part Timer. Watch the checkout.
- Check over there. - Yes.
What's this?
Busy?
How's the business going?
Sure.
Mic check. One, two, three.
Did anything happen while I was gone?
- Hello. - Hi.
Do you need anything?
I'm good.
Next.
(Goodbye)
No.
That's right.
This is where Five Dollars lived.
Cut the apple in half and put it on the plate.
Take this.
Darn it. It should've been her son.
He's the cause of all this.
He needs to be punished.
- Did you find anything? - Nothing.
Bye.
- Have a good day. - Bye.
Let's go.
There's nothing here. Let's check the real estate office.
- Turn the CCTV off. - What?
Turn the CCTV off.
Oh, right.
Meat. Come here.
- You can come out now. - Is it okay now?
Hold it in the back.
- You can come out now. - What is that smell?
- Watch out. - Oh, my hand.
- Be careful. - My leg.
Be careful.
- Be careful. - My legs feel numb.
Get me some water. Thank you.
Fish. Meat.
Cover the windows.
Okay.
- I feel dizzy. - Get him a chair.
(MS Mart)
No, don't.
Eat slowly.
You'll get sick.
That's strange.
What is?
I just delivered to this house,
and they placed an order again.
Maybe they missed something.
No.
It's the same order again.
Maybe it's an error.
Five, zero, five. What does that mean?
Oh, I know. "Deliver it to Unit 505."
"It's on me."
Mom. What's the unit number?
Unit 408.
Next to Five Dollars?
Yes.
Mom. It...
That house wouldn't order anything.
That house is empty.
- What? - Ms. Chairwoman...
nagged at Geumsung Realty...
that the empty house was using electricity.
- Oh, my goodness. - Ra Hee.
Ms. Chairwoman fell off the fourth floor.
- Yes. - It...
Maybe it's the wrong address...
Five, zero, five.
That's Yul.
Five zero five?
No, it's SOS.
- It's... - I know what this is.
I'm saying it looks like 505.
What?
It's Yul.
We should check the site first...
If what he said is true,
the serial killer took the kid as a hostage.
What if it's not?
Then Dae Sung will be arrested.
We'll also be in trouble.
I'm retiring soon,
but will you be okay if you get fired?
Let's check the site first.
Listen to me this once for goodness' sake.
Then let's go through the back.
He isn't likely to open the door.
He's probably focusing on that.
Right here.
Yul.
- Yul? - Yul.
Let me try.
Yul?
Yul.
Shoot.
- Yul. - Yul.
Yul.
- Yul. - Is no one in?
Yul!
- Hey, you made it. - Open up!
We must get in.
Seo Yul!
Yul.
You know how to break in?
I learned how but I'm not good at it.
Yul. Sweetie.
What are you doing?
You know what happens if you don't listen to me, don't you?
Open the door.
Open...
Hurry up.
I'm trying okay?
Give me a while.
Does anyone have a flashlight? It's too dark.
(Police)
Okay.
Fish is trying to break in but there's no sign anyone's in.
What's that up there?
Yul!
Hello? A kid's in danger.
Break through the window or the main door.
Yes.
They'll take ten minutes at least.
I wonder if the ladder truck can get in.
Dae Sung, I need a few of you here.
Where are you going?
Stay right as you are.
(Police)
Don't move.
Where is she? What's going on?
Oh, my gosh!
It's Yul!
- Oh, dear. - Yul!
Will someone do something?
- Is that Yul? - Yul!
Find something to catch her if she falls.
- Go. - Something to catch her with?
Let's check the recycling bins!
Don't move. Stay right as you are.
That's it. Stay very still. Don't move.
A digital door lock.
Yes.
He bought one.
(Closed temporarily)
Look around.
Part Timer, take this.
Let's go.
Is anyone home?
- Who is it? - I'm a police officer.
What's the matter?
Excuse me.
What...
Spread it all out.
- Help us. - Okay.
Here. Take this too.
Take this for me.
Yul.
Yul, hang in there. Stay still.
Is that A Hee?
- My gosh. - A Hee!
- What's she doing? - Hang on tight.
- What will she do? - Yul, keep still.
Oh, dear...
What are you doing there? I'm in.
That's the digital lock from Geumsung Realty.
Geumsung Realty had the new one he'd bought.
Check this unit first.
I'll open that door too.
Be careful.
(Police)
Officer Do, are you crazy?
- A Hee! - She's out of her mind.
Watch your step.
Be careful.
- Be careful. - Careful.
A Hee!
Oh, dear...
She's out of her mind. She's crazy.
She's coming down.
Take your time.
- That's it. - Be careful.
Watch out.
Yul. Hang in there.
Stay right where you are.
Thank you.
It must be nice.
- Do something. - Watch your step.
A Hee...
Don't move, Yul.
Yul.
Take my hand.
It's okay. I will...
hold tight and never let go of you.
Grab hold of me.
Take her hand.
Be careful.
- A Hee, watch out! - That's it.
- Be careful. - There you go.
That's it. Hold on tight.
- Yul. - You're all right.
- Be careful. - Yul.
You're all right.
- Yul. - You're okay.
- Be careful. - Be careful.
- Hold on tight. - Be careful.
They are safe.
- Gosh. Thank goodness. - Gosh.
Gosh, Do Crazy.
Yul. Are you all right?
You must have been scared.
Yul.
Where is...
your dad?
Yul is fine.
Seal off the entrance, please.
Seo Cheon Kyu...
It's okay.
I'm just going to check something. I'll be back right away.
Stay here and wait for me. Okay?
Dae Sung.
A Hee.
Who are you?
I recognize you.
You're neither a man nor a woman.
You monster. How dare you?
You're the monster, not me.
I'm a friend of Kyung A, the girl you killed. You scumbag.
What on earth...
I know her.
Nguyen Thi Zhonglin.
That's Yul's mother.
Did she see this?
I found two corpses in Unit 408...
- Yul. - of Jinsong Apartment.
I need backup.
Let's go.
Are you all right?
What's that?
Mom, take Yul.
Go to Unit 409!
Unit 409?
What?
Hey!
Hey. Are you all right?
Don't move.
I have eyes on the suspect!
He's going from the 4th floor to the 1st floor!
Hey, there he comes.
Freeze!
- Gosh. - Goodness!
Stop right there, Seo Cheon Kyu!
This is Nawoo Two. We have an emergency.
A murder suspect is on the run toward Nawoo Elementary School...
from Jinsong Apartment.
Did we lose him?
I'll go with him. Don't worry.
Are you okay?
Excuse me.
I heard a kid was locked up inside.
Where is she?
Oh, well...
She's scared and in great shock.
I don't think you can talk to her now.
We'll talk to her and bring her to the police station.
Let me go with you. Drop me off at the supermarket.
I should go and look for Seo Cheon Kyu.
Ma'am, it will be hard to look for him while driving.
Let me go with you too.
Sure.
This will be enough to put him away.
We'll find him soon...
once the police start looking for him.
Okay.
Then I'll keep Yul with me.
(Geumsung Realty)
Where do you think he went?
He knows now that he can't hide in a vacant unit anymore.
He won't leave this neighborhood that easily.
- Why not? - He didn't leave...
even after killing his wife.
Something must be keeping him here.
- Go. - Okay.
(Cafe)
Hey.
Oh, my. Hold on.
Let's see.
Hello?
Meat. Where are you now?
Okay.
He just went into the alley next to Hansol Studio.
Go into the alley.
Ma'am! There he is!
- Right there. - Where?
Go left.
That way.
- Over there. Step on it! - To the right?
(Mother)
Mom. It's dangerous. Stay home...
I'm fine.
I'm with Meat.
I'll be home soon.
Yul.
Dae Sung. How's Yul?
Is she okay?
Where are you?
- Are you home? - Yul?
- Yul? She's with Dad... - Hey.
Are you in the supermarket?
If you're still there, check...
the order number 505. Don't deliver it. Never.
That will put you in trouble. Don't deliver it!
What are you talking about?
If you don't do as I say, you'll die.
I could just set this place on fire.
Okay.
I get it.
Darn!
- That doesn't sound right. - Five zero five.
That's what Yul said instead of SOS.
It's Yul. Yul is what Geumsung wants.
That's why he never left this town.
I'll request the location track on Ms. Han's phone...
and a search around this area.
If she calls you again, don't try to do anything.
Act like you know nothing and buy time.
The line got cut off.
Yul's with me in the supermarket.
Dad went to the police station to talk to Doo Hyun.
I was talking to Yul.
- Are you with Yul? - Yes, it's just the two of us.
Are the police going to the supermarket?
No, I don't think she's in condition to talk to them today.
It's only the two of us here.
Just us two.
(Design, construction)
If you mess with my kid or yours,
I'm going to kill you.
Too bad.
They might end up dead tonight...
like other women.
Whether it's my wife or my daughter...
or anyone else,
I like the feeling of having control over them.
When I don't,
it makes me very upset.
You wish.
Don't be ridiculous.
Meat!
Meat.
(MS Mart)
Over here!
(Police)
Meat.
Ms. Han. Are you okay?
A Hee. Dae Sung's in danger. We have to go to the supermarket.
What?
(Police)
Where's my daughter?
Kwon Bo Yeon.
Lee Kyung A.
Your wife.
Yul's mom, Nguyen Thi Zhonglin.
The police have videos of you beating and murdering them.
Five Dollars' body was found in your hideout.
Yes. I know.
You think I can't kill you...
when I killed them all?
You couldn't kill Ms. Chairwoman and Detective Choi.
And you think their current condition...
is better than being dead?
Whatever.
Where's Yul?
She's all I need.
You may kill me, but you can never take her.
She's my daughter!
- Yes. - Dae Sung!
- Dae Sung. - Dae Sung.
Unfortunately, she may be your daughter, but you don't own her.
Just because she's your daughter,
doesn't mean you can order her around.
Think about it.
How can you ever have someone your way?
You can't even do that with yourself.
- Dae Sung. No. - Dae Sung.
Dae Sung.
What do you think you're doing?
Things aren't going your way even now.
- Dae Sung. No. - Dae Sung.
- No. - Dae Sung.
So you're weird...
for thinking that's possible.
Dae Sung.
- Dae Sung. - Dae Sung.
- Dae Sung. - An Dae Sung.
Dae Sung. Open it.
Dae Sung. An Dae Sung.
Dae Sung.
Is it for kindergarten class?
- It's for adults. - What?
That toy washing machine is a great shaker.
Okay.
Daesung Mart, right?
You messed up my delivery.
I never ordered this.
It's the second time this week.
What about your shoes? Are you hurt?
What happened?
Here.
You idiot. So why would you...
risk your life for someone else's business?
(Samyu Peaches)
A Hee!
My gosh.
Go, quick!
- Dae Sung! - Dae Sung!
Dae Sung!
Are you okay?
- Dae Sung. - Get up.
Seo Cheon Kyu, you're under arrest for murder.
You can hire an attorney,
and you can explain yourself.
I didn't risk my life for someone else's business.
I didn't...
try to avenge the victims.
I just...
hope that a customer I saw yesterday...
gets to come back today and tomorrow.
Without...
any troubles or fear.
Hey.
Who do you think you are?
Who are you?
What are you?
Who do you think?
Even if it didn't involve him,
when he saw someone get hurt or die, he cared about his neighbors...
instead of turning a blind eye.
He listened even to a little girl.
That's right.
If not for Dae Sung, none of us would've cared.
We'd have let it go thinking it wasn't my business!
That's right.
Dae Sung's nosiness...
caught a killer.
Come along.
- Mom. - Dae Sung.
Well done.
You did great.
Well done, son.
Well done.
You did great.
Good for you.
I'm proud of you.
We'll take it from here.
Come with us. Get in the car.
Watch him carefully.
Good job.
Thank you.
Yul.
Are you okay?
(MS Mart)
Hi.
You didn't have to come and get me.
Why did you even bother?
Let's go.
Spinach.
- And two zucchinis. - Two zucchinis.
- Here you go. Cook something nice. - Thank you.
I'm here on my own, sorry.
I can't leave the stall to deliver.
Are you sure?
Of course, I am.
What are you doing? How rude.
Hello? Mic test. One, two.
This is a notice from the women's society chairwoman.
Today in the ground-level parking lot,
we're selling fresh organic produce delivered...
directly from the field.
Just for two hours. It's a limited deal.
They're offering a special deal,
So fill your shopping bags with some great items.
Oh, my gosh.
I got here first!
- This looks so fresh. - They're all fresh.
That one? Yes, sure.
Products sent me.
She sent you something to celebrate your recovery.
Tell her to just be a good chairwoman.
Once I'm out of here...
Mom.
What are you doing here?
I told you Products sent you a gift.
Mom.
She called around and finally reached her in the US.
My baby...
My dear baby...
Are you okay?
You're coming with me.
I'll treat you well.
- Goodbye! - Thank you.
Bye.
You want this?
(Courageous Civilian Certificate)
- And that too. - Okay.
She had a store since she was younger.
That's her son.
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hello. - Congratulations.
You're so handsome.
Not really.
He's such a good son.
What took you so long? Hurry up.
You got even prettier.
You should be a model.
Part Timer, we need help.
Okay, coming.
Do you have clam meat?
- Clam meat? - Yes.
I'll get you some.
Are you in a good mood?
You're so pretty I almost didn't recognize you.
How cute.
What's this?
(Chocolate Pie)
- Who would open... - I apologize.
I was passing by and came in to get something.
I thought I should apologize while I was here.
I was just doing my job but...
I got you all wrong.
This is on us.
Thanks.
And don't ever come to...
our store with a frown, dear valued customer.
Always by our side Happy, happy MS
Hey, Yul. Hello!
- Are you back from school? - Yes.
- I ate and am off to extra class. - Is it Yul?
Where's Grandma?
Grandma!
Hi. Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Dae Sung, when will you visit?
Next month. With A Hee.
Okay. You have to visit, okay?
Yul, if you want to come back here,
- just... - Yul!
Let's go!
I have to go now.
- Bye. - Okay.
- Take care. - Bye!
I'm jealous.
She's much cuter now.
(Pineapple)
You. What do you do for a living?
Right now, I'm a cashier.
Then...
what do you dream to be?
(Mom and Son Mart)
(The Killer's Shopping List)
(Special thanks to actor Park Chul Min.)
(Thank you for watching The Killer's Shopping List.)
(Goodbye!)