Rak!
You!
What's going on? What did my son do?
Your son got my girlfriend pregnant.
Don't expect me to accept a promiscuous
woman like you as my daughter-in-law.
Never.
I'm not backing down that easily.
They have no idea what I’m capable of.
I'm sending all three of you
to study abroad.
So, how can we meet?
My class is at ten o'clock,
Monday to Friday. Come if you're free.
I'm so glad to have a friend
who's pregnant along with me.
Our babies will have playmates.
They won't be lonely.
Yours will probably be born before mine.
Probably just around the same time.
But no matter what,
my baby will have to call yours
the older sibling.
I don't care what Madam thinks.
To me, Mr. Chen is
the eldest son of this family.
Thank you for respecting me and Chen.
We're in the same boat.
Madam sees us both as outsiders.
We need to stick together.
That's the only way to stand up to her.
If you're free,
come visit me at the stall anytime.
Yes, Big Sister.
What are you boiling?
Chinese herbal tea, ma'am.
You said you had mouth ulcers.
I haven't been sleeping well
for the past couple of nights.
It's almost done, ma'am.
Thanks.
Once you're done, boil this tonic too.
What kind of medicine is this, ma'am?
It's a tonic for pregnancy.
Boil it and make Chan drink it every day.
Yes, ma'am.
She'll be glad to know you care.
It'll be trouble
once her belly gets bigger.
What did you say, ma'am?
I said don't forget to boil it.
No, ma'am. I won't forget.
Just understand how the machines work.
We don't have to do the work ourselves.
Chen, do you like working here?
I can do anything
that helps lighten Dad's load.
Wow.
Dad's lucky to have you.
Otherwise, he'd be tired all alone.
Once the three of you graduate,
he'll have plenty of help.
No way. I don't like working
at the rice mill. I won't do it.
Then why'd you ask to work here?
Because Mom said
I couldn't just sit around.
If you want to go see your girl, just go.
Are you sure?
Go quickly and come back quickly.
I know what it's like to be in love.
Thanks, Brother.
You helped me and Hong before.
Consider this payback.
Then, I'll go and come back fast.
All right.
Who's that, Tub?
An athlete in training?
He's the son of Madam's friend.
TEACHER NATE'S MUSIC CLASS
It's delicious.
Ranee.
-Good morning.
Have you met Opas yet?
We haven't talked yet.
No, he was out riding.
You both love horseback riding.
You should get along well.
When Opas
saw the horse, he ran off
to the stables and left me behind!
If he stays the week,
he can ride until he's satisfied!
All right.
Oh.
Speak of the devil!
Here he is.
Ranee, meet Opas.
Hello.
Excuse me, I'll go get ready.
Where are you off to?
She has singing lessons.
She's been chosen
to perform for the new principal.
Let Opas drive you then.
He drives well
and has his license.
You don't have to worry.
That way, he won't get bored
listening to us old ladies
talking about the past.
Opas,
can you drive her?
Sure, Mom.
Cha-aim,
go with them.
Yes, ma'am.
-Excuse me.
-Go ahead, dear.
-Come, sit down.
-Yes, Mom.
-Drink some water?
-Sure.
Aunt Pissamai, your horses are so strong.
-Were they good?
-I really liked them.
Really?
Will the rice be delivered
to the customer on time?
Yes, Dad.
Where is Wee?
Oh? Was Rawee supposed to be here?
So he didn't come to help you?
I haven't seen him, Dad.
All of your younger brothers
are still acting like kids.
I must have raised them too comfortably.
Please don't tell Madam
that Rawee didn't come.
He'll get scolded.
Thank you
for looking out for your brother.
Seems like you're the only one
I can truly rely on.
Rawee's still young.
He'll become more responsible in time.
Keep working.
I'm going to talk with Hui for a bit.
Yes, Dad.
Hui.
Yes, sir.
Let me walk you in.
All right.
Mr. Wee.
-Come here. Mr. Rawee.
-Cha-aim.
Who is he, Cha-aim?
The son of Madam's friend.
Why did he bring Ranee?
He offered. She didn't really want him to.
Is he trying to court her?
Definitely.
He's a real threat.
I heard he's studying engineering.
He's just so-so.
But his mom's really close to Madam.
She's trying to match her son
with the Young Miss.
It all depends on Ranee.
Even the most stubborn heart
softens with time, Mr. Rawee.
And he's staying over
for a whole week too.
A whole week?
And they like similar things too.
Like what?
Horseback riding.
She said he rides really well.
He even looks like a professional athlete.
Are you still mad at me?
I'm man enough not to blame others.
You and your brother
are two different people.
And you've never done
anything wrong to me.
Why would I be angry?
That's good to hear.
Also, a single hand can't clap.
Chan's the ambitious type.
She's always wanted
to be part of a rich family.
Anyway, what brings you here?
Do you need any help?
What's this?
Payment for horseback-riding lessons.
I have more. It's all I've got.
I smashed my piggy bank for it.
Why do you want to learn?
I want to ride with Ranee.
And I want to look more impressive,
way more than that city guy.
I get it.
You're not going to teach me?
I like your spirit.
I'll teach you for free.
Really?
Thank you so much!
Save that money
to buy Ms. Ranee a birthday gift instead.
It's coming up soon.
When's her birthday?
Wow, look at this Madam Social Climber.
Completely gone.
Is this girl starving
to death or something?
Did Chanraem drink the tonic?
She did, ma'am. She drank all of it.
Then boil another batch for her.
Consider it making merit for the child.
Yes, ma'am.
PISSAMAI FARM
This is the saddle.
It's like a seat cushion for riding.
These are the stirrups
where your feet go.
To measure the stirrup length,
stretch your arm out from the saddle…
This is the girth,
to secure the saddle tightly…
Rawee?
This is
the bridle.
You use it to control the horse.
Rawee.
Oh, hey.
What are you doing?
Learning how to ride.
What brought this on?
I want to ride horses with you.
Hello there. Are you Ranee's friend?
Not just a friend.
I'm someone special to her.
Thank you.
Is everything going smoothly today?
Yes, Dad.
What about Rawee?
I must have left the mill
with the right person.
Rawee probably doesn't like
this kind of work.
But Madam forced him to come here.
She's worried you'd favor me over him.
Ngor,
I'm going out.
Watch over the house carefully.
Yes, ma'am.
Is it gone?
Yes, she drank it all.
She must really like the taste.
And how was she after drinking it?
Oh.
When I went to her room,
she always slept like a log.
Make her another batch.
Yes, ma'am.
Don't be afraid.
If the horse bucks,
you have to hold steady.
Relax. Don't tense up.
You can't be stressed when riding a horse.
I'm right here. No need to worry.
Okay.
When will I be able to ride like that?
What, are you going
to just sleep all day long?
You aren't going to help me
at all, are you?
Chan, what's wrong with you?
My stomach hurts so bad, Auntie.
Oh?
I feel nauseous,
like I'm going to throw up…
Don't puke here!
Come on, let's go outside. Can you walk?
I'm dizzy, Auntie.
I…
This isn't looking good.
Let's take you to the doctor.
Are you okay? What's wrong?
I've been having sharp stomach pains
for two days now, Auntie.
Go see a doctor.
You're pregnant. You need to be careful.
I'll watch the stall for you.
I'm feeling a bit better now.
-Thanks, Auntie.
-Alright.
Hong!
-Are you okay?
-Auntie…
Hold on just a bit longer.
Madam!
Madam! Chan has stomach pains!
Then take her to the hospital.
-Prajak, take her.
-Yes, ma'am.
Be careful.
You're picking things up fast.
You've really lightened my load.
Thank you, Dad.
Soon, I might not even need
to come to the mill anymore.
Anyway,
if I also want to learn about the hotel
operations, would it be possible?
Why not? It's family business.
All my children
should learn everything,
so I'll know who's suited
to take over which part.
Thank you, Dad.
Chen! Chen!
What is it?
Hong fainted at the market.
She was bleeding too.
No one knows what happened!
Come.
I'm all right now.
All right.
What did the doctor say?
It was severe food poisoning,
likely due to an infection.
You eat carelessly.
And the baby?
The doctor said the baby's fine.
But the doctor also said
we should monitor her closely.
Go rest.
-Go.
-Yes, ma'am.
All right.
Madam, would you like your snack now?
I've lost my appetite.
Dear…
I'm sorry.
I couldn't save your child.
It's all right.
You're still young.
You can get pregnant again.
Have you liked Ranee for a long time?
Not that long, time-wise.
But feeling-wise…
it feels like forever.
You've got a mouth on you.
Ever been punched in school?
I don't use violence.
Ranee doesn't like that.
Just kidding.
Has Ranee ever mentioned me?
Never.
Our families are pairing us up.
My mother and Aunt Pissamai
have been friends since school.
I came this time to meet her formally.
Honestly,
I like her a lot.
Once we graduate,
we'll likely get married.
Have you even asked Ranee
if she wants to marry you?
She'd never go against Aunt Pissamai.
As for you,
I think you should give up
before it hurts more.
You should take your own advice.
Because Ranee and I love each other.
Wait.
Let's settle this with a competition.
Whoever loses steps aside
and stops pursuing Ranee.
What competition?
Horseback riding.
I've only just started.
Five laps.
I'll give you a two-lap head start.
First to finish five laps wins.
Be brave. Let's settle it.
Was the baby saved?
No.
It was a very early miscarriage.
I don't know what she ate…
or maybe she lifted something too heavy.
What were her symptoms before that?
Wait a second, Auntie.
Madam.
What did you eat
to end up with such bad food poisoning?
I'm not sure.
Don't blame it on the tonic I gave you.
I don't, ma'am. I didn't drink it.
Why not?
I didn't like the smell.
But I appreciated your kindness,
and I was afraid you'd be upset.
It was expensive. I didn't want to throw
it away. So, I gave it to Ms. Hongyok.
She liked it a lot.
So I kept giving it to her.
Why the hell would you do that?
Busybody!
We need to make a deal.
How are you feeling?
You had a high fever just now.
My head feels dizzy, dear.
Then rest some more.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll be right here.
Did you eat anything unusual lately?
What caused the bleeding?
Not really. I've been careful.
But there was…
the tonic that Chanraem brought.
What tonic?
I don't know.
Chanraem said
Madam gave it to her to give to me.
Chen?
I hope she'll be fine.
She can have another child.
Madam!
If you hate me, take it out on me!
Why did you have to hurt
my wife and child?
Hey? What are you screaming about
in my house?
You came just in time,
to hear how cruel your mother is.
Watch your mouth.
You told Chanraem to give a tonic to Hong.
That's why she miscarried!
Is that true, Mei?
I didn't tell her to do that!
Why would Hongyok lie to me?
It was Chanraem
who meddled
and gave it to your wife on her own.
What kind of tonic?
A prenatal tonic!
Everyone takes it. I meant well.
I did a good deed,
and now it's being twisted.
Did Chanraem even take it herself, Mom?
Chan is here.
Chan, did you take the tonic from my mom?
Yes.
I can vouch for her. She drank
every drop in the pot every day.
If you drank it all, how did you have
any left to give to my wife?
I split it in half.
I wanted to please Ms. Hong
since we're both expecting.
If my tonic was poisonous
like you suspect,
Chan wouldn't be standing here right now.
Then how do I know
you all aren't in on it?
So you're determined to accuse me?
Chen.
I understand you're hurt
and you want answers,
but I can promise you
Mei would never be so heartless
as to kill an unborn child.
Then I'll take your word for it, Dad.
May I go now?
What are you standing around for?
Yes, ma'am.
He stormed into my house
and yelled at me like that.
If you weren't around,
would he even respect me?
I'll go take a shower, then.
Wee.
Three workers were absent today.
Any problems?
No problems, Dad. Everything's fine.
We need to make a deal.
If anyone asks
whether you drank the tonic I gave you,
you say yes
and that you shared some with Hongyok.
But I didn't take it.
You will say you did!
Okay, I drank it!
Say what I told you
if you still want to live in this house.
Could the one Madam meant
to poison for a miscarriage
have been me?
Hong?
-Nurse.
-Yes?
Where's the patient in Room 16?
She's in the operating room.
Why is she in the operating room?
Ms. Hongyok's condition worsened. She had
abdominal pain and continued bleeding.
Her parents were here
and gave consent for emergency surgery.
What kind of surgery?
A hysterectomy.
I know very well what I did
was wicked…
But I had to do it
for my son's future.
What happened to Hongyok
wasn't my intention. Even so,
I was the cause of it.
I can't deny it.
I accept all karma that comes from this.
Let it fall upon me alone.
Please don't let it
harm my family.
Madam.
I have something to discuss with you.
I heard about Hongyok.
I'm truly sorry.
She must've had
a bad reaction to the tonic.
I want to make it clear again.
I didn't know
Chanraem had given it to your wife.
Whether you believe me or not
is up to you,
but I've told you the truth.
I suppose you can rest easy now
that I can't have a child
to compete with yours.
You were never a match for my son anyway.
Where's Rawee?
I'd like to know that too.
What do you mean?
I'm tired of lying for him.
He skips work every day.
Where does he go?
To see his lover.
Rawee doesn't have a lover.
Of course he does.
He talks to me about her every day.
He's completely smitten.
Who is she?
Madam Pissamai's niece.
If I remember correctly, her name's Ranee.
And today's her birthday.
He went to the stables early this morning.
I won't believe your slander
until I see it with my own eyes.
If you don't believe me,
-then go see for yourself at the stables.
-I will!
Don't you dare
tell Rawee that I know about this.
It's none of my business.
You took my child.
Now I'll make sure
your child causes you endless pain.
Yes.
-Young Miss!
-Hang on. Hey!
Quiet down already.
All right, let's continue.
You're coming, right, Kaew?
Yes, Anong wants to see you.
Yes. See you later.
What is it?
You have to go to the stables now!
Why?
Mr. Rawee challenged
Mr. Opas to a horse race!
Huh?
Yes.
He just started learning.
He's going to get himself hurt.
Hurry. They're about to start.
Let's go.
Yes. It's all right.
PISSAMAI FARM
Has it started?
Why is Rawee riding alone?
Mr. Opas is giving him
a two-lap head start.
How many laps are they racing, Tub?
Five laps.
Why are they even racing, Tub?
Tell me now.
Tub?
They made a deal.
Whoever loses has to back off
and stop courting you.
Lap two. Mr. Opas, get ready!
Do you think he can win?
It's like a turtle racing a rabbit.
But in the end, didn't the turtle win?
Four laps each!
It's a tie now!
Thanks, buddy. You were amazing.
Did you give me a sick horse?
You picked that horse yourself.
It's the one you've been riding every day.
Don't blame the horse
if you can't ride it properly.
A real sportsperson knows
how to win and lose
with dignity.
Miss Ranee also saw the whole thing.
I won. Don't forget our deal.
Fine.
Well done.
Thank you, Tub.
You have no rivals now, Mr. Rawee.
Where's Ranee?
Huh? Where did she go?
She was just here cheering for you.
Then please take care of this.
Yes.
You're amazing, Tub. You taught
a beginner to beat someone like that.
That horse didn't eat yesterday
and trained all day.
How could that horse run five laps?
Just don't tell Mr. Rawee.
Handsome and cunning…
totally perfect.
Did you see me
win the horse race against Opas?
I did. But I wasn't pleased.
What? Why not?
Why would you challenge him
to a deal like that?
Because I didn't want him
chasing after you.
And what if you had lost?
Even if I had lost,
I wouldn't have honored that deal.
I mean… I'm already in love.
How could I give up
on you just like that?
You're such a sly one.
Yeah.
Winning the race
was your first birthday present…
even though he gave me
a two-lap head start.
You've just started riding,
but what you did was impressive.
So, doesn't that deserve a reward?
I worked so hard, you know?
I had to sneak out to practice
behind Dad and Mom's backs.
My whole body aches,
and then I still had to…
What excuse should I use for sneaking out?
Who is it?
It's me.
Mom?
Yes, Mom?
I'm going to the hotel banquet.
Are you coming with me?
I'll pass.
I don't really feel like dressing up.
Suit yourself.
I'm off now. Your dad's waiting.
Okay, Mom.
Hello, Madam.
Thank you for coming, dear.
It's Ranee's birthday.
Of course I had to come.
This is Wallop, my youngest nephew.
-Hello.
-Oh, hello.
He's quite handsome.
Take your aunt to have
some refreshments over there.
Please go ahead.
Toey, hello!
-Hello.
-Alright.
Is this a birthday party
or a matchmaking fair?
There are so many boys.
What's gotten into you today?
You've been moody since this afternoon.
Hello.
What are you doing here?
Got lost on the way back from the market?
I came to find my son.
This isn't an airport.
Aren't your sons supposed to be overseas?
One of them is still here. Rawee.
I guess your dear niece fooled you.
Those two are secretly seeing each other.
Impossible.
I saw your niece kiss my son on the cheek
at the stable earlier today.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Where is my son?
I don't know.
I do.
Opas?
What do you know? Tell me.
Rawee and Ranee
really are together, Auntie.
I saw a little birthday setup
at the stable.
I think Rawee arranged it for Ranee.
Rawee!
Mom?
You want to ruin your future
over a woman just like your brother?
Watch your mouth!
Don't you dare compare
my niece to a prostitute!
If anyone's future is getting ruined,
it's my niece's,
being seduced by your lying son.
You think your niece is so pure?
All sweet and proper on the outside,
but behind your back,
she's flirting with men.
She even kissed my son in broad daylight.
Don't even try to deny it.
If I don't stop this,
your niece will end up pregnant
and get expelled from school in no time.
You shameless boy-chaser.
You foul-mouthed hag!
Apologize to my niece now!
-Apologize now!
-Auntie, no!
-Don't stop me!
-Auntie.
-Let's go back, Auntie.
-Mei!
Let go of me!
Ranee,
tell me she's lying.
You didn't do what she said, right?
Tell me.
Say something!
I was the one who started it.
Shut up!
Don't take the blame for her.
If she weren't a shameless flirt,
would she have kissed you?
Vile! Disgusting!
Tub! Drag that woman out
before I kill someone!
Stop!
Don't touch me.
I've spent more than enough time
in this disgusting stable!
I'll send Rawee abroad immediately.
Remember,
you two won't ever see each other again.
Go!
Once she finishes high school,
I'll marry Ranee off to Opas
and end this once and for all!
Auntie.
You'd better do what you say.
I will.
Go! Don't you dare
long for her again. Go now!
Ranee!
If you'd just done what you promised me,
none of this would've happened.
As for you two,
I'll deal with you tomorrow.
Come with me.
I love Rawee. I don't think
I can stop loving him, Auntie.
No matter how deep your love is,
you'll never end up together.
You have to help me. Madam
tried to poison me to force a miscarriage,
but it didn't work.
I don't think she's going to stop there.
She's nearly due. I'm scared
she'll die with the baby still inside her.
Or maybe fate
is sparing Rak from misfortune.
Welcome home, Son.
Thank you, Mom.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon