I have three sons. Let's see
if any of them can do better than someone
without an education like you.
He and I are both Dad's sons. So why does
he always get more than me?
Can you promise me,
no matter what happens,
you'll marry only me?
Get out!
-Have you heard about it?
-What is it?
If you want my help,
we need to make a deal.
What do you want? Say it.
MANAGER ROOM
Thank you very much
for helping resolve
the situation at the hotel.
Don't worry, Dad. I'm not here
to steal my brother's position.
I'll just step in
and stabilize everything.
After that, it's up to you.
When you move in,
just turn a deaf ear.
Don't mind anything Mei says.
I accepted that the moment
I agreed to help you.
I knew Madam
would think I orchestrated all of this.
But I don't care.
I just want to bring Hong
to live under the same roof as you.
I've been alone for so long.
I'm really lonely, Dad.
I want a family.
Even if we argue every day,
it's still better
than hearing nothing but my own breathing.
Slow down or you'll choke.
Yes, Mom.
Madam! She's here!
Bring my things in.
Just stack them here first.
What are you doing?
I'm moving in.
So of course, I need to bring my things.
Today?
Yes. You gave your word, didn't you?
Or are you going back on it?
You two can leave now.
So, where's our room?
-Ngor.
-Yes, ma'am.
Take her to see the room. Since this is
all so sudden, she can clean it herself.
Yes, ma'am. Follow me.
You two, take my things up.
My brothers-in-law are all here.
What are you having? I've been
moving stuff all day. I'm starving.
Mind if I join?
Hey! Let's toast!
-Yeah!
-It's so refreshing.
-Yes.
-It's great.
-It is.
Look who's here! Our new hotel manager!
Hey.
All right. Thanks, everyone.
Eat and drink all you want tonight.
It's on me.
Wow.
-Please have a seat.
-Get him a glass now.
Have a seat, Manager.
-Cheers.
Yeah!
We're officially husband and wife now.
How about a honeymoon tonight?
Ouch!
So you rushed the Christian wedding
because you had wicked intentions, right?
I was just asking!
We can't honeymoon just yet.
I won't feel right
until both our families accept us.
Mom definitely won't acknowledge
the ceremony.
She'll say it's a different religion.
If they really refuse to let us marry,
will you still do what we agreed on?
You're not afraid of the hardship?
If I have you, I'm not afraid of anything.
-What was that?
-Sounds like a chair fell.
Could it be a burglar?
Wait for me.
I thought it was a burglar.
Turns out it's just some street drunk.
Who are you calling that?
Who else? Just look at yourself.
You're a mess.
The new manager of Charoenrung Hotel?
What a disgrace.
Are you talking about me or your son?
Chen! If you're drunk,
go back to your room and sleep it off.
Where? Where's my room?
I don't see any room.
Go throw up outside! Filthy!
Dear.
Why did you get this drunk?
Good timing. Take him back to your room.
Let's go. I'll take you to bed.
I just had a little to drink.
I'm not drunk.
If you want to stay in this house,
you'll follow the rules.
But if you're going to get drunk
and cause a scene,
go stay somewhere else.
And if you can't quit drinking,
then take your wife and leave.
He's not usually like this, ma'am.
Today was just a special occasion.
I don't care.
If you want to stay here,
you follow my rules.
And don't think you can turn
people against me again.
All the staff here,
I hand-picked every one of them.
I won't make the same mistake
I did with the hotel staff.
Hong, take Chen to bed.
Yes, Dad.
Let's go.
Enjoy yourselves while you can.
Once Rawee graduates and returns,
I'll appoint him
as the new hotel manager immediately.
You're the one who told your father
you didn't want the position.
Then give it up
because I'm certain Rawee
will manage the hotel
far better than you ever could.
I'll go get you some tea.
No need. I'm not drunk.
I just wanted to provoke Madam.
I thought so.
You've never gotten that drunk before.
I didn't want to act timid
in front of her from day one.
Being drunk makes it easier. No matter
how harshly I speak, Dad will forgive me.
That woman really hates you.
Two of her sons failed,
yet she still insists
on pushing the third for the position.
Let's hope he's like his brothers,
book-smart but useless at real work.
I hope so too.
Just watch.
I'm going to rise above all her children.
And you, build your reputation
as the first daughter-in-law.
Dominate all the others
and bring them under your command.
We will seize
all the power in this family…
and make Madam Mei choke
on her own rage until it kills her.
CHAROENRUNG HOTEL
-Good afternoon, sir.
-Hello, Mr. Chen.
Welcome back to Charoenrung Hotel.
I've reserved the entire floor for you.
Thank you. You know exactly what I want.
My pleasure, sir.
Sir, may we take a few photos?
Rawee, come home soon.
I can't stand watching that Chen
bask in glory any longer.
Your father and I built
this hotel with our own hands.
But now everyone thinks it belongs to him.
What did your aunt say?
She told me to come back immediately.
She said I can't keep studying.
Same with my mom.
She wants me back to work at the hotel.
So, what do we do now?
Marriage?
What is it, Madam?
Ranee won't return
unless I allow her to marry Rawee.
What did Rawee say?
He won't come back
unless we let him marry Ranee.
That girl again.
But they really love each other, Mom.
They've been dating for five or six years.
No! I said no!
If I let Ranee marry into that family,
it's like throwing her to the wolves.
I will never allow it.
No matter what, I'll never let
our family be tied to that family.
Fine. I'll stop sending him money.
Let's see how long he lasts.
Mr. Heng, how are you?
-I'm good.
-Great.
Just place the file there.
-Please have a seat.
-Thank you.
So, how's the marketing plan coming along?
HONGYOK GOLD SHOP
Please come in.
-Hello.
Thank you for visiting my shop again.
I promised I'd come, didn't I?
Didn't your husband come too?
He's still in a meeting with your husband.
Well, today I want
a matching gold necklace and bracelet set.
We've got plenty to choose from.
Let's look at bracelets first.
All right.
Can I ask you a favor?
Of course.
I saw someone
selling lod chong on the way here.
It looked delicious.
Could you go buy some for me?
Oh…
Please buy two, Korn.
I've been craving that too.
That shop's been open for ages.
-Let's look at the bracelets.
-Perfect.
This one just came in.
Right. I haven't seen this one before.
I can't take it anymore.
That man keeps stepping on our children,
keeping them beneath him.
He takes all the credit
and acts like he owns the hotel.
That's how Chen trains his people.
Trains? More like crushing them.
He's just doing what I taught him,
learning everything hands-on
so he truly understands the work.
I don't believe that.
He has ulterior motives.
I must stop him before the hotel
can't survive without him.
Then who would manage the hotel?
It'd have to be me again.
Rawee, of course.
I'm sure
he can do it and better than him too.
But what about his condition?
If he can't marry Ranee,
he won't come back.
Can you really accept that?
She's disappeared, as if she's died.
I wonder if my niece ever thinks of me.
I think you might have
to give in to her, Madam.
It's not that easy.
Here you go.
You want a chew? It helps relieve stress.
You go ahead.
The mail's here, ma'am.
Is there a letter from Ranee?
No, ma'am.
Then why didn't you say so right away?
Why let me get my hopes up like that?
I was just about to say it,
but you spoke first.
Hey?
Who knows how she's doing right now?
What do you think? Do you like it?
I do.
This is our new home.
So? Do you like it?
Yes.
Yes, but could you lower the rent a bit?
This is already a great deal.
It's close to the main road
and not far from Charoenrung Hotel.
You're from Bangkok.
You're probably not familiar with it.
That hotel
is the most famous in the province.
Then we'll take it, Auntie.
All right, there's a three-month deposit
required in advance.
But since you're newlyweds
just starting out, I'll give you
a discount. Just a two-month deposit.
-Thank you.
I've got a big vegetable garden out back.
When you move in, help me take care of it.
You can take the extra veggies
to eat or sell. I'll give them to you.
Thank you very much.
Feel free to look around.
-Yes, Auntie.
-Yes, thank you.
I'm starting to lose patience with Chen.
Same here.
They're not training us.
They just want to grind us down.
I'm basically his assistant now,
carrying files and setting up meetings.
I haven't learned a thing.
I had it worse. I had to run around
pampering the wives of clients.
Today, I had to buy lod chong for them.
I'd never bought anything
from the street in my life.
Our family's richer than theirs.
How can they boss me around like that?
I'm the hotel owner's son
and the deputy manager.
And he never introduces me to anyone.
Whenever we meet senior guests,
he hogs the spotlight and sends me away.
Hong's no better.
She never says a word in my defense
and keeps using me over and over.
NOW HIRING: MULTIPLE POSITIONS
INQUIRE INSIDE
Hello! A table for how many?
I'm here to apply for a job.
Please wait a moment.
He's not even our real brother.
He should have treated us well.
That's right. If it weren't for Dad,
I wouldn't have stayed this long.
Hong's getting worse by the day.
I'm quitting.
And if you quit, what are you going to do?
I'm not going to work at the rice mill.
I hate it.
Rak.
Who did you see?
It's nothing. I thought I saw someone.
I think it's time Chen
returned to managing the rice mill.
I agree.
Eat a lot, okay?
You too.
I'm not a dog.
-Aren't you a dog?
-No. Just eat.
Who are you?
Miss!
I missed you so much.
I missed you so most too, Cha-aim.
I thought I'd never see you again
in this lifetime.
Of course, you would.
Why would you think that?
You gave Madam your ultimatum, didn't you?
That you wouldn't come back
unless she allowed you to marry Mr. Rawee.
So she really won't give in?
Not exactly.
Her tone's getting softer every day.
Madam misses you so much.
She's lost a lot of weight.
Don't tell her I'm back just yet, okay?
I won't.
I want you and Mr. Rawee
to get married too.
Rawee and I are lying low,
waiting for the right time
until both our mothers finally give in.
You can hide, but please
let me see you once in a while, all right?
I missed you so, so much.
Smells amazing.
Don't tell me you made all this?
Cha-aim snuck it out
of the kitchen back home.
You met Cha-aim?
Yes. I snuck over to the stable.
I just wanted
to catch a glimpse of Auntie.
But I bumped into Cha-aim instead.
Don't worry. She won't say anything.
Actually, Rak and Korn
almost saw me today too.
I'm debating
whether I should just tell them.
-And did you tell them?
-I left before anyone could see me.
But it's a shame. That restaurant was
hiring for so many positions. I missed it.
With your hotel degree from the US,
do you think they'd hire you?
I was only going to show them
my high school diploma.
They'll know you from your last name.
Your family's famous in this province.
It's worth trying.
Maybe they'll take me as a temp worker.
You're doing so much for me.
I'll find a way to earn more too.
Let's eat first, okay?
Here you go.
If my mom and your aunt
still won't give in after all this…
once our two-month lease is up,
we might have to move
to Bangkok to find work.
All right.
You're really okay with that?
You won't regret this?
I won't. But I am a little hurt.
Hurt? Why?
You keep asking
if I'm scared, if I'm sure,
if I'll regret this over and over.
It's like you don't believe I love you.
I'm sorry.
Sorry isn't enough.
You need to be punished.
What punishment?
You'll wash the dishes,
fold the laundry, and iron the clothes.
And you'll mop the floor too.
I already swept.
You're ruthless.
I've got to stay sharp to keep up
with my cunning husband.
If you're going to work me this hard,
then when I get sore,
you'll have to give me a massage.
Come on.
-Thanks.
-All right.
I want to open a movie theater.
I'm quitting my job to help Dad.
I'll quit and help Mom
take care of the market and collect rent.
No. You have to marry Duangporn first.
The position of deputy hotel manager
sounds a lot more respectable.
That way, Duangporn's family
won't look down on you.
Then I'll hold out
and wait until after the wedding.
It's because of your son
from your old life.
He's the reason our kids
have to feel this uncomfortable.
Who wanted it to be this way?
It's our fault, Mom,
for doing things without consulting Dad.
Please don't blame him.
Always defending your father.
Then let's settle on this plan.
Settle on what?
Good timing.
I think the two of you
are getting too full of yourselves.
Did my little brothers come crying to you?
Are you playing dumb,
or are you just that clueless?
Just because your father
favors you doesn't mean
you can bully my kids however you want.
Madam, you've misunderstood us.
So when you let that woman
make me go buy lod chong for you,
that wasn't bullying?
What did that mean, then?
Seriously?
Ronnakorn Trongpanich
is the rightful heir to the hotel,
not some errand boy.
Have you two ever introduced us
as deputy hotel managers?
You deliberately keep me under you.
And to think we three siblings
let you live here.
If we hadn't accepted you,
you would've been shipped back
to your hometown a long time ago.
So what now?
Are you going to kick me out?
Calm down, dear. They just misunderstood.
Let's talk when we're all calmer.
I agree with Hong.
Seeing my children fight like this…
is heartbreaking.
Then who started it, Dad?
All right. Let's not dwell on this.
We've had a long day.
Get some rest. Sleep it off.
We'll talk again in the morning.
Let's go.
Settle everything
while there's still time.
The real manager of Charoenrung Hotel
is about to take charge.
Dear, wait for me.
So does that mean you're letting
Rawee and Ranee get married?
Don't start with me right now.
Worry about your own wedding first.
Yes, Mom.
Where have you lovebirds been?
We went to pick vegetables.
The landlord gave them to us.
We have plenty, Cha-aim.
I'm thinking of selling some.
So much trouble for the sake of love.
It's not trouble at all.
As long as it's honest work, I don't mind.
If Madam saw you two like this,
she'd definitely give in
and let you marry.
I hope she gives in soon.
We're nearly out of savings.
Your aunt's not the problem.
It's my mom I'm worried about.
Speaking of Madam Mei,
there's big news.
Mr. Rak is getting married!
Oh? Who's he marrying, Cha-aim?
Miss Duangporn,
the textile factory owner's daughter.
Auntie once brought me
to a party at their house. She's pretty.
Do you know when the wedding is?
Wishing you both
a long life together filled with love.
Thank you.
May you be wealthy and prosperous,
with abundance to spare.
Thank you.
This way, please.
-Hello.
-This way, please.
I wish you and sister-in-law
lots of happiness,
a love that lasts forever, and a baby soon
so I can help take care of them.
Just one envelope, Mom?
Not enough? I'll add another one then.
Here.
Thank you, Dad.
May you both be happy together.
If things get hard, forgive each other.
When it's my wedding
and you're not as emotional,
I'll be upset with you, Ngor.
Of course, I'll be emotional.
I love all my young masters equally.
Too bad Rawee isn't here
to share this joy.
Indeed.
Thank you.
I've waited long enough.
Mr. Rak! My nephew's still here!
Close the door.
No one left now.
Mr. Rak, that tickles.
You're still up?
I was waiting for you.
Your shirt button came off.
I fixed it for you.
And what are you reading?
Old lecture notes.
I'm reviewing them so I don't forget.
So diligent.
So did you catch the wedding car in time?
Of course.
How was it?
Rak looked so sharp
I almost didn't recognize him.
And he was smiling the whole time.
He must be really happy.
I went to the market earlier
and overheard vendors say there's
a big banquet at the hotel tomorrow night.
Wow.
Mom really went all out.
Well, he is her favorite son.
No surprise she's going all out.
And that's not all.
Tomorrow, there's going to be
a parade around town.
What kind of parade?
Thank you.
Is this part of the Chinese ceremony?
I wouldn't know. I've never seen
anything like it in my life.
It's all for showing off.
They're just trying to flaunt their wealth
like they're rich beyond measure.
These nouveau riche types.
Rak looks very handsome.
Let's not have a wedding like this, okay?
I'd be so embarrassed.
I'm not Mom's favorite.
She wouldn't go this far for me.
Was that Ranee?
What? Who?
That was Ranee.
-Where?
-Oh?
Maybe I was seeing things.
They're acting like celebrities.
So annoying.
I bet Madam's just worried her son
doesn't have as many connections as I do.
I still haven't forgiven Duangporn.
She betrayed me.
You have to get back at her for me.
Chan!
You're going to fall.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Did they hire you?
-Of course!
They're short-staffed.
You're really something. You found
a way into your brother's wedding party.
It's an important moment in Rak's life.
I just wanted to be part of it,
even in a small way.
Just be careful. Don't get caught.
Don't worry. This vendor
is off the regular menu.
I won't be serving
the VIP tables or anything.
Anyway, I have to go to the restaurant.
You might have to head home alone.
-Okay.
-I'm off.
Wait, drink it first.
I ordered it for you.
I'm off then.
Cha-aim?
Auntie.
How could you do this to me?
Ranee!
-Ranee!
-Miss!
Where are you running off to now?
Dear.
You don't love me anymore, do you?
You're the only family I've ever had.
How could I not love you?
But you chose Rawee.
You're the one who made me choose.
Why can't I have both you and Rawee?
Five or six years
isn't enough to prove our love?
You hate Madam Mei.
What does that have to do with us?
I've just sent you a letter.
I've given up everything.
You can do whatever you want.
I'm ready to support you in anything.
Please promise you'll visit me
once in a while. Please.
Thank you.
Don't leave me again, my dear.
Tub.
That man looked so familiar.
I feel like I've seen him before.
Those Chinese boys look the same.
Was he more handsome than me?
You're the most handsome.
The three of them look the same.
They all have the same name… Young Master?
I think you're just mixing it up
with your dream.
You told me
about that dream once, remember?
-Did I?
-Yes.
Don't overthink it,
or you'll stress yourself out.
Let's go feed the horses.
Rassamee must be starving.
Right! I'm going now.
Let's go.
Rassamee!
If I give in that easily, I'll lose face.
It's their side
that needs to come and kneel, begging me
to take you as their daughter-in-law.
Will they agree to that?
Even if they don't want to,
they'll have to.
It's better than losing the hotel
to the ex-wife's child.
You mean Chen?
Yes. That boy's incredibly capable.
Everything he touches turns to gold.
When he ran the rice mill,
it kept expanding.
Now that he's managing the hotel,
it's booming.
Wealthy clients are booking banquet halls
even a year in advance.
Unlike Mei's other two kids. Useless.
No wonder Madam Mei
called Rawee back to work.
He's her last hope,
the only one she can use
to push Chen out of the picture.
That's why they'll definitely come begging
for you to be their daughter-in-law.
And what will you ask from them?
We absolutely cannot mess up
tonight's banquet.
Yes, sir.
Call in the staff from every department
involved in the banquet to my office now.
Yes, sir.
Why are you all staring at me like that?
You're making me nervous.
I haven't seen you eat food I made
in years.
Seeing you here today
for the first time again,
it's just exciting.
She's touched.
We won't stare anymore.
All right.
-Please go ahead and eat.
-All right.
Why didn't you invite
Mr. Rawee to join us?
He's not free today, Grandma.
Are you done yet? The guests are arriving.
Yes.
-Thank you.
Please, come on in.
Congratulations.
Good evening.
-Good evening.
-Good evening, sir.
-Please come inside.
By the way, where's Mr. Chen?
I haven't seen him.
He's inside organizing everything. This is
big. He didn't want anything to go wrong.
I see. Congratulations.
Please, come in.
Right this way.
Today is my son's wedding banquet.
It's a family affair.
I believe you understand what I said.
You don't want me attending?
That's right. It's none of your business.
Stay out of sight.
Don't even think of stealing
the spotlight from my son.
You've already taken too much.
If you can't bear to see Rak shine,
then just go home.
Your son's wedding
will be the talk of the town.
There has been an explosion
at the Charoenrung Hotel.
Rawee!
The one who stands to lose power
if you take over the hotel.
That's your prime suspect.
Submit your resignation today.
Don't stall any longer.
Chan, you remember that woman, right?
She hurt you before, right?
Don't pick some random girl.
I've already picked someone for you.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon