=Reply High School=
(An incident that occurred
at Busan WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL.)
(Student CHOI DAEWON who attended school
with all of you has gone missing.)
(All students should also take charge)
(of some areas for searching.)
SADAHARU: It's okay.
SADAHARU: I'm here!
SONGHA: So we need to go to the first floor now.
(Students are calm before searching)
SONGHA: We should look for CHOI DAEWON.
- JAEWON: Why are you scared over this?
- WOOLIN: Seriously!
WOOLIN: Hey, the door is open here. Be careful.
JAEWON: I told you he wasn't in the Principal's Office.
(Once it starts, everyone's busy running away)
TRAINEE: Ah!
(Shrieks erupting from every side)
TRAINEE: DAEWON, are you here?
TRAINEE: Wow! What!
TRAINEE: Ah!
TRAINEE: Wow, this is... Ah!
(Ghosts keep popping out even while escaping)
(A desperate struggle to escape)
(Someone is broken down)
(Only the STAFF is satisfied
with the completion of the search)
TRAINEE: Oh, I'm scared!
HANBI: Wow, I thought there was a ghost behind me.
(Someone scarier than the ghost is coming from behind)
(Next search team)
(HANBI and JUSTIN)
HYUNJUN: Have a good trip.
(Now sending them off quite coolly)
JUSTIN: We need to hold hands.
(As soon as they exit the classroom, they look for hands)
- HANBI: Need to hold hands? - JUSTIN: Hold hands.
JUSTIN: Hold on.
(Suddenly starting to warm up under the moonlight)
HANBI: Let's do it!
JUSTIN: Ten.
(Simulation?) - JUSTIN: One time.
- HANBI: One time. Like this.
(Then hurriedly find hands to hold)
HANBI: As long as it's not bugs, I'm not scared.
SADAHARU: I can't do it.
(A terrified voice heard from somewhere)
SADAHARU: I can't do it!
HANBI: Oh, hold on. I'm saying I really can't do it.
(JUSTIN, HANBI)
HANBI: Hey, is this right?
(No bugs will come out)
TRAINEE: Hey, look at that. Ah...
(Finally came down all the stairs)
JUSTIN: Wait a minute.
JUSTIN: Just for this moment,
JUSTIN: you might forget that I'm your hyung.
(Rudeness ahead)
HANBI: Seriously, you can't leave me behind.
(More worried about slippers than etiquette)
HANBI: I'm in slippers, so I can't run away.
(Reached the lounge) - JUSTIN:
We're going in there? - HANBI: Oh, wait.
(Even the lounge they always enter is scary)
JUSTIN: Go in.
HANBI: Oh, there's nothing.
HANBI: Well!
HANBI: Relax.
HANBI: I'm a bit nervous.
HANBI: It's still the beginning. Just the beginning.
Hey, don't freak out. Don't freak out.
(HANBI consoles himself and sits down)
HANBI: WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL Night Rules.
HANBI: Please take note of the following precautions.
(Let me inform you...)
(In 1992,)
(JANG MINYEONG, who graduated
from WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL,)
(JANG MINYEONG)
(is still attending this school.)
(Searching for JANG MINYEONG who hasn't left)
(The staff are about to)
(Starting the school search)
(search every corner of the school.)
(All students should also take charge)
(of some areas for searching.)
HANBI: This person is JANG MINYEONG, I guess?
JUSTIN: Yeah.
HANBI: 1992 is even before we were born.
JUSTIN: Exactly.
(Long before they were born) (AI generated image)
TRAINEE: Let me check.
(JANG MINYEONG roaming WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL)
TRAINEE: It's been more than 20 years.
- TRAINEE: 30 years.
- TRAINEE: It's been more than 30 years.
(Night Rules) HANBI: If you see
JANG MINYEONG's photo or name,
HANBI: or if you see any shape,
HANBI: you must never talk to,
touch, or make eye contact...
HANBI: But I already touched them. What do I do now?
(Shouldn't touch anything recklessly)
HANBI: It should be fine.
JUSTIN: This is bad.
HANBI: If you see or collect JANG MINYEONG's items
in the Principal's Office,
HANBI: please make sure to put them in the cabinet.
HANBI: It's dangerous to leave items
outside of the cabinet, or to possess them.
HANBI: If you see JANG MINYEONG,
for safety, please evacuate to the restroom.
(This means you might encounter JANG MINYEONG)
HANBI: Oh, hold on. Wait!
HANBI: I absolutely need to run away from this.
(JANG MINYEONG)
HANBI: If you hear any sound in the restroom,
cover your partner ears and leave immediately.
HANBI: If you're alone, cover your ears with something.
HANBI: Let's stick together!
HANBI: Absolutely,
let's cover each other's ears like this.
JUSTIN: Okay.
(If you meet student JANG MINYEONG,)
(please be cautious.)
DANIEL: Oh! The content's changed!
(MINYEONG who was here is gone)
WOOLIN: Hey, MINYEONG disappeared earlier.
JAEWON: You are right. Oh? Where did MINYEONG go?
(They're on their way to find MINYEONG)
HANBI: You said left, right?
JUSTIN: I'll be watching from back there.
- HANBI: If left, then here, right?
- JUSTIN: I'm looking behind us.
(Arrived at the 1st floor while stubbornly
saying whatever they want)
JUSTIN: Can you see?
HANBI: You look this way. I'll look that way.
JUSTIN: In one go.
HANBI: In one go. Quickly glance over.
HANBI: Let's pass. One, two, three.
(Starting from the left)
HANBI: One, two, three.
(This time on the right)
(MINYEONG's friend runs away after seeing people)
JUSTIN: Hey, wait a minute.
(The older one immediately runs off
leaving the younger one behind)
JUSTIN: Hey, wait a minute. Hey!
(As warned, the younger one blurts informal speech)
JUSTIN: Hey! Wait!
HANBI: Haha!
(The soul left behind on the 1st floor)
JUSTIN: I can't get my voice out. Ah!
DANIEL: Ah, JUSTIN doesn't scream when surprised.
(How JUSTIN gets surprised)
DANIEL: He gets surprised like this.
STAFF: HANBI and JUSTIN are also really scared?
DANIEL: JUSTIN is very scared.
- SONGHA: I'm not sure about HANBI.
- DANIEL: HANBI seems similar to us. Normally.
SONGHA: Isn't it that they're very scared
if they're similar to us?
(Quick to grasp the subject)
SONGHA: Seriously.
(The two cowards SONGHA
and DANIEL mentioned keep searching)
HANBI: Hey, for real!
(MINYEONG's search continues
in a somewhat funny manner)
HANBI: Let's hold with the opposite hand.
HANBI: Here.
(Just grabs both hands)
JUSTIN: Wait a minute.
JUSTIN: Which room are we?
- JUSTIN: Which room is this?
- HANBI: Principal's Office.
(Making WOOJEONG HIGH's eldest whine)
- HANBI: Wait. Why is there a wall there? - JUSTIN: Wait.
(Something covered with a white cloth)
HANBI: Stand over there.
JUSTIN: Why! Those things...
JUSTIN: Why did they make it like this here?
The Principal's Office?
- JUSTIN: No, this is a person.
- HANBI: Calm down.
HANBI: Okay, let's think about what we need to do now.
HANBI: We're now...
- HANBI: Well... JANG MINYEONG's items...
- JUSTIN: From here.
HANBI: Ha...
(Must be put inside the cabinet)
HANBI: It needs to go inside the cabinet.
JUSTIN: Cabinet?
HANBI: Let's go in first.
(Gather all courage and proceed to the door)
JUSTIN: Shall we go in?
HANBI: If you scare me, I'll be mad.
Got it? I've warned you!
(As scared as they are, they talk a lot) - JUSTIN:
Can't do this! - HANBI: Really can't do this.
(Still haven't gone in) - HANBI:
Go in. - JUSTIN: I'm going in.
HANBI: I'm really going in.
(Nothing much here)
HANBI: Oh!
JUSTIN: Hyung!
HANBI: Eh!
HANBI: Don't provoke me. Please.
JUSTIN: If you do it like that...
Then if you do it like that...
(Ring-ring)
HANBI: Why a call now?
(The mysterious phone suddenly starts ringing)
HANBI: Why is there a phone call causing chaos?
HANBI: Hey, check it quickly.
(JANG MINYEONG)
HANBI: Hey, it's JANG MINYEONG!
JUSTIN: MAX CHANGMIN?
HANBI: Not MAX CHANGMIN, but JANG MINYEONG.
(Wanting to see the PE teacher)
MAX CHANGMIN: Wow!
(After MAX CHANGMIN visits briefly)
JUSTIN: Still...
HANBI: Wait. But first, let's think about
what we need to do.
JUSTIN: They're humans.
- HANBI: In the P-Principal's Office, there's...
- JUSTIN: It's a person.
(No interest in the rules) HANBI: If you see
or find JANG MINYEONG's items,
HANBI: must put them in the cabinet.
(JANG MINYEONG's items are boldly placed on the desk)
HANBI: We need to put them in the cabinet.
HANBI: We need to put this there.
(Other people's business) - HANBI:
We need to put this in. - JUSTIN: Put it in.
- HANBI: It needs to go in.
- JUSTIN: Where's the cabinet?
(On the way to the tricky cabinet)
HANBI: Oh, wait. There's surely someone here.
- HANBI: I doubt it. I don't trust you guys.
- JUSTIN: Hey!
(Here we go) - JUSTIN: After doing that...
- HANBI: Just do it.
- HANBI: I'm HANBI HONG!
- JUSTIN: Ah!
- HANBI: Ah!
(Camera director) - HANBI:
I'm HANBI HONG! - JUSTIN: Ah!
(Only moved to find HANBI)
- HANBI: Ah! - JUSTIN: Ah!
(Frozen)
JUSTIN: Seriously...
HANBI: Ah.
(Unexpected courage course added) - HANBI:
Don't do that! Seriously! - JUSTIN: Really! Don't do that!
(First, packing MINYEONG's items into the bag)
HANBI: Wait, this... Sorry,
I'm too curious, I'll just take a look.
(Sneaking a look at the senior's student record)
- JUSTIN: Hey, you shouldn't look. - HANBI: Hey!
JUSTIN: Hey, you shouldn't look!
(Let's look together)
JUSTIN: Wait a moment.
HANBI: Wow, a tall sitting height.
(Sitting height: 87cm)
HANBI: Hey, the sitting height is tall.
HANBI: Wow, 9m... 50m sprint in 9 seconds!
- JUSTIN: 9 seconds!
- HANBI: I am...
(To be exact, 14.25 seconds)
JUSTIN: Faster than me, I got 13 seconds.
HANBI: I'm at an advantage.
(Ran with fans in 14 seconds)
JUSTIN: Wow!
- JUSTIN: Ah, but if I really run...
- HANBI: Ah, this...
JUSTIN: Really fast.
- JUSTIN: This one.
- HANBI: Hey!
(Finished reading and started packing the bag again)
HANBI: Okay, got it. I saw it well.
HANBI: Sorry, but...
(Going again)
- HANBI: Please, seriously, stop it!
- JUSTIN: Seriously!
JUSTIN: It's okay, right?
- HANBI: I don't know. I don't know.
- JUSTIN: What about this?
- HANBI: Put it in. Put it all in.
- JUSTIN: Okay. Okay.
HANBI: Hey, I'm going all the way over there.
(Now they really have to go through this path)
JUSTIN: Let's go together.
HANBI: Let's go together.
JUSTIN: We should hold hands.
(Everyone holds hands as if directed)
HANBI: We should hold hands.
SONGHA: Ah, did we go holding hands like that?
(A past self that's unfamiliar in many ways)
DANIEL: I've done unimaginable things.
JUSTIN: You're a human, right?
HANBI: Crack!
(HANBI HONG just kicked them down)
JUSTIN: Is it not?
HANBI: If it were a human, I apologize.
- HANBI: It's a mannequin. Would it really move?
- JUSTIN: Please...
(It's going to move)
HANBI: Hey! Wait!
HANBI: So they are screaming.
They're not just screaming for no reason.
(For some reason, don't want to open the two doors)
- HANBI: Hey, I'm opening this. - JUSTIN: Open it.
- JUSTIN: Hey, momentum.
- HANBI: You! This! You throw it.
TRAINEE: Hey, wait a second!
(Open)
- HANBI: Ah!
- JUSTIN: Ah!
(Empty)
(Unexpected calmness)
(A door closes abruptly while they're off guard)
(Insanity)
(Laughter emerges at the peak of fear)
- JUSTIN: Ah, for real! - HANBI: Ah, seriously!
SONGHA: Now the marbles should come out.
DANIEL: So, along with the marbles...
- DANIEL: Hair.
- NICHOLAS: And the hair.
SONGHA: Was there hair?
DANIEL: There was hair.
(Long hair flew in from the window) - SONGHA:
I didn't see it. - DANIEL: We ran at full speed.
JUSTIN: Is it coming? Or not?
(Arguing over the window) - HANBI: Ah! Wait.
Why is it open? - JUSTIN: Be sure. Make sure.
(Hair that ultimately couldn't fly in)
HANBI: Just go...
JUSTIN: Why did you make the color like this?
JUSTIN: Seriously...
JUSTIN: Why is it blue again?
JUSTIN: Earlier, I...
JUSTIN: Actually, I said I wasn't scared, but I was.
JUSTIN: Ah, seriously, I can't take it.
(Looking back at myself in the dark)
HANBI: I'll protect you.
(The fear of empty spaces)
JUSTIN: Earlier...
(Ring)
JUSTIN: Wait!
(Instinctively evacuating to the staff zone)
(The restroom is supposed to be safe)
HANBI: To the restroom!
HANBI: Ah, wait. Why is this corner like this?
JUSTIN: Why?
- HANBI: Let's go to the restroom.
- JUSTIN: Go slowly.
HANBI: Go directly to the restroom.
- JUSTIN: Slowly. - HANBI: Run.
Let's run to the restroom. How about it?
- JUSTIN: Run to the restroom... Restroom?
- HANBI: They say the restroom is safe.
HANBI: Yeah.
(Still not going in, Having a chat)
JUSTIN: We shouldn't run here.
HANBI: No, we might need to go to the restroom.
I have a bad feeling about this.
HANBI: A hallway in a straight line will have something
HANBI: chasing us for sure.
(Victims)
DANIEL: Yeah, it's in a straight line.
HANBI: For safety, evacuate
to the restroom immediately.
JUSTIN: Why is it like this?
(Missed HANBI)
JUSTIN: Why for safety?
JUSTIN: Hey, wait.
(Leaving the sibling behind and entering
the restroom first) JUSTIN: Hey, wait.
HANBI: Oh, wait. Come in.
JUSTIN: Why red?
HANBI: Ah, why is the light only on here?
(MINYEONG...)
(Leaving HANBI behind and running)
HANBI: Hey, come here.
HANBI: You have to cover ears. Where are you going?
(No presence of mind to cover ears)
HANBI: You need to cover ears.
(If you hear any sound from the restroom,)
HANBI: You need to cover ears!
(immediately cover the other person's ears)
HANBI: You need to cover my ears!
(According to the rules, cover each other's ears)
- HANBI: Go back in. - JUSTIN: Go in.
(Returning to the restroom)
(MINYEONG...)
(It's not our MINYEONG)
- HANBI: Cover ears! - JUSTIN: Cover ears!
(MINYEONG!)
(We also covered our ears)
- JUSTIN: Sorry!
- HANBI: Sorry!
(Just feeling sorry for everything)
- HANBI: I'm sorry! - JUSTIN: I came to help.
- HANBI: J-Just graduate. Please.
- JUSTIN: Really!
(I'll manage)
- HANBI: Ah!
- JUSTIN: Ah!
(Nagged once and got severely punished)
HANBI: Ghost of 1975, I'm sorry for being so loud.
(The senior is sensitive because of many visitors)
JUSTIN: Really!
TRAINEE: Straighten your legs a bit
(Leaving to let the senior ghost of 1975 rest)
TRAINEE: Ah, my...
- HANBI: I think there's something?
- JUSTIN: Hey, wait a minute.
(Feeling it) - HANBI: I think there's something?
(Hi, I'm MINYEONG)
TRAINEE: Hey, it might move.
TRAINEE: Oh, it seems
this guy is about to charge forward.
(Ah)
(Charging is my thing)
(Unlike the HANBI, who hid quickly)
(JUSTIN ran away with full power)
(DAEWON hasn't been able to stop since)
(Gone)
(Polite ghost greeting and leaving)
(DAEWON taking refuge behind the wall)
STAFF: It's over.
(JUSTIN will sleep here)
HANBI: Hey!
HANBI: Where did you go? JUSTIN?
(Barely breathing)
HANBI: How could you leave me behind?
(Too serious to complain about his condition)
JUSTIN: Just now...
JUSTIN: I think I got around 6 seconds for 50m.
(DAEWON effect advancing record by 8 seconds)
HANBI: You were really historically fast!
(Observing the breaking of a record)
DANIEL: I'll surprise them from over there.
TRAINEE: Let's go.
(Preparing a surprise for friends who worked hard)
TRAINEE: I'm going to the restroom.
(HANBI and JUSTIN almost reaching the auditorium)
- JUSTIN: There's nothing else, right?
- HANBI: Surely nothing will happen here again, right?
(Are you going to do it?)
(Frightened)
HANBI: I knew you guys would do this!
- HANBI: I knew it would be like this, you guys!
- JUSTIN: I knew it!
(Didn't know about this, did you?)
(Second ambush by the maknaes)
(But actually, this one was more surprised)
HANBI: What is going on with you?
You're scaring yourself!
WOOLIN: I thought he'd come out here.
Why is it coming out here?
(Success anyway)
DANIEL: So, I thought they would come out here,
- DANIEL: but they came out here.
- WOOLIN: What?
(What's the point of guessing?)
HANBI: Ah, I already predicted it.
(You're going to be surprised)
JUSTIN: Ah, I knew it!
NICHOLAS: It took really long.
HANBI: Us?
(HANBI JUSTIN, recording the longest time: 34 minutes)
TRAINEE: Ah, this...
(Meanwhile, someone's scream echoes to the classroom)
- KASSHO: Is it SADAHARU?
- HYUNJUN: HARUTA.
CHARLIE: HARUTA?
- CHARLIE: HARUTA is here.
- HYUNJUN: Huh? What?
(Beep)
(Another person with a pea-sized heart)
(Going to pick up now)
TRAINEE: It's not me, right?
TRAINEE: Who is it?
(Camera going straight ahead with no hesitation)
TRAINEE: HYUNJUN, let's go.
(Next up 1. HYUNJUN)
HYUNJUN: CHARLIE, let's go.
(No, no?)
CHARLIE: Alone? Alone!
HYUNJUN: Why am I the only one alone?
CHARLIE: Let's go! Haha!
KASSHO: Alone?
KACHIN: Wow! Really alone!
(Celebration, solo debut) - KACHIN:
Really alone! - TRAINEE: Bye-bye!
- TRAINEE: Ah, this isn't right.
- TRAINEE: Bye-bye!
(Solo debut? News also reached the auditorium at that time)
DANIEL: HYUNJUN is going alone? Why?
- WOOLIN: Because it's fun.
- NICHOLAS: Because it looks like fun.
DANIEL: Wow, will HYUNJUN be okay?
JUSTIN: He shouldn't be doing it alone.
HYUNJUN: What if I don't understand this?
(Reason why HYUNJUN shouldn't be sent alone)
STAFF: If you've read everything, we'll proceed.
HYUNJUN: Wait a minute!
HYUNJUN: Don't do it!
(Swinging in the air)
HYUNJUN: Ah, but it might unexpectedly not be scary.
(Peeking)
HYUNJUN: Ah. This is unexpectedly okay.
(Doesn't seem unexpectedly scary?)
HYUNJUN: This is unexpectedly okay.
(No, it seems like we've taken the wrong path?)
JAEWON: I think he went the wrong way.
HANBI: Should go that way.
HYUNJUN: It's the wrong way!
HYUNJUN: Oh, left!
(Knew it)
HANBI: Oh, my!
(Reasonable doubt) DANIEL: Isn't he just going to
pass by the Principal's Office like that?
HYUNJUN: Okay, Career Counseling Room.
(Really passed by the Principal's Office)
(It was covered with cloth to discourage entry,
but he is going right through it)
HYUNJUN: Hello!
HYUNJUN: I think I'm in the wrong place.
(No)
HYUNJUN: Is this right?
(Searching again)
TRAINEE: He's good.
(Auto-tuned scream heard for the first time)
JAEWON: What?
(Absurd)
JAEWON: Is the microphone always like this?
(Auto-tuned scream echoed
through the third floor classroom)
HARUTA: As expected, it's HYUNJUN.
(Not surprised)
(Eek)
(Why the arms?)
(Shoo)
(Return)
(Absurd)
HANBI: He threw it outside!
DANIEL: Did he just throw it outside?
HYUNJUN: Okay.
HYUNJUN: Was everyone like this?
(No way)
(Peeking out)
(Arrived at the hallway in front of the restroom)
JUSTIN: Hey, can he go into that restroom alone?
DANIEL: Wow, that restroom really seems impossible.
DANIEL: I really...
- DANIEL: I would cry if I was alone there.
- HANBI: Exactly.
HYUNJUN: Please don't move.
HYUNJUN: I'm really sorry.
(The restroom everyone fears)
HYUNJUN: Ah, really...
HYUNJUN: Ah!
HANBI: Himself...
DANIEL: Go in while surprising them.
(Weapon acquired)
HYUNJUN: MINYEONG? What's up?
HYUNJUN: Ah!
(1 scream, 1 shock)
HYUNJUN: What's next?
(Motioning wildly)
(If you hear any sound from the restroom,)
(cover ears with something)
HYUNJUN: Cover my ears with something?
(Well, where are you?)
HYUNJUN: Where are you?
(Right next to you)
HYUNJUN: Wow!
(Frozen)
HYUNJUN: Oh, I'm okay with this now.
I'm fine with that kind of thing.
(Seems like he gained some courage?)
HYUNJUN: Like this?
(Retaliation?)
STAFF: Aah!
HYUNJUN: Wow, ah!
(Then, what about this)
(Peas)
(Exits quietly)
HYUNJUN: Hehe! Wait a moment...
(HYUNJUN's fear experience ended)
(HYUNJUN enters the auditorium)
- TRAINEE: Well done! - TRAINEE: You did well!
NICHOLAS: HYUNJUN, why did you struggle so much?
HYUNJUN: I couldn't understand the rules.
WOOLIN: You are really foolish.
- HYUNJUN: Thank you.
- NICHOLAS: You were cool!
(Meanwhile, in the classroom)
TRAINEE: Aaah!
HARUTA: Watching a movie is okay,
HARUTA: but I really can't handle haunted houses.
HARUTA: If there's a mission,
I really won't be able to move.
TRAINEE: Why?
HARUTA: You haven't gone into a haunted house with me.
HARUTA: KASSHO knows.
(Experienced)
HARUTA: It's no joke
HARUTA: how scared I am.
(Not good in real situations?)
TRAINEE: It's getting scarier and scarier.
HARUTA: Hurry up!
HARUTA: If we're going to do it,
I want to do it quickly.
HARUTA: No.
HARUTA: I don't want to do it.
HARUTA: I want to avoid it as much as possible.
HARUTA: It's fun!
(Inconsistent feelings)
HARUTA: Ah, it's fun.
HARUTA: Anyway, the STAFF...
HARUTA: Anyway, everything that comes out is our STAFF.
HARUTA: Just do it.
(Relaxed horror experience simulation)
KACHIN: Ahahaha!
HARUTA: Do it like this, okay?
(And the next order is)
TRAINEE: Let's go.
(KASSHO, HARUTA, KACHIN picked)
- TRAINEE: I'm so glad it's not me. - TRAINEE: No way...
KASSHO: Okay, let's go.
HARUTA: You have to protect me.
HARUTA: You have to protect...
KASSHO: Okay, okay.
KASSHO: It's scary.
(Whoosh)
TRAINEE: It's really too much!
- TRAINEE: Move back, come back.
- TRAINEE: Like this.
TRAINEE: Uh, look back, check behind.
HARUTA: I'll go in the middle.
(Calmly)
KACHIN: Okay, got it
(Two anxious types and one stable type)
KASSHO: Oh? Oh.
(Cameraman)
HARUTA: Please save me.
KASSHO: Please save me.
HARUTA: Could you please save me?
(Two anxious types wanting to cling to someone)
KASSHO: Oh, it seems scary.
(Japanese Zone) (Thai Zone)
(Reciting a storm of native language for survival)
(All read)
KASSHO: Okay, let's go.
KASSHO: Wow, that's really scary.
HARUTA: There won't be any on the stairs, right?
(Hurry)
(I'm scared too)
HARUTA: Enough, enough.
(The fortunate point is)
- TRAINEE: Don't do it now. - TRAINEE: There are no stairs.
(DAEWON, are you there?)
KASSHO: Because it's dangerous.
(The youngest is very strong-hearted)
HARUTA: Isn't it over there?
(Immediately checking)
KACHIN: Not here, not here.
TRAINEE: Uh oh!
(Welcome scream signaling the start) (Quick exit)
(It's a disaster for the anxious type)
KASSHO: Hey, where are you going?
KASSHO: Where are you going?
(Returned to the starting point in 5 seconds)
KASSHO: KACHIN...
(Left behind)
KASSHO: What about KACHIN?
(Energetically)
KACHIN: Ah, bro, just come! Come.
(Just a calm little brother)
KACHIN: There's nothing, nothing at all.
HANBI: KACHIN is brave.
(The reassuring youngest brother, KACHIN)
HANBI: He's reassuring.
(On the other hand)
HARUTA: Sorry, KACHIN.
HARUTA: I'm too scared.
(The older ones not living up to their age)
HARUTA: I can't do it.
(Frozen after making eye contact with the STAFF in the restroom)
KACHIN: Please don't come out.
(Slowly getting frustrated)
KACHIN: Ah, this is the cameraman.
- KACHIN: Cameraman.
- HARUTA: Sorry, sorry.
(What a boldness)
DANIEL: He speaks very clearly.
(Hug)
HARUTA: I really can't do this, seriously!
KASSHO: Principal's Office?
HARUTA: Seems like it, right?
(In front of the Principal's Office)
KASSHO: Principal's Office.
(Thunk)
KACHIN: This is right...
HARUTA: Please don't make any noise.
(Don't want to?)
TRAINEE: Aaah!
(Frightened out of one's wits)
KASSHO: Here, here, here.
(PTSD)
JUSTIN: Me too!
HANBI: I was surprised too
(Blink)
(KASSHO and KACHIN are behind the column)
KASSHO: I'm really scared.
KASSHO: HARUTA?
KASSHO: HARUTA!
- HANBI: HARUTA ran away.
- DANIEL: HARUTA panicked.
(Estimation of HARUTA's current state)
DANIEL: He might be like this.
KACHIN: HARUTA.
HARUTA: Well... Could you come get me?
(Bro, I'll save you!)
KACHIN: Come here, come here.
HYUNJUN: Oh KACHIN!
WOOLIN: You're so brave!
HYUNJUN: KACHIN is cool.
(The number one choice for guys you'd
want to do a horror experience with)
(Rescue successful)
TRAINEE: Oh, scary.
HARUTA: If I were alone, seriously...
HARUTA: It wouldn't have worked for me.
(KASSHO too)
HARUTA: I couldn't go at all.
(Once more: Open Sesame)
TRAINEE: Aargh!
HARUTA: Hey!
(Frustration)
HARUTA: Stop!
KASSHO: What did you say?
(Wish: Stop)
HARUTA: Stop!
(Don't want to?)
TRAINEE: Did you say 'stop'?
TRAINEE: Ohhh!
TRAINEE: Whoa!
(With brothers who have the ultimate impact)
KACHIN: It's okay, it's okay.
KACHIN: It's okay, it's okay!
(The youngest who doesn't know how to backtrack)
KACHIN: We have to take the stuff...
HARUTA: Why are you...
HARUTA: How can you do that?
(Research subject)
HARUTA: Are you crazy?
- JAEWON: I think this reaction is the best.
- DANIEL: I know, it's the best.
HARUTA: I want to try it.
(In the meantime, they all want to wear the wig)
KASSHO: Oh, try it on, try it on.
HARUTA: Don't come!
(Struggling to move forward to the next area)
KACHIN: Hey, look over there.
TRAINEE: Ha!
(MINYEONG appears, making everyone nervous)
KACHIN: Excuse me.
HARUTA: What are you doing now?
(Subdue)
(Wow)
(KACHIN, who was always just nice, hides his strength)
SONGHA: Wow, KACHIN is really brave.
HANBI: Did he take the wig?
KACHIN: Hehe!
(HARUTA, you wanted the wig)
- KACHIN: HARUTA. - HARUTA: You should watch carefully behind.
(This is a bit)
HARUTA: Ah, maybe this won't work?
(Return)
KACHIN: Okay, okay.
(That person is scary)
HARUTA: I just need to say it here, right?
(The three arrive at the restroom before they know it)
HARUTA: Here it is.
- HARUTA: Here, right?
- KASSHO: Does the color make you uneasy?
HARUTA: Exactly.
(It's practically labeled as an uneasy place)
HARUTA: This is the only restroom.
(But it was written in the rules that it's safe)
HARUTA: That's right, this is the place.
(HARUTA leads the way for the first time in a while)
HARUTA: Oh, am I supposed to speak here?
HARUTA: DAEWON?
(3, 2, 1)
HARUTA: Are you here?
(Bang!)
(Waaah!)
SADAHARU: Oh, that scared me!
(The thrill of spectating)
SADAHARU: Oh, that was surprising.
(Calm)
- HARUTA: Ahhhh! - KACHIN: Okay, okay.
(Hehehe?)
(Bang bang bang bang, hurry up and leave)
(Whimpering)
TRAINEE: I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
KACHIN: Got it, got it! Slowly!
(The boldness of someone scolding a ghost)
(Cautiously stepping out of the restroom)
WOOLIN: It's coming, it's coming!
(The final act everyone is waiting for)
- TRAINEE: Let's go, let's go! - TRAINEE: They're going.
SONGHA: They're running! They're running!
(DAEWON is coming)
(Type 1: Panic)
TRAINEE: Whaaaaa!
(Type 2: Evacuate to the restroom)
HARUTA: What's this? Where did it go?
(Type 3)
KACHIN: DAEWON, where did you go?
DANIEL: Did someone run that way? One person?
NICHOLAS: KACHIN, KACHIN.
(What on earth happened to KACHIN?)
KACHIN: What's going on? Where did he go?
KACHIN: DAEWON!
KACHIN: Where did you go?
(Pursuit)
STAFF: Where did KACHIN go?
TRAINEE: He's here.
(Regret, Relief)
- KACHIN: Is it over? - HARUTA: Is it over?
KACHIN: DAEWON left. DAEWON...
- STAFF: Did he run away?
- KACHIN: Yes.
(Exorcism ending)
NICHOLAS: Do we have to go too?
(Should we slowly start to scare them?)
- HANBI: Shall we get prepared too? - NICHOLAS: Shall we?
HYUNJUN: I want to try, I want to try.
(Whisper)
TRAINEE: Here, here.
HYUNJUN: Can't we do it here too?
(Waiting with a doll)
TRAINEE: Wow!
(The trio arrives unaware)
TRAINEE: Great job, everyone.
STAFF: Shall we move a little to the side?
HARUTA: Go this way, over there.
(Suspicion)
HARUTA: It's fine, it's fine. There's nothing, nothing.
(It's there)
HARUTA: It's gone now.
HARUTA: Hurry, hurry.
(Fortunately? It seems they didn't find it)
(Doll charged)
STAFF: One, two, three.
(A rewarding reaction for the preparations)
KACHIN: Pretty.
(Stable like concrete)
KACHIN: So cute.
NICHOLAS: It's over. Let's go.
(Disbelief)
HARUTA: Ah, lies.
(Group 1 waiting)
NICHOLAS: It's really over.
- TRAINEE: Wah!
- TRAINEE: Ugh!
(Collapse)
(Haha)
(Get up, there's still one more step)
TRAINEE: Aaah!
(TATA also waiting)
TATA: HARUTA!
KASSHO: What is this guy?
(Haha)
(Rock star appears)
KASSHO: That was fun.
KACHIN: You've worked hard.
(It wasn't fun)
TRAINEE: HARUTA is a legend.
TRAINEE: Did HARUTA cry?
(Meanwhile)
HAMIN: Why are you standing so close?
CHARLIE: It's scary.
(Now only two people are left in the classroom)
HAMIN: I'm scared too, so don't hide behind me, okay?
HAMIN: I'm scared too.
(The lights suddenly go out)
(Unidentifiable footsteps too)
(Bell sound)
CHARLIE: HAMIN!
CHARLIE: HAMIN! HAMIN! HAMIN!
HAMIN: How did you do that?
(Amazing)
(Unplugged the power strip from behind the desk)
CHARLIE: I don't know.
(Reading the Night Rules carefully)
HAMIN: Since all doors and windows are closed,
HAMIN: they said to stop if you hear a voice.
HAMIN: And,
(Memorizing like studying for a test)
HAMIN: don't use the third stall in the restroom. Three...
HAMIN: Let's go for now.
HAMIN: Let's go!
(Bold start)
- HAMIN: Just go for it. - CHARLIE: Okay.
(As learned)
- HAMIN: Don't look at the window, look down. - CHARLIE: Okay.
(Waiting for welcome) (Search area)
- HAMIN: Left, left. - CHARLIE: Left?
(No look and pass) (Leaving with no gain)
(Just in case)
HAMIN: Don't look back, don't look back.
(While just looking forward) (Bang) (Whoosh)
CHARLIE: Ah!
HAMIN: Hey, I'm scared too.
HAMIN: I'm scared too!
(Dragging)
(Whether scared or not)
(Dragging with force)
HAMIN: I'm scared too. Me too.
(In front of MINYEONG in an instant) (Hi)
CHARLIE: Oh, hello! Oh, hello!
- CHARLIE: Oh, oh!
- HAMIN: It's scary, I'm scared too!
(Pull yourself together)
- HAMIN: Over there! The restroom is over there! - CHARLIE: Oh!
(A man who knows nothing but to advance)
- CHARLIE: No! - HAMIN: Follow me, follow me.
(It only took them 50 seconds to reach the restroom)
CHARLIE: Oh, what's this?
(Ignored)
HAMIN: It was always there, always there.
(Surprised auditorium at CHARLIE's scream)
TRAINEE: Oh, that surprised me!
TRAINEE: Wow, that was surprising.
HANBI: What's this?
- WOOLIN: When did you come?
- HANBI: When did you come?
HANBI: When did they come?
(Everyone's confused at the fast pace)
- TRAINEE: Why are they so fast? - TRAINEE: What's with them?
HYUNJUN: What, they're here already?
(Suddenly)
- HAMIN: No, it's here. - CHARLIE: Hyung, are you here?
(Strict)
- HAMIN: No, it's not here. - CHARLIE: Hyung...
(According to FM, right in front of the third stall)
HAMIN: DAEWON, are you there?
(Calm)
CHARLIE: DAEWON, are you... are you here?
(Won't harm)
HAMIN: DAEWON, are you there?
(Looks like DAEWON isn't here)
- CHARLIE: Not here? - HAMIN: Seems like he's not here.
CHARLIE: Oh, what do we do?
(Push)
(Even the leisure to joke around)
CHARLIE: What... are you doing?
(The leisure ends there)
CHARLIE: What! What!
CHARLIE: Aaah! What is this?
(What is this?)
HAMIN: Are we going this way?
(DAEWON's last sprint ended blandly)
STAFF: It's over.
HAMIN: It's over?
HAMIN: Did we find DAEWON?
STAFF: You passed by him earlier.
HAMIN: Ah...
(They say DAEWON can't rest in peace
because of his frustration...)
(After the horror experience)
(HYUNJUN brought JANG MINYEONG's mannequin)
(Shh!)
(First victim: SONGHA)
HYUNJUN: SONGHA, SONGHA.
- SONGHA: Huh?
- HYUNJUN: Come over here once.
SONGHA: Oh, what a scare!
(World happiness)
(Second victim: WOOLIN)
HYUNJUN: Hahahaha!
(Clearing out the dorm and moving again with dignity)
(The final destination is the auditorium
with the showers)
(Setting up the mannequin
at the entrance of the auditorium with showers)
(Waiting for the right moment in the lounge)
(That moment,
KASSHO and SADAHARU finished their shower)
TRAINEE: What's that?
(Next victims: KASSHO, SADAHARU)
- TRAINEE: What's that? - TRAINEE: What?
KASSHO: This is dangerous.
SADAHARU: So scary, really scary!
(Giggles at the screams
heard all the way to the lounge)
(Last victim: JUSTIN)
JUSTIN: What...
(Pause)
HYUNJUN: Ah, I'm really sorry.
SONGHA: I'm scared.
(Thus, the final night
of the 8 days of school life ends.)
(Now the only thing left is
the WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL's festival!)
(September 2025
WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL entrance ceremony)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE: Through your life
at WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL,)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE: you received scores
through various assignments.)
(The class with the highest score during school life)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE: The class with the highest score will)
(The subtitle of the fan meeting is the name of the top class!)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE: give their name)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE: to the fan meeting.)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE: Total 150 points.)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE: Five Boys Over Flowers class
has a total of 130 points.)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE: WONHA~JANNI class
has a total of 170 points.)
(Mid-term tally)
(Currently, 1st place WONHA~JANNI)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE: But! It's not over yet.)
(Points at stake in the final festival too)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE: In the school festival,)
(WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL's festival, 1st place: 100 points)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE: the class that wins 1st place gets 100 points.)
(2nd place: 50 points)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE: The class in 2nd place gets 50 points.)
(3rd place: 30 points)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE: And the class in 3rd place is given 30 points.)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE:
It's a situation where a comeback is possible.)
(All three classes can win!)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE: During the remaining period,)
(TEACHERS' OFFICE:
please do your best in stage practice.)
ALL: Yes!
(WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL's festival D-24)
(The practice room they returned to after school life)
TRAINEE: Also my wounded
TRAINEE: heart...
DANIEL: That's right!
(Thud)
TRAINEE: Footsteps.
DANIEL: Okay.
HANBI: You have to match the footsteps here.
TRAINEE: Seven, eight...
(Detailing again from the sound of footsteps)
TRAINEE: Footsteps.
TRAINEE: Step by step, the sound of footsteps.
(Starting with the group song "Into The New World")
TRAINEE: Let's match it.
(A.U.I "You, In the Fantasy")
(Thorough monitoring is essential)
TRAINEE: Step by step, it's matching well now.
(D-23)
TRAINEE: Looking back at it,
(Five Boys Over Flowers "Love And Remember")
TRAINEE: it was really beautiful.
SONGHA: How should I express this song with my face?
HANBI: With a hint of sadness in the smile?
SONGHA: Looking back at it, it was really beautiful.
SONGHA: Moments that will never come again in my life.
HANBI: Why like that...
HANBI: We have this moment now, the trainee period.
HANBI: It will end someday, right?
HANBI: We prepared for evaluations, recorded together.
HANBI: These are all memories, we can't go back,
while thinking about those things.
SONGHA: Hmm, then,
SONGHA: let's focus on that expression when we do it.
HANBI: Seven, eight...
(Though the class songs compete for points)
HANBI: Love
(Class '00 reflecting on the meaning of the song during practice)
HANBI: and remember...
(D-22)
DANIEL: Seven, eight...
DANIEL: Boom
(WONHA~JANNI "CALL ME BABY")
DANIEL: Boom, ta, ta, ta, ta, ta.
DANIEL: Precisely, thump, thump, thump, thump, thump.
(Smooth sailing for Class '10 under DANIEL's guidance)
DANIEL: Six, and...
(D-17)
DANIEL: Thump, snap, oh yeah!
(Practice room visited every day
until the body remembers)
DANIEL: Harder, harder, harder!
(D-15)
(Endless practice time for a perfect stage)
(D-14)
DANIEL: Don't get tired.
DANIEL: Don't make that face
like you're going to mess up dancing already.
(Strict discipline at A.U.I)
DANIEL: Look, is the energy going to disappear?
DANIEL: Is it going to disappear?
JAEWON: It's not going to disappear.
TRAINEE: We're not going to lose.
DANIEL: The center really needs to give off energy.
DANIEL: When you go to the center,
your expression and dance, everything!
(As the performance day approaches,)
DANIEL: This is how you should go.
(DANIEL takes care of even the smallest details)
DANIEL: One, two, three, hey.
(D-12)
TRAINEE: Love you, this feeling...
(D-8)
(D-7)
(D-6)
(D-5)
(D-4)
(D-3)
(D-2)
(WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL's festival D-1)
=Episode 8=
(We Go Part 1)
(10 AM, WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL)
- TRAINEE: We're here.
- TRAINEE: Go down.
HYUNJUN: Wow, it's so nice.
CHARLIE: Hello!
(Students arriving at WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL)
TRAINEE: Hello!
HANBI: Wow, it's the school!
- HANBI: It's been ages since school.
- JUSTIN: Hello!
TRAINEE: It's been a while.
TRAINEE: Wow!
HYUNJUN: It's been a while.
HANBI: It comes to mind when I went to school?
- TRAINEE: Let's go in.
- TRAINEE: It's really been a while.
(Students with fresh memories
after visiting for the first time in a while)
TRAINEE: It's really been a while.
HANBI: When I first came to school,
I walked right here.
JUSTIN: That's right.
HANBI: Do you remember?
JUSTIN: Of course.
HANBI: Whoa, this place is big!
JUSTIN: It's really big!
(Why the sudden surprise while reminiscing?)
TRAINEE: Stage! The stage!
TRAINEE: Where we played soccer.
- TRAINEE: WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL festival!
- TRAINEE: It's too big!
TRAINEE: WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL festival!
(The festival stage set up on the school field)
(WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL Festival)
TRAINEE: Wow, it's WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL.
(WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL)
TRAINEE: They've even made a WOOJEONG HIGH sign for us.
TRAINEE: You are right.
(School Festival)
TRAINEE: It's so pretty, really pretty.
TRAINEE: Yay!
TRAINEE: WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL.
JUSTIN: Let's go up.
(They step up with excitement)
(Unable to hide their smiles)
CHARLIE: Nice!
(Full of excitement)
TRAINEE: Oh, this is the place...
DANIEL: The stage is huge, isn't it?
TRAINEE: So this is where we get ready.
(They look around every corner of the stage)
(Greeting simulation)
TRAINEE: It goes up to number 12.
(They're thrilled for their very first stage)
(They carefully check even the backstage area)
HANBI: Oh, there's an exit here too?
(Already checked)
SONGHA: Yeah!
TRAINEE: The stage is nice.
(The quick-moving oldest members)
HANBI: The stage is really great!
STAFF: The audience seating will start from here.
(The trainees gather at center stage)
TRAINEE: It's right in front?
HANBI: I can see the audience really well.
JAEWON: Oh, hi!
(It finally starts to feel real,
thinking about meeting fans up close)
(Emotional)
JUSTIN: Wow, this is...
HYUNJUN: Say hello, say hello.
TRAINEE: Hello.
HYUNJUN: Hello.
HANBI: At a place where we used to hang out...
HANBI: It's amazing to perform here.
HANBI: I remember this.
HANBI: Wow...
(It feels different being back at school)
TRAINEE: It's been a while.
HANBI: That's the waiting room over there.
(SMTR25)
HANBI: The waiting room, the waiting room.
HANBI: Wow, this used to be the music room.
(A spacious waiting room for 15 trainees)
TRAINEE: This is the first time here.
HANBI: Hey, there's even a sofa!
HANBI: It's quite spacious probably
because there are so many people.
(Unpacking in the waiting room one by one)
JUSTIN: There are name tags outside.
JUSTIN: You can find and take your name tags.
- TRAINEE: Okay.
HANBI: Let's grab our name tags.
SONGHA: Shouldn't we be wearing in-ears for this too?
TRAINEE: I guess we should.
TRAINEE: We couldn't hear anything earlier.
(Getting ready for full stage rehearsal)
(They pick up their name tags)
(And in-ears, trying to calm their nerves)
STAFF: I'll secure your in-ears with tape.
(They fix them tightly so they won't fall out)
(They also check the mic fit)
SONGHA: Let's go, guys, let's go!
TRAINEE: Guys, let's go to the stage!
TRAINEE: Let's go!
(Off to stage rehearsal!)
(Finally, it's time to stand on stage)
DANIEL: We can do this! Fighting!
TRAINEE: Fighting!
HANBI: Whoa!
(WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL school festival)
(Blazing sunlight)
(Weather forecast: clear and refreshing)
(What will happen in four hours)
(Didn't expect the show to move this fast, huh?)
HANBI: The weather is so nice.
TRAINEE: Is everyone here?
(Unaware of what's coming)
(The trainees are full of excitement)
TRAINEE: Are the mics working?
HANBI: First off, everyone? Everyone!
(HANBI tries to calm the excited group)
HANBI: Be quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet.
HANBI: Let's greet them first!
(Facing all the staff involved in the performance)
HANBI: We'd like to say hello to everyone. Two, three.
(Greeting)
ALL: Hello!
ALL: Please take good care of us.
(They clap for themselves modestly)
TRAINEE: Let's try it.
TRAINEE: Let's do it.
HANBI: Could you play the song for us, please?
(They run through "Into the New World"
for the first time on stage)
(CHARLIE has a flying jump part)
CHARLIE: Hey, oh!
(Not enough space to jump)
(After the first stage rehearsal)
(Decided to adjust CHARLIE's position again!)
SONGHA: We'll just fix CHARLIE's part,
SONGHA: as there isn't enough space.
(Joking)
SONGHA: CHARLIE, want to jump from here?
(Jumping into the audience seats)
(The scary part is, it's actually possible)
(Anyone having any more issues?)
SONGHA: Anyone having any more problems?
(Nope)
SONGHA: None, right?
(While the staff reset things)
SONGHA: The set is really cool, kind of really...
SONGHA: It feels like a school festival, doesn't it?
SONGHA: Like they spent a lot of money!
SONGHA: It feels more like a college festival.
JUSTIN: Hey! Hey!
KASSHO: Hey!
SONGHA: Isn't that totally OH HYUNJUN?
(HYUNJUN's tone)
(Perfectly imitated)
JUSTIN: There's no 'Hoi'?
(What they mean by "hoi" is...)
(A sound that habitually comes from CHARLIE's part)
TRAINEE: Hoi, hoi, hoi, hoi.
(They say "hoi" more than Dooly)
JUSTIN: Here's "Hoi".
(Hoi...!)
TRAINEE: There's no "Hoi", "Hoi"!
SONGHA: Or later, we could go up there
SONGHA: and write "hoi" with a marker.
- KASSHO: Hoi, hoi.
- JUSTIN: Hoi, hoi.
(Too many "hoi"s could be a problem)
TRAINEE: Hoi, hoi, hoi.
(Next, rehearsal for Class A.U.I, Year 90)
JUSTIN: We'll get it done.
HYUNJUN: Let's do it.
- TRAINEE: We can do it.
- TRAINEE: Fighting!
(Class '90, "You, In the Fantasy" stage rehearsal begins!)
SADAHARU: It really feels like a school festival.
(Enjoying, wholesome bottled water)
HANBI: Feels like a school festival.
SADAHARU: Feels like a school festival.
HANBI: Being at school like this...
HANBI: It really feels like a school festival.
HANBI: With friends right in front of us!
HANBI: Our alumni are here.
(Group of alumni)
TRAINEE: Wow, at school...
HANBI: It really feels like a school festival.
HANBI: It's a strange feeling.
HANBI: I've never actually
performed at a school festival.
(First rehearsal finished)
(Heavy breathing fills the microphones)
NICHOLAS: Let's line up once when we stand in a row.
JUSTIN: Energy!
HYUNJUN: It's all about energy!
HYUNJUN: Energy!
(Their voices blast through the in-ears)
HANBI: It's all about energy, energy.
(He responds back)
DANIEL: Energy!
(Catchphrase)
(The rehearsal for Class '90 resumes)
(Monitoring friends' performances)
KASSHO: Let's do it one more time!
JUSTIN: Just the positions!
JUSTIN: Just one more time!
(Rehearse once more)
(Meanwhile, the audience has grown)
(Under HAMIN's watch)
SONGHA: Fighting!
(Rat-a-tat-tat)
(A clumsy but kind older brother)
(It's still party time here)
TRAINEE: You are
TRAINEE: in the fantasy.
(Song ends)
(Disperse)
(Class '90 A.U.I's "You, In the Fantasy"
stage rehearsal ends)
TRAINEE: Are you okay?
TRAINEE: No issues, right?
TRAINEE: None.
(KASSHO is completely worn out)
NICHOLAS: Water... is there any?
(Cries for survival everywhere)
TRAINEE: Is there any tissue?
(Outdoor performance)
KASSHO: It's harder when it's outside.
KASSHO: Wow, even just marking positions is exhausting.
(Checking KASSHO's condition)
HAMIN: Wow, you've gotten old, huh?
HAMIN: You aged after dancing twice!
(Rapid aging)
JUSTIN: Ah, this is...
(Immediate diagnosis)
HYUNJUN: Your stomach hurts, right?
JUSTIN: It's because I'm too full.
WOOLIN: I'm hurting here...
(Zombie)
JUSTIN: I can't breathe.
HYUNJUN: I've got a bit of a feeling
like I need the restroom.
(STAFF:?)
STAFF: You can go to the restroom.
HYUNJUN: No, it just feels like it...
HYUNJUN: It's like it's coming out here...
TRAINEE: Let's go!
("Love And Remember" stage rehearsal)
SONGHA: Yes, we'll try "Love And Remember".
(This time, DANIEL is watching)
(If you guys weren't here, our class would be first...)
(It's just the editing)
HANBI: You need to move further back there.
(Issues noticed during practice)
HANBI: And KACHIN, you should pull that back.
- KACHIN: Ah, yes yes!
- HANBI: Yes, there.
(They adjust things one by one)
HANBI: Where is it, there...
(Totally exposed)
(Forehead forcibly exposed by the strong wind)
SONGHA: Ah, my hair seriously...
KACHIN: When I sing "I love you,"
my hair keeps messing up like this.
HANBI: Mine does that too.
It turns into perilla-leaf hair.
(Wind-grown organic perilla leaves)
(Perilla leaves appear)
(Another perilla leaf)
(Perilla leaves are dicot plants)
(Perilla leaves gone)
(New perilla leaf arrives)
- TRAINEE: Thank you.
(Practice ends, the "perilla leaves" disperse)
(SONGHA elegantly wipes off sweat)
(What about enthusiastic KACHIN?)
(Full sauna mode)
SADAHARU: Did you shower?
KACHIN: Yeah!
KACHIN: I'm the only one sweating.
(Class '10, "CALL ME BABY" stage rehearsal)
(For now, focus on the formation)
DANIEL: Let's focus on the formation.
DANIEL: And go hard!
- HAMIN: Right from the start?
- DANIEL: Yes, go hard right away
(Dancing hard)
(Professional monitoring agent SONGHA)
(Tenant moved in upstairs)
(If only that class wasn't here...)
(Mid-point check)
DANIEL: With pace and slow.
DANIEL: Match the moves precisely!
DANIEL: Don't lose energy here.
DANIEL: Let's take a short break.
DANIEL: Then go hard again.
DANIEL: Just 30 seconds.
(What you can do in 30 seconds)
TRAINEE: Because of the dust.
SONGHA: Oh.
SONGHA: DANIEL drank mine.
(Drinking mineral water with a straw)
TRAINEE: Oh, SUNGHYUN.
(Spurt!!)
TRAINEE: Oh dear.
(Spraying more than drinking)
SONGHA: SUNGHYUN, what are you doing?
(Accidentally turned into a water dispenser)
SONGHA: It's too hot, right? Because of the sunshine...
HARUTA: It's way too hot.
(After the rehearsal ends,
Class '90 heads to the waiting room!)
TRAINEE: Can I still pull it out?
NICHOLAS: Wow.
KASSHO: Wow, my legs feel so heavy.
JUSTIN: We need to manage our stamina well.
If we're out of breath from the start, we're dead!
JUSTIN: We have another rehearsal later.
JUSTIN: Let's go harder then.
(Camera rehearsal in the evening)
JUSTIN: Yeah, camera rehearsal.
TRAINEE: We have to go hard
during the camera rehearsal anyway.
TRAINEE: Might as well do it then.
(Cold bottled water is a good device
to take out the heat)
HYUNJUN: I don't think I can focus
if I see my older sister.
(HYUNJUN's older sister even applied)
KASSHO: Is she really coming?
(and got selected as an audience)
HYUNJUN: Yeah, she really is.
(On stage)
NICHOLAS: Talk about your sister if you want!
JUSTIN: Ms. Big Sister.
JUSTIN: Please give a big round of applause.
(Perfect way to embarrass his sister)
(Expected reaction from his sister)HYUNJUN: That's not the HYUNJUN
who was lounging at home, right?
HYUNJUN: What do you think of HYUNJUN you saw on stage?
JUSTIN: Oh, that's nice!
(What????)
(Was she impressed by the lounging HYUNJUN?)
JUSTIN: That's actually kind of really touching.
HYUNJUN: You think it's touching?
JUSTIN: I mean, you showed
a cool side of yourself on stage.
(Understood?)
HYUNJUN: My older sister is a fan of DANIEL.
HYUNJUN: She really likes him.
(HYUNJUN's older sister's favorite)
HYUNJUN: For real.
HYUNJUN: She really likes DANIEL.
HYUNJUN: She also likes you, KASSHO.
KASSHO: Really?
(Bias)
HYUNJUN: But...
HYUNJUN: My sister has her picks!
KASSHO: Still...
(Favorite DANIEL)
HYUNJUN: DANIEL.
(Second favorite KASSHO)
HYUNJUN: KASSHO.
(Grin)
JUSTIN: That's it?
HYUNJUN: Oh, but SONGHA...
(It's clear that the younger brother isn't on the favorite list)
HYUNJUN: Everyone seems to like him.
(Stage rehearsal finished)
ALL: Thank you!
DANIEL: Hehehe.
(Somehow DANIEL seems excited)
DANIEL: You're in the fantasy.
SONGHA: Come here.
DANIEL: What am I, a puppy? Just go like that?
SONGHA: You're going to do it, aren't you?
Then okay, I got it...
(Correct)
STAFF: The writer is calling you.
DANIEL: Yes.
(DANIELsuddenly smiles and heads somewhere)
(He goes into the waiting tent)
DANIEL: Hehehehehe.
DANIEL: Just wait, HANBI!
(They prepare a surprise party for HANBI,
whose birthday is today)
(Unaware of anything,
HANBI is monitoring stage rehearsal)
(Heading towards HANBI with a birthday cake)
(Delivering fake announcements
to catch HANBI's attention)
(Focused)
HANBI: Yes, yes.
DANIEL: Five, six, seven, eight!
HANBI: Happy birthday to you.
(The surprise birthday party)
ALL: Happy birthday to you.
(For HANBI, started by DANIEL's lead)
ALL: Happy birthday to our dear HANBI.
Happy birthday to you!
TRAINEE: HANBI!
HANBI: Thank you.
TRAINEE: HANBI, HANBI!
HANBI: Thank you!
HANBI: Thank you so much.
(First, make a wish)
HANBI: I should make a wish first, right?
HANBI: A man holding flowers.
HANBI: Please remember Five Boys Over Flowers.
(A quick promo moment)
(After making a heartfelt wish, blowing out the candle)
(Happiness doubles when shared)
DANIEL: HANBI, there's one more gift.
HANBI: What is it?
SONGHA: HANBI's been
using the same wallet for a long time.
HANBI: Oh, that's true!
SONGHA: So we wanted to get you a new one.
(A wallet gift for HANBI)
HANBI: What is it, what is it?
DANIEL: Do you recognize it?
TATA: Do you know it?
(Remembered the wallet HANBI was fond of)
HANBI: Isn't this the one I mentioned before?
(Touched by their thoughtfulness)
HANBI: Thank you so much.
HANBI: My favorite item has changed.
It used to be my monitor, now it's this wallet.
(Favorite item changed to the wallet)
(The party ends with another round of thanks)
HANBI: Wow, it's nice.
HANBI: I'll carry it well, thank you so much.
(PM 5:30)
TRAINEE: Let's head to the field.
(Camera rehearsal)
TRAINEE: Let's go.
- TRAINEE: Thank you.
- TRAINEE: Let's go.
HANBI: Let's go to the stage.
(The trainees prepare for the camera rehearsal)
(But)
(The STAFF suddenly call an emergency meeting)
STAFF: Oh, is it raining?
(Is it raining...?)
(While celebrating HANBI's birthday,)
(Dark clouds roll in)
(And then it starts to rain)
(The clear weather)
(Suddenly changes unexpectedly)
(The STAFF scramble at the sudden rain)
STAFF: Since it's raining, please get ready
and wait in the waiting room.
ALL: Yes.
JUSTIN: No!
HANBI: Why is it raining...
DANIEL: It's raining quite a bit, isn't it?
HANBI: Yeah, it really is.
(Raindrops getting thicker)
(Even pooling water on the stage floor)
(STAFF step in to manage the situation)
STAFF: We'll sort out the situation now.
ALL: Yes.
(According to the forecast, the rain should stop at 6:30)
STAFF: We expect it to stop around 6:30.
TRAINEE: Yes.
(For now, all schedules are delayed until then)
STAFF: At 6:30, change outfits
- STAFF: and proceed with the camera rehearsal.
- ALL: Yes.
STAFF: If it's still raining and the stage is slippery,
STAFF: we'll cancel today's rehearsal.
(Camera rehearsal)
(A full run-through before filming to check
camera angles, movement, and timing)
(They may have to go straight
to the real stage without rehearsal)
(For students with no broadcast experience,
it's practically a gamble)
(Up to the camera rehearsal)
TRAINEE: Has the rain stopped?
(The rain gets heavier as time passes)
TRAINEE: It feels like it slowed a bit.
WOOLIN: Wow, it's raining a lot?
KASSHO: Exactly.
TATA: Is it raining?
NICHOLAS: TATA, look.
JUSTIN: It's raining a lot.
TATA: Huh???
(The changing schedule is shared with the trainees)
STAFF: Let me update you.
(Rain is now forecast until 9)
STAFF: It's now postponed to rain until 9 o'clock.
(They decide to wait until 7 o'clock)
STAFF: We'll monitor the situation until 7 o'clock.
NICHOLAS: Okay.
(Current time PM 6:30)
(They should be doing the camera rehearsal
according to schedule)
(Assessing the situation, HARUTA goes outside to check)
HARUTA: It's raining more than I thought.
(Current time PM 7:00)
HARUTA: I didn't know it would rain like this.
(HANBI also joins)
(More rain than expected)
HARUTA: It's raining more than expected.
HANBI: It's raining a lot.
HANBI: Even though I like rain, this is too much.
HARUTA: The weather is always bad.
HARUTA: But it was nice this morning.
HANBI: Yeah, the weather was really clear this morning.
HANBI: Who would've thought it would suddenly rain?
HARUTA: I can't see when it'll stop.
HANBI: It shows no sign of stopping.
HARUTA: But!
HARUTA: We'll do well tomorrow.
HANBI: Oh, confidence.
HARUTA: We have to do well.
HANBI: We definitely have to do well tomorrow.
(They desperately hope the rain stops)
HANBI: I wish the rain would stop.
HARUTA: I want to get on stage soon.
HANBI: Right.
HARUTA: I'm excited.
(Instinctively doing choreography)
(As if sensing their eagerness,
the rain begins to ease)
(Finally, the rain has stopped)
(They remove all the water from the stage for safety)
HYUNJUN: The rain has stopped!
(The good news reaches the trainees)
TRAINEE: The rain has stopped.
(They finally prepare for the camera rehearsal)
(PM 9:00)
TRAINEE: Let's go, let's go!
TATA: Nervous, so nervous.
(After about four hours of waiting)
HAMIN: Let's go!
(Finally heading out for camera rehearsal)
KASSHO: Let's go.
(The weather turns chilly after the rain)
(The current perceived temperature is...)
TRAINEE: Cold! Cold!
(Even the lighting looks like a Siberian freezer)
(The blue lighting reminds them of someone)
TRAINEE: MINYEONG!
(MINYEONG has "ascended")
TRAINEE: So cold!
HANBI: It's okay. Once we dance, we'll warm up.
(Before the camera rehearsal)
HYUNJUN: Well, just...
(STAFF announcement)
HYUNJUN: They said don't dance too hard.
HYUNJUN: If the stage is slippery,
tell them right away!
HYUNJUN: They said not to dance too hard.
(Stage check is the priority for safety)
JUSTIN: It's fine though?
HANBI: Seems fine.
JUSTIN: It's fine.
HANBI: It's actually better because it's less slippery.
NICHOLAS: Maybe it depends on the shoes?
SONGHA: It probably depends on the shoes.
STAFF: We'll begin the camera rehearsal.
ALL: Yes!
(First, a stage check)
STAFF: Everyone, standby. Two, one, go!
(Into The New World)
(They run it like a real performance)
(With full outfits and everything prepared)
(As if it's the real performance)
(The problem is...)
(Even after wiping, the stage is still slippery)
DANIEL: Don't go forward!
(Right as he says that...)
(People start slipping everywhere)
(TATA coming to take care of his older member)
TATA: See?
(Camera rehearsal stops)
TRAINEE: Oh, no...
(HANBI, JUSTIN...)
TRAINEE: Who said it wasn't slippery?
(HANBI is checking if everyone is okay)
HANBI: Are you okay?
HYUNJUN: Pain is youth!
(If you're hurt, let's go to the hospital)
HANBI: This spot is really...
HANBI: I think this white part is the problem.
(The stage looks frosted)
HANBI: It's like dew.
(River located right next to the school)
(After the rain, the school is in thick fog)
DANIEL: Let's bring some towels and wipe it together.
DANIEL: If 15 of us wipe it together,
it will be done quickly!
HANBI: If all 15 of us clean together, it'll be fast.
HANBI: Everyone, grab towels!
(While the STAFF devises stage countermeasures)
TRAINEE: It's very slippery here.
(A bunch of "foot-powered cleaners" appear)
(Among them, the pink version is exceptionally good)
TRAINEE: Hey, Cinderella!
(It's HYUNJUN)
(Found a new talent)
TRAINEE: HYUNJUN!
(No one can keep up)
NICHOLAS: HYUNJUN!
HANBI: HYUNJUN, you need to clean
there quickly. What are you doing?
SONGHA: Our Snow White!
(It's Cinderella?)
HYUNJUN: It's Cinderella, Cinderella.
(Got teased by his seniors)
SONGHA: Cinderella, sorry.
NICHOLAS: Hey, Cinderella, here!
(STAFF also join Cinderella)
TRAINEE: Cinderella is young.
(They scrub hard with all their strength)
SONGHA: Why does it feel the same even after cleaning?
HYUNJUN: No, it's not.
SONGHA: Is it not? Is it just my imagination?
HANBI: No, it keeps coming back
no matter how much we clean.
HANBI: Clean it once, and then clean it again.
(If you wipe like grilling meat)
HANBI: Keep wiping and...
DANIEL: Even if we keep cleaning,
DANIEL: it might never go away!
HANBI: Maybe it'll disappear eventually?
NICHOLAS: Maybe by tomorrow morning.
(But once the sun rises, they can't check lighting)
SONGHA: As long as it's gone by tomorrow morning,
- SONGHA: that's fine.
- TRAINEE: All right.
(Tonight's stage check is essential)
HANBI: If you come over here,
HANBI: you can apply anti-slip tape to your shoes.
(Reinforcing shoes for safety)
TRAINEE: Take two and attach them to your shoes.
(On shoe soles)
TRAINEE: Okay, put them on the front of your shoes.
(Attaching sandpaper-like tape)
TRAINEE: Attach it to the front part of your shoes.
(To increase friction)
(And reduce slipping)
(Attach sandpaper tape thoroughly on the shoe soles)
HYUNJUN: Done!
HANBI: Let's dispose of the trash
after using the tape, everyone!
(For even safer measures)
TRAINEE: Oh, nice.
(Attach anti-slip tape on the stage as well)
(There's just one problem)
KASSHO: It got really scratched.
(Because of the sandpaper tape)
HARUTA: I'm sorry.
(Scratches on the stage)
HARUTA: I did it.
(For the trainees' safety)
(Decided to forgo the stage's shine)
HANBI: Hey, it's all about energy!
TRAINEE: Energy!
HANBI: Even if bones break, we keep going!
DANIEL: Just run like you've lost a rib!
(No, absolutely not)
DANIEL: I think you shouldn't
be scared by the slippery floor.
TRAINEE: Yeah, just go for it.
SONGHA: If we fall, we fall.
DANIEL: Getting scared of slipping is too tempting.
(Their ruthless friendship)
HANBI: Jjolmyeon noodle is delicious.
JUSTIN: Am I the only one who found that funny?
HANBI: Shall we try it, everyone?
HANBI: Like this?
(Stage prep completed)
(Such polite and well-mannered guys)
ALL: Thank you.
HANBI: Hey, that's basically a scream.
DANIEL: The crowd mentality is really...
DANIEL: Amazing! It's just that one person...
DANIEL: As soon as it gets a bit loud,
people start screaming!
(Resetting the mood)
TRAINEE: Okay, please quiet down again!
TRAINEE: Silence!
HYUNJUN: Our math teacher's name was 'JUNGSUK'.
TRAINEE: Please be quiet.
STAFF: If it's still slippery even after reinforcement,
STAFF: don't push yourselves and tell us right away.
ALL: Okay.
TRAINEE: Let's do our best!
(Seriously, don't overdo it, come on...)
TRAINEE: Let's do our best.
TRAINEE: Let's go!
(Camera rehearsal resumes)
(Go easy to avoid injury)
(Thankfully, it ends safely)
SONGHA: Oh, this floor tape is nice!
JUSTIN: Very, very nice!
HANBI: Let's be more energetic together...
HANBI: Even if we can't hype it up,
just imagine we are.
(Holding back laughter)
(Failed)
HANBI: Can you not laugh?
- HANBI: Why are you laughing like that?
- DANIEL: Wait a moment!
DANIEL: It'd be nice if we made more eye contact.
DANIEL: I get energy every time I see HYUNJUN!
JUSTIN: I also get strength when I see HANBI.
HANBI: We're always together when we come in.
(Each one is presently the most
empowering to the other)
ALL: Fighting!
(Rehearsing even the special effects timing)
(Checking fireworks positions for safety)
(Rehearsal conducted within time limits
with official cooperation)
("Into The New World" camera rehearsal ends)
HANBI: Wow.
HANBI: It's really...
TRAINEE: Yeah.
JUSTIN: Didn't the explosion give you energy?
HANBI: Yeah, it did.
SONGHA: It really did.
HYUNJUN: I feel like I might cry.
DANIEL: The view from here is the best!
SONGHA: It's so pretty, beautiful!
SONGHA: Hey, DANIEL.
SONGHA: You're beautiful too.
HANBI: I knew you'd say that!
(Teasing)
(While STAFF prepare the next stage)
DANIEL: What is this?
(Handshake with the fans)
HANBI: It's close to the audience.
HANBI: But it might be hard to see at night...
DANIEL: I don't think we'll see them well.
(Worried about not seeing the audience)
HANBI: Oh, but still...
HANBI: Hey, you can see your breath!
(Trainees are worried about light, temperature, and humidity)
HANBI: It must be cold, I can see my breath.
HYUNJUN: Okay then.
(Next, "You, In the Fantasy" camera rehearsal)
HYUNJUN: Let's enter.
STAFF: The members will go up first.
(They head to the stage with cheers!)
TRAINEE: Fighting!
TRAINEE: Let's go!
JUSTIN: We...
JUSTIN: When the camera's on us, let's do well.
TRAINEE: Okay!
JUSTIN: I trust you!
HYUNJUN: Let's go!
(A belief without moderation)
JUSTIN: I believe...
("You, In the Fantasy", first stage in costume)
SONGHA: Since it's our first time
performing in costumes...
HANBI: Right.
HANBI: We haven't done it in costumes before, have we?
(Dress rehearsal: Rehearsal in actual stage costume)
HANBI: We haven't done a dress rehearsal, have we?
(They fix issues immediately)
(During rehearsal)
STAFF: Manager, this bag!
HYUNJUN: Could you secure the bag for me?
STAFF: The firework will explode at the very end!
WOOLIN: Let's move one line back...
(They adjust positions for effects)
STAFF: A bit more back.
TRAINEE: We can do it, we can do it.
HYUNJUN: Are you okay?
TRAINEE: Ready.
JUSTIN: You have to keep smiling.
(Before starting the final rehearsal)
HYUNJUN: Just once, let's do it once.
(The Class '90 gathers instinctively)
(Hype-up chant)
HYUNJUN: Five, six, seven, eight.
ALL: A.U.I!
(Their chant is always slightly off)
(Friends cheer like it's overtime in a soccer match)
ALL: Yay!
TRAINEE: We can do it, we can do it!
(Compared to the original "You, In the Fantasy")
(Choreography has many
more jumping and lifting sections)
HANBI: Wow, it looks exhausting just watching.
SONGHA: It's not over, it's not over!
(Shaking his head)
SONGHA: But honestly,
"You, In the Fantasy" is really hard.
HANBI: Right.
(Finally, the rehearsal ends)
TRAINEE: Ending fairy HYUNJUN.
TRAINEE: Nice!
SONGHA: It's tough though.
(Only heavy breathing)
(And body heat remain on stage)
TRAINEE: No.
(Though it feels like they're out of breath)
(Thanks to the staff)
ALL: Thank you.
JUSTIN: Thank you!
(They were completely worn out when exiting)
(Even though it's not an easy situation)
KASSHO: I feel good.
KASSHO: Too, too much.
(Every stage is precious to them)
HYUNJUN: Indeed, the '90s are really not easy.
(The era when only the strong survived)
TRAINEE: It's really tough.
HYUNJUN: While dancing, its...
(Leg injury)
HYUNJUN: Its leg fell off.
HYUNJUN: It might need surgery.
(What a fragile doll)
(Next is Class '00 camera rehearsal)
SONGHA: We... mood, mood!
TRAINEE: Fighting!
SONGHA: It's all about expressions for us!
SONGHA: We're different from the '90s!
TRAINEE: It's pretty.
STAFF: The outfits look great.
(A sudden compliment)
TRAINEE: Totally cool, right?
HANBI: A little...
HANBI: Doesn't it look mature?
STAFF: G.O.D has that mature vibe.
STAFF: Cool.
HANBI: Thank you.
TATA: Thank you!
STAFF: No, that compliment was for HANBI.
(What a bad person...)
DANIEL: What expression should we have today, HARUTA?
HARUTA: Sexy!
HARUTA: That's the way to go.
JAEWON: Who's the sexiest here?
HARUTA: First of all!
HARUTA: It's me.
DANIEL: I knew it.
(Love Myself)
HARUTA: First one is me.
HAMIN: I wasn't even expecting it.
HARUTA: You're cute.
(Cuteness)
HARUTA: You two are cute.
JAEWON: You mean there's no chance?
HAMIN: You're cute!
JAEWON: He said you're cute.
(The second sexy person is)
HARUTA: I'll pick DANIEL.
(DANIEL!)
HAMIN: Why me?
DANIEL: Looks like you know your stuff.
HAMIN: Why don't you say anything to me?
(Sulking)
(Good-looking, sexy, beautiful, tall, his nose
could be a slide, hair as dark as Snow White's,)
(jawline so sharp it could be a knife, eyelashes
so long they could be used as an umbrella in the rain,)
(lips so pretty it's a shame the mic covers them,
neck so long and beautiful that passing giraffes got jealous)
(and when in Kenya, if you fall into his eyes,
you'll never hit the bottom...)
(Meanwhile, Five Boys Over Flowers
come for camera rehearsal)
SONGHA: Yes, please take care of us.
(There's no one in the audience seats now)
(But there are die-hard fans backstage)
(Completely immersed...)
(Faithful to the lyrics)
(Showing off stainless gloves)
(Excited in mesh outfits)
(When the song ends)
(The ending fairy they wanted to try)
(Ha...ah!)
(The younger ones beside them)
(Warmly wrapping HARUTA)
(Gradually turning into moans)
HAMIN: We have to let him go!
CHARLIE: HARUTA, you have to go.
HAMIN: We have to let him go.
HAMIN: You have to go, HARUTA.
(They're sending off a perfectly fine guy)
DANIEL: What's wrong with them?
(Five Boys Over Flowers camera rehearsal ends!)
ALL: Thank you!
HANBI: "CALL ME BABY", fighting!
DANIEL: I'm most nervous about "CALL ME BABY"!
DANIEL: It's so scary performing "CALL ME BABY"!
(Covering seniors' stages is always nerve-wracking)
CHARLIE: It's cold.
TRAINEE: Hello.
(It's only a camera rehearsal,
but they still walk in feeling nervous)
DANIEL: Hello.
TRAINEE: Hello.
HAMIN: Rehearsal...
("CALL ME BABY" camera rehearsal begins)
TRAINEE: Energy.
- HARUTA: Don't get hurt.
- DANIEL: Expression.
- HARUTA: Energy.
DANIEL: Smile!
CHARLIE: Yes, sir!
(Bright smiles)
(Winks)
HYUNJUN: Wow, HAMIN is so cool!
KASSHO: That's insane.
JUSTIN: This is great!
(Spoiler from someone who saw it)
JUSTIN: Tan-tan-tan, hey!
TRAINEE: "CALL ME BABY" is awesome!
DANIEL: What?
(Voice source: HYUNJUN)
HYUNJUN: "CALL ME BABY" is awesome!
DANIEL: I know it too.
DANIEL: They say it's awesome, hehe.
(At this moment, encouragement
is more valuable than rivalry)
HAMIN: Too much.
(After pouring out sweat)
STAFF: Good work.
(Camera rehearsal ends)
ALL: Thank you.
HAMIN: Thank you.
(About to enter)
(When one person greets)
ALL: Thank you.
(Everyone follows endlessly)
HAMIN: Thank you.
TRAINEE: Good job!
(Camera rehearsal for each class stage ends)
HYUNJUN: That was awesome.
TRAINEE: That was awesome.
HYUNJUN: I saw you smiling.
HYUNJUN: You were awesome!
DANIEL: No...
WOOLIN: So cool!
(Hardcore fans giving personal comments)
WOOLIN: Wow, that was really cool.
HYUNJUN: Exactly.
HYUNJUN: Our DANIEL is cool, right?
(It's me saying thanks?)
(Me too...)
HYUNJUN: Please give lots of love.
HYUNJUN: A.U.I class will win anyway!
WOOLIN: Even second place...
HYUNJUN: Even second place...
(Gradually shrinking wish)
STAFF: Did you finalize the closing greetings?
SONGHA: Yes.
SONGHA: We're just getting started.
(Each member is given 10 seconds
for the closing greetings)
SONGHA: We still have so much to show.
SONGHA: Please support us until the end.
SONGHA: Please get home safely.
SONGHA: Take care not to catch a cold.
SONGHA: Bye!
TRAINEE: Isn't it over 10 seconds?
SONGHA: No, it was exactly 10 seconds.
HANBI: Want me to count?
SONGHA: Okay.
(Counting to ensure it lasts ten seconds)
HANBI: Five, six, seven, eight.
(The comment is)
HANBI: Ten.
(That long)
SONGHA: Now, we're just getting started.
HANBI: nine,
(How is he)
HANBI: eight,
(Supposed to...) - HANBI: seven,
- SONGHA: We have a lot we couldn't show you yet,
(Huh?) - HANBI: six,
- SONGHA: please watch until the end.
(No way)
HANBI: five,
(This is) - HANBI: four,
- SONGHA: Be careful on your way back.
(Actually worked?) - HANBI: three,
- SONGHA: Be careful not to get a cold.
(He even has time)
- HANBI: two, - SONGHA: Bye!
(To spare)
HANBI: one.
HANBI: Oh, it matches perfectly.
SONGHA: This is what it means to be a pro!
(Camera rehearsal all done)
TRAINEE: Two, three!
ALL: Thank you.
TRAINEE: Fighting for tomorrow!
(Resolving to fight on tomorrow)
ALL: We'll do our best tomorrow!
HANBI: Thank you! Everyone, you've worked hard.
HANBI: Thank you!
DANIEL: See you again tomorrow!
(See you tomorrow, let's head home for now)
ALL: Thank you.
NICHOLAS: Let's go, let's go.
(Even though it's October...)
DANIEL: Happy New Year!
(Happy New Year in advance)
NICHOLAS: Let's go, let's go.
HYUNJUN: Thank you.
(Staff member's birthday today)
DANIEL: Happy birthday!
NICHOLAS: We have to go, we have to go.
(Go home now)
HYUNJUN: Have a good day!
STAFF: It's over, it's done!
HANBI: It's over now.
(Thanking the backstage staff)
HANBI: You've worked hard.
STAFF: Well...
STAFF: You know it's not really over, right?
(Since it's not really over, another thank you)
DANIEL: It's over.
STAFF: It's not over!
TRAINEE: It's finished.
TATA: Isn't it over?
(Confusion due to over-immersion)
DANIEL: A whole month-long journey!
(Today's business is over. Please head back)
STAFF: It's over for today, you did well.
(After the camera rehearsal...)
JUSTIN: Today, there were some parts that felt lacking
JUSTIN: and parts I want to improve,
JUSTIN: so,
JUSTIN: I'll do image training until tomorrow
JUSTIN: and do well on stage tomorrow.
(Next Episode Preview)
(School Festival D-day)
TRAINEE: WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL!
(The day of the school festival has arrived)
ALL: Hey, hey, hey! Fighting!
HYUNJUN: Oh, oh!
HANBI: Oh!
(Watching the audience enter one by one)
TRAINEE: Awesome.
(Festival atmosphere even before starting)
HANBI: I suddenly feel nervous.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
(Joy quickly turns into nervousness)
TATA: Oh, I'm nervous.
HYUNJUN: Start, start.
(Heart racing uncontrollably as the start approaches)
TRAINEE: Let's go!
WOOLIN: Fighting!
(Full of nerves and excitement)
JUSTIN: Fighting!
(They step onto their own stage)
(Moments made more fun together)
TRAINEE: Being able to talk, listen,
TRAINEE: and enjoy the stage together...
HYUNJUN: Your...
JUSTIN: No, that's the wrong pitch.
CHARLIE: Actually, HYUNJUN too.
(They keep bickering even today)
CHARLIE: He's the loudest one.
HYUNJUN: You're louder.
(Yet filled with friendship)
JUSTIN: We're going.
KASSHO: Well done.
HAMIN: Good job.
DANIEL: This is the most fun!
(An unforgettable memory for everyone)
ALL: Thank you.
(The final story of WOOJEONG HIGH SCHOOL is coming)
(And still remaining)
HANBI: Hey, we don't know yet, we don't know.
(Final winning class announcement)
TEACHERS' OFFICE: We'll reveal the final results immediately.
JUSTIN: Please...
HAMIN: Please!
TEACHERS' OFFICE: First place is...
(Which class is the ultimate winner?)
TEACHERS' OFFICE: It's...
(Ending song: "Into The New World")
=Reply High School=