Cherry Boy Diner
Here, eat up.
This is a hamburger.
Drink this, too.
Do you have somewhere to go?
Can you wash dishes?
Honey.
You know I can't work
for the time being.
We can't pay you.
But you can eat and sleep here.
You're back.
Leave it.
Where have you been?
It's been a whole week.
I've always been gone.
Why care all of a sudden?
Pest control.
What?
I got rid of some bugs.
I see.
Let me see.
How clumsy.
- Honey.
- All right, boys.
This place is pretty good.
- Did your trip go okay?
- There, there, it's okay.
Hey, Cherry Boy! Where have you been?
Wow.
You know, your girls were very
lonely when you were gone, but, uh...
Don't worry, man. I took care of that.
Thanks. Have a seat.
- Hello, sweetie.
- Who are you?
What are you doing?
What? It's okay. It's okay.
- Let go.
- No, it's okay.
Stop, stop!
Don't worry.
Oh, is that for me? You
want to really piss me off?
Fuck! Jesus!
Come here!
You're fucking dead!
Please forgive me! Don't make me leave.
Please let me stay here.
- I'm sorry...
- It's all right.
You killed a bug, that's all.
Nails.
From now on, that's your name.
The Old Woman with the Knife
Sir, what are you doing?
What are you staring at? I'm
elderly, so get up right now!
Show some goddamn respect!
Looking down at your phone
as if you don't give a shit.
This seat is designated
for pregnant women like me.
How should I know if that's a baby
or if it's full of food you
shoved down your throat?
- Show me then!
- Stop that!
I said, I'm pregnant.
There's a man in that designated
seat, so why bother me?
Why, you little!
What are you glaring at?
Girls these days don't get married,
don't have kids,
and just want to mooch off men.
And they play the pregnancy
card when it's convenient for them!
- What?
- Can you quiet down?
What?!
The exit is to your right.
If you wish to go to Bomin
Hospital, please get off at this stop.
This stop is...
Gosh, you old hag.
Give me some damn space, will you?
- Coming through.
- Excuse me, I'm getting off.
Jeez, move aside.
- Excuse me.
- My goodness!
I'm sorry.
Hello? Sir?
It wasn't me, I swear!
Just a moment.
You said you'd help my son.
- Ma'am, you can't do this.
- Can you please help me?
- It'll be quick.
- You can't.
- I know this is Sinseong Agency.
- No, it's not.
- You've got the wrong place.
- Just hear me out!
Hornclaw.
Snake plants are easy to grow.
It's perfect for beginners.
I bought it for you, though. Take it.
It only needs water twice
a year. And it even flowers.
Jeez.
She just doesn't get it...
You have to be familiar
with growing plants to like it.
I'm afraid I'll kill that thing,
so take it home today.
Greenleaf. All she sees is bright red.
It's nice to see something green.
That way, she can see beyond her world.
Your estrogen is spiking.
And why care for her so much?
She's always cold in return.
How would you know?
- The weight of time.
- Weight of time?
Exactly.
Gosh, stop wearing knockoffs.
It looks so cheap.
Hey, this is authentic.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello, Gadget.
Long time no see, Sohn.
Can I have a word with you?
Pest Control Target: Chairman Shim
This isn't pest control.
It's just murder-for-hire.
His mistress ruined
his wife of 30 years.
Getting rid of blood-sucking
vermin like him
is exactly what pest control is.
Request: Painful Death, Leave
Behind Will, Retrieve Wedding Ring
She says pain is building
up every day like mileage.
Did she give you money?
I said no, but she insisted.
She even bawled her eyes out.
How can we run this
place without these funds?
- If Godmother finds out...
- Gadget.
Flies are pests, right?
They feed on dead bodies
and transmit diseases.
You know,
they've been around a long
time, spreading pollen.
They're useful bugs,
managing the ecosystem.
Who cares how dirty it is
when it's helpful to us?
We just need to retrieve the ring.
Let's forget this.
Gadget.
Pest Control Report
15 mg of Botulinum Toxin
on a crowded subway...
Okay, there we go. We're done.
There you go. Good girl.
The surgery went well.
You did a great thing.
People feel bad for injured strays,
but it's not easy to
actually save them.
All right, then.
Ma'am.
This one's already so old,
so the shelter probably won't take her.
Adoption will be hard, too.
They may have to put her down.
So, could you make a call for me?
- For what?
- The shelter won't reject her
if the rescuer calls.
Is this part of your job?
It's awful to be abandoned just
because you're old and sick.
She's already been
abandoned once. Right?
It's okay, you'll find a good owner.
Hold on.
Stay there. Good girl.
Is this going to hurt a lot?
I heard they cut you open
while you're still awake.
We'll stitch you up
nicely. Don't worry.
Please spare me!
Please!
- You're fine, kid.
- I'm sorry.
Jeez, scared the shit out of me.
Sorry.
Don't be so scared. It'll be fine.
Do you by any chance
want to sell one of your corneas, too?
Right now?
It's a headache for us too,
but the client is insisting.
How much for one?
It's 50 million for the kidney,
and I'll add on three big ones.
- Thirty million?
- Yes.
- That's no good.
- Why? What is it?
Look, sir.
I'll be living with one eye for
life. How will 30 million help?
Huh?
Glasses are so expensive these days,
so why go so cheap for a cornea?
All right, then.
I'll give you a big one.
- Ten.
- Ten big ones?
Ten seconds.
For me to kill you.
Fucking bastard!
What are you doing? Who sent you?
I heard you pulled out an eye recently.
By taking someone else's client.
Did that bastard Park send you?
So, why steal clients from friends?
- Okay.
- You'll see each other soon in hell.
Is Park dead, too?
You must have a specific
goal for you to go this far.
My goal? To become famous.
This is where sensitive
nerves are. You like that?
Please, spare me...
That, I can't do.
All I know is to kill slowly...
and painfully.
Where did he go?
What the...
Stop!
Okay! Stop!
You've trespassed. This is my turf.
Just as bold as I had heard.
You've heard of me?
An from Banpo, Yoon from Dongtan.
And even Gu, today.
Aren't you wasting your
skills on silly street fights?
So, you're a stalker fan?
Farewell.
Hold on!
Wait, hold on!
Let's talk, okay?
Let's settle with this.
Are you sure? I don't go for cheap.
- I said no. Why do you keep doing this?
- Why not?
You know he's a disgusting pest.
So, why say no?
I know what you mean, but
you've got the wrong place.
I'll do whatever you say.
- Please kill him.
- You need to leave, now.
I can't.
I have to kill that
bastard, Han Seong-do.
I can't leave... My poor son...
Have you had something to eat?
If not, join us.
Isn't this a hassle?
It's easier to use the app.
You're the only one who does this.
This is going to take forever.
Declined
You cleaned it all up, right?
Any cameras or witnesses?
I mean,
I don't get why the client
asked us to kill him
- in such a crowded place.
- Don't worry.
I'll leave before I become useless.
I didn't mean that.
Is this about the woman out there?
It's nothing.
It's a woman named Madam Hong.
Her son's girlfriend
fell victim to druggies.
She died of an overdose.
The son barged in, got pounded,
and now he's in a coma.
I get why she's so upset.
But it's a tricky case,
so Sohn declined.
Satisfied?
By the way, I booked you a health
exam at Dr. Chang's hospital.
Mr. Sohn's orders.
You were showing off.
As if you wanted someone
to acknowledge you.
You chase after targets
and pressure them
until they're about to turn crazy,
then kill them in the most
painful way possible.
And that's why you're called Bullfight.
Enough with the crap. Get to the point.
Instead of those useless,
meaningless jobs,
join us in the good
cause of pest control.
Pest control?
To kill off insects?
Exactly. The cockroaches
of our society.
We seek to exterminate them
and save people from suffering.
Goodness.
Is this a house of salvation?
Come on.
You can't just leave.
You prick!
Then I'll kill you and leave.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Bullfight, you can't do this here.
I get that this place is serious.
He was just kidding around.
Cut him some slack.
Watch who you hire.
There's a lot of protein precipitate
in your cerebrospinal fluid.
Any hand or foot tremors lately?
No, not at all.
Here, the color shows
significant degeneration.
Don't tell the agency for now.
I can't do that.
Then today will be the
last time I see you.
What's your next mission?
You have to take it easy.
Have I ever taken it easy?
That damn old coot.
Where did he hide it?
For goodness' sake!
Can't you stuff your face
without being so damn loud?
This smell.
I'm sick of it!
Why bother living?
Why is this disconnected?
Who are you?
What do you want?
I'll do whatever you ask.
I'm sure those old folks did
whatever you asked, too.
So, why did you kill them?
You mean Granny Park?
Come on, sir.
They let me go without any charges.
You'll wish that they hadn't.
Start the car.
Silver Life Care Center
Dad!
- Dad!
- Eun-ho.
It wasn't me.
Eun-ho, it wasn't me!
What's with you?
Come on, stay still.
Don't look at me like that. You
forget things when you're old.
A woman in her forties
died in this accident.
According to witnesses,
a prospective suspect was seen near
the vehicle just before the accident.
The suspect parked the
car at this intersection
and left the victim in the car,
aware of the approaching train.
- The suspect chased after the witness
- Crazy world, right?
up to a nearby police
station and then ran away.
The police are suspecting this
to be a cover-up suicide case
and are looking for the suspect,
- who is a male in his mid-fifties.
- Have a nice day.
You're ten minutes early.
I work on a timely schedule.
Did your boss not train you?
How rude. So...
What the...
Staged Train Accident,
Police Hunting Down Killer
How shameful, for someone
who's been so dedicated...
It's not easy for me either.
But a single stone can
flip over a whole car.
Rules are rules.
- I'll send someone.
- No, I'll do it.
You, Godmother?
Well, I'd be grateful, but...
Where will you find him?
It's obvious where he'll go.
Old people need a lot of care.
Will it be okay?
You know,
"the weight of time."
You're back.
How was it? Did it go well?
Well, I got rid of your headache.
But I guess you weren't waiting for me.
Oh, what the...
What's this?
We asked for the ring, not his fingers.
Check if I got all 28 pieces.
Mr. Sohn.
Could I have a word with you?
You here for me, Godmother?
What an honor.
What happened?
I saw Eun-ho.
She died. Ten years ago.
If only she hadn't met
that damned preacher...
I wouldn't have had so much rage.
Then perhaps my life
could have been different.
You walked the path given to you.
There's nothing more to life and death.
Just leave, please!
Kill me before you go.
You think I can't?
You think I can't kill you?
I told you to stay calm.
- Or you can't see clearly.
- Don't you get it?
Not everyone can live
as heartlessly as you.
You ruined the mission
because of your feelings.
By the rules, you must die.
This was going to be my last mission.
I was going to grow some flowers
and open a fried chicken place.
So...
You two bore me to death.
Who are you?
Who the heck are you?
We've met before.
Move.
This is my job.
But it's mine, too.
Did Sohn send you?
If you had handled your job properly,
I wouldn't have had to come.
So much for being a legend.
Hair turning white, and wrinkles, too.
Getting so old already?
Shut up.
I don't need any backup.
Then finish this.
Since it's your job.
They say that when it's time...
those you miss come out to greet you.
I think my daughter was there...
to tell me it's time.
That I've done enough.
She was there to greet me.
Dr. Chang
The person you are calling
is currently unavailable...
Sir, she's still not picking up.
- Let's go back.
- No, we'll finish the job.
What if something's wrong?
Nobody's answered at home all day.
Emergency Medical Center
I told you, no excuses are
allowed at the edge of your knife.
- No matter who you face.
See what happens when you
open up to other people's stories?
Remember.
Don't shoot a butterfly with a gun.
What the hell?
Let's go now.
Don't move. I barely patched it...
What are you up to?
I heard a screech
and noticed a car on
the side of the road.
I peeked in and found you there.
You refused to go to the
hospital, then passed out.
It's an 8-cm lacerated wound,
including a cut to your right lat.
It barely missed your organs,
which is why you survived.
Forgive me for cutting your clothes
off. They were drenched in blood.
Where's my stuff?
I kept them safe.
You shouldn't do this.
You already bled too much.
Oh my. Bear with me.
What happened today...
Everyone has their own story.
Put this on before the nurses arrive.
I'll pack you some meds.
You're late.
You sent a backup.
Why?
You don't trust me?
The tide is high,
and I can't have you swept away.
You're a great asset to this agency.
Why is this knife so dull?
It may look dull...
But it's still plenty useful.
Right.
By the looks of it,
you picked up random strays
and gave them all kinds of jobs.
But our job is sacred,
eradicating malignant vermin.
For instance,
pest-controlling those druggies
who scammed a naive kid
and drove her to her death.
The jobs you've been rejecting are
what we're supposed to be doing.
Jeez, you're so frustrating.
Those druggies are pretty
much like the mafia.
One bite and we're dead, like
eating toxins in a blow fish.
What do you want me to do?
How convenient, cherry-picking jobs.
It's my authority.
And authority comes
with responsibility.
Then try it yourself!
Sure, why not?
And about Bullfight,
he has a clean background
with great skills.
Accept him as one of us and
cook him a meal sometime.
Your father looks so
young in that picture.
Were you in diapers then?
Right!
You were in your prime, too!
What's the rush?
Hang around a bit more.
Why don't you grow out your nails?
What?
They used to be fancy.
Try painting them.
Why?
You want me to rip off your face?
You have something
to do before that, no?
You got your wounds treated like a dog.
Which means...
you left a witness.
If the agency knew, wouldn't
you end up like Gadget?
Now I see who you are.
You do? Me?
I do.
A brat with a death wish.
Right.
You may be past your prime, but I
heard whoever crosses you is dead.
I know many specialists look up to you.
Then stay out of my sight, okay?
If you wish to live long.
Watch who you hire.
That would be my business, Godmother.
Do you want to die, you crazy bastard?
If not for money or justice,
then why are you here?
For the legend.
You came to the right place.
I like the look in your eyes.
Pest Control Report
Pest Control Target
Boss, Madam
Driver's License
Press Card
Registration Card
Pest Control Report: Moon
Hornclaw, Pine Tree Hornclaw
Mountain Hornclaw
Pest Control Target: Bae Jong-sun
Request: Crush Skull
The 4th Unnatural Death Case
A Child Neglected After Father's Death
From Orphanage to Asylum
Assigned To: Hornclaw
What should I do with you?
Animal Hospital
Don't be picky with food, okay?
Yes, sir!
Right back at you, Daddy.
All right, see you later.
I want the truth and an apology
for the sudden death of my wife
in the hospital during her surgery
Hey, get rid of that!
- Yes, ma'am.
- Apologize.
What are you talking about?
- Apologize!
- You should know better!
Seriously, stop it!
Apologize!
Hae-ni's Fruit Shop
Hello.
Hi.
Oranges, Watermelon, Peaches
Oh my, welcome!
These peaches are in season.
They're as sweet as sugar.
- I'll take some, then.
- How many?
Is four enough?
That's a lot.
You'll eat them all in no time.
Quite good for a seven-year-old, right?
Thanks.
Her mom is an angel?
Yes, because she's in heaven.
What happened?
Her surgery went wrong,
so she spent five years on
a sickbed and then left us.
Since then, my son-in-law
can't sleep at night.
That's why he always
takes night shifts.
And he's been
protesting alone for years,
which is meaningless.
He says he does it to
honor the deceased.
Goodness me, I talked too much.
Take this too, a bruised one.
People don't buy these
because they're blemished,
but they actually taste better.
- Thank you.
- Please come again.
Look, Hae-ni.
Your dad is here.
Hae-ni.
Daddy!
Why are you so late?
- Have you eaten?
- Yes.
- I missed you.
- Hold on, Hae-ni.
Ma'am!
Why did you come?
My family has nothing
to do with anything.
Why?
What?
You saw what I carry around.
But you're a good person.
You saved a stray dog.
I'm not a good person.
Only good people can say that.
How's Braveheart?
Braveheart?
She seemed brave, so I...
You're bad at giving names.
Why don't you want to see a doctor?
My company might lay me off.
It must be a scary place if you're
worried about such a thing.
Then stop by my clinic
if your wound worsens.
And take Braveheart out
for a walk from time to time.
I don't know what to call you.
Could you tell me your name?
Do you think I'm a good person, too?
Braveheart.
Okay, you're Braveheart from now on.
This building has stood for
40 years on this costly land.
It'd be great to demolish it
and build something new.
Not as easy as it sounds?
This gimp was born as prey,
and an old lioness is blocking its way.
I think her claws have fallen out.
She's never made any mistakes?
She was perfect. Unbelievably so.
A living legend, who
fascinated and terrified us.
They were all captivated by that story.
Jeez, what happened?
There was this guy named
Ryu who built this place.
You prick...
I was late because
of the prayer ritual.
To make sure that my family
goes to heaven.
When he died,
Godmother wiped out 28 men
all by herself for revenge.
She sure did.
Then she changed her name
from "Nails" to "Hornclaw."
But that was ages ago.
Expired waste should be
disposed of, don't you think?
Hello, ma'am.
Hello, Granny.
Oh, hi.
- On a walk with Braveheart?
- Yes.
Can I play with her?
- Hae-ni.
Sure.
Here you go.
Let's go, Braveheart.
Hae-ni, don't go too far.
Okay.
Your girl seems smart.
She's a lot like her mom.
My mother-in-law told you, right?
She was fine, and then suddenly...
The head of that hospital said,
"Everyone who's after money
always starts by asking
for a heartfelt apology."
Back then...
I wanted to end it all.
Or actually, I wanted to...
Kill her?
Would you eat with us?
We're on our way to lunch.
No, I'll just...
You're back.
Come with us. We all
need to eat, you know.
Sorry, but I should just go.
Pretty please.
Come with us.
I have a recital next week.
You should come, too.
Sorry, but I can't go
to places like this.
But I practiced my dance really hard.
Hae-ni, what's with you today?
Please don't mind her.
Eat up.
Hornclaw.
What?
My name.
One claw, two claws, three claws,
- four claws...
- Hae-ni.
It means the claws of a beast.
Is that so?
- I didn't know.
- Look over here!
Don't do that without
permission, Hae-ni.
See? Looks good, right?
Give me your number.
I'll send it to you.
Hae-ni.
Sorry about that.
Oh my gosh. Daddy, look.
Someone broke that and ran away.
Isn't that expensive?
Hello.
How can I help you?
Dr. Kang Bong-hwe, Veterinarian
There's this old hound...
An old woman I know.
She's been acting strange these days.
Why is that?
Sorry?
She's shaken by trivial things.
Gets scared often.
Or craves food she never liked.
You'll have to visit somewhere
else for psychogenic illnesses.
This is a hospital, though.
We only treat animals.
Aren't humans...
animals, too?
They are, but I can't treat them.
That's weird.
Pretty sure I saw you treat people.
Hello.
Oh, hello.
- She won't eat anything.
- Oh no.
It must've been tough. Come inside.
Okay.
I'm sorry, sir.
I want some strawberries.
Strawberries are out of season.
What about Jeju oranges?
These California oranges are sweeter.
Come on, that can't be.
Sir, look.
Come to my recital next week.
Sorry, I'm too busy.
Come on, I practiced my dance so hard.
Really? Can you show me?
- So good, sweetie.
- Wow, you're so good.
That fruit shop owner
sure is good at her game.
What are you up to?
This is old, wrinkled, and bruised,
but she said it tastes the same.
She said people only buy
the pretty and fresh ones
because they don't know.
If you ever lay hands
on Dr. Kang's family...
You're serious, huh?
That nerd must be a real charmer,
melting even your ice-cold heart.
I'll leave, so stop it.
What?
If I leave, there will be no
threat to Sinseong Agency,
and that innocent man will be safe.
I don't like that.
You'll lay down your knife
and retire all because of him?
Now that you're old,
did feelings invade your body like
germs through your chapped skin?
Are you drowning in pity, guilt,
protectiveness, or some shit?
What is your goal here?
My goal?
People are funny.
Even when they're lost, they
ask where others are going.
Do you even know where you're headed?
Well...
Age doesn't matter.
You can look all you like.
But you don't deserve him.
See this?
Who would pay the same money for this?
Get some rest.
I'm fine.
I'll get you a new ID and a ticket.
No need.
I'll stay where I want to.
Do as you wish.
But from now on,
you and I both...
will make sure to never
have anything to protect.
It's been ten years already.
Great work.
Protect Sinseong Agency with that.
I want the truth and an apology
for the sudden death of my wife
in the hospital during her surgery
Hey, watch it!
I have the worst luck today.
- Ma'am!
What's wrong, ma'am?
Pest Control Target
Request: Crush Skull in Front of Child
Guess this is a serious grudge.
In front of his child?
Can't say.
The client wants full confidentiality,
so I can't tell you much.
Why not give it to
your loyal Bullfight?
Client requested a female specialist
of similar age to the victim,
which is why I'm asking you in person.
Rather than have someone
else make a mess of it,
I'd rather you handle this cleanly.
What the...
Who's the client?
Oh, Godmother...
Why are you doing this to me?
Why is Dr. Kang being targeted?
"Ask questions, and you'll
be killed on the spot."
You made that rule.
I didn't make that rule
just to catch some fish.
It was to take the ocean.
You don't even know which
way the ship is sailing!
The son of the hospital head said
that Dr. Kang killed his mom.
So, he's out for revenge.
And he dropped a fortune on it.
Dr. Kang is not that kind of person.
It did seem strange.
The so-called son of a hospital
head was wearing a fake watch.
Sohn said to take it
anyway. Money's money.
But just in case...
I did some digging.
Ten million? Raising it to
a hundred million, fucker.
Let's see how big your guts are.
Fuck, you in or out?
I'm all in, you bastard.
That fucking son of a bitch...
Who the hell are you? Hey!
Why did you put a hit on Kang Bong-hwe?
Who?
I don't know anything, really!
I was paid. I just followed orders.
By whom?
On the phone...
We talked on the phone.
My phone's in my back pocket.
- Call him.
- Yes, ma'am.
What's up?
There's a lady here...
Granny.
I don't think you have time
to fool around with that loser.
What do you want?
Equal ruin?
Dr. Kang's shift ends soon.
Want me to help you again?
Wait, hold up!
Thank you.
Are you okay?
- Hey, watch it.
- Sorry.
Sir!
No... Sir!
Please don't leave me here by myself!
I'm sorry...
What are you doing here?
- I'm so relieved.
- Pardon?
Please enjoy, from Braveheart's mom
You don't need to worry about us.
No, it's...
Wait.
Is there anything
you want to say to me?
You've lost weight.
Be sure not to skip meals.
So, is your heart racing?
Why make this so complicated?
There's no point
if you can't figure out
the reason on your own.
You should go rub him out.
Why waste time with me?
I wonder why.
Maybe I wanted to see the legend.
You must be disappointed.
I am.
In myself.
For spending my whole
life searching for such crap.
Stop this.
If you mean me, you already found me.
No.
I haven't found it yet.
This isn't the real fight.
Don't even think of retiring.
And also, you'll never beat me.
You've got something to protect,
while I've got nothing to lose.
Welcome.
This place is so nice.
Shall we sit here?
I can't wait any longer.
A daughter... No.
Two sons... No.
1998, 1999.
No...
Bae Jong-sun
Family: One Son
I'm your new housekeeper...
Hi there.
Allergic to pollen...
Son can't swallow
pills, grind into powder
Give me some water.
Will you eat?
No.
When does your dad get home?
After midnight.
Or sometimes not at all.
How long have you been working here?
Ten days?
Work's not too hard?
Goddammit.
I'm sorry. I'll clean it up.
Jeez, seriously?
Who the heck untied these shoelaces?
Blow to occipital and
parietal bone, crushed skull
So, he's aiming for
the back of my head.
Listen carefully.
If I don't come back,
you leave through there.
Don't starve like a
fool waiting for me.
Find a new owner or
rummage through the bins.
Do whatever it takes to survive.
Just don't let the dog catcher get you.
You're going to hit Han Seong-do's den?
I'm going to do a job
worthy of Sinseong Agency.
Killing pests and
saving people in pain.
Madam Hong's case is not as
simple as getting rid of one druggie.
Just rub out that vet
and be done with it.
Why poke at such a big wasp nest?
It'll be war if you screw up there.
You may be the Godmother,
but you can't do that job alone.
This will be my last job.
I'll disappear whether
I survive or not.
So, you can run this place from now on.
If you're that worried, send a backup.
That guy, Bullfight.
This is so sudden. What
am I supposed to say?
Come on, get a hold of yourself.
- Bon apptit!
- Thank you for the food!
What the hell?
Are you happy living off
of others' blood and tears?
An old hag?
What bastard hired a hag like you?
Who was it?
Oh Gwang-ryul? Jeon In-deuk?
Surely not Madam Hong?
It doesn't matter who kills you.
What matters is why you're dying.
Boss!
Hey! Prepare this old hag's funeral!
Godmother!
You can't do this.
I know you're the Godmother,
but it's too dangerous.
You'll die there!
Do as you fucking wish.
Hey! Get her!
Get her!
Hurry, find her!
- What the...
- What the heck?
Hurry up!
Where's Bullfight?
What about him?
Where is he right now?
Why the hell would I send our
next ace into that death trap?
And Godmother, everyone has
their own quota of goodwill.
You're letting Dr. Kang live because
of something personal, right?
And that's why you want to quit.
You've lived too long, dear Godmother.
You!
I got her.
In front of Room Four.
If you're so old, just
die! Why bother living?
Look here, Mr. Sohn.
This is so out of line. How much
have you earned from me?
How dare you fucking trash
my business like this?
You've deserved to
die several times over.
Why complain in the face of such luck?
Let's meet to negotiate...
What the fuck?
So, are you going to apologize?
I'm tired. Let's just end this.
You disgusting vermin.
Snack on these on your way to hell.
Little worms, it's time to eat!
Pour it in every corner.
- Have fun!
- Goodbye, Granny.
- Hurry up, guys!
- Yes, sir!
Hey! Stop him!
I said stop, you prick!
Hey!
You're not done yet, right?
What? Are you her son?
Well, from the same family.
You son of a...
Where the heck is she?
Where are you?
Are you okay?
Die!
Are you worried?
Yes.
Then assign Bullfight as
backup. Do it yourself.
Sohn won't do it.
If I assign him, will he go?
Just do as I tell you.
I'll make you dinner.
In the condition you're in?
I can still cook a meal
for my colleague.
Ordinary people...
What?
I guess ordinary people...
must eat like this often.
What made you start this work?
To be useful.
One time when I was
young, I was so hungry
that I ate the neighbor's
bell flower roots.
But they turned out to be wild ginseng.
My family went broke paying it
back, and they kicked me out.
I worked as a maid
and kept getting beaten,
abandoned, and running away.
Everyone told me to go die.
Calling me the most
useless bitch in the world.
And when I was 16,
I met someone who took
me in as their family.
What is your name?
Min Seol-hwa.
What a pretty name!
He fed me,
housed me, and gave me work.
And he was the first
person to call me useful.
Don't dodge it like that.
Flash your reflexes like that,
and you're basically
screaming, "I'm a killer."
Hide it even if it means getting
your head bashed in. Got it?
Yes.
That's it for today.
I believe this work is sacred.
Each of us is saving the world.
Even if no one else knows.
I'm jealous.
I had that kind of
person in my life once.
Very briefly.
Tell me.
Do you remember when we first met?
Was it 25 years ago?
Hi there.
I'm sorry, Do-young.
Wow, this is so touching.
Then...
you must know why I came for you.
You won't feel better even
if you kill me yourself.
So, why be lame and leave
your ancient revenge to others?
You should torment me to the end.
If you just drink up
whatever's given to you,
you'll end up dead.
Especially from a colleague you trust.
You failed...
You failed on purpose?
Knowing I'd come?
Fifty-fifty.
But I knew you would find me.
That's why you made...
such a mess.
Think of it as being clawed by a beast.
See you in hell.
Your precious ace is history.
I shouldn't have accepted you here.
When did you ever accept me?
It was for us...
For Sinseong Agency!
I did all of that for us!
Sure, you did your best.
What do you think
your father would have done?
You'll do it, right?
All the work you couldn't finish?
Burn this place down.
And you leave here, too.
Hae-ni!
Daddy's here!
Look how cute your daughter is!
Did you see me?
Where is she?
- Hello.
- Hello, sir, ma'am.
Where's Hae-ni?
Hae-ni? She was the first one out.
- Then I'll check the restroom.
- Okay.
I'll look inside a bit more.
Hae-ni?
- Hello.
Got you!
I'm sorry.
You grabbed me so suddenly...
Haven't you gone too far?
She's just a little girl.
What...
Will you still keep pretending
after reading this?
I thought things over
at the gates of hell,
but I felt really bad for Hae-ni.
She'll most likely end up
alone just like we were.
I know because I've been there.
I'd be breaking my rule,
but I'm so upset, I can't help it.
That's the problem with humans.
When you're feeling down,
everything goes out the window.
You understand, right?
I'll throw the biggest party ever.
You come here alone.
To Happyland.
Who the heck are you? What do you want?
You can't call the police.
I'll bring her back.
Don't be ridiculous!
I'm reporting it right now.
Trust me.
Hae-ni will be safe.
It's me that he wants.
Please bring Hae-ni back, okay?
This is because I saved
you that day, isn't it?
You weren't supposed to be saved,
but I saved you, didn't I?
Even so, I don't regret treating you.
It was something I had to do.
Why isn't it moving?
Hi!
Braveheart, remember what I told you?
Braveheart...
Approaching target.
Copy. No blind spots.
All clear.
Third floor!
Spread out!
Target exposed! Fire!
Team B, entering the third floor.
Provide cover.
- Just shoot!
- Stairs on the third floor!
Help me...
Squeeze in from both sides!
Going in!
Come out!
No hurting children.
That's your rule, isn't it?
Don't kick her!
All right, then.
Drop your gun.
What took you so long?
I thought I'd die waiting.
So, this is the farce
that you prepared?
You worried my ancient revenge
would be lame, didn't you?
Sure.
These losers I'm working
with could do a lot better.
You've got some nerve!
- How dare you...
- Captain Lee.
I paid you in full in advance.
Is there a problem?
My guys are all dead
because of your stupid plan.
Didn't you know you were
just human shields?
Say that again, you...
You crazy bitch, you think
you're still the Godmother?
Get the hell up!
Hey, get up!
Get up!
Let go!
Shit!
I told you. You shouldn't
underestimate her.
I'll go up and pay you a generous fee.
Drive safe.
You fuckers!
Don't be so pathetic.
I'll cut off her ear.
The rest, too!
What should I do for
you to give her back?
Give her back?
Take her yourself.
Why do you keep bringing
Dr. Kang in between us?
That vet is someone to be protected,
and I'm trash to be cleaned up?
It seems so.
Why are you doing this to me?
Then what about you?
Aren't you waste to dispose of?
Since you're old and useless.
Someone said, even if
you're old and useless,
you shouldn't be thrown away.
You can never protect him.
I'll kill him. And his entire family.
You'll protect them like that?
Granny...
Keep this up,
and I'll throw her off.
- No...
- You're all dead, bastards!
What now?
The winner will have to take your car.
You didn't learn right.
If you treat others like vermin,
you become useless vermin yourself.
Sorry, I was self-taught.
Can I kill you?
Sure. Weren't you going to?
Where are you looking?
What the... Is that it?
You don't want it?
When does your dad get home?
After midnight.
Or sometimes not at all.
You should get to bed now.
By the way, what music
are you listening to?
This?
Listen when things are hard.
No, this isn't it.
Are you giving this to me?
It doesn't seem fair to keep two.
Should I drop one?
Do what you want.
But you'll regret it.
I gave it back to you.
Thanks for that.
Bae Do-young.
Didn't I tell you to come
out and greet me
as soon as I return
from work, you prick?
Who do you take after to be so weak?
You damn idiot!
Sir.
What the heck?
You're a legend. Is
this all you've got?
This is the police.
I've been kidnapped.
Please call my dad.
I'm Kang Hae-ni.
Please check my location
and come find me...
Remember. This is a
seed that you planted.
Unlike some people, I keep my promises.
"Promises"?
Have a good day!
Don't you get it yet?
So stupid!
Are you stalling for time?
For her?
For goodness' sake,
look at me.
Look at me!
Don't be too upset.
I'll be following you soon.
Finally...
you're here.
This time, I won.
Because...
I'm the one...
leaving you behind.
Have a good day.
Take your medicine at lunch.
Why were you good to me?
You didn't even...
recognize me.
Do-young, where are you going?
I forgot my indoor shoes!
You didn't see anything.
Forget all this.
Can I come with you?
Later, when you grow up.
I'll...
come find you.
For sure!
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I was scared.
What if...
you forgot about me?
Now you remember?
Yes.
How?
When it's your time to die,
your whole life flashes
before your eyes.
I promise.
One day, you'll be much
stronger than your dad.
Until then, hold tight to your grudge.
For today, sleep well.
Tomorrow will be better.
Can we...
What?
go to Happyland together?
Happyland?
The amusement park.
My friends all bragged about going.
Can we go?
Shall we?
Liar.
You never answered.
I guess it's not...
your time to go...
yet...
Can you
swallow your pills now?
He's a new member of our family.
I know I did something bad, but I
was mad that you'd leave me again.
Still, I'm sure you'll
be the one to survive
because you have people to protect.
Ryu.
This didn't happen to you because
you had something to protect.
In the end,
we all break and fade away.
You're back so early!
But maybe living on with
that loss isn't so bad after all.
- Hallelujah!
We sincerely welcome
the return of President Jee
- Amen.
Even when I was locked in prison,
those who sued me...
those hypocrites!
Whoever they were,
I never held a grudge.
- Amen!
My dear child.
Let me warm you up nice and toasty.
And Ryu...
It seems it's still not time
for me to join you yet.
Cult Leader and Founder Sexual assault
cases highlighted by recent media
Declined
Physical castration, removal of eyes
So much work to do.
Declined