Characters, behaviors, places, agencies, occupations and events
in this series are fictional and for entertainment purposes only.
It is not intended to promote any action in the series.
Viewers’ discretion is advised.
So? How's my home? You're all so stunned, aren't you?
So you're not gonna be doing anything else but drinking, three days straight?
How about this? If you're bored, then let's watch a movie.
Hey, I don't think that's the one.
What? What? A Porn? Phee, put that on!
Alright.
Who wore the mask?
Why haven't you ever brought him to us?
It's Non. He's not here anymore.
You two got in when we were in 12th grade so you never met him.
I think he might be dead already.
It may not be like that.
Your friend might just move. Don't overthink.
Hey, but I want to remake the film.
Right? Making new memory...
Why do we have to actually do this?
I just don't want him to get involved with what we have done.
If he finds out, and what?
It ended a long time ago.
I just wanted to know...that why you never wanted to ask me...
what we are for all these times?
Friends, indeed.
Hey!
It's like someone's watching us...
Who's that?
Shit!
Ahhhhh!
Por!
Hey, Por. C'mon!
Shit!
I think it's Non Ghost.
Because we continued filming the story that he wrote, it's cursed.
And he's now killing each one of us.
Ahhhhhh!
Did we really wake him up by continue shooting his movie?
Well, there was nothing before that.
Everything happened after we shot the movie.
We must break the curse.
We must destroy everything that belongs to Non.
Like, the hard disk.
So, what really happened to the guy named Non?
What did you three do to him?
I don't know. Ask someone else.
Destroy it.
Hey!
What the hell?
Are you guys that scared that it turned you nuts?
I'll look at it, no matter what.
Hey, what if something happens after we take a look at it?
Who will be responsible?
Then, we won't look at it. We'll wait for Uncle Dang to arrive,
get us out and then we'll have a look.
Tee, we made it!
Uncle Dang, this way! Uncle Dang!
We're in a big trouble, Uncle.
You must get us out of here ASAP.
Shit, Uncle Dang!
When I saw him, he was driving in.
When he was getting closer,...
it's just like what you saw.
What if this continues,
the next one is going to be one of us.
So the one who killed Uncle Dang and hurt Por
is still around here somewhere, right?
Then, I'll go out and get help.
No, Top. You'll run away alone for sure.
I wasn't running away.
If I were going to, would Tee and I turn around and come back?
Let Top go. The way in and out is so crooked.
Does any of us ride better than him?
Hey!
I don't think we should let him go alone.
What's the problem, Phee?
You don't trust your friend?
Trust?
Well, it was you two who were about to destroy the hard disk.
You both hid the truth from us,
and you wanted us to trust you?
I've told you the hard disk is cursed.
Oh, and is it? There's proof that it isn't.
Phee, why are you having so many issues with us?
Aren't you worried about Por, who's dying in the house.
Or do you want him dead?
Hey! That's enough!
How about I go with Top?
So Top can't run away.
Is that alright with you all?
Alright.
Hey, did you hear something?
Nope.
You didn't?
Phee, can I have the car key?
Shit!
It's the walkie-talkie.
1 to 2, do you copy? This is the valley mansion.
Anyone there? Over.
This is the valley mansion.
We need help immediately. Over.
Is anyone there? Do you copy? Over.
White, if we can't reach the outsiders,
can we tune them for us to communicate?
Here, Tan. I've already set the channel.
If you guys don't get too far from each other, you can still talk.
So everyone will feel better.
Alright.
C'mon.
This is scary.
Right.
Man!
C'mon. Just a bit.
Look at it.
Unbelievable.
Three years ago, you all came here to just shoot a short film?
So determined.
No, I think Por just wanted to brag about how wealthy his family was.
If the whole valley could be bought,
I think his Dad would really buy it all.
But what could we say?
They are really rich.
When Por wants something, his parents give him all.
Just shooting a lame short movie,
they bought a hundred-thousand Baht camera for him. That's nuts!
Right, about a guy named Non, what happened?
Why are you all so scared of him?
Or...did you do something to him?
Did you kill him?
I didn't kill him. No one killed anyone.
It's just that one day, he disappeared.
We did nothing to him.
You're not lying to me, are you?
Why would I like to you?
What will I get from lying to you?
Well, I just saw that you're scared of him getting back at you.
Alright, alright. Non and I used to have a bit of a problem.
But that passed a long time ago.
You don't need to know about it.
Okay.
Fuck, Tan.
Fuck! How should we go?
I guess we'll have to push it.
Come help me.
Damn it!
Lower. Move it lower.
One. Two. Three.
Let's go!
Okay.
C'mon, harder!
We're almost there.
Go. One, two...
C'mon. A bit more.
So what should we do with Uncle Dang's body?
We can't leave him like that.
Let's do what we gotta do.
I feel sorry for him.
I think we should carry his body into the house.
It's the least we can do.
Okay, let's do it.
No!
Don't touch Uncle Dang's body.
What if our fingerprints got on his body...or even DNA?
And there's an autopsy, we all will be doomed.
Then, burn him, so there won't be any fingerprints and the body.
Are you out of your mind?
You're just gonna burn him, just like that?
You treat him as if he's not a human being.
One more thing, we still don't know who did this to Uncle Dang.
Don't you wanna find the killer?
That's right, Tee. You can't do that.
This is considered concealment of the body.
But we can't leave him like this. What if his corpse attracts somewhat animal here?
We're in the middle of the woods.
Hey, don't you fucking get it? I've told you, don't touch him.
Or do you want to be the killer?
But when we lifted his motorbike, our fingerprints were already left there.
Don't worry about it.
We'll tell them that you guys had good intention.
Tee.
Hey.
Look.
Why don't you guys find something to cover his body?
His corpse is fucking scary.
Okay, got it.
Shoo! Go away!
We're so sorry, Uncle.
I'm sorry I put you through all this.
Actually, you didn't wanna come, but I kept asking you to come.
And now, we're in a dangerous place.
I'm sorry.
Just forget it. When you asked me, you didn't know
that things like this were gonna happen.
Now shit happened. We just gotta get through it.
You know I'm a fighter. And I’m always aware of things.
Should we try to reach Top and Tan to see where they are now?
Of course.
1 to 2. Top, can you hear me? Over.
Tan, can you hear me? Copy? Over.
Can't reach them. I guess they're out of range now.
Maybe, they're closer to the way out now.
That's good. They probably can get someone to save all of us.
It looks like there are no houses here.
Are we in the right direction?
I think it's the right direction...or is it not?
What? How would I know that.
I followed the route you told me.
Hey, hey, hey!
Ahhhhhhh!
Top, do you copy?
It's not working. What should we do?
We gotta help them.
White, you don't have to go. Stay here.
No, Tee. Let's go altogether.
I don't want to be alone and go nuts.
White, I think you should stay with Fluke to look after Por.
Jin, Tee, you two, come with me.
Show-off.
Help me! Top! Top's gone...
Phee, Phee, Jin!
Hey, shit!
Help me!
What hit you?
The motorbike fell...next thing Tan knew was Top was already gone?
Tell me exactly what happened.
Before the motorbike fell,
Top was scared of something so he pulled off the direction.
When I got up, he was nowhere to be found.
So I walked back to you guys first.
Or could Top be the next one?
Shit, I've told you it's cursed. He won't stop easily.
And now, he's doing it again.
That's on you, Phee. You let him go.
What? How did that have to do with me? Top volunteered.
Or could it be that that dumbass Top sneak out alone?
Because a guy like Top wouldn't miss a chance to get away.
He must have been waiting for the right timing, I think.
I don't think so.
If he really wanted to do that, he wouldn't have to let himself get hurt.
And what about the motorbike? Is it gone too?
I didn't see both Top and the motorbike.
If Tan hurts this much, how injured is Top going to be?
Then, I think we must do something.
Oh, shit.
Are we almost there?
We're in the right direction, aren't we?
If we get off this spot, we're there.
It's right here.
Around here.
Hey, Tan, look.
Is this where you guys fell?
Yeah, Top pulled out of the way, and we fell here.
From the tire print...
It's going that way.
So did Top really run away?
And left us all here?
But he didn't have to crash the motorbike, did he?
Look at his size, he could kick Tan off the road.
And one more thing, he's a coward.
He wouldn't dare run away alone in the woods like this.
Then, we should follow.
So we'd know if he really ran away,
or was it a setup of the ninth person.
Is it early morning or late night? I can't even tell.
I heard the thunder. Seems like it's about to rain.
Sadhu. I hope it's not gonna rain. We'll be in more trouble.
Look.
Or is this the legendary dwelling of Janta?
It looks like it's about to rain, Fluke.
Won't it be more difficult for us?
That time...
Por, what is it? Can you hear me?
I shouldn't have...taken his money...
Fluke, what did Por say?
Can you help me listen to him?
Move over.
Nothing, Por must be murmuring.
Sick people do that.
You were there too, Fluke.
Por, what is it?
Por, Por, can you hear me, Por?
Por!
The day Non...disappeared...
Ahhhhh!
Por!
Hey, Fluke, that's too harsh.
He'll bleed to death.
What was he saying earlier?
What was Por trying to say?
I couldn't catch it either.
But I think you should...go somewhere else first.
I'll clean the wound. And, you don't have to see something nasty.
Are you sure?
Yeah, just go already!
What are you doing?
Nothing. I'm just thinking whether I should stay and help you.
I said no. Didn't you hear that?
Just go take a shower and then we'll switch.
Hurry up and come back.
Don't fall asleep anywhere.
Sorry for intrusion. But for your life's sake, I have to look.
Shit, it's broken.
Fuck, it's blood.
Fuck!
This is Top's wallet chain.
Must be his blood.
He must be badly injured. I was riding with him and look at how bad I am.
He's the rider. I don't know if he's alive.
If this really is Top's blood, if he bleeds this much, how can he walk?
I think if he does walk, he won't be far.
The engine won't start.
The rider is gone.
Or is he trying to escape from something?
What makes Top like this?
I don't know. But I think he must be inside.
He's hurt and on foot. He can't be far away.
Shit.
Shit, where could he go?
Hey, calm down.
Top!
What the hell is this?
This is the cult that Por said.
This is for real, man. This is the real deal here.
Or the one who took Top was really the ghost from the legend?
I don't know. Whether it's a human or a ghost,
we must find Top and bring him home.
That's easy to say, but what can we do?
We don't know where Top went.
The fastest way to find him is to split up.
If we do that, it will be exactly like in a horror movie.
I agree with Phee. It's too dangerous if we split up.
So do I. We'll stay alive together, we'll die if we separate.
It's really dark out there, and I don't know what's inside.
I know that everyone's scared now,
but it's Top's life we're talking about.
The sooner we find him, the better, right?
But if another one of us disappears, we'll be fucked.
You know you have asthma, yet you still smoke.
I'm smoking because I'm scared.
If I don't smoke, I can't control myself.
What's that smell?
...No.
Dust...
What's that box?
This is...
Ahhhhh!
Por!
This is fresh blood.
Or Non sold his soul to the devil and gave his life for sacrifice?
Leave Non out of this for once.
We're looking for Top. Focus!
Hey, Tee!
You guys, move!
Damn.
Shit...is that...
Shit.
Is this Non?
What are you doing?
I think he's gone.
Fucking scary.
It's like in the movie, but we could die for real.
Don't worry, I'll protect you.
This is frustrating. Let's get out of here.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not. It's for real.
I think when the masked man touched it, it fell into the slit.
Did you open the file?
Yes, I just wanted to check if it still worked.
And what did you see?
Nothing. It's just a video of you guys getting drunk and partying.
That's right.
There's nothing. Why would you wanna watch it that much?
If you're free, go downstairs and give me a hand.
I think I'm gonna re-sew Por's wound.
Okay.
Wait.
What?
And how about Phee and Jin?
You're not gonna wait for them?
You should survive first before helping others.
Shit, but Phee and Jin are inside.
Shit!
Tee!
Let me go.
Tee, where are you?
I played the video in the hard disk earlier.
Fluke walked in and saw.
Tee, come home, hurry. Fluke is really scary.
Shit!
Fuck!
Damn in, where is he going?
Shit.
Fuck!
White said that he'd already played the video earlier.
And Fluke's acting weird.
Why would White play the video for?
We've talked about this that we won't play it. It's cursed.
And the masked murderer might go straight to the one who played it.
Fuck.
He might go back and kill Phee and Jin.
We should help them first.
No, I'll go home and help my partner.
Por's dying. Fluke won't be able to fight.
We must go back and help Phee, Jin and Top.
Forget it. My partner is in danger. I must go help him.
Tee, wait for me.
Por! Por! Por!
Fluke! Fluke! Come see Por now!
Por looks like he's having a seizure.
Move.
White, I told you to help me find the tools to sew Por's wound, didn't I?
And what are you waiting for? Get over here!
What are you going to sew his wound with, Fluke?
Whatever that I can use.
Just help me look for the tools.
Is that okay?
Normally, it has to be clean needle and thread.
You, dumbass White,
I asked you to help me find stuff not arguing with me!
Even I didn't study medicine,
but you gotta do fucking whatever you can.
But if you won't do shit,
just let Por die already, you piece of shit!
Damn it!
Now, what the hell are you waiting for?
Get over here!
White, how long have you had the gun?
Why didn't you tell me?
You have this useful stuff and you didn't tell me about it?
Shit, or are you the murderer?
No.
I guess, the masked murderer could be home now.
Shit, Tee, calm down.
Fuck, how should I warn White?
I don't understand why you all didn't want us see the video.
Who would want to see the video of a friend disappearing?
Hello, White! Hello, White!
Can you hear me?
Hello, Tee.
White, listen. Right now, the murderer is heading home.
If you're not too far away, we can still communicate.
Everyone would feel better.
C'mon.
Oh, Tan...
Shit.
I think I should push it.
Alright, let's do it.
Back off.
One, two, three.
Go!
That's scary.
Shit, you just leave me?
And action!
C'mon, Tan, we're almost there.
One...Two...
Let's do it again.
Again.
Should we start?
Yeah, let's try.
Accelerate.
Right.
More, more.
Yeah, Tan. I can do it. Let's go.
A bit more.
Right around here.
Tan, look.
Was this where you fell?
Yeah, Fluke pulled off and we fell here.
Fluke?
Oops!
Top!
Top, Top, Top, Top!
Is it early morning or is it late night? I can't tell.
I heard a thunder. Looks like it's about to rain.
Shit!
There's so much blood, if it were a man,
he probably dead be...ooh, sorry.
Sorry, tongue twister...
Hey, Tee!
I slipped.
Cut, cut. Let's do it again.
Hold my hand.
You're dead if you hold it like this.
Right into your hand.
This is frustrating. Let's get out of here.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not. It's for real.
I think when the masked man touched it, it fell into the slit.
Is this Non?
Guys, bottoms up!
Bottoms up!
Bottoms up! Up! Up!
Alright, bottoms up for the second time!
Cheers!
Yeah, done. Amazing!
You drank the whole thing?
Yeah, I haven't had soda in so long.