♪In a flash, back to the past♪
♪Your shadow appears so fast♪
♪Again and again♪
♪Our warmth fades away♪
♪We're at the edge, no words to say♪
♪Cross the line, it's you and me♪
♪Softly saying goodbye, set free♪
♪Walking paths we once knew♪
♪Reliving sweet times with you♪
♪But in your world, I was blank♪
♪Through the crowd, I hug you tight♪
♪Like raindrops in the cool night♪
♪Memories frozen, love so bright♪
♪I don't want to forget♪
♪Our light♪
[An adaptation from Eternal Love
by Ye Feiye from China Literature]
[101 Marriages]
[Episode 24]
Chengchi, you're here.
Chengchi,
I'm leaving the country.
That's good.
Got anything you want to say?
Just wishing you the best.
Chengchi,
I knew it all along
that my mom drugged you
and set you up with Lanshan.
I chose to ignore it
because I wanted
a better life.
I'm sorry.
♪Love wrapped in memories bright♪
♪Your touch lingers in the night♪
♪How can I tell night from day♪
Chengchi,
the En you've known for over 20 years
wasn't real.
♪Not just a glance, here to stay♪
♪You know I hate lies, they betray♪
Don't ever forgive me.
En.
♪Teaching me to walk away♪
♪In the world we both betrayed♪
♪Without me in the display♪
Take care of yourself.
♪Not just a glance, here to stay♪
♪But yesterday won't hold on to♪
♪Forever slips from view♪
♪Soft words were all we knew♪
♪But love still feels untrue♪
♪Thanks for this last glance too♪
♪Even as we part, we fray♪
Comfy, Mom?
Spit it out.
Well,
since my leg's better,
maybe you could head home?
Dad's missing you.
Your dad's fine.
My job now
is taking care of you.
I don't need to be taken care of.
Look,
I can run,
I can jump.
Sit down.
We need to talk.
Okay.
Your Aunt Wang's niece
is back from abroad.
How about we have her over
for dinner?
No.
You have to.
Your dad and I agreed:
once you settle down,
I'll leave.
Great.
Just great.
Another blind date?
Yeah, Lanshan.
His parents won't let him out
or use his phone
until he is
successfully matched.
They're just
trying to keep us apart,
afraid I'll reach out to him.
It's ridiculous,
trying to come between
two people who clearly
love each other to death.
It's not their fault.
It's mine.
Don't worry.
We'll find a way
for you two to meet.
Alright, I have to go.
I'm hanging up.
Dad, Mom,
I know I hurt Shwenny
and you both,
but it was all a misunderstanding.
Please give me another chance.
A misunderstanding?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Are you saying I imagined it?
Lanshan,
we can forgive many things,
but as our family's daughter-in-law,
you need to be above reproach.
You should leave.
What are you doing?
Dad,
Mom,
at first,
I thought Shwenny forced
and betrayed me,
but I realized
I fell in love with him first.
Only with him
can I be my true self.
But later,
I hurt him
out of my own foolishness,
leading to us falling apart.
I don't want to lose him again
because of it.
Dad, Mom,
I love him so much,
I'd give my life for him.
Chu!
What's going on?
Mom, Dad,
Chu means everything to me.
I'm begging you,
please let us be together.
I can't live without her.
Your everything?
Your everything cost me my grandson!
My grandson!
Mom, the...
The baby was born with severe issues.
Chu didn't tell us because
she didn't want to hurt us more.
She ended her pregnancy
and carried that burden alone.
Mom,
we'll have more children,
lots of them.
Even so,
what happened between you
and Han Chengchi
is still a fact.
Dad,
I just met with En.
You've misunderstood Chu.
Listen to this
if you don't believe me.
Why did you call me here?
Shwenny,
the thing between Chengchi and Shan...
My mom drugged him,
and he mistook her for me.
That's why it happened.
Please forgive Shan.
It wasn't her fault.
And...
I'm sorry,
Shwenny.
Thank you for telling me.
Shwenny,
do you really
only care about Lanshan?
Yes.
This kid's a true romantic.
Takes after me.
Dear,
if it was a misunderstanding
and they love each other so much,
it's not right for us
to stand in the way.
Let them be.
I'm done.
They can do what they want.
I'm packing up to go home.
Let me help you pack.
Thanks, Dad.
Thanks, Mom.
Mr. Han,
there's a Mrs. Gu here to see you.
Mrs. Gu?
What a surprise.
What brings you here?
Chengchi,
I went too far
back then.
I'm here to apologize.
Please, for En's sake,
leave our family alone.
Mrs. Gu,
you must be joking.
Letting your family off the hook?
Not a chance.
Chengchi,
if En hadn't left you,
you might never have found the drive
to now become
who you are today.
In a way, we helped you,
didn't we?
And what makes you think
I'm happy with who I am now?
If you hadn't been poisoning En's mind,
she might still be
the carefree girl she used to be.
I was different too!
You ruined so many lives
for money!
Shan,
she got lucky,
she has Shwenny.
Without him,
she'd have ended up like me and En.
When...
I lost her,
I swore
I'd never be weak again!
Even if it took everything I've got,
I'd bounce back.
So no,
you don't deserve my forgiveness.
Alright, it's done.
Thanks.
Chengchi,
I'm leaving.
I hope you find real happiness.
♪Sadness fills the rainy day♪
♪No blame for love's decay♪
♪The moments still shine through♪
♪This hurt's hard to swallow♪
♪I braved winter's hollow♪
♪But fell in the coldest night♪
♪Admitting the wrongs felt right♪
♪No strong words to hold tight♪
♪Love wrapped in memories bright♪
♪Your touch lingers in the night♪
♪How can I tell night from day♪
♪Was it love that caused our flight♪
♪The warmth won't just fade away♪
♪Not just a glance, here to stay♪
♪You know I hate lies, they betray♪
♪So you never let truth sway♪
♪Lucky the mask hides the fray♪
Sir.
♪In the world we both betrayed♪
♪Without me in the display♪
♪The warmth won't just fade away♪
♪Not just a glance, here to stay♪
♪But yesterday won't hold on to♪
♪Forever slips from view♪
♪Soft words were all we knew♪
♪But love still feels untrue♪
♪Thanks for this last glance too♪
♪Even as we part, we fray♪
Chu,
wear the outfit I picked
and meet me by the lake tonight.
I'll be waiting.
♪Poems often go like this♪
Chu,
that arm injury
wasn't on you.
I just went along with it.
After all,
without that fall,
I wouldn't have seen
how gentle you are
or ended up repeating a year
in the same class as you.
♪Same spot, same time♪
♪Always finding a sign♪
♪Every heartbeat close♪
♪Sparks fireworks♪
♪I miss you, miss you♪
♪Your gentle smile lingers on my lips♪
It's a card for Mrs. Sheng.
Now that it's official,
it is
yours.
Silly Chu,
do you think your kicks
scared me off?
No.
I was just mesmerized by you.
I couldn't stop thinking about
how many more surprises
you might have
♪This sweet dream♪
Chunney,
you're terrible.
Why didn't you ask
why I wasn't at school?
I got stabbed protecting you.
But that's on me too.
I just assumed
you knew.
So,
it wasn't your fault.
It was my mistake.
Your feelings for Han Chengchi...
That's on me, not you.
But that day made me realize
how I really feel.
The wind's strong.
You should go inside.
It's not good
for your recovery.
I'm fine.
I like the wind.
This spot feels right.
♪Replaying it♪
Chu,
the moment I took that knife for you,
I knew
I love you,
more than anything.
But someone as amazing as you...
[Gu Lanshan, I like you. Let's date.]
how can I make you love me?
In the past,
I've fought for you
a hundred times.
♪Engrave this beauty in my heart♪
♪Every day from now♪
This is the 68th time, right?
No,
it's the 69th.
If I had the chance,
I'd do it a thousand more.
I want to give you
a lifetime of happiness
to make you love me forever.
Silly.
Chu,
I heard
you and Sheng Shi divorced.
Maybe give Shwenny a chance?
He regrets
not telling you he loved you sooner.
Please give him a chance.
He wants to help you
get rid of Sheng Shi,
the guy you hate.
[ID Application Sheng Shi - Shwenny]
If you agree,
there'll be no more Sheng Shi.
Just Shwenny.
Seriously?
Stupid Shwenny.
Have you finished?
Chu,
the first time I saw you,
standing there
all shy and delicate,
you had my heart.
Every smile, every look,
you drew me in.
And when I took that knife for you,
I realized I loved you
more than anything.
I wanted to
give you the world,
but instead,
I hurt you.
I'm sorry.
I know I've made mistakes
and hurt you before,
but now
I'm ready to listen and will treat you
the way you deserve.
♪Memories hold tight♪
Chu,
will you give me another chance
and marry me?
♪But I slowly turned away♪
♪Your shadow fades to gray♪
Wait.
I have something to say.
Shwenny,
when I first met you,
you called me a country bumpkin.
I hated you
for being
so arrogant and cocky.
But that same arrogance
let you put up with my stubbornness.
You told everyone
not to mess with Gu Lanshan.
Why are you picking on Gu Lanshan?
She's my wife.
and I won't let anyone
hurt or slander her!
Do you understand?
Gu Lanshan is someone
you shouldn't mess with.
I suggest you get rid of
any bad ideas you have.
Trying to mess with my wife?
Did I ever touch you?
Miss Gu,
if you want to
test your man's love,
find another way.
Don't drag my wife into it.
I thought...
you looked pretty cool.
You knew I was afraid of the dark,
so you'd come up with
all kinds of excuses to walk me home.
And it is you
on so many nights,
who lighted the way for me,
pushing away the darkness.
I realized
the brightest light in my life
has always been you.
I used to think
I must've done something incredible
in a past life
to be lucky enough
to have you as a friend.
But then, suddenly,
I became your girl.
And people started saying
you bought me like I was for sale.
That hurt.
I couldn't accept it.
How could you treat me like a commodity?
You know I hate that.
It felt like you were
tearing open old wounds.
But then,
when Mo was in the hospital,
you told me
[Inpatient]
you'd only save him
if I married you.
Shwenny,
we've been through
so many misunderstandings,
slanders,
and so much hurt.
I almost
lost you forever.
But we've grown through it all.
We've learned how to
really love each other.
Without these ups and downs,
I might never have realized
how much you love me,
or...
how much I love you.
Some memories aren't great,
but they're ours,
and they mean everything.
I'm so glad
you're still here with me.
You've been my light,
and now,
I want to be yours.
I'll stay by your side.
You said in your letter
that you've fought for me
a hundred times.
Well,
this time, the 101st time,
let me fight for you.
Shwenny,
I'm going to steal you away
from everyone else.
I want to spend my life with you.
Marry me.
I will.
So, will you finally say yes?
Put the ring on.
♪Our warmth fades, edge at last♪
♪Cross the line, it's you and me♪
♪Softly saying goodbye, set free♪
♪Walking paths we once knew♪
♪Reliving sweet times with you♪
♪But in your world, I was blank♪
Alright.
Congrats, you two.
This is what real love looks like.
I could
live off this love for a year.
A year?
Try a lifetime, okay?
Let's go home.
You look dashing today.
Thank you, Mrs. Sheng.
I'd trade all the riches in the world
for a lifetime with you, Lanshan.
♪Poems often go like this♪
♪That moment felt like fate♪
♪Falling for you♪
♪Like spring breeze warmth♪
♪This sweet dream♪
♪Everything about you clear♪
♪Every heartbeat close♪
♪Sparks fireworks oh♪
♪I miss you, miss you♪
♪If you need me♪
♪I'll hold you tight♪
♪Engrave this beauty♪
♪In my heart♪
♪Every day from now♪
♪In my memories♪
♪Replaying it♪
♪I miss you, miss you♪
♪If you need me♪
♪I'll hold you tight♪
♪Engrave this beauty♪
♪In my heart♪
♪Every day from now♪
♪In my memories♪
♪Replaying it♪