Xin'er.
Is that you?
Mother. Xin'er.
We might need to stay away
for a while.
Well...
Why do we have to move again?
Xin'er,
could you go beg that noble lady?
We used to move every three years.
It hasn't even been a year yet.
Can we delay it a bit?
Mother,
we might have to make a living on our own from now on.
Well...
Did you offend that noble lady?
She has been so good to us.
She gave us such a nice house,
and sent us money every month.
You mustn't let her down.
Mother,
just listen to me.
Pack up quickly,
or we'll lose our lives.
Oh.
Also,
the small box I asked you to keep last time,
find it quickly.
Huiwen!
Sister,
you're back.
Huiwen,
pack up quickly.
We must leave at once.
Hurry up.
The sacrificial ceremony begins.
Consort Yu didn't know at this time
that after the ceremony,
she would become a prisoner forever.
I followed Aunt Huixin all the way
and finally retrieved the key evidence
of Consort Yu's murder of Queen Yun.
I rushed back to the palace in time
and presented it to King Yunqiu in person.
King Yunqiu was furious.
On the spot,
he banished Consort Yu to the Cold Palace.
I owe Yunchuan,
so this should make up for it.
Next,
I should do what I have to do.
Ling Xuele.
What are you thinking about?
You look distracted.
Nothing.
Are you thinking about
leaving?
I was too suspicious of you before.
Today I realized you truly want to help His Highness.
From my observation these days,
His Highness also hopes you will stay.
I will only bring him more trouble.
Why would he want me to stay?
That's because
the spectator sees more than the player.
But I see it clearly.
His Highness treats you
differently from others.
I didn't expect
you to be so brave
to distract the assassins and save Aunt Huixin,
helping us get the evidence to overthrow Consort Yu.
If you really leave,
who would His Highness and I
repay?
Let's not talk about this now.
Is His Highness in his room?
He's been locked inside for hours.
Speaking of today,
it should have been a happy day.
The truth about Queen Yun's death is clear,
and the culprit has been executed.
But on His Highness's face,
I don't see a hint of joy.
Even so,
how can what is lost
ever be brought back?
He just needs some time alone right now.
Today is the anniversary of Queen Yun's death.
Isn't that His Highness's birthday?
Yes.
How could I have forgotten that?
Come here.
You always have the best ideas.
Go on.
Okay.
Stop right there.
How dare you serve me
this disgusting food?
Consort Yu,
this is all we have here.
Whether you want to or not,
you have to eat it.
Is that how you speak to me?
Believe it or not,
when I get out of here,
I'll kill every single one of you.
Do you still think
you're a high-and-mighty consort?
Let me tell you,
no one who comes here
ever walks out in one piece.
You insolent servant!
How dare you talk back to me?
We remember very well
how you usually treated us.
I advise you
to stop making a fuss.
Otherwise,
your days ahead
will be even harder.
You!
You insolent servant!
Get out of here!
Get out!
I still have one unfulfilled wish in my heart.
I wonder if you'll be happy for me
when you hear it, Mother.
I originally thought there was no one
left in this world for me to care about.
The passion of love
is ultimately fleeting.
If I can't grow old with the one I love,
why involve those innocent women
in this senseless
struggle for royal power?
After all I've been through,
I've met someone.
Someone I
am willing to give up everything to protect.
I just don't know her feelings.
If our feelings are mutual,
I am willing to give up everything
to protect her.
And marry her.
No matter what,
you must never forget
that Yunchuan is the son of the man who destroyed our country.
Yunchuan.
I want nothing more than to confess my feelings
to you.
But I must avenge my country,
and I don't want to let you down
or use you.
Or use you.
So I can only choose to leave.
Ling Xue'le.
What are you doing here?
Why aren't you going in?
Your Highness,
What wine would you like for dinner?
The usual.
Same as always.
Then I will go prepare it.
Your Highness,
Lady Pingle seems to have drunk too much.
Xue'le.
Tingfeng.
Coming, coming, coming.
Lady Xue'le usually
does this.
I'm just imitating her.
Hurry and call the doctor.
What?
Hurry.
Okay.
Your Highness,
I'll leave
the soup here for you.
Xue'le.
How is she?
May I ask
if Lady Xue'le ate
anything unusual?
We've been eating the same food these past few days.
There's nothing unusual.
Besides,
she was perfectly fine during the day.
Could it be
that she secretly ate something?
Tonight,
she drank a little wine.
Could it be related to this?
Your Highness,
Lady Xue'le is exhibiting
symptoms of poisoning.
Poisoned?
In my opinion,
this poison
has been in her body
for quite some time.
It is exactly because of the wine
that the spread of the poison accelerated.
What kind of poison is it?
And when was she poisoned?
I'm afraid it's been more than a few months.
As for the poison,
please forgive my incompetence, Your Highness.
I cannot identify it yet.
However,
Your Highness does not need to be overly anxious.
I can perform acupuncture on Lady Xue'le first
to seal her meridians.
As long as the poison doesn't invade her internal organs,
her life will be safe for now.
Okay.
Then I'll have to trouble you
to perform acupuncture on her quickly.
Please.
Your Highness.
Lady Xue'le
has only been in the palace for a few months.
Could it be
that she was poisoned before entering the palace?
But
why would she hide it from us?