=The Origin of Eternity=
=Episode 9=
At least,
I was honest last night.
I didn't deceive you.
Am I right?
Bai Ze,
I swear.
If my father fails to keep his word,
you can take
my life.
Qinghuan. Qinghuan.
Let's go.
Come on.
♪Will we meet again
if I implore one more day?♪
♪I turn into the gentle mist
and caress your face♪
♪Will we bid goodbye to each other
after singing the farewell ballad?
(Bai Ze,)
(ask me to stay)
(or look at me one more time.)
♪As the graceful string breaks,
the strong devotion♪
♪Become the lingering feelings of love♪
♪Journeying through the vast time♪
♪We stop at the end
of the reincarnation cycle♪
♪The time was fleeting away
before the iris wilted♪
♪But we made a promise for this life♪
We're home.
Take a seat first.
Qinghuan,
turn that mechanism
to the left.
(The Secret Arts of Youming)
The Secret Arts of Youming?
Qinghuan.
Bai Ze?
Qinghuan! Qinghuan!
You're not Bai Ze.
Martial Brother,
how could you help an outsider
to harm me?
Who told you to use my appearance?
Father ordered me to do it.
If I don't show up in your appearance,
how can I make the demon
let down her guard
and obtain the Secret Arts of Youming?
Father.
Bai Ze.
Master.
I ordered you to reflect on yourself
in the forbidden area.
How dare you break out
without permission?
What are you trying to do?
Are you going to betray your sect?
Master,
Qinghuan is my wife.
I promised to defend and protect her
in this life.
We'll live and die together.
I won't allow anyone to hurt her.
Darn, you!
From now on,
the Qingyun Sect
will never accept a traitor like you!
You captured my father without reason.
Now you broke in
and trampled on us at will.
You call yourself a righteous sect?
No one cares to stay in your sect!
Shut up!
Nie Youming poisoned people
to cultivate The Secret Arts of Youming.
The Qingyun Sect gets rid of evil
in the martial arts circle.
We're frank and righteous!
You're lying.
My father never cultivates
The Secret Arts of Youming.
Let alone poison people.
Demon, you're speaking nonsense!
I've already found out.
The poison that Nie Youming cultivates
is you.
You're lying!
"Dragonflies flying in Tongliang.
Cocks crowing at the stars.
The widowed swan crying in the wind.
The cuckoo sobbing and worrying
about the nether world!"
Qinghuan!
Qinghuan, what's wrong?
This is bad.
That's the Poison-Calling Technique.
Qinghuan!
Qinghuan.
Qinghuan, are you all right?
Qinghuan!
Qinghuan.
Nie Youming,
how could you plant
the poison in Qinghuan?
You're inhumane!
Have you lost your mind?
She's your daughter!
She's the Holy Priestess
of the Youming Cult.
For her to die a martyr
for the survival of the cult
is something she ought to do.
You're an animal!
Qinghuan.
Nie Youming, stop it now.
Or else I'll take your life!
You're too late.
Once I've triggered the technique,
she would lose all her consciousness.
She's no longer Qinghuan.
You made me do this!
I wanted to train her
for another three years.
If you hadn't pushed me
into such a situation,
I wouldn't have called her this early!
Kill them all!
Qinghuan.
Qinghuan?
♪Wandered off from the crowd♪
♪As more wonderful things await♪
♪A sunset from the past resurfaced♪
♪Thousands of sailboats drifted
in the sea of clouds♪
♪And docked at different piers♪
♪Only the catkin willow
and my graying hair remained♪
♪Let's take on♪
♪Another year♪
♪I traveled alone toward daytime
as I waved aside the night♪
♪The tapping rain♪
♪Awakened the sorrow♪
♪I'm crying out in loneliness
amid pandemonium♪
♪I endured countless ordeals
from worldly entanglement♪
♪Knowing how difficult things
are for the first time♪
♪After you overcome
the vicissitudes of life♪
♪Only then do you understand
the fickleness of the world♪
♪I wanted to enjoy the years
but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪Only then do you understand
the fickleness of the world♪
♪I wanted to enjoy the years
but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪Knowing that I can't turn back time♪
♪You would not be intoxicated by sorrow♪
♪Until you were embroiled in love♪
♪I wanted to enjoy the years
but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪Knowing that I can't turn back time♪
♪You would not be intoxicated by sorrow♪
♪Until you were embroiled in love♪