=The Origin of Eternity=
=Episode 10=
I know
you would
remember who I am.
I'm Bai...
Bai Ze.
Why would I lie to you?
You're my favourite person
in this world.
♪Will we meet again
if I implore one more day?♪
Silly.
Because I love you.
♪Will we bid goodbye to each other
after singing the farewell ballad?
♪I turn into the snow
to freeze fickleness♪
♪As the graceful string breaks,
the strong devotion♪
♪Become the lingering feelings of love♪
♪Journeying through the vast time♪
Dear.
♪The time was fleeting away
before the iris wilted♪
♪But we made a promise for this life♪
♪I couldn't free myself
from the entanglement of love♪
♪I didn't want to see
a tearful farewell♪
♪I was obsessed
with the love of the past♪
♪If only I could first see you
in the next life♪
♪I wish we could be together again♪
♪For another thousand years♪
♪Will we meet again
if I implore one more day?♪
♪I turn into the gentle mist
and caress your face♪
♪Will we bid goodbye to each other
after singing the farewell ballad?
♪I turn into the snow
to freeze fickleness♪
♪As the graceful string breaks,
the strong devotion♪
Qinghuan.
Bai Ze.
I knew it.
I knew
that you recognise me.
I'm sorry, Bai Ze.
It's fine.
It's not your fault.
But
I have become
the heinous Demonic Maiden.
No.
No, you're not.
You're innocent.
No matter what,
you're the one I hold dear to my heart.
Let us
bear everything together.
All right?
It will be fine.
Bai Ze.
Master.
Now or never.
Kill her now.
I can't.
I can't obey you this time.
Wayward disciple!
Heed me. Kill her now.
Master.
I'm very grateful to you
for saving my life
and raising me.
There is nothing I can do to repay you.
But Qinghuan is my wife.
I love her and I want to protect her.
I want to protect her forever.
Please let go of her.
I'm willing to trade my life for hers.
You!
I beg of you, Master.
Bai Ze.
Qinghuan, fret not. I'm here with you.
I will protect you.
Please carry on with your life well.
Qinghuan.
♪I turn into the snow
to freeze fickleness♪
Qinghuan.
Master, let go of me.
♪Journeying through the vast time♪
Qinghuan.
♪The time was fleeting away
before the iris wilted♪
♪But we made a promise for this life♪
♪I couldn't free myself
from the entanglement of love♪
♪I didn't want to see
a tearful farewell♪
♪I was obsessed
with the love of the past♪
♪If only I could first see you
in the next life♪
♪I wish we could be together again♪
♪For another thousand years♪
(Ever since the death of Qinghuan,)
(Youming Cult is eliminated)
(restoring eternal peace to
the martial arts world)
(without strives.)
(Bai Ze left Qingyun Sect
and led a secluded life.)
(He spent the rest of his life)
(by the tomb of Qinghuan)
(and never stepped in
the martial arts world.)
I will come to you
in the next life.
Your Highness.
As the Crown Prince of the Ling Empire,
you're summoned by the Empress
of the Sheng Empire
despite you being in poor health.
This is ridiculous.
Here in the Sheng Empire,
I'm but a hostage.
Anping, listen.
Act and speak in discreet.
The current Ling Empire
has become so fragile
that a gentle breeze can make it fall.
I, Bai Ze, Crown Prince of Ling Empire
come to greet, Your Majesty.
You have been here for two months.
But
this is our first meeting.
I'm born weak.
And I collapsed after catching a cold
on the way to Sheng Empire.
Therefore, I failed to seek
an audience with you.
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
Crown Prince, why didn't you
be on your knees
before the Empress of the Great Sheng?
Getting down on your knees is the proper
etiquette to greet the Empress.
Your behaviour seems to be rude.
Be on your knees.
It doesn't matter to me.
I heard that the Crown Prince of
the Ling Empire, Bai Ze
is as elegant as the willow in spring
who possesses unparalleled beauty.
I heard that the Empress of
the Great Sheng is extraordinary
and with a regal quality.
I came here representing the Ling Empire
to request an eternal peaceful alliance
with the Sheng Empire.
Are you going to sit behind the veil
after you have invited me over,
Your Majesty?
How insolent of you!
Well said.
♪Wandered off from the crowd♪
♪As more wonderful things await♪
♪A sunset from the past resurfaced♪
♪Thousands of sailboats
drifted in the sea of clouds♪
♪And docked at different piers♪
♪Only the catkin willow
and my graying hair remained♪
♪Let's take on♪
♪Another year♪
♪I traveled alone toward daytime
as I waved aside the night♪
♪The tapping rain♪
♪Awakened the sorrow♪
♪I'm crying out in loneliness
amid pandemonium♪
♪I endured countless ordeals
from worldly entanglement♪
♪Knowing how difficult things
are for the first time♪
♪After you overcome
the vicissitudes of life♪
♪Only then do you understand
the fickleness of the world♪
♪I wanted to enjoy the years
but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪Only then do you understand
the fickleness of the world♪
♪I wanted to enjoy the years
but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪Knowing that I can't turn back time♪
♪You would not be intoxicated by sorrow♪
♪Until you were embroiled in love♪
♪I wanted to enjoy the years
but it turned into a disaster overnight♪
♪Knowing that I can't turn back time♪
♪You would not be intoxicated by sorrow♪
♪Until you were embroiled in love♪