What are you…
doing here?
Gyeon-U.
Gyeon-U!
I'll save him.
I'll fend off all misfortune.
I promise you to free him from misfortune
after the next three weeks.
Were you at the funeral?
Ji-ho. He filled me in.
I couldn't have been there.
I was so not there.
You little brat.
Do you think I'm here for you?
I'm here to see your grandmother.
Bad accidents were like fate.
They were always waiting for me.
Lucky breaks were like a miracle.
They never happened to me.
A girl said she'd be there for me
until darkness gave way to light.
Her hands were so warm
that I thought I could be happy for once.
But it turned out to be
an impossible dream.
Gyeon-U.
Bae Gyeon-U.
I'm sorry, Gyeon-U.
Don't cry.
You don't get to snivel now.
Fancy meeting you here.
You ignored me?
You crazy?
Let's do this tomorrow.
Not tonight.
Have you really lost it?
What the heck?
What…
did I do to deserve this?
I didn't ask you to like me.
Hate me all you want.
You know I can't do anything
however much you hate me!
You could've
just gone on hating me
and loathing me.
Why are you taking it this far? Just why?
Just…
how much more pitiful must I be
to make you stop?
Gyeon-U.
I'm sorry.
Damn it.
Go away!
Get lost!
Just go!
I wasn't saying that to you.
You really are a shaman, after all.
I can tell by your shamelessness.
You must've had fun.
It wasn't like that.
I meant to tell you from the start.
But I couldn't
because you hated it so much.
You may feel sorry for me for now,
but soon, things will get real fun.
"You're plagued with misfortune."
"You're jinxed."
"You'll die soon."
Taunting me with stuff like that
will become enjoyable to you.
You'll see me struggle desperately
and do everything I'm told
as if I've become someone's marionette.
You'll end up laughing at me too.
You try so hard.
You have no idea
you're a frog in boiling water.
I'm not like other shamans.
I know everything I say
will sound like an excuse--
They're not excuses.
They're lies.
Of all the things you said to me so far,
how many of them weren't a lie?
Who is it?
Who could be this vile?
This boundary was made with the purpose
of making the one inside
an evil deity.
An exchange of equivalents.
The caster bet their own life.
Be very meticulous.
Seal the place from the outside
so not even an insect can crawl in.
If nothing can go into the house,
nothing will end up as a sacrifice.
-Close the door and seal it
With my bright energy I rebuke you
The sun rises in the east
-Close the door and seal it
With these amulets I command you
Release the inauspicious energy
-Close the door and seal it
The sun gives out fire of samadhi
It dims the ill light and subdues ghouls
-Close the door and seal it
Sacred warrior sent from above
Crushes vile traces causing diseases
-Close the door and seal it
With diamonds we shall subdue the ghouls
And make everything fair and promising
Just why isn't she picking up the phone?
What's wrong? Are you worried
Yeomhwa might have harmed her?
Watch it.
Master.
Why are you so worked up?
Your thoughts must be
going in that direction too
seeing how you keep calling her.
Wait.
-Do you hear that sound?
-What sound?
A phone ringing.
WOLSEONG SHRINE
SPIRIT-MOTHER
Seong-A!
You're back.
I see you've decided to torture me today.
Why didn't you answer your phone…
Why the long face? What's wrong?
-Mother.
-What?
At the abandoned house…
What about the abandoned house?
Did something happen?
Well?
At the abandoned house…
Go on. I'm listening.
I was found out…
to be a shaman.
Gyeon-U knows.
It's an amulet
that wards off evil.
You could've drawn it on my face only.
In case she doesn't cross over.
She was with you for such a long time.
I did it to protect.
To protect you.
I thought you'd be devastated
if you found out I'm a shaman.
I'm sorry
for wanting to be your friend.
BAE GYEON-U! SAVE HIM! PROTECT HIM!
For just five days starting tomorrow.
Stay friends with me
for just five more days.
You can hate me
and yell at me all you want.
Stay by my side for five more days.
BOOK ON THE SECRETS OF THWARTING EVIL
This boundary was made with the purpose
of making the one inside
an evil deity.
Once inside, even the greatest shaman
will become a sacrifice.
They'll be overcome
by the evil spirit and die.
Come on. Not just anyone
can become an evil deity.
They must kill 100 living people,
not just spirits, to…
No way.
Is it almost there already?
With just a couple left to go?
Did you ask her
if she met Yeomhwa at the abandoned house?
-Not yet.
-Why are you dragging it out?
Just ask her.
Good morning.
-Dear viewers, our guest today
-Did you see her yesterday at the shack?
is highly sought-after.
Hello.
I'm Yeomhwa, a medium. Nice to meet you.
Before we start…
-Yes, I saw her.
-You saw her?
What was she doing there?
Did she tell you anything
or perhaps harass you?
She didn't say much.
We just danced together.
You danced? Why?
She told me to dance
the Flower Lantern Dance.
That's a dance for two, so--
My goodness. You're really something.
You dared dance alone
with that notorious Yeomhwa?
It's worse than smoking with an elder.
General.
She'll become a great shaman. My word.
Shut your damn mouth, will you?
What's the matter?
She said she was one of the shamans
Great Aunt had called
and said she'd arrived a bit early.
That's a complete lie.
-What?
-Don't get me started.
Our elder shaman gathered
great shamans for nothing.
That witch beat us to it.
She cast a spell that turns anyone
entering the shack
into an offering to the evil spirit.
She even put up her own life.
The law of equivalent exchange.
We couldn't risk our lives,
so we sealed the shack from outside
instead of going in.
That reckless wench.
Why try to serve an evil spirit
and not just some ghost?
Doesn't she fear hell?
Hell isn't far away.
Life as a shaman is hellish already.
Seeing ghosts isn't a skill or talent.
It's a curse.
Stacking up karma with her tongue, I see.
ONE OF THE THREE KARMAS,
CAUSED BY ILL SPEECH
I'll get ready for school.
Gyeon-U, I'm sorry.
Give me just five days.
What's up with you two?
What's going on?
Nothing's going on.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Seeing ghosts isn't a skill or talent.
It's a curse.
Patch things up.
I can tell you two argued.
Patch things up already.
Or it'll ruin our assessment.
We didn't argue.
Do you think I'm stupid? You argued.
Big time, too.
For the first time in my life,
I like your direct approach, Hye-ri.
Don't be silly.
If you two won't make up,
at least tell us why you argued.
It's been bothering me all day.
It's a personal matter.
It has nothing to do with you guys.
Come on, don't be like that.
I wish they didn't serve
braised beans at lunch.
Do you have to bring up
braised beans right now?
When can I talk about them if not now?
I should mention braised beans
when they're served.
If I were to say I hate braised beans
when they weren't served for lunch,
that's talking behind their back.
That's doubly hating on them.
I don't dislike braised beans that much.
But some may feel bad about it
and won't say they dislike
braised beans to their face.
They don't want to
hurt the beans' feelings.
They might whisper,
"I don't like braised beans,"
but I wouldn't assume
that they doubly dislike them.
Most likely their dislike
is only half the regular amount,
since they're keeping quiet
to preserve the beans' dignity.
What is she talking about?
If Seong-A is Gyeon-U's braised beans…
demanding he explain
why he dislikes his braised beans
is almost cruel to him.
I'm…
I'm a shaman.
I said I had a part-time job,
but I'm actually a shaman.
That shaman in the video
Ju-seung was on about
is indeed me.
I got initiated at eight,
and I've been a shaman ever since.
I didn't attend
elementary and middle school.
There were times when I wasn't a student,
but I was never not a shaman.
I wanted to be an ordinary student.
That's why I kept it a secret.
I swear it was never to deceive people.
Then I met Gyeon-U who hates shamans,
and I wanted to be his friend.
So…
ever since then…
I'm sorry.
I lied.
Then last night,
Gyeon-U found out the truth.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Why did you want us to be friends?
-Because--
-We can be friends with anyone we want.
Do we have to have a reason?
There usually is a reason,
especially for shamans.
He really does despise shamans.
Why don't you just tell him
that you're keeping him close
to protect him for 21 days?
But he was right about me
befriending him with an intention.
I guess, but…
"You're destined to die in 21 days."
Stuff like that…
should only be shared
after you've actually saved them.
Before then, you'd only be
scaring and threatening them.
I guess you're right, but…
How many days are left?
Five days.
That many?
How would you find Yeomhwa
when even I couldn't?
Have you lost all your powers?
Why waste time and energy
when you won't be able to find her?
Shush it.
Don't quibble about my decision.
I reached out
to all my emergency contacts.
Yeomhwa did some serious preparations.
She sold her house and her office
and canceled all her bookings.
She scraped together all her savings,
disconnected her number,
and went off the grid.
There must be something she still fears
if she has gone into hiding.
Do you really think so?
I'd say she cut contact
so no one would disturb her.
It's clear she's determined
to serve an evil deity.
All the more reason to find her, then.
I must find her
and knock some sense into her.
I'm off.
A typical behavior for a shaman
serving a general god,
jumping in like a good little soldier.
I wouldn't say anything if you served.
I'm the one who actually served.
Weren't you discharged
for medical reasons?
I got possessed when I was in the army.
I was supposed to say "attention"
in a manly voice when…
We'll finish making the slide deck today.
No one's going home until then.
And you two.
I won't let you sneak off
for archery practice or whatever.
Got it?
-Why's he the best archer?
-Darn it.
Let's go.
I won't let him catch on
that I knew you were a shaman.
If he found out
that I was in on it from the start,
-then he'd really have no one to turn to.
-Right.
I'll feel guilty for us both.
Stop feeling bad and protect him well.
Then get him to apologize
when the 21 days are up.
Okay?
It will take ages to make the deck.
Do you have business
with my legs?
No, it's nothing. Let's go.
It's still fast asleep.
My baby.
Where did my baby go?
The baby's gone.
-That's dirty.
-The baby's gone.
Stop going through the trash!
Listen, dear. Your baby's not here.
Babies can't be out here.
That would be dangerous.
-Your hands are dirty.
-Where…
What's the matter?
-What is it?
-Wait.
Wait. Oh, my goodness.
-You thief!
-What on earth?
-What's wrong?
-Give my baby back to me!
What are you doing? Wait. Let her go!
-Do-yeon.
-What's wrong?
-You thief!
-Wait.
-Hey.
-Calm down.
-Stop it.
-Wait.
-Let go of her.
-Thief!
Calm down. Relax.
Oh, my gosh.
No, wait.
What's gotten into you?
Stop, you both!
Don't look at him. Don't.
Loud noises wake the Baby Ghost.
A Baby Ghost isn't all that bad.
What can a baby do but cry?
If it cries, comfort it.
But if you fail to do so…
Then it'll be a disaster.
No, don't cry. He's not a bad person.
He's just plagued by misfortune.
Peekaboo.
Thank you.
Whatever. Human Amulet to the rescue!
Why did it shatter?
I held his hand.
Are you hurt? Let me see.
It's okay.
-Hey, you're bleeding.
-I'm fine, all right?
Hey. Are you really okay?
It's a graze.
A little blow on it will do.
Are you okay?
-I'm so sorry.
-It's fine.
And you? Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Why did the glass suddenly shatter?
-Beats me. But let's--
-I'm going home.
How can you say
you'll go home in this situation?
You said we could go when we were done.
All done.
LIFE AND ETHICS
PRESENTATION DECK
Do-yeon took care of the deck.
Something's not right.
I need to look into it.
You want to visit my place? But why?
I thought
it'd be nice if we became friends.
Why would that be nice?
It'd make more sense if you wanted
some tips from the deck expert.
Exactly. I want to learn from you.
Hello.
No one's home.
My parents both work.
This is impressive.
I'd like you to go into detail
about what you find so impressive.
Oh, well, you know…
I mean…
So the ghost wasn't stuck to Do-yeon.
You have a great eye.
This makes it much easier.
No.
Is 500,000 won too little?
Then…
how about a million won?
Patricia is my child.
Do you think I'll sell her for money?
I'll treat your child like my own.
I'll love and cherish it.
I fell for it at first sight.
Can you… Please?
You're lying.
You tried to obtain her with money.
That can't be true love.
Leave.
I'm her mom. You don't qualify.
Okay, I'll leave.
I'll leave for now.
Calm down.
For just five days starting tomorrow.
Stay friends with me
for just five more days.
What in the world is she up to?
Gyeon-U.
Hey, Gyeon-U. High-five.
Is it pity?
It's friendship.
They were all spells.
It wasn't pity or friendship.
You were just being a shaman
from the start.
Nothing's working out, huh?
Do you want an amulet?
The amulet…
The Human Amulet didn't work.
The Baby Ghost stuck to the doll
must be really powerful.
I need to get the doll
if I'm to perform a rite
and weaken its power.
Your power didn't work
on the boy who found out
you are a shaman?
-Yes.
-Then you don't yet know
if the Baby Ghost is strong
or you're plain weak.
Human or not, all amulets are the same.
When did your powers stop working?
Think carefully.
When do they stop working?
I wouldn't know.
My amulets are always effective.
What do you say?
Do you want a new one?
Let's stay moisturized.
Now, the social ideology…
This headache is so annoying.
Sir.
My head aches.
Mine too. What's going on?
Open the windows
and let in some fresh air.
Sir, can I go see the nurse?
Yes, go ahead. Be quick.
Let's sit up and stretch a bit.
Do-yeon.
-Did you think about it?
-About what?
About your doll.
Could you give it to me?
Hey, Ku Do-yeon.
Why did you spray water on her?
-Are you a sociopath?
-That's rich coming from you.
-What?
-Hey, don't fight.
I'm fine.
You keep quiet.
Do I have to be okay with it if you are?
-Let's work on our assessment.
-I am.
We're at the library. Keep it down.
You keep it down. You're louder.
And the second slide.
This isn't right. Fix it.
However loud I try to be,
I can't be as loud as you.
And…
as for the second slide,
you just don't get it
because you have poor taste.
What, taste? "Taste"?
-You are a sociopath.
-It looks like it'll cry soon.
-"Taste," my foot.
-First,
whether it works or not,
let's try being the Human Amulet again.
Please.
Just one more time.
The spell.
Again.
I don't know you well,
but I know about shamans.
You've been casting spells on me,
haven't you?
Is this how it works?
How did you know?
What you're going through now
must be hellish.
The power of the Human Amulet
disappeared completely.
I can…
no longer protect Gyeon-U.
JEIL GENERAL HOSPITAL
Human or not, all amulets are the same.
Think carefully.
When did your powers stop working?
Why are you here and not in bed?
I'm okay. I wasn't hurt.
Doesn't being here hurt your heart?
I brought it upon myself.
That's a stretch.
Do you want to lean on my broad shoulder?
No, thanks.
Oh, my gosh, Gyeon-U.
Oh, look at you.
Oh, Gyeon-U.
My powers as a Human Amulet disappeared.
It doesn't help even when I touch him.
Then the shelves toppling over…
Yeah. It was his misfortune.
Why did it have to disappear now?
That's because Gyeon-U dislikes me.
However kind someone is to you,
you'll still hate it if you hate them.
It means nothing to you.
It's the same thing.
Why are you being so dramatic?
I should've stopped when he caught on.
I should've looked for another way then.
I guess I got too greedy.
"It's all for Gyeon-U's sake."
"So I have no choice."
It was all an excuse.
There's no way I'm the only solution.
There is no one and only way
to save a person's life.
I just wanted to be his amulet.
Even for just a while…
I wanted to be
an important person to Gyeon-U.
So what?
What's your plan now?
I'll find another way as soon as possible.
For now,
I prepared this just in case.
Right now, this is
the only countermeasure.
All right.
I'll put this in his underwear for you.
I've pulled myself together.
I almost lost Gyeon-U
while chasing my own greed.
No more clumsy act
about wanting to be his friend.
As the Heaven and Earth Fairy,
I'll focus on saving Gyeon-U only.
Okay, he can go home
as soon as the dizziness goes away.
-Thanks a lot.
-No worries.
-Thank you.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
Good idea. Look out for him,
kid with a nice build.
I'll settle the hospital bill.
No, sir, you don't have to--
Shush it. I want to do this for you.
I'll kill you if you refuse.
Just say thank you.
Adults are rich.
The total is 498,000 won, please.
-What?
-It's 498,000 won.
It's fine.
It's okay. Let's go.
Four hundred…
The amulets are being prepared.
I want 100 as soon as possible.
The real problem is the Baby Ghost.
Come with me already.
Lady Fairy, get rid of a ghost for me.
Oh, my gosh.
Dear, you can't bring this in here.
No, it's mine. Leave it alone!
She had a miscarriage
in the last month of her pregnancy.
Poor thing.
She hasn't been
in her right mind since then.
All she does all day long
is walk around with that stroller.
She recently picked up a doll somewhere
and carried it around,
calling it her baby.
I think that's when she got possessed.
She threw out the doll one day,
and now she goes through trash
all over the neighborhood looking for it.
Jeez. Look at that smile.
She must've completely lost it.
She's not possessed.
Take her to a doctor.
You didn't even
-take a good look at her.
-I'm a shaman.
I can tell at a glance
whether someone's lost their mind
or possessed.
Maybe she's both possessed
and out of her mind.
No way. Ghosts can't possess crazy people.
Why not?
How can a ghost take over
when there's nothing in there?
There's no mind to control.
It's the ghost that gets antsy.
"What's up with this person?"
"What's wrong that they don't fear me?"
Give me back my baby!
Why are you doing this?
Dear.
Hey, dear!
What does your baby look like?
My baby?
-She's pretty.
-Does she wear a blue dress
and a white blouse underneath it?
She's about…
this big and a bit dirty.
The blue dress sparkles.
Her dress has too many holes.
I held the baby close
in case she felt cold.
It's the doll.
I can do it.
I can get rid of the Baby Ghost.
Wait.
Lady Fairy.
-Who is it?
-Hello.
I'm a friend of Do-yeon's.
I don't have friends.
It's me, Park Seong-A.
Are you cosplaying?
I'm a shaman.
BAE GYEON-U
Dang it. I answered the call.
Hello? This is Gyeon-U's phone.
Hey.
What are you doing with my phone?
I didn't mean to answer it.
I just happened to…
It must be a foreigner.
The name's in English. "H."
Is it an important call?
Sorry, my bad.
Patricia's haunted?
You feel suffocated and nauseous,
and your head aches, right?
It's all because of the Baby Ghost
stuck to that doll.
I'm not buying that.
You must have nightmares
where a newborn cries all night.
You should've sold it to me
when I offered a million won.
You speak like a true villain.
Why are you suddenly showing
your true colors?
It's hard to get Baby Ghosts to cross over
because you can't reason with them.
Calming them so they fall asleep
and don't cry is the best bet.
And I just found someone
who can do that the best.
Who's that?
The mom.
ARCHERY TEAM
Hui-na.
I'll be much more unhappy
than you want me to be.
Don't worry.
You know good things never happen to me.
Don't cry.
Try to pull yourself together.
I'm sorry for…
Yet again, I…
What's her problem?
I didn't mean to listen in.
I happened to overhear.
Why did she call in tears?
To make you unhappy?
Why do you take such calls?
What was that about?
She's a friend.
CHOI HUI-NA
She was a nice person,
but she changed because of me.
So you two should stop too.
It's okay to do that.
Keep your distance from someone like me.
What?
Hey, Ji-ho.
You really can do that.
I won't resent you guys for it.
Is he actually crazy?
What if I refuse?
Is my outfit not sending a clear message?
I'll take it from you forcibly.
If I don't, you'll keep suffering.
Insomnia and chronic headaches
will keep troubling you.
It won't kill you,
but that's not the case for someone else.
They'll die.
What will only give you a headache
can cause accidents for that person.
You have lots of dolls.
Give up just one for a friend.
-I'm not anyone's friend.
-Then be one from now on.
Be my friend.
You're unusually upfront.
I see why the woodcutter
hid the fairy's clothes.
You became
way too strong.
Thanks for the compliment.
How you show up at school…
Is that all fake?
Maybe?
I bought Patricia second-hand.
My mom threw her out in secret
because she looked spooky.
I guess that lady must've found her.
I found Patricia by chance
and brought her back home.
You were in so much pain.
Why did you remain on this side?
You're finally back.
What's going on?
Why are you here? Were you waiting for me?
Yeah.
Why? Did something happen to Gyeon-U?
I'd say
something is about to happen.
I'll do it.
Human Amulet.
You went to great lengths for Gyeon-U,
and to be honest, I didn't really get it.
I'll be much more unhappy
than you want me to be.
But I got it
after spending time with him.
I want to do the same for him.
If he died like that,
it would torment me forever.
Human Amulet or whatever.
I can be one too, right?
Well…
I can't?
You can.
If that's how you feel.
For the poor, annoying punk
who has no one to call his own…
You'll be a shaman…
and I'll be his Human Amulet.
For now, that's all we are.
Something with eyes, a nose, and lips.
-With eyes, a nose, and lips.
-Give Gyeon-U something you touched a lot
that has eyes, a nose, and lips.
When you're not by Gyeon-U's side,
that will protect him in your place.
Eyes, a nose, and lips…
Hey.
Why do you have eyes, a nose, and lips?
Cherish it. It means a lot to me.
I don't need it.
Keep it, punk.
I didn't do my part in the assessment.
-Let's work on it together all day long.
-I'm busy today.
With what? Do it with me.
Should I yell?
Call when you're done with whatever it is.
I'll be waiting.
Hey, take this with you.
Like I said, cherish it.
It means a lot to me.
Why is he so clingy?
Let's go.
I'll take you to your mom.
Have you seen a woman
in a flower-patterned dress
pushing a stroller?
It's not her.
Oh, my gosh.
Where is she?
My baby's gone.
My baby's not here.
Let's say there's a stranger
crying on the street, all alone.
My baby's gone.
Even so,
I want my crush to be someone
who'd go over and comfort them.
I'd just stand there
until they stop crying.
I can stand by their side
even if I don't know why they're crying.
Are you done crying?
You shouldn't touch that stuff.
It's icky.
Icky.
Let's go.
Hello.
You have a lovely stroller.
It's my baby's cart.
-Isn't it pretty?
-It is.
What's that over there?
-What?
-What is that?
My gosh.
Your baby's lovely too.
My baby is gone.
My baby.
Where have you been?
Mommy's been looking for you.
You sweet thing.
I see why you didn't leave.
You'd been looking for your mom.
It's so strange.
Everything about the two is fake,
but that love alone is real and true.
Goodbye.
WASTE BAG, JANGAN CITY
Gyeon-U.
Even if I wasn't a real friend…
Even if it was all a lie…
And even if it was fake…
My heart hurts so much.
Doesn't that mean my feelings
for you are real?
It hurts so bad.
I really…
feel like I'll die.
So there was a reason you got gutsy.
I don't get you yet.
Why are you nice to me?
Why don't you stop doing this?
She needs to live a good long life.
When she dies, she'll go to hell.
Why do I feel like something's off?
Do you both think I'm stupid?
You're doing this
because Seong-A told you to.
Weaklings
lose out eventually.
It can't be.
No, you can't do that. Not…
Is what Seong-A said true?
Just hate me.
Subtitle: Jennifer Jean Lim