THE LATE OH OK-SUN
CHIEF MOURNER: GRANDSON, BAE GYEON-U
STANDARD ROOM
Don't you dare mess with him.
He's mine.
You don't scare me.
Why not?
Because the really scary person
is sitting right behind me.
Gyeon-U.
Can you do something about that glare?
Excuse me.
Mr. Bae. A moment, please.
Oh, sure.
He has me on tenterhooks.
I wouldn't mind the deathly glare
if I'd actually done something horrible.
But I'm protecting him here.
He has no clue.
Ma'am. Your grandson's a bit ungrateful.
Just wait
until I ward off your misfortune.
I'll make sure you make up
for all of it with love.
She must've been a bad person.
-There are no visitors.
-I know, right?
You see, you must order
a minimum of 30 portions of food.
In that case…
19 CONTACTS
Is 19 people too few?
However few visitors you have,
you must order 30 portions of food.
Okay.
Enjoy the meal.
It's my first time at a funeral.
What am I supposed to do?
SPIRIT-MOTHER
MY DARLING SPIRIT-DAUGHTER
POWER OFF
The person you have called
is not available.
You'll be connected to voicemail.
How could she hang up like that?
Who can I call other than Mother?
PARK SEONG-A
Jeil Funeral Hall,
Standard Room, Oh Ok-sun.
Come if you have time.
Gyeon-U's grandmother passed away.
It's a nasty energy, all right.
But it's not so bad to anger the spirits.
DIVINE PUNISHMENT FOR A FORBIDDEN ACT
Maybe you're being dramatic,
Village Chief.
People have died.
Three people died in this house already.
Houses in other villages
sell for hundreds of millions of won.
Why do you think
house prices here are frozen?
You're our only hope, General Dongcheon.
Don't worry. I'm good at this.
Big Sister, are you ready?
Let's go.
-Put the lights down. Let's begin.
-Yes, ma'am.
Mom.
Mom…
Oh, Mom.
How could this be, Mom?
You sold off all the wealth you had
and ended up penniless.
What's this, Mom?
You could've at least put
some flowers around her photo.
The armband.
If you go to the office
by the main entrance…
-I'll go get you one.
-Give me yours.
What is it?
Can't give up the chief mourner role?
You're being ridiculous.
That won't change anything now.
If you had wanted to kick him out,
you should've done so long ago.
When I said
we should send him abroad
or anywhere else,
before Mom spent
her remaining savings on him!
Don't you remember
how much she hated that idea?
I do remember!
But you should've persuaded her somehow.
You're the eldest son, aren't you?
Honey. You too, stop it.
Please calm down, will you?
Come on. Hand it over!
Don't touch him. He's bad luck!
I'm sorry, Uncle. But please…
Could you let me stay here?
Who are you calling "Uncle"? Why you…
What do you think you're doing?
It's disrespectful.
What?
Why kick him out
when he's stayed here until now?
You want the world to know
how messed up your family is?
Do you think being loud
means you're right?
Are you a shaman?
Yes.
-My gosh.
-What?
-So what?
-A shaman?
A shaman at a funeral?
Don't you know shamans can't be here?
How dare you act like
she's a ghost already?
You called this con artist, didn't you?
-No, it's not what--
-You stay out of it.
Must you defame her
even on her final journey?
-Fine. Today's the day.
-I'd rather take on a ghost.
People are much worse.
-Come with me.
-Leave him alone.
Big Sister.
Isn't it a bit weird?
Dongcheon!
Gwi, as in "ghost."
It's a curse! Get out this instant!
A PUNISHMENT FOR ANGERING SPIRITS
Get out now!
A GHOST
You're still here?
TO BLOCK
THE LATE OH OK-SUN IN STANDARD ROOM
HAS BEEN MOVED TO SPECIAL SUITE 2
STANDARD ROOM
Hello. Thank you for coming.
How unfortunate.
Just say thank you.
It's the perfect time to say that.
Thank you.
How did you know to come?
Seong-A told me.
Seong-A?
Park Seong-A?
So, the thing is,
she works part-time in this area.
She saw you and told me to come.
She should be clocking out soon.
Get changed
and join us like you just arrived.
GET CHANGED AND JOIN US
LIKE YOU JUST ARRIVED
I don't have other clothes.
Hey, Gyeon-U.
Your parents…
They'll be here soon.
I'll leave. Don't worry.
Will you?
Thanks.
-You'll leave? For real?
-Yeah.
See you.
Bye. Get some rest.
You look like a mess.
CONDOLENCES
You didn't stop him. I thought you would.
You heard what the man said.
"Thanks."
Of all the things
people said to Gyeon-U today,
that was the one nice thing.
You can't stop him then.
About earlier.
I wouldn't have been mistreated so badly
if I hadn't been a shaman, right?
You would've been.
Because we're nothing but noobs.
Hey, Shaman. Can you get home on your own?
-Sure.
-See you tomorrow.
You'll return my money and that's it?
You said you could do this.
That was before I got hit by a curse.
It's a miracle
that only three have died so far.
Even ghosts would perish here.
You and your excuses. You're just a quack.
Watch it.
Don't call another shaman
to try to exorcise the ghost.
Whoever offers to do it
would be the real quack.
Here's your money.
What am I to do if even a rite won't work?
If it's hiding
its murderous energy so well,
it means it's
an exceptionally strong spirit.
Until the spirit moves away on its own,
there's nothing us humans can do.
All we can do is pray.
"Drive out the darkness."
"Let go of the evil within."
Just pray.
Are you all burned yet?
Don't let anyone near the house.
We'll see if we can find a solution.
Okay.
Let's head back, then.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
-Pack your stuff.
-Okay.
Hello.
Hi.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
What a shame.
The bike's new.
What was that noise?
Is there an accident?
-A kid was hit!
-I think a child was hit.
-Someone call an ambulance.
-Call 119!
-Was it an accident?
-Hurry.
Oh, no.
You don't have to walk me further.
Get going now.
Okay, then.
I'm off.
What's wrong?
What?
It's nothing.
I heard your grandmother passed away.
She's finally free from you.
Congratulations.
I know you gave fake amulets
to my spirit-mother.
I won't tell on you. Make me 100 more…
No, make me just 50 more.
Are you some thief?
-Please.
-I can't make you any more.
I sent you a link instead. Check it out.
EPISODE 1. FLOWER MASTER'S
LIFESAVING AMULETS
What's this?
I started an online lecture series
on amulets.
It's 500,000 won per month,
but a 12-month plan is
5.4 million, with a 10% discount.
Are you some thief?
Oh, please. Call me entrepreneurial.
Hey, kiddo.
Aren't you
General Dongcheon's spirit-daughter?
Don't you know she's no ordinary shaman?
If she helped you become a shaman,
you must be pretty powerful too.
Why's a tiger cub harassing a fox?
Don't you call me again.
Bye-bye.
I'm sorry, Gyeon-U.
I'm sorry I upset you, Gyeon-U.
My grandson
is plagued with misfortune.
Please save my grandson's life.
How could this be, Mom?
THE LATE OH OK-SUN
How did you end up like this?
If you had wanted to kick him out,
you should've done so long ago.
Before Mom spent
her remaining savings on him!
I'm sorry…
for being the source
of your misfortune, Grandma.
Are you okay? You took a hit earlier.
It stung a bit.
It jolted me awake.
You really are a strong shaman.
I wonder who the crazy bitch is.
She offered herself as a living sacrifice
to strengthen an evil spirit.
BOOK ON THE SECRETS
OF THWARTING EVIL
She should've known better
than to use those vile spells.
It could cost her life.
"I'll cut a long lock of hair short
and pull out nails."
"I'll write a secret spell with blood
and become a shaman
serving an evil spirit."
"A spell that promises the evil spirit
to go to hell with it."
A GHOST
Whoever did this, she's not a human being.
It's a ghost in a shell of a human being.
How could you, Mother?
How could you ignore my call?
What are you doing in the dark?
Great Aunt?
When greeting an elder,
you first say, "How are you?"
Where are your manners?
How are you?
Hello. I'm fine.
Do you know how much I needed your help?
Ring, ring, ring!
It wasn't just you, okay?
I needed help too.
Don't lie. Why would you need help?
I bet your clients called for help.
You always need to have the last word.
You two are still on great terms.
This is not funny, Great Aunt.
I'm facing a massive life crisis.
Goodness.
It's not just a crisis but a massive one?
Yes.
He's my first love.
How is that Gyeon-U's fault?
They should blame his misfortune.
But he must survive 21 days
to get an apology
from those nasty people or fight them.
There's no point if he dies before then.
Once I fight off his misfortune
and he becomes normal,
Gyeon-U won't be hated.
Actually, he'll be really loved.
Because he's the nicest ever.
Mother. Great Aunt.
Please help me.
I'm too unskilled yet to protect Gyeon-U.
Great Aunt, look…
I'm on my knees.
You fool.
You went on your knees just like that?
What else should I do?
I have no idea what to do.
-Do you like him a lot?
-I love him.
You should be the one
protecting what you value.
Weaklings lose out eventually.
BOOK ON THE SECRETS
OF THWARTING EVIL
Hang, as in "to defeat."
Ma, as in "evil."
Bi, as in "mysterious."
Seo, as in "writing."
"Writing on mysterious knowledge
of defeating evil."
"Book on The Secrets of Thwarting Evil."
It took me 30 minutes to read 4 letters.
It'll take me ten years
to read the whole thing.
I'll never finish it in my lifetime.
HANJA DICTIONARY
Wow, Seong-A.
What's gotten into you?
Why are you studying?
-Any good with hanja?
-I can barely read hangul.
Damn it.
What is it?
What is this antique?
It's a book full of secrets
that make you a damn powerful shaman
who can take on even the strongest ghosts.
They say a way to protect Gyeon-U
is written somewhere in this book.
It's too hard. I don't understand a thing.
Let's find another way, buddy.
TRAVELING AROUND KOREA
Gyeon-U will miss school, won't he?
Yeah. Wouldn't it be best for him
to be alone?
I guess.
He'd be bothered
if there's someone by his side.
Right.
My goodness.
Hello, kid with a nice build.
-Do me a favor.
-No, thanks.
I'm the archery team coach.
I have crazy strong arms.
He'd want to be left alone.
There should be no one by his side.
No.
Absolutely no one.
So,
you left something behind?
-Yeah. I'll leave as soon as I find it.
-No, wait.
Stay here. I'll get it.
No.
It's a thing girls use in secret.
So, have you eaten?
Shall we eat together if you haven't?
I have a pretty huge appetite.
My mother says
if you can lift a spoon,
you can chew and swallow.
That's what life is like.
You didn't even drink water
at the funeral.
Did you eat anything after you left?
At the funeral?
Were you there?
I didn't see you.
Ji-ho.
He filled me in.
I couldn't have been there.
I was so not there.
So, have you… Did you eat?
I'm great at rinsing rice.
Do you want to watch?
-No, thanks.
-Come on.
You'll change your mind
-if you see me do it.
-I won't.
Watch, at least.
If you can't find what you came for,
please get going.
Gyeon-U.
Gyeon-U, don't entertain such thoughts.
What thoughts?
Bad thoughts.
That you want to die.
That ghost
only comes to those
who have such thoughts.
Your grandmother would be sad…
to see you like this.
Please leave.
Hey, Park Seong-A.
Park Seong-A?
She was here?
Forget it.
What do you want?
The coach asked me
to give you the archery team room key.
I did what I was told to do. Bye.
HWAMOK HIGH SCHOOL
ARCHERY TEAM
Give me Yeomhwa's number.
Why do you have this?
-Give me her phone number.
-I don't have it.
She's a regular. You have her number!
I don't have it.
Goodness.
Here.
YEOMHWA
What kind of nonsense is this?
Well, she's…
She's awfully famous.
"Influenza"? That's what she is now.
She's the first shaman
to become so well-known.
She's so popular,
so her number's never disclosed.
If you tap on this and send a DM,
she replies.
Shall I do it for you?
Forget it.
Don't sell Yeomhwa anything.
You'll be punished.
Well done.
I thought I'd die before my time.
Didn't you say you'd meet Dongcheon soon?
Why did you even hide?
You could just meet here and talk.
Well…
I don't look pretty today.
I want to look so pretty
that she'll be stunned.
Will this make me look nicer?
What do you think?
Mother!
You kneel all the time now.
What is it now?
I need your help. There's no time.
BOOK ON THE SECRETS OF THWARTING EVIL
Hey, that's against the rules.
A Suicide Ghost is stuck to Gyeon-U.
It looks like he let it in only recently.
It doesn't follow him around yet.
You've delayed it by about two days, then.
But don't let your guard down.
Suicide Ghost is quick and quiet.
If it gets as close to him
as a noon-time shadow…
NOON-TIME: 11:30 A.M. TO 1:30 P.M.
He'll die.
He'll take his own life.
My gosh.
You and your damn first love.
It's a tough one.
Do you want to save him that badly?
-Yes.
-How about him?
Does he have a reason to live?
It's a Suicide Ghost.
First, he must want to live.
You wanting him to live isn't enough.
He might not know if he wants to live yet.
If you're too sad, that's the first thing
you become unsure of.
Make him want to live first.
Can you do that?
Yes. I'll try everything I can.
This is all I have to offer.
Oh, gosh. Thanks.
The framed folk paintings tell me
my mother-in-law kept her refined taste.
May I ask why you're here?
Well…
Here you go.
USONG COLUMBARIUM 2-28-501
Neither my wife nor her brother
had a single photo of their mother.
We had nothing to put next to her urn.
But now that's settled.
You have lots of photos here.
Thank you,
Uncle.
What's an amulet?
It's just a little piece of paper.
But what sets it apart
from other pieces of paper?
An amulet contains heart.
The determination to protect someone.
The hope that they will stay safe.
The well-wishes for their future.
Those are what fend off misfortune
and protect someone.
What if it were a human
instead of a piece of paper?
-A human?
-Humans are powerful.
They're warm.
"A Human Amulet."
This turns a person into an amulet.
Write on your body
instead of on a piece of paper,
stick close to him,
and share your warmth like this.
Then misfortune will be driven out.
We must hold hands?
You don't have to hold it.
You can brush his with yours.
Sharing your warmth is what's important.
-Mother.
-What?
Oh, right, he's your first love.
Are you too shy to touch him like this?
It's the best method, Mother.
Oh, my gosh. You little…
Wish me luck.
Why didn't you tell me
about the Human Amulet sooner?
I will save Gyeon-U
with my physical touch.
Gyeon-U!
Gyeon-U, long time no see.
Hey, it's great to see you.
Shall I read your palm?
I'm really good at it.
What now?
Should we bring out the child in him?
Hi.
That's too close.
Have you eaten?
Did you sleep well?
Gyeon-U, sit with me.
Is this necessary?
-Then…
-Unnecessarily clingy.
Hey, Ji-ho, morning to you too.
Did you study last night?
You're acting real strange.
What was that?
What?
Here.
Guess which finger I poked you with.
Go on.
-This one.
-Wrong.
This one.
It's too early for that.
Why did I use this finger?
Guys, you're mistaken.
That was me trying
to bring out the child in you.
You're no better than a tabloid hack.
Didn't I tell you to look into it
before spreading a rumor?
-Exactly.
-I'm a victim of fake news too.
Now that's the downside of mass media.
What's going on here?
Why are you sulking?
Our poor Gyeon-U
almost got framed because of him.
-Him, an arsonist? How ridiculous.
-Right.
I went to ask our math teacher
for help with a problem.
What?
An arsonist?
You bought that stupid rumor
and made the kid write a report?
It's not like that, Coach Yang.
Spare me your excuses.
Why would Gyeon-U set a fire?
Why would he set fire to the storage?
The only thing he sets fire to
are the girls' hearts.
I must say he set fire to mine too.
In the end, our homeroom teacher
apologized to the archery coach.
I told you to watch what you say.
I'm not the only one in the wrong.
You spread rumors too.
Not again. Watch your tongue.
Did you forget already?
Well, Gyeon-U even missed school
for a few days because of that.
I feel so terrible about it
that I don't know what to say.
He didn't miss school because of you.
Gyeon-U's grandmother passed away.
That's why he missed school.
Put your face down on your desk.
-You idiot.
-Seriously.
-You should've been careful.
-Smack him.
It made no sense.
I'm glad you're not
being mistaken anymore.
Show some remorse.
Tap my hand again.
Stronger this time.
Well done.
-Let me help you.
-What?
I'll do it. Why are you doing this?
-Hey, wait.
-Hey.
Gyeon-U, where were you?
Why is there so much dust?
-What…
-Look at all this.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my gosh.
Thank you. You got it for me.
What are you doing to Gyeon-U?
Is it a new way of bullying?
It's not.
Would you like it
if someone kept doing this to you?
That's not what I did.
I know that.
You did this.
I'm not bullying him.
What an interesting method.
A person can be an amulet?
So when I touch him like that,
it's not just for my own greed.
The determination to save Gyeon-U.
With that pure intention,
I'm willingly sacrificing myself
to save a life, okay?
There's no ulterior motive.
Stop it. It looks like you totally
have an ulterior motive.
Does it?
Does it have to be so hard?
Can't you just tell him everything
and offer to help?
No. You saw what it's like.
Me being a shaman
puts Gyeon-U in a tight spot.
To accept my help, he must trust me.
A shaman at a funeral?
Must you defame her
even on her final journey?
I can't make things
even more difficult for Gyeon-U.
So what?
You'll become a weirdo for him?
Yeah.
I may not get him to understand,
but I can protect him.
If I have no choice
but to be hated by him, so be it.
I'll just focus on
what I can do right now.
Hey.
You sound like
you're being genuine.
Hey.
I am being genuine.
I'm genuinely a shaman, punk.
What are you doing?
-How far will you follow me?
-What?
Oh, well…
-Until you catch me?
-I just caught you, though.
This is the opposite direction
of where you live.
I'm not going home.
Where are you going?
To the columbarium.
Gyeon-U.
Your grandmother…
She must've been really competitive.
A bouquet of flowers won't make her smile.
She only smiles when you put
a gold medal around her neck.
She's a total gold medal hunter.
You've got this, right?
-Look at mommy.
-I'll get you something yummy.
WE WELCOME THE FIRST-YEAR STUDENTS
Let's eat something tasty.
GYEONGGI YEOUN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
You have to beat your classmates.
-Here. Rock-paper-scissors.
-Rock-paper-scissors.
NATIONAL ARCHERY COMPETITION
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Grandma.
So you were happy that day.
That made you happy.
I'm glad.
JOONGHYUN HIGH SCHOOL
ARCHERY TEAM BAE GYEON-U
When did he…
Three,
two,
one.
For this practical assessment,
you're to pick a key theme
from the chapters of Life and Ethics
and come up with a program
to improve awareness on that topic.
We're all in the same group.
PARK SEONG-A, BAE GYEON-U
I'll give you ten minutes.
Pick a group leader
and if possible,
decide who will give the presentation
so you don't fight later on.
I'll lead our group. No objections, right?
No. You've already taken
the leader's seat too.
-Hey.
-What?
-You be the leader.
-Me?
And you're the assistant leader.
But we don't need one.
-Do you want a beating or not?
-Not.
So just do as I say, okay?
They're screwed.
And I'm screwed too.
Do-yeon.
Why do you have such a nasty thing
clinging to you?
-You're putting my Gyeon-U in danger.
-You do it, then.
The Three Ominous Ghosts.
There are three types of ghosts
you must avoid.
Smiling Ghosts, Dancing Ghosts,
and Baby Ghosts.
What do you think they have in common?
They're all fine being on their own?
That's kind of right.
To be exact,
those three ghosts don't complain.
Most other ghosts move on
when they're consoled,
but not them.
You can't reason with them.
You can't talk to them
if they're not reasonable at all.
But you need to talk to them
to help them cross over, right?
Then the Baby Ghost
will be the most troublesome.
It can't talk at all.
That's right.
That's the worst of the three.
I can barely handle a Suicide Ghost,
and there's a Baby Ghost too?
What should I do, then?
You can wait.
Sorry.
What's up with her?
Ji-ho, you and I will do the research.
Gyeon-U!
You came to the archery field.
Yeah, just because.
How did it feel to shoot after a while?
Did it feel like second nature?
Are you getting back into archery?
No, I'm not.
Come on.
You should've cleaned up after yourself.
You can't just leave like that!
-I cleaned--
-Come with me, punk.
Clean up before you go. Follow me.
-But I--
-Follow me, I said.
Mop every corner, okay?
Under that desk too.
Gyeon-U.
Isn't archery just amazing?
I'm not saying
you should get back into it.
Well…
You know,
girls dumped me left and right
when I was young.
I never got why, but they did.
But you know,
girls who rejected me
with a short, sharp, "I don't like you,"
stuck in my mind forever.
"I should've said this to her face."
"I should've made her
pay me back for the handbag."
"I'd paid 2.5 million won for it
at a duty-free store."
Those girls appear in my dreams even now.
I can never forget them.
But think about this.
"This is what I don't like about you."
"This is why I don't think
we're a good match."
Girls who cared enough
to put in the effort
to explain before the break-up?
I didn't think of them ever again.
"Oh, yes. That happened."
"There was that girl." And that's it.
You were with this bow for ten years.
Even if you want to break up,
put time and effort into it.
Here.
That way, you'll have no regrets.
Who is that?
You don't know Bae Gyeon-U?
The best in the high school division.
He must've decided to come back.
-He's good.
-Agreed.
He's so cool.
He's awesome.
I see he really likes archery.
What a relief.
Here's a special tip
just for my Flower Fam.
When you're plagued by a Baby Ghost,
most shamans will sell you
a Protective Amulet.
But would Baby Ghosts know what that is?
No, no.
They'd have no clue.
So, Protective Amulets?
I don't use them.
I go for wish-granting ones.
Baby Ghosts only leave
when you wish for the good
of both you and them.
You must make an amulet with a kind heart.
Like who? Just like me.
Wish-Granting Amulet, ready.
I'll put it in Do-yeon's desk drawer
tomorrow to console the Baby Ghost.
Suicide Ghost.
Just you wait.
KU DO-YEON
My goodness.
Oh. Hey.
You got here really early.
Good morning.
Hi.
Are you off to shoot some arrows?
-No.
-I know that's what you're off to do.
You absolutely love archery.
We should talk.
Don't you think
you're following me around too much?
Oh, yeah? I don't think so.
Why are you following me around?
Don't do that.
I'm not following you around.
You just happen to be everywhere I go.
Do you call that an excuse…
I see it didn't work.
I want to ask you something. Can I?
-Yeah.
-About archery.
How does it make you feel
when you shoot the arrow?
That's him.
The haunted kid.
-Yes. He causes the accidents.
-The accidents were all him.
I heard.
-Because of him…
-Will something happen today?
That kid suffered too.
-So what if he's great?
-Three.
-The other kids suffer.
-Two.
Something happened on the bus last time.
One.
He's good, I guess.
I feel good.
However strong the wind blows…
I can beat it with a single arrow.
That's cool.
And I'm proud of you.
You want to know why I follow you around?
Kids should be protected by adults,
but you protect yourself.
That's why I want to be nice to you.
Can I do that?
Is it pity?
It's friendship.
Come on.
You'll change your mind
if you see me do it.
Guess which finger I poked you with.
Go on.
Well done.
I'm sorry.
-Hey, Gyeon-U.
-What?
High-five.
-Right now?
-Yeah, right now.
Sure, I guess.
Come on. Hurry.
First love.
Here we go.
SPECIAL THANKS TO OH MIN-AE
Hi. Good morning.
The weather's lovely.
What's he doing instead of archery?
Romance is in the air, I see.
From now on, nothing bad will ever happen.
Because I'll ward it all off.
This is what's bad
about being in a group of three.
I feel left out.
-Let's talk.
-About what?
-I have to dash to my part-time job.
-I'll walk you.
This boundary was made with the purpose
of making the one inside
an evil deity.
I found you.
You, the mask on your face.
Can you take it off for a moment?
Subtitle: Jennifer Jean Lim