All right.
Let's keep the lip balm.
Drink that. You seem cold.
Thanks.
Leave it.
I'd rather not get it wet. I'm fine.
Well, I'm not.
I'll get another one.
No, I really…
Sorry.
Drink that. You might catch a cold.
What happened to these photos?
What are you doing?
Who did this?
No one should draw this amulet
on a person's face.
What are you doing?
Someone drew an Ward Off Evil Amulet
on the photo and erased it.
This is a spell to chase away ghosts.
You shouldn't draw it on a person's face.
I know that.
You do?
I do.
-And that's why I erased it all.
-Who told you
erasing it would cancel out the curse?
Drawing it on a living person's face
may not be all that terrible,
but it's a different story if the person's
been dead for less than 49 days.
It's asking the King of Hell
to curse the dead.
It's a strong curse
condemning your grandmother to hell.
Erasing it alone isn't enough.
So,
the target wasn't me
but my grandma?
These photos…
We must burn them, Gyeon-U.
What happened?
You look like you barely escaped drowning.
I told you it'd be a waste of time.
You really don't know
where Yeomhwa might be?
What are you looking at?
A photo album.
Your old photos.
Isn't my Seong-A adorable?
Are you cross-eyed?
Erasing the ink won't undo the curse.
A wish doesn't get canceled that easily.
A wish to cause harm to others
also counts as a wish, after all.
No wonder.
I thought it was weird.
My wish never came true.
I wished for an ordinary life
with my grandma, but that never came true.
That person's wishes
would always come true.
"That person"?
Do you know who drew these?
Can we meet them right now?
What if you do?
I'll ask them
to take back their wish.
We'll do a cleansing rite
and a rite to pray
your grandmother reaches the afterlife.
Then, you can keep these photos.
Sure.
She might grant you a favor
though she'd never bat an eye
even if I got on my knees.
You know the person who drew these.
It's the shaman you danced with.
She drew these.
She said she was one of the shamans
Great Aunt had called.
That's a complete lie.
That witch beat us to it.
She cast a spell that turns anyone
entering that shack
into an offering to the evil spirit.
I don't get you yet.
Why are you nice to me
when you're so close to Yeomhwa?
Are you two having fun together
toying with me?
By any chance,
if you're toying with me right now…
can you let me off just this once?
My grandma's photos…
really mean a lot to me.
I beg of you…
Heaven and Earth Fairy.
My hands are so cold.
I'm sorry.
I know you won't believe me…
but I met Yeomhwa for the first time
at the abandoned house.
She's really a stranger to me.
And I have
no plans or intentions
to toy with you or anyone else,
ghosts included.
I don't want to make others cry.
Isn't it good?
-Good choice, right?
-Where should we go later?
So you like it?
WHO IS IMMANUEL KANT?
How about this?
What?
Well…
It sucks.
That hurts.
So do better.
That's what people like you do.
I should be praised for doing it at all.
-Are you proud of that?
-I'm not ashamed.
You should be, though.
Are you ashamed of me?
Is that why you're so mean to me?
I'm not being mean at all. I just…
Hey, that's Gyeon-U.
What? Gyeon-U?
I'll be back soon.
What? Hey.
Where are you going?
To touch Gyeon-U.
To touch him? What for?
Gyeon-U!
You can't get on through that door.
Sorry.
It's pretty obvious he's off to see H.
I'd like to see her face.
And hurt her feelings while I'm at it.
I guess the family
just can't agree on anything.
I've opened this case so many times.
I won't be long.
Ma'am. I just need to check.
She wouldn't have stopped
at drawing Ward Off Evil Amulet.
At least, I wouldn't have.
This is…
What do you think you're doing?
Have you been well, Father?
"Father"?
Did you get permission before coming here?
-Go home.
-I want to talk to the shaman.
-What?
-I want to ask her something.
Go home for now. I'll call you.
I know
you won't call me.
The shaman is the only one
who has my number.
The rest of you didn't save my number
in case my misfortune rubbed off on you.
I can't reach the shaman.
It says the number has been disconnected.
I'm not asking this for my sake.
This is about Grandma.
You dare mention my mother?
I won't move an inch until you get her.
I'll speak with the shaman and then leave.
I won't approach or touch anyone else.
I won't answer even if I'm spoken to.
I promise.
Let's be honest.
She's adorable in this photo.
How exactly?
Where? Her gums?
You little…
Welcome back, adorable fairy.
I found a Ghoul-Making Amulet.
We must cleanse it immediately.
AMULET THAT TURNS A SOUL INTO A GHOUL
How did this vile thing
end up in your hands?
I know both the shaman who cast the curse
and the deceased who was targeted.
Then you do meet
the requirements for cleansing it.
But first things first. You said you knew
this shaman who made the amulet.
Why do you know them?
How do you know them?
It's Yeomhwa.
Yeomhwa is the one
who made this amulet.
You're pretty gutsy.
You want me to cleanse
the amulet on the photos?
Well…
My grandmother did nothing wrong.
It's not like
you were born a Newly-Dead
because you did anything wrong.
You're innocent too.
Just…
I'm begging here.
Don't you know what I do?
Misfortune will flock to you,
and blocking that is my priority.
Don't let the misfortune
seep into this family
and take it all with you, Newly-Dead.
So there was a reason you got gutsy.
Your grandmother died
because of you only recently,
but you found an ally already?
After I write this…
And then the final touch.
-Is that right?
-Yes.
Wait, but the lines…
Is this it?
Give it here. I'll do it.
You don't know the deceased.
Stay put. Seong-A has to do it.
Sorry.
I've made a lot of these,
but I've never cleansed one.
I didn't realize
you've had your spirit-daughter
curse others.
It was before I met Mother.
I was with my birth parents then.
Keep your focus.
I am focused.
I tried running just in case.
The curse on Oh Ok-sun,
born in 1951, the Year of the Rabbit,
shall be undone as of now.
May it be done immediately.
-May it be done immediately.
Well done.
You're good at this.
We'll wrap things up now.
You must be exhausted.
Go get some rest.
Yes. Rest up.
Thank you.
MISSED CALLS
PYO JI-HO
The cleansing.
Can't we do it out here?
We must do it inside. It's inside.
What's inside?
Something that doesn't suit a Newly-Dead.
Like pointless hope.
Give me the key.
I don't think he has it on him.
It must be somewhere here.
Found it.
Why are you so cruel?
-Who are you?
-What do you think? I'm Gyeon-U's…
I'm not his friend, exactly.
I'm a shaman.
So you gave him that.
I did not.
Keep it safe.
Don't let her take it from you.
Let's go outside.
We'll talk outside.
Why?
I'd rather stay here.
Fine.
Gyeon-U.
Will you wait outside?
I wonder.
What do you plan on saying…
that you can't let him hear?
It's just
some shaman stuff.
As fascinating as it sounds,
I want Newly-Dead to stay and listen.
Shall we cleanse them together
or will you burn them alone?
I'll just stay here.
You can talk.
It's fine.
Tormenting people must be your thing.
Not really.
I haven't really tormented people.
I control things that aren't people.
That's great.
I'm pretty good at controlling things
that aren't people too.
Gosh, how scary.
Sure, let's talk outside.
Will you stay standing there?
No.
But you are still standing there.
Are you out of your mind?
Why touch that tainted stuff
with your bare hand?
It can't be.
No, right?
It can't be what I'm thinking…
No, you can't do that…
I get your contempt for Yeomhwa,
but you shouldn't counter a curse
with another curse.
Did you get
your patron deity's permission?
Did the General give you the green light?
He said he'll punish me.
That's only right!
You want to use his great power
for something so vulgar as a curse.
No wonder the General God's angry.
So I said I'd accept the punishment.
What?
The Japanese said
that you dig two graves
when you curse someone.
One for the cursed and one for you.
To dig a grave for Yeomhwa,
I must dig one for myself.
Isn't that right?
"To kill"?
TO KILL
I was at the columbarium.
I took care
of the Ghoul-Making Amulet too.
I plan on doing my best
so Ms. Oh can cross over in peace,
so why don't you stop doing this?
Did you cause this fuss just to say that?
It's not "just that."
Humans are not like animals.
They feel emotions.
If you hit a mother,
only she will writhe in pain.
But if you hit her kid in front of her,
they both suffer.
In fact,
the mother suffers more.
Emotional pain is worse
than any physical pain.
So what?
You hurt Gyeon-U to get to his grandmother
and then hurt her to get to him.
That's how you've been
tormenting them, right?
I bet you won't cleanse the photos anyway.
You're going to burn them, no?
Why do you think so?
What shaman preparing a cleansing ritual
comes without cleansing water,
incense, or candles…
and only brings a lighter?
Are you the only shaman?
I'm a shaman too.
Not bad.
Is what Seong-A said true?
Were you
not going to cleanse the photos at all?
What do you think I'd have done?
If they must be burned, this is better.
I don't want
your dirty hands touching them.
If you insist,
I have no more business here.
I should go.
But Newly-Dead.
Of all the people to ally with against me…
you chose the Miwol-dong Baby Shaman?
Your life…
It's truly pitiful.
Have you been calling Gyeon-U
Newly-Dead all this while?
That's what you call
the ghost of a person who died recently.
Gyeon-U's alive and well,
so why call him Newly-Dead?
Just why?
It's a curse.
Pray and beg.
Are you crazy?
Not to me.
To your original patron deity.
Did you think I wouldn't realize
you were serving an evil spirit
and not your patron deity?
Even if you'd tried to cleanse the photos,
you would've failed.
I saw through you the moment
you called Gyeon-U Newly-Dead.
Just how much evil did you do?
Your spirit vessel is cracking.
So what?
You must beg your patron deity.
Ask them to return to you.
A shaman can't serve evil spirits.
Shut your mouth!
Or it might get ripped open.
What's the bottom line?
The shaman hovering around Gyeon-U
is deadly scary
but feeble in shamanic powers?
His 21 days are up in just 2 days.
Why now?
Don't worry. I'm here.
Starting tomorrow,
hug him whenever there's a ghost nearby.
You see the ghosts,
and I must do the physical touch.
Yeah.
We'll have to show some class teamwork.
-Is Gyeon-U okay?
-He'll be okay.
I'm handling things outside.
And your robot friend
is guarding him inside.
That little punk. He's doing his part.
By the way,
why do I feel like something's off?
It feels like I forgot
something important.
Like what? Think carefully.
I'LL KILL YOU, PYO JI-HO
Whatever. I must've messed up again.
See you tomorrow.
Two days.
We just need to get through two more days.
Once the 21 days are over,
you can stay away from shamans forever.
You'll be the same as everyone else…
and be at peace.
BAE GYEON-U! SAVE HIM! PROTECT HIM!
By burning the precious photos,
you saved your precious grandmother.
Ignore what she said. You're not weak.
You're strong enough.
Just hate me.
If I were you,
I'd hate shamans too.
I'm sorry.
Telling someone to hate you…
hurts even if you don't mean it.
You're the one who should hate me,
you dummy.
This is it?
You thought
this could stop me?
Just one more.
If you kill one more person,
you can ascend and become an evil deity.
Just one more.
If you kill
just one more person…
How's this?
Will this help
speed up the process?
Make haste and ascend.
Please come to me…
and be my patron deity.
Hey.
You disinfected your hand, right?
You can't let it get infected.
Goodness.
I can take care of myself.
Can I have a word?
You too.
Yes, you.
What about the presentation?
You two are the only ones
who have done nothing.
I'll do that now. I promise.
I'll get right to it.
Sorry.
For today
and for yesterday.
If I hadn't said anything,
you'd apologize again tomorrow.
I have a question. What about Seong-A?
She didn't do it either.
Yes, she did.
She did it really well too.
Thanks. I heard you did
my share of work on the assignment.
Your shouldn't waste your precious time
on such stupid stuff.
So which of these photos
have ghosts in them?
This one.
And this one.
I knew this was an actual ghost.
No.
Not that one.
Here. The ghost is standing right here.
Here?
You're a truly mysterious species.
It's so cool.
There's not much time. How frustrating.
You traitor.
Move. You're in the way.
-Help me.
-What?
I want to take ghost photos.
Ghost photos?
Here.
Any pictures I take have ghosts in them.
What kind of ghost is this
that it's stuck to the floor like this?
It's a dog.
A Dog Ghost.
What?
Good luck.
You know we're on different teams, right?
-I'm open.
-Over here!
-Come on. Here.
-Pass me the ball.
Hey, what on earth…
Now.
Sir!
He's breaking the rules. Sir!
Fairy.
-Oh, right. There's one.
-Hey!
-Here!
-And this one?
-Over here!
-There aren't any.
Nice pass!
One animal.
-Pass me the ball!
-Two. One human and one animal.
What's wrong with you?
Sorry. My bad.
Sweet Bok-i. She's so cute.
Hey, Fairy.
What's wrong?
Faceless Ghosts?
SO-CALLED "EGG GHOSTS"
GHOSTS WITH NO EYES, NOSE, AND LIPS
-Hey.
-Sir, he keeps playing foul.
-What are you doing?
-Class President.
I'm sick. I'm going home.
-What? That goes on your record.
-What's gotten into Park Seong-A?
What's up with her?
She didn't look unwell.
She didn't look well either.
Take it. Seong-A has something to say.
Seong-A?
Hey, it's me.
Hey, Ji-ho. Make contact whenever you can.
-Stay with him at all times.
-What? Why?
Sure thing.
Don't worry and rest up. Bye.
I knew it. Does she badly need my help?
No.
It's not that. She's just…
You look relaxed.
Do you have time to kill?
She told me to work hard
for our presentation and not upset Hye-ri.
But she's in a foul mood 24-7.
Seong-A wasted her breath.
You be quiet.
Can you finish your parts by today?
By today?
I have archery practice this evening.
Oh, do you?
Then you have until tomorrow morning.
Pull an all-nighter.
Pull an all-nighter?
-By ourselves?
-Yeah.
You're a genius, Hye-ri.
I promise to pull an all-nighter.
Let's stay up all night, friend.
What's wrong with you?
He's so sweaty. Gross.
Your face is red.
You look even uglier.
What was that?
Oh, my goodness. This is so…
There are Egg Ghosts everywhere.
It's so gross.
Egg Ghosts…
I mean, Faceless Ghosts
are usually harmless.
But not when there's
a whole group of them.
It means they're expecting a master
to come and give them new faces soon.
They'll be the first
to celebrate the birth of an evil deity.
And it's obvious
who that evil deity will be.
It must be the one sealed up in the shack.
Let's head there first.
Okay.
Jeez, I really don't want to go.
Yeomhwa.
You are well and truly out of your mind.
First,
let's do what we can right now.
How dare you act up, you weaklings?
You little…
I'll come for you!
Gosh, you're so scary.
What do we do now?
We should find that marionette's head.
If we don't undo the spell on it,
ghosts will keep coming.
The head spreads the word
that an evil deity is on the way.
She's right. We must find the head first.
All right. Let's find the head.
By the way,
Heaven and Earth Fairy
seems more knowledgeable
about this area than you, my dear general.
About the Ghoul-Making Amulet too.
I suppose you're feeling better
judging by how you're yapping again.
I'm just curious.
I'm bubbling with questions.
Like I said, I have questions.
Just go find the head.
Gyeon-U.
What?
My bow's weight is off.
Take a look for me.
Let me see.
Stand over here.
What feels off?
I can't say.
Is the center off-kilter?
A bit.
Doesn't it feel off?
Try drawing it.
-It feels okay.
-It's okay? Really?
There's no way it's fine, though.
-Was archery a touchy-feely sport?
-Are you sure it's not off?
-You're weird. What's wrong?
-No, it's the bow.
-Well?
-Sir?
A motorcycle!
A bicycle!
Hey.
A cart!
Let go.
-Let go.
-Why are you so strong?
Watch out!
We live in a dangerous world.
Don't we, Gyeon-U?
Seriously…
Gyeon-U!
-Sir. Let me help you.
-Me too.
-One, two.
-Hey.
-What? Why?
Forget it.
About Seong-A.
What? Seong-A?
What about her?
Why ask about her all of a sudden?
It's nothing.
Is this it?
My gosh! This is it!
It's disgusting! Yikes.
Bring it over so we can burn it.
Burning won't do any good.
A rumor should be countered
with another rumor.
The fastest way to get the ghosts to flee
is to make them think
the evil spirit won't ascend.
I get it, but doesn't that hurt?
You sliced your hand as if it's nothing.
It hurts more if you hesitate.
I've done this when I was a kid.
Good guy. Hang in there a little longer.
Come back to life,
Gyeon-U Gyeon-U.
Get out.
Get out!
Okay, I'm getting out.
Good night.
I have a question.
Ask away.
Do you know the shaman you danced with?
Are you two close?
She's Miwol-dong Baby Shaman.
But that was the first time
I met her in person.
She should live a good long life too.
When she dies, she'll go to hell like me.
MIWOL-DONG BABY SHAMAN
An eight-year-old baby shaman.
Seong-A starts her day
a little earlier
than other children her age.
DOCUSERIES THREE DAYS
Roses are in bloom.
Right here.
That's right.
My daughter got a rose tattoo there.
She's with child.
What?
But she's only 20 years old.
As for who the father is,
she will never tell.
Are you pregnant?
How do you know that, Mom?
Have you heard of Miwol-dong Baby Shaman?
She was in a documentary ten years ago.
She was pretty famous.
That's me.
You won't make much with such small fries.
You can't even make
a proper Ghoul-Making Amulet?
Don't cry.
You shouldn't cry.
This is what makes Mom and Dad happy.
I won't see any ghosts.
I'll be a good girl.
Don't leave me.
Please don't leave me.
Kiddo.
You're tempting the heaven's punishment.
Why would you bring that up?
I can share it nonchalantly
because it's not a big deal.
I first started school
as a middle schooler.
Those who suffered
because of Miwol-dong Baby Shaman.
Justice lives, and it prevails.
-Do it quick.
-Did you think it was over?
WE HATE YOU,
MIWOL-DONG BABY SHAMAN PARK SEONG-A
I never imagined this, honestly.
TEACHING MIWOL-DONG BABY SHAMAN
A LESSON
I got what I deserved, I guess.
The end.
It's done.
Stop acting tough and get over here.
What are you both doing?
When kids don't cry
when they're supposed to,
it breaks us adults' hearts.
My heart's broken right now.
Don't be dramatic.
This is nice.
Hey.
When did you and Seong-A get close?
We're not close.
Last year, when we were in 10th grade.
Then you don't know
what she did before then?
You were there when she explained.
She didn't attend elementary
and middle school.
Exactly how horrible have I been to her?
Do you both think I'm stupid?
I've met so many shamans.
You touch me because Seong-A told you to.
It's what she used to do.
You're right. You heard me say,
"Come back to life, Gyeon-U Gyeon-U."
You'd be an idiot not to catch on.
Do you believe it now
that Seong-A's trying to protect you?
Yeah.
Gyeon-U.
Just you wait until tomorrow's over.
You ungrateful little punk.
What's so special about tomorrow?
You just need to know
that you've been a huge jerk.
See you tomorrow, Gyeon-U Gyeon-U.
You don't get to call yourself a father!
How dare you, you brat!
You piece of shit.
You punk.
Jin-ung?
You're out of your mind, punk.
Bok-i.
You idiot.
Bite him.
-You can do it, Bok-i. Bite him.
-You little…
Bite the man hard.
Do it!
What was that?
-Hey.
-Well done.
Seong-A.
I didn't do anything, Gyeon-U.
I really didn't.
What? I was just…
Let's continue with the group work today.
My gosh. You're awake for once, Seong-A.
Jin-ung's not here?
-No.
Right, it's about time he went back
to his old ways, isn't it?
Let's get your desks into formation.
So change your phone number and move.
Mom. Don't call anyone, okay?
Especially not me. Okay?
The bastard got out of prison!
If he finds you this time…
you'll die.
I said I knew you well, didn't I?
Hey, you!
I won't beat you up. Stop right there!
Kim Jin-ung!
Hey!
Are you here, son?
If I catch you, you're dead meat!
Hey, son!
Come out and talk to me.
Kim Jin-ung!
What's this?
A ring?
Let me summarize it one last time.
We're covering
Kant's anthropocentric philosophy.
What's the main idea again?
It's all about putting people first.
Humans are to be at the center,
not machines.
It's not about money but about people.
People are precious beings,
so they shouldn't be treated
as a means to an end.
-Why?
-What?
What do you mean, "why?"
What aren't you getting
about not treating humans as a means?
Sir.
I'll go and get Jin-ung.
-Where…
-Hey.
Is Jin-ung in here?
Please help!
-I can't go inside.
-Help!
Bok-i, I can't go in here.
Help me!
Damn it.
Help!
I really shouldn't do this.
Lady Fairy went into the abandoned house.
Help…
Jin-ung, breathe.
Jin-ung!
Release him already!
Stop it!
Hello, Shaman.
Shouldn't you say hello back?
SPECIAL THANKS TO GWAG JA-HYEONG
You should have let me die then and there.
Gyeon-U!
A person shouldn't do this
to another person.
I chose the last offering for you myself.
Shall I tell you
why your life is a living hell?
Come with me, you nutcase.
Why is it Gyeon-U again?
Because he's easy prey.
How much evil did you commit
that everything's so dark?
I'll just kill you all!
Was I human?
I found you.
Subtitle: Jennifer Jean Lim