[IAN] They blew something up.
Look for Liam Roja!
If anyone sees someone trying to escape,
shoot to kill!
Isko, are we all gonna die?
- You're not going to die.
- I need to leave!
Come on!
[FIN] Is it possible that Liam was there?
Maybe he really needed your help.
[LUNA] Thank you, dude.
- Where did they go anyway?
- [LIAM] Probably to the private dock.
- [LUNA] Let's go?
- Let's go.
[OLSEN] The private dock…
I'll check it first.
Let go of your anger.
What's done is done.
Let's not blame one another.
- [BEN] Stay here.
- [ICE] I'm going with you.
[REPORTER] Renowned jeweler
and celebrity manager Ronaldo Chan
is now in critical condition
after a shooting incident
earlier on Sampaguita Street, Manila.
Hello, sir.
Where are you going?
To the private deck.
There are speedboats there.
[LIAM] You're one of the hostage takers!
[JULES] No, he's not! No!
[IAN] I just agreed to my brother's plan.
Who's your brother?
The one who put the vest on you.
I wanted to help the hostages,
but I couldn't.
- It's too late now.
- [LIAM] Not yet.
Go.
Let's go, dude.
Olsen, keep your eyes peeled.
We don't know how many of them there are.
Here they come. Get down. Get down.
- [LIAM] Go, go.
- [LUNA] Get down!
- [LUNA] Olsen?
- Olsen.
- [GIRLS] Hey!
- Because of you, my mom almost died!
- Bro…
- [BEN] Stop!
Enough.
- [LIAM BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [LUNA] Bro, enough.
- Enough, please!
- [BEN] Stop it, you two!
[HUFFS]
Stop it, you two!
Think about how we're going
to get out of here!
[OLSEN BREATHING HEAVILY]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
We need to get back to Mama.
Fin, let's go.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
I also found social media records
showing that Ona Chan,
together with Jules Santos,
Bogs Lim,
and Ice Mercado,
checked in at La Playa Roja.
And this is their last post.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Sir, after this,
we lost communication with La Playa Roja.
We're going back to La Playa Roja.
But we must do this quietly,
and move fast.
This is a classified operation.
No information leaves this room.
Understood?
- Sir, yes, sir.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're not being vigilant.
[LUCAS] The diamonds are now in my hands.
I don't care.
What I'm telling you--
You don't care about your cut?
- We'll get a bigger cut then.
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What I'm telling you
is that you've done a messy job tonight.
Sir, isn't it your job
to clean up the mess?
Do your job then.
[SNICKERS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma! Come on.
- Where's your grandpa?
- He's waiting. Let's go.
Hurry up!
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
- Clear. Come on, come on.
- Come on, come on.
[LIAM MUTTERS INDISTINCTLY]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Chief.
There are only five men on guard.
You got this.
Go on. Be careful.
- Bro.
- Oh?
- Let's go.
Be vigilant.
[LIAM] Stay here, okay?
[BEN] Be careful.
- Ben, be vigilant.
- You too, you too.
- [GRUNTS] Argh!
- [KNIFE WOOSHES]
- [GROANS]
[BODY THUDS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LUNA WHISTLES]
- [MAN GRUNTS]
- [KNIFE WHOOSHING]
[KNIFE WHOOSHES]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BLOWS LAND]
[GRUNTING] Argh!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS] Argh!
[BODY THUDS]
- [KNIVES WHOOSH]
- [GROANS]
[GOON GROANS]
[LIAM PANTING] Let's go.
[OFFICERS] Go, go, go!
[AREZA] Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Sir.
- Is everyone ready?
- Yes, sir!
Let's move!
Let's go, let's go!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
We need to keep moving!
Your friend might've told them
about our plan.
I'm sorry! I didn't know!
I'll take you to the speedboat.
What? What about you?
I'm staying here.
Bro, we're not leaving without you.
I'm not leaving without Mama and Papa.
[WIND BLOWING]
[KNOB CLICKS, DOOR OPENS]
Hey, where have you been?
Uh, Dado…
I've been looking for you.
Where did you go?
I just needed some fresh air.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
Fresh air, huh?
Hmm?
Then why do you look worried?
I'm just thinking about the hostages.
I'm wondering if they escaped.
That's it.
You've thought about that?
How would they get off the island?
They, uh…
planned on using the speedboat
at the private dock.
Speedboat? Hmm?
Who are you referring to?
[TENSE MUSIC]
[OLSEN] There.
They're here.
Come on!
[WENDY GRUNTS]
[ICE] Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Grandpa, please take care of Mama.
[BEN] Okay.
Here's the key to the speedboat.
- [KEYS JINGLE]
- What are we waiting for?
Let's go!
- [FIN] Let's go.
- [LIAM] Let's go.
- [LIAM] Let's go!
- [FIN] Hurry!
- [FIN] Come on.
- [LIAM] Come on!
Those who are positioned
near the private dock,
Liam Roja and his group are en route
to escape near your location.
If Dr. Jessie Morillo's with them,
catch him.
Bring him here.
As for the rest…
just shoot them.
Let them all die.
[RADIO BEEPS]
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[JESSIE] Go!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- [JESSIE YELPS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [SCREAMS]
- Duck down! Duck down!
[GUNSHOTS]
- Let's go!
- Jessie! Let's get out of here!
We can't leave yet!
- We're all going to die!
- How about the others?!
- We need to leave now!
- Stop it!
- We're all going to die here! [SHRIEKS]
Let's leave now!
No! I don't want to die!
I don't want to die with Jessie!
Let's leave!
- Hurry up!
- [JESSIE] Shut up!
[CONNEY] You're so selfish!
I don't want to die here!
[JULES BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BOAT ENGINE REVVING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [OLSEN GRUNTS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[BOAT ENGINE REVVING]
Pa!
Pa! The speedboat!
Hide!
[GUNSHOTS]
Get out of there!
Come on!
- Let's go!
- [WENDY GROANS]
[GUNSHOTS]
- Olsen, ammo!
- Liam!
[GUN CLICKS]
[RAPID GUNSHOTS]
- [FIN YELLS]
- [PIERCING NOISE]
[LUNA] No!
[PIERCING NOISE]
[EXPLOSION]
[FAINT HEARTBEAT]
[PIERCING NOISE CONTINUES]
[GROANING]
Argh!
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [HIT LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [YELLING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
- [HITS LAND]
Liam!
[GOON YELLING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OLSEN] Come on.
- Ice, let's go. Hurry.
- [MUSIC BECOMES PENSIVE]
- Luna?
- Let's go!
Hey! Hey!
What?
Why did they leave us?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
How are we getting off the island?
Doc Jessie left us, son.
We can't stay here for long.
Back! We need to go back!
Mom, come on.
- [FIN] Let's go, Chief!
- [LUNA] Hurry!
- Chief!
- Ice, come on. Stay close.
Huh?!
[MUSIC BECOMES DRAMATIC]
[GASPS] They're here--
- [SCREAMING]
- [BULLETS THUDDING]
[CONNEY SCREAMS]
[RAPID GUNSHOTS]
- [CONNEY SCREAMS]
- [WATER SPLASHES]
- Conney!
- Faster, Jessie! Faster!
[WHIMPERING] Hurry!
[MUSIC BECOMES INTRIGUING]
Magnus? Magnus!
- [GASPS]
- [PANTING]
- What could've happened--
- Wait, wait. I'll take this.
- [GASPING LOUDLY]
- [RIFLE CLICKING]
Oh my God. Oh my God.
- Where's our son?
- Damn it! No ammo.
We need to find Liam, please.
I'm begging you.
We need to look for Liam.
[PANTING LOUDLY]
Someone's coming.
[MUSIC BECOMES SUSPENSEFUL]
[GRETA PANTING]
[SIGHS]
Boss, if we don't fight back,
they'll get stronger.
One of them has to go.
[EMIL] Who escaped on the speedboat?
They already told us who.
It's the Morillo couple,
their nurse Claire, and Jules Santos.
Our guys are after them,
but we don't have updates yet.
[SHARP STING]
[MOTORBOAT ENGINE WHIRRING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[POLICE] Let's go! Let's go!
Clear! Clear!
Let's move!
[MUSIC BECOMES THRILLING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
- [INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WENDY GRUNTS]
Mom, let's stay here.
Mom? Mom, come on.
Okay.
- Stay here, all right?
- Mm-hmm.
[HUFFS]
- Hey, who's there?!
- [LUNA] Olsen, it's us!
[INTRIGUING MUSIC FADING]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- [LUNA] Olsen!
- [BEN] Hey, hey!
- [WENDY] Olsen!
- Let him go!
- What's your problem?!
- I do have a problem!
- What?!
- [LUNA] Calm down.
We could've been out of here,
but you let them get the key from you!
- [WENDY] Son!
- I didn't let them. They took it from me.
Then, the bad guys came.
You saw what happened, right?!
I didn't do anything!
You've done nothing
but put us all in danger!
- Please! That's enough, son!
- You keep nearly getting us killed!
You told them where we were hiding!
You got my mom shot, Liam!
- Stop it! Enough.
- My mom was shot!
Now, it's your fault
we didn't get to escape.
- You asked me what my problem was.
- [WENDY] Enough. Stop.
You and your mother
are nothing but trouble!
- What did you say?
- Liam!
- You heard me.
- Olsen, stop it!
You're dragging my mom into this?!
Your mother's hands are dirty, Liam!
- No, no, son. Don't!
- Always have been. Didn't you know?!
- Stop it, Olsen! Stop--
- No, Mom. No!
He should know it. Get this!
Your mother made my mom
take the fall for her case!
And what for?
In exchange for a million pesos!
One million, Liam!
We lost her for ten years!
All for a million pesos!
All because of your mother!
[WENDY] Stop it, please.
Because she had the money,
your mother took advantage
of our situation.
- Olsen, stop!
- Mama could never do that.
- So, my mom's a liar now, huh?
- [WENDY] Stop!
- Mom? Mom?!
- Mrs. Wendy?
[FIN] Ice! Ice! Help me with them.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- [BREATH SHAKING] Enough.
- [OLSEN] Hold on. Let's lie down.
- [BEN] It must be the stress.
- Liam, are you okay?
- [FAINTLY] Huh?
- I'm sorry, Mom. I'm sorry.
- Are you okay?
[OLSEN] It'll be okay. I'm so sorry.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES THRILLING]
Where's our rescue?
They're still not here.
[JACINTO] Why didn't you tell me about
the La Playa Roja operation?
Boss Emil wants
more booby traps planted.
[DADO] If anyone goes there,
boom!
Don't blame Liam.
[LIAM] We don't know
what the truth really is.
You know, I don't care
if you believe me or not.
I'm sure they'll kill Liam
once they find him.
We need to get to him first.
No, stop! Please spare us!
[GOON] Kill everyone
who tries to escape!