You think you can just buy us with money?
If it wasn't for me, you'd have been
dead a long time ago, Olsen!
Why won't you just apologize to Olsen?
You side with them
as if they're your family!
Liam and I are your family!
I'm your wife, Magnus!
Auntie Wendy. Olsen.
I'm sorry.
What Mama did was wrong.
Liam, are you forgetting
the other thing you did to us?
What else do you want me to do?
Kneel in front of you?
Will that undo the gunshot my mother took?
Olsen, Liam, stop it.
Can't we focus on escaping
from this island first?
Three people are patrolling
the north perimeter
in the villa areas. Over.
Do you have visual on the hostages?
- Command, negative.
- Maintain observation of the area.
Report any movements right away. Over.
Let's go! Let's leave this island!
Go and save yourself.
You have parents
who are worrying about you.
You and Olsen,
you're my family.
Luna knows where the staff are.
We'll take as many as we can.
Okay. We'll get the hostages
in the banquet hall out.
We'll meet here after.
We'll try to look for Fin and Grandpa too.
- Okay.
That's the spirit!
- One, two--
- We're just wasting time. Let's go.
[LUCAS] How did Dr. Morillo,
his wife, and Jules Santos escape?
They're guarded by police, and I'm sure
there are police officers over there too.
- Put your guns down!
- Hands in the air!
[OFFICER] Confirmed, sir. Ben Bonifacio,
Head of Security at La Playa Roja.
Let them go.
We're here to save you.
Sir, this is where the banquet hall is.
All the hostages are there.
The base of operations
of the hostage takers
is most likely in there too.
How can we get there without being caught?
Sir, every area
we'll pass through has guards.
It's dangerous, sir.
It'll be safer if we approach
from the sides.
We'll have more hiding spots.
Okay, let's form three groups.
The first group
will head to the north side.
The second group will head out west,
here in the lagoon area,
and the third group
will guard the beachfront.
If anything goes wrong,
you know what to do.
- Am I clear?!
- [OFFICERS] Yes, sir!
The goal is extraction.
We need to get the survivors out alive.
We have to get them off this island.
- Let's move!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- [OFFICER 1] Let's go!
- [OFFICER 2] Let's move!
- [BEN] Be careful, Fin.
- Let's go, Chief!
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Lucas just gave me a report.
Dr. Morillo has escaped with his wife,
along with one of the influencers,
Jules Santos.
They managed to reach Alicante alive.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
We need to tighten our security
across the entire island.
We must have eyes on every corner.
Stay on alert.
I'm sure police officers
are already on the island.
Why didn't Captain Jacinto alert us?
We can't rely on Captain Jacinto now.
Why?
What happened?
Lucas also reported that
he's in detention.
So we're doomed.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
So we've lost our protection?
[MUSIC SWELLS]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOMINGO] I don't like wasting my time.
All I want is for you to explain this.
Make me understand.
Why did they find this inside your house?!
[ENVELOPE SLAMS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
With all due respect, sir,
that money isn't mine.
Are you saying that two million pesos
just magically appeared in your house?
Cash?
[CHUCKLING]
Don't take me for a fool.
Answer my question.
- [SLAMS]
- Where did you get that money?!
Someone is sabotaging me, sir.
They planted the money in my house.
We suspect that you have a hand
in what's happening in La Playa Roja.
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
We still have the hostages
and the VIPs of the resort.
They'll act as our protection.
- Dado.
- Sir?
Get one of the hostages
from the banquet hall.
Gwen, make sure the staff
stay in the stockroom.
Ian.
Connect all TV monitors to one source.
That can be arranged, but…
[CLEARS THROAT] What for?
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
It's getting too boring for us
and the guests here at the resort.
We need to entertain them.
Yes, sir.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GRUNTS, GROANS]
[EMIL] Was it Magnus?
Is he hurting you?
How many times has this happened, huh?
Padua, get up.
Why? What do you want from me?
Just do as we say. Get up. Hurry!
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[LOCKS RATTLING]
[CELL DOOR, LOCKS RATTLING]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LOCKS RATTLING]
[LATCH CLANKS]
[METAL DOOR CREAKS]
Padua. Long time no see.
What do you want from me?
[CHUCKLES]
It's you who needs something from me.
Remember, you are charged with murder.
You killed a fellow cop
and got involved in drugs.
If you serve your sentence,
you'll be dead before you get out of here.
I can help you.
In exchange…
I have a job for you.
We'll make big money there.
Their guests are all rich.
What we'll take from them
won't put a dent in their wallets.
It's time to make those bastards pay.
La Playa Roja?
Magnus Roja's property?
You know him?
No.
But many people know that billionaire.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir.
That's my former fellow inmate,
Diosdado Menor,
an explosives expert.
He's one of the sharpest people I know.
He works clean.
Ian Menor, Dado's younger brother.
An expert when it comes to computers.
Lucas Esteban, another former inmate.
Ex-special forces.
He was stationed in Mindanao
for ten years.
He's a veteran fighter.
He doesn't hesitate to kill. Right, Lucas?
That's Roberto Bobong Aguas,
Dado's recruit.
He's an arms expert.
He can use any kind of gun.
A sharpshooter.
I also recruited a martial arts expert.
Hm.
[DARK MUSIC SWELLS]
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EXHAUST FAN WHIRRING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LOUD THUD FROM DISTANCE]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
- [ICE] Olsen!
- [GROANS]
Olsen!
[MAGNUS] Wendy!
What's wrong?
Hm?
Sorry.
It was just a bad dream.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I see. Uh… go back to sleep.
They haven't returned yet.
I didn't mean for you and Greta to fight.
I shouldn't have told my son
about what happened.
I made a promise to your wife.
I made a promise to my friend.
Don't blame yourself, Wendy.
Magnus.
Promise me you'll forgive Greta.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MAGNUS SIGHS]
You're such a good friend.
You know I'm not.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
You know what?
The first thing I'll do
once I get off this island
is treat Mama to grilled pork belly.
[OLSEN CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
We'll eat it with our hands.
We'll also have pickled papaya
and spiced coconut vinegar.
I'll let her eat her heart out for once.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Why that specifically?
Because grilled pork belly
is her favorite.
But I usually forbid her from eating it
because she has high blood pressure.
Then you shouldn't feed her that.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Life is short.
Hey, don't worry too much, okay?
Yes, life is short, but…
we'll get through this. I promise.
I'll even go with you
to buy grilled pork belly.
The rice is on me.
Pfft! Just the rice?
Then I'll buy you
some soda too. [SNICKERS]
How about
dessert?
Hey, didn't you just say
your mom has high blood pressure?
The dessert is for me.
[OLSEN SIGHS] Fine. Dessert's on me too.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Ice, run. Go--
- [GUNSHOTS]
Ah! Olsen!
[GUNSHOTS]
[OLSEN GRUNTS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GRETA] In a week's time, Wendy,
you'll finally be free.
It's been ten years, Greta.
Thank you for enduring this much.
But…
I have another favor I wanted to ask you.
What is it?
Can you
keep our agreement a secret?
Especially from Magnus.
Of course.
But why?
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
If only you knew what we've been through.
Magnus and I almost separated.
Many times.
But in the end,
we're still together.
Maybe that's what happens
when you truly love each other.
I can't risk damaging
our relationship again, Wendy.
And this…
This secret
might ruin my relationship with Magnus.
Greta,
you can trust me.
I won't let that happen
to your relationship.
Or our friendship.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[LIAM] Careful.
[LUNA] What are you saying, bro?
What I'm saying is,
what if my anger has no basis?
What if he really had nothing to do with
all the things I'm blaming him for?
With everything I found out
about Mama,
I don't know what to believe.
I'm so confused.
What is the truth?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Can you do it?
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
- [EMIL] Ayen!
- Bro.
Ayen!
[LIAM] Shh, shh.
[EMIL] Ayen!
Ayen!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EMIL] You walked out on me again!
This is for you!
For you and your sibling!
Bro.
I believe that everything will be fine.
We will be able to escape here alive.
Hmm?
- Let's go.
- Come on.
[HOPEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[LIAM GRUNTS] Hmph.
Come.
[EMIL] So? Did you see her?
[GOON] No, sir.
[EMIL] Look for her everywhere.
Don't stop searching.
Come. Let's go this way.
Ayen!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LUNA] Hurry.
[WENDY] Magnus.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
I should be out there, not Liam.
But you're also needed here
to take care of Greta.
I know how hard it is for a parent
not to know what's happening
to their child.
I trust God to keep them safe.
You know, Wendy,
I regret…
being a…
bad father and having
a bad relationship with Liam.
It's my fault for not believing in
what he wanted to do.
And in his capabilities.
You know the bloody irony
of it all is that
it took a hostage situation happening
for me to see how lucky I am
to have a son like him.
I've seen your son.
He's brave.
He's bold.
Despite everything,
you and Greta were able
to raise him to be a good man.
You know, Wendy,
while you were in jail,
Chief Ben was a good guardian to Olsen.
You were too.
Olsen told me a lot about you.
You and Papa
acted as Olsen's fathers.
Thank you so much, Magnus.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm sorry, Wendy.
I'm truly sorry that
you didn't get the chance
to be with your son
while he was growing up.
It's all because of Greta.
Magnus.
Wendy.
I admire you.
The sacrifices you made for Olsen.
Your
unconditional love for him.
For being a good mom
and a good person.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY, SNIFFLES]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES STIRRING]
Come on.
[LUNA] Dude.
Let's rest for two minutes.
Sure.
[BOTH PANTING]
[OLSEN] Let's go.
Careful.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GOON AND OLSEN GRUNTING]
[GOON GROANS]
[OLSEN GRUNTS]
- [COCKS RIFLE]
- [RAPID GUNFIRE]
[ICE] Olsen! Olsen!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
Ice?
- I'm sorry!
- It's okay. I'm okay.
Hey, hey, hey.
Be strong, okay?
I'll keep you safe.
I promise. Come on.
[CARIASO]
Everyone, stay alert.
[LIAM] Would you do anything for
your family? Even if it's wrong?
[EMIL] Even VIPs will get killed
if you don't do what we want!
[TOPAK] We're all going to die!
We can't just wait for their next move.
We need to rescue the hostages.
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
[LUNA] There are guards everywhere.
[GOON GRUNTS]
[LIAM] When I come back,
I'll have our staff with me.