A hostage situation is currently unfolding
at the famous and exclusive
island destination,
La Playa Roja.
We just heard the news.
Two of the escaped hostages are now dead.
- Who?
- A Jules Santos and a Mama Ona Chan.
[WENDY] Olsen, what happened to Liam?
- Liam! Liam!
- Ma'am! Ma'am!
What are you doing, Ma?
You might have wounds
and just not be telling me.
I promise, I'm not hurt.
I'm okay, thanks to Sir Magnus.
- Magnus?
- He saved me.
He would've done the same for me.
He reminds me of you.
He has a big heart.
Thank you for saving Liam.
- You didn't abandon us.
- Thank you too, sir.
[LENI] Aren't we going home yet, Pa?
[EMIL] You and your sister
can go home first.
I need to finish my mission.
Ayen's not with us on this island.
She's here.
But your sister changed her mind again.
But I have made up my mind.
I'm going to kill Magnus.
After that, we will live a luxurious life
just like the Rojas.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Uh, nurse? I have a question.
When do you think I can be discharged?
Our companions have already left.
You're not cleared for discharge yet.
Your blood pressure is elevated.
Oh, all right.
[JOY] Uh, ma'am? What about me?
I just need to verify your records, ma'am.
I'll get back to you.
- [JOY] Thanks.
- Sige.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [JOY] Ma'am?
- Hmm?
We're still lucky, huh?
We got out of that hellhole.
Mm-hmm.
Too bad Love didn't make it out with us.
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
Oh, Love…
And Smile--
I mean, Leni.
[JOY SIGHS HEAVILY]
I hope the ground swallows her up.
I wish. Damn that Smile.
[JOY HUFFS]
By the way, Joy,
do you remember how
you accused me of being the traitor?
Hmm?
- Sorry, ma'am.
- "Sorry"?
I think you're the reason
my blood pressure's elevated!
But, ma'am, what about
Sir Liam and everyone else?
Do you think they're okay?
A-And are we really safe?
Did you hear about
Ma'am Jules and her manager?
But Doc Jessie and Ma'am Conney are fine.
They were saved.
And the police are all over Alicante.
No one in their right mind
would attack us here.
So you have nothing to fear.
Okay?
We're safe here.
- [TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
- [WOMEN SCREAM]
- What--
- My apologies, ma'am.
I'm the bodyguard of Mr. Maristella.
[HAPPY SIGHS IN RELIEF, PANTS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- Happy, Joy.
- Uh. [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Hello, Senator.
I'm Joy. Hello, Senator.
I'm really glad you're both okay.
I know you went through hell back there.
But I have to ask…
Did you see my son?
Is he okay?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Enough! [SOBS]
- [WHIP SNAPS]
- [DADO GRUNTS]
[MACKY SCREAMS]
Enough!
We need him alive.
[MACKY GRUNTS, GROANS]
[SHOUTS]
- [MACKY ON VIDEO] Please…
- [DADO] Huh?
- [WHIP SNAPS]
- [AGONIZED SCREAM]
This is enough
to warn anyone who tries to defy us.
Sir Macky, Senator?
Uh… [CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY] He's fine.
If… If I remember correctly,
he was at the restaurant dancing.
We were all dancing along.
Then he went off with his group.
- I went back to the rest of the staff.
- Um… what group?
The VIP hostages.
Guests, Senator!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
She meant to say, VIP guests, Senator.
Yes, guests.
So you're not sure if my son is safe?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Um…
Senator,
a lot of people were left behind.
Maybe you could send some help?
Senator…
The hostage takers are ruthless.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING, SCREAMING]
- [WHIP SNAPS]
[SOBS] Oh my God!
Oh my God!
[SCREAMS]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOAT MOTOR HUMMING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HUMMING CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE BUZZING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GRUNTS]
- [MACKY ON VIDEO] Aah! Enough!
- [CHUCKLES]
- Please! Enough!
- [DADO] Huh?
[PHONE RINGING, BEEPS]
Boss Emil?
Those cops won't quit.
They won't leave the island.
And more are coming.
What do you want me to do?
Ask the senator for 100 million
for Macky Maristella's life.
To make up for the ransom
we won't get from the escaped VIPs.
Boss Emil, don't forget about our deal.
I won't just ask
Senator Maristella for money.
You negotiate with him about that.
What matters now is that we stop
the police from sending reinforcements,
and that we get rid of the ones
still here on the island.
Find a way to take care of
that nosy cop too.
Yes, sir.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[NEWS ANCHOR] According to the police,
a rescue team has been deployed
to La Playa Roja.
But we haven't received an update
regarding the hostages there.
One of the hostages is the son
of Senator Eduardo Maristella,
Macky Maristella.
[PHONE CHIMES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's go, let's go.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
We're severely undermanned, sir.
Ammo is running low.
Only nine of us are left.
Estimated nine suspects
left on their side.
They are armed with M4 rifles,
M9 pistols,
and hand grenades.
How will you be able to evacuate
the civilians, Lieutenant?
We'll take them to where we docked, sir.
We'll send the coordinates.
But, sir, the area's
covered with explosives,
trip wires, and landmines.
I sent Cariaso and Bautista
to check if the path is safe to use.
Sir,
once evacuation is complete,
we need immediate reinforcement
to neutralize the suspects.
Where is the senator's son?
We saw Macky Maristella
during the encounter yesterday.
But we weren't able to secure him.
Can you confirm if he's still alive?
No, sir. We cannot confirm his condition.
[DOMINGO] We may negotiate.
But let me repeat,
I will not agree to the demands
of the hostage takers.
Carry out your plan.
Evacuate all civilians to safety.
I'll send reinforcements immediately.
Okay?
Copy, sir.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
With all due respect, Senator,
you are not authorized to come in here.
Have you seen this?
[LUCAS] Senator Maristella,
do you still want to see your son alive?
Of course you do.
Then help us convince
that damn Major Domingo.
Tell him to get rid of the police here,
and not to send reinforcements.
So what are you planning to do?
Senator Maristella.
I can assure you we're doing
everything we can to save your son.
But let me reiterate,
we will not give in to the demands
of the hostage takers.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [LIAM GRUNTS]
- Eat up, son.
Mm.
Mm…
Have some.
- Finish it, son.
- Ma.
Please, I'm okay.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INHALES, EXHALES DEEPLY]
I know you're not, Ma.
Lieutenant Areza said
they're getting ready
to get us off this island.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you still mad?
Or not?
[LIAM] Would you do anything
for your family?
Even if it was wrong?
What do you mean?
What Mama did to Aunt Wendy…
That was so wrong.
But her reason for doing it
was so she wouldn't be parted from me.
Does that justify it?
In my opinion, dude,
it's still wrong.
But maybe our perspective will change
once we become parents ourselves.
What you did was wrong.
So wrong.
But, Ma…
I can't stay mad at you for too long.
No matter what you do…
I'll still love you the same.
[GRETA BREATHING SHAKILY]
I love you too, son.
There's so much happening, Ma.
I don't know who to trust anymore.
Can you believe that Smile,
a member of our staff,
is Emil's child?
I really think he's the leader
of this hostage taking.
Leader?
Emil? He's the leader?
[SIGHS]
Everything was planned out.
Every detail.
I almost forgot, Ma.
What were you telling me earlier?
Something about it being your fault.
[GRETA WHISPERS]
I didn't mean for this to happen.
[VOICE BREAKING] It's all my fault.
It's all my fault.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
You were awake?
What was your fault?
I meant…
what I did to your Aunt Wendy.
But we're okay now.
You said we're okay now, right?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Good morning, dude.
Morning.
How are you feeling?
I'm still alive.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Here, have some water.
Drink up.
Thank you.
I have some good news, bro.
Hmm?
Lieutenant Areza said
Joy and the others
safely reached Alicante.
[LIAM EXHALES]
- We really are the best tandem.
- [BOTH CHUCKLE]
- [HIGH FIVES]
- We both did a good job.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's all good. [CLEARS THROAT]
Thanks.
I'll get going.
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
I'm so proud of you, son.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
I failed to save all of our staff, Ma.
Son,
you couldn't possibly have
saved all of them.
I know that. I know that.
But trust me, I will make sure
that everyone who was involved
in their deaths,
everyone responsible for
what's happening now,
pays the price.
I will make sure they all pay.
Son, your wound.
[GRUNTS]
It's okay.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
I've already told them
that Lieutenant Areza
is asking for backup.
Thank you, Olsen.
Let's just wait
for the lieutenant's go signal.
Then we'll get out of here.
Okay.
I'm glad, dude.
They're starting to feel happy again.
And hopeful too.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
How about you?
Did you also lose hope?
No.
I can't give up.
Exactly.
How about… [CLEARS THROAT]
Liam?
Is he okay now?
He said he's okay now.
But he doesn't look okay to me.
Once the police backup comes,
we can get out of here.
Let's take him to the hospital.
Thank you, dude.
Thank you for looking after him.
I look after everyone.
Don't mention it.
I hope you guys go back
to the way you used to be.
- [STUDENT 1] Criminal's son!
- [STUDENT 2] Criminal's son!
Hey, get back here!
Criminal's son!
[STUDENT 2] Criminal's son!
[STUDENT 1] Criminal's son! [LAUGHS]
[STUDENT 2] Criminal's son! [LAUGHS]
Ooh, criminal's son! [LAUGHS]
Hey, where are you going?
Stay here!
- [GROANS]
- Criminal's son!
Criminal's son!
- Wimp!
- Criminal's son!
Hey! Stop that!
You want to get hurt too, huh?
Do you guys want to get expelled?
Feeling cocky, huh?
Hey, what's that?
- Let's go! Run!
- Run!
Who's a wimp now, huh?
Are you all right?
Just tell me if they bother you again.
I got your back.
Thank you, Liam.
Let's go.
[LUNA] Before,
remember, you used to have
each other's back.
That was a long time ago, Luna.
- A long time.
- That's too bad, dude.
- You were like brothers.
- And?
Am I the one who ruined our relationship?
That was him.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Then I found out
that his mom is awful.
- She used my mom--
- [LUNA] Olsen.
Please.
Enough of this.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
I'm glad to hear Liam's okay now.
I hope you--
[SORROWFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I hope you and your wife
can figure things out as well.
Magnus, I don't want…
to get in between you and Greta…
but I hope you don't stay mad at her.
Yes, Greta was wrong for what she did.
But because of what she did,
my son was saved.
Despite all that's happening…
you're still thinking…
of ways for us to be okay again.
If you needed help…
why didn't you come to me?
You know I'd have helped you, right?
So why was I not
the first person you went to for help?
After what happened between us,
how could I ask for your help?
So you asked Greta instead.
That was a mistake.
Well,
if it concerns our children,
we'd know
what's right and wrong.
The thing Greta asked in return…
was going to help your son too.
That's why, Magnus,
I hope you'll stop feeling angry at Greta.
I know you're thinking
that what she did to me was wrong.
But remember,
what I did to her was also wrong.
It wasn't just you.
It was both of us.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Greta, what's wrong?
[SORROWFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Ice, what's wrong?
- Liam's wound won't stop bleeding.
- What?!
- Come on.
Let's go.
Liam, stop moving.
Your bleeding will increase
if you keep moving.
- [LIAM BREATHING HEAVILY]
- Just keep calm. Okay?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
Bear with it, son.
- Just bear with it a bit more.
- Ma.
- [GRETA] You've got this.
- [ICE] We're gonna stop the bleeding.
Don't worry.
- I'm right here.
- Okay.
[LIAM GRUNTING IN PAIN]
[LIAM CONTINUES GRUNTING
AND PAINTING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
We can go home now?
We'll all go home.
What did you mean when you said
I did something in the past?
You still want to take
my husband away from me!
- That's not true--
- Liar!
Traitor!
This is the first time I've seen Liam
up close. He's pretty cute.
[OLSEN] Don't you have a boyfriend?
After everything we've done so far,
I feel like I can do anything.
You're even capable of forgiveness.
I don't think I can hate her.
I just can't.