[AREZA] I know what kind
of bombs they planted.
Military-type IED.
Lieutenant, the bomb here is rigged.
We can't move it. It might explode.
Do you know how to disarm bombs?
I'll teach you how to disarm a bomb.
Find the latch
at the side of the doorframe.
Open it.
Liam, what do you see?
[LIAM] There's a small control board
and a terminal block
numbered one to three.
[AREZA] It only passes through
terminal number three.
The rest are decoys or secondary lines.
Don't touch lines one and two.
They're not part of the active circuit.
Good job, Liam.
The bomb has been disarmed.
Yes!
- Let's go!
- Come on!
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Lucas, pick up. They're here.
[AREZA] Yes?
Emil Padua's daughter is in the ward.
Most of them are on the rooftop.
Okay. We'll handle them.
Sir, extracting the hostages
won't be easy.
There are bombs attached to them.
They used a transmitter
and receiver module.
After we secure the hostages, that's when
we're going to remove the bombs.
[LIAM] We need to move fast.
Before the sedated guys
regain consciousness.
What did you do?
[MACKY] I broke the transmitter.
The bombs won't explode.
They use the transmitter
to trigger the bomb,
using distance as a trigger.
Now that the transmitter is broken,
the bombs are useless.
Good job.
Is he really my father?
Yes.
You already saw what kind of person he is.
Do you still want to recognize him
as your father?
Olsen.
How are you?
I'm still not okay.
[SNIFFLES]
There are so many things on my mind.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
What is it?
Macky broke the bomb transmitter.
It's been deactivated.
It won't explode anymore.
What are you up to?
I'm a nurse.
I was just checking his wounds.
Make it quick.
Go back there right away.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Macky has a plan.
We'll attack them together.
We just need to wait for the right moment.
Ice.
We don't stand a chance against them.
We need to get the guns
that we took from the resort.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Tell Macky and Fin
that I also have a plan.
What's your plan?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[LUCAS SIGHS]
Brother.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have
mentioned Junior.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
He was only three years old then.
I promised him I'd take him out.
But I couldn't stop myself from drinking
before picking him up at his mom's.
You didn't mean for it to happen.
You're right, Lucas.
What kind of father would want to be
the cause of his own child's death?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Can we talk?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
We're on the first floor.
We're on the way to the commissary.
The plan is simple.
Surprise Padua and his men
and secure the hostages.
[CABRAL ON THE PHONE]
Copy, Areza. Backup's ready.
They'll just wait for your signal.
Just make sure that the hostage-takers
don't find out what you're doing.
Otherwise, they might do to the hostages
what they did to Jacinto.
- Yes, sir. Let's move.
- Let's go.
My mother told me…
that my real father died
before I was born.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I only found out now
that she lied to me.
My real father is still alive, and…
I really feel…
that it's you.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
If you're really my son,
what do you want to happen?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
What is Olsen doing?
Apparently, the bombs are useless now.
Macky disabled the transmitter.
We can escape.
Olsen will try to get a gun.
Gun?
What are you talking about?
Olsen said we should stay alert.
Are you crazy?
Why aren't you stopping your son?
He's going to get all of us in trouble.
Including Liam.
Olsen's right.
This may be our last chance.
We have to fight.
You're taking their side again?
I'm not taking any sides.
Not Olsen's. Not Wendy's.
My only goal here
is for all of us to escape safely.
We all know that they are
going to kill us,
so we need to fight back.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Let Mama go.
[SCOFFS]
Are you an idiot?
Do you know what your mother did to me?
Hmm?
She just used me.
If I'd really gotten her pregnant
and I'd found out,
I would've taken responsibility.
But what did she do
when there was a problem?
She disappeared without a word.
She made fools out of both of us.
We're the same.
I just said I didn't know, right?
That's why I'm asking you myself.
As…
As your son.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Pa…
Please.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm not even sure if you're really my son.
But one thing I'm sure of is that
you're your mother's son!
And like her, you're probably
just taking me for a ride!
You know, I never imagined
I'd meet my father like this.
But what can I do? You're here.
We're here now. What else can we do?
So…
why don't we start over?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MACKY] I can't stand this anymore.
I've had enough! I'm sick of this!
Wait, wait, wait!
Are you out of your mind?!
If you leave, you're going to explode!
You're going to die!
Let me go!
- [FIN] Fine! Go! I won't stop you!
- I'm really leaving.
All you do is cause trouble anyway!
- For your dad and for all of us!
- [ICE] Fin, stop.
- Good riddance! Go die for all we care!
- What did you say?!
- [LUCAS] Hey!
- [SENATOR MARISTELLA] Macky!
Oh really?! What, think we'll do nothing
just because you've got a bandage?!
Shut up!
Why? Just because you're
the senator's son?!
If you want to die, do it alone!
- You really won't stop?!
- [ICE] Please don't hurt him!
- [WHIMPERING] Please…
- Sir…
[KEYPAD BEEPING]
[LINE RINGING]
Lucas, please pick up. Come on.
[CALL DISCONNECTING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Please stop…
- Sir…
[FIN] Sir, I don't want to die.
I don't want to die--
[GRUNTS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HOMER] Shut up, all of you!
[MACKY] Let go of me!
[FIN] Why are you beating me up
instead of him?!
- Beat him up!
- Is that what you want?
- [ICE] Stop it.
- Is that what you want?!
Is that what you want?!
Get him over here.
Why?
[GRUNTS]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [MACKY GRUNTS]
Hey, that's enough!
Hey!
[MACKY INHALES SHARPLY]
[OLSEN] That's enough.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[LINE RINGS, THEN DISCONNECTS]
[MACKY BREATHES HEAVILY, GROANS]
Stop it.
[MACKY GRUNTS]
Get back to your places!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Fin.
[HOMER] Hurry!
[MACKY BREATHING HEAVILY]
[HOMER] Settle down now.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
We're almost there.
[EMIL ON RADIO] Dado, come in.
Dado?
It's Emil Padua.
We need to secure Dado
before Emil finds out.
- Let's go.
- Let's move!
Captain Jericho Jacinto?
Sir?
Are you ready to talk?
Many lives depend on
the information you'll tell me.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[EMIL] Dado?
[RADIO STATIC]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Dado's not answering.
What happened to him?
He went with Liam Roja
so he could lead him to his companions.
They must've encountered
a problem because of Liam Roja.
He won't stop until he saves everyone.
Well, the opposite will happen.
Because of him,
they will all die.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUN COCKS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Dado and his companion are gone.
He might have told Emil!
They might kill more hostages
if you attack them.
All units, hold position!
I repeat, hold position!
Lieutenant, I have to go back upstairs.
The lives of my mom
and the hostages are in danger.
I'm going to talk to Emil Padua.
Stay here!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
Lieutenant Areza was the one
who had evidence gathered against you.
You have a connection with Emil Padua.
You were in the same unit together.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
And his release from jail…
You were the one who arranged it, right?
So you can't deny Liam
and Greta Roja's accusations against you.
That you are involved in what's happening.
If you want to know everything…
the truth…
I'll tell you, sir.
Everything.
But…
you have to promise me
you'll protect me
once all of this comes out.
And what kind of deal
are you asking for, Jacinto?
Immunity.
And protection for my family.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Liam!
- We don't have time!
They'll kill my parents
and the other hostages!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I can't let you attack them like this.
If something happens to them,
it'll be my fault!
[GRUNTS, PANTS]
We will negotiate with them.
They haven't gotten what they want.
We can't negotiate with demons!
What's your plan, huh?
A surprise attack?
They've probably already thought of that!
Liam!
Listen to me.
They might've already gotten the money,
but they don't know
how they'll get out of here.
And we'll use that to negotiate.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
You're asking for a lot, Jacinto.
Especially for someone
who has lied over and over again.
But fine. I'll indulge you.
That is, if you give me new
and useful information.
But if it's just garbage,
then… no deal.
I'm not the mastermind
of the hostage taking at La Playa Roja.
[SCOFFS] Then who is?
Emil Padua?
[CHUCKLES]
That's useless information.
You know,
you're all going to rot in prison.
It's not Emil Padua.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
It's Roja.
What?
Greta Roja is the real mastermind
of the hostage taking at La Playa Roja.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC SWELLS]
She told me
to recruit people
to carry out the hostage taking.
So I approached Emil Padua
and told him to lead
and put together the team
that would carry out the operation.
And why would Greta Roja have
her own resort taken hostage?
For money.
That's it, sir.
Mrs. Roja lost
hundreds of millions gambling.
To recover that money,
she made sure…
she'd get a big cut
from the hostage taking.
[GRETA] Captain Jacinto.
Please, just call me Jericho.
I asked you to meet with me
to make a proposal.
So I can at least start
paying off my debt to you.
Everything, including the interest.
You know I own a luxury resort, right?
[CHUCKLES]
You're going to use it as collateral?
Something like that.
I'll use my VIP guests as collateral.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
How?
Even though the security
of La Playa Roja is tight,
theft can still happen.
The VIP guests who check in…
their jewelry is no joke.
[CHUCKLES]
So to pay off your debt,
you want me to conspire with you
to rob your own guests?
So you also think like a criminal.
I just don't know what to do anymore.
I'm in a tight spot.
My husband doesn't know
that we barely have
any money left in the bank.
You think like a criminal, but…
You know what?
If you're planning
to commit a crime anyway,
go big.
W-What do you mean?
How much would we
even get from a simple robbery?
Why not…
do a hostage taking instead?
When does your resort have
a lot of VIP guests booked?
We'll do it that day.
I'll put together a group
to attack your island.
What if…
What if someone gets hurt?
We're just going to scare them.
Are you sure?
To make it more convincing,
your family
will have to be held hostage too.
But…
she strictly instructed me
not to let anyone else know
that she was behind it.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Believe me, sir.
I can prove everything I said.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[DADO PANTING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Boss.
What happened to you?
[DADO PANTING]
Liam escaped.
He took my gun and radio.
And Conrad… He's dead.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
We'll teach Liam Roja a lesson.
We'll kill his mother.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Any mistake could put
the hostages at risk.
I will make your son pay
for what he did to me.
- [GUNSHOT]
- Ma!
We need backup on the rooftop.
- [MACKY] Hurry!
- Nobody move!
[RAPID GUNSHOTS]
[SHOUTS]
Homer, don't let your son get away!
[RAPID GUNSHOTS]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]