[GRETA] All 200 guests of
La Playa Roja are complete!
[LIAM] We're fully booked.
- Go, go, go!
- Go for gold!
I'm in. Once I have fixed
everything, I'll call again.
I'm leaving. My flight's tonight.
Why don't you leave now?
You're free to go. Leave.
Goodbye. Adios.
I was hoping to be assigned to your team.
I really appreciate your guts.
You have drive. Unlike some.
Your dream finally came true.
You finally have my life.
Let me be a mother to you this time.
Please let me fix my problems myself.
[EMIL] I've waited for this for so long.
[EMIL'S DAUGHTER] They have to pay
for everything they've done to me.
[EMIL] Don't worry. Everything's ready.
They'll pay dearly.
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [LUCAS] We have control of the CCTV.
Let's go?
[GUNSHOTS]
- Pa, where are you going?
- I'll just check on Caballero.
Something must have happened.
[MAGNUS] What do you want from us?
Can we not fight right now?
People's lives are at stake!
- Including the lives of my parents!
- And my grandfather's.
Oh!
Pa?
Hey, wait!
That's Chief Ben, no--
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
No one is looking.
Ma!
[OLSEN] Ma, we're here!
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ma! Ma--
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Hide, hide!
Ah!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Pa? You're alive?
[FIN] We almost died.
We only pretended to be dead.
We thought you were one of them.
- They're coming!
- [WENDY GRUNTS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hide, hide!
Tres, they're dead.
What?
Who took them out?
Maybe the one who was assigned here.
All right, get back here.
Let's go.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FIN COUGHS]
Shoot them, shoot them!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let's go!
Aah!
[ALL GRUNTING, SHOUTING]
[BEN] No! They can handle it!
- [GRUNTING, SHOUTING]
- [BEN] You'll just get hurt!
- Ugh!
- [BEN] They can handle it!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[AGONIZED SCREAM]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[FLESH PIERCING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC RESUMES]
[GUNSHOTS]
[BEN] Are you okay?
- [LIAM] Grandpa!
- [BEN] Okay.
- [OLSEN] Ma! Ma!
- [LIAM] Are you okay?
- [OLSEN] Thank you!
- Are you okay?
[WENDY] Olsen, son! Are you hurt?
- [LIAM] Oh no, Fin!
- [OLSEN] I'm okay.
- Come on, hurry!
- [BEN] Let's go!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[MACKY] Guys…
Don't be afraid.
No matter how much they ask for,
Daddy can pay for it.
I'm sure that's for all of us, right?
Are you paying for our ransom too?
I don't have money.
- [SNIFFLES]
- Why are you whispering?
Shh!
Huh?
That's what's so annoying
about poor people.
They act like it's our fault we're rich.
[TOPAK] Hey, you're too loud.
- I'm just telling the truth.
- Shut up!
- It's not my fault we're rich.
- Jabbas! Jabbas!
- Jabbas!
- You know what?
People like that should just die.
[MACKY] Jabbas!
What I'm saying is,
they're poor and we're rich.
It's not my fault.
Repeat what you just said.
You heard me loud and clear.
- [JABBAS GRUNTS]
- [WOMAN SCREAMING]
Say it again.
Say it!
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
It'll be a waste of a head.
Once we get the money,
we'll decide what to do to him.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JABBAS GROANS]
- [FIN GRUNTING]
- [WENDY] Hey, hey, hey!
[BEN] Go ahead.
[FIN GROANS]
[WENDY] Careful!
[BEN] Here, sit him down.
[WENDY] There, there.
[FIN GROANS]
[WENDY] Careful, oh!
- [BEN] Sit, sit.
- [OLSEN] Sit down first, Fin.
- I hacked the CCTV here.
- [FIN BREATHES RAGGEDLY]
So we're safe for now.
- It's okay.
- [BEN] Does it hurt?
So you're Liam.
I'm Wendy, Olsen's mom.
Too bad it's our first time meeting.
I'm Liam.
I know you.
Olsen and Grandpa Ben told me about you.
- [BEN] One more?
- [FIN BREATHING HEAVILY]
Mama, Fin, Grandpa, stay here first, okay?
- Treat Fin's wound.
- We'll lead them away.
Let's think about the next step later.
Wait, son.
Maybe we should just wait here
for the police.
I'm sure one of the guests
has already called for help.
Ma, there's no signal.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
But it's too dangerous.
There are too many of them.
They're holding my mom and dad.
Liam.
Right now, there's nothing you can do.
How will you get them out?
There are too many armed men there!
They were right in front of me
at the house earlier.
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LIAM] I couldn't do anything.
I wanted to save them,
but there were too many,
so I stayed hidden.
- Liam, you did the right thing.
- [GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
If you fought back earlier,
you'd all be dead by now.
[GLUM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JESSIE] Conney?
Con--
Are you still awake?
Why?
You want to check if I'm still breathing?
You seem too eager to be single again.
W-What are you saying?
Jessie, I read the annulment papers.
Am I that easy to replace?
It's hard to explain.
- [SULLEN MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BREATHES DEEPLY]
I just suddenly felt like
I didn't want this anymore.
Because you already have someone else!
You know, that never even crossed my mind.
Because I believed
it would be you and me
until the day I die.
Do you still want to fix this?
Fix what?
Haven't you already made up your mind?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Listen carefully!
- Get up.
- Move it.
[EMIL] Listen!
This won't take long!
It's simple!
You just have to buy your freedom…
for fifty million!
- Sir, sir!
- Shh… Shut up.
[BOGS] What if we can't pay?
I'm poor.
Then you'll die.
Unless you can borrow money
from Jabbas Cheng's bank.
It's not that easy!
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
[JABBAS GRUNTS]
What do you mean?
- What's not easy, huh?
- [JABBAS GRUNTS]
Are you all stupid?
Since you're the smartest one here,
Jabbas Cheng,
you'll go first.
But you own a bank.
You can make it happen.
Let's call your dad.
Tell him you were kidnapped in Cebu.
So, he has to bring the money
to the National Library in Manila.
Someone will approach him there.
And that person will give him
the next instructions.
Remember…
[EMIL] No police!
Or you'll die.
[OLSEN] Take it slow, man.
[JABBAS] There's no signal, remember?!
Do I have to say it again?!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
No… No.
- No, no, please…
- [LUCAS] Open your eyes.
[JABBAS WHIMPERS] No…
- Jabbas Cheng, open your eyes.
- [JABBAS WHIMPERING]
I said open your eyes.
[JABBAS WHIMPERING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[EMIL] Call your dad.
[MUSIC BECOMES SUSPENSEFUL]
[LINE RINGING]
- [MAN SPEAKING] Hello?
- Daddy!
We're here at La Playa Roja!
We were kidnapped here!
This is Jacob Cheng.
I'm unable to answer the phone right now.
Please leave your message after the beep.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC SWELLS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GUNSHOT]
- [DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Hey! Hey! Hey, what's that? Hey!
- I told you, I'm not joking around!
- [FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's make this quick!
Next.
[EMIL] Doctor Jessie Morillo.
Conney Morillo.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What you'll do is simple.
Call Doctor Marco,
your only son.
Tell him that on your way back to Manila,
a car blocked your path,
and you were taken hostage.
He needs to withdraw money from the bank.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
The bank will ask my son
what the 50 million is for.
It's not that simple.
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
Tell him…
the MRI and CT-scan machines
you ordered have arrived.
And that the importer requested
cash payment.
How did you know that?
Stop asking questions.
Tell your son to bring the money…
to the old St. Peter Parish.
He'll find a red trash bin there
where he'll drop the money.
And then, he'll leave quietly.
Remember…
No police.
Or…
we'll kill you.
We'll give you the 50 million.
We won't fight back. No police.
Great.
[CHUCKLES]
Very good.
Since you two are obedient,
you won't die.
[CHUCKLES]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- [DOOR THUDS, OPENS]
- [MAMA ONA GASPS]
[TENSE MUSIC STING]
[MAMA ONA SIGHS SHARPLY]
My goodness!
You almost gave me a heart attack, Luna!
I'm sorry, sir.
You said you were hungry,
so I brought you some food.
Don't you have something
with meat, like pork or beef?
I don't eat that.
No wonder you easily get nervous.
This is a healthy dish, so try it.
This is all we have.
It's not like I can cook now, right?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
All right, fine.
[CRUNCHES]
Sir, we have to be careful.
A lot of people are dead already.
They're monitoring the CCTV,
so we can't just sneak out.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
We don't have phones.
We don't have Internet.
How are we going to ask for help?
[LUNA SIGHS SHARPLY]
Sir, I remember something we were told
during our briefing in the kitchen.
Aren't you with influencers?
Do you think they have pocket
Wi-Fi with them?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, you're right!
The thing is, our building
is on the other end.
So, how are we going to go there?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LIAM] They killed a hostage already.
My goodness!
Why isn't help coming?
I'm guessing that no calls
are going through.
They must have knocked out
phone and internet services
before storming the resort.
The attack was meticulously planned.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
They… They even know about
the guests' occupations and businesses,
and even their relatives'
contact information.
Not just the guests,
but the staff's information too.
They researched everything.
- How did they do that?
- I don't know. We have no idea.
Who could they be? Tsk.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
All I know is that they have
a smart and cunning leader.
We'll find out who they are
once we've called for help.
How are we going to do that?
I need to restore the internet.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[VENT COVER THUDS]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY, GRUNTING]
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey. Hold on.
Don't you know there's
a CCTV camera on the left?
Did you forget?
Look.
See?
[PHONE THUDS]
My speargun won't reach that far.
- This will.
- [GUN COCKS]
Hey. Are you an idiot?
They'll hear the gunshot.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [THUDS]
- [SCRAPING]
What are you doing?
Watch and learn, man.
Don't you remember this?
[WHOOSHES, THUDS]
Aim properly.
Get another one.
Reach for it.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUCKS FINGER]
- Get it.
- Got it.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
- [WHOOSHES]
- [GLASS BREAKS]
Yes!
What did I tell you?
[GUN COCKS]
You just have to use your head sometimes.
- [LIAM] Hey!
- [OLSEN] Duck.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Uh, Tres?
A CCTV camera is down.
What now, Mr. Computer Engineer?
Can you fix it?
The wiring's shot, Mr. Security Guard.
Look.
But I can still use that dish.
I just need a modem
to connect to the internet.
I'll figure something out.
[HUFFS]
Where will we get that?
Don't we have guests
that are online influencers?
I'm sure they have satellite
Wi-Fi in their room.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
It couldn't have broken down on its own.
Their cameras are scheduled for
maintenance every three months.
They upgrade their system every year.
It couldn't have broken down on its own.
What does this mean, Pa?
Let's go!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DADO] Ian already cut the wires.
One of the satellite dishes is missing.
Is someone sabotaging us?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Someone broke it.
We've got company.
Tell our men to find them.
[GRUNTING SOFTLY]
[LIAM] All clear?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
They went through here.
Get in there. Catch them.
Catch them.
- [GUN COCKS]
- Hurry.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I can't run anymore.
Mommy, we're not going
to leave you.
Remove their blindfolds
and call their son.
Fifty million pesos.
You'll see a red barrel.
Dump the money in there.
- [GUNSHOT]
- They went through here.
- Get in there.
- Catch them.
We've been followed.
Are you a chef or a thief?
What's your plan?
Restoring the internet is
our only hope.