- [OLSEN GROANING]
- Bro, are you okay?
- Stay over there!
- [GRETA YELPS]
Olsen!
Emil is still alive. He's here.
He wants revenge
because I had an affair with his daughter.
And now she's missing, and Emil thinks
I know where she is, but I don't.
I don't know.
[DADO] Don't try to remove that.
I'm the only one who can remove it.
If you get more than 50 meters away,
this is what will happen to you.
- The bombs will detonate automatically.
- [EXPLOSION ECHOING]
[OFFICER] Hurry up, keep running!
Abort mission.
Withdraw and exit
the hospital immediately.
What happened?
[EMIL] Bring Captain Jacinto to me.
- [GROANS]
- [EMIL] We have something to discuss.
We need more hostages.
Don't worry.
It's safe downstairs.
The cops were pulled out.
That was the agreement I made
with the general.
[GASPS] Who…
Who are you?
Where's Papa?
Bring me to him.
No, you must stay here.
Your father asked us to protect you.
Look, you shouldn't have come back here.
Your father made sure you were sent
to the hospital to be treated,
but he knows once you recover,
you'll go straight to jail.
That's why we tried to get you out
before we attacked, to ensure your safety,
but you're just so stubborn.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm Homer, a friend of your father.
Lucas is my brother.
We owe Boss Emil a lot,
so we won't abandon you.
If you really want to repay Papa,
then stop him.
Listen.
Just trust your father.
He won't let you and your sister down.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What's the patient's name?
How long have they been confined here?
[GWEN] It's only been a few days, Doc.
Her name is Marie Santos.
I wanted to get her out
when the commotion started,
but I got scared.
Plus, she's not strong enough to move.
What happened to her?
She just got out of surgery.
[IVAN] For what?
Let's just hurry, Doc.
Thank goodness you're here.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[CUTTER CRANKS]
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
What's the situation inside?
We were able to tap into
the security cameras earlier,
but we lost the feed.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE BEEPS]
- [INHALES DEEPLY]
- [LINE RINGS]
I cut the CCTV connection, Boss Emil.
I've done what you asked.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
Maybe you can tell Lucas--
Listen, okay? We aren't done yet.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Based on the last CCTV footage,
Emil Padua and his accomplices
are still on the rooftop
with the hostages.
The hospital security team said
they can't verify
if there are any more civilians
left inside.
The building has been almost evacuated.
"Almost"? They aren't sure?
As well as Emil Padua's daughter,
there's Captain Jacinto,
and the cops assigned to watch him.
The hospital security team can't verify
if there are any more civilians
left inside, sir.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ICE BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[JOY CRYING, WHIMPERING]
It hurts. It hurts so much.
- [CRIES]
- I know it hurts.
But be strong.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [KNOCKING]
- [WHIMPERS]
[ICE] I got it.
[JOY CRYING]
[HAPPY] Joy…
Listen. Take a deep breath.
[JOY WHIMPERS, CRIES]
[JOY GROANS]
[WHIMPERS]
I don't want that. Don't do it.
We need to clean your wound.
[JOY WHIMPERING]
You can do it.
[JOY CRYING]
[WHIMPERS]
- Hand me that.
- The gauze?
Wait. Here, here, here.
Give me that.
[MOUTHS SILENTLY]
[BOMB TICKING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC STING]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[WHISPERS] There's a bomb.
What?
They planted bombs again?
[MINNIE BREATHING HEAVILY]
They're here again?
[MIKE EXHALES DEEPLY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MINNIE EXHALES SHARPLY]
[BOMBS TICKING]
Where do we go now?
Come. Let's go this way.
Come here. This way.
Come here.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [EXHALES SHARPLY]
- [MINNIE] What is it?
There's a dead man.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Cover…
Cover your eyes, baby.
Come on. Let's go.
[MINNIE BREATHES SHAKILY]
- [MADDIE WHIMPERS]
- [MINNIE] Dear…
Come on.
- Mommy…
- Don't look.
- Don't look. Don't.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey!
- Run!
- [MINNIE] No!
- [ROMAN] Freeze!
- [MINNIE SCREAMS]
[MINNIE CRYING]
- [MIKE] Sir, no. Please.
- [ROMAN] Where are you going?!
- We have a child, sir.
- [ROMAN] Answer me!
- We have a child. Please--
- [ROMAN] I don't care!
- Go over there!
- [MINNIE] Yes, sir.
We'll go with you.
Okay.
[IVAN] This is a bullet wound.
How did she get this?
Uh, she was in an accident, Doc.
But I don't know the full details.
Her wound is infected again.
I have to clean it again.
We will continue with the treatment.
If that's the case, Doc,
I'll leave her to your care.
I have to review the antibiotics
and IV that were given to her.
Why is the name written here different?
"Gregorio Valdez"?
Sorry, Doc.
You're aware of the situation right now.
There's a hostage situation.
The nurse earlier was probably in shock
and gave me the wrong chart.
I need to review her chart.
I'll check the hospital records.
Just treat her.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOMBS TICKING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BEEPS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DADO CHUCKLES]
Boss Emil.
The building is secured.
Sir, without the CCTV feed,
we won't be able to know
what's happening in there.
You're right.
But if there's no CCTV,
Emil Padua won't know
what we're doing either.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Who's this?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Emil?
Thank you for being obedient,
General Cabral.
Are you sure all your men
left the building?
Yes, I'm sure.
Good.
Because no one's allowed
to enter or exit anymore.
There are bombs planted
at all the entrances
and exits of the hospital.
If someone tries to pass through,
boom!
Emil.
No one needs to get harmed, okay?
That depends on you.
All the CCTV cameras here in
the hospital are disabled now.
But remember, I have eyes here inside.
Tell me.
What do you really need?
Just wait for my next order.
Listen to what I say,
because if you don't,
I'll kill one of the hostages.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[REPORTER] Sir, who were you talking to?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I can't shoot him
without someone hearing it.
I know what to do.
No, Wendy.
[WENDY BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [GASPS LOUDLY]
- [SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey!
[WENDY] No, please.
Please don't kill me!
- What are you doing here?
- I'm just looking for my son.
Are you sure?
- I'm begging you--
- Stay right there!
Don't move! Come here!
[WENDY WHIMPERS]
[GRUNTS, GROANS]
- [GROANS]
- Come on!
Go on, Wendy. I'll handle this. Go.
- [SCREAMS]
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC SWELLS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [FREDO GRUNTS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTING, GROANING]
Go ahead!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MAGNUS GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[MAGNUS COUGHS]
[GROANS]
Wendy.
[COUGHS]
[TENSE MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
General Cabral said we should
find a change of clothes.
We can't wear our uniforms.
We'll pretend to be civilians?
He said we need to
keep an eye on the place.
What about this guy?
He won't be able to leave anyway.
Let's go.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I thought there were no cops
left in the building.
Go ahead. Shoot me.
Hasn't your boss told you?
We'll blow up the hostages.
Don't pull out your gun. Key.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [GRUNTING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Get up!
Get up.
[JACINTO GRUNTS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Keep walking.
Go in. Go in!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hurry up!
Olsen?
Son!
- Olsen, son!
- [OLSEN GROANS] Ma.
- Magnus!
- Pa!
[MAGNUS GRUNTS]
[WENDY BREATHES SHAKILY]
You'll pay for everything you've done!
Good for you.
Your family is all together.
But it's okay.
Soon, all of my family
will be together too.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GOON] Go in!
Go in! Hurry up!
Boss Emil, I brought you a gift.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You'll be useful to me.
And you?
You might be useful to me too.
Don't strap bombs on them yet.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
Go sit there!
Hurry up!
You guys explain to Mr. Roja
what those are for.
Leave them out of this!
I'm the one you want, right?
Right?
Come on!
Let's settle this once and for all!
Just the two of us!
Relax, Mr. Roja.
We'll get there.
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HOMER] Open it.
Where's the pharmacy?
Where is it?!
This way. Follow me.
- Relax.
- Don't tell me what to do.
Hurry up!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC SWELLS]
Why did you say earlier
that we might be brothers?
Isn't it better if we all know the truth?
Your mother and my husband had an affair.
[HOMER] Get the meds needed. Go!
[GRUNTING]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [GRUNTS]
[MILA] Get out of there.
If you want me to get out of here alive,
you'll help us.
[REPORTER] The hostage takers
have Liam Roja.
You know, I don't care--
What did you say? You don't care?
- We're going to abandon them?
- [JOY] We don't have a choice.
Which one of you wants to show off
to those stubborn cops below?
Padua, calm down.
I don't think you believe me,
so I'll give you a demonstration.
Padua. Padua, wait.
Just look up to the sky, General Cabral.
One of you will have to fall from heaven
and go to hell!