Just kill me instead.
Let my family go.
[EMIL] None of you deserve to live!
- Enough, please!
- Magnus!
Stop! Don't!
Don't! [GROANS IN PAIN]
- [LIAM GRUNTS]
- [EMIL GROANS IN PAIN]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[SHOUTS FURIOUSLY]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [GROANS]
[MAGNUS] Greta.
[SOBS] I'll call for help.
[MAGNUS] I'm sorry.
[SNIFFLING]
[EMIL, TEARFULLY]
You've done nothing wrong, Ayen.
Magnus used you.
Greta murdered you.
I couldn't protect you. [SOBS]
I won't give up. I'll continue my revenge!
Liam, enough. I'm begging you.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I didn't expect it to go this far.
- Come with me.
- No, I'll talk to him!
[EMIL GRUNTS]
[SOBS BROKENLY] Leni! Leni!
- Wendy!
- [WENDY WHIMPERS]
The truth is, you don't owe me anything.
But your mother does!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
- [GUNSHOT ECHOING]
- [HOMER GROANS]
[SCREAMS IN PAIN]
[HOMER] Go ahead!
Shoot me dead!
[OLSEN] I won't do that.
I may be your son,
but we are not the same!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BAGS THUD]
[PLANTS RUSTLING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Liam!
Dude!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Liam!
Bro!
Liam! Liam…
Papa got shot! He needs help!
Your mom?
[VOICE PROMPT]
The subscriber cannot be reached.
- Please try again later.
- [FIN] We're almost there.
[MACKY] Let's go.
Fin, were you able to reach Olsen?
- Not so far.
- You still can't?
[VOICE PROMPT] The subscriber
cannot be reached.
But we're near.
See? There it is.
- It's right there!
- We're here.
[EMIL GASPING, GRUNTING]
Mama's gone.
Emil killed her.
[GROANS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
And Emil?
I don't know.
[EMIL BREATHING LABORIOUSLY]
[GROANS]
[BREATHING LABORIOUSLY]
[SHARP GRUNT]
- [GUN COCKS]
- [OLSEN] Liam, get down!
[GUNSHOTS]
[PAINED GRUNT]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Liam Roja!
Get out here!
You took everything from me!
Let's finish this once and for all!
Show yourself!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let's end this!
- [EMIL SHOUTS FURIOUSLY]
- [RITA SCREAMS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[BODY THUDS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[OLSEN] Macky!
[CAR DOORS SHUT]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Papa was shot. Doc, help him!
- Where is he?
- [LIAM] Over there. Let's go!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[EMIL GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUNSHOTS]
["ROJA" THEME SONG PLAYING]
[SONG CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUNSHOT]
[GUNSHOTS]
[FURIOUS SHOUT]
[AX SWISHING]
[FLESH SQUELCHES]
[GROANS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING
UNDER THEME SONG]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC FADES
INTO POIGNANT MUSIC]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
Mama taught me right from wrong.
That's why it's difficult
to accept all this.
She hurt a lot of people.
A lot of people got put in danger.
A lot of lives were lost.
All because of her decisions.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
I know Mama believes she did
everything because of love.
Love for her family.
For us.
For me.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
But there are times when love,
when it's not guided by conscience,
leads to destruction.
The line between right and wrong
becomes blurred.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
No life is more important than another.
And it's not right to sacrifice
the lives of others
for your own family's sake.
At the end of the day,
I think Mama realized that.
She understood that.
She regretted everything she had done.
She regretted all of her decisions.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
And in the end,
Mama sacrificed her life…
to save me.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
For the family she loved.
I know it's hard to erase
the anger in your hearts.
I try to suppress it too, every day.
But if there's one thing
I learned from all of this, it's this.
Hate
and thirst for revenge
will only bring unimaginable destruction.
[LIAM BREATHES DEEPLY]
It is only love
and forgiveness
that can save us.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I know she's not here right now,
so I'm going to say this myself.
[STIFLED SOB]
I ask all of you for forgiveness.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
For all that has happened to you…
For all of the lives lost…
I'm sorry.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I hope you can find it in your hearts
to forgive.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OLSEN] Ma! Here.
Cheers? To a new beginning.
Be careful, it's hot.
I even burned my tongue.
[OLSEN CHUCKLES]
[OLSEN SIGHS]
A fresh start is hard as well.
Especially if you're not here.
You know, Ma, you're thinking
of whatever again.
Whatever that is, we can do it.
But it's true. We really have nothing.
Did someone offer you a job already?
All the places I applied to
never replied back.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Something will come.
Just have faith. That's all…
That's all we can hope for.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
After surviving the hell we went through,
now we're facing a new hell.
You know, son?
Sometimes…
Sometimes, it gets exhausting.
I'm fed up with this life.
Not everything is easy, right?
But…
that's why we're getting a fresh start.
And, hopefully,
our new life will be so good
it makes up for…
everything that happened to us.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[LIAM] This place
was never meant to die.
I want to reopen it.
Resort. Restaurant.
Everything.
But, dude, do you think
anyone will still go here?
After everything that happened here?
You know, dude,
La Playa Roja…
It's not just a business.
It's a legacy.
It's my parents' legacy.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
So I have to continue it.
That was my promise to Papa.
And I'm sure…
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
…that's what Mama would have wanted.
Dude.
If that's the case,
I'll help you.
I promise you that I'll do
everything I can
to make La Playa Roja become
the best resort restaurant
in the world!
Of course you should.
- Thank you, okay?
- Thank you, Chef.
You're welcome, Chef.
[LUNA GIGGLES]
But wait,
who's going to manage this place?
[HOPEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
You should eat, Magnus.
I'm sorry, this is all I brought.
Wendy…
Thank you for visiting.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I know what you're going through.
You have to be strong.
Don't get discouraged.
You can get through this, Magnus.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
One day, you'll be released from here,
and be with Liam.
Well, that's all I'm holding on to.
To be with my son.
How is he?
You know, knowing Liam,
most likely, he's still grieving
over Greta's death.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
He meets with Olsen.
Wonderful.
I'm happy they're friends again.
[MUSIC TURNS MELLOW]
I'm sure Greta would have been happy
just the same.
You know, it's actually true
what they say.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
You only realize how important someone is
when you lose them.
Greta's passing has made me realize
how much I truly loved her.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
My only regret is…
not being given the chance to…
make up
for all the pain I caused her.
Magnus,
it's Liam you should make it up to.
I was also like that.
I made so many mistakes and have so many
shortcomings when it comes to my son.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
But
I'll make it up to Olsen.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
And I won't let him suffer anymore.
You're right.
[GLASS THUDS]
Dude, this is on the house.
- [PLATE THUDS]
- [CHAIR SCRAPING]
Man!
- [CHAIR THUDS]
- [GLASS CLINKS]
I accept. I like the sound of it.
"Olsen Bonifacio,
General Manager of La Playa Roja."
It clicks. It clicks, dude.
I know this is what you really want to do.
You still remember that?
You even got mad at me
when I asked your dad to train me.
- Let's forget that, man. That's over.
- [OLSEN CHUCKLES]
I hope so.
Dude.
Thank you.
Papa said you also visit him.
Of course, dude. He's like family to me.
Like you.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Sorry.
[PHONE RINGING]
Mama keeps on calling me.
She wants me to go with her somewhere.
I don't know where though.
Go with her.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Go on.
Okay, dude.
[LIAM CHUCKLES]
I'll just change. Thanks again!
This had better taste good.
Of course! Let's meet tomorrow.
[REPORTER] A few weeks after
the bloody incident at La Playa Roja,
the ransom money has been returned
to the victims' families.
But according to the report,
they've yet to recover
jewelry worth millions
that victim Ona Chan allegedly gave
to the hostage takers.
The police are still searching
for the missing jewelry,
while investigating the whole incident.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes, Ma?
[WENDY] Son, where are you?
We're supposed to meet, right?
Tell me where we're going first.
To Magnus' rest house.
Sir Magnus' rest house?
But it's under investigation, Ma.
We're going there?
I just want to check something.
Just what are you gonna check?
Son, I'll tell you about it later.
Let's just go. Let's meet up.
Okay, I'll go. Let's meet there.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CABRAL SIGHS] It'll help your case
if you talk, Sebastian.
How am I gonna talk when I know nothing?
[SCOFFS]
Just tell us where you hid the missing
jewelry that belonged to Ona Chan,
and the money.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
Who knows?
If you show that you are cooperating
with the investigation,
you may be forgiven by
the people you've wronged.
Especially your son.
I don't care about any of them anymore.
[SCOFFS]
Perhaps you have accomplices out there,
so you don't want to talk?
I already told you everything I know!
[CABRAL] Sebastian.
Just tell us who
your accomplices are already,
as well as where you hid the jewelry
and the money.
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why are you so interested
in the jewelry anyway?
So you can get some for yourself?
You'll look for it and steal--
[BANGS ON TABLE]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't lump me in with the likes of you!
Huh?!
If you're gonna be stubborn,
I won't be able to help you!
I'll say it again.
I don't know anything!
- [GRUNTS]
- [THUDS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL STING]
- Bro, have you heard?
- What?
Some of the ransom is still missing
from the hostage-taking incident
at La Playa Roja.
- Really?
- They said it's mostly jewelry.
- Yeah?
- Worth a fortune!
Where is it hidden?
Nobody knows.
[GUARD 2] Those hostage takers are clever.
If they can't benefit from it,
then no one will.
I'm guessing that Homer Sebastian
knows where it's hidden.
He's just not fessing up.
But once he gets out of here,
I bet he'll go back and get all of it.
- It's gonna be a feast for him!
- [SCOFFS]
That's if he can get out from jail.
With how heavy
the charges against him are,
he'll probably die in here.
[GUARD 1] You have a point.
It's gonna take him an entire lifetime
before he can leave.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[VAN DOOR SLIDES OPEN, THUDS]
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
The jewelry you're hiding
is worth millions.
Find an island
and take some hostages.
[OLSEN] What are we doing here?
The police just won't leave
this place alone.
I hope they don't come today.
Money and material possessions
are not the answer.
You risked your life for them
countless times!
And then what?
We're still going to suffer?!
The decision is yours, Aunt Wendy.
What choice will you make?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]