Who exactly is this Emil?
He said your family wronged him.
Particularly your husband.
What are you looking for?
Whose locker is this?
This belonged to one of my staff,
who turned out to be Emil's daughter.
Did Greta say where she was going?
Liam, we tried to stop your mother.
But she wouldn't let us.
There's so many of you here,
but you didn't stop her?
Seriously, Liam?
So much has already happened!
Why don't you try thinking of ways
to get off this island?
Emil needs to be gone.
Don't you see?
He doesn't listen to you!
If I were you, I'd strike first.
[OFFICER] Sebastian.
You're free.
We need to find the hostages.
Especially the senator's son.
As long as he knows
we're holding his son hostage,
he won't let the police storm the island.
Senator.
I have your brother with me.
Homer.
- [GRUNTING]
- Homer.
- [GUNSHOTS]
- Homer!
Don't try to follow me!
Damn you, Senator!
If something bad happens to my brother,
I will kill your entire clan!
- Where's the money?
- They have it.
I need you to do one more thing.
Let's stop this, Pa.
You already got a lot of money, right?
Isn't it enough?
This wasn't just about money.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Leni?
Leni, dear!
What…? Leni!
Dude,
I want to apologize again.
I was also there
when your mom insisted she'd stay.
But I couldn't do anything.
But you didn't say
to just leave her on her own.
That's what Auntie Wendy said, right?
To leave Mama on her own?
[MAGNUS EXHALES DEEPLY]
[SIGHS] You and Olsen should talk.
What if Emil already has Mama?
Pa, from what we know of him,
he'll definitely harm Mama.
He might even kill her!
So Auntie Wendy shouldn't have
decided to leave her.
Olsen isn't wrong.
And you can't blame his mother
for what happened.
Really, Pa?
You're still siding with him?
Even after this has happened?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[EMIL] You tricked her!
You fooled Ayen!
Do you remember the crap
you did to my daughter?
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
If there's someone
who should be blamed for what's happening,
it's me.
- [SCOFFS]
- [SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OLSEN] Why, Sir Magnus?
Why should we blame you?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mike has a plan to save all of us.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
Leni!
Boss, what happened?
My daughter isn't waking up.
Leni! Wake up!
Boss, we have another problem.
The police or military
might attack us anytime now.
Why?
What happened?
I talked to Senator Eduardo.
Homer is out of jail, but everything got
messy when I couldn't show him his son.
[LUCAS] Homer fought back,
and they exchanged fire.
The line got disconnected.
Now I can't contact him!
I need to bring my daughter
to the hospital.
I know, sir.
But how are we going to do that
if we get attacked by the police?
[BROODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAGNUS] We're not safe here anymore.
We're too exposed.
You need to evacuate.
If we continue walking down this path,
we'll reach an old construction site.
It was an old project of ours
that was never completed.
Anyway, we can use it as a hideout
until rescue comes.
[MAGNUS] So, okay.
You must go now.
Come on.
[WENDY] You're not coming?
I will do everything I can
to save all of you
because you're my responsibility.
You're going to stay here?
[LIAM] Pa.
What are you planning to do?
I'll talk to the leader
of the hostage takers,
and I will negotiate with them.
Sir, wait a second.
That's dangerous.
[WENDY] Magnus.
Do you really think he'll listen to you
after everything that's happened?
I don't understand. Why--
I have to do this, Wendy.
Liam, stay here. Olsen, you too.
Protect all of them.
[MAGNUS] Okay?
Go! You must go now!
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[REPORTER] The police and the military
are preparing an extensive attack
against the hostage takers
at La Playa Roja,
while the authorities are taking in
the rescued hostages from the island.
According to police reports,
a lot of civilians
are still trapped there,
including the son
of Senator Eduardo Maristella,
Macky Maristella,
and the Roja family.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[WENDY] Magnus.
[MAGNUS EXHALES DEEPLY]
You're putting yourself in danger, sir.
Are you sure about this?
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
If that's the case, sir,
then you'll need this.
Chief Ben.
Thank you.
Yes, sir.
Take care of them.
[WENDY] Magnus.
You know they will kill you.
Can't we just wait for rescue to come?
I have to find Greta, Wendy.
I'm sorry.
You did what you could.
Don't blame yourself.
Like I said earlier…
I take full responsibility
for all that is happening now.
How are you responsible for all of this?
I have to go.
Be careful, sir.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
- Liam.
- I'm coming with you.
No. Son, this is my battle.
Nope. This is our battle.
This is our family's battle.
No, it is mine.
Go back with them.
You know me.
I'm stubborn.
Since when did I listen to what you say?
I won't just sit here
while Mama's in danger
wherever she is.
[MOTOR BOAT RUMBLING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[LIAM] Pa.
Hey, careful.
Liam.
How is it?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[MIKE] Hurry. Come on.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come here.
[MIKE] Come on.
[MINNIE] Go to Luna.
You're going down.
This was supposed to be a railroad tunnel.
They won't be able to find us here.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LIAM GRUNTS SOFTLY]
Pa.
[GRUNTS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[LIAM GRUNTS]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Go.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC FADES]
- [MIKE EXHALES DEEPLY]
- Daddy.
Are we really safe here?
Yes, dear.
You should rest.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[MIKE GRUNTS]
How are you feeling, hon?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Much better.
Thank you. We're safe now.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BEN EXHALES DEEPLY]
I didn't know Olsen
went through all of that.
I also found out
that I have a lot of things
I don't know about our family.
About you and Magnus…
Is it really over?
Pa--
You said it was already over.
Dear,
I can feel it's not over yet.
Maybe that's why Ma'am Greta
is so mad at you.
Because she sees
and feels it too.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[VOICE QUIVERS]
[SNIFFLES]
Do you still love Magnus?
How about Olsen's father?
Did you love him too?
I've made plenty
of wrong decisions in life, Pa.
You said you didn't know
that man was a criminal.
I didn't tell Olsen about that either.
What else are you hiding
from me and Olsen?
You said
you left that man
because he was a criminal.
I was already pregnant
with Olsen at the time.
Dear…
Uh…
When you returned home to me,
you said that Olsen's father
was already dead.
Is he really dead already?
Pa…
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Do we really have to talk about him?
[WENDY SNIFFLES]
You know, dear…
I didn't know you were
hiding so many things from me.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYS]
They're almost done with the trap.
[OLSEN] Is it long enough?
Yes. Give me the other end.
All right. Perfect.
I got it.
Lay it down.
[OLSEN GRUNTS]
When those animals find us,
let's lead them here.
They'll die for sure
if they fall down there.
That's a very good idea, Olsen.
So what, are we really going to stay here?
What about Liam and Mr. Roja?
What if they need help?
You're worried about Liam?
Is it wrong of me to get worried?
So many have died, Luna.
What, you want more casualties?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You can go. We'll finish up here.
[MUSIC BECOMES SUSPENSEFUL]
- [SCREAMS WILDLY]
- [GUNSHOTS]
[PANTING LOUDLY]
[DADO] After him!
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [PANTING]
Hey!
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [MACKY] Help! Help!
[GUNSHOTS]
Catch him! Hurry!
- Ice, Luna, get inside. Take cover.
- [MACKY] Help!
[DISTANT GUNSHOTS]
Help! Help! [PANTING]
[OLSEN] Sir Macky!
- [FIN] Wait! Wait! That's a trap, sir!
- [OLSEN] No, stop!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC SWELLS]
Help! Help! [PANTING]
- [OLSEN] Sir Macky! No, stop!
- [FIN] Wait! Wait! That's a trap, sir!
- They're after me!
- Wait! Wait!
If you move, you'll fall into our trap!
You'll be impaled, sir!
What was that?
Olsen and Fin need backup.
They found us.
[JACINTO] We need to find Emil
and get rid of him.
Have you seen Emil?
[GOON] Why do you want
Sir Emil dead?
That's not part of our agreement.
He didn't keep his word.
Why sentence him to death right away?
[LUCAS LAUGHS SINISTERLY]
Don't move!
[GUNSHOTS]
- He might have Mama!
- Liam! Liam!
[EXPLOSION, GUNSHOTS]
- [JACINTO] Greta!
- What's going on?
We have to go. They've turned on me.
- What?!
- We don't have time for this. Come on!
Don't go with him, Ma!
Get away from my mom, or I'll shoot!
[LOUD THUD]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[JACINTO] Drop your gun.
Listen to your mother!
Greta.
Explain everything to your son!
What do you need to explain, Ma?
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]