I have never seen myself before
Why didn't I see myself before?
How can I stay in this dream?
How can I get out of this dream?
Love is a game of playing games
I'm so excited!
How can I blame you? I'm willing to hate you
How can I hug you?
I'm afraid that the spring breeze will gently blow away my memories
I dreamt that I would have a chance to be together
Qingtao!
Master!
I'm here!
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's all my fault.
I was so unlucky.
Master Yan Cheng
You and Mo Yao came to me again
You've never known me before
You blamed me for not protecting you
That's why you suffered this wrong
I'm in a bad mood today
Qingyu will be ruined
I can't be with you
You should be a girl who can't be with you
In my eyes
You are the girl who can't be with you
Qingyu is never under this ruse
Yan Cheng
It's okay
If you don't want to say it today
I won't ask you
But I have one thing to say
As long as you have me in your heart
I will never marry you
It's okay
I'm so sorry
I'm sorry
I'm really sorry
It's okay
You saved me in my hands.
You're doing this for me.
I want you to be killed!
I dare to do it again.
You will be the one who killed Yong Shi.
You should change your mind.
You can marry the crown prince of Yan City.
He's a woman who can't bear to see the world.
He'll cherish you.
Don't be so sad.
I heard you went to Tang Wan An Temple.
Where did you go?
Did you go to Feng Han?
I'm fine.
You should take care of yourself.
You can't get married.
I really feel sorry for you.
But the manor is the military family.
They don't care about your status.
They're just family.
They're just a few of them.
No one can know that
I was forced to marry the crown prince of Yan City.
I was forced to marry the manor.
It's not just a good manor.
I can't help but beg for mercy.
I saw it first.
I agreed to marry a foreigner.
Why?
You're really worthy of that little bitch.
Why do you treat me like that?
You bastard.
What's the point?
You dare to hit me?
I'll kill you, you crazy woman.
You little bitch.
You're going to marry a foreigner and still keep Peijing Ming?
I must take this opportunity to go.
My husband was a servant under the guard of the crown prince of Yan City.
He told me about the secret.
In the picture of the girl in our house,
she was buried in the flower building of the Tian Shui River.
Or was it the prince of Yan City who saved her?
Don't talk nonsense.
If the girl was really buried in that place,
how could the manor in the Pingnan Manor still come to the house?
Maybe the prince was snatched by her.
It's not certain.
Someone sent snow to Lingchuan.
The mother of Qingtong's daughter is not dead in the plague.
She was hit by a blow from the ancient books.
She is broken.
The plague is just a sign of her death.
Moreover,
Shen found this hairpin on her.
It's really what the former court knows.
It's said that it was the princess of the former court.
It's only a sign.
If the former court is sick,
tell the princess about the secret.
Why did the king of Pingnan investigate Qingtang in secret?
Why did he take Yan City to Qingtang?
I have an answer.
Qingtang's body
must have a hidden clue.
Caiwei, help me wipe the body.
What do you want?
What do I want?
Feng Nanzhi.
Nanzhi.
Bai Congzhi,
Hualong,
Jinye.
I can not help you.
But if you have to sell this place,
I will do it.
I will share the food with you.
Tomorrow,
my father-in-law will be Yan City.
Not you.
Your father-in-law,
but you and I will be close.
Like me,
I will hide a secret from you.
Hide?
You said hide?
I have a little self-love.
If we really had a father-in-law,
how could we have noticed it at this moment?
Bai Congzhi,
you lied to me.
Now you know
it's not a good thing.
I...
Shen Qingtang,
that night,
you were hit by something.
But the truth is,
you saw it clearly.
I tried.
Bai Congzhi,
help me.
Help me.
Qingtang,
I want to have a day when I have no proof.
Why do I have to be like this?