I have never seen myself before.
Why didn't I see myself before?
How can I get out of this dream?
Or is it just a game?
I'm so curious.
How can I blame you? I'm willing to hate you.
How can I hold you back?
I'm not afraid of the wind and memories.
I don't have any regrets in my dream.
The Love by the River
Episode 19
You knew my identity. You would bring me a secret weapon.
Why did you have to protect me?
I only want you to know who you are.
But I don't know you hate me so much.
Even if I'm close to you, you must get out of here.
Go!
He Zongzhi!
I...
I regret it.
I used to be a living hell.
I shouldn't have forced you.
I'm sorry.
You're leaving.
I'm afraid of the wind and memories.
I don't have any regrets in my dream.
The love by the river
I'm afraid of the wind and memories.
I don't know you hate me so much.
Even if I'm close to you, you must get out of here.
The flowers are falling gently.
They're falling slowly in my heart.
I'm afraid of the wind and memories.
The moon is shining.
The sky is shining.
I'm sorry.
Can you forgive me?
I'll take you away.
Don't go.
I won't go back.
I'll take you away.
Pei Tengzhi.
The wind and memories.
Miss. Miss.
Are you awake?
Where are we?
Miss, you forgot again.
This is your home, Lingchuan.
I'm your maid, Caiwei.
You don't remember?
I forgot again.
When we were in the mountains,
we had to pick herbs and herbs.
You didn't fall down the mountain.
The doctor said it was a blood pressure.
It's possible that you lost your memory.
You really don't remember anything now?
Caiwei.
I fell down the cliff that day.
Was it only me?
Did I go there at the same time?
Did I have a...
a young master with me?
No.
I went to the mountain with you that day.
Miss.
You should rest for a while.
I'll go get the medicine for you.
Okay.
I'm here.
A few days ago,
I got a few herbs.
Your master was laughing when he drank them.
The herbs you gave me are all good.
My lady is awake now.
Except...
he forgot everything.
I really don't remember anything.
The doctor said
people who suffer a lot
will forget the past and force themselves.
Some people may never remember it again.
There are still a few herbs.
Go back and give it to him on time.
Your master.
My lady has already forgotten everything.
If you really love him,
please let him go.
Let's forget about him.
He hates me.
He doesn't want to remember me.
If he wants to sacrifice himself,
he has to sacrifice himself.
I can also not be a companion.
If this time,
we come back to the palace,
he still can't accept me.
I will
let him go completely.
Mr. An,
I have done everything.
I caught a snake
and put it on the way to Miss Qingtang's front.
When she is scared,
don't worry, she is not poisonous.
When that time comes,
you'll just get out of there.
My lady,
I won't leave you alone.
I will.
My lady.
Mr. An,
you know my lady
doesn't like you the most.
You are just a fool.
I was born to be like this.
I will do this only.
According to what you said,
the mind of a woman
is still the same as the magic of a hero.
Is it really useful?
Mr. An, believe me.
These are all the words of the people.
Hurry, hurry.
She is just like the one in the big flower shop.
Miss Da Xun.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I just have to slip all the time.
Thank you for your help.
I am so sorry to take your place.
You don't need to be so polite.
I'll help you.
You don't need to thank me for your help.
You'll come here
to marry me, right?
I'm a master of the Escort.
I live in Lingchuan Town.
Are you really okay with your foot?
I'm fine.
But...
Sir,
have we met before?
Maybe.
I think you're also familiar with
the fate of the Escort.
You're so close to me.
Let's go.
You're the Crown Prince of Yan City.
I think
you two are more suitable for each other.
It's him again.
Why is there him everywhere?