Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series are fictional
and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Hello, all my fellow cavity crew!
This is “Hungry while sleeping,
Yawning when waking up!”
This adorable Sant is here to snack for you!
And the snack Sant will be eating today is…
Gugg!
I haven’t told you to join yet.
For those who love dancing,
please subscribe to the “Gugg The Wa” channel.
Go.
What?
Don’t forget to subscribe.
Leave!
Since it’s our channel’s 3rd anniversary today,
I’ll be holding a Q&A session,
answering some questions sent to my inbox.
The first question is from Hungry Bird.
Sant, where are you from?
I'm a person everywhere...
except when I'm drunk.
I’m kidding.
I’m an out-of-town kid,
but not an overseas one.
Here’s the second question.
Which faculty are you studying at?
From what i checked
you’re fine.
You can go home today.
Cut! Wrap it up!
Great job.
Since I’m an influencer,
of course, I study at
the Faculty of Communication Arts.
In one day, apart from running this channel,
do you do anything else?
I start my morning with a light exercise.
Thank you, kiddo.
Thank you.
After that, I attend classes as usual.
Then after class, I do some extra jobs
to build new connections.
Big sister, it’s done.
Little boy,
do you accept an extra job?
Hey?!
So, show me how to solve this question.
Solve that in the blacket first.
Great job!
Soda, I’m off to work.
I’ll hurry back.
Don’t be stubborn with him, alright?
Please take care of her for me.
Noted.
Don’t worry at all.
And at night,
I’m seeing all my fellow cavity crew like this.
Awww.
E-Wen, the leader of the cavity crew fandom
sent you 1,000 hearts.
Alright. I’ll let her ask me one more question then.
This is her question.
I’ve seen you take on all sorts of jobs.
What’s the weirdest one you’ve ever done?
The weirdest one I’ve ever done?
Looking back about a year ago…
Huh?
ONE YEAR AGO
You want me to ask for a breakup
with your boyfriend for you?
ONE YEAR AGO
He’s not my boyfriend yet.
We’re just in the talking stage.
I’m supposed to meet him
for the first time tomorrow,
but last night,
I swiped right on someone else
and we just clicked.
Then just call the first one and cancel!
Then he’s going to call me and chew me out.
So you’re making him yell at me instead?
I’ll give you 5,000 baht.
His name is Jay,
and he said he’ll be bringing
a white flower with him.
Dude, I’m not ready for a relationship now.
Meeting her will just waste her time.
His name is Jay,
and he said he’ll be bringing
a white flower with him.
He’s strange but good-looking.
Hello?
How could you just hang up on me like that?! Hello?
Are you Queen?
Jay!
Jway.
Jay.
Whatever it is!
Queen asked me to tell you that
she’s sorry she couldn’t make it today.
If there's nothing else, I’ll leave now.
Hold on, little bro.
I was so stunned back then.
Do you guys know what he told me?
He said…
Ouch!
Hey, what was wrong with him?!
Nothing was wrong with him,
but something is wrong with me now!
Everyone, I have to end my live stream for today.
See you later.
Thank you for watching.
Turn it off.
Turn it off!
Ouch!
What’s wrong?
I don’t know.
I suddenly got a sharp toothache out of nowhere.
That’s not a surprise to me, though,
since you’re eating sweets everyday.
Go see the dentist.
No, I’m fine.
I’ll take some painkillers, and it’ll be fine.
Painkillers?
Let me see your face.
Oh, it’s swollen, isn’t it?
See the dentist.
Dude, I heard moaning sounds all night.
Do you think we’re being haunted or something?
It’s not a ghost.
It’s my voice!
Ouch!
Shit.
Your condition is even worse than last night.
This is not right.
Go see the dentist.
Do you think I don’t want to go?
Will you pay for me, huh?
Come on. I don’t have money.
But I think there’s one place that can help you.
FACULTY OF DENTISTRY
At the Faculty of Dentistry,
they offer special prices for dental work.
It's for cases where dental students
are just starting out.
If you're interested, just go through the system,
and they'll handle everything for you.
I’m here for dental registration.
Please register right here.
After you’re done, please head inside.
Even with half his face showing,
he’s still this good-looking.
Imagine how amazing he'd look fully revealed!
Oh wow, with a dentist this handsome,
I’d let him pull all my teeth out!
I’m sorry I just finished treating a kid’s teeth.
Jay!
Jway.
You want me to ask for a breakup
with your boyfriend for you?
I’ll give you 5,000 baht.
Hold on, little bro.
She’s already dating someone else.
She doesn’t want to waste your time.
How about you?
Are you taken?
I’m not.
Your smile is lovely.
Do you want to hang out with me?
Huh?!
What a small world, Sweet Smile Boy.
Whoa.
Look at that.
Your tooth decay has reached the root already.
Perfect timing.
I’m looking for a root canal treatment case
to send to my professor.
Are you interested in being my case?
How long will it take?
Like, how many minutes?
We’d need to drill the decayed tooth,
expose the nerve, clean it,
and then fill it up and crown it.
The whole process should take about a semester.
A semester?
No, that can’t be.
You’re just trying to get back at me, aren’t you?
Get back at you?
For what?
If I have to get my teeth done by you,
I’d rather go to a normal dentist!
Hey, what’s not normal about me?
Do you really want me to be honest
about why you're not normal?
You’re hiring me to hang out with you?
I’m not an escort boy, you know.
How much do you want?
500? 1000?
Just here to tell you you’re dumped,
I’m already getting 5,000.
If we’re going further,
that should be at least 10,000, right?
Deal.
After the job, I’ll transfer it to you.
This is the deposit.
Seriously?
Are you hungry?
Have you eaten yet?
There’s a great coffee shop over there.
I’ll treat you.
Let’s go.
Come.
You already said you’ll treat me, okay?
Thank you.
What’s with that face?
It’s not delicious?
I can’t explain it in words.
It’s not like any other shops I’ve tried before.
How about some coffee instead?
I’ll order for you.
No.
I don’t drink coffee.
How can someone not drink coffee?
That’s kind of weird.
Do you want to taste it?
No, thanks.
I don’t like snacks.
And you’re calling me weird?
You’re the one who’s totally weird.
Well, snacks are for kids, you know.
Allow me to educate you.
I run a snack channel,
and even people from
your parents' generation watch it.
What’s the name?
“Hungry while sleeping, Yawning when waking up”
It’s just a small channel, though.
I mean, what’s your name?
Why do you want to know?
Once today’s over, we won’t see each other again.
I’ll call you Sweet Smile Boy then.
Okay?
Please enjoy the movie.
Thank you.
You said you don’t eat snacks, didn’t you?
I’m not eating this.
I bought it for you.
Who told you I’m going to eat it, huh?!
Awww, come on.
-You smell nice.
-I do?
Yeah.
Poking, poking, poking.
Oh, don’t.
Awww, stop it.
Are you crazy?
Let’s watch the movie, okay?
Can I get two kisses?
It’s ticklish!
Let me do it a bit.
Shhhh!
Just don’t care.
Let’s continue things between us.
Stop it.
Awww, no.
I smell good?
You do.
There are a lot of people here.
-Stop it already. I’ll watch the movie.
-Don’t be loud.
There are a lot of people here.
I’m shy.
Oh, come on.
It’s ticklish!
Poking, poking, poking.
Shhhh!
Why?!
Is your dad a gecko,
or is he the owner of the theater?
The staff hasn’t even said anything,
so if you’re not happy, go watch somewhere else!
Hey, that’s enough.
Don’t care about him.
Let’s continue.
I’m shy.
Excuse me.
Do you need any help?
Hey,
if you’re going to be all over each other like that,
go do it somewhere else.
People are here to watch a movie.
Leave!
Get out!
Get out already.
Go!
Get out.
Get out!
Go somewhere else!
-Get out!
Get out.
Yay!
Woo-hoo!
Get out!
And now you’re asking me why you’re weird?
And how am I weird?
You do you!
I’ll go find another dentist.
Hey! Hold on!
All the root canal cases
in the faculty are full right now.
If you’re going outside,
it’ll cost around 20,000 to 30,000.
Can you afford that?
20,000 to 30,000?
It looks like
you’ll have to get treated by me after all,
Sweet Smile Boy.
Thanks for your concern,
but before coming here,
I searched and found a kind dental clinic
near the university with a reasonable price.
Hey, that place!
I know it might be a little more expensive,
but I’m sure it’ll be more
comforting in the long run.
Bye.
Hey, but that clinic…
SHLAM DENTAL LAB
This is not as advertised!
Hey, bro?
Here for a dental treatment?
Well, hop on the bed.
Don’t I need to fill out my medical history first?
Whoa, your cheek is so puffed up.
Your tooth must have decayed
all the way to the root by now.
Hello.
By the way,
how much does a root canal treatment cost?
500 baht.
Huh? Why is it so cheap?
It’s just 500?
Who’s going to treat it?
I’ll just pull it out.
There’s no need to keep it.
Don’t be scared.
You've got plenty of other teeth to chew with!
Come!
Wait, I’m just asking.
-I won’t get it done today.
-Come!
Hold on!
Darling, where have you been?
I’ve been looking for you.
I’m sorry about that.
My boyfriend’s not all there right now.
He thought this was a coffee shop.
So are you going to get the treatment or not?!
He won’t dare to.
Nope, I mean, he won’t.
We’d better leave now.
Since when have I become your boyfriend, huh?
Hey.
I’m helping you, okay?
You really don’t know
that this clinic isn’t up to standard?
The faculty is already looking for
someone to handle it.
Why didn’t you tell me that
my case would just be an extraction and done?
Listen up.
Teeth are part of the body your parents gave you.
It's my job to take care of them,
even if the person doesn’t want to keep them.
You're not me, so you wouldn't know.
Someone like me isn't even sure if I’ll have
money to buy food to chew tomorrow.
If you want to earn some money,
I have an easy job with good pay.
It’ll take less than an hour. Interested?
No!
1,000?
What’s the job?
Confess my love to someone for me.
Alright.
Don’t tell me
the person you want me to confess to is you.
What if it’s me?
Then, 1,000 isn’t enough.
How much then?
I bet you can’t afford it.
What a relief that person isn’t me,
but it’s him.
Who?
It’s that person
with a sweet smile.
You’re asking me to tell myself
I love me in the mirror?
You’re smart.
Follow what I say.
Hey, I’m sorry…
for not taking care of you well enough,
causing your tooth to decay.
I promise that from now on…
I promise that from now on
I’ll take good care of you,
starting by having him treat my teeth…
even if I treated him badly before.
Say it now.
even if I’ve treated him badly many times.
If I apologize sincerely,
he’ll probably be willing to take care of my teeth.
You’ve said it,
so now show it with actions.
I’m waiting to hear it.
Are you shy?
It’s fine.
I’ll turn around.
Take your time, no rush.
I’m waiting to hear it.
Say it now.
I’m sorry!
Hey!
for making you wait for nothing,
but in this lifetime, I’ll never agree
to get my teeth treated by you!
Let’s go!
Eh!? Hey!
I wish you could’ve seen his face
when I rejected him.
He was totally in shock.
Ouch!
I think right now,
your situation isn't that different from his.
Now, you’re left with just two options.
Option 1 is to take the money he gave you
and go get your tooth extracted.
How about the other option?
Say sorry to him.
Scratch that option then.
Why so?
He might be a little weird,
but he didn’t really do you any harm.
That's in the case where I haven't
done anything to him before.
You have?
I haven’t finished the story.
After he went to confront
that couple at the cinema,
I…
Hey, did you see the faces of that couple?
When I walked in, they looked so shocked.
Their faces were like this.
It was so satisfying!
How dare they mess with someone like me?
Are you hungry?
Let’s eat something.
I’m hungry.
There's a noodle shop right across.
Just cross over, and we're there.
We can eat here. It's easier.
Come on!
Let’s go. It’s so delicious.
I guarantee it won’t disappoint you.
-Come.
-Huh?
Hey!
Actually, taking the boat
like this feels pretty good.
It's a whole different vibe.
Eh? Hey!
How could you do that to me?!
What?!
Damn it!
You treated him that awfully.
Lucky enough he didn’t pull all your teeth out!
You’re right.
That's why I don't want him to treat my teeth.
Then, you’ve got one option left.
Just pull that tooth out already.
There’s one more option.
I invested my money in something.
If nothing goes wrong,
I can get all my teeth treated.
You did?
What did you invest in?
Crypto or stocks?
A lottery.
Come on.
Someone like me can only manage to do this much.
Even though I wanted to buy a lottery set,
I could only afford to buy one.
I can buy you one more.
I’m kidding.
FACULTY OF DENTISTRY
How is it going with your Sweet Smile Boy?
He’s still stubborn.
I guess I’ll have to keep pushing a little longer.
Seriously, what did you hold against him?
Why are you pestering him this much?
I'm just concerned about my patient as a dentist.
That's all.
You’re overthinking it.
I think you should worry about yourself first.
If you can’t find a case
for root canal treatment this semester,
you won’t graduate with your friends, you know.
Yeah, whatever.
He’ll come back for treatment
with me, trust me.
Hey.
Have you watched this?
It’s been shared in the university group chat.
Hello, welcome to… Gugg…channel.
Well, because my friend
has a terrible toothache
and quickly needs money for treatment,
tonight I’m doing a challenge.
I’ll dance non-stop
until the donation goal is reached.
Let’s do it!
He’s going all out.
Super.
Jimmy has five sunflowers.
Sea has four more than him.
How many sunflowers does Jimmy have?
How do we solve this question?
Soda, pay attention to your homework first.
Don’t play with your phone now.
Sant, look at Gugg.
He’s dancing non-stop.
Thank you for watching me.
Don’t forget to tap the screen
and donate to my friend,
so he can get his dental treatment.
He has a severe toothache, everyone.
Let me show you my dance step.
Gugg!!
Soda, continue with your homework.
I’ll be right back.
What are you doing?!
Why didn’t we discuss it first?!
If we discussed,
would I get to do it, huh?!
How many hours have you been dancing?
Three.
I’ve set the donation goal to 35K.
It’s almost reached.
Now, we’ve got…350.
How many days do you have to dance?!
Stop it already. Enough.
I’m…totally fine.
I’m doing this for you.
Gugg!
Fine.
If you don’t stop, I’ll dance!
I’ll dance while having a toothache!
Sant!
Sant, stop!
I won’t!
If you want me to stop,
you must stop first!
Wow, the viewers hit 5,000 already.
Donations are coming in fast too.
They’re getting viral.
Gugg, you did it!
Our donation goal has been reached!!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Thank you, all the sweet tooth crew!
We will never forget this kindness.
Thank you.
Gugg!
It looks like you’ll have to find
a new case for root canal treatment
instead of your Sweet Smile Boy.
Ouch!
Ouch, it hurts!
So, where did the skilled guy from earlier go?
I’m sorry.
That was the best idea I could come up with.
Why did you say sorry?
I should thank you.
Thanks, my bestie.
That gives me goosebumps.
You think it’s only you who feel that, huh?
It looks like you don’t need to get treated
by your strange dentist anymore.
-You’re getting on my nerves!
-Ouch! My back!
You!
Shit.
Why is my nephew calling me now?
He probably watched the live
and was worried about you.
What’s up, Onew?
Uncle, we’re screwed.
Our house is flooded.
This year, we couldn't harvest the rice at all.
Now they’re asking for the fertilizer payment.
I heard our grandma mention
she might borrow from a loan shark to pay first.
But we still haven’t finished
paying off the old debt.
Alright, tell grandma not to borrow yet.
I just got a lump sum of money.
I’ll transfer it to her soon.
Uncle, are you here for a root canal treatment?
Yes.
This way, please.
Alright.
-Please.
-Thank you.
All the root canal cases
in the faculty are full right now.
Listen up.
Teeth are part of the body your parents gave you.
It's my job to take care of them,
even if the person doesn’t want to keep them.
Hey, I’m sorry…
for not taking care of you well enough,
causing your tooth to decay.
I promise that from now on
I’ll take good care of you,
starting by having him treat my teeth…
Next, we will announce the first prize
for the draw on April 16, 2025.
The winning number is 48260…
482609.
Soon, you won’t feel hurt anymore!
Pull the tooth!
Ugh!!! No way!!
How did you end up here?
Don’t you have to go treat Uncle’s teeth?
He’s my friend’s patient.
I just walked him there. That’s all.
This way, please.
Alright.
Thanks.
-Uncle, please take a seat.
-Sure.
Ugh!!!
No way!!!!
Bro, I’m sorry.
Is it still not too late
to get a dental treatment with you now?
You know,
I’ve never left you behind, right?
Shit!
He hasn’t transferred me the money.
Damn it.
I should have collected the payment
before taking the job.
Hey, someone jumped into the river!
Someone fell into the river!
Are you okay?
Help!
I bet it’s not…
Look. You’re soaked.
You’re soaked.
But this time, you can't leave me again, okay?
I'll clean the root canal
and do a temporary filling for you today.
Hey!
Sant!
You’ve been making that moody face all day.
My tooth hurts!
Then you go sit over there.
I'll handle the directing instead.
It looks like someone’s free like me now.
Do you want to relax somewhere?
I’ll give you a ride.
After that day,
did anyone else ask you out to the movies?
Nope.
I’ve been working nonstop, super busy.
Who would want me as a boyfriend?
Back then, one person did, didn't he?