Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series are fictional
and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
This is “Hungry while sleeping,
Yawning when waking up!”
Sant is here to snack for you!
Ouch!
I suddenly got a sharp toothache out of nowhere.
At the Faculty of Dentistry,
they offer special prices for dental work.
It's for cases where dental students
are just starting out.
Jay!
I’m looking for a root canal treatment case
to send to my professor.
In this lifetime, I’ll never agree
to get my teeth treated by you!
Why so?
Do you want to hang out with me?
You’re hiring me to hang out with you?
I’m not an escort boy, you know.
You really don’t know
that this clinic isn’t up to standard?
Uncle, are you here for a root canal treatment?
I’m sorry.
Is it still not too late
to get a dental treatment with you now?
I’ve never left you behind, right?
Ouch.
It hurts.
I told you to brush your teeth properly,
but you didn’t believe me.
Mom, will the dentist hurt me?
Don’t be scared.
I won’t allow the dentist to hurt you, Sant.
The dentist is ready.
Alright.
Let’s go.
Hey.
How are you feeling?
Is the painkiller I gave you okay?
It's okay.
Actually, I don’t need the treatment anymore.
Do you want me to carry you again or what?
Go sit over there.
I'll clean the root canal
and do a temporary filling for you today.
Let me adjust the seat a bit.
Lie down comfortably. Don’t tense up.
I'll give you a numbing injection first.
Hey!
Hey, can you hear me?
I’m alright now.
Some patients who are extremely
scared of dental procedures
may experience panic attacks.
Who's scared?
Next time, if you're scared, just tell me first.
How would I know?
I can't even remember
the last time I went to the dentist.
I think you’re not ready today.
Let’s make an appointment later.
Today, just take the painkiller first.
And next time,
it won’t be like this, right?
Let me handle the stress on that.
You're the patient.
Finding the right treatment is my job.
If I can't handle something as simple as this,
then I won’t be able to graduate.
It’s a piece of cake.
Jway can do it.
FACULTY OF DENTISTRY
Da.
Have you ever met a patient
who's afraid of dental procedures?
Like, panic-level afraid?
Yeah.
But that doesn’t count, though,
since you scared them,
and they were afraid of you.
Stop, stop, stop!
Patients like me, okay?
This morning, I treated a kid,
and they even gave me a gift.
Fine. Just forget about it.
How did you manage to
make them not scared of you?
If you want to know, open it.
For what?
You’re curious, aren’t you?
Shit!
What the hell are you playing?
Now, open it again.
Why?
It can only scare me once, buddy.
Yeah. That’s my secret, Captain.
Once you know something,
you won’t be afraid of it anymore.
Cool.
You’re trying to convey…
what?
Hey?
Tell me.
Leave already.
Yeah, I guess I’m just being silly!
Then let's just break up.
Senior, I’m sorry.
Hold on.
Is this sentence included in your script?
I’m sorry.
I have tried my best,
but this is all I could do.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
- Hey!
- Come back!
Hey!
Cut!
Sant! What on earth is wrong with you, huh?!
You’ve been making that moody face all day.
Who the hell would want to work with you?!
I don’t want to have a moody face.
My tooth hurts!
Eh? You didn’t see the dentist?
It’s a long story.
Anyway,
it looks like the painkiller
can't even handle me anymore.
Then you go sit over there.
I'll handle the directing instead.
Go. Go.
Get up. Get up already!
What do you want me to do then?
Take care of the location.
Go already.
Eh?
This way, please.
Head straight.
Hold on.
Please stop here.
There's a film set ahead.
Why aren't you resting
with a toothache this bad?
If I rest, will the work get done?
I'm not as free as you, you know.
Cut! It’s a pass.
Everyone, let’s change the location now.
Thank you so much.
I’ll be right back. Give me a second.
Sant,
we’ll move to film inside the building.
You don’t have to take care
of the location anymore.
Then, I’ll take care of the extras for you.
Un is in charge of that.
I’ll be an extra.
With your face, you'd just steal the scene.
Head home and rest. Look at your cheek.
Eh?!
Safe trip home.
Yeah! I’m coming.
Oh,
it looks like someone’s free like me now.
Do you want to relax somewhere?
I’ll give you a ride.
No, thank you.
I can go on my own.
What’s wrong?
Why did you turn stiff just like that?
I can’t think of a place to go.
Do you really have to think
about something like this?
Does that mean you never rested?
That’s not true.
I have such a good work-life balance.
The other day, I taught
a student to do her homework.
That’s your job, isn’t it?
At night, I ate snacks.
That’s your live stream job.
Get inside the car.
Huh?
Ouch.
I'll teach you how regular people rest, okay?
I’ve just realized our university
has this kind of cafe.
Has it just recently been opened?
It has been open since my freshman year.
What’s good at this cafe?
Sant, of course.
Huh?
Croissant.
But from your condition now,
I don’t think you can eat it.
I’ll order something else for you.
Thank you.
Drink it.
It’s on me.
You said that yourself, okay?
Yeah.
This reminds us of that day, doesn’t it?
What day are you talking about?
Our first date.
Date?
I was just your escort boy.
Drink slowly.
Don’t rush.
It’s going to be a long day today.
What again?
After we finish this,
let’s watch a movie.
Do record players still exist these days
Why not?
It's classic.
I even booked a screening room.
Pick the film.
Are you usually hot-headed?
Why did you ask me this?
That day when we went to the movies,
why did you pick a fight with them?
Oh, I see.
I’m usually not that type of person.
I'm not even the type to fight,
but that day was special.
Why was it special?
Well, I saw you enjoying it,
so I didn’t want anyone to interrupt.
Why wouldn’t I enjoy it?
Someone treated me to drinks and snacks.
After that day,
did anyone else ask you out to the movies?
Nope.
I’ve been working nonstop all day, super busy.
Who would want me as a boyfriend?
Back then, one person did, didn't he?
Hey, give me a second.
I’ll go to the restroom.
Eh?
Are you going to leave me again?
No.
I’m really going to the restroom.
I swear.
I’m going with you.
Don’t!
Wait here, okay?
It takes ages for each one to arrive.
Book a seat for me too.
Excuse me, let me go to the restroom for a second.
Big sister, hello?
Sant, are you free?
Come help me carry the furniture to my room.
I'll give you some snack money.
Sure. I will…
- Hold on!
- Darling, where have you been?
I’ve been looking for you.
Hey.
I’m helping you, okay?
You really don’t know
that this clinic isn’t up to standard?
Is it still not too late
to get a dental treatment with you now?
I’ve never left you behind, right?
I've got an errand to run.
Maybe next time.
Huh? Did I mishear that?
Sant, you're turning down a job?
I’m really sorry.
Maybe next time.
Yes.
I’m sorry for keeping you waiting.
Uncle, let’s go.
You drove here,
so why are we riding this?
If I drive, then it's not really a break, is it?
You know, the view is different
when you're the driver
versus when you're just a passenger.
Stop rambling.
If you're lazy, just say it.
Here.
I heard you complaining that you wanted
something refreshing to drink.
Being this much of a spender on me,
what are you hoping for?
Do you want it or not?
It smells good,
and it’s not too sweet.
You’re treating me so nicely.
I bet you must feel something for me.
Not at all.
I just wanted you to drink something yummy.
Looking ahead gets us there faster,
but sometimes it makes us forget
how beautiful the journey is.
I’m willing to drive slower
so I can enjoy the view more clearly.
Wow,
our campus view is this beautiful, huh?
Seriously?
We pass by here every day,
and you’re just noticing it now?
Right? Why have I never noticed it before?
This is the end of today’s trip, right?
I'll get off at the university entrance.
I'll take a motorbike taxi back.
It’s not over yet.
We’ve got one more thing left to do.
What is it?
Go stargazing with me.
Stargazing?
I already got permission from the professor.
We have 40 minutes before the building closes.
Wait.
Why are you taking me up here?
At least
you don’t feel tense
like you did in the morning.
Stress is one of the factors that
can trigger a panic attack in patients,
so helping the patient relax
is also part of the treatment.
I see.
You took me around all day to help me relax?
Yes.
But that’s not it.
When we get dental work done,
we usually just hear the sounds
without knowing what the dentist is doing.
That’s what makes it scary, right?
Now, go sit over there.
This is the tool
I used to clean your teeth
during the procedure.
My friend once told me that
the more we understand something,
the less scary it becomes.
Do you think that's true?
It’s probably true.
At least today, it made you brave enough
to look me in the eyes more.
Is this all you wanted me to come for?
Oh, nope.
There’s one more.
Are you going to treat my teeth now?
No,
today, just bear with the sound of the tools.
I told you,
I’d take you to stargaze.
Hey,
I’m no longer a kid.
You’re right.
You’re not a kid,
but a stubborn kid with a toothache.
Try listening to it again.
Yes.
Hey!
Can you hear me?
Don't feel bad.
Things like this take time.
At least it's way better than
earlier this morning.
I know you've done everything you could.
There are many cases where patients
are afraid of dental work
because of bad experiences as kids.
Is there something I don’t know yet?
Nothing.
Sant.
I think you should go find a new case.
I’m sorry for wasting your time.
Huh?
And he walked away just like that?
Yeah.
He didn’t pick up my call either.
What are you going to do now?
What can I do?
Since in the end,
treatment is a team effort, I can't do it alone.
Didn't you say you wouldn't leave him?
Who’s leaving whom? Say it properly.
If you think he has something
he’s not ready to share,
just give him some time.
Some things, no one wants to
go back and think about.
I think you understand that well.
JENG
Gugg!
Tonight, you can call me Sugar Daddy!
Hello?
You haven’t finished your work?
Where are you now?
Tonight, I’ve got to go edit the film at Un’s room.
I see.
What time are you coming back for dinner?
Today, I bought a full set for you, all out.
Oh, I think it's probably early in the morning.
Go ahead and eat first.
Sorry,
catch you later, buddy.
Got it.
We’ve finished filming,
but my heart is still waiting for love!
Single and ready to mingle!
Of course!
- Are you promoting yourself?
- Yeah.
Eating sweets this late,
do you hate your dentist or something?
Hey, how did you get here?
I drove a car.
Oh, I mean, what are you doing here?
Look at my uniform.
I’m working a side job.
Oh wow.
You’re buying beer.
Are you even 20 yet?
Show me your ID card.
Fine.
I don’t want to drink it anymore.
Hello?
Huh?
Stomach issues?
Eh? It looks like I’ll be running
the shop alone tonight.
Can you find someone to cover for you?
Alright, I can do that.
I’ve been resting the whole day.
It looks like I’m getting broke.
Are you sure you can handle it?
Of course.
You can handle the stock check.
I’ll take care of things here.
If you like chocolate,
would you like to have some bread to go with it?
I guarantee it’s delicious.
I’ll take it too then.
Thank you.
Please warm it up for me.
Sure.
Ouch!
Thank you.
Let me see.
Are you alright?
It’s totally not a big deal.
Just apply some toothpaste, and it'll be fine.
Who said that?
Applying toothpaste will make the wound worse.
You should use ice to compress it instead.
Come.
Ouch.
And you said you’re alright?
What a regret.
If it were the ring finger,
it would probably be better.
What’s with the ring finger?
If it’s the ring finger…
Congratulations!
We hope your love lasts long.
It’s alright. We’ll stop by again later.
What are you playing?
Continue working.
Thank you for using my service.
Free gifts for you.
Eh?
Sugar daddy, two cans for me?
Thank you.
Hold on.
One is mine.
The other is yours.
Let’s find somewhere to sit down and drink.
Do we really need to come
all the way up here just for beer?
We can finally watch the stars together.
My grandpa once told me that at our home,
the stars are up in the sky,
but in Bangkok,
the stars are on the ground.
Look, that building still has its lights on.
You might not know, but for people like us,
Bangkok is the place
where we work day and night
just to become those little stars
on top of the buildings here.
Are you alright?
Of course.
I have Gugg who helps me.
By the way,
invite him here.
I’ll go buy some more beers.
He’s not available.
He’s at his friend's place editing a film.
I see.
Oh, it looks like there's a kid left behind.
No wonder you seemed so frustrated
when you were down there buying stuff.
You might not know,
but Gugg and I have been
inseparable since kindergarten.
We were in the same class,
and sat next to each other.
I still remember in high school,
we'd skip class and hang out on the rooftop.
When we were bored, we'd play hide-and-seek.
You played hide-and-seek on the rooftop?
After two rounds of walking,
you’d find each other already, right?
Exactly.
That's why we made the rule harder.
The person who's looking
has to keep their eyes closed.
- Then what's fun about it?
- If you don’t believe me, close your eyes now.
Count one to five.
Just so you know, I'm really good at hiding.
Don't peek!
Fine.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
I’m going to start looking for you now.
I’m walking now.
Who the heck came up with this game?
It's so damn hard.
Give me a hint.
Help me out!
It’s still hard.
Can we do this then?
If I ask you something,
answer me, okay?
Alright.
When you were little,
you were abandoned, right?
Why aren't you answering me?
How could you know that?
Well,
if it were someone else,
they’d be happy to take a break,
but you seem frustrated
when you're not doing anything.
I think you’re the type of person
who always wants to do something for others.
What happened?
When I was about eight years old,
I had a severe toothache,
so my mom took me to
the dentist near our place.
That was my first dental visit.
I was really scared,
but my mom told me not to be scared.
If there's anything, just hold her hand tight.
But when the time came,
my mom wasn’t there anymore.
Where did she go then?
I don’t know either.
After that, I never saw her again.
My dad died,
and my mom disappeared,
leaving me to grow up with my grandparents.
Maybe it's because of this
that I don't like being alone.
I always find myself offering to help others.
Is that because you’re afraid that if you don't,
one day no one will need you?
You know what?
Every time I sit on the dentist's chair,
it makes me think back to that day,
the day I kept asking myself over and over.
What did I do wrong?
What wasn't good enough about me
for my mom to leave me?
I got you now.
I found you.
Can you not open your eyes now?
I don’t want you to see me like this.
No matter how many times I have to look for you,
I'll always find you.
♪ Since you came into my life, it’s been so bright ♪
♪ With you right here, it feels so warm, so right ♪
Don’t cry.
♪ So stay with me, don’t ever leave my side ♪
I’m already here.
♪ ‘Cause every day, you make me smile ♪
Hey!
Did I fall asleep without realizing?
Based on how you look now,
you probably shouldn't even ask, huh?
Why didn’t you wake me up then?
I already tried,
but you insisted on sleeping here.
Since I couldn’t stop you,
then I should just join you, right?
I’ll head back to my room now.
Hold on.
Don’t forget our promise.
What promise?
You promised me
you'll have a dental appointment
with me the day after tomorrow.
Nonsense!
Why would I say such a thing?
You must have been drunk!
Hold on.
I’ll wait for you.
See you then.
I caused myself a problem again
because I was drunk!
You came so late.
Your patient has been waiting
for so long already.
I knew
you were definitely going to come.
Eh? What are you doing here, Uncle?
Young man, isn’t this unit 31?
Well, it’s not.
This is unit 13.
Unit 31 is over there.
I’m sorry.
No worries.
I don’t think he’s coming anymore.
Come help me with the lab instead.
He promised me already.
He will come no matter what.
This is unit 13.
I hope this patient isn’t coming
to the wrong unit.
Please take your seat.
Doctor, hello.
Hi.
Take your seat.
What brings you in today?
Mom.
Mom?
It’s alright. Stay still for now.
Doctor, where is my mom?
It’s okay.
Stay with me for a while.
Let me check your teeth for a moment,
and we’re done, okay?
Mom!
Don’t be scared.
I’m here.
I’m not going anywhere.
I promise.
I’ve put in a temporary filling for you.
For now, chew on the other side
and avoid hard foods.
Remember what I said?
Got it.
I remember. You've said it 3 times already.
You're talking so much.
It seems like you're not in much pain anymore.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
To test
if you can do what I explained or not.
I told you, this cafe’s croissants look delicious.
What are you waiting for?
Why don’t you eat it?
I can really eat it, right?
Of course.
Just make sure not to chew with the side I filled.
How is it?
You said it was delicious,
but the dough is just okay,
the butter's nothing special...
but why the heck is it so damn good?!
What?
Nothing.
I’m just thinking about the day we first met.
Why?
Is it funny that I'm obsessed with sweets?
No.
If that's what I thought,
I wouldn’t have said that to you that day.
What did you say?
Like that.
Like what?
I said it when I got out of the water.
Excuse me, please.
I didn’t mean to leave you.
I just went to the restroom,
and when I came back, the boat had already left.
I think I like you.
Huh?
Date me, okay?
Do you remember now?
Kind of.
Yeah, to be honest,
I don't really remember either.
I only kind of remember,
not even sure what you said to me that day.
And do you remember your answer that day?
You're such a generous spender, buddy.
Do you think we'll have
enough money left to pay the rent?
So, even with the donations from last night,
we're still short by 2,000.
I’ll try talking to him.
Uncle, we have been broke recently.
Can I postpone paying the rent, please?
If you need anything, go ask the owner.
My mom owns this dorm.
Why didn’t you tell me that?
Handsome bro,
can you lower the rent for me, please?
Alright.
But you must be my secretary
for one week, Sant.
Deal?