Why haven't you asked him
to be your boyfriend yet?
I already asked him out once and he rejected me.
This time he has to ask me instead.
Ah, so that’s how you think.
That’s why you didn’t dare
ask me to be your boyfriend.
I want to say I like you.
If it’s just the two of us,
I’ll do whatever you say.
Doctor, how is her condition?
The patient has acid reflux,
which is causing chest tightness.
We've already given antacids,
and we'll do a thorough check-up tomorrow.
That’s the miracle of the Venerable Father
who keeps danger away!
You should give credit to the meds he injected.
But there’s one thing I’m concerned about.
She keeps insisting on going home.
Please take care of that for me.
Thank you.
Why should I stay?
It’s a waste of money,
and I’m fine now.
You said the same thing before we came.
Don’t be stubborn, Grandma.
Go talk to Grandpa.
He’s really worried about me.
He won’t let me stay here alone.
He went back home already.
What?!
Behave yourself, okay?
I’ll visit again tomorrow.
No way!
I said it’s a waste of money.
Do you even know how much this room costs?
Mom, I’ll take care of that.
I haven’t seen you in ages.
You’ve grown so much, Sant.
Mom, I’m hungry.
Is there anything to eat?
It’s on the table.
I prepared it for you.
It’s Sali cake!
Hello?
I’ve finished packing.
Are you sure I can’t bring my son?
Grandma said if anything emergency came up,
we should call your mom back to check on her.
Here, I bought you some snacks.
These are from abroad.
Whoa. Thank you.
Have you eaten yet, Dad?
Let’s go get something to eat.
It’s on me.
Hotpot or sushi?
Uncle Sant, what do you feel like eating?
I’m not hungry.
Eat without me.
You said you weren’t hungry, didn’t you?
I’m not hungry.
Go ahead and eat.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Okay.
Do you want some?
All the yummy stuff's gone already.
You took too long to decide.
Here you are.
There's one can left.
Well...
it happened a long time ago.
Maybe she really came back
to apologize this time.
You think I never gave her a chance?
Actually,
I know she has been
keeping in touch with Grandpa.
One day, I secretly used his phone to text her.
That was the day I told her
I won first prize in
the garland contest of the province.
I hoped she'd show up,
but, in the end,
she didn’t.
Deep down, I thought maybe life was hard for her,
and that’s why she didn’t dare to come.
But it’s turned out,
she’s been living comfortably all along.
Do you still think I should forgive her?
Auntie, are you looking for something?
My watch.
It’s the silver one.
I have no idea where I left it.
It’s expensive too.
Let me help you find it.
Are you Sant’s friend?
Oh, I’m his senior.
Sant came to me for dental work.
I see.
And how’s he doing now?
Well…
I really shouldn’t be asking that.
Showing up out of nowhere like this,
of course, I think he’s not okay.
Is this the one?
Yes!
That’s it.
Thank you.
I remember that model’s a limited edition, right?
My mom has the same one.
Yes, I got it when I was traveling in Europe.
Oh, but that model has a lot of fakes.
The way to tell is to flip it over.
If there’s an engraved logo on the back, it’s real.
Actually, Auntie, you don’t even need to flip it.
If you bought it in Europe,
it should be real no matter what.
Or what you showed us all along
isn’t the truth?
Sant's dad passed away when he was little.
I raised him all by myself.
There’s not much to do out here
in the countryside.
One day, a man asked me
to move to Bangkok with him.
He promised to open a beauty salon for me,
but only if I left Sant behind.
I really wanted to talk to Sant,
but everything happened so fast.
Back then, all I thought was
I’d go work, save up,
and bring him to live with me.
But that salon he promised?
He gambled it all away on online betting.
Then he left me for another woman,
and dumped all his debt on me.
My maid’s salary could only cover the interest.
I couldn’t afford to go back to my son.
Maybe Sant doesn’t need all that.
Maybe he just wants his same old mom back.
At the very least,
I think he deserves to know
the truth about his mom.
So what if he knows?
Just carrying the burden here
is hard enough for him.
Why would I add myself to the load?
And is this how you want him
to understand things?
To remember that
his mother left him to live a comfortable life?
At least,
he won’t have to keep worrying.
This is the only thing I can do for him.
Onew, did you see Yada?
She came to borrow my bike.
I’m not sure where she's going.
The bike?
You already found out, right?
Yeah,
in the end, she broke up with me.
I kind of saw it coming,
so I brought this along.
I promised her I wouldn’t drink.
Okay.
Whoa…
Whoa.
Can I ask?
What did you guys argue about?
She just went back to her ex, a guy.
How did you find out?
Did she tell you?
She posted photos of them together.
Do I even have to ask?
When we were together,
I knew she still hadn’t gotten over her ex.
She used to date a guy before me,
so it’s hard not to compare.
So what’s the big deal, huh?
When we were together,
I was always worried...
if I could live up to her ex.
He had something that no matter how hard I tried,
I couldn’t be.
Everyone’s been telling me
to go back to dating guys.
But here’s the funny part, you know?
All the guys I dated...
were scared I’d eventually
go back to dating girls.
But what can I do?
I made my choice.
I think
you just haven’t found the right person yet.
It’s hard, but don’t give up.
There’s definitely someone good waiting for you.
Yeah!
I’ll just go ahead and announce
to the world I’m single!
Hey, be careful.
The signal isn’t working.
Back then, your mom tried to contact you.
But it was I who didn’t let her.
I wanted your mom to feel guilty for leaving us.
I’m sorry, Sant.
Why are you apologizing?
I’m happy I got to live with you.
No matter how hard things were,
you never left me.
The doctor told me this morning
I’ve got acid reflux
because of gallstones.
Surgery could fix it,
but I’m not sure...
my body can handle it at my age.
Grandma, you’re strong.
That’s nothing. You’ll be fine.
Sant,
promise me you’ll forgive your mom.
I don’t want to leave with any regrets.
No, don’t say things like that.
Sant.
I’m not promising anything.
Let’s talk when you get better.
Sant.
Ouch!
Grandma?
Grandma?!
Someone, please help my grandma!
Grandma!
How is her condition?
The doctor said she’s got a blood infection.
She needs emergency surgery.
Grandpa!
Dad!
- Dad.
- Grandpa, get up.
Be careful.
I called out to her myself.
Grandpa, sit down.
Everyone’s scared of losing their mom.
No one knows that better than you.
No, I’m not going.
I’m waiting for my mom.
Mom! Mom!
Where are you?
She didn’t show up to console me that day either.
Hold on.
Do you want to be like her?
If you leave now,
you’re no different from her.
Grandma’s strong.
She won’t leave us that easily.
The surgery’s done.
Grandma said the doctor is safe now.
You’re so excited you’re mixing up
your words, Grandpa.
Haha, I meant the doctor said she’s okay now.
I said it correctly already.
Grandma,
I brought you some oranges.
How are you feeling?
I'm okay now.
The doctor said I can go home
the day after tomorrow.
Aww, and here I thought I’d get an inheritance.
Turns out, it’s just debt. Do you want it?
Have you talked to your mom?
Not really.
You promised me already.
I’m feeling a lot better now.
So now it’s your turn to keep your promise.
Any food? Any food?
I’ll treat everyone tonight to celebrate
Grandma’s coming back home.
Tell me what you want to eat.
Sant, your mom already left.
I know.
I didn’t buy any for her anyway.
If we hurry, maybe we can still catch her.
This is my family.
I can take care of it myself.
No one else needs to get involved.
Sant,
her life isn’t as easy as you think.
She didn’t tell you
because she didn’t want you to worry.
You think I didn’t know?
Just holding her hand, I knew.
No rich woman’s hands are that rough.
She left me behind because she hit rock bottom.
I’m her son.
Didn’t she ever think how hard it was for me?
I had no mom to cheer me on like other kids.
Huh?
Sant,
she might not have reached out,
but she was never truly gone.
She was always there for you.
every time you went live.
Hello, all my fellow cavity crew!
This is “Hungry while sleeping,
Yawning when waking up!”
This adorable Sant is here to snack for you!
If you’re enjoying the stream,
don’t forget to send hearts to cheer me on!
E-Wen, the leader of the cavity crew
fandom sent you 1,000 hearts.
I’ll let her ask me one more question then.
Don’t forget to say hi when you join in.
Today, I’m eating my croissant.
It’s from my regular shop
that I’ve been to often
since I’ve just moved to Bangkok.
Welcome back to my channel,
“Hungry While Sleeping, Yawning When Waking Up!”
It’s this same boy, Sant,
in a brand-new location
with a very special guest, Dr. Jay!
Dr.Jway!
Anyone who has joined,
feel free to say hi in the chat!
E-wen, our top fan, sent 100 hearts already.
Thank you!
Hey, are you introducing
your boyfriend to us, Sant?
Eh? How did he know?
That’s right.
She named herself "E-Wen"
because it fits
since she believed that’s
how you should call a mom like her.
Hey,
can you take me to see my mom?
It’s full.
We can go now.
Excuse me.
Did the Bangkok bus leave already?
Just left a minute ago.
Next one’s in two hours.
Come on, Sant. Let’s go home.
No. I’m not going.
I’m waiting for my mom.
She’s not coming back.
She has to.
She has to come back for me.
I said, go home.
No way!
I’m not going.
I’m waiting for her.
Mom! Mom!
Where are you?
Mom!
Sant!
What’s wrong?
Mom!
I’m right here.
I’m here.
Mom!
Don’t cry.
I’m right here. I’m here.
Mom, I love you so, so much.
Don’t cry, sweetie.
Good thing she didn’t make it in time.
Otherwise we’d have a sobbing kid.
Who?
Who’s crying?!
Whoa.
Who let you wear someone else’s shirt?
Grandpa did.
I said I was cold last night,
so he gave it to me.
The smell of the old owner is good, though.
Then keep it.
It’s yours now.
Don’t give it back.
Thanks.
Oh, before she left,
your mom gave me this.
She said it’s your favorite,
but I doubt it.
She probably remembered wrong.
Hey, wait.
This is the taste I missed.
It’s so sweet!
Eh?
Didn’t you say you don’t like it?
I changed my mind.
It’s good.
If you don’t believe me, try it.
Nope.
You know I don’t like desserts.
Are you sure?
You think I don’t dare to?
Oops.
ONE YEAR AGO
Dude,
I’m not ready for a relationship now.
Meeting her will just waste her time.
Hey, give it a try.
From what I’ve seen,
she’s actually pretty sweet.
And so what?
No matter how cute…
She’s playful too.
Most importantly, she loves sweets,
just like you used to.
Hello? Jay, are you even listening?
Yeah, I’m listening.
What’s her name again?
So, that day,
you liked me first, didn’t you?
Who liked you?
I was just glancing.
Mmm...
you liked me.
But you went up to talk to the girl next to me
because you were shy.
Stop it.
Well, you must’ve liked me too.
Otherwise, why would you go with me after that?
I was in it for the money, obviously.
Swear on it then.
If you’re lying, may you get a cavity.
I don’t know!
Who remembers stuff like that?
It was so long ago.
It’s okay if you don’t remember.
Let’s go on our first date again.
What do you say?
Whoa, who’s this stylish guy?
Give me back my friend!
Gugg,
I’ve been hiding something from you.
What is it? You’re scaring me.
Well,
I’m dating Jay.
Sant! You said it?
Nice one, friend.
Wait. Why are you acting weird today?
You usually say you already knew,
or like, “Finally, you told me!”
You’ve watched too many movies.
I mean it.
I didn’t want to hide it anymore.
Yeah?
So if I saw a photo of you two kissing cheeks,
I’d believe you.
Who’d even have that?
Exactly. Who would?
No one would
because you’re not even dating!
I’ve got to go.
See you, bestie.
Bye!
Bye.
Look how happy you are.
I’m heading out now.
Okay.
I’m almost done getting dressed.
See you there.
Can I ask you something?
Why aren’t we going together?
If we did, it wouldn’t feel like our first date.
I told you
we’re recreating our first date today.
Whatever makes you happy.
See you.
Auntie.
Auntie?!
Yes, you.
This dorm’s management
loves nitpicking tenants,
but never does their own job.
I suggest parking elsewhere.
This is just a friendly warning.
I’m off.
Bye now!
Oh, Jay!
Mom?
Here’s some water.
Just now one of the tenants,
I don't know which room,
called me “Auntie.”
Hey? What the heck?
Should I check the CCTV and have them
kicked out of the dorm, Mom?
No, no.
How have you been doing, Jay?
Great.
What brings you here today, Mom?
I was bored
and I only have you, Jay.
Can’t I come visit once in a while?
Of course, you can.
But maybe let me know first next time.
Why?
Hold on.
What’s with the outfit? Where are you going?
Uh... I'm, I'm… going…
Going?
I'm going to my old school to help out
with career day with a friend.
Which friend?
Da.
You know, the one whose number is next to mine.
What time will you be back?
Around 7 PM.
Is something wrong?
Why so many questions about me all of a sudden?
Nothing!
I’m just worried about you.
Can’t I even ask a few questions, huh?
Of course you can, Mom.
I’ve only got one mom, you know.
I’m happy you care.
You're going to your old school, right?
I’ll give you a ride.
What?
Can’t I give you a ride?
Can’t I, huh?
Sure, sure.
With that smile,
how can I not fall for you?
Gugg, what are you doing here?
I was nearby and brought your favorite chicken.
Eat with me.
I can't finish it alone.
All my friends ditched me to go on dates.
Sure.
Don’t you want to do that too?
Huh?
I mean, go out.
Oh, well… yeah, I want to.
There’s nothing more to do this semester,
but I don’t know where to go.
Where do you usually hang out on your day off?
The library,
the lab,
or tutoring sessions.
And when you had a partner,
where’d you guys go?
When I had a partner?
We mostly just studied at the library.
Maybe an outdoor movie at most.
Whoa, you can’t live like that forever.
Let me show you something fun.
I’ll go change.
Meet you outside the ward, okay?
Bye-bye. See you.
Bye.
Hello?
Where are you?
I’m sorry, Sant.
Well, I’m…
I’m…
I’m here.
I thought something came up.
Something did come up.
My mom suddenly showed up at the dorm.
And how did you get away?
Someone randomly parked in Madam's spot,
but don’t worry.
We locked the wheels already.
Uncle, that’s my mom’s car.
Oh crap!
I’m so sorry.
I didn’t know you had more than one car, Madam.
I’ll take care of it right away.
Yeah. Hurry up.
Which key?
- Ugh, it’s not this one either.
- Come on!
I’ll find it myself. Give it to me.
You don’t know a thing.
Why did you bring so many keys?
I'm getting fired for sure.
Hey, help my mom.
Hurry up.
Yes, sir.
- You too.
- Yes, sir.
How come you messed up your job like this, huh?
My mom is not like the others, you know!
This is nuts.
The whole thing is crazy!
I texted her, saying I have an errand.
From now on, it’s just the two of us.
This outfit… this place…
It really feels like that day again, doesn’t it?
Not quite.
It’s missing the flower.
Go on a date with me, will you?
♪ You're like a magic potion,
you're my special one ♪
♪ Not a pill or syrup, but the right stuff ♪
♪ No fever late at night,
but you’re the cure that I need, all right ♪
♪ Whenever I see you, I feel better than fine ♪
♪ Magic potion, you're my magic potion ♪
♪ La-la, la-la, la-la, la-la ♪
Seeing this reminds me of that day.
Why?
Are you afraid I’ll ditch you again?
What’s there to be afraid of?
Nope.
Finally we got to wear matching shirts
like you wanted, huh?
Who calls them matching shirts?
Since you know me this well,
we’re a perfect match.
Dude, Jay totally played it cool with me.
He acted like he didn’t care about his birthday,
so I planned a huge surprise.
Let’s see if he can keep his cool after this.
Tadaaa!
Wow!
Jay! Jay!
Jay, wake up!
What happened last night?
Why are we like this now?