Judging from the color of her sash and robe,
this woman was likely a courtesan called Nual.
There's no doubt, sir.
Nual's ghost!
Nual! You're alive?
He's after you because you saw his face, right?
I saw the face of the one who hired him.
Nual can't go back to Fang's just yet,
not until the case is over.
This is my father's old warehouse.
I promise you'll be fine here.
Stay still!
They snuck in, and Boonta screamed hard like she was dying.
She was struggling that much?
There was a loud noise,
and the whole warehouse was shaking.
They let the slaves join in!
Really?
Where are you taking the food?
Are you
eating with your husband?
Husband, my butt! I'm taking it to Aunt Mian.
She's staying at her husband's.
She's still sick, so I think I should visit.
Bye.
I'm going.
Don't worry.
Hey! Where are you lot going?
- It's urgent! - Go.
What's so urgent?
We're about to open soon!
Ming, come with me. It's urgent.
You have something urgent too?
It's as the people say.
Luang?
There are too many numbers.
How do you read this?
It's not hard.
Above the vertical line is chang.
The upper left is tamleung.
The upper right is baht.
Lower right is saleung.
Lower left is feung.
Below the vertical line is phai.
When you read,
chang, tamleung, baht, saleung,
feung, phai.
You can shorten it to one of the quarters.
You think this is not hard?
I need some "aspirin" in my hands.
- "Aspirin?" - Yes, sir.
What does it mean?
I mean, it gives me a headache, sir.
Fang asked me to do her account,
but it wasn't this complicated.
Then you should learn this.
Soon, when you live in my house,
you can spare my headache.
The headache is not coming soon.
It's now. Dokgaew is coming here.
Crap! How did she find this place?
What are you doing here?
What about you? What are you doing here?
What an odd question.
I'm here to see Chang.
Chang is working here.
But I saw Boonta going in earlier,
and Luang Vasuthep followed her inside.
They both looked suspicious.
I suspect that
Boonta is seeing Luang Vasuthep behind your back.
She's probably seducing Luang Vasuthep.
He's your close friend and cousin.
How could he betray you like this?
You just saw that and think that far?
I know you and Luang Vasuthep are close, and you trust each other.
But love is not something you can control.
If you don't want to regret this,
I think we should barge in.
Dokgaew!
She's here to catch Luang Thukkarat with her.
Why is she getting jealous of Luang Vasuthep instead?
Where is Boonta, sir?
I saw her come in with my own eyes.
Where did you hide her?
You were probably seeing things.
Chang and I are here alone.
I wasn't seeing things.
Dang saw it too, sir.
I did, sir.
Because I saw you,
your plan is ruined.
Is that why Chang is covering up for you?
Why would I do that?
To hide it from Chaai.
Why else would you and Boonta sneak in?
What am I in your eyes?
Do I look like someone who can steal my friend's girl?
Do I also look stupid enough to pick this place
to do something behind Chaai's back?
Dokgaew.
Your idea is nonsensical.
I'm right here working.
Puek and Boonta can't do anything weird.
So you two can prove to me
that what I said is false.
Is there anything else unclear?
If Boonta isn't here,
what are you doing here, sir?
I'm here to visit Chang.
It's what cousins do.
In an old warehouse, sir?
Oh? Chang uses this place to work occasionally.
Do you expect him to go to a temple?
So why are you here, Dokgaew?
Dang heard rumors from the market
that you and Boonta were making love here.
I felt uncomfortable.
I don't want your reputation ruined by the gossip.
So you're here to tell Boonta off.
But she saw me instead, so it's a misunderstanding.
So that's what happened?
I misunderstood you too, Dokgaew.
I thought you came here to catch Chaai in the act.
Or...
Did you come here to catch Puek?
I didn't come here to catch anyone.
I'm glad nothing's going on.
I'm going home.
- Let's go, Dang. - I'll walk with you.
I have all day to walk with you.
No need, sir.
We came here on our own. We can go home on our own.
I'll check on Boonta.
Don't go.
Come on down.
Dokgaew won't come back.
Go without me.
Boonta!
We're in the middle of a chaos!
Yet you snuck out to see your man?
Mother, why are you here?
I followed you!
And it's not just me.
You all can come out!
What are you all doing here?
We all were wondering the same thing, sir.
Just why does Boonta keep sneaking out?
So she snuck out here to see you.
He's not buying your freedom, and you're stupid enough to offer yourself.
Boonta, don't you know restraint?
No matter how good a man looks,
no matter how good he is in bed,
if you sleep with him without getting paid, you're stupid!
Please stop.
You all are misunderstanding.
That's right. The rumors are false.
Chaai and I didn't come here to "hook up."
I mean, we weren't making love, and we weren't
doing anything indecent.
And I intend to buy her freedom.
I'm just trying to convince my mother
so that Boonta can live happily in my house.
Can Mrs. Tubtim be convinced?
She seems to want Dokgaew desperately as her daughter-in-law.
Are you buying Boonta off as your second wife?
I intend to have only one wife.
No! Mother, wait!
That's not it! That's
a woman, not a ghost!
She's alive.
Nual!
Help me down.
So, what happened to Nual?
Why is she here?
Mother, that body wasn't Nual. It was Oeb from Hom's.
Nual
found out something about the suspect.
Chaai is hiding her here for her safety.
He's trying to find the suspect.
Do any of you know anything about Oeb?
Oeb is of Vietnamese descent like me, sir.
Lamduan and I have known her since childhood.
We were neighbors.
Your home is Tha Tien, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
I heard the girls at Hom's say
before Oeb disappeared,
she snuck out of the brothel
and got caught and locked up.
That's just like Lamduan's case.
I once went into Hom's brothel.
The room she used to lock someone up was totally closed,
just like the room I locked Lamduan up in.
When Lamduan ran away, I found her at Tha Tien, sir.
Luang is asking about Oeb.
Yet you're telling him about Lamduan. Are you stupid?
I just remembered it.
They're connected, aren't they?
Do you know if Oeb or Lamduan
had a man courting them?
Oeb disappeared the same day Nual did.
We found no sign of struggle where the body was found.
The people nearby
never heard any cry for help, sir.
Oeb's body was found on the side of Khlong Lod.
That wasn't far from where Lamduan was found.
Their bodies were in similar conditions.
They both were also wearing purple sashes.
If the same killer killed them both,
it appears they target...
Target courtesans who wear purple sashes, right?
- That's right! - Yeah.
Those crime shows I did weren't a waste after all.
Well, if you weren't a courtesan,
I would push you to be a police officer.
That's a great idea.
We've never had a female police officer.
If you become the first, that'd be interesting.
Is that right? I just want to help Chaai catch the killer soon
so we can live in peace, not in fear.
If you need our help,
please let us know.
We're willing to help.
Nobody else should die.
Spear and sword shows.
Spear and sword shows?
Lamduan and Oeb's backs
were slashed in lines.
They looked like cuts from a spear or a sword.
Their bellies were bruised like they were smashed in.
They were probably crushed with a pestle
until their guts and feces
spilled out all over their robes.
Someone who can do this
is probably an acrobat, sir.
The people who perform such dangerous stunts
are the Vietnamese Troupe.
I'm going to investigate them.
Luang.
Are you sure you can go on your own?
Your disguise sucked when you visited my place.
Would you take Chor with you?
That's her hometown.
No!
You see? If I went with him, Boonta would kill me.
Also, I was born and raised there.
If I went in disguise, I would look familiar and arouse suspicion.
And If I went without a disguise,
they wouldn't welcome a courtesan like me either.
You won't do this. You won't do that. What will you do then?
I was in a lot of TV shows.
This is what we do.
(Episode 17: The Detective Couple)
Boonta used an excuse to hang out with her man.
But you allowed her to go.
You want Boonta to spend time with Luang. Is that right?
What do you know?
I just said I was willing to help.
How could I have said no?
She went in with a great disguise.
They won't blow their cover, Mother.
I forgot to ask Mian to give her some birth control soup.
Forget it.
If she gets pregnant,
Luang's mother won't lay a hand on her.
I don't want to talk too much about this.
- Is it true? - It is.
But I can't just keep quiet either!
- This one seems to know a lot of things. - The other day,
- I saw Pan. - She's like an old woman next door.
- Come on. - She's Yam's wife, right?
I saw her coming out of the house at night.
I don't even want to imagine what...
I got customers. I need to serve Khanom Jeen.
Gorgeous lady.
I would like two Khanom Jeens, please.
Of course, gorgeous.
She's a sweet talker.
- Here you are. - Thank you, gorgeous.
There's a lot of Vietnamese around here lately.
You're not from the capital, are you?
These Vietnamese fled from the War of Hue during King Taksin's reign.
Are you here to see their acrobat troupe?
I've only heard about them.
I've never seen their show.
I need to warn you to be careful.
Muen Haw doesn't like people sneaking around his house.
He's embarrassed
by his retarded son,
who's also ugly.
What? Really?
Oh no!
My husband!
Does your arm hurt?
This is bad! Who's going to provide for our family?
No!
What do we do now?
Does your arm hurt? Does it? Hey!
Your staff hurt my husband.
How would he provide for our family now? What if he loses his arm?
How would I live?
- Dear, no! - Hey.
- Just calm down. - How do we live now?
Just calm down!
What are your names?
My husband's name is Choed. My name is Boon...
Pa!
Boonpa, sir!
I'm a jewelry merchant. My husband
is a painter.
Yeah.
Where are you from?
We're from...
From where?
From the North.
Yes.
We came to this place
to take painting jobs around Wat Liab.
That's right, and you hurt your arm. How would you paint now?
I think we need a place to stay for a few nights.
- This is stressful! I'm too stressed. - Stop!
You can spend the night in my cabin.
It's vacant.
He got hurt because of my people.
I'll take responsibility.
Once you get settled, I'll get some medicine for you.
That's too kind of you.
Thank you so much.
Come on.
Yes, sir. My luggage!
Walk slowly, my dear husband.
This is it.
Thank you.
Dum, give me a pot of medicine.
Quick.
Boil this and drink it.
Later, Chuen
will get a doctor to see his arm.
It's fine, sir.
It doesn't hurt as much now.
I'll feel better after some rest.
You can get some rest. You've worked hard all day.
Is that how you talk to your wife?
She seems to love you so much.
Why are you so cold and distant as a husband?
Well...
My husband used to own slaves.
It's an old habit.
Thank you so much for your help.
Dear, you have to get some rest too.
Let's go.
Here.
Did you call me "dear" earlier?
Yes, sir.
If I hadn't said that, they would have been more suspicious.
Then,
I'll change the way I talk to you too.
I'll call you wifey.
My beloved wifey.
Is that good?
Just call me
baby, sir.
Wifey?
Okay.
Then you call me
"my dear," alright?
Of course.
My dear.
My dear Chaai.
Is this all?
You! You troublemaker!
- Father... - Father, don't hurt him. He didn't mean to.
Don't interfere, Chuen!
His mistake
caused trouble for everyone!
And you think I shouldn't punish him?
I'm sorry, Father.
If you can't do a simple job,
just leave my house!
You're a waste of my food and water!
I promise! I won't make a mistake again!
You shouldn't have been born as my son!
What are you looking at?
Go and rehearse your show!
Go! I said go!
Go!
He's too cruel.
Could Muen Haw be the killer?
He can be a suspect.
But don't be convinced yet.
Father shouldn't have hurt you this badly.
It's alright.
I made a mistake.
I deserve punishment.
He did it because he loves me.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
All I want is
to be with Father and you.
Let me see your arm.
What are you doing here?
Well, we came
- to take a bath. - For a walk.
Yeah, we'll take a bath and go for a walk.
Choed, let's go.
Come on.
Let's take a bath and go for a walk.
Come on, dear.
Luang, sir.
We should leave.
Don't make them more suspicious.
Since you told them we're taking a bath,
let's take a bath.
You mean together?
We're husband and wife. Why would we not?
If we don't, they will get suspicious.
- Huh? - Come on.
My dear, I don't think I'm comfortable with this.
Shouldn't you turn your back?
I'll rub your back if you do.
What did you moan for?
My back is red all over, right?
It's probably
not as red as my face.
Let me see, then.
My dear, have I ever told you this?
You smell so good.
Even when you're in the water.
It's probably the scent of potpourri.
My mother smoked my clothes with it.
If you like it,
I'll hold you like this more often.
I don't want to end our disguise as a couple.
I don't want to either.
I wish it were real.
I'll wait for the day it becomes real.
It won't be long.
I promise.
Over there.
Dum likes to play with carcasses!
Carcasses?
The animals. Cats and dogs in the village disappeared. They found him.
They saw Dum smash and hold dead animals.
It's a nasty sight.
Dum is half-witted.
He always embarrasses his father.
Unlike his younger brother, Chuen.
He's handsome and smart.
He's also a great acrobat!
The elites are coming.
I'm not talking about bad things anymore. It's going to bring bad luck.
- I have to go. - Okay.
Khanom Jeen right here!
Khanom Jeen!
- Walla's Khanom Jeen! - Use the clothes.
Pra Aphai's Curry with beansprouts
- and Sahatsachai's chili powder! - We're here anyway.
Let's stop by the market. Maybe we would find a good gem.
I'm going to make a ring for my daughter-in-law.
Who do you mean?
Who else could it be
if not Dokgaew?
Did Chaai agree to that?
He will agree.
If he wants that vile woman as a wife,
I'll only allow her to be a slave wife.
The main wife, legally wedded and respected,
can only be Dokgaew.
If he obeys you,
soon we will have the big day!
Of course. Come on. Let's get a good gem.
Right.
Let's go.
Wow.
- This one is really good. - That's right.
How much is this?
Are you mute?
Well...
How much have you bought one for?
We're new in the business.
We don't really know the price, ma'am.
You became a merchant without knowing the trade at all?
This gem looks familiar.
Where did you get that piece of gem?
- I borrowed it from her. - Oh crap!
Where are you from?
You sound weird.
We're from the North, ma'am.
And...
These gems do look great, ma'am.
But they got some great ones over there. At the other booths, ma'am.
Merchants usually don't tell customers to go to others.
I'm just an honest merchant.
Over there! See?
They have great gems too. Dozens of them, ma'am.
- Look. - What?
Let's go to other booths.
You're buying a gem for your soon-to-be daughter-in-law.
Let's buy from a merchant who knows their stuff
and looks more trustworthy.
Wait, ma'am.
You're buying one for
your daughter-in-law?
Your daughter-in-law should be
around my age, right, ma'am?
I think you should do something simple, ma'am.
There's a trend for "quiet luxury," ma'am.
Kwai? (Stupid)
- Are you calling me stupid? - Whoa!
No, ma'am.
"Quiet luxury" is a European word, ma'am.
It means "low key rich" and "not obviously expensive," ma'am.
Mrs. Tubtim and Mrs. Pikul, I think we should go to other booths.
These merchants are weird.
I don't think you can trust them, ma'am.
- Hey, come on! - I agree.
Let's go. I can't take them anymore.
They got a dozen booths over there.
You let a customer name the price? I'd like to buy it.
Oh, are you not selling?
It's fake.
Wait. Are you packing up?
What's wrong with you?
Chuen!
Why are you here?
I'm here to see you.
I haven't seen you for a few days.
I miss you.
I miss you too.
Tonight, I'm all yours.
Let's go back to the earlier booth.
The merchant didn't make too much sense,
but the gem is better.
I don't think it will be too expensive.
But...
Where are they?
That couple packed up and left just now, ma'am.
Why did they leave? It's still early.
I don't know, ma'am.
They looked like they were running from a debt collector. There they are!
Tubtim, where are you going?
Wait for me!
Where are they all going?
Sorry.
Excuse me.
Tubtim, slow down.
Slow down, ma'am.
Stop. I'm tired.
I can't keep up anymore.
- Slow down, ma'am. - My robe is coming undone.
I can't run anymore.
My robe is coming undone.
Tubtim.
Do you like their gem so much
that you have to run after them?
That's not it.
Something about the couple bothers me.
I think they look familiar.
There you go again! Tubtim!
Thank you for your help, Dum.
Without you, we would have been in trouble.
Why do you have to hide?
Well...
Those aunts are "bullies."
They insulted us, saying we sell fake gold
and fake gems.
So I don't want to sell to them.
My dear.
You share the same suspicion I have, right?
Who are you running from?
Should I help you?
How would you help us?
Come on.
If you remember,
when I investigated Lamduan's death,
The killer might have taken Lamduan through the roof.
- The roof? - The roof, sir?
There are no holes in the roof.
It's too tall to climb, isn't it?
If Dum could carry a woman
while climbing a roof
using a single rope,
he could have taken Lamduan from Fang's.
He doesn't need a ladder.
He came and went in a flash.
He didn't even need to get rid of the evidence.
If we can identify him this much,
we don't need to be undercover anymore. Let's just arrest him.
If I arrest him,
I have to arrest him in the act.
Dum.
What are you doing here?
I saw this cat running around.
Boonpa gave me some snacks, so I fed it.
She gave you a snack?
I helped her and Choed up the roof to hide from market visitors.
So she gave me some snacks.
They're nice to you
to manipulate you!
That couple
is suspicious. They look like they're investigating something.
I don't trust them.
There he goes.
Father!
Where's that couple?
They just packed up and left.
The man said his arm is fine now.
He's not hurt as badly as his wife claimed.
Dum is the killer?
Dum performs spear and sword shows well.
He can carry people up high.
He likes to steal animals and kill them brutally.
It's possible that he does the same with humans.
You mean the killer uses acrobatic skills
to climb the roof
and take a locked-up woman out to kill?
When Lamduan disappeared,
their troupe was fixing our roof.
And when Oeb disappeared,
Hom's brothel hired them to fix their roof too.
He's worse than an animal.
His face is ugly, yet his mind is uglier.
That's why he treats humans like animals.
It's because he was abused like an animal.
I won't do it again...
You shouldn't have been born as my son!
But that cannot justify
him killing someone.
It could have been someone else who's a great acrobat like
Chuen.
When he fought off the thugs at the market,
he proved a capable fighter.
He loves his brother more than anyone.
He could be doing this to protect his brother.
That's right. The day Lamduan disappeared,
both Dum and Chuen were here to fix the roof.
They both were also fixing the roof at Hom's
the day Oeb disappeared, sir.
So, the killer
could have been either of them.
We cannot identify the killer for certain
until we catch him in the act.
If we want to catch him in the act,
we need to lure him out.
Ming, get the Vietnamese to fix the roof.
Yes, Mother.
Wrap it well.
It's hot.
This is for Nual, right? I'll bring it to her.
Again?
What again, Aunt?
While you were away,
Lamjeak volunteered to deliver Nual's every meal in your place.
And she always comes back with a smile.
I wonder what's so good about that place that keeps you going back.
Whoa. What could it be?
I just want you all to get some rest.
Boonta, you just got back. Go take some rest.
- I'll deliver it to her. - Okay.
- Bye, Aunt. - Thank you.
Look at her go.
She dresses well too.
She's giving a seductive look.
Be careful.
(The moon)
(is floating in the sky.)
(The sky is clear and brightly lit.)
(In the air)
(is the light of fireflies, flashing.)
(It's a glittering night of cold dew.)
(The wind blows...)
Sorry.
I didn't mean to spy on you.
Chaai asked me to come and see if it's safe.
I didn't think
I would get to listen to a beautiful song.
Well...
I saw fireflies, and they reminded me of home, sir.
Are there many fireflies back in your hometown?
Yes, sir.
They're just small bugs
that nobody cares about.
Their lives are so short.
I should go.
Fang's open by now.
Wait.
In case it rains on your way back.
Only your kindness
is enough for someone like me, sir.
Please accept this.
I want you to live a long
and healthy life
so you can keep singing beautiful songs.
Yes, sir.
Did you bring Nual's meal?
Chang?
You can leave it with me.
I can't. If I leave it with you, I won't see...
I won't get to return your umbrella.
Here, sir.
Let me take Nual's meal inside.
There will be a feast at Wat Suwannaram.
My mother is attending.
I would like to introduce you.
Are you "going public," sir?
- A singing contest? - Come with me.
I've always dreamt of a singing contest such as this.
I'm not worthy of that big an event, sir.
But I, for one,
would like to hear you sing.
You can do it, Lamjeak.
You nailed the acting, Mother.
Was that slap real?
- Take her away! - Go!
Ugly and mean.
What a pity.
Boonta's plan to lure out the killer is immaculate.
Where did he take Boonta?