Ming fought for love.
I have to fight for myself.
If the contract can be altered,
I'll make money and buy my own freedom.
If you're willing to outbid him,
I'll sell you to her.
- How much? - Ten chang, sir.
(Come this way. The seller is kind.)
(And pretty.)
Boonta is saving up to buy her freedom.
She's working for the Indian owner's clothing store.
Have you seen Boonta?
I haven't, ma'am.
I haven't, Mother.
When I left, if I wasn't seeing things,
Master Chaai was there too.
I have to do something now.
Why is our profit
so little this month?
Two of our ships sank, so there was a lack of supply, sir.
If that's the case,
how would I find ten chang to pay?
Magnate visited Fang's and asked to buy Boonta, ma'am.
(Episode 5: Jeed and The Memory of Boonta)
Is everything alright?
Thank you, sir.
It seems you've paid a lot in bribes.
That's how your trade has been going so well.
I'm merely following their traditions.
How can I help you today?
What's going on?
Why did you bring Sarung here?
Why was he beaten up?
Don't even pretend.
I hired him to work.
His job is to go out and collect money from our sales to the Siamese
even when he was just caught dealing opium!
Yet he slacks off.
He snuck out to work your cargo ships!
That's damaging to my business!
"Shut up!"
I refused to hire a Siamese because they're lazy,
corrupt, and cunning.
You're no different. "You stupid monkey!"
Hey, calm down!
I didn't know he was working for you.
I hired him
because he used to be a lead sailor and knows how to navigate.
Nobody is collecting the money from my sales.
And I'm off to Singapore in just a few days.
I have no money to buy goods from there, and my journey is delayed.
That's your responsibility.
How is that my responsibility?
That's Sarung's fault.
A Chinese like you
have an easier time conducting your business with the Siamese.
You're allowed to have your own warehouse
while I am not!
If you're willing to sell much of the goods in this warehouse to me
at a price lower than the market price,
I'm willing to let this go.
The Thais beg me, and now the Europeans too.
Do you think I'm your cash cow or something?
I say no!
If that's so,
I'll have my payback
to satisfy myself.
Hey, what are you standing there for? Go!
Stop!
Let go!
- Stop! - Calm down!
After your sales,
- my store's stock has almost run out. - Right.
I came to buy clothes at Hua Taphao. They have good stuff here.
What's going on?
You're always picking a fight!
- I'll get you out of here. - Stop!
I said stop!
Stop!
That's what happened, Luang.
I deserve justice.
You took your fellow Siamese's side once.
Now you're taking the Chinese's side too.
So they favor China this early?
Don't accuse me of such a thing
when you're clearly in the wrong.
You used violence and damaged Magnate Thong's goods.
You have to pay him for damages, Captain.
Otherwise, I'll report this to the Resident of Singapore.
You've caused an incident twice.
You might think it's not a big deal.
But if a rumor of this spreads,
it could affect the trade deal
that Hantri Baraney's entourage is negotiating.
The side that would lose out is yours.
Fine.
All right.
I'll pay.
What about Sarung, the one who caused it all?
If I find him,
I'll deal with him.
Hantri Baraney?
Baraney?
Bur...
Burney?
Am I in the middle of the Burney Treaty negotiation?
Hello.
Your "bar" is slanted on one side.
My "bar?"
You're biased, sir.
You don't like the Europeans.
You don't treat the Chinese like you do them.
I don't pick a side.
No matter who it is, I have to do my duty.
The Europeans are waging war on Inn-Wa.
That's why I have to keep an eye on them particularly.
You're afraid they'd colonize us, right?
You can rest easy, sir.
I don't know history as much as Kedsurang does.
But I can tell you this.
We're the only nation around here that's never been colonized.
Are you a cloth seller
or are you an oracle?
How did you know
that I was selling clothes?
Hey, don't tell me
you were stalking me again, weren't you?
You were with the Indian just now.
I heard the rumor of you helping him sell so well.
People were vying to "F" your clothes.
You know too much.
Did you really just hear a rumor?
Did you "F" some?
I'm a man.
Why would I buy those clothes?
Could it be you sent someone there?
How many did she buy?
Don't you have to go back to Fang's?
Thank you anyway for supporting me.
Tomorrow, please come again and "F" some more.
We're not going tomorrow, sir.
We have too many clothes already.
Wait! You haven't paid.
Pay for your drink.
I don't have any!
Nobody lets me work!
How would I have money?
That's not my problem!
You drank at my place. You have to pay!
I don't have any!
What would you do?
Fine...
I would do this!
Boys!
That's enough!
You killed my mood.
Mother didn't come?
She went out in the morning.
Pad, that's not your usual look.
I think I saw some women at the temple
wearing similar colors.
Are these colors trending?
You should ask Chaai.
Lately,
Chaai often patrols around the clothing store.
It seems
he has taken a liking to a seller.
You said you can't force love.
So that meant
you already have someone you love, right?
I have to go to work.
I don't think so, sir.
This Little Market has a lot of goods.
This place is as good as Sampheng.
If you still have no idea what to gift His Majesty,
what about a silk fabric?
That's what you suggested last time.
I think His Majesty already has a lot of good silk.
I want to get something else.
I think we should check over there.
Please help me!
I'm getting robbed!
They're robbing people at the market?
Young Miss, don't smile yet.
You're going to blow your cover.
We should follow them. Luang is going to suspect us.
Chaai, wait for me.
Wad, the wife of the Library Chief,
wishes to see the clothes at her house.
- So that's why we had to close the place for now. - Yes.
- Is it far away? - We should...
- Ouch! - Who's that?
Hey! Come back and fix this!
- I'll be back. - Yeah.
Won't you apologize at all?
Darn you! You dare hurt me?
You think I'm scared just because you're a man?
I did action scenes, you know!
You scoundrel!
This is not the time to get horny!
Don't struggle.
I recognize you.
You're a courtesan at Fang's.
I'm going to kiss you!
- No! - Stay still!
- Here goes! - Ah!
Take this!
Young Miss, that's...
You think you can put your hands on me just because I'm a courtesan?
You...
- That bag is... - Mother, Aunt!
Why are you here?
Mother!
When I'm away, you take your chance
and cause trouble at the market?
I don't know who you stole it from.
All I know is
he ran into me and the Indian and ruined our products.
He also tried to molest me.
I'm seeking maximum punishment, sir.
That was my fault
but she was in my way, sir.
I saw her dancing seductively when she was selling clothes.
A courtesan like her
just gets excited when she sees a man.
I should kick you again! Why?
Was I dancing on your grave or what?
What I do is none of your business.
Remember that in your empty skull!
Even if I walk around naked,
you have no right to do this to me.
That's called "sexual
haramed?"
"Har" something.
That's obviously sexual abuse!
Whether it's a courtesan or a noble,
or any other woman,
or even if it's a man,
if they don't consent,
you have no right to touch, speak to, or even look at them with horny eyes!
How can you stop me? As if you were the only victim.
I'm hurt too.
The bruises on my body are proof!
What about this, huh?
If I hadn't defended myself, this torn sash wouldn't be the only damage!
It would have been ripped off!
All right, Boonta.
Stop arguing.
Dokgaew.
Do you have anything to say?
He's a thief.
He took your money.
Is this not too risky, Young Miss?
Why don't you just hire him to wreck the Indian's store?
So the courtesan won't come to the market anymore.
That would be suspicious.
Even if she doesn't come to the market,
Chaai would be visiting her anyway.
It's best to let something happen to me
right in front of Chaai.
Make Chaai work
so he doesn't have time to visit her.
What if Sarung gets caught?
I'll just forgive him out of pity.
Chaai would see that I'm a good woman,
who is kind even to a thief.
I wish no punishment to him.
I can't help but feel sorry for the man.
He's probably hungry with no means.
That's why he decided to do something reckless.
Nobody is hurt anyway.
I don't want this to go any further.
I'll think of it as making a merit.
Hey, Miss!
Miss, ma'am.
This is not the time to be generous.
I know you're kind, but please have some "limit."
This scoundrel took your money, ma'am.
He tried to molest me.
He caused trouble for all of us.
He needs to be jailed, ma'am.
Also, he needs to pay for the damage.
If Sarung does this on his own, the punishment is on him.
If he has an accomplice,
the accomplice would share half the punishment.
Sarung was fired from his job, sir.
He's alone with no friends.
He can't have an accomplice, right?
It's up to you to decide, Officers.
I think you two can come to a fair decision.
You think I can't punish you
just because you're a European's underling?
I was wrong, sir.
Please don't punish me.
I can't jail you
but I can fine you.
You're lucky Dokgaew spared you.
But you still have to pay damages to the Indian.
And to me for compensation, sir.
What she said.
I'm really sorry.
Let me help you pay for the clothes damage.
Keep this for your own expenses.
I received enough from Sarung.
I still have to apologize.
Mother found out. I can't help you anymore.
I understand.
The next time you visit the market,
or the next time I visit Fang's to sell clothes,
I'll ask for your advice again.
Of course.
- I have to go now. - Right.
Goodbye.
During the interrogation,
Yod already accompanied Master Tubtim and Master Pikul home.
Master Tubtim told Yod to tell Luang Thukkarat
that he was to accompany you home.
But...
Chaai has work to do,
so he asked me to come in his stead.
I would rather not impose, sir.
We can go home ourselves.
It's not an impose.
I have free time and I'm willing.
Or do you have other plans?
Is that why you don't want me with you?
I'm going straight home as I'm worried about my mother.
You can see me off at Sampheng Dock.
Once I get on the boat,
you can rest assured.
Boonta.
What are you doing here, sir?
I saw your sash was torn.
I'm here to give you a new one.
It's just a small tear. It's fine, sir.
Please take it.
I sent someone to
"F" too many of them.
Then that's fine.
But I'll pay for it.
I'm rich today, from the fine.
Luang is richer.
Please take it.
I was going to buy you sandals last time.
And you're still rejecting me this time?
Okay, sir.
There will be no next time, though.
So,
I have to go.
Mother is probably waiting to deal with me.
Excuse me.
If something happens,
you can tell me.
I'm willing to help.
Mother won't hurt me, sir.
I'm her moneymaker.
Goodbye, sir.
Mother, I'm sorry
for doing this behind your back.
I had to. Otherwise, I'll have no money.
Or would you pay me a salary?
Why would I pay you? You're the one that owes me!
Then you have to let me work small jobs.
Let me make some money.
You...
If Captain Jon hadn't requested not to hurt you,
I would flog your back off.
And for the rest of you who covered up for her,
nobody requested your safety.
How should I punish you, huh?
Mother, I told them to keep quiet.
I'll take all the punishment, ma'am.
Fine.
I'll factor this into your debt as you have wasted my time.
And I'll close your room upstairs.
If you love her so much, take her to your bedroom.
As for Mian and Ming,
if you're not honest and loyal to me,
you can go work for Boonta instead.
Mother.
That's all.
Go back to work!
Go!
Yes, ma'am.
Boonta, darn you! You screwed me.
Go.
Ming.
I made this money selling clothes
and from compensation.
Take this money, apologize to your father-in-law, and pay her dowry.
I was going to give Lamduan this money to buy her freedom.
But she's dead now.
I think you need it more.
Aren't you saving up to free yourself?
I am.
But I'm having an easier time here than everyone, including you.
Take it.
It's best to be with your family.
I'll ask you one thing though.
You love your family.
Other people love their families too.
They wouldn't have wanted their wives and daughters to work here.
I know you're just following Mother's orders.
But your real job is
to protect the women here,
not hurt them, isn't it?
I have to.
If you have to, be as gentle as possible.
Even if you're a pimp,
a guard at a courtesan house
has his honor and pride too.
I'll try then.
Boonta.
Thanks a lot for your help.
She doesn't let me work. How can I buy my own freedom?
What are you mumbling about?
Why aren't you sleeping?
I can't sleep.
My back hurts.
Oh my...
Lamjeak.
I saw you working hard. I think your body may be stiff.
Let me give you a massage.
Lie down.
Hey! Whoa!
Let's begin.
The other one.
Good?
Well, it's good.
This is about right?
Yeah, good.
So
Why do we have to sneak in here?
I'm just worried
that Pudsorn would see this and tell Mother.
She irritates me.
Yeah, right.
- You like that? - Yeah.
Are you sure you know how to massage?
You can't just massage on your own. You need a teacher.
I've had a teacher.
Pressuring with pull,
stretch, and stop
will help your blood flow
and get back to a natural state.
See? My massage is "free" and doesn't cost a dime.
Yeah, do it.
You're good at this.
I'll make you feel even better.
Come on.
Put your hands on the back of your neck.
- Back of my neck? Yeah. - Back of your neck. Here.
Ouch.
- This will hurt a little. - Go on.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
"Okay."
Is that good?
- Yeah, good. - Come here.
- The next one is even better. Stretch your legs. - You sure?
Okay. Stretch.
Reach backward with both hands.
Both? Yeah.
- Ready? Breathe in. - Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Chor.
Hurry up with your shallots. The water is boiling.
Yes, Aunt.
Oh, hey!
Lamjeak. Where have you been?
Did you have a rough night, Lamjeak?
Is that why you're in this state?
No. Boonta gave me a massage.
Massage?
What massage? Why are you in this condition?
- Hey! - Oops!
Hey!
Lamjeak said you had a teacher.
I did.
But not a massage teacher.
Oh, Chor. Please give me a chance.
No one is born capable.
Just tell me how you like it.
I'll improve.
Then you lie down.
Press for the duration of one breath.
Boonta.
Hey!
Yeah. There. My shoulders. Yeah!
I'll get your neck and shoulders.
- Oh, you know? - This side too.
I carried your curry pots and it made my shoulders
- all stiff. - Let's get your neck now.
You're making me drool.
I'm loving this so much.
Come on. Who's next?
Why can't I do this?
Was that too hard?
That's good.
This is relaxing.
The bowl sunk. My turn. Now!
- Get up. - Let me pay.
Here.
- Come on. - Come here. What massage would you like?
I'll pay first. Here.
- Pay before service. Here. - Boonta!
Are you charging them money?
- I'll tell Mother. - Hey!
- Let me go! - Take her here.
Let go!
- Come here. - Come on.
- What are you doing? - Come here! Push her down!
- What are you doing to me? - Hold her! That's right!
Oh...
Is this good?
It's good.
Boonta is helping us relax our bodies.
Yes.
Boonta.
You go and buy condiments as I say.
I need to do something.
I'll be back soon.
Wait for me here. Here.
This is my time.
Aunt! You haven't told me what to buy!
Why is she in such a hurry?
One pinch.
Hello.
- This? - Take a look.
Come on. Don't keep us waiting.
It's Tiansin!
Oh! I won!
- I won! - There you are!
Oh! Boonta! You scared me.
- How much did you win? - I won the lottery!
First prize?
How much did you win? I want it too.
Are you lucky though?
Do you really want to buy some?
Boonta. Luang?
- Run! - Police's here!
Let me go!
Run!
Aunt, wait!
- Go! - Aunt!
- Quick! - Run!
Aunt, wait!
Aunt!
Hey, move!
Oh, sorry!
Aunt!
Move it! Move!
Sorry!
Aunt!
Sorry, ma'am.
Oh?
Aunt Mian?
Aunt Mian told me to take you by this boat.
Come with me. Quick!
Okay. Aunt!
I need to get out of here!
Boonta? Boonta!
Boonta...
No more... Oops!
Where's Boonta?
Where did Aunt Mian tell you to go?
Why didn't you answer?
Boonta.
You...
You... It's Boonta.
Boonta didn't attempt suicide.
Boonta was murdered.
What are you saying?
When I was in the water,
I saw a brief flashback.
I saw someone chasing Boonta
and that was before I fell into the water.
So you think you didn't try to kill yourself?
Someone tried to kill you.
Boonta.
Back then, something was strange.
But I didn't pay attention. I was worried about you.
After that, Fang's staff took you back.
Do you remember the one who chased you?
I don't.
I can't recall.
Was that all you see?
Yes, sir.
Didn't you see me in that flashback?
I didn't.
I'll investigate this and find the culprit.
You need to be careful.
Yes, sir.
Aunt, was she taken in by the police?
Why would they take her? She didn't do anything.
Even me,
all I got was a warning.
They won't arrest her.
Aunt Mian! Why did you leave me behind?
It was an emergency. I had to run.
Are you alright? Where have you been?
Why are you soaking wet? You...
Did you and Luang make love in the water?
I fell into the water. Luang saved me.
If you don't believe me,
you can ask Yod.
- That's true. - Yod.
So...
Let me warn you. Even if you were husband and wife,
if Mother finds out, you have to be careful...
Aunt! I said we didn't do anything!
It's fine. I understand.
Some things are hard to quit.
What? I said we did nothing. You too!
He looks handsome,
but his teeth are black with betel. I don't like it.
Are you still up?
Yes, Mother.
What's wrong with you and Yod?
Suddenly, you're copying the Europeans.
Why have you brushed your teeth white?
Yod.
Put your head up. Let me see your teeth.
Yod!
Why have you brushed your teeth white?
Obsidian teeth
look way healthier and more beautiful.
Did you hear that, Yod?
Chew some betel to blacken your teeth now.
- Now! - Yes, sir.
Are you afraid I'd be more handsome?
I heard that.
I'm going, sir!
Mong Chank, you have been a monk for three years, right?
Mother.
Your memory is too good.
I'm counting the days and nights.
Don't you think of leaving monkhood?
I'm getting old.
Chim and Chaai are busy with work.
When will we be all together?
If he wants to stay a monk to study Dharma
and carry on Buddhism,
you shouldn't object, Mother.
Brother Chaai.
You don't chew betel much,
but why are your teeth suddenly so white?
Chang, please talk some sense into him.
He won't listen to me at all.
All of a sudden,
Brother Chaai does things he's never done.
It's probably for something special.
I have to go to work.
If you're not going home yet,
please stay and talk to Monk Chang.
Master Chaai seems strange, ma'am.
Is it because of that woman?
Don't tell me he whitened his teeth for her?
What do you need to discuss with me, sir?
I need your further statement.
Don't tell me...
Hey, sir! I was kidding. You brushed your teeth all white.
Here, sir.
Aunt.
You can go back to work.
It's all done.
I said
you can go back to work.
Then please be quick and leave.
If Mother sees you, I'll
be in trouble.
You came to our kitchen and told Aunt Mian to go away.
Is there a secret or something?
I suspect
that the one who had your boat sunk
is Dokgaew.
Puek suspects that Dokgaew hired Sarung
to cause trouble at the market the other day.
I knew it.
If I bought a lottery, I would have won.
Did you buy a lottery?
It's just an analogy.
I think it might not have been Dokgaew.
It's Gaysorn.
Gaysorn seems to dislike me too.
So we have two suspects now.
If we catch the perpetrator,
we'll find out who hired him.
How do we find him, sir?
The perpetrator wore a blue turban.
I saw half his face.
And...
He had dark brows.
He had sharp eyes.
His nose didn't seem too big.
Oh, more importantly,
he had a mole under his right eye.
Why is Boonta so lucky?
Why is it so hard to kill her?
I'll find another way, ma'am.
Stop for now.
Boonta's had too many incidents.
Luang Thukkarat must have caught on to something by now.
Yes, ma'am.
Gaysorn.
Yes, dear.
There you are.
Who were you talking to?
I came to tell the servants to cut some branches.
What do you need, dear?
I heard that
Chim, Luang Thukkarat's older brother,
is joining the bid for bird nest tax.
I would like you to negotiate with Luang Thukkarat.
Tell them not to outbid me.
Gaysorn.
If I were put in charge of that tax,
I might become an official with my own land.
We won't have to pay tax on our properties.
So the other officials
would stop looking down on me and picking on me.
I'll try to talk to Dokgaew.
What? You would like me to invite Dokgaew over for lunch?
Yes, Mother.
I have something I need to ask her.
Chaai wants to see me. Walk faster, Dang.
Stop!
Sarung, move it. You're drunk.
Don't get in our way.
Before you go,
I need my money.
I already paid you. What else do you want?
What you paid me
didn't even cover the fine!
If you don't pay me more,
I'll tell Luang Thukkarat
that you hired me
to play a thief.
What do you say?
I won't pay you.
Who would believe a drunk sailor like you?
Let's go, Dang.
- Hey, let go! - I said pay me!
Whoa! Pay me!
- Let me go! - Don't try to run!
Sarung, let go!
Stop! I give up!
Why didn't you arrest him, sir?
If I arrest the hired thief,
I would have to arrest the one who hired him too, right?
If Chaai finds out,
would he still want to see you?
Please don't tell Chaai.
I beg you.
What do you want of me?
I'll do anything.
You promised.
Do you know the person in this drawing?
I won't wait until I get a husband, Aunt,
because I'm going back to where I belong.
Please find the Hoan for me.
Do you know, sir,
that I came from the future?
So why have I come here?
When can I go back?
Why would you want to know about a solar eclipse?
I'm not the same old Boonta you used to know.
Is Nual in the kitchen?
Did she sneak out to see her husband again?
I keep shedding tears
sleeping with countless men.
Yet you're just enjoying yourself.
What's wrong with Boonta?