So I don't have enough work to do?
Is that why she's making me babysit?
Under every crate in my ship,
there is a double lion symbol.
That means someone snuck it in to frame the ship's owner.
If you don't want to disgrace yourself,
don't steal my property.
If you want to own her,
you can buy her for ten chang.
Your status and his are too different.
Your love is not meant to be.
Luang may love you,
but do you think his mother would approve?
I'm leaving the child with you.
Don't worry. I'll take care of her.
Someone save my daughter!
Boonta's inside? Boonta...
- Chaai, watch out. - Boonta...
Your arm.
(Episode 10: Whether You're a Goose Or a Swan, I Still Like You)
I'm sorry, sir.
You got hurt because of me.
Thank you for saving me though.
Please promise me
you'll never risk yourself like that again.
Yes, sir.
Your face is all dirty.
You're as hot as a nuclear reactor right now.
What did you say?
I said keep a distance, sir.
I don't want to.
And I don't want to be just friends.
Please don't keep your distance because of Dokgaew.
Even though my mother wants to match me with her,
I only love her like a sister.
Until now,
I was afraid to lose face
or lose my pride,
but now I'm afraid to lose you more.
You said I should "move on"
and start over.
Are you ready to start over with me?
(Luang may love you, )
(but do you think his mother would approve?)
So you admit it now
that you love a courtesan like me?
What about your mother?
Would she approve of me
like you do, Chaai?
The fire spread to almost ten households.
Hob's brothel was damaged too.
Could it be an arson?
Nobody would dare.
If they get caught,
it's punishable by death.
Then where did the fire start?
From my apartment, sirs.
The fire
started in my apartment.
We were lucky we could put out the fire quickly.
Otherwise, it would have been like in the first reign
when the fire spread from Wat Sampleum all the way to Sampheng.
There were serious damages nonetheless.
The Police Force is taking donations for help.
That could help with the relief efforts.
Even if the authorities are helping,
the culprit should pay too, shouldn't they?
I didn't want it to happen, Hob.
My daughter was responsible for the fire.
I'll help as much as I can.
Everyone.
Come and take some money.
I'll do what I can.
I really
feel sorry for Mother.
The fire spread to the house. We have to close down and repair.
We're lucky our kitchen is still intact.
Aunt, we're out of work temporarily,
and we have to donate a lot of money to repair houses and other brothels.
At least, Mother is kind enough to let Ming off.
She also gives his family the hut in the banana bush.
Our Mother is so generous.
So...
Why are we cooking these foods?
Well,
Mother is going to deliver food to your Luang.
Every time they meet,
they usually fight, don't they?
Not exactly fight.
They just don't get along.
Why is she cooking for him all of a sudden?
- Could it be... - What?
Is Mother falling for him too?
Nonsense!
You don't have to worry about Mother stealing your husband.
I was just kidding.
I wanted to repay him for saving my daughter.
You girls hurry up.
- The people are hungry. - Yes, Mother.
Come on. Hurry up. Quick.
You're all looking miserable.
Here.
Don't just sit there.
If you have children, tell us. We'll give you more. Come on.
Take some of this, kid. Eat a lot.
Let me help.
Here.
Heaven always finds a way to test me.
Whoa.
Boonta.
Give this to Luang Thukkarat.
Take Kleeb with you.
Go, sweetie.
If you want to repay him, why don't you give him yourself?
Just do as I say.
If you hesitate, I'm going to punish you. Go!
Come on, Young Miss.
Here, sir.
Mother told me to give you this, as a thank you for saving Kleeb, sir.
Thank you.
We're starting to get hungry.
I'm starting to get hungry.
I'll let you take care of me for this meal.
Eat with us here.
Chaai's meal would taste ten times better.
It's fine, sirs. I've already eaten.
And I need to help them out.
Young Miss, give Luang the food, please.
Yod, take one.
Let's go, Young Miss.
Here, Uncle.
They asked for a donation again?
Is my house an almshouse or what?
The patrol said there was a fire last night, sir.
Where was the fire this time?
In an apartment near the Courtesan Houses.
I heard it was close to Fang's, sir.
Move, hey.
Move over there. Get closer. It'd be easier.
Thank you for your donation of sugar and rice.
I really didn't want to ask anyone.
Every time there is a fire or a disaster,
the authority asks for donations from us traders
and wealthy people to help the locals.
But that doesn't mean I donate willingly.
So you're making this donation
just for your image. Is that right?
That's not the case, sir.
The people are in trouble.
Magnate Thong is not a petty person.
He's happy and willing to help.
Those who are more fortunate can help.
That's true.
If you do good deeds with a negative mind,
how would it be a merit?
What's she bragging about?
Dokgaew and I
are willing to make this merit, sir.
I brought some clothes for the people to change.
There are volunteers during this age?
They give out supply bags too?
Chaai.
Please help me give out clothes to the people.
Here.
They look cute.
They look so good together. As if the gods match them.
Is that right, Fang?
She sure smiles a lot.
Are you jealous?
How am I jealous?
She can smile all she wants. I couldn't care less.
Everyone!
If you haven't received food or need more, please come here.
- I hope that's true. - You can't eat clothes, can you?
Come on.
- Here. - Nobody's coming.
We have cups of rice. Over here!
Who are you looking for?
These people are waiting for clothes.
Please smile.
They're going to think you're a demon.
Smile.
Boonta.
Let me go, sir.
Let go!
You ignored me
because you're still mad
that I let Gaysorn sell you out
when I knew you were framed, right?
I didn't want to let her.
I really couldn't say no.
So that means
Boonta didn't poison your wife?
Sir?
So you forgot everything.
You really forgot the love I have for you?
What happened, sir?
Poor thing.
Now that Bua's gone,
you have nothing left.
I'm not a cruel man.
However,
I have to hold up my end of the deal.
You will live here as a slave.
Gaysorn will be taking care of you.
Don't worry, dear.
I'll teach her to work.
I trust you.
But please
show her a little mercy.
A former elite like her
probably needs time to adapt.
Please let me go.
You shouldn't do this.
Calm down.
I just want to comfort you.
I want to let you know
I've always had eyes on you.
I've loved
and adored you all this time.
But I...
It breaks my heart to see you suffer so much.
I want to help you.
Help...
How, sir?
If you
agree to be one of my wives,
you won't be a slave anymore.
I respect you as my savior.
Gaysorn, too, has been
good to me.
I don't want to cause any resentment.
Please let me be just a slave.
I don't intend to force anyone.
If you don't agree, then so be it!
Even if you don't have feelings for me,
I still intend to buy you back home.
At least, it's better than working as a courtesan.
Fang told me
even if she agreed to sell you to Captain Jon,
if I pay her ten chang,
she'd sell you to me.
Ten chang?
Mother sure is stingy.
Boonta, don't worry
that Gaysorn won't approve of you.
This time, I'll make her understand.
Well, you said you knew
I was framed and I didn't poison your wife.
Do you also know
who did it and why they put the blame on me?
Dear.
So there you are.
Did you finish giving out everything?
Yes, dear. I did.
I'm here to ask you to go home.
If you want to,
let's go home together.
Today is a really long day.
You won't start over with me,
but you would start over with Magnate Thong?
I haven't started over with anyone. Hey...
Don't get the wrong idea, sir.
Then why were you holding his hands like that?
I wasn't holding him. He was holding me!
If you didn't consent,
why didn't you resist?
I wanted to find out who tried to kill Boonta,
so I just played along.
You played along
because you wanted that information?
Such dedication.
It's just a hand. It's nothing.
I've done worse.
I'm an actress!
You see, sir.
I didn't consent,
but at least, I found out more about Boon...
About myself, sir.
What did you find out?
The fact that
Magnate Thong wants me as a wife,
but I said no.
What if Gaysorn
found out?
Is it possible that she was upset
and framed me for her poisoning?
She's probably the one who ordered a hit on me.
It is possible.
But you still need evidence.
I'll find that evidence, sir.
By involving yourself with Magnate Thong again?
So this time you consent.
Luang, you're still mad about that?
Chaai, sir.
You asked me about my mother.
I spent all night thinking about it.
I believe that, even if she's now biased against you,
if she gets to know you,
and be close to you like I do,
she would certainly approve of you.
I will prove to her that even if you're just a courtesan,
you're the woman I decided to love
and spend the rest of my life with.
Wait a minute, Chaai.
I think you shouldn't go that far yet.
You said that to me
but if I start over with you,
I would probably hurt you again.
Let's not be anything more yet.
If we can't stay friends,
we can just be acquaintances that come and go.
One day, you will marry someone worthy.
For me,
I will go back to where I belong.
That settled it, sir.
I have to go.
Chaai!
You did the right thing, Jeed.
Don't let it get too far.
Chaai!
Why are you here?
You left me to hand things out alone.
Before I knew it,
you disappeared.
I don't think he has to tell you where he goes.
You're not his Siamese twin.
You're not his Siamese twin either.
You don't have to be with him all the time.
Puek came looking for me.
We have urgent work, is that it?
Let's go.
Chaai!
I'm going home soon.
If Boonta returns,
this will have nothing to do with me anymore.
He and Boonta can continue their relationship.
Boonta!
What did you do to Chaai?
Why did he walk away looking so upset?
What about Magnate Thong
and Aunt Gaysorn?
They looked upset too.
Was that because of you?
Magnate Thong is upset, and Chaai too.
Does everything have to be Boonta's fault?
Look, miss. I'm just a courtesan.
What can I possibly do?
I'm glad you realized you're just a courtesan.
Don't even try to match our class.
That's harsh.
Wait. What did you call Chaai just now?
I call him Chaai.
He told me to call him that. If you want to complain, complain to him.
But now,
he and I are nothing.
I'll call him Luang again, ma'am.
Boonta! You...
So heroic.
You came at just the right time, sir.
Otherwise, it would have been fun.
You're a high-ranking official's daughter,
yet you behave in such a way.
Can you still say you outclass a courtesan?
Why do you have to protect her every time, sir?
Or you kept following Chaai
not only to keep me away from him
but to see Boonta yourself.
You have feelings for her.
Dokgaew!
If that's the case,
should we join forces?
Dear.
So there you are.
Muean.
Yes, ma'am.
I want to get my nails done.
Get the manicurist here.
A lot happened in just a couple of days.
It would be good to get some rest.
Mother is generous. She lost income, but she allows us to take days off.
I'm going back home.
And I'll make merit for Lamduan.
I'm visiting my mother too.
But I don't have a home or a family.
I'll just sleep all day.
Me too.
Not having a husband
is kind of nice.
- And I will... - My master wants her nails done.
They say you do house calls.
Do you accept this job?
Or are you afraid?
Come in!
Okay.
She's so mean.
Madam Gaysorn.
You didn't have to come out.
I'm bringing her to you.
If she dares to come,
I should dare to welcome her myself.
You let her go alone?
We tried to stop her,
but Boonta insisted on going.
We didn't know what to do.
Aunt Mian, don't worry too much. I think she can survive.
Easy, ma'am.
I heard you're skilled,
so I wanted to support you.
What colors do you have?
Most do bright red.
If you want another color,
I can mix some yellow in.
You can have different shades of orange.
What color would you like?
Ma'am.
I'll have the color that's on you.
What a good choice, ma'am.
Show me your hands, please.
Let me put this here to rest your hand.
My master's hands are soft and delicate.
If you scratch her even a little,
you're getting it.
No clipping then.
Can I have some hot water, please?
I need to dissolve
this acacia sap.
I'm not your servant.
If you want something, go get it yourself in the kitchen.
Okay.
Excuse me. Can I have some hot water, please?
Thank you.
If this weren't King Rama III's era,
I would have thought they all got the same surgery in Korea.
He's good at finding these girls.
I understand now why the wife hates Boonta so much.
No matter where you look,
you'll find a girl who looks similar to your husband's crush.
Thanks.
This gives me the creep.
It's like I'm seeing myself.
Are you pretending to be nice to me
because you think I'd let you back in as his mistress?
Don't think I don't know
that he keeps visiting you often.
So you know, right?
I fell in the water and lost my memory.
I don't remember what happened between you and me.
And I'm not being nice to you
because I want to be his mistress.
I just want money.
I want money more than I want a husband, ma'am.
But if you hate me, I understand.
I just want you to hate the right person.
I'm just here doing my thing.
It's your Magnate that keeps chasing me.
Are you saying I can't keep my husband with me?
No, ma'am.
I'm saying that Magnate
is not my "type."
I mean
I don't like men who look like that.
No matter how much he tries, I would always reject him, ma'am.
Such arrogance.
How dare you act like you're above my master?
Hey, you.
I'm just trying to comfort your master.
I understand that
men in this age
usually have multiple wives.
And women still depend on men.
But from what I've seen of you.
You're beautiful,
rich,
and powerful.
More importantly,
your husband seems quite fearful of you.
If you're a bit more decisive, you can get him under control.
But if I were you, I wouldn't tolerate someone who doesn't appreciate me.
I'd rather stay single and rich.
You think I'm stupid,
and you're so smart?
Is that why you dare lecture me?
You can have your opinion, ma'am.
I'm just trying my best.
It's almost done, ma'am.
All done, ma'am. Wait a bit until it dries.
What about my toenails?
My master told you to do her toenails.
Well.
As soon as she said she'd pay extra,
you said yes without a second thought.
You can't survive on pride, right?
Only money can "knock everything."
What did you say?
I'm not insulting your master. Don't worry.
But I actually want to.
I actually cared about her,
yet she's making me do her toenails.
I even have to come and get a towel to wipe her feet. Such a bully.
Darn it.
Come in already.
Okay.
We have to go to the bedroom to get a towel?
You can't just use any towel on my master's feet.
There are high-quality towels in that chest.
Pick one you want to use.
You said I can't just pick any towel?
Why won't you pick one?
Hey, you.
You get paid to work but you want me to do everything for you?
Am I getting my cut of money or what?
I'm going to get some hot water.
Pick a towel and follow me.
Okay.
She's so rich.
I should find some clues about Boonta.
What are you doing?
You're wasting our time.
You keep my master waiting.
I'm just going in.
She didn't
scold me or
curse me at all?
Was that too easy?
Let's do your toenails, ma'am.
Darn you!
Did you hurt my master?
What's wrong? I'm sure I haven't even picked anything.
Don't pretend to blame me!
You!
- How dare you, Boonta? - Let go.
Let me go! Let go!
- Let go! - How dare you?
You dare...
You got a fight in you, huh?
That hurts! Ah...
Boon...
Take that!
Let me go!
- You're going to bring it, huh? - Let go.
That's your pay.
The money my master paid you
is equal to what a courtesan earns in one night.
You can spare yourself from serving a guest tonight!
What happened?
Who did this to you?
Gaysorn's servants did this to you?
It's because of Gaysorn.
She pretended to be hurt when I clipped her nails.
The servants got upset and jumped on me.
Luang, sir.
If I report them for assault,
I wouldn't get any justice, right?
Once upon a time,
I used to be a swan.
Why did my life change so much?
Those in front of you are geese.
You can't tell a goose from a swan?
Well...
They walked here right "on cue."
I'm a goose then.
Here, all I get is insult and indiscrimination.
I can never rise as a swan again.
Even if you're a goose,
you still have your qualities.
It's like you're
telling me to be proud to be a goose.
Whether you're a goose or a swan,
I like you just the way you are.
I want you to be happy with your life.
Don't compare yourself to others.
I can't accompany you to Fang's.
I have urgent work in Pak Nam.
You're going out of the "province" this time.
I mean outside of the capital, sir.
That's right.
Rumor has it that the children's wrist slasher is there.
So...
Be careful, sir.
Even if we're just acquaintances
and not friends,
do you still care about me?
Well, we can care about each other anyway.
Then I care about you too.
Here, sir.
I told Yod to get you some Chinese medicine.
Boil this and drink it. It will heal you.
I'll be back as soon as I'm done.
Thank you, sir.
You're Boonta, are you not?
Yes, sir.
We're from the Police Force.
Magnate Thong's staff reported
that you stole Gaysorn's gold bracelet.
Kleeb, try combing her hair.
Mother!
Boonta is in trouble, Mother.
I think this is a misunderstanding.
I didn't steal anything.
You're not just a courtesan,
you're a thief too!
I'm not.
That's not mine.
How did it get in your basket then?
I don't know!
Did you steal it from her?
Mother, why would I look for trouble?
I've never seen this bracelet before.
So why were you at their house?
You know they hate you so much there.
- I went to do her nails, Mother. - Whoa!
I didn't think they'd frame me. Mother...
It's not your job to question her.
Arrest this vile woman.
Hey!
- Mother, help me! - Boonta!
- Boonta! - Mother, help me!
- Boonta! No! - Mother!
- Boonta! - Boonta!
No, I'm not going in.
I didn't do anything.
Hey, sir!
Why did you put me in jail? I didn't do anything.
You haven't even charged me yet!
The evidence incriminates you.
You're in temporary custody.
There will be an investigation later.
What the heck? I didn't do anything! Let me go!
What should I do now?
What's that?
Darn it.
What the heck?
Boonta has been arrested, ma'am.
A slave like you would be punished hard in jail.
A courtesan without honor like her would have it harder.
Nobody would have mercy on her.
That's true, ma'am.
As time passes,
she will be forgotten there.
At some point,
I'll have Tis take care of her.
What if Luang Thukkarat saves her?
Luang Thukkarat can't save her that easily.
I'll ask my uncle to be strict too.
What are you smiling about?
Help me!
Officers!
I didn't do anything! Why did they frame me?
I didn't steal anything. If I did, I would have stolen more!
I don't want to be in jail.
Get me out!
Stop smiling!
A ghost!
You darn police!
Why did you lock me in with a dead body?
If I die in here,
I'd join forces with this corpse
and snap your necks as ghosts!
You stop smiling?
If you call me a dead body again,
I'll snap your neck myself!
So you're not dead?
Of course not.
If you cry so hard like that,
I can't die in peace.
So
What happened to you, Aunt?
If you call me Aunt again, I'll slap the taste out of your mouth!
I'm not even 30 years old.
Then we can be friends.
What did you do?
I don't know.
I got framed for stealing.
It doesn't matter how serious, or guilty or not.
When you get tortured, you will confess.
Don't tell me you turned out this way
because Aunt, I mean you...
You refused to confess?
(If he gets put in jail today, he will be tortured into confession.)
(For us, jail is Hell.)
Screw me.
No, I won't take this.
I won't stay in jail.
Mother! Chaai!
Help me!
Whoa! Why do you keep smiling?
(Guest Starring - Deejai Deedeedee)
Could the solar eclipse happen today?
Last time, you framed her for poisoning you.
If you would do anything to kill her,
I'll do anything to save her myself!
Slaves like us, without a master,
we don't have the right to defend ourselves or any protection.
If I have a master,
I can get out of here, right?
Who is your master?
Nobody tells her Chaai is away.
What's so urgent, ma'am?
Kill Boonta in jail.