They had history, yet Mrs. Gaysorn
still hired Boonta to her house.
She even allowed her to search
for a chest that contained gold.
Could it be that what happened was what this courtesan described?
I did it because I felt angry on my master's behalf.
I couldn't stand seeing Boonta stealing my master's husband, Your Honor.
What would be her punishment, Your Honor?
Fifty flogging with a leather whip!
Where is this solar eclipse taking you?
Wherever it is,
I have to go on my own way.
But you're going your way without me.
How would I live then?
Boonta!
If you would do anything to kill her,
I'll do anything to save her myself!
Muean.
Thank you so much for saving me.
This is nothing to me, Master.
It's a shame Boonta was acquitted.
It's her.
She's the reason you got hurt.
You did that to yourself.
Yet you still dare to blame someone else?
You couldn't just sit still.
You just had to go and embarrass yourself.
Are you really
the wife that I'm supposed to honor?
You're the reason behind everything.
I did all of this because of you!
What did I do?
You think I don't know?
You do your business.
You got rich and became a magnate.
Yet you have no ranks or titles.
You married me for my status, didn't you?
Ever since I got married to you,
I have always let you have your ways.
But you had to take Boonta in and trample all over my heart!
You are saying that I owe you.
I don't dare say that, dear.
I just want to warn you.
Don't be too shameless with these things.
You still need me, after all.
If I'm still here,
- Boonta will never step foot... - Fine! Try it!
We'll see what happens.
(If you're willing to outbid him, )
(I'll sell you to her.)
How much?
Ten chang, sir.
You greedy pimp.
You're trying to extort me.
You think someone will always protect you?
Oh, Boon...
How long have you been here?
Since last night.
Don't tell me you all slept here?
Well...
You slept like a baby.
I think you should sleep a bit more.
Yeah. Sleep a bit more.
You woke up so late.
I think you're good now.
I said I'm fine. Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
I'm taking a bath.
A bath?
Hey.
Are we all taking a bath together?
It's hot.
Making beds made me sweat all over. I need a bath.
I want to wash my body.
I want to wash my hair.
Let's take a bath together.
What's wrong with them?
Is the water cool?
Come on.
You see? Those girls
were afraid you'd drown yourself again if you were left alone.
I know they're worried,
but I'm not drowning myself again.
Drowning myself at this point won't do a thing anyway.
That's why I have to stay in this body.
I need to survive.
Good. You finally realized that.
Oh, my death!
I'm going to die because of you.
Why did you brake so suddenly?
Are you still thinking about killing yourself?
- No. - What do you mean "no?"
You were talking about dying just now.
Luang, sir. It's good to see you.
Please help me convince her.
- What's wrong, Aunt? - What about you?
Just go and see your man.
Maybe you can stop being sad
and stop thinking about dying.
Please help convince her, sir.
Mr. Husband.
Aunt!
Wait, Aunt.
I already said my farewell.
How am I supposed to act now?
What's that, sir?
Pay me back for your hairpin
and pay for my shirt that you took and sewn.
Wait, sir.
Are you collecting debt?
That's why
you can't run and disappear from me again
until you pay your debt off.
What's that? You're supposed to give flowers or a gift to a sad person.
But what did you do? Who collects debt in this situation?
I don't want you to leave me again.
Even if I want to, I can't leave now, sir.
So that's a promise.
These are geese.
You said you were a goose, didn't you?
I knew you'd like this.
I may not know where your home is.
But here,
I'll be your home.
I can't go home anyway, so
I'll stay here
and be happy in my new home.
What did you do?
Thank you for being there for me.
After all the trouble I put you through,
you still
won't give up.
Now you've won me over.
Let's start over together.
You love me?
So we're finally lovers.
Wait a minute, sir.
We're in a "chatting" phase.
"Chatting?"
You mean when you're chatting with me like this?
It's not just about the weather
or saying hello or those kind of things.
We need to chat about
what we have in common and what we like
and learn about each other.
It feels a bit complicated, but
it's quite special.
So am I your special one or not?
A special one can kiss, right?
Yes, sir.
So I can do the same thing you did.
Hey...
This side too.
Here too.
(Episode 12: This World is Harsh... But With "BBQ," We're Fine)
As a thank you to all guests
who visit Fang's Courtesan House again tonight,
I'm happy to give you free booze
on the house!
Fab, fab, fab!
Oh, Luang.
You're not in disguise tonight?
I don't think he's here to hang out.
He came in uniform.
I think he's here for an arrest.
The whole unit's here.
We've received an anonymous report
that you sell illegal liquor here.
I'm here to investigate.
Over there.
Get in.
These jars of liquor
were bought from my frequent brewery.
But last time, you used to serve
a strange-looking liquor, right?
Screw me!
Aunt, did I get us in trouble?
If that's the case, feel free to search, sir.
These jars are from Heng's Brewery.
But these look like fake copies, sir.
Take Fang in for questioning.
Mother?
- Mother. - Ming?
How did it go, Ming?
I tried to reach out to the officers
who promised to have your back, as you said.
No one is willing to help, Mother.
Jerks.
They only treated me well when they wanted my money.
Yet when I'm in trouble, they never help.
Please don't worry, Mother.
Boonta volunteered to help with Luang Thukkarat.
Rumors spread fast.
The whole Sampheng knows now
that Fang's serves counterfeit booze.
That's right.
Mother is in custody.
Guests are flocking to other brothels.
What should we do to fix this?
What can we do
except wait?
Wait?
If we want to win this cleanly,
we have to wait for the investigation to show that Mother is innocent.
Fang's is known as the best courtesan house in town.
Its reputation has been flawless.
Could it be that it's a setup?
Right? I'm thinking the same thing.
Someone definitely sets Mother Fang up to frame her.
Who do you suspect?
Magnate Thong, sir.
It's because of Magnate Thong
that I'm in here.
Magnate Thong?
He found out my father was going to win the bid for bird nest tax.
So he asked the Liquor Taxmaster
to tell the police my father brewed illegal booze.
My family's entire wealth was seized.
My parents and I got in jail.
This "case"
is exactly the same as Orn's family's "case."
It's also the same as when Bua was caught selling sugar.
There's no doubt. It's Magnate Thong, sir.
I visited Mother Fang. When I was leaving,
I saw Magnate Thong
approaching her in jail, sir.
Magnate Thong?
I never thought
the owner of a courtesan house like you would be in this predicament.
You came all the way to visit me.
I don't think you're here just to see me.
I'm just here to tell you something.
After you got arrested,
your brothel went quiet.
If you don't get acquitted soon,
if this drags on,
I'm afraid your brothel will have to close down soon.
You're telling me this
for what, sir?
I just want to help, seeing as we're well acquainted.
If you agree
to sell Boonta to me for a cheaper price,
I would be happy to be your witness.
How dare he use such a dirty trick?
I won't let this go.
I'll find evidence to acquit Fang myself.
Luang.
I'll help too.
You can trust me.
A lead, diva, and main character like me
have made a lot of money.
I'll make Fang's brothel popular again
without spending a single cent of Magnate Thong's money.
You said we had to wait?
Let the police work the case, but we have to deal with this crisis.
We have to seize our customers back.
If we can't sell booze,
we will sell something else.
Something else?
Something new and unusual.
- You mean... - Are we going to do a harem?
Not that!
I mean, we have to do something better.
This is "soft power."
This is our national dish.
Thank you, ma'am.
Take it back.
Will Mother be angry
if she finds out?
She won't be mad
if I make this
become ten times more.
Here.
What are you going to do with these things?
If Karaked can do it,
I, Boonta, can do it too.
Yeah. I hope so.
If you can't make that money back, Mother's going to kill you.
Okay!
Thank you.
Is it done?
This is a "buffet."
This is the menu we proudly present.
It's all-you-can-eat.
Everything on the menu for one price.
Wait.
What are you so proud of?
I haven't seen a single guest.
Are you sure this will sell?
You know only the Chinese like to eat pork.
Rest easy, girls.
Before the "grand opening,"
we need a "soft opening."
Please come in.
- There they are! - Oh? It's the Luangs.
- We've got guests. - Yes, sirs.
But one's got a wife. One's just left monkhood.
What a group of guests we have.
Music on.
Have you heard of this "buppay?"
- It's a "buffet." - "Buffet."
Grilled meat?
Are we going to grill meat
on this thing?
Yes, sir.
We have carefully selected the ingredients.
It's good and clean. It's all-you-can-eat.
So...
How...
How do we eat this?
You can grill the meat with nothing,
or with Mala, or with cheese and butter.
If you can't find cheese and butter, it's fine.
Our specially marinated pork will do.
But before you start,
you have to grease the grill.
So the meat won't stick.
Wait until the pork is cooked.
This is our special soup, sirs.
We have vegetables too.
Dip it in our special sauce.
That's Fang's specialty.
Come on.
Blow on it. It's still hot.
Say "ah," sir.
How is it, sirs? Oh yeah. Follow it with kimchi, sirs.
Or any other side dishes.
That's not raw pork, right?
- Follow it up, sir. - "Ah."
You barely have to do anything.
Just sit and eat. We've got you taken care of, sirs.
Boonta.
Your plan to draw guests in is working!
Doesn't it? For Thais, the only thing better than superstition
is "Moo
Kata."
Let me tell you. If I were richer,
I would serve it on a belt.
That's going to draw even more guests.
We can do that! You wrap it in a leather belt, right?
Not a leather belt.
It's a conveyor belt. It goes like "swoosh."
It will arrive at the table without anyone moving. You see?
Oh? Boonta.
I think I should get some more soup.
- Hey. - She's crazy.
Get rich. This is it.
That thing is popular?
The girls at Fang's won't last more than a few days.
Fang will have to accept my offer.
Are you sure, Master?
I see people keep going in and out of Fang's.
Of course I am!
I did it twice against Ard and Tan.
She's just a courtesan house owner.
She has no protection. How would she make it out?
What's the matter, Luang?
We've received a report
that Fang's brothel sells illegal booze.
The booze that was sent to her place
was from your brewery.
You're definitely mistaken.
I have my license.
I pay taxes and do everything by the book.
If that's the case,
let us search your brewery.
Thai people and booze are inseparable.
They were not drunkards back in the day.
So, what did they drink back in the day?
Water and tea, of course.
It wasn't until the Chinese came.
They built breweries.
They monopolized liquor and became taxmasters themselves.
That's how booze becomes widespread.
So, does that mean
monopoly started in this era?
Well, things are tempting.
Everyone knows that if you're the Liquor Taxmaster,
you can monopoly everything from building a brewery
to all the trade in your own areas.
They're set for life!
So small-time brewers have no chance then.
Who would dare?
Everyone knows that the Liquor Taxmaster
has the authority to punish illegal brewers.
If you're caught brewing illegally,
you're sent to the police.
It's a punishable crime, and they can fine you.
So that's why!
Magnate Thong used the crime of non-existent booze
- and took down Orn's family like it was nothing! - Really?
I knew it.
What did you say they brew?
Non-existent booze?
What brewery does it?
We searched all over. There is no liquor described in the report, sirs.
However, Ming and Mian
said they had received liquor from Heng's staff.
If it didn't come from here,
where could it have come from?
Could it be that the jars were swapped on the way?
Who was the staff who delivered to Fang's that night?
It was Sang, sir.
Where is he?
He's been gone for days.
All I know is he lives around Khlong Rong Mai, sir.
- Take him in. - Yes, sir.
Stop!
After him!
Yod, come on!
Stop!
Tell me the truth. Did you deliver fake booze to Fang's?
What brought you here so early, Luang?
This won't take long.
We just need you to come in to give your statement
about the report that Fang's serve illegal booze.
You'd better not be accusing me.
I have no involvement or conflict with anyone there.
Why would I do that?
If that's the case,
what about this gambler?
Are you involved with him in any way?
Who is this?
I don't know him.
He named your household in his statement.
What did my staff do?
Your staff
asked to buy Heng's liquor
from Sang that night.
What do you want?
Come.
Why are you standing in my way?
Move it.
I can't be late for Fang's delivery.
I don't want to miss the casino tonight.
Then sell this delivery to me
and go gambling.
I'll deliver this batch for you.
Is that him? There he is, Ming.
I'm here, Aunt.
Come on.
See?
This is all.
Ming.
Take it to the back.
Yes, Aunt.
You two, follow me.
(Fang's Brothel in Sampheng is serving illegal liquor)
(and opium in secret, please investigate soon.)
Your staff swapped out the liquor
and left an anonymous report
to the police himself.
Do you still deny
your involvement in this matter?
Luang, sir?
What about Mother?
Mother!
Mother.
- Mother! - Young Miss Kleeb.
Kleeb, sweetie.
I miss you so much, Mother.
I miss you more than anything, sweetie.
Thank you so much for helping me, sir.
We're just doing our job.
I owe you anyway, sir.
If you're biased against me as other officers,
I would have never been acquitted.
Thank all of you too, for taking care of my place.
Yes, Mother.
I'm just trying to repay you for helping me.
When I was in jail,
I genuinely felt jail was truly hell for us.
Now, do you realize
why Mother agreed to buy you off of them?
Look, you were either going to jail or getting sold to another brothel.
There is no happier place for us, Boonta.
Agreed.
But I think
Mother bought you for profit.
Would someone like Mother let a chance to make money slip?
Are you accusing me of being greedy?
You're getting it.
What were you doing with these grills?
Boonta borrowed your money and started a BBQ business, Mother.
Boonta! You turned my brothel into a grill place?
But I made your money back, Mother, with profit too!
Here. Take a look, Mother.
What exactly have you done?
How did you make so much?
You need this too, Mother.
- Thanks, Aunt. - It's our soup.
Let's eat. Get this piece.
Is mine done?
It sure looks strange but tempting.
So this is what Chang and Chim praised so much.
It doesn't just look good, sir.
It tastes so good your mouth lights up. It's the best in town.
If you get a taste, you're going to want more.
For you, Mother. Have this piece. It's done.
Eat it with kimchi.
Dip it in this, Mother.
Young Miss, this is for you.
Wow.
How is it, Mother?
It's... not bad.
Keeping your cool, huh?
Oh!
It's so good my mouth lights up!
It surely is the best in town!
Is that right?
Mother.
We have two Luangs from the police force who "guarantee" it's good.
- I think it's time for the second branch. - Yeah.
Don't take it too far, Boonta.
Have you asked us at all?
We're working hard enough to serve the guests.
Do I still have to carry these heavy grills around?
Pudsorn can speak for herself,
but I'll do anything if it makes money.
- Me too. - Me too.
Me too. I have a family to provide for.
That's almost unanimous.
Perhaps it's time to hang up your boobs and work these grills, Pudsorn.
Aunt!
That's great.
Stop smiling and eat something.
If you don't stop smiling,
Chaai will be too distracted
to eat anything.
I'm happy, sir,
that you and Chaai saved our Mother.
Otherwise, Fang's Brothel would never have been this lively.
Agreed. By now, the suspect is probably getting what he deserves, right?
He will
because he's not just facing your case
but other cases as well.
With evidence this solid,
do you still deny it, Magnate?
So it is now confirmed that
Magnate Thong and his slave
set up Fang and accused her
of serving illegal liquor, which is false.
You also forged a false report to Tralakarn.
With this false accusation,
you're punishable by up to 50 flogging with a leather whip
and up to four times fine.
Write a report to the jury
and confirm their punishment.
I did not intend to cause chaos.
I just wanted to teach the brothel owner a lesson.
That is all, Your Honor.
Moreover, this is my first offense.
Please have mercy.
First offense, you say?
This is not the only case you're facing.
What do you mean?
Master...
Master.
Watch your steps, ma'am.
Thank you so much for helping me out.
I won't bring trouble to you and our family again.
Then stop trying to take Boonta in as a wife.
What does Boonta have to do with this?
You think I'm so stupid I couldn't see?
That you're doing all you're doing
because you want her!
You ended up in the jail she went to.
Isn't that what you wanted?
I know I made a mistake.
Just don't exaggerate, please.
If you don't care about your honor,
please care about your child's,
and my honor when I went to the jail pregnant!
The people are going to talk
about how a Magnate became so helpless
- that he needed his wife to protect him! - Gaysorn!
Muean?
I've helped you for the last time.
If you cross the line for Boonta again,
I'll let you deal with the consequences of your own actions.
It's all because of you, Chaai.
I'll make your life a living hell!
You made me fight Captain Jam.
Yet you dare ask me to hire you?
It was all my fault.
I did it because I was greedy.
I promise I'll never do it again.
What about how Captain Sut fired you
for smuggling opium in his ship?
You expect me to hire you to bring me troubles?
Magnate!
I'm done with that.
I swear I'd never do it again.
Navigating is not the only thing I can do.
I'm capable
of news hunting too.
Is that so?
If your news proves interesting,
I'll hire you.
Someone give me more booze!
Make it quick.
Why are you drinking so much today?
I have money!
I'm going to drink all the booze in this place.
I'll also visit Fang's.
How did you get so much money?
By working, of course.
A drunkard like you?
You don't have the strength to work.
My job
does not require strength
like you manual laborers.
All I do is trade secrets for money.
What secret?
Are you sure you weren't so drunk you heard things?
I wasn't drunk.
I heard Sarang saying that with my own ears.
Didn't they say Captain Henry
came to do business in trade?
Why would he bring a battleship?
But that Sarang guy
used to work on the ship Guardian.
His news is solid.
The Europeans invaded Inn-wa before.
They can take their fleet
to invade us too.
What are you talking about?
The people have been saying the Europeans are invading us with battleships.
Those captains used their businesses as a front.
They were actually here for intel?
Yes, sir.
The whole market has heard this rumor.
The people are panicking.
Could it be
that what we heard is true?
At this time, the Europeans are close to conquering Inn-wa's Amarapura.
If they do beat Inn-wa,
the European threat is something we should watch out for.
Perhaps
this is just one of Sarang's lies.
Luang, sir.
What are we going to do?
What's wrong?
Can't I get a little touch?
Come here.
- What are you doing? - Let go!
I have money!
Can't I hang out at the best Courtesan House?
- Take him out. - Wait.
Maybe you need a special service.
- I'll get you a girl. - No!
I'm going to sleep with the prettiest courtesan in this place.
I want to sleep with Boonta.
If you're here to pick a fight, go back to where you came from, Sarang.
- You... - Wait, sir.
Boonta doesn't accept guests.
Then Pudsorn.
Pudsorn is already taken.
But...
Lamjeak, sir.
- Lamjeak. - Yes, Mother?
Yes, sir.
Come on. I'll take care of you, sir.
Let's go.
Watch your steps. I'll show you to your table.
Boonta. Walk slowly, sir. Let's go.
- What are you looking at? - Sorry, sir.
Keep an eye on him. If anything happens, let me know.
Yes, Mother.
Why did you hire Sarang and pay him a lot
to spread the rumor, Master?
Let's give Chaai some work to do.
Drink it! Drink!
I'll teach you a lesson today.
Mother saw you teaching Kleeb to read.
I failed my Thai exam but I know the letters to the T!
What did you write? It looks strange.
Help!
Whoa!
Should we take her to a doctor?
- No. - Madam Gaysorn is giving birth!
The baby's here.