You got extra money from last night's guest?
A bland-looking woman like you
will never get to be his regular.
Then let's find out once and for all.
I'm going to make an "event" where you compete for guests.
Please come to Fang's brothel, sirs.
If you're interested in what we're doing,
please come and find out, sirs.
As a peacekeeper in this town,
I have concluded
that this event shall not be ignored.
Are you drinking without a companion?
If you will take care of me, I'll consider the offer.
- This is for you. - Boonta is seducing him! I'm going to slap her!
Your cover will be blown!
If you come and flirt with me,
I'll pay you more than this.
What if Gaysorn finds out?
Just don't tell Gaysorn then!
If she finds out,
I'll know it's you, Come!
It's here, sir.
Just now,
Luang Thukkarat
paid you how much?
He paid me
one chang, sir.
You said you would pay more than he did, right?
If you could pay me two or three,
that would show him your superiority, sir.
Boonta.
You sure are playful.
I'm not playing, sir.
If it's too much, then that's fine.
If you don't want to pay me that much,
it's really fine.
It's better to keep your money for your family.
I'm the breadwinner.
Gaysorn wouldn't dare to say a word!
Your Gaysorn is really kind.
She's such a good match for a wealthy man like you, Magnate Thong.
Let's just stop
talking about everyone else. Let's talk about us.
Let's start with
a drink,
just like you did with Luang Thukkarat. Would that suit you?
Are you interested in me or Luang Thukkarat, sir?
You keep mentioning his name.
Come on.
Do this.
Will you drink with me now?
I'm sorry.
- What did you do? No, thank you, sir. - I'll wipe you.
- I'll wipe you. - No, thanks!
-Hey! No! - Let me wipe.
Sorry.
I just tripped on something.
Luang? Are you bullying me on purpose?
The bully here is you.
You've been trying to one-up me since you showed up.
I'm not so upset as to take revenge.
I just don't like
how you're being inappropriate with Boonta.
You paid to drink with her. That's all you're supposed to do.
Don't make a situation and try to take advantage of her.
Police officers are conspiring to accuse me?
Do you have evidence to back your accusation?
You know what you're doing.
If you won't admit it,
you can file a complaint with the Police Force.
We're willing to go to court to prove it.
If you're afraid Gaysorn would find out,
or if you're afraid for your reputation,
I think you should go home, sir.
- Come, go home! - Wait, sir!
Where's my money?
You're still asking for it?
Leave!
Magnate, sir!
Luang.
Thank you so much for your help.
Both with the money and that Magnate.
From now on, you should call me
Chaai.
Why, sir?
So I won't get confused
if you call me
or someone else.
Of course, sir.
It's nice and short.
- Chaai, why are you... - Dokgaew?
Young Miss?
- What happened? A drunkard throwing a tantrum? - Where's my Young Miss?
It's nothing, Fang.
It's just a drunk man. I got him under control.
- Young Miss, where are you? - Don't worry, Fang.
- I'll take care of this. - Young Miss?
You're a guest of my place too.
I can't possibly bother you now.
Let Ming handle him, sir.
It's alright, Fang.
I'm willing to. I'll take care of this. I'm happy to.
Come on!
I told you not to drink too much, didn't I?
(Episode 8: The Ace Courtesan... The Top Girl at Fang's)
How much?
You're winning, Chor.
Am I
not too late to join the fun?
I was thinking this event wouldn't be complete without you.
It looks like Pudsorn is winning today after all.
I get to sleep with her, right?
I have never bedded with her before.
Maybe today is your day.
You little woman.
Yes, sir. You pay Pudsorn the most money, making her the winner.
Ming.
Take Captain upstairs to wait.
Yes, Mother.
Upstairs please, sir.
Mother.
I don't want to service him. Last time, he beat up Nual half to death.
They said he also beat Oeb at Hob's brothel and gave her bruises all over.
She had to take several days off, Mother!
It's your competition.
You won. How can you withdraw?
Just bear with it for a bit. When he's done, he pays you anyway.
I don't want his money, Mother,
if it means I have to risk my life.
Pudsorn.
Just because you're the draw of my place
doesn't mean you can do whatever you want.
It's my order. You have to do it.
Or you can
kill the lights and send someone else in.
It's dark. He won't be able to tell you apart.
Who do I send in, Mother?
Come on.
What's wrong with your master?
Why is she doing such a reckless thing?
If she gets caught,
how would she face anyone ever again?
How can you go home like this anyway?
I know another of your secrets,
yet I have to help you keep it.
I'd rather not know.
Dokgaew.
It's really late.
Please go to bed, ma'am.
Magnate is probably busy with work.
Dear.
Were you drinking?
Where did you drink? Who did you go with?
What now?
What's with all the questions?
I'm so tired.
Magnate was drinking at Fang's, ma'am.
Boonta.
Did he sleep with her?
No, ma'am.
It's a real shame you lost.
I wanted to see Pudsorn taken down from her pedestal!
It's fine, Aunt.
I felt like I won just being able to keep up.
I felt like I'd overcome myself.
Now I know I'm good and I'm worthy.
Thank you so much, Boonta.
Because of you, I'm way more confident in myself.
It's not because of me.
If you had refused to fight, I couldn't have done anything.
It's because you were willing to fight and change yourself for the better.
You're really amazing.
I'm sorry for underestimating you.
Last night, you proved to me that
you can be a great rival for me.
It's true I'm still number one now,
but I can't underestimate you anymore.
I never wanted to compete against you, Pudsorn.
I just try to do my job the best I can.
I'm glad that's your attitude.
We can stay friends then.
I don't want to consider you an enemy.
Calm down, girl.
Does the word "friend" to you mean the same thing to us?
Friends must be genuine, and support each other.
Don't be jealous. Don't backstab. And most importantly,
we're not your servant.
I know!
I'll try not to be the same as I've been.
I know you're not really a bad person.
You just like to act like you're above everyone else.
You're obsessed with being number one because you want attention.
It's because it wasn't easy for me to come this far.
Servicing guests with my body isn't the only thing I do.
I take care of them
both physically and mentally.
I sing and dance. I pour their drinks. I satisfy them.
I keep them company.
Some guests don't even want to sleep with me.
They just want a shoulder to cry on.
Do you think you can
just go ahead and do these things?
I had to train
and endure.
So was I wrong
for wanting to be number one?
You're not wrong.
I see everything you do, Pudsorn,
so I've never doubted why you're number one.
You're not a stupid beauty like people say.
You're just selfish and you lack sympathy.
But you can be both a capable and a good person.
You're better now.
Keep up the good work.
Thanks.
Wait.
Hey. Let me see.
Why haven't you got any bruises at all?
You spent last night with Captain Jam, didn't you?
Or you didn't enter the room?
So who took your place?
Lamjeak!
That Captain hurt you this badly?
Lamjeak, please help me.
I'm really scared of that Captain.
If you take my place, I'll pay you more.
Please help me. I beg you.
I'll tell Aunt Mian to cook some rice porridge. Then I'll feed you.
I'll get some Bengal roots in the banana bush to heal your bruises.
Lie here and wait for me.
I'll get a Chinese Doctor.
No!
I'm not hurt that much.
I'll be fine after a few days of rice porridge.
Just see a doctor.
I'll pay.
Pudsorn!
- Boonta! - Boonta!
Boonta, where are you going?
Mother.
Are you so happy?
What are you talking about?
You don't have to do anything.
You can sit pretty and count the money we make!
Hey!
You say we're like your family.
You claim to be our mother. You say we're your children.
What kind of mother makes a living out of her child's blood and suffering?
- You dare call me out? - Dare or not, I am calling you out.
You keep getting rich. You're the only one living the easy life.
But us, your fake children? We lie down in pain half to death.
Tell me, Mother.
Don't you feel embarrassed or ashamed of these words?
- You! - Slap me, Mother.
After you slap me, check on one of your children.
Lamjeak almost died at the hands and feet of that sick Captain.
You know why?
Because you never say no to a guest.
You're stingy.
You're hungry for money.
You don't even think of protecting your own people.
Can you sit up?
- It's not hot anymore. - Easy.
That's enough for me, Aunt.
Thank you.
She got hurt so badly that she could only drink porridge water.
Is Captain Jam even a human?
If all you can do is drink porridge water,
how can you have any strength?
Want some more, Lamjeak?
Thanks, Aunt but no.
If she can't eat, just stop.
I'll dress your wounds.
Come on.
Get up slowly.
Come here.
Come on, Lamjeak.
So this is what they call "yellow chin."
A Chinese doctor is here.
This way, please.
You'll be fine in no time.
Chor, I'll be back.
Where are you going this time, Boonta?
Don't worry. I'll be back soon.
This is medicine for your internal injuries.
Boil and drink this medicine three times.
You'll feel better soon.
Thank you.
No, just lie down.
You can take off work until you recover.
Mother.
A courtesan like us
can't choose the guest.
But you're in charge of this place.
You can choose, can't you?
You can choose what to do.
Why do you like to come to this place?
I didn't really want to come, sir,
unless something happened.
So what happened?
My friend was assaulted.
I'm here to report a crime.
I understand you're furious for your friend,
but no courtesan has ever reported such a crime.
I'm here, sir. I'm the first.
I sympathize with you and your friend,
but I'll be truthful with you.
While being a courtesan is not illegal,
you're under no protection by the law.
It's a job you do willingly.
You accept violation for money.
Hey, Luang.
Are you saying that we
have to accept the risks just because we do prostitution?
- Please calm down. - Luang, sir.
Is it because we're courtesans?
Is that why we have to tolerate an exploitative employer?
And a piece of trash guest's abuse?
We can't complain anywhere.
We have no safety in our lives.
We have no place in the world. We don't exist.
We don't deserve to be protected by the law.
We don't have the same rights as those of other occupations. Is that right?
We work to make a living too.
We provide for our families just like everyone does.
How can I answer your questions?
I'm not the one who wrote the law.
I was speaking as a police officer,
but as a man,
I understand and agree with you.
I want your friends
to have equal rights like everyone.
So I hope
one day, courtesans as an occupation
will be genuinely accepted, sir.
Captain Jam.
Oh, Fang.
What's so important
that brought you all the way here?
I'm here for payback.
For what?
For hurting my child half to death and making her take days off!
- You dare slap me! - Yeah!
In the past, I've always kept one eye closed.
But this time it's too much.
If you still keep doing this,
don't step foot at my place again.
You're not welcome!
"Wench!"
Did you report this to the police?
No matter what era,
the police never help the people.
The law doesn't protect us.
And that Captain is a foreigner!
It's hard to get any kind of justice at all!
I came to terms with that long ago.
We were never accepted.
Whether it's the police,
the people, or the Luangs, they never see our pride.
All they do is look down on us.
Nobody would take our side.
So we take our side.
- Help her up. - Hey.
- Everyone! - What?
I think we should form a Courtesan Union.
- What's that? - It's about this, Aunt.
We'll receive fair pay.
We'll receive health insurance.
And more importantly, we can take days off like in "Gangubai!"
What's that?
Aunt, we work so hard.
We deserve good fringe benefits.
My voice alone won't be loud enough. We have to join forces.
Mother will believe us.
So are you asking us to go against Mother?
It's not like that. We're just calling out what's unfair.
Don't let anyone take advantage of you.
And don't let anyone hurt you.
Even if we sleep with men
out of necessity or pressure,
we have our pride. We're humans just like everyone.
Boonta.
Mother won't give in.
Aunt! If she truly loves us, she would understand and do what she can.
That's easy for you to say.
What are you girls doing together?
You startled me.
How are you, Lamjeak?
I'm feeling better, Mother.
Spend this money on some medicine.
Come back to work when you recover.
That Captain won't step foot here again.
Yes, Mother.
Wait, Mother.
- Mother! -Hmm?
So did you deal with that Captain Jam?
You think I'm so heartless
that I don't care about my children?
After all,
I'm a woman like you all.
I know how you girls feel.
But as the boss of this place,
it's hard for me to openly protect you.
You have to understand that too.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Mother,
for saying bad things to you.
I...
I was mad.
From now on, I'll
think more before I speak.
So what you said back there...
Did you hear all that?
So can you do that for us?
I'll sleep on it.
Thank you.
Good fringe benefits?
Boonta!
- I don't understand a word but it seems to be good. - It's good.
We're getting fringe benefits, insurance,
What's that "Bai" something?
Oh! We'll be like "Gangubai."
Dang!
Dang, is that you?
It's me, Young Miss.
How did I get back home?
Luang Vasuthep took you home.
When we arrived at the gate, I told the servants to carry you up here.
My mother didn't find out, right?
I dealt with that and silenced everyone, Young Miss.
If Madam Pikul finds out you got drunk,
I'll personally take care of them all!
Did you change my clothes?
Thank you for your help.
Please keep this a secret.
Nobody must know.
What kind of woman is she? All she does is make trouble.
Young Miss.
Luang Vasuthep won't tell anyone of this.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have helped you this much.
Don't talk yourself out of this! I won't believe a word you say again!
Get the hell out of here. Go!
I'm going, Young Miss.
Lamjeak!
Choi?
What are you doing here?
I'm here for you.
Our mother is dying.
Lamjeak.
Mother?
Are you worried your family would see your bruises?
Choi was crying so much she didn't notice. I sent her back.
Let me put on your make-up. Here.
What is this?
Powder mixed with curcuma.
With a little bit of water.
This should work as a foundation.
Your powder is too white.
It's going to make your face look pale.
And it can't cover your bruises.
Come on.
Let's get the bruise here.
This shouldn't hurt, right?
It's working great.
It's gone!
- Really? - Yeah. Look.
One on your neck.
- Does it hurt? - No.
Why am I so good at this?
- It works? - Yeah.
Yeah. Let's get this too.
Oh!
Lamjeak, where is your home?
- Ban Dokmai. - Ban Dokmai?
I still don't know where it is.
I need to hire a boat.
- How would you know... - Where are you going?
Lamjeak is visiting her mother.
We're here to hire a boat.
Are you going with her?
Yes, sir. I'm going with her.
Then let me give you a ride in my boat.
Is that okay, sir?
You shouldn't have to.
It's just a short trip. It won't affect my work.
Let's ride with Chaai. It's for the best.
It's better than hiring a boat and swimming.
Have you lost your mind?
How could you call him by name?
Why not?
Chaai told me to do so.
They don't do that here?
Apart from his family,
nobody would dare.
Yeah.
- So... - I gave you permission.
I'm not revoking it.
We're almost there.
You said your family sold flowers. Shouldn't we go to Pak Khlong Talad?
I don't see a flower here.
What exactly did you mean?
I said my home is Ban Dokmai.
That doesn't mean we sell flowers. My family makes fireworks.
So your "Dokmai" means fireworks?
- Yeah. - So...
You must have a lot of fireworks at home, right?
We do. My father was the best "Fai Phaniang" maker.
But I prefer pretty stuff, like "Ped," "Pla Duk," and "Pla Chon."
Those are fish, aren't they?
So you don't know what those are?
Thank you.
Come on. Let's go.
Sorry, sir. I was caught up in the conversation.
Thank you so much for the ride.
We'll be on our way.
Have a safe trip back, sir.
Lamjeak!
Lamjeak! Help!
Mother is getting worse!
Mother? Let's go! Quick!
She has been throwing up and had watery diarrhea since last night.
Have you called a doctor?
I don't have money left. I spent everything on Chinese potion.
But it didn't help.
Here.
I have money. Go get a doctor. I'll watch her.
- Yes. - Go!
You should stay with your mother and sister.
Yod and I will go get you a doctor.
- Let's go, Yod. - Yes, sir.
Mother.
Would she be okay? Would she die?
Your mother will be fine.
Luang is going to get a doctor.
Choi, get the remaining potion.
I'll wipe her and feed her potion while we wait.
- Okay. - Go.
Lamjeak, let me help. I know how
to do first aid. Come on.
I used to care for patients.
- "Patient..." - Sick people.
I used to care for sick people.
- Let's wipe her. - Please help my mother.
Mother.
We'll give you a wipe.
It's not a deadly diarrhea as you feared.
It's just food poisoning.
If you take my medicine continuously, she will recover.
Here, sir.
Is this not enough for the medicine, sir?
It's not that.
My Luang already paid for the doctor's fee
and your mother's medicine.
Yod.
Escort the doctor to his home.
Yes, sir.
Thank you so much for your help.
I didn't do anything. Luang did.
He helped you non-stop.
If it weren't for you, would I be this lucky?
You are a generous man, sir.
You are a kind woman too.
I'm glad you were there for me.
Yeah.
My life has been bad.
My father died in a firework explosion.
My mother is never in good health.
She and my sister are the only people in my life.
You have to provide for your family.
Is that why you have to work at Fang's?
Boonta.
A poor person like me doesn't have many choices.
I only hope that
my loved ones can live in peace.
Do you know? When Ming brought Choi in to see me,
I got so deeply scared.
I was scared she was sold into the place.
I'd rather work hard alone
than let my sister join me.
Lamjeak.
Your sister will never do this work.
I'll be there for you.
If you need my help, let me know.
But
I don't have much money.
If you're in trouble,
I'm willing to give you all I have though.
Thank you, Boonta.
Don't cry.
What's wrong?
You seem quiet.
Are you ill?
Lamjeak's story reminded me of myself, sir.
You're thinking of your family?
Some things are
not worth thinking of.
Lamjeak's family and mine
are similarly suffering.
I have been working hard since I was young
because I wanted my loved ones who love me
to have a good life.
Food delivery, sir.
- Mr. Eff? - That's me.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
Goodbye.
Hello, Grandma?
(Jeed, have you had lunch?)
I'm working. What about you?
Don't forget your lunch.
(Take care of yourself, sweetie.)
Yeah. Love you.
- This is for Yao, and this is for Bank. - Thanks.
- What would you like? - One black coffee.
Want some sugar?
You shouldn't be working in concession with that face of yours.
Would you like to be an actress?
What are you talking about?
Boom, do I have anything on my schedule tomorrow?
What's the matter?
Tomorrow is my grandma's death anniversary. I want to visit a temple.
Okay. I'll take care of that.
(Mom)
Mom?
Give it to me. Let me talk.
Hello, ma'am?
She's working.
Oh, ma'am?
Are you still trying?
When she was working hard,
she had no one at all.
The only one who struggled for her was her grandma.
Now that she's a star,
you and her father keep trying to reach her.
At least Lamjeak still has someone.
I have no one now.
The one who I wanted to have
is already gone.
That's why I work hard just to spend on myself.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what, sir?
I'm sorry I made your family turn out this way.
I used to wonder what I did wrong.
Someone reported
that you sold sugar to the Europeans without permission.
Search the place!
Yes, sir.
Boonta.
I brought you medicine.
I'm trying to find a way to help.
Thank you, sir.
Please be patient for a bit longer, Bua.
Yes, sir.
I know you were just doing your job,
but I don't want to see you ever again.
I was too honest.
I was too obsessed with duty.
Had I been more flexible,
more lenient,
and less egoistic,
you probably wouldn't have ended up this way.
But from what I've heard,
Boonta herself has some ego too.
And...
It turned out this way because you and Boonta
were in love, right?
How could you just say the word "love"
without feeling anything?
I wasn't talking about myself, sir.
It was about you
and the old Boonta.
I'm New Boonta.
What does that mean?
I am the new Boonta who has no memory of the past.
Whatever happened, just let it go.
Let's "move on," sir.
"Moop on?"
"Move on" means
to move forward
and not dwell on the past, sir.
What about us?
Just "set zero," sir.
Start over.
We can
stay friends for now.
Why is Boonta taking so long?
She said she would see Lamjeak first. I don't know what's going on.
Sir.
Luang, sir!
I have something to show you.
Come on.
- We'll be back. - Yes, sir.
- Where are you taking me? - This way, quick.
Do you like it, sir?
Did you ask Lamjeak to do this?
Yes, sir.
I wanted to see it.
I thought if you saw it,
you would feel better.
Do you care about my feelings?
Yes, sir.
Friends can care about each other.
I think I'm starting to feel bad again.
Then let's see the next one.
(I'm sorry I took her place, )
(and I can't accept your feelings now, )
(when you've always been there for me since I woke up in this era.)
It's just a temporary joy.
Suffering doesn't last either.
It will pass, sir.
No matter what it is,
you and I will get through it.
Please do something, Mother.
Otherwise, I'm going to lose Chaai to Boonta.
Hurry up. I need to make merit!
Push them off.
The police have received a report
that opium was smuggled onto Chim's ship, sir.
From now on, Kleeb will be living here.
So Mother thinks I don't have enough work to do?
Is that why she's making me babysit?
I told you I'm New Boonta.
I'm not the same old Boonta you know.
I like the new Boonta too.
Luang may love you
but do you think his mother would approve?
Someone save my daughter!