(REC)
Is This Working?
Is It?
Oh, right. it's working.
Hey, Joon. It's ready. come here, quick.
Come here, quick. come on.
I'm not ready yet.
What to prepare?
Stop acting like noble
Look, look.
Are we really need to do this?
Why?
Now, it makes me nervous
Why are you always like this,
right before we start something
Just acting casually.
Look, It looks good.
Isn't this going to be look weird?
Come, come here.
Look at this, It looks good.
No, It looks weird.
I spent so much time to adjusting this.
Alright, now it looks fit.
What's up?
It's enough, stop it.
Come on ~
Stop it.
Joon, come one
Shit, splash on camera.
You always like this.
Please, only this time.
Let's put this down.
Let's soap you
Stop moving.
Alright, turn around.
Come here.
Feel my warm hands.
Shit, it's hot.
Again, what ~?!
Okay, turn around, turn around.
You.
Washing hair.
Stop it.
Wow, look at those tight bum.
Yes. That's nice.
Good, look at that hair.
You are 'wolverine'!
Oh My God!
You're so wild!
Look, It's 'Brad pitt'!
Hey', I'm your fan.
Can you shake hands for me?
I'm without make-up on,
Can you shot this later?
Since when you put on make up?
When I first saw you I was confused
whether you're gay or not
Look, now you've got so much hair.
Look at those wrinkles on forehead.
Digital technology is good, don't you think?
I hate what you saying.
You think I don't know how to
fancy up myself?
My friends get expensive cosmetics
from their boyfriend.
Have you ever got me, anything like that?
Hey, miss. Our face is on our
own responsibility.
Stop pinching me.
What else I didn't do for you?
Well, do you want me to spill everything?
It's just I didn't have chances,
It will takes days to tell all.
How come you so shameless?
Shameless?
You should think be more conscience
Conscience?
Yes, In my point of view.
I'm being conscience.
Hey, 'Brad pitt'.
Look at those love handle
Hey, hey!
Let me go.
Are you playing hard to get?
Just, stop it. Makes me feel ill.
Well, Joon-Seok got pissed off.
Such a girl.
If it is, shoosh!
My sweet bunny, Are you angry?
What's wrong, 'Brad'.
You should acting!
I asked you not to call me that.
You always say things I don't like.
You always telling me
I do say things you don't like.
Well, today is special day.
Well, set now.
Please, please!
Good, good.
Come here, sit down.
It's our 5th anniversary cake!
Hold on.
It's ready.
It's special day, let's put this on.
Just this time, okie dokie. good.
You always like hot and cold, make me sick.
But you enjoy it, don't you?
You look pretty, sister.
Am I look okay?
Yeah.
Let's sing.
Song is.
Congratulation! let's celebration,
You know this one right?
Let's go.
Congratulation! Let's celebration!
Let's celebrate our 5th anniversary!
Ready, one two three.
Shit!
Cut it out!
Stop wipe out, you should eat them.
You're so cruel.
You're.
Just stop it.
I know you like this, am I right?
You're so
Come here,
here.
I'm going insane.
Look at those hair,
navel...
Hey, Young-joon!
Are we really have to this?
Wow, you're changing your decision again.
No, It's not like that.
It feels like we're pervert.
What, pervert?
Yeah.
A lot of people shooting this for their own.
As you saying we're pervert country!
Well, that's what people saying
when they are distribute on internet.
You should know that already?
Why, You don't wanna do it?
No, It's not that.
You don't want to do it?
Yes...
Really?
If that's what you want.
Let stop here!
I'll just record myself.
Pervert.
Song Young-jun is pervert.
I'm pervert.
Are you really okay with this?
There are no right or wrong here,
We're just like each other
and that's why we're doing this.
Are you pissed?
Am I you?
Gosh, You not gonna talk to me again?
Well?
Young-joon?
Come on...
Hey...
Can you promise me?
What promise?
This is first and the last time we do this.
I'm not gonna do this again.
We're not pervert who recording this, always
Today is special. it's special event
Okay! okay?
Hey lady, your butt, sexy, sexy!
Come here, let check out those butt.
See. You can do this.
Wow, you're so handsome, My 'Brad pitt'!
Are you happy?
Yeah.
Come here.
You should take my order.
Why aren't you moving?
- No, no.
- Wait, wait.
Hold on.
Greasy.
Quick.
I'm Done.
Done?
You're so pretty.
Pretty? is it working?
Sister, You look pretty.
All set,
ready action!
Wait,
It's a microphone!
This?
Well, then
Mr. Seo Jun-Seok, introduce yourself please?
Introducing myself? What the hell?
Just tell me your name and age.
Do like when you're on group blind date.
Group blind date?
Then I'll just tell my Chatting ID.
What? 'VEGEMIL-B'?
Yeah, You remembering?
How could I forget that corny name?
Are you touched?
No, It's just fascinating.
I was once well known hottie.
After I met someone, I'm fermented.
I'm old news.
Fermented? You think you're 'KIMCHI'?
Don't you know how country boy
you were back then?
You were so 'VEGEMIL-B'.
What's wrong with 'VEGEMIL-B'?
Ours were. 'SOLEMIO'?
That is cheesy!
Cheesy? It means a 'my sun',
what's wrong with this?
It's better then yours.
What's wrong with 'VEGEMIL-B',
Don't you know they are delicious!
They are delicious?
Come on! We're not gonna
talk about old story until sunrise.
Let's be more serious. From self introduce.
Ready, action!
Self introduce, hmm.
My name is Seo jun-seok.
26 years old. Sexual position is secret.
My ideal man is older handsome boy.
Finish. done?
Okay!
Jun-Seok.
Yes?
What day is today?
Today?
Today is Friday.
Is that all?
Today is the 5th year anniversary
of the day I met someone I love.
Isn't my voice all girly?
Yeah,
so girly. No, i'm kidding. Just kidding.
What are you shooting now?
Recording that we're doing,
is like 5th year anniversary album?
But, it's feel like i'm shooting a porn.
Porn... Don't be up-tight.
Well, just call it 'YA-DONG'.
'YA-DONG'?
Yeah, That's more relevant.
5years.... That's long time.
How was it?
I'll be honest.
Go on!
My boyfriend name is Song young-jun,
30 years old.
He's such a kid at that age.
So one-sided mind. totally one-sided.
You always want to your own way.
Not a human being. Just animal.
That means you been going out
with animal all these years.
Yeah. it's animal.
So.
But because of me,
he became a human being
I'm so pleased.
Then, next time when you asked
to be with Mr. Song again?
Never again.
How should I?
He always want to his own way.
Picky choice of meal,
go to movies only he wants.
And have sex when he wants.
Whatever he only wants.
If someone asks me to do it again
I won't do it. i'll stop them.
You're so mad at me.
It pouring out so naturally.
Why not? I'm telling the truth.
Are you feeling guilty?
Yes, It hurts.
Sharp sword ran through my heart.
It hurts.
I feel like i'm a celebrity.
Right this before,
You were saying you won't do it.
I'm getting used to it now.
What we gonna do?
What?
You probably get pissed after you saw this.
Why?
Are you stooting weird way?
Show this!
What?
Look at this, roots will never change, right?
What is this!
This is trues.
You look pretty.
You look best, after you took a shower.
Just give it to me.
No! no!
When you hated me most?
When...?
Well...
When you telling me that...
About what?
Things you always telling me.
"We've got no future."
"We must get married with woman."
"Korea gay community is not change."
That sort of things, I hated those stories.
It's true.
I know.
But... did u ever thought about me?
Sorry, just wait!
I feel wonderful.
What the... Are you recording me?
Yes.
Is there anything to drink?
There it is.
Surprise!
'VEGEMIL-B'!
I will put strow on.
Here we go.
Thank you.
It's so delicious!
Is that good?
I love!
You acting like old people.
Now, I'm going to ask you.
What?
From now on, I'm going to ask you.
What were you doing at shower?
Anyway, Am I look okay?
It's working fine, You look handsome.
Well, yeah.
If you're wondering,
rewind recorded part previously.
There is a fantastic film ready for you!
Attractive actor in it?
Of course!
Actor quite not fit the line, kind chubby.
I don't see any fat.
His face in not so attractive either.
But, my manhood is huge!
Isn't that matters?
Then, show me. Would you?
One time!
It's no good luck.
Show me, please!
Stop acting noble.
What kind of person is
young-joon's boyfriend?
My boyfriend?
Yes.
I have one boyfriend.
He is...
Young and spoiled.
Simply a baby.
Is that all?
I'm so disappointed.
My darling is just sweet and tender.
And he is mature even though he's young.
What happen, you're commending?
Today is special day.
Special day.
What do you like about me?
About what...?
Yes.
I just can't pick one thing,
but good person?
Feeling good, nice feeling.
Nice feeling.
With you, I feel comfortable
without any thinking.
This sort of things led to us until now.
Usually, romance of gay guys in Korea
are 1 year equals 10 years.
5 years equal 50 years
that means we're married couple.
Am I right?
Married.
Married, then who is husband
and who is wife?
I'm a top, that means i'm a husband.
What is that, you're very conservative.
Oh. no.
For that matter, i'll be doing a top today.
You think? If you think you can try, go ahead.
You're born bottom.
Come here. come.
Let me go.
Put the camera down.
Come here, bottom boy.
Bottoming for me.
Sorry, I was wrong.
You always pounding me like this,
did you know?
I don't know, didn't know
I'll let you know.
How much do you like me?
How much?
This big.
What? really?
All except for this big. would you believe?
Should I believe or what?
Well, How much do you like me?
As much as we made love.
As much as we made love?
Then we should do it everyday.
Honestly, What am i for you?
To me?
You were being corny.
But I like corny.
Not being covered up, That's being honest.
Is there anything would you like to do?
Now?
We have finish 'YA-DONG' first.
Later...
Later?
That beach, I'd like to go there again.
Where you asking me to break up
with big fuss.
Yeah, there.
Even though, I loved it there.
Go again, I'm promise.
When we go if you ask me to break up again.
I'll do it.
That was, when I was young.
Now I'm grown up.
I don't believe you. It's not convincing.
Now, let's get into the main course?
Main course?
Look up, I can't see your face.
Young-joon, in the future....
You're not going to upload this on 'P2P'?
I'll upload this later as...
'VEGEMIL-B and SOLEMIO's 5th year
anniversary sex tape' on internet.
If that happens, you're dead meat.
You can't trust me?
You didn't act like I can trust you.
I was a bad person to you.
Well, now you know.
Are we going to break up someday, right?
Why are you talking about that,
all the sudden?
Why?
When time comes...
I'm wondering, how I'm gonna feel
when i'm watching this film.
I'll just masturbate.
You're so low! dirty!
Am I low? dirty?
Yes.
Would you like taste of dirty?
Tickle me,
Sorry.
I told you shave some.
Hey...?
What?
Can you live without me?
Of course, there are so many
good gays out there.
Right!
I think we should remember this moment.
Like video that we're recording now.
You told me, you gonna masturbate.
You always acting so sensitive about
for funny jokes that I made.
You should just listen to me what I say.
You don't seem to respect me.
Anyway...
Do you like making love with me?
What are you going to do, if I said not really?
I'll make up to you.
Young-joon?
Yes?
My darling?
Why?
Your eyes look sad.
Even after I do this?
Come on.
Slowly.
Give it to me.
What's wrong with you?
It's nothing.
Such a kid.
I think something in my eyes.
I'll record this.
To make fun of you, later.
You were just a kid after all.
I can smell you from my hands.
Try smell them.
It's nice.
Do you know that?
While i'm working, when I think of you,
I smell my hands.
Each time I do that,
It feels like i'm talking to you,
and having sex with you
It just feels like you're just next to me.
Aren't you a pervert?
What?
If i'm a pervert, you're one, too.
That makes us, pervert couple.
Your smile is your best feature.
I wish you always smile.
Darling, can you make that face again.
Look at this.
Surprise!
I didn't expect anything today,
but I was really really happy.
Thank you for loving me and care about me.
And thank you for making me happy.
You were always my best,
and will be.
I think,
we are happy people.
As time goes by, many things will be forgotten.
I think we should remember today, forever.
You're liar. I don't smell anything.
Don't skip your breakfast
because I'm not with you.
Don't smoke because you get stress.
When you're drunk,
ask help to other people next to you.
I had so many things wanted to say.
But, I'm worried you might think it's too much.
However,
take care of yourself, well. right?
Can you promise me?
Your nose is runny.
Did you record? got it?
My darling, I'm recording all of this.
You should‘ve record them.
It's disgusting.
Come here.
I'm tired.
It's too much.
Catch me if you can.
It's tough.
For the last...
Record us that we're heading towards beach.
Step into the water.
I can't see my face.
Hold on.
Can we... do that?
I don't think so.
No. no. no.
Joon! joon! joon!
Start!
One.