[English subtitles are available]
Make My Heart Smile
Episode 5
You’re not Ye Zhenhan!!!
[Complaint Center]
[Come in half an hour,
or face the consequences.]
What does the screenshot mean?
The complaint period is still valid?
Two options for you.
Accept the complaint
and give full compensation.
Or you can sign a contract with me
and pretend to be my girlfriend.
Gu Yanluo,
you’re using my dilemma!
You broke your promise, first.
[Complaint confirmed]
Let’s negotiate.
Fine, I’ll accept it.
But,
you can’t tell others about that.
Or I won’t agree.
Even if you want me to, I won’t.
Come on. Sign it.
Party A, Gu Yanluo. Party B, Ye Zhenhan.
Item 1, without Party A’s permission,
Party B shall not tell anyone else
she once pretended to be his girlfriend.
Item 2, without Party A’s permission,
Party B shall not contact or talk
to Part A’s friends or families.
Item 3, in Charlotte College,
without Party A’s permission,
Party B shall not approach Party A
or try to harass him.
Item 4, when Party A needs Party B,
the latter must come to him immediately.
Item 5, Party B shall continue
to pretend to be Party A’s girlfriend
for one year?
You really wrote down our agreements?
Yes, you can see.
Uh,
don’t you find Item 3 and Item 4
a bit conflicting?
Item 3,
in Charlotte College,
without Party A’s permission,
Party B shall not approach Party A
or try to harass him.
Item 4,
when Party A needs Party B,
the latter must come to him immediately.
They compliment each other perfectly.
To pay off the debt?
It means,
when I pretend to be your girlfriend
in front of your families,
I don’t need to pay the debt?
What? It’s a contract.
Isn’t it clear enough?
But why?
There’s no reason. We simply help each other.
Fine. You’re not completely cruel.
Contract agreed.
[Ye Zhenhan]
Lu Yao,
do you know how shy he was yesterday?
Look at me. Look at me.
What’s the problem with my handsome face?
Have you ever seen anyone so narcissistic?
Well, he’s indeed handsome.
Even in a hot pink shirt,
he looks elegant.
Ye,
do you know you have talked
about Gu Yanluo for half an hour?
Are you falling in love with him?
How... How’s that possible?
I was simply forced
to sign a contract.
He gave a good offer, anyway.
Good offer?
That’s so naive of you!
You’ll face your future mother-in-law, right?
You know what?
Mothers-in-law are toughest rivals,
especially rich women.
I met his mother before.
She’s nice and kind to me.
She’s a rich and polite woman.
She wouldn’t embarrass you
in the ball.
You know what?
In idol dramas,
a smiling tiger is the final boss.
You’re so simple-minded.
I’m afraid you won’t survive long.
Who is it?
Hello?
Gu Siwan?
But I...
Lu Yao,
I shouldn’t have gossiped about others.
Soon after I signed the contract,
I have to work now.
What?
Gu Yanluo’s mother asked to see me.
My God! See? What did I say?
She’ll give you a head-on blow soon.
No, no.
I’ll go get ready.
You haven’t told me how to modify them.
Narrow the waistline of the girl’s style,
and widen the shoulder part
of the man’s style.
Use the space cotton.
You’ll check on the samples
before the sales.
I’ll send samples to the manufacturer, then.
No problem. Love you!
See you.
If we don’t issue any new styles,
my beauty won’t help anymore!
Pick up the phone! Pick up the phone!
[Debtor]
Come on. He can’t be relied on
at such critical moment.
[Drama Queen Ye shared a location.]
[Drama Queen Ye: Your mother has come.
Come and help!]
Siwan!
I was drunk in the ball.
She sneaked out in the canteen.
This is a good chance.
I’ll get more information from her.
Where’s Mrs. Gu?
She said she was stuck in a traffic jam,
and she would be late for half an hour.
She asked us to chat and wait for her.
Fine.
My cousin... He’s a Leo.
He’s... He has much self-respect.
And he’s proud.
He’s very possessive, too.
What star sign are you?
I...
I’m an Aquarius.
It’s conflicting against Leo, I guess.
An Aquarius wants freedom.
How did you know my cousin?
We met each other
totally unexpectedly.
Screwed!
I’m sorry.
Make way. Make way.
- I’m freaked out!
- I’m sorry.
- How were you riding?
I’m terribly sorry.
My apologies.
Siwan, are you alright?
I’m fine.
I’m not fine!
Look.
I’m sorry, sir.
We... We didn’t mean that.
How... How much is the painting?
How about I pay for that?
You think you can measure arts with money?
You crashed my inspiration.
I’m terribly sorry, sir.
Since you think
it can’t be measured by money,
how shall we pay for that?
Girl,
do you know how much
my efforts are worth?
Sir, may I have a try?
Why doesn’t she answer the phone?
I’m finished.
I’ve thought about it for a long time,
and I felt something was missing.
So,
the flower is what is missing.
I never expected you to paint so well.
Looks wonderful!
Could you make a painting for me?
Gu Yanluo,
when did you come?
Just now.
I didn’t know you were artistic.
Life is hard, and I need more skills.
Don’t you know I’m a talented girl?
Stop being narcissistic.
I’ll go pick up Auntie.
Let’s meet in the restaurant.
Okay.
You’re born to be conflicting.
Get on well with each other.
I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean that.
Let me clean it.
You really like
to ruin my shirts.
Because your mother asked to see me.
It makes me so nervous.
Don’t move.
Wait a second. It’ll be finished soon.
It’s done.
Does it look better?
It’s a little heart.
You always wear white shirts.
It looks good with some color.
You’ve got ideas.
Your mother is waiting for us.
Don’t keep her waiting.
Let’s go.
His handsome face touches me so much.
You must calm down before him.
Auntie, look.
My cousin has good taste.
His girlfriend is beautiful and talented.
She’s also so lovely.
Sure.
Look at Zhenhan.
She’s not only beautiful,
but also has a good character.
I grow to love her more.
Ask Yanluo to bring you home
and I’ll make you something to eat.
Thank you, Mrs. Gu.
You’re welcome.
You’ll be part of our family, sooner or later.
Don’t be shy.
Yeah, yeah.
Mrs. Gu,
Yanluo and I talked about that.
At this time,
we want to focus on our education,
and aren’t hurry to settle down now.
Right, Yanluo?
Yes.
Silly boy, why are you eating alone?
Share some food with her!
You know what?
You must be nice to Zhenhan.
If you don’t,
I won’t let you go!
Don’t think you can be bold with me,
simply because my mother supports you.
Try messing with me again,
See if I’ll tell Mrs. Gu about it.
Have more of it to make you smarter.
In a relationship,
a couple should be sweet
like them, right?
Precisely.
This is right.
Well,
why don’t you get engaged now?
Sorry, sorry.
Mom, Zhenhan and I
will discuss about that.
Right?
It doesn’t matter. Enjoy the food.
Then we can negotiate.
Enjoy it.
[Girls’ Dormitory]
What was the matter with me today?
I knew I was pretending to be his girlfriend.
But why was I so shy?
Shame on me.
Zhenhan!
Trouble is really everywhere.
Jiuyue?
I received your message.
I come,
to work together with you.
Jiuyue,
I think there’s some misunderstanding.
What?
Didn’t you accept my gift
and weren’t you going to
fight for a bright future with me?
Yes. But I don’t mean
what you mean.
What do you mean, then?
You don’t like that gift?
It doesn’t look good,
but I made it myself.
No.
Did I do anything wrong?
You’re different from what I imagined.
But you’re a good man. I’m serious.
We’ve been together for so long.
I was used to having you around,
but you’re standing off me lately.
Zhenhan, I like you.
Stop!
Yan Jiuyue, I’m sorry.
You’re going too far.
I can hardly catch up.
I want to calm down.
I gotta go.
But...
Zhenhan!
How come?
We were close before the vacation.
Why are all indexes declining sharply
after the vacation?
Is she...
From twelve to one every noon,
you used to practice English
in the lakeside corridor.
Why are you coming so early today?
No wonder I didn’t find you there.
I read about it that,
reciting English words when hungry
can be inefficient.
So, I plan to have something to eat
before I study.
You didn’t like to do this.
You said it was a waste of time.
You only came to study alone.
I'm now in the junior year.
I should take part in some social practice.
No way! No way!
It doesn’t make any sense.
You look very abnormal.
Have a crush on someone?
What makes you think so?
Well, I haven’t tried
a straight-A girl.
If you don’t like her,
I’d like to try.
How dare you!
See? Stop denying.
If you don’t want me to chase her,
play games with me over night
and make me happy.
You’re so angry.
Looks like you’re very territorial.
Don’t touch it!
You can’t use it.
I don’t think such a cheap thing is yours.
Why can’t I use it?
You just can’t!
You look weird.
Six major elements for accountancy
are assets, liabilities
equity,
income, expense and...
- I just come to take classes.
- Profit.
Why did I become
- Gu Yanluo’s girlfriend?
- These six elements are reflected
through report forms,
namely three financial sheets
we usually mention.
They are
Balance Sheet,
Income Statement and Cash Flow Statement.
These three sheets are closely related.
They reflect each other and make a balance.
In this class, we’ll...
What are you doing?
Learn basic principles.
Everybody, hope you’ll listen carefully
and make notes.
None of your business!
Only with enough basic principles
can you use what you learnt
to benefit society.
Sure.
I encourage you to do social practice
- during vocations.
- Item 4 of our agreements.
- I need you. Reply quickly.
- You should combine
the theories you learnt in classes
with the actual situations
you meet in society.
I’m in class!
What exactly do you want?
Do you have time tomorrow?
No.
Zhenhan, tomorrow is the weekend.
I want to take you to a place.
Do you have time?
When can they stop bothering me?
I’m afraid I’m busy tomorrow.
Tomorrow is my birthday.
I can ask someone
to take your place in the library.
Is that okay?
All right, then.
My mom said she would cook for you.
Let’s go tomorrow.
Sorry, but I don’t have time tomorrow.
You’re not sick.
You’re sick!
Since you’re not sick,
why do you turn me down?
Shall I remind you of Item 4 of the agreement?
Dude, we’re on the campus.
Shall I remind you of Item 3?
Yanluo!
Yanluo,
the Publicity Department organized a trip
to the suburban hot spring.
You’re the president of Students’ Union.
Would you like to go with us?
Sorry, but I don’t have time for that.
Jiuyue,
isn’t it your birthday today?
Why are you taking me to the amusement park?
Zhenhan, you love the amusement park most.
Don’t you remember?
Right.
It’s the most romantic place
a straightforward man can go.
Much better than that icy man.
Let’s go and see what we’ll enjoy.
Okay.
Life is full of tests.
It’s not written in the book.
Zhenhan, have you decided which to ride?
Uh, I...
How about this one?
It looks lovely.
Zhenhan, don’t you love roller coasters the most?
Shall we go ride one?
It’s over there.
Yes, yes. Let’s go ride it.
Zhenhan,
Don't be scared.
I won't be scared.
Are you?
I’m not scared.
Even if you are, you can’t run away.
You look a bit nervous.
I don’t.
I’m not nervous.
Here it goes!
Jiuyue, how... How are you feeling?
Are you alright?
Yes.
Shall we sit down?
No, no, no.
Zhenhan,
when we took the roller coaster
for the first time,
you didn’t enjoy it.
Now you’re so excited.
What a surprise!
You... You have such a good memory.
What... What are we going to do next?
Next...
Shall we try the Ferris wheel?
You said
you loved to enjoy the scenery up high.
Up high?
Fine.
Jiuyue,
I’m suddenly a bit tired and hot.
Shall we sit and have a rest?
Fine.
The Ferris wheel is so high.
God, what should I do?
Jiuyue.
Jiuyue!
I suddenly feel a bit thirsty.
There’s a vending machine.
Could you go buy me a bottle of water?
- Okay.
- Ice water, please.
Wait a minute, then.
Thank you.
Pick up the phone, Lu Yao!
You stalked me?
You look beautiful,
and you’re my cup of tea.
And I don’t need
to stalk anyone.
If I like you,
I’ll confess to you directly.
I’m sorry,
but you don’t look handsome enough.
You’re not my cup of tea, either.
I don’t like
to play around.
I don’t like you.
So, I’ll turn you down directly.
Farewell.
All right.
Girls like to refuse men before saying yes.
Well, I don’t have many shortcomings.
I’m mostly short
of you.
Could you stop being narcissistic?
No.
Go to hell, then.
Can God stop torturing me
for even a single day?
I’m afraid of nothing, but height.
What should I do?
I’ll be dead up there.
Being humiliated is better than being dead.
[Evil Creditor]
[Debtor]
You’re going too far!
You want me always to be there for you.
But when I need you,
you’re never there!
Damn the arbitrary items!
My phone is running out of power.
What should I do?
[Evil Creditor]
Gu, you finally called back!
You have no time, do you?
Why are you calling?
I’ve got some emergency.
If you help me,
I promise I’ll always be there for you.
You will?
Say it again and I’ll record it.
This is very urgent!
What do you want?
Uh...
Hello? Where are you?
Answer me.
President,
you want me to go back?
But I’m not on the campus.
It’s not very convenient.
Something urgent? I must go back immediately?
Okay, I see.
See you later. See you later.
What happened?
You heard that.
President of Students’ Union summoned me.
Listen.
There’s an urgent mission.
Within half an hour,
Ye Zhenhan must come back.
Are you leaving now?
A man’s voice?
Hello? Hello?
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed
is powered off.
Why powered off?
I’m leaving, then.
Why don’t you leave after having the water?
All right.
I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
- Uh, it doesn’t matter.
- Let me wipe it.
I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
It doesn’t matter.
Jiuyue,
I’m very sorry.
I really have something urgent to do.
Next time...
Let’s come out and have fun next time!
I gotta go.
You’re not Ye Zhenhan!
What nonsense are you talking about?
Zhenhan has never forgotten my birthday.
Today isn’t my birthday.
She doesn’t dare to take roller coaster.
She loves to enjoy the scenery
up in the Ferris wheel.
Mostly importantly,
there’s a crescent scar on her leg.
But you don’t have it.
Who are you?
Why are you pretending?
[Outpatient]
[Inpatient Department]
Here we are.
[Push]
Zhenhan.
Mom, Zhenhan and I
will discuss that.
Right?
Your cousin said
they would talk about that.
There’s hope.
Do you think we need to talk about it?
No. Don’t even think about it.
My cousin is handsome, rich, and intelligent.
Ye Zhenhan will like him for certain!
Zhenhan is a kind, lovely and gallant girl.
Yanluo will like her for certain!
You’re an arrogant, proud, and brash man.
I won’t like you.
You’re an odd and irascible girl
who loves to lie.
I couldn’t love you, either.
It’s so sweet of them!
Their eyes are full of love.