[English subtitles are available]
Make My Heart Smile
Episode 15
Rival in love versus secret couple
The man who bumped you...
You know him?
Yes,
since we were little.
He looks arrogant now.
When he was little, however,
he was a snotty boy behind me.
You grew up with him?
Not really.
He moved away after primary school.
We didn’t keep in touch.
Let’s go.
Yao,
shall we have lunch?
No, thanks. I’m on a diet.
I left my helmet in the cafe.
Wait for me.
How time flies!
It’s all your fault.
Because of you, I can’t drive her home.
How can I break it down?
Oh, I know.
take a seat.
Thanks.
The trailer is coming soon.
Don’t worry.
I’ll get you and your motorcycle
back to school safely.
Leave the repair thing to me.
The motorcycle can be repaired.
What makes you unhappy?
It’s a limited edition?
It’s a birthday gift from my father.
I’ve been protecting it carefully.
I haven’t even scratched it.
It’s my fault.
Screwed! I destroyed it!
From your father?
It should be cherished.
Don’t worry. I’ll get it fixed as soon as possible
in case your father gets angry.
He won’t.
He passed away.
I’m sorry.
Oh, playboy,
look what you’ve done!
Sichen.
Well,
could you listen carefully to me?
We’ve signed the contract
to be a judge for the fashion competition.
If you don’t cooperate,
we’ll pay for breach of contract.
Whose problem is it?
Why didn’t you ask me when you signed?
Now you’re asking?
You signed the contract and you shall go.
I... I... I...
I...
I meant good!
I did that for you!
I want you
to be more popular
and more famous
in China!
I don’t need to get popular
through a competition.
Why don’t you?
Think about it.
The more competitions, the better.
Look at the competitors.
- I’m in the game.
- Look.
Come on. Just have a look.
They’re excellent.
Have a look.
Sichen,
come on, have a look, all right?
Anyway,
when you sit on the rostrum
as the judge,
you’ll look cool.
Just go.
No.
Sichen, listen to me, all right?
See? Game over.
It’s my fault?
Come on, Sichen.
[Resumes of competitors
for GS Fashion Competition]
All right, then,
if you don’t want to go,
I’ll negotiate with the sponsor.
I wonder if they’ll agree.
I’ll go.
Did... Did I hear it right?
I mean I’ll be the judge.
Leave the resumes to me.
Really?
Oh, my God, I...
Are you kidding me?
Ask again and I’ll reject
No, no, no!
I won’t ask again. I won’t.
Take your time.
I’ll get to work.
[Resumes of competitors
for GS Fashion Competition]
Xingxing, I’m back.
Weimian, Yan Jiuyue’s birthday is coming.
What gift shall I give him?
Birthday?
He’ll like anything you give him.
You have no idea.
When he mistook me for you,
he gave me a wooden board,
asking me to work together with him
and fight for a bright future.
Really?
He’s adorable.
Adorable?
You couldn’t be more perfectly matched!
So,
you wouldn’t give a worse gift.
Xingxing!
Zuo Sichen?
Can you remember me?
Why are you here?
It’s been years,
and I still call you Xingxing.
But you sound distant.
I’m so sad. You don’t remember me at all.
Shall I still call you Snotty?
Come on.
For a sugar painting,
you ran after me across three streets.
Because you snatched it from Zhenhan!
Sugar painting?
Here’s your sugar painting.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- You’re welcome.
Well, I’m grateful to the sugar painting.
For getting punched by me?
For making me know you.
You still sound honey-lipped.
What? Do I look cooler?
You’ve indeed changed.
More shameless and glib-tongued!
You’re going to be
a real lady killer.
I don’t want any other ladies.
Oh, why are you in our college?
I came for you.
Just joking.
I come for classes.
Why I haven’t seen you before?
When I was in the first year,
I went abroad as an exchange student.
So,
I failed to meet you on the campus.
You’re brilliant.
You’ve grown mature.
Stop calling me Snotty.
It spoils my cool image.
Now I'm your senior.
Yeah, great painter.
Well, I still love the sugar paintings
we had when we were very little.
So do I.
I haven’t found Lu Yao,
but I saw something unexpected.
What do you mean?
I would like to ask you.
Don’t you want to say something about it?
Little Luo,
you must take it seriously!
As your buddy,
I’ve got the latest news
about that man.
Come on.
You know what?
You’ve got a strong rival in love.
He’s Zuo Sichen.
He has great talent for arts.
After half a year’s learning,
a famous foreign college took a fancy to him.
He became the youngest
international exchange student.
in our college.
Are you listening to me?
You know what? In the past three years,
he has held personal exhibitions.
He was also on arts magazines.
Lately, he’s been invited to be the judge
at GS Fashion Competition
your company is sponsoring.
You’re the honor of Charlotte.
But as the saying goes,
there’s always a better person than you.
He’s an international school hunk.
Are you done?
You!
Why don’t you have any sense of crisis?
Look. Look.
Look! Look carefully!
Look at the photo.
They looked so sweet.
You just didn’t see it.
They knew each other when they were little.
You knew that?
Screwed!
You... You fell behind at the starting line.
Make way. Make way.
When you have time to frighten me,
why don’t you solve your own problem?
Yanluo, Yanluo!
I’m caring for you.
He looks cool and fashionable.
All girls will have a crush on him.
You should be cautious.
See you at the night market.
Wait a second.
come on eat
Does it taste good?
How lovely!
You want it?
Let me get it.
First.
Put it down.
It’s okay. Try again.
Come on. Let’s try this one.
Okay.
Do it.
You’re indeed my cool boyfriend!
You’re amazing!
How will you award me?
Award for a claw game?
What do you want? I’ll think about it.
Fine.
Here comes the lightning round.
What did you do today?
I took classes,
designed new clothes
and had a meal with Lu Yao.
What else?
I met Zuo Sichen.
The man we met in the cafe.
He went there for you?
No.
What a coincidence!
He studies in the Art Department
of our college.
He used to be very timid.
Now, he’s brilliant.
He even won a prize
at La Biennale di Venezia.
That’s the dream of all artists.
I’m not interested in anyone else.
Where are you going?
Home.
You asked me to come and now you leave.
It’s so hard to make a young man happy.
You wait for me!
I didn’t have enough to eat for dinner.
I made some midnight snacks.
Would you like some?
Let’s have the lightning round again.
Face-saving Gu,
what’s the matter?
Why are you suddenly so curious?
What advantages
do you think I have?
Advantages?
What? None?
You have too many advantages
for me to think of any now.
Say something important, then.
Advantages?
You look more handsome than stars.
You have a perfect figure as super models have.
But, if you can smile more,
you’ll look more handsome.
You study well and do well in sports, too.
You’re good at all subjects.
Go on.
But you make life hard for people around you.
As your girlfriend, for example,
I’m under great pressure.
However much pressure you have,
you’re mine only.
Also, I’m yours only.
What...
What do you want?
I’m thinking
I must reaffirm my position
as your boyfriend.
Wait, someone’s coming.
Ignore that.
I’d rather hide myself.
Xia Yuanqing?
Yanluo,
I made a cake for you.
Cake?
Thank you, but...
It’s too hot out here.
May I come in?
I don’t eat dessert.
Take the cake back.
I don’t know you don’t eat dessert.
Don’t make it anymore.
Yanluo,
I just fear you feel bad after breaking up.
Then I come for a visit.
It’s too hot out there.
May I have some water?
Here.
Yanluo, I can’t have cold water these days.
May I have some hot water?
What are you doing here?
Yanluo, I was just walking around.
Sorry, but you can’t go there.
If you’ve got nothing else to say,
please leave.
I...
The cake will taste bad after a long time.
Enjoy it, Prince Charming.
I’ll throw it away, then.
We were going to kiss
when my rival in love suddenly came.
What a complicated story!
♫ Happy birthday to you ♫
I’ve made my wish.
Well, blow the candle.
Three, two, one.
♫ And realize we love each other ♫
Zhenhan,
could you realize the wish
I just made?
Sure, if I can.
What wish did you make?
I... I wished
you could be my girlfriend!
♫ You smile so sweetly ♫
I swear
I’ll protect you and take care of you.
I...
Do you remember this?
It’s...
My sister gave this to me.
She said you gave it to her
when you mistook her for me.
So, my answer is below the box.
Let’s travel together, despite difficulties.
Zhenhan, you agreed?
Happy birthday, Jiuyue.
I’d like to celebrate
every birthday of yours.
Let’s enjoy the cake.
♫ Seeing you feels like seeing myself ♫
♫ We feel happy even if we argue ♫
♫ We have fun all the time ♫
♫ And realize we love each other ♫
You’ll give her a gift?
Little Luo, you’re romantic at last.
Weimian said Yan Jiuyue confessed his love
to Ye Zhenhan.
She also mentioned a token of love.
I thought your rival in love stung you.
Shut up and tell me what to do!
Don’t rush.
I’m in the middle of something.
I’ll instruct you soon.
Sir,
if you fail to pick the one you like,
you can design it by yourself.
Design it?
Yes. We’ll instruct you.
Okay.
Why can’t I start it?
What’s the problem?
Yao, here I am.
Do you need any help?
I need you to walk away.
Don’t! I come to help you.
Here, sir.
Sir, I’ve checked the spark plugs.
There’s no problem with high voltage
or cylinder pressure.
Please check it
and see what the problem is.
Okay.
The engine is aging.
And there’s water in it.
It’s scrapped.
Scrapped?
How come?
Sir,
I didn’t even ride it on rainy days.
Why is there water in it?
I opened the nozzle and checked it.
The oil quality has changed.
The engine is aging, too.
There’s lack of oil,
but you shouldn’t have added water.
I didn’t add water.
I would never do that.
Is it because of the wet weather?
Please check if you got it wrong.
Yeah, sir.
Can it be repaired?
The engine is so aging
that it’s no more produced.
We can hardly buy a new one.
I know.
I’ve looked for it for a long time.
Isn’t there any other solutions?
I don’t have any.
Thank you, sir.
Tell me the engine model.
Yao, don’t worry.
I’ll find it for you.
Take your time.
Ask me if you have any problems.
Okay.
♫ It’s clear after a heavy rain ♫
♫ Sunlight drives away the dark clouds ♫
♫ The next bright season ♫
♫ Breathe freely ♫
♫ There are beautiful scenery front ♫
♫ But I just want to tell you now ♫
♫ My heart is not at peace recently ♫
♫ Especially when I saw you ♫
♫ It pops unceasingly ♫
♫ You suddenly got upgraded ♫
♫ Become the focus of my life ♫
♫ Blink my eyes ♫
♫ Like you are here ♫
♫ These sweet little secrets ♫
♫ I don’t know if I should tell you ♫
♫ I want to keep it to my own ♫
♫ A whole forest of secret love ♫
♫ Memories that belong to us ♫
♫ Grows a bit densely ♫
♫ I treasure everything ♫
♫ The sweet you and me ♫
♫ No more ice in our relationship ♫
♫ Everything is very comfortable ♫
♫ We have a natural understanding ♫
♫ I’m in a good mood with you ♫
♫ I want to be with you forever ♫
Without flowers, it looks less romantic.
For your love confession,
romance matters a lot.
Imagine it.
When Ye Weimian comes back home,
she can see the room
full of flowers and balloons,
and her favorite toys.
She’ll be excited.
Then you can take out the bracelet
you made by yourself
and confess to her lovingly that,
Honey, I want to stay with you forever.
Perfect!
Hello?
Gu Yanluo,
why didn’t you accept me
even after you broke up?
Why don't you like me
There’s no reason in love.
Stop drinking.
I want it!
I just want it!
Ask Fang Meimei to pick you up,
in case of danger.
What are you doing?
Xia Yuanqing, what happened?
Rogue!
Don’t touch my skirt! Go away!
Where are you?
I’m at Frost Bar. I’m so scared.
Come and get me.
[Arrogant Gu]
Don’t come to such a place anymore.
I’ll get you a taxi
and you can go back to the college.
No way, Yanluo!
If I go back now,
the supervisor of dorm will see me.
Well,
I’ll drive you to a nearby hotel
and you can check in.
But it’s too late.
I haven’t had anything with me.
My dress is wet.
Something terrible just happened.
I’m so scared.
Yanluo,
we’re classmates at least.
Could you help me?
What exactly do you want?
May...
Can I change my clothes at your house?
Then I’ll go back to school.
It’s the safest to stay at school.
I’ll leave immediately after I get changed.
come, then.
For the sake that we’re old family friends,
this is the last time I help you.
Hope you won’t do this again.
My bedroom is over there.
Go get changed
and then leave.
Go ahead.
[Arrogant Gu]
Why doesn’t she answer the phone?
Where’s she?
[Missed Call Arrogant Gu]
You can’t wear this one. Get another one!
Why?
This T-shirt looks the cheapest
among all your clothes.
Get another one right away!
Because she gave you
this T-shirt?
Get another one!
You...
You set all this?
You’ll get back to her?
Why?
What makes me worse than Ye Zhenhan?
I don’t need to explain to you.
Yanluo,
she isn’t in the same world as you are.
If you like such a girl,
I can stop wearing expensive clothes.
I can stop being fastidious.
I can turn into the girl you like.
Yanluo!
I don’t need that!
Take off my T-shirt!
Yanluo!
Yanluo, you...
Let me finish, Yanluo!
Yanluo, it’s the last time!
I’ll let you go after I finish.
Yanluo, I love you for the longest time
and I’m the best girl for you.
Yanluo,
we have fans who support our relationship,
don’t we?
Speaking of the family background,
we make a perfect couple.
Yanluo,
did you hear me? Yanluo?
Yanluo, we make the perfect couple!
Yanluo, did you hear me?
I know it,
but it doesn’t know me.
I would have picked
the Mechanical Department.
Little Luo, come and look at it.
Look at me, first.
Don’t we stay with each other,
but hate to look at each other?
Your face looks the same.
I mean the T-shirt!
Sure enough,
love makes a cool guy odd.
You’re my beloved young man?
Sounds so romantic.
Read it backwards.
My beloved young man is you?
Sounds so sweet.
What a secret lovey-dovey thing!
It must be the sweetest art.