[English subtitles are available]
Make My Heart Smile
Episode 23
I won't be your Achilles' heel.
Ye Zhenhan.
No, I mean Ye Weimian.
Ye Weimian, make it clear.
I'm never a burden to Yanluo.
The future of you and your sister
or Yanluo's reputation,
which will you pick?
Don't bother!
I'll pick it myself.
Yanluo,
it's my own business.
I can handle it.
Your business is mine.
Yanluo,
you'll risk your pride, honor
and even your future
simply for her?
Why do you do this for her?
Many things don't depend on
if it's worth it,
but if I want it.
No matter what happens,
let's face it together.
Ye Weimian, is this what you want?
In people's eyes,
Yanluo used to be perfect and unreachable.
But since you turned up,
he's been criticized, encumbered,
and condemned.
Now he's even risking his future for you!
You don't deserve to be his girlfriend!
Xia Yuanqing!
That's enough.
You don't know anything.
Don't be self-righteous.
There's nothing in it.
In your eyes,
I may be a girl who always tries to hurt her.
But I hate her,
simply because I like you.
Yanluo, I have never meant
to hurt you.
When you hurt her, you hurt me.
Yeah, in your heart,
my care for you isn't as much
as you care for her.
Don't mind what she said.
Yanluo,
if there's some more trouble,
don't risk your future for me again.
I've carefully thought about
what consequences I would bear.
After changing the list without permission,
I might no longer be the president
of the Students' Union.
But if people know
you took classes for your sister,
you'll have unbearable consequences.
I took classes in the Finance Department
for Zhenhan.
Xia Yuanqing is right.
You shouldn't take
such responsibilities for me.
These things
don't matter to me.
What... What matters?
You.
Luckily, the list was changed.
Lu Yao, thank you for coming
and taking the place of my sister.
You're welcome.
Gu Yanluo asked me to come.
He feared if you showed up together,
people would gossip about you
and even find out what you did.
Little Luo is always rigorous.
As soon as he saw the list,
he asked to me pick Yao here.
What? Can I get extra points
for the boyfriend probation?
You finally did something right.
People are watching. Behave yourself.
So what?
I just want everyone to know
a popular young man like me
has already got a girlfriend.
Others should stop dreaming!
You stop dreaming!
- I'll pull your hand.
- Zhenhan,
are you still worried?
I still feel uneasy.
Uneasy?
What happened?
Weimian said that
Xia Qingyuan figured out our secret.
What?
I'm fine.
There's some ending work of the forum.
Get back to work.
I'll take you to a place.
Let's go.
It's where you want me to see?
So many DIY works!
There're real masters in ordinary places.
Look at the cup.
It's broken.
But it has a beauty of regret, doesn't it?
And this vase.
What a special pattern!
I love this place!
Would you like to make one?
♫ It's clear after a heavy rain ♫
♫ Sunlight drives away the dark clouds
The next bright season ♫
♫ Breathe freely
There are beautiful scenery front ♫
♫ But I just want to tell you now ♫
♫ My heart is not at peace recently ♫
♫ Especially when I saw you
It pops unceasingly ♫
♫ You suddenly got upgraded
Become the focus of my life ♫
♫ Blink my eyes Like you are here ♫
♫ These sweet little secrets ♫
♫ I don't know if I should tell you ♫
♫ I want to keep it to my own
A whole forest of secret love ♫
♫ Memories that belong to us
Grows a bit densely ♫
♫ I treasure everything ♫
♫ The sweet you and me ♫
♫ No more ice in our relationship ♫
♫ Everything is very comfortable
We have a natural understanding ♫
Thank you
for doing everything for me quietly.
You make me braver
to face everything.
You're so concentrated
on designing the patterns.
This is our featured series.
There's not much time before it's issued.
I must finish the drafts soon.
If I don't have enough time,
you can paint the patterns
with your poor skills,
all right?
Since when did I say no to you?
But wait...
Why don't you have enough time?
I...
We both have our own boyfriend.
You can't always enjoy your love
while I'm busy with working.
After I finish this series,
you can design the new series.
Just make a sweet series about you and Mu Ze.
Forget it.
You and Gu Yanluo make a perfect couple.
Mu Ze and I
make a worst one.
Lu Yao,
Mu Ze turned into a loyal man,
simply for you!
What else do you want?
Don't tease me.
Look who I am.
Oh, I've got something serious to tell you.
You can discuss with Mu Ze
for future promotion.
He has a quick mind.
Ye,
you sound very weird.
Did anything happen?
I...
There's something very important
that I must do it personally.
You can read this book.
Jiuyue...
I...
What's the matter?
I want to give up the quota
for exchange student.
Weimian is having a rise in career and love,
but she's stuck in trouble because of me.
Since we were little,
Weimian's been sacrificing for me.
Everything happened because of me.
I want to do something for her, too.
Do whatever you want
and I'll always support you.
Zhenhan.
Mr. Ma.
What's wrong?
I come to confess something to you.
In fact, I'm not Ye Zhenhan.
I'm her twin sister Ye Weimian.
Are you kidding me?
You...
You mean you're not Ye Zhenhan?
But you look the same.
Then what do you come for?
Mr. Ma, well, it's a long story.
I'm a third-year student
of the Fashion Department.
Then I came to the main campus
and made a very big mistake.
I...
Excuse me.
Hello?
Okay.
Okay. Bye.
What a coincidence!
Go to the headmaster's office with me.
Come this way.
I've got everything ready.
The flight tickets are ready, too.
However...
Even though you passed the exam of
the foreign college,
you still need to prepare a lot
for the interview.
You've said that a million times.
Stop nagging!
I won't run away.
You did that many times!
Fatty,
follow him.
Don't move.
Go have some tea around.
I'll say goodbye to my friend.
Go ahead. Go.
Give me the certificate.
Yes, here it is.
[Certificate]
It's the proof of your brilliance.
I'm going, then.
Come back early.
I'll be waiting for you.
Come in.
Sister
Zhenhan?
Headmaster, if you don't need me,
I'll get back to my work.
Go ahead.
I received
an anonymous report letter.
There's some evidence in it,
together with a flash drive.
I took classes in the Finance Department
for Zhenhan.
Xia Yuanqing is right.
You shouldn't take
such responsibilities for me.
Who's it in the video?
He's there. There.
Little Luo, something's come up!
- Something terrible!
- What's the rush?
Zhenhan, she...
Let me explain.
Ye Zhenhan was summoned by the headmaster.
I called Yao.
She told me that
Ye Weimian came to confess herself.
Wait for me!
And me!
Be right there.
Lu Yao,
I come to see Xingxing.
I kept calling her, but she didn't answer.
She's not in.
I just want to say goodbye to her.
I'm leaving.
She isn't in.
Before she left,
she said there was something important
that she must do it personally.
It's me.
I took classes in the Finance Department
in my sister's name.
It was also me
who instigated Gu Yanluo to change the list.
They're both innocent.
It's not true, headmaster.
I fell in a coma several months ago.
My sister didn't want me
to fall behind in study
or lose the quota as the exchange student.
Then she took classes for me.
It was my fault.
Headmaster,
Zhenhan was in a coma
and she didn't know anything!
I did everything alone.
No, that's not true!
Headmaster, it was because of me.
All right. Stop.
It means
you admit you pretended to be her?
I'm sorry, headmaster.
I'll accept any punishment.
But my sister Zhenhan and Gu Yanluo...
They're innocent.
We'll figure it out.
We won't wrong anyone innocent,
or ignore anything against school rules.
Come in.
You're just in time.
Gu Yanluo, stay.
The rest of you can leave.
Go back to classes.
Gu Yanluo, look what you've done!
I'm sorry, headmaster.
I made the mistake.
You're the president of the Students' Union,
and an excellent cadre.
Instead of telling us, you helped them.
Do you ever respect school rules?
Headmaster, I did that,
because I knew what they suffered
and I was touched by them
who defended each other.
So, you abused your authority
and played favoritism?
It was my fault.
I'll quit my job and accept any punishment.
Do you think this is over
when you simply quit your job?
I hear
Ye Weimian is your girlfriend.
You made mistakes deliberately for her!
What's wrong with you?
Why did a girl make you lose your mind?
Yes, you'll graduate next year.
You can quit the job
as the president of the Students' Union.
But don't you care for your future?
Why must you get stuck in such a dilemma
at this important moment?
You make me so disappointed!
Headmaster, sorry to have let you down.
But I still hope
you can show some mercy
in the investigation,
given that they have a reason
and Ye Zhenhan corrected after she woke up.
We know what to do.
But you should also think carefully about it.
Love relationship isn't forbidden in college.
A good relationship
will make the couple better.
You should also
reflect on yourself for this!
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have left things to luck
and got you in such a dilemma.
Is this what you want?
In people's eyes,
Yanluo used to be perfect and unreachable.
But since you turned up,
he's been criticized, encumbered,
and condemned.
Now he's even risking his future for you!
You don't deserve to be his girlfriend!
I shouldn't have been your Achilles' heel.
[Headmaster's Office]
It doesn't matter. Don't worry.
Before there's a result,
there's still hope. I'll...
Don't bother.
I can handle it myself.
Let's break up for a while.
What?
Break up?
I mean let's break up
and cool down.
Don't interfere with my problem anymore.
I'll take care of it.
Ye Weimian,
what do you mean breaking up for a while?
I don't agree.
Ye Weimian!
Gu Yanluo,
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have been your burden.
But I really don't know
if we should be together.
Ye Weimian!
Gu Yanluo, where's Xingxing?
You didn't see her coming out?
Who? Xingxing?
Wait.
Let go of me!
Gu Yanluo!
I said, let go of me!
Tell me what happened to Xingxing?
I said, get out of the way!
She...
Zuo Sichen,
I've been bearing with you for a long time!
Could you think carefully
before you do anything?
Don't only care about your own feelings.
If you really like her,
don't bring her so much trouble,
but think about what she needs!
- Gu Yanluo...
- Don't try to stop me.
Or you'll be sorry.
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed
is powered off.
Ye Weimian, listen!
I don't allow you to do that!
I don't agree!
♫ There's always a cloud ♫
♫ Refuse to dissipate ♫
♫ There's always someone ♫
♫ Shelters you from trouble ♫
♫ One day he'll be happy ♫
♫ For holding you in his arms ♫
♫ There's always a flower ♫
♫ Refuses to wither ♫
♫ There's always someone ♫
♫ Loves you with a true heart ♫
♫ One day dark clouds will ♫
♫ Finally go away ♫
But, can there be an ending
for our story?
♫ The smile long gone ♫
♫ Now comes back ♫
♫ Could it be my fantasy? ♫
♫ No more trying to be a pleaser ♫
Good morning, Your Highness.
♫ No more trying to ♫
♫ Change your taste ♫
♫ The world is beautiful ♫
♫ There's another feeling ♫
I deliberately brought it back for painting.
Do you know why?
Why?
Because I'm a face-judger.
I have no inspiration
unless I look at your handsome face.
So, can we pass the dinner
for tonight?
♫ There's always a flower ♫
[I'm sorry.]
Ye...
Ye Weimian.
♫ Loves you with a true heart ♫
♫ One day dark clouds will ♫
♫ Finally go away ♫
♫ No more time ♫
♫ Will be wasted ♫
You're my beloved young man.
♫ Will be shed ♫
♫ The world is beautiful ♫
[You're my beloved young man.]
My beloved young man is you.
Now that you drew it,
there should be a happy ending.
Hello, everybody.
I'm Ye Weimian,
from the Fashion Department of Art College.
Art College? What's going on?
Today,
I want to confess a mistake to all of you.
Must we read the self-criticism
in front of everyone
if we make a mistake?
How humiliating!
My twin sister Ye Zhenhan,
is a third-year student
of the Finance Department.
Several months ago,
she fell in a coma because of a car accident.
To maintain her quota
as the exchange student,
I made a wrong decision.
I pretended to be her
and took classes in the Finance Department.
That's Ye Zhenhan?
No, it's her twin sister.
So, here,
I'd like
to say sorry
to all teachers and students
I contacted and deceived.
I will drop out of school willingly
and bear the responsibility for my mistake.
But I earnestly request our school
to forgive my sister Ye Zhenhan
and Gu Yanluo who helped me.
They shouldn't be punished
for my impulsive decision.
Leaders and teachers,
hope you can give them a chance.
Thank you.
She sounds poor.
She did that to protect her sister.
If she's expelled,
how cruel it will be!
Don't talk nonsense!
Even if she's poor, she broke school rules!
Let's go.
Ye Weimian,
you're a loser in life.
When you leave school
and leave Gu Yanluo,
can you still fly?
♫ The misty city is getting cold ♫
♫ I'd like to cover my longing for you ♫
♫ You bear it alone,
with your tears running ♫
♫ Your innocent smile
is replaced by tiredness ♫
♫ I miss you again when the wind blows ♫
♫ But I'm not willing to tell you ♫
[Gu Yanluo]
♫ In the dark night, I pray for dawn ♫
♫ Stretching out my hand ♫
♫ I want to touch you, but fail ♫
I'm sorry, Gu Yanluo.
Weimian, open the door!
I know you're in!
Weimian!
♫ Memories are filled
with the secret of youth ♫
Weimian, Weimian.
Ye Weimian, I told you that
no matter what happened,
we would face it together.
You also said that
we should trust each other.
But what are you doing now?
I don't mean I don't trust you.
I trust you so much
that I did that.
Open the door, then.
Open the door!
Leave.
I'll handle my own problem.
You'll no longer
be involved.
Handle it?
You mean dropping out of school?
As your boyfriend,
I don't allow you to do that!
You're
no longer my boyfriend.
I thought carefully about it.
Let's...
Let's break up.
No.
I don't agree!
It doesn't matter.
Two persons are needed in love.
But one person is needed
for breaking up.
Now I'm already at the bottom.
I'd like to suffer alone.
You...
You can have a better choice.
At such an important moment,
I can't help with anything.
Neither can I.
Boys,
the bell rang.
Didn't you hear that?
Go to your class.
Sir, we don't have a class.
You don't?
Then do some self-study.
Ah?
What?
Want me to find you a room for self-study?
Do you mean that?
No, sir. I've finished my self-study.
What about you?
Sir, I never do any self-study.
Fine, fine.
Since you're free,
do me a favor.
I remember you're both
from the Finance Department.
Right?
Contact numbers of two thousand schoolmates
from the Finance Department
need to be upgraded.
Help me sort them out
and upgrade them.
What are you waiting for? Go.
Jiuyue,
I'll leave the job to you.
I don't want it. It's your own job.
Don't. Don't.
Handle it yourself.
- Take care of it.
- I won't...
Take care of it. Hold it.
Good boy.