GYEONGSEONG CREATURE
I have arranged it
with Director Ichiro of Ongseong Hospital.
The child in your womb
will hold a very special meaning
not only to Mr. Ishikawa, but also to me.
That being said...
please take exceptional care of yourself,
Miss Akiko.
Sorry, but we are closed for the day.
The spores stopped floating around
an hour ago.
Has it awakened?
Yes, but it's not moving.
Perhaps we used too much nitrogen gas?
What's on your mind?
Seishin.
Lieutenant Colonel Kato, we have a guest.
This is Lady Maeda.
She is the wife of Commissioner Ishikawa
and the daughter
of Lieutenant General Maeda of the Army.
Outsiders are not allowed down here.
She's also the most generous sponsor
of our hospital, Colonel.
Is that it?
I'd advise you not to get too close.
Seishin.
So you were still alive.
Teacher Seishin.
GYEONGSEONG CREATURE
BETWEEN JUSTIFICATION AND EXCUSE
EPISODE 8
AWAKENING
He must have gone through an ordeal.
He hasn't been able to sleep a wink
or swallow a bite of food.
What about Tae-sang?
He didn't make it back.
And the merchants in Bonjeong
have all been arrested.
Yes, hello.
Yes.
- Yes, sir.
- Quiet!
Sit down!
Mr. Gu, what's going on?
Why haven't we heard from Master Jang yet?
Is he... not coming to save us?
Is that it?
Damn it!
PAWNSHOP
CLOSED FOR THE DAY
Tae-sang.
What are you up to?
Hurry back home, will you?
Is he dead?
He's breathing, just about.
Take him so he can get treated.
- Hurry.
- Yes, sir!
Kill him...
Find...
the bastard
and kill him!
All of you, stop and stand back!
As you were.
Sir! I have something to report.
Is it urgent?
First Sergeant Haneda
was found next to the body dump.
He has a serious gunshot wound.
My apologies, Lady Maeda.
Would you wait inside for just a moment?
Mr. Jang!
What are you... doing here?
I came in to do a job
but missed my chance to leave.
So I need you
to help me, Lady Maeda.
Are you saying that a Josenjing
is still hiding in here?
Yes, sir. It seems so.
Director Ichiro!
The Josenjing seems to be in this wing.
This soldier just found blood
near the supply room.
Lady Maeda, I'm afraid
now is not a good time...
It's an emergency! Emergency!
Lady Maeda is in danger!
Find Lady Maeda immediately! Now!
Lady Maeda.
No questions. Just drive.
Go.
Thank you.
What should I do, ma'am? Shall I stop?
To Bonjeong.
PAWNSHOP
CLOSED FOR THE DAY
Were you at Golden Treasure again?
Waiting for me?
It's been four days.
The fact that he hasn't reached out
means it's unlikely for him to return.
Besides, our job was to find Myeong-ja.
Since we've done our part,
it is time for us to head back home.
Get ready to leave early tomorrow morning.
I should have stayed in his place.
It was his choice.
All he had to do was save Myeong-ja, but...
because of us...
I should've stayed
and found a way to rescue Mother.
I should've at least gotten revenge
on those who did that to her.
Then he wouldn't have been left alone.
And I wouldn't be wracked with guilt.
What do you mean by that?
I met Mother.
She's still there...
at Ongseong Hospital.
It's been in that state
ever since Lady Maeda's visit.
It seems to be enraged by something.
It's looking for its young.
Sir?
It's not enraged,
but agitated.
I'll ask again.
Where are the Josenjings
you helped escape?
I don't know.
Where is Jang Tae-sang right now?
I wish...
I wish I knew.
You don't seem to understand.
Should we start over?
Over...
Start... over...
Have you ever had
your nails plucked out?
Have you ever been burned...
or gone through electric torture?
Do you know what happens
when water mixed with chili powder
is poured down your nose
while hanging upside down?
Persist to that point,
and a person can no longer remain human.
If you're ever in such a situation,
don't try to hold back and ruin your life.
Just tell them everything you know.
I won't ever resent you for betraying me
in a situation like that.
Keep that in mind.
Let me ask you again.
What is the true purpose of your pawnshop?
Are you rebels?
Or do you secretly fund
the independence army?
Answer me!
Where is Jang Tae-sang?
Goddamn it...
You are awake.
Lady Maeda.
Your fever has gone down, thankfully.
Your wounds are also healing well.
How long have I been here?
As of today, it's been four days.
You caused quite a stir
at Ongseong Hospital.
Though you didn't need to risk your life
over someone else's trouble.
It's not like you.
It just
made me a bit angry.
It's not my fault that this country
has come to this.
It's not my fault those people
were kept in there and suffering, but...
But?
But...
once I saw it with my own eyes,
it made me angry.
It pissed me off.
Could you not stand the injustice
as a fellow Joseon person?
No, I couldn't stand it
as a fellow human being.
Do you think all human lives are equal?
Do you somehow think they're not?
Do you still
consider us friends?
A serial murder case?
Yes, 11 deaths around Cheonggyecheon
over the past four days.
We've requested the military ward
for autopsies.
An unusually large number of corpses
were in a very strange state.
Strange? In what way?
They were missing their brains, sir.
He's from the military ward.
This is the House of Golden Treasure!
No.
We haven't put the store up for sale.
What are you talking about?
Dead...
What do you mean? Who's dead?
Just who do you think you are?
You watch your mouth
and the crap that comes out of it!
That's right, you heard me! Oh, pipe down!
Shut your trap,
or I will sew it shut for you.
Like they know it all.
How dare they say shit like he's dead
as if they have a say in it?
You've got to be freaking kidding me.
House of Golden Treasure.
I believe my employee
has already answered that question.
Me?
I'm the master of this shop,
Jang Tae-sang.
Yes.
I'm still alive and well.
More people have been eyeing up
my treasured shop lately, haven't they?
Tae-sang, you...
Look what you've done.
You didn't have to close up shop.
I was only gone for a few days.
No wonder they got the wrong idea.
Are...
Are you all right?
Of course I am.
You're not hurt?
Of course not!
Fool!
If you're okay,
then what took you so long?
Did you enjoy giving this old woman
a heart attack?
You heartless boy!
Hey, I'm sorry.
I had my reasons!
So calm down, Mrs. Nawol.
I said I was sorry.
Enough of this.
You should go and fetch Mr. Gu now.
Where is he?
Get up.
No! I won't go!
Get out!
Master Jang!
Wait here.
Stop right there!
Where do you think you're going?
Is that Jang from Golden Treasure?
I'm here to see Commissioner Ishikawa.
Hey, you! Are you ignoring me?
Go tell him I'm here.
You insolent bastard!
Swinging a fist at someone
who's come to have a conversation
is what thugs do.
If you're a police officer,
why don't you act like one?
You caused a bigger scene than I expected.
Only because you told me to do
whatever it took.
So,
what did you do with the Joseon people
you helped escape?
Which Joseon people are you referring to?
Like I said, I'm here as a representative
of the Bonjeong Merchants Association.
I'm asking you to release
the wrongfully imprisoned merchants.
No less than ten violations
were committed that night.
Loud singing, jazz-playing,
violation of public order
and security regulations, et cetera.
Let's settle this with a fine.
Do you think money
will fix this situation?
It's the cleanest and easiest way,
isn't it?
And if I refuse?
Then all businesses in Bonjeong
will close up starting today.
You know that the fundraising party
for the war effort will be held
in two days.
All deliveries of food and drinks
to the party will be stopped.
Plus, all the officials and their wives
who have put in orders for their garments
will not be able to receive them in time.
When that happens,
the authorities will begin to investigate.
That would put you in a tight spot,
would it not?
Is that a threat?
When there comes a time
for the weak to be strong,
we do something called "unite."
We are simply doing what we can do
in light of the situation.
Know your limits.
Don't risk your life
for matters that don't concern you.
I learned an important lesson
from my visit to Ongseong Hospital.
When you need to risk your life,
you go all in.
If you hesitate to do so,
you'll end up dead.
I know the prime suspects
in this incident.
Jang Tae-sang
of the House of Golden Treasure,
Yoon Chae-ok the sleuth, and...
a Joseon courtesan named Akiko.
Miss Akiko?
Are you okay?
Do you have reasons to believe
that they are suspects?
The suspects I've just mentioned
all entered Ongseong Hospital
and then escaped.
What exactly happened at the hospital?
I'm not inclined
to divulge that information.
It's a military secret.
Akiko.
Aki...
What in the hell...
Tell me.
What went on in there?
What exactly is happening
inside Ongseong Hospital?!
As you know,
the price for my information
is quite steep.
And confidentiality
about Ongseong Hospital
is considered to be
of the highest level, you know.
I can only hand over such information
when enough trust has been built.
Are you trying to strike a deal?
Mr. Ishikawa!
I'm trying to talk about mutual trust.
I have already kept my promise
and returned Akiko to you.
Now it's your turn.
Release my people.
Get out!
You're all released!
Released! We're free!
Master Jang...
You're alive?
Can you stand up?
What took you so long?
Let's get out of here first.
Come on.
Bonjeong!
Do you all want to die?
Be quiet!
Bonjeong.
- Mori.
- Yes!
Commissioner, sir.
Keep Jang under close observation
from now on.
Pardon? Again, sir?
Understood, sir.
MILITARY WARD, UNDERGROUND LAB
HUMAN EXPERIMENTS, LADY MAEDA
LADY MAEDA
Don't worry too much. He'll be all right.
I owe Mr. Gu too great a debt.
Hardly.
I can't even count
all the times you saved his life.
He just repaid you for one of them.
The aftermath of torture...
lasts a while, huh?
You should go now.
No, I'll stay here.
There is someone else waiting for you.
She came by every single day
to check whether you had returned safely.
Leave Mr. Gu to me.
Go pay her a visit.
Aren't you having dinner?
I'm not hungry.
You go and eat.
Should I grab some dumplings for you?
I'll be right back.
Who are you?
You're still as aggressive as ever.
Now that you've seen my face,
will you let me go?
Master Jang...
I felt the same way.
I also...
missed you a lot.
Did you have something to say?
Tell me.
How much do you know
about the underground laboratory
in Ongseong Hospital?
Are you even remotely aware
of what exactly is going on there?
There is nothing I don't know about.
What have you done to Akiko?
I asked you what you did to her!
You seem to be mistaken.
You have no right to ask me such things.
And I have no obligation to answer you.
What's that now?
From the beginning, our relationship
was formed for mutual benefit.
I needed a husband
so I could come to Joseon.
And you needed my good name and lineage
to move up and succeed.
You suddenly assuming
the role of my husband like this
puts me in an awkward position,
Mr. Ishikawa.
You shouldn't have touched Akiko.
And you had no need
to send Mr. Jang in there.
We agreed not to interfere
in each other's personal lives.
You're the one who broke the agreement
in the first place!
I respect what you do for a pastime.
But having a child
is a completely different story.
Did you know that Jang Tae-sang
found himself a woman?
A Joseon woman named Yoon Chae-ok.
Apparently, she's young and pretty.
How unfortunate for you.
All that effort nursing him back to health
was absolutely in vain.
Here are your dumplings.
Let's get going.
What a fool!
Stop.
Go... go away!
Get away from me!
Myeong-ja?
So, these are the Najin?
Correct.
They were found inside the glaciers
of Muryong Snow Mountain,
where the Na people live.
And you're saying
that this enters the human brain
to create creatures like Seishin?
No.
With Najin alone,
it only turns them into predators.
While retaining the appearance of a human,
they will hold only the survival
and hunting instincts ,
and prey primarily on human brains.
Highly aggressive and more violent
than most predatory animals,
they can move quickly
and heal wounds almost immediately.
Then why does Seishin
appear the way she does?
Because she was injected with a serum
that contained anthrax.
Once injected with this serum
during their predatory stage,
they will move on to Seishin's phase.
Do they have any weaknesses?
They hate sunlight and fire,
and they are weak against nitrogen.
Get a hold of yourself.
Why are you doing this?
Myeong-ja!
How horrid.
To remember what it was like
to be human, even in that state...
Ongseong Hospital.
They must've experimented on her.
A flare was fired from Jongno, sir!
Over there! Get her!
Stop!
Don't lose her. Get her!
Yes, sir!
It was not able to remember at first,
not until it met its daughter.
Daughter?
Seishin has... a daughter?
She snuck in here, looking for her mother
who had gone missing ten years ago.
When it recognized its daughter, it...
flipped a switch, I think.
And her daughter's name is...
Yoon Chae-ok.
She works as a sleuth.
Did you know
that Jang Tae-sang found himself a woman?
A Joseon woman named Yoon Chae-ok.
- Find her!
- Yes, sir!
- This way too!
- Hurry up!
- This way!
- Move!
- Find her!
That way! Get her!
Are you all right?
If she's caught, she might get killed.
No, she will go through much worse.
Like my mother did.
Go after her!
Run!
Catch her!
Go.
Don't kill me...
Please don't kill me!
Please don't...
Hold it!
That way!
Find her!
Don't lose her!
Stop right there!
Don't kill me...
Please don't kill me!
Please don't kill me...
Don't kill me!