­
It's really… What is this feeling? I feel proud.
Wait! My phone!
I think I left it behind. I'll bring it right away.
- Yes.
- Just a moment, one minute!
One minute.
Starting from now, one minute!
It can't possibly be.
It musn't be.
Because the me he sees isn't real.
Ju Yeon, I found it.
I should check.
Let's find out my true feelings about him.
♫  This day ends  ♫
My heart is beating
faster than this person who ran at full speed.
Do I really like this…
♫  Don't lose your light yet  ♫
♫  You are warmer than anyone else  ♫
Do I really like…
Are you okay?
It seems I like him.
Why did you suddenly run over here?
You're not fully recovered yet.
I checked you for arrhythmia or something.
So what is my condition?
You are normal.
What about you?
Then, what about you?
Perfectly, I'm normal.
♫  Even in dreams  ♫
♫  I will protect you  ♫
How often do you change the litter pad?
From time to time.
Do you also care for their nutrition by using organic food?
- Yes.
- Well.
Will Cola come into contact with other dogs during walks?
No, never mind.
Please keep his cleanliness at the highest level
to avoid transferring any harmful substances.
Please hand him over.
It's very troublesome if he catches a disease.
This dog is very shy with strangers.
Keep an appropriate distance from other dogs,
but allow him to socialize with gentle dogs, so he doesn't get intimidated.
Yes, please.
Also, when he sleeps,
he really likes sleeping in someone's arms.
Please hand him over.
You'll leave him in my care for two nights and three days, right?
Ah, Cola looks handsome just like your dad.
- Dear, dear.
- Dad?
Did I hear that wrong? Dad? Who? Me?
Then, are you Cola's big brother?
Big brother…
It's just a mere animal my brother is raising.
- I will go.
- Yes.
- Take the best care of him.
It is an honor to be with the precious heroes of South Korea.
I heard once you get on the coach's bad side, it's over.
That's why you should be careful too.
But I’m sure that together we will overcome any difficulty.
Still, I feel healed thanks to our interpreter.
The Athletes' Village training schedule will be tough, but let's overcome it together.
Without you, I can surely overcome it.
To do so, there are a few things we must adhere to.
What? Did you two already know each other?
- No, I don't know her.
- Oh, you startled me.
Hello.
I am Cha Si On, the youngest ever to be selected to the national team.
Please take care of me.
The atmosphere is too solemn.
I think she just came here to have fun.
Respecting commitments is a minimum requirement in any sport.
Not only did you not show up for the pre-meeting, you were also late for orientation.
Your behavior is unspeakable!
The basis of sports is a promise.
From not showing up for the pre-meeting to being late for orientation,
it's all bad attitude.
Show up at 5:00 p.m. sharp in the Athletes' Village today.
If you are even one minute late, you can give up playing for the national team.
If you are even one minute late at 5:00 p.m. sharp in the Athletes' Village today,
I'll take that to mean that you'll give up playing for the national team.
It's the message from the coach.
Please don't run into him. Please don't run into him.
Please don't run into him. Let's go further.
Oh my, Mr. Lee.
Yes, you are here.
- Have you had a meal?
- Of course.
Have you eaten?
I should treat you sometime.
No, no. I will treat you.
Why do you say that? You're the one who has been through much more.
Oh my. By the way, you look even more dashing today.
Oh, no. It's not.
Ju Yeon. I see.
You were troubled by too much work.
You were lonely because you weren't dating.
Yes, our Ju Yeon. You were lonely.
I see.
Our Ju Yeon was lonely. I see.
I came because I heard there's a crazy woman in the changing room.
But it was you.
Ah, let go. What are you doing?
I already knew it. You need a blind date.
Ah, let go of me, please.
Because I'm practicing mind control.
It was like a mental victory. I see.
By the way, who are you going to set her up on a blind date with? An athlete?
It's a secret, but the players in the Athletes' Village are handsome.
Stop! Stop!
You dressed like this today? Are you going out?
It's cool effortless look!
Since I'm coming here, I dressed up naturally, as if I had not dressed up.
It's obvious that you've put a lot of effort into dressing up.
Player Si On, a player must distinguish between public and private affairs.
Stop nagging me!
Just don't be late for the media day tomorrow.
I myself need a mental victory before the interview.
Well, so speaking of which,
I don't think I necessarily need to go.
Or we can have a video call consultation before the interview.
Well, I'll be on standby 24 hours a day, even in the middle of the night. How about that?
Dr. Kyeong, why are you suddenly like this?
You have to distinguish between work and private life.
Player Si On.
Then let's consult now. The interview is nothing.
There's nothing to fear from the cameras and the reporters.
Don't avoid it, stand up straight. And look right in the eyes! It's too easy. Right?
Hey, little cutie.
Mister!
Right now, with Dr. Kyeong…
Where did she go?
Oh no, I can't look at his face.
Mind control… I'm not flustered at all.
I'm not flustered at all.
Not at all.
It's okay, yeah. It's nothing.
I'm fine.
I'm fine, yes.
- What is fine?
- Oh, you startled me.
What's fine? What is it?
Hello.
- What?
- My mom.
Oh my, awesome.
Be quiet. No, no.
What is it?
It's nothing.
No. Oh my.
I sometimes hear that I resemble a celebrity.
What will happen if those two people become so close
and my brother's memories come back?
Am I still a child? Why do I have to go with my mom?
You are still a child.
You have to get to the Athletes' Village by 5:00, right?
Let's meet at the entrance later, and don't cause any trouble.
Oh, stop nagging me.
I want to go with you.
I don't want to go with my mom?
Hey! You shouldn't say such mean things to your parents.
If you act rudely to your mom, you'll be no good.
She's going with you like this to support you.
You will regret all your unfilial behavior later.
Be good to your mom!
Ah, why does she keep calling me?
- Who is it?
- My mom.
Well…
Sometimes it might be better not to answer than to speak harshly.
I've organized the expected media day questions and the answer guidelines on a USB.
Ah, wait.
Looks like I left it in the car. Wait a moment.
Give it to me at the Athletes' Village later. Don't think of not coming.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Really, sir?
If it's the village youth association records, are all the residents who lived there recorded?
That's great.
No, no.
I can go there right away tomorrow.
- The customer is currently on a call…
- Why isn't she answering the phone?
So… that…
What should I suddenly say?
You go to English kindergarten, tell him she's on the phone.
She's busy.
Where is she?
Where? Do you mean where she is?
Well… The stadium?
The national tennis team players.
Tell him she went to the orientation.
Tennis orientation.
Really? Can I have the address?
Address! Address!
The address. She said it's on the back of the schedule.
Here.
All right. Okay, thanks.
Goodbye, yes.
It seems Sae Yan's father sent him. Why doesn't she answer the phone?
Yes, then I'll see you tomorrow.
Yes, thank you.
What are you looking at?
You're here as the coach's interpreter, not as the coach. You understand?
Stop pretending to be a coach.
You acted almost like an Oscar Best Actress winner.
Me?
Do you know me?
Didn't we agree to pretend not to know each other?
It's all for you.
You don't want to see my face either, do you?
Of course.
Hey, you don't know anything. That Athletes' Village is like the military.
You have to stick with me for 24 hours.
Will you be able to have to eat, sleep,
and live together with someone you don't like?
I mean, just seeing your face makes me want to hit you.
The fact that I have to endure it is so annoying.
Just thinking about it is already dreadful.
Right. If you get stressed, you'll get wrinkles here.
Right?
That's why I'm considering it.
What?
I'm already this annoyed, so I wonder how annoyed you must be?
If you work out so hard that you're almost dying,
and your ex is always in front of you 24 hours a day,
not only will you get wrinkles, but you'll also cry.
If I could only block your path, I would sacrifice myself.
Hey, you!
You better think carefully. Okay?
Oh, my. She…
Now, everyone this way.
Load all the big luggage into the luggage compartment.
Now, hop on quickly to the fun Athletes' Village.
- Who gave you permission?
- Oh my.
Oh my.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm not hurt. I'm fine.
My car is over there, so let's go.
Ju Yeon! Ju Yeon!
Please take my car.
- My car.
- No, there's no need for that.
- Is that okay?
- Of course.
Sit next to me, put a tangerine in my mouth,
and talk to me, so I don't fall asleep.
This is some kind of driving date.
Since it's for work, please take my car.
Please take my car.
Take my car.
I'll just…
I'll take the Player Lee Shin's car.
No, that…
Are you all right?
Let me see.
You're fine. You're fine.
See you later at the Athletes' Village.
Oh, Sis. Sis!
Don't get in that car.
Why are you interfering, Interpreter?
She has to go with me.
I don't want to ride in that car.
If you don't want to take the car, ride the bus… Please.
Or take the coach's car… Please!
We will be taking Mr. Lee's car.
That old car. Ah, sorry.
Classic car!
You sent me in a taxi that night, saying you had something to do.
Yeah, a lot happened that night.
Thanks to you, I slept fitfully at night.
Slept fitfully? Why?
What happened?
Come on, let's go together.
No, wait a minute.
Just the two of you?
Ju Yeon has to come with us.
All three of us should go.
Ah, no. No!
Then…
All three of you. Take my car, all of you.
All together?
You must stick close to me.
Even when going to the bathroom. Okay?
What's going on with Mr. Lee? Is there something with him?
There's nothing. That…
You answer the phone. Mom has been looking for you for a while now.
Right! I need to call your mom back.
I'll make a call and go. Take this and go first.
No, stay with me.
What happened?
Why did you sleep fitfully?
You don't need to know.
Huh?
Why did you sleep fitfully?
Did something happen between you and Ju Yeon?
It's because...
your dog marks its territory just anywhere.
I thought it was something serious.
Did you leave Cola safely at the dog hotel?
I don't know. Just take care of your own dog.
Don't bother me.
But you like it, right?
I told you. We can just leave him at the pet hotel.
Kun said he's postponing all his schedules and coming tomorrow night.
Let's leave in two days, shall we?
But what did Kun do at the dog hotel that made them tell him not to come back?
And every time Shin goes to the Athletes' Village,
you don't have to follow him like this.
You received Shin's diet plan, free-time, PT, and Pilates schedule. Right?
Oh my! Shin is not that young. If he follows that schedule, his body will just…
I've made sure to check with the team members that he started his weight control.
And you rushed to renewhis contract with the agency
without even consulting me. Right?
I suppose it's better if I take care of the intense work. Right?
Let me handle this… How can you keep digging up herbs like this every time?
Do I just turn it like this?
Oh, my gosh.
There's no strength in the sound.
Here, take a bottle of this and drink it.
Why aren't you answering the phone?
Some foreigners that I guess your parents sent came looking for you.
So what did you say to them?
Please tell them I ran away or that I was missing.
Just tell them I'm dead.
If I get caught, I can't come back to Korea again.
What? I told them you went to orientation.
I gave them the official document from the association.
Oh, my gosh. When?
Ju Yeon, please get in.
Ju Yeon.
Sae Yan, let's go!
Get in. Hurry up and get in.
Then, I'll take the front seat.
- Get in now.
- You drive…
Get in!
Hey!
Hey, this is a new car.
You need to drive well.
Sae Yan, what's going on?
Ju Yeon, please fasten your seatbelt.
Oh, I'll take care of mine.
You don't need to do this for me.
That's my seatbelt.
Oh no! What should we do?
Skinship!
No, no. Skinship is not allowed!
What? Who are those people?
Wait, Sae Yan. Drive slowly!
Sae Yan! Sae Yan!
Someone in front!
This is driving me crazy.
It seems I've probably missed the golden time.
Is everyone okay?
Shall we get going then?
Slowly, safe driving! Slowly.
You got startled, huh?
If we're late, I'll get fired.
You have to be alive to get fired.
I'm alive, right?
We almost got hurt.
Besides, do you know how dangerous it is to sit in the middle?
Sis, are you hurt?
Look in front!
I have a bit of a headache.
You got startled.
What driving license did you get, bumper cars?
You did that on purpose to finish me off, right?
No. If I wanted to finish you off, I would have done it when I was alone with you.
Do you two know each other?
- No!
Sorry, sorry. From now on, I'll drive safely.
The more I struggle to get out, the more I feel like I'm sinking in.
All my attention is focused on this person.
No more, romance is not allowed.
Ju Yeon, you don't look well?
Hold on.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
I have a headache and feel a bit nauseous. Maybe it's motion sickness.
I think I'll feel better after some sleep.
- Ju Yeon.
- Here.
- Ah, thank you.
Let's avoid meeting as much as possible.
Don't look, and don't listen.
I'd rather sleep.
Who were those people chasing us earlier?
They were people sent by my father.
My family is a bit strict.
If I get caught, I won't be able to return to Korea again.
Why did you decide to run away from home and stay in Korea?
I'm trying to find someone I desperately miss.
- Someone you desperately miss?
- Ah, I'm hungry!
I guess my blood sugar dropped because I was startled earlier.
The next rest area sells amazing sausage and rice cake skewers.
Rice cake skewer?
I heard Ju Yeon, whom our interpreter dotes on,
say her favorite snack is sausage and rice cake skewers.
Oh my. She's not even a child.
Really? Then we should go if it's her favorite snack.
Right?
And actually, the fuel light has been on for a while too.
- Huh?
- Yes.
Even plants propagate.
It seems like Nurse Song might like me,
or maybe she doesn't.
It would be nice if I could get a hint.
Nurse Song, please send me a signal.
­
I love you not because I love you,
but because I cannot help it.
Oh my! Why did he leave quotes in the group chat?
Professor Han is indeed an old man.
It's such a poetic and heart-fluttering phrase.
Her sensibilities match mine so well.
Now.
Let's go have lunch at a place with a nice atmosphere today.
Really?
Pasta?
Lobster?
No, no.
A herbal whole duck soup restaurant with a yard!
Oh my!
Lately, my body has felt quite weak.
I'll really nourish my body well today.
She has good tastes that match mine.
I really like houses with such yards.
I want to live in such a place.
Don't you think so, Professor Han?
Does she mean she wants to live in such a place with me?
Is this a signal?
Does she like me?
Will I finally be able to propagate?
Well, let's go eat.
Call Te Oh, too.
- I have eaten well.
I can afford this much.
Professor, it was truly delicious.
- I have eaten well, Professor.
- No, no.
Everyone, go out and get some fresh air.
We'll go out first.
- I have eaten well.
- The check, please.
Thank you.
By any chance, are there coffee candies?
No, my woman…
No, my crush really likes them.
Please try looking there.
Ah, it's not here.
Coffee flavor!
- Thank you.
- Yes, thank you.
Come to think of it, you and Professor Han are wearing couple outfits.
Couple outfits?
For some reason, you and Professor Han seemed
like a loving married couple.
With the elderly?
Elderly?
You're wearing similar colors.
I think I should just throw this outfit away.
I was kind to him because he reminds me of my late father.
Huh? Your father?
Ah, a married couple? That really upsets me.
It's my first time seeing Nurse Song angry.
It's understandable to be angry. Aren't they a generation apart?
You went too far.
No, that's not it.
Nurse Song.
Let's go.
She thought of me like a father, not like a romantic relationship…
Driving in Korea made me tense, and now I'm tired.
I'll take over the driving from now on, Interpreter.
Everyone, go to the restroom and come back.
You too, our hardworking interpreter, go and come back from the restroom.
I'm fine. I have a big bladder.
Everyone, don't be late.
If you guys are late, everyone from athletes to staff will be fired.
Then, I'll go buy some snacks.
Oh, wait a minute. Just a minute.
Let's each buy something delicious.
All right.
All right, here.
Everyone takes ten thousand won.
All right, get off. Let's go! To buy something delicious to eat.
Please go buy some snacks.
- Hey.
- Why?
Watch your mouth.
If you do that, it'll be obvious that we dated for a little while.
It's not obvious that we dated briefly,
but I can't hide that I hate you.
Sorry.
So you're not going to the rest stop, right?
Ah, that's great. I saved my money then.
For whose benefit?
Move aside.
Oh, it's cold.
You! Oh, it's cold.
Since I just made ten thousand won, should I go and rest in the car?
Hello.
Please give me four iced Americanos.
No, please give me three.
Here is the receipt.
Hello?
Yes, Sae Yan's father.
Your daughter is with me.
Yes.
No, no, no!
I'm not dating her again. Please just take her home.
Yes.
We are at…
Come to your senses, Kyeong Ju Yeon.
Why on earth are you doing this, huh?
Why did you buy this jelly?
No, I bought it because I wanted to eat it.
I really like jelly.
I love it.
I like jelly the best in the world.
How much is it?
It's 2,000 won.
She's feeling nauseous, and she has a stomachache.
- Motion sickness?
- Yes. She also has a bit of a headache.
She slept with the clothes over her head.
Oh, a cold?
She's been a bit sensitive with me all day long.
And she got a bit irritated with me.
Oh, I guess it's not you, but your girlfriend?
A girlfriend?
Well, we're not an official couple yet.
But we're in a similar kind of relationship.
Did she have a fever?
Is there any possibility of pregnancy?
Pregnancy?
No, I mean, if she gets pregnant just because I hugged her once,
then all the people in the world…
Please give me motion sickness pills, cold medicine, and painkillers.
- It's 10,000 won.
- Okay.
- If I exclude this, it's 8,000 won. Right?
- Yes.
Here it is.
Yes, thank you.
- Thank you.
- Take care.
Is it a delicious restaurant? I happen to have 2,000 won left.
Let's just go. We need to hurry now.
No, it will be quick. There's only one person in front of me.
All right then, you have to come back quickly.
Yes, I'll be there soon.
Oh no, I'm going to miss the bus at this rate.
Then go ahead and order first.
Oh my. Thank you, young man.
Please give me 50 of these.
50?
Jeon Sae Yan, you're no longer in my life now.
Ju Yeon? Ah, I need to be quiet.
Right, everything will be perfect once my brother arrives.
Okay.
Good, good.
What? Why did he come with Jeon Sae Yan?
Ah, right, whatever.
He's not staff, so he'll manage to come on his own.
Oh my, oh my, excuse me! I'm over here!
Yes, goodbye.
Ju Yeon!
- What's going on?
- You also didn't get in the car?
Why did they leave us out and depart?
Wait! Let me make a call.
Oh, right.
Ah, my phone is in that car. You try calling.
Hold on. Just a moment.
Don't have it?
Seriously, just stay still.
Public phone booth…
Do you happen to have your wallet?
I don't.
Sorry, this is all for you.
Hello.
This is Kyeong Ju Yeon. Did you leave us behind?
Oh dear, I'm sorry. We were in a hurry so I went ahead with Ju Yeon…
Ju Yeon?
What? Have we already arrived?
Hey, why are you here!
What did he say? Give it to me.
Hey, Lee Shin. You come back right now.
What? Where is everyone?
What did you say?
What? Where?
A resort…
A resort?
Okay, just wait there for now.
Yes.
- The resort, here?
- Yes.
Yeah, the truth is I was going to leave without you!
- So what are you going to do?
- Are you trying to get me fired?
Lee Shin!
I'm a national representative.
Do you know how much I'm worth?
I work for the country, you know?
Why do you keep interfering in my life?
If you keep doing this, I won't stay still.
Why do you keep appearing and interfering in my life?
You're the one who suddenly barged into my life and caused a mess!
This bracelet, I'm going to cut off the bracelet.
Let that go.
Why don't you let go first?
How can I trust you? You let go first.
Then let's let go on the count of three.
One.
Two.
Three!
Are you doing well there?
Yes.
Don't worry. I won't lose you.
You said it would be faster if we take the shortcut.
You said it would take 30 minutes, but it's already…
What's wrong? Are you in pain again?
I have some over-the-counter medicine.
Really? That's a relief. I was in so much pain, so I almost cried.
Knowing you might be in pain, I went to the pharmacy earlier.
You have a band-aid, right?
My heels have been peeling and bleeding since a while ago.
Band-aid…
What I have with me now is just… cold medicine and…
Just cold medicine and motion-sickness pills.
Medicine for menstrual cramp…
There is no band-aid. You didn't buy the most common thing.
Let's just go.
- Well…
- I'm fine.
Take a rest before we go.
Player Lee Shin must be waiting, so we should hurry.
Are you…
Are you that worried about Shin?
Yes, I'm worried about him.
If Player Lee Shin is late, Sae Yan will be late too.
If Player Lee Shin doesn't join the team, Si On won't be able to join, either.
If that happens…
Don't make me talk.
Why…
Why have you been like this all day?
You are sensitive and avoid me, and don't even make eye contact…
You don't even look at my eyes. Are you angry with me?
No.
Is there something I did wrong?
- No…
- Well, then.
Is it because of what happened that night?
As a doctor, I examined you because I was worried. What's wrong with that?
It's been too hard, so I've become a bit sensitive.
Let's take a rest a bit before we go.
Let's do that.
Aren't you tired?
I'm tired.
Let's take a rest here for a bit before we go.
Now.
It's not a ring.
What are you talking about? I thought you were going to kneel and apologize.
Even if there is no band, let's disinfect it.
I won't do it now. I'll do it later.
Let me see.
You're pretty hurt.
It makes me sad.
I'm okay.
I'm not okay.
If you disinfect, I'll give you a gift.
What gift…
Ta-da!
Even with this?
Sausage and rice cake skewer.
Oh my!
If you don't like it, then never mind.
Just a moment.
Okay, then let's start the disinfection!
Oh, no. It must hurt.
You're bearing it well.
Ah, you're bearing it well.
Please.
You're acting like a crybaby.
This isn't that painful.
Huh, what? Are you crying now?
I'm not crying.
You're crying.
There are tears in your eyes.
I'm not crying.
You said you've never cried in your life, but you're quite the crybaby.
If that's not tears, then what is it?
Look, look! I didn't cry.
Now I can finally see you properly.
Your eyes.
Okay, the disinfection is done.
Eat.
Yes.
I had no intention of cutting it, but what's so great about this bracelet?
Life in the Athletes' Village seems like it'll be bleak from now on.
Okay, okay.
It's done. It's done.
It's a little short, but it's okay.
By the way, where is she? Why isn't she coming back?
Is she very angry?
Yeah, but it's okay because I made this.
Lee Shin, you deceitful jerk.
Go to hell.
But I came up here in a fit of anger,
but where on earth am I now?
What is this?
Are there snakes here?
Oh, that startled me.
She left her cellphone behind.
She is so bad with directions.
Why can't you do something right?
Jeon Sae Yan! Jeon Sae Yan from Napoli!
If I find you, I won't stay still.
I don't even have a cellphone.
What? Isn't this the place I came earlier?
Ju Yeon.
Hey!
You have to find me. Why are you looking for Ju Yeon?
Why are you only coming now! I almost got bitten by an anaconda!
If you're glad to see me again, just say it's nice to see me.
And are we in the "Amazon"? Why would there be an anaconda?
You look like the kind of person who would soak an anaconda alive in alcohol and drink it.
If you had come any later, I'd have buried you alive here.
Now you're finally showing your true colors.
If you keep doing that, you climb down alone.
To make the snakes come out, I guess I should call them.
Hey, shut up! Shut up!
You are as cunning as a fox.
Then, why are you trying to work where I am?
What's the reason you insist on working?
If you stick with me, we'll just fight.
If I stay there, it'll be easier to ask around, and I'll have a reason to stay in Korea.
Right, did you find that out?
You said there might be someone you know in the countryside.
But that wasn't the place.
Right?
You can't possibly be of any help to my life.
I guess I need to mobilize all my connections now.
I'll ask Ju Yeon unnie, or I heard your brother is the CEO. So I'm sure he knows a lot of people.
Why? You saw a snake? Where is it?
There?
I want to go to the bathroom.
I think there's a bathroom if we go a little further.
No, no. My stomach hurts.
You go there and keep a lookout.
Keep a lookout.
Wow, seriously.
- You're impossible to deal with.
- Go further. Go further.
Oh, that's enough. There.
Oh my, my stomach hurts so much.
Really?
I'm giving this to you. Eat it.
What's this?
You want me to eat this while smelling your poop?
Just eat it.
Oh, right.
Just in case.
You take all of this.
What's this?
And you also left your phone behind.
Right.
And since the caretakers come by here frequently, don't worry too much.
There is a large temperature difference in the mountains.
What are you doing?
How long will it take to poop? Are you constipated?
I held my poop in for a long time.
Do you see that red ribbon tied to that tree over there?
Having red ribbons like that on the trees makes it look totally like Christmas.
Did you tie it?
No, I didn't do it.
Mountaineers tied them there, so we wouldn't get lost.
There's one over there too.
If by any chance you are left alone in the mountains.
- You know?
- Yes.
Keep watch here quickly. I will answer the call of nature. Okay?
Turn around, turn around.
Are you seriously…
Are you really about to… Are you seriously going to poop right here?
Yeah.
What are you doing? Let's just go to the restroom.
Hey, I'm really going to poop. I unbuttoned it and unzipped it, so don't look.
Don't do it. I hate it. I really hate it.
Is this how parents feel when they leave their children behind?
No, no, no.
Yeah, you'll feel better if I'm not looking for you.
This is for the good of everyone.
This is the recreation forest near the rest area.
I'll send you the location, so you can come this way.
Okay.
Are Kun and Ju Yeon coming?
Hey, you stepped in poop. Right?
Hey, I think something bit me.
I feel like a snake has bitten me.
Hey, what should we do? There was a sign back there saying that snakes come out.
Hey, hey.
Then, call 911 quickly, hurry!
Yes, this is near the walking trail by the recreational forest.
We climbed up about 20 minutes.
I think he was bitten by a snake. What should I do?
30 minutes?
Hey, since I can't see it, you take a look.
No, are you crazy?
No, not my butt, higher up. Higher! Hurry!
Hey, I actually haven't even pooped.
Then, I'm sorry, but please come as quickly as possible.
Yes, yes. I'm sorry.
They might not be able to find this place.
I'll go and bring them here. Okay?
I think I'm dying now.
I've never lived my life the way I wanted.
And I haven't properly fallen in love yet.
Dying while pooping in the mountains?
Don't publish an obituary.
At least I want to be remembered by people as an honorable person.
It might not be a venomous snake.
Now.
You said there's a big temperature difference in the mountains.
And.
Thank you. I only have you.
You'll feel a bit better now.
It's good.
This is tasty.
I can't believe that my last supper in life is chocolate.
It's so cold.
It seems the poison is spreading through my body.
I'll go and get someone to suck out your snake's venom.
No, no.
Don't leave me alone.
I don't want to die alone. No, no.
There will surely be a male caretaker nearby.
If not, I'll go find a wild man.
Hey, it looks like I'm being punished for my bad deeds.
What?
Actually, I contacted your dad to come pick you up.
What? You!
Forgive me.
It's gotten much shorter, but you have thin wrists.
And,
I know the person you're looking for.
Really? How do you know my real dad?
Real dad?
You said you know the person I'm looking for?
I'm looking for my dad.
Not your first love?
Who is my first love?
Jeon Sae Yan.
The poison is spreading.
Lee Shin, you can't die. Pull yourself together.
Hey, Lee Shin, are you okay?
Ah, seriously.
Hey, Lee Shin.
It's not a snake bite. It's a bee sting.
If you don't have any specific allergies, there shouldn't be a problem.
But your guardian is quite remarkable.
You thought he was bitten by a snake, and you sucked out the poison for him.
Then, we'll get going.
- Thank you.
Sae Yan, what happened?
Nothing happened.
What on earth are you two up to?
Why did you just leave us at the rest area?
And what happened here so that an ambulance came?
What's up? What happened?
What's wrong?
We're out of gas.
What?
I mean…
I told you earlier that I needed to fill up with gas.
What should we do? We need to be there by 5:00.
See! See!
I knew this would happen.
Are they the only ones who haven't come yet?
Oh, seriously.
We only have 30 minutes left.
Ah, these guys.
The line is busy…
Oh my, they're on a call again.
The line is currently…
Ah, these guys are driving me crazy.
Aren't we going to be late?
How could you forget to refuel?
It's Guk Bong again.
What will happen to us by the time the tow car arrives?
We'll be kicked out one by one.
If Lee Shin can't get there, little cutie will also be out of the team.
Then there's no need for a team doctor.
Hey, little cutie.
Cha Si On?
Coach. Yes, I'm talking to you!
If they are late again today, you’ll be the first to go!
Okay, okay! I can do it.
Come on. Move, move!
They are here.
She came here. He came here.
No problem. It's okay?
It feels like a month has passed even though nothing has started yet.
Come quickly, hurry.
That's a relief.
You still have a lingering attachment to the sport, right?
You can be honest.
Let's go.
Is this where you want to stop by?
Do you remember?
The place where we first met.
15 years ago.
The place where you saved me.
A place where memories with you are preserved intact.
You asked if I was okay. Right?
You also asked if I had no more regrets about you.
I'm trying to show my feelings now.
I'm trying not to lie to myself or you anymore.
I will reveal and show everything...
more proudly and confidently.
I…
I can't do that.
I don't have the right to do that.
I'm sorry.
That's a lie.
Look into my eyes and say it.
If that's the truth,
look into my eyes and say it clearly.
You are such a fool.
Even if you deceive me,
don't lie to yourself.
Let's stop pretending...
we're okay.
♫  You light a small light in a corner  ♫
♫  Of my heart that I had ignored  ♫
♫  Where will it be, that day  ♫
♫  How much further do I have to go before I can see  ♫
♫  Even if that unreachable dream  ♫
♫  Turns away from me and becomes more blurred  ♫
♫  I will walk towards that day  ♫
Even if everything changes, there are some things that don't change.
If it's okay with you, we…
Don't even think about sneaking in some skinship.
What are the side effects? I need to figure that out, so I can steal the research.
Now I'm in big trouble.
There's nothing we can do. We're already in the same boat.
I sent something important yesterday.
Jealousy is also a natural emotion.
I feel like I'm going to die of embarrassment.
I've come this far by deceiving people.
I feel like I'm about to be exposed as just someone who's only flashy on the outside.
Mr. Lee, are you okay?
Let's admit it together and be honest.
If you want to love, don't hold back for a moment.