[Previously]
I know it's dangerous here.
Stay with me.
You shouldn't go out anywhere yet until we catch the culprit, alright?
And what if you can't catch the culprit?
Then stay here… indefinitely.
[Pha Pun Dao School]
I think…
Torfun has picked this time for me.
Isn't this... the car that hit Torfun?
Pour your heart into pouring the water and receiving the blessing.
(Pali chanting for merit transference to the deceased and blessings)
[Torfun Chareonpon | Born: 21st April 1997 | Died: 9th April 2020]
Torfun, I have become a volunteer teacher now,
I probably won't be able to bring you flowers for a while.
I really don't know…
What exactly you want me to leave to me,
but I believe…
That it's in Pha Pun Dao, right?
Wish me luck, alright?
I'll be leaving now.
♫ The story that's been told however many times is still the same ♫
♫ It's that I love you, love you. It has never changed ♫
♫ If perhaps the stars hear the words of the prayers within my heart ♫
♫ No matter how many thousands of times, I'll still ask for my heart to be near you ♫
[A Tale of Thousand Stars]
[Chapter 8]
[Pha Pun Dao School]
Are you ready, Phi?
I don't know.
Phi, you don't need to overthink it, alright?
Phi, just tell everyone
what you had told me.
I believe that everyone will understand.
Su Su.
[T/N: "Fighting" or "Good Luck"]
Have you seen the Chief?
Just now, it was like I briefly saw him for a moment.
I guess he must be talking with my dad.
Thank you so much everyone for coming to celebrate this today.
Our school could be restored successfully
because of the physical effort from everyone,
each and every one of you who worked together,
along with the strong determination of Khru Tian,
who has always been giving his all for this school all this time. Right?
On this occasion,
I'd like to invite Khru Tian to come up and say something,
Just a bit, in honor of our new school. Right? Alright, alright.
A round of applause for Khru Tian, please.
After you, Khru Tian.
Thank you.
I feel very honored
to speak today on the occasion of the reopening of this school.
I feel so very glad to be able to stand right here.
If I could go back to the first day I came here,
I probably wouldn't believe that I would be able to stand here.
Because the truth is,
I didn't intend to come here to be a good teacher.
I came here
because of an unresolved feeling that I had.
[My students: Ayi… He's the oldest kid in the class.]
I thought that... if I could make myself useful here,
what I had been carrying, it might be able to be lightened.
But it turns out…
I kept creating problems each and every day.
But I was lucky that everyone here was able to forgive me.
These bicolored stir-fried veggies, give it a try.
Hey, give it a try.
Everyone gave me a chance,
cared for me, as if I was a member of the family.
It made me realize the value of my life,
it made me know what happiness is,
to the point that it made me feel like... this place was truly my home.
Because this big bird's protecting your village from the mean Green Giant!
Honestly,
I should be satisfied and let go of what I have been carrying.
But the more that everyone is good to me like this,
what I'm carrying becomes heavier.
It's so heavy that I'm not able to carry it any longer.
Everyone,
I almost died once.
And there was a person from here..
that gave me her heart,
allowing me to be able to continue living.
Didn't you say that you didn't know Torfun?
So why do you have Torfun's journal then?
Everyone,
The person who gave me their heart was Khru Torfun.
What?
Khru Torfun has already departed from us.
- Are you serious?
- What's that?
Khru Torfun died?
And I am the one...
who made Khru Torfun die.
Why, Tian?
Why did you have to lie to us?
Is Khru Torfun really dead?
We are so disappointed in you.
Why did you lie to us? Why did you deceive us?
Is this true?
Why did you make us like you and then you did this to us?
Everyone is really upset.
Khru!
I think you should go home for today. No one is coming.
Chang, you can go ahead and return first.
I would like to wait a little longer.
Aai Seetian!
How are you, Meejoo?
And...what about Ayi?
Mom said not to come, but I snuck out.
I missed you, Aai Seetian.
I also missed you.
So, what do you want to learn today? Hmm?
What does "death" mean?
Mom said, you had caused Miss Torfun's death.
Grandma…
The school restoration is already complete.
The arsonists have also already been caught.
So there's no longer any reason for you to stay here.
You don't need to give me a ride then.
Thank you for letting me stay with you.
From now on, if you need anything, go tell Chang or Ai Rang, alright?
Everyone here is very disappointed in you.
Just leave.
I don't want to see your face again.
Leave that here.
Just the heart that you took from her...
is already more than enough.
My honest feelings are... if it were possible,
I'd like to return it to her as well.
[Phaphirun Unit]
This is Phupha speaking.
It's me.
Have you lost your mind?
What now, Ai Mor?
The thing about Nong Tian, of course.
I told you that so that you could find a chance to ask him about it.
I did ask him.
By dragging it out of him in front of everyone like that?
Just that was nothing compared to what Torfun had to face.
Seriously, dude.
Isn't you doing something like this too harsh?
Huh? Ai Phu!
- How was it, Rang?
- I didn't see anyone.
Khama...
Ah, Khru Tian, did you need something?
Is Longtae here?
I brought his shirt to return to him.
Longtae, I... haven't seen him since this morning.
I guess he probably went to help them pick the tea leaves.
How about this then? Khru you can leave it with me.
I'll give it back to Longtae when he comes, alright?
- Sound good?
- Okay.
Thank you, Khama.
Yes, Khru...
Longtae... Come look at these caterpillars, Son.
They came to eat my flowers and leaves,
so most leaves have bite marks.
Do you want me to go get pesticides then?
No, how can you kill them, Son?
Did you know,
These caterpillars, although they eat some of my flowers and leaves,
but once they grow up, they'll become butterflies.
and they'll return and help with the pollination process with the flowers
they might return to reproduce my flowering plants further.
And just think about it,
if you were a flower,
would you be angry and hold a grudge against the caterpillars?
Really think about it, son.
Everyone here is very disappointed in you.
Just leave.
I don't want to see your face again.
P' Torfun is the one that made me want to enter college.
She was the only person who believed that I could do it.
And she was even the person who went to talk to my dad for me too.
I'm really sorry, Longtae.
P' Tian,
I want to know what exactly happened to P'Torfun that day.
My team has already patrolled from here to here.
We also found some tools that had been left behind.
They should have known that the route to Pha Pun Dao cliff
is a route that we patrol frequently.
So why the hell did they still think of using this route?
Chief, Sir.
The other day, Ai Choak's team saw traces of truck wheels,
but none of the trees were cut down.
I think that it's pretty strange, sir.
This could be their plan to distract our attention.
Anyway, during this time, I'd like everyone to monitor especially closely.
Especially the route to Pha Pun Dao cliff.
If you find anything suspicious, report it to me immediately.
- Does everyone understand?
- Understood!
- Go.
- Go! Go! Go!
Ai Chang! Here!
- Ai Noi, take this! Aai!
Let's go! Hurry!
Ai Phu, where is Nong Tian?
I had him go back to the teacher's house already.
Why the hell are you being so hasty?
If you came to talk about this, then I don't have time for it.
Ai Phu!
And what if I told you that Nong Tian wasn't the one who killed Nong Torfun?
Would you have time to talk to me then?
How could it not be?
Here.
In here are documents about Nong Tian's heart transplant surgery
and also documents regarding Nong Torfun's organ donation.
It's also recorded though that Nong Torfun got hit by a car at 1 a.m.
So what the hell about it?
Dude! But Tian got sent to the hospital around midnight though!
So that means that there's no way that Nong Tian was driving the car that hit Nong Torfun!
[Medical Certificate for Heart Transplant Patients]
[...required a heart transplant due to myocarditis]
[April 9, (00:15 a.m.)]
If you didn't hit her, Phi... then who hit her?
That bastard will soon learn that he shouldn't mess with my friend.
He doesn't know what your car can do, right?
Tian,
I don't think this is going to work anymore.
Just cancel it.
If I back out I'd be a chicken then,
right?
Ai Prem,
you can take care of him for me, right?
Sure I can. Easy.
Then go for it,
if you win against him, then take his damn car.
Deal.
Hey, Ai Tul. I'll be right back, alright?
You're okay, right?
Hey, I'm okay.
Hey, Ai Tian!
Ai Tian!
Hey, Dude!
Tian!
Hey! Tian!
At that time when I was taken to the hospital for heart transplant surgery...
That night, it was Nong TIan's friend who drove the car that hit Nong Torfun.
And he used money to silence this case.
Nong Torfun's aunt admitted it to me herself.
Hey, Ai Phu!
Then why didn't you tell everyone the truth, Phi? That you didn't do it?
For me... it's not important who was the one that hit her.
Because in the end, I'm the one who gave the weapon that hurt Torfun either way.
You are right.
P'Tian,
can I punch you?
So we'll be even.
Go ahead.
Geez!
That was for not revealing the whole truth to me.
We are even now, alright?
Thanks.
But I'm not sure if other people will understand you like I do.
Just this... makes me happy as it is.
So what are you going to do next, Phi?
I think that...
there probably won't be anyone who'd want to send their kids to study with me anymore.
Does that... Does that mean you're going back then?
Not at all. I can't go back yet.
There's still one more matter that I still have to do for Torfun.
I'm going to go up to make a wish at Pha Pun Dao cliff.
And did you already know, Phi, what P'Torun wanted to wish for?
I don't know.
And there will probably never be a day where I'd know either.
The Chief already took the journal away.
But I think that no matter what Torfun would've wished for,
I'd still go up and make a wish for her...for her wish to come true.
But, Phi, if you need me to help with anything, tell me. Alright?
You don't need to tell me. I was about to ask anyway.
Longtae, take me to Pha Pun Dao cliff.
I'm going to go up at the end of the year. That way I'll remember the way.
That might not be a good idea, Phi.
The villagers just got haunted there.
Joma also ordered everyone not to enter the forest
until the guardian spirits of the forest and mountain forgive us, Phi.
I'm going to Pha Pun Dao cliff, not Ghost Hill or anything.
Come one. Help me out a bit.
Consider it as doing it for P' Torfun.
Fine then, Phi.
So...
when do you want to go there?
Right now.
What?
Let's go right now. Nothing is certain anymore.
I want to go there as soon as possible.
Okay, Phi, I understand.
Then let me go back and get a flashlight from home first.
Phi, wait for me here, alright?
Ai Choed, I've checked that no one is following us.
What if a ghost is following us?
Don't say that.
Come on. We need to hurry or else we won't be able to deliver the stuff in time.
I'm scared of ghosts, too. Damn it.
Please warn everyone not to go to Ghost Hill.
The spirit there is very vicious.
Choed, come here. Who helps you feed your kid?
I let Saeng take care of that. I'd rather finish this job.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Let's go.
Is that a human?
Come on, who would dare to get in here?
Hey, if it's a person then we're screwed.
Hurry up. We are late.
Let's go, let's go.
Hey!
- Longtae!
- Phi, I told you to wait outside―
Keep it down!
Why?
Because I saw Toa and Choed sneaking into the forest,
so I followed them in of course.
- Phi, are you sure?
- Yeah.
Right now, no one would dare to enter the forest, especially those two.
Exactly! That's why it's even more suspicious.
I have a gut feeling that something bad is going to happen though.
If... If that's really the case, shouldn't we go get the Chief first?
It's already too late.
If we don't hurry and follow them now, we'll end up losing them.
I don't want anything bad to happen to the village anymore.
- Are, are you serious, Phi?
- I'm serious.
Come on. Let's go.
But that's the way to Ghost Hill.
Yeah, just come already.
Phi, wait up!
Tian.
They are shrewd, I'll give them that.
They know the villagers are too afraid to come here,
so they're using this place to store their illegal goods.
Phi, what do think is inside there?
This place must be their storehouse before they sell it off across the border.
Is that Por Liang?
Why can't I be right when buying the lottery like I am with this?
With such a big matter like this, shouldn't we go get the Chief, Phi?
By the time we go there and get here,
Those guys will probably already happen to run away with their goods.
P-Phi, what are you doing?
At the very least, we'll have evidence incriminating them.
Shit!
- Run!
- Get him!
Khama?
- Khama?
- Yes?
Khama, is Tian here?
Khru, he... stopped by since early this morning and left a long time ago.
Is that so?
Have you gone down to check the waterfall yet?
I went to look already and he wasn't there.
He's not at the school either.
Ai Longtae isn't home either.
Otherwise, I'd have Ai Longtae help you look for him.
So, where did Longtae go?
I don't know either, Chief.
I haven't seen his face since around the afternoon.
I know you guys are hiding around here.
Are you guys going to come out nicely or do you want me to drag your corpses out?
Longtae,
they don't know that there are two of us.
How about this,
Longtae, you go and run first, alright? And take the phone with you.
I'll lure them away for you.
No way, Phi. I'm not leaving you, Phi.
I know.
Hey, Phi! Phi! Phi!
Help me! Help!
Stop!
Hey, Phi, easy. Let's talk about this first.
You run fast, don't you?
Ouch!
Drag him up here.
Well, well.
Look who's here.
In actuality, it's Khru Tian, the hill top teacher with a fiery passion himself.
Last time, it was so fiery that it set the school on fire. Did that not discourage you yet?
Or could be that this time, the entire village needs to be set on fire?
Damn it!
And your cellphone?
I don't have it.
You don't have it, huh?
Do you have it now?
I don't know.
Maybe it fell.
- Do you want me to look for it, Sir?
- No need to.
This area wouldn't have any outsiders enter it anyway.
Just make it so that he can't get out of here to snitch on us.
With that, it'll be finished.
Who'll be finished exactly?
Do you know who I am?
My father is the Permanent Secretary of the Ministry of Natural Resources and Environment.
If anything happens to me,
it's sure to get sticky for you Por Liang.
I can assure you, that if you let me go, Por Liang,
things will definitely go much smoother for you.
I don't give a damn about how powerful your father is.
What a waste of time.
Finish him off.
If anything happens to me, my father won't let you go for sure!
Do you have any idea who the hell you're talking to?
I can guarantee you this, your father won't even know that his son is dead.
Kill him.
Follow and get rid of him!
Let's get out of here. Go!
­
Where are you running off to?
Tian, are you alright?
I'm alright. Chief, are you alright?
I'm alright. Come on, let's go!
Tian!
Chief!
Chief! Chief!
P'Rang!
Chief!
Chief! Chief! Chief!
- Stop the bleeding first!
- Chief!
- Nong Tian, get up first.
Chief! Not yet!
Chief, wake up first!
Chief!
Anyone! Help!
Help!
If I hadn't been here,
Chief, you yourself, wouldn't have to go through the trouble to taking care of me.
But I'm happy to.
I told you already...
I have a duty to take care of you.
Just think of this place as your home, alright?
Let's stay here together for a long, long time.
...forever.
Can you?
Help!
Hornbills are monogamous.
When a hornbill finds its partner,
they will be together for the rest of their lives.
And what if its partner dies?
If its partner dies,
the one that's left will wait for it's partner in the same place until it dies.
[Directed by Noppharnach Chaiwimol]
Hello?
What happened?
And is he safe?
Watch him for me.
I'll go up there as fast as I can.
We've already caught the perpetrators that set fire to the school.
Who are they?
Well, they're Por Liang's men, of course.
As for Por Liang, it's game over for him already.
Right now, the police in pursuit of arresting them.
And also…
there shouldn't be anyone who'd dare to mess with you now.
So... the village should be safe now then.
And you are as well.
Then... I probably don't have any need to inconvenience you any longer, Chief.
Have I ever said that you inconvenienced me?
This place is also... not that far from the school.
There's also water and electricity, ready to be used.
It should be more convenient.
And?
In case you'd like to continue staying here...
Chief, is this a question or an invitation?
We're late. Hurry up and eat.
There's somewhere I need to take you to.
Chief, tell me clearly.
Chief, do you want me to continue staying here?
I do.
I think, that if you stay here,
then you'd probably be able to better prepare your teaching plans.
And also... it would probably be good for the kids too.
Just that?
Well, if I come home
and have someone waiting to give me a massage,
then it'd probably be nice.
Let's eat.
I'm already full.
In that case, I have something to show you.
But you must close your eyes.
What is this, Chief? What are you doing?
Be patient, you'll find out soon enough.
Is it too tight?
It's just right, Chief.
Let's get going. Come on.
[A Tale of Thousand Stars]
♫ You were not the one I was hoping for ♫
♫ And I may not have been the one you were thinking of ♫
♫ From the first time we met, it felt as though we've met before in a dream ♫
♫ My heart flutters when you're close to me ♫
♫ Within a split second of being close to you, my whole world changed ♫
[Preview]
Thank you, Chief.
Thank you for taking such good care of me.
Khru, do you know what's even harder than apologizing?
That thing is... knowing how to forgive yourself.
So, Phi, are you still going to Pha Pun Dao cliff?
I've already done everything that you wanted to do. All that's left is probably this one.
This is the last thing I can do for you to return the favor.
♫ It's that I love you, love you. It has never changed ♫
♫ If perhaps the stars hear the words of the prayers within my heart ♫
♫ No matter how many thousands of times, I'll still ask for my heart to be near you ♫