♪～
(Sena) âŸ¨ Rather than telling someone how you feel â†’
When did it become easier to keep it within yourself?
(Sena) âŸ¨ Rather than my feelings â†’
What does the other person think:
I'm the first to think about itâŸ©
(Sena) âŸ¨If the other person doesn't know â†’
I can't believe I didn't feel that wayâŸ©
âŸ¨ I might not be able to move forward, but â†’
It won't go backwardsâŸ©
âŸ¨ But is that really okay? âŸ©
(Ui) Can't we just start over?
I want to be a family with Sena.
I have no intention of changing Sena's work or life.
I'm rooting for Sena right now.
So even getting married doesn't have to be a quick one â†’
You don't have to live with me.
Even on weekends, Sena and
If I could spend time together with Sakura â†’
I think I'm happy.
(Sena) Ui-kun's feelings are incredibly pleasant.
But I'm sorry.
There's someone I like right now.
(Ui) Are you dating that person?
(Sena) That's not true, but...
(Ui) So then â†’
I don't want to give up yet.
Eat crab.
Hot! Heat... (Sena) Are you okay?
(Chihiro) Even so, I never thought she would be proposed to.
(Yuho) What did you say?
(Sena) I said there's someone I like. (Akiho: Chihiro) Ugh!
That's what I said!
(Sena) Well, Matohara-kun is not dating â†’
I don't really know what you're thinking but...
>>The next thing to be clear: â†’
It's a matter of Matohara's feelings and his ex-girlfriend.
He also said that Ui-senpai proposed to him â†’
"What do you think of me?" I asked.
(Sena) What...
>> If you don't know what to say, you have to blast out â†’
I won't move forever! (Akiho) No doubt.
♪～
(Sena) Good morning. (Madohara) Good morning.
It's early.
(Sena) Matohara-kun has something I want to talk about.
(Madohara) I was also thinking about talking to Koyama-san.
How was your business trip?
(Sena) It worked.
(Matohara) Um...
The night Koyama came to stay again â†’
Sorry I left silently.
(Sena) Don't worry about that anymore.
Sorry I ended up misinterpreting the phone this weekend.
(Matohara) No... I'm sorry, too.
I'm worried about the two of them...
(Sena) Ui-kun told us why he suddenly disappeared eight years ago.
Sakura was the child of the dead brother.
(Matohara) What...
(Sena) Raising Sakura on her own instead of her older brother â†’
It seems it was very difficult.
(Matohara) Was that so?
(Sena) So after that story...
(knock)
(Indigo) Good morning. (Matohara) Ah, good morning.
>> Um... To Madohara-san â†’
Oh... It's a customer.
(Matohara) Customer?
What's wrong, all of a sudden.
(Kanako) Yes, this is the scarf I lent you the other day.
(Matohara) I'm going to go to the trouble...
(Kanako) It's not good if Yu felt cold.
And thank you.
Jan! It's her special lunch box.
(Matohara) What?
(Kozue) She... (Ai) I said she.
(Madohara) Kanako What are you talking about?
>> Well, I'm working again today, good luck.
bye bye.
(Kozue) I used to say they were friends...
Da Kyung... It's scary.
♪～
(Matohara) Sorry, I was in the middle of the conversation.
(Sena) Ugh.
It seems that he called her.
(Matohara) No, I'm my ex-girlfriend.
We've already broken up now...
(Sena) But?
(Matohara) I don't really understand why you're saying that.
(Sena) If they really broke up, wouldn't they have to say it?
(Matohara) That's right... right?
♪～
(Shoko) Sena-chan has something to talk about, right?
Look, hey?
(Sena) Are you talking about a proposal?
>> Proposal!?
(Sena) It's deliberate.
I heard it from Ui-kun, everything. >> What?
(Sena's voice) You've been intentionally bringing us together up until now.
I thought it was weird.
>> Then it's quick to talk.
And what about the proposal?
(Sena) I refused.
>> What are you doing?
I would definitely be happy if I were to become a family with Ui.
(Sena) Mom doesn't decide.
That much of a sudden "Become able to live alone" â†’
Even though I said that...
>> Is it okay? Ui is the president of a listed company â†’
What's more, she's raising Sakura in great detail.
All of the things I thought were terrible were Sena's misunderstandings.
Above all, we've been with you for five years â†’
He knows all Sena's weaknesses and bad points.
It's not the best.
What's your dissatisfaction?
(Sena) It's not that I'm dissatisfied.
>> So what? Are there any other good people too?
(Honoka) Why do I have to be sued?
(Matohara) Please stay calm.
(Sena) Kajino Honoka You are â†’
Representative of the apparel company I lived with for five years â†’
That means that Nagumo Eiji sued him, right?
(Honoka) Yes, we were common-law married.
But last month suddenly â†’
"Let's break up â†’
I'm going to cancel the apartment so please leave."
I couldn't get in touch with him after that, so â†’
I went to work and protested.
But they couldn't take it properly...
If so, then it was at least a common-law marriage â†’
He said he would not be satisfied unless he received the property division.
[Asset division! ã€•
[I'll have you do it]
(Hoka's voice) Then this is...
(Kotori) It wasn't a common-law relationship â†’
You've been filed to confirm it.
(Honoka) I thought I would shut up if I sue her, I'm sure.
Um... sorry but â†’
Why did the two of you get a normal marriage?
Didn't you take it?
He had no intention of getting married.
Maybe they wanted to avoid changing their lifestyle.
My hobby is work, only half the week â†’
He was the kind of person who never came home.
(Matohara) Half of the week?
(Sena) Is there anything that can prove a common-law relationship?
>> This is the apartment where I lived together â†’
This is a rental agreement.
It says me as "wife."
(Sena) I see.
However, this may not be enough.
>> For example, the household finances are the same â†’
There is a resident registration statement.
Or about the two of you â†’
Is there anyone who will testify?
When I moved into this apartment building â†’
I invited a friend to throw a party.
This person, Sakimoto, is a mutual friend â†’
He would have testified about our relationship.
(Sena) If Nagumo testified that he recognized Honoka as his wife â†’
I think there is room for rebuttal.
>> That's good...
I'll contact Sakimoto.
(Kotoriyu) It's like this, isn't it? A common-law marriage.
Separate surnames are possible â†’
It's good that you're not bound by procedures or laws.
(Sena) But when there is a problem â†’
It's difficult to prove whether it's a common-law relationship.
(Kotori) That's right.
Oh Matohara-kun, is there anything you're curious about?
(Matohara) I think that's what the relationship really was like.
Since it is called a common-law relationship, it is the intention of both parties to marry â†’
We need to live together in a married couple, right?
At least it doesn't seem like the other party had a will to marry.
(Hayakawa) The other side is the head of a famous apparel company.
(Hayakawa) If the assets are divided for five years, there is a possibility that the amount could exceed 100 million yen.
Even if it's a lie, I think it would deny common-law relationships.
As expected, those who have had a divorce are different.
(Hayakawa) We haven't had much trouble though.
Yes. >> One-sidedly said goodbye â†’
You don't want to pay and file a lawsuit.
Isn't that person too trash? (Indigo) That's true.
(Matohara) Do you think Koyama-san had a common-law relationship?
(Sena) I don't know.
But there's a rental agreement that says "wife" â†’
There is also a testimony from a friend. (Matohara) That's true, but...
(Sena) It's not easy to prove it, but â†’
I want to be her strength.
>> OK. For now, let's try and proceed in the way Koyama wants.
What could prove a common-law relationship â†’
Will you get a lot of things? (Sena) Yes.
ðŸ“±(Vibration sound)
(Kanako's voice) "I'll go to the store tomorrow night!"
(Matohara) I hope you don't come to work like that all of a sudden.
>> Eh, I wanted to meet you.
(Matohara) What's wrong, from before.
Why are you dating now...
>> [We're still dating, right? ã€•
(Matohara) [What are you talking about, it's already over]
>> [I don't know about that]
(Matohara) [Sorry, I have to go because I don't have time anymore]
>> [Would you leave it even though it's cold?] ã€•
(Matohara) [I'll talk slowly again so I'll go home today]
(Kanako's voice) She wrapped her scarf.
You'll only do that kind of thing for your lover, right?
(Matohara) I just thought it would be bad to catch a cold.
>> Yuu is always kind to me.
Even at university...
(Yasda) [Huh? ã€•
(Yasda) [Ah, ah, ah... Did you cut that? ã€•
[You've got a beautiful muscle right now, right? ã€•
[I... sorry]
(Matohara) [I think it's great though]
♪～
(Kanako's voice) Yu has always helped me.
(Yasda) [The first period after the end of the day] (Matohara) [I understand! ã€•
>> [The second period from Demon! ã€‘ (Matohara) [Really, how long are you talking about it? ã€•
>> [Huh Yasuda-kun] (Yasuda) [Huh? ã€•
[Wasn't it a byte today? ã€ (Yasuda) [No, I'm today...]
[Wow, that's right! The worst I've forgotten it.
(Matohara) [Really? ã€• >> [Dar~]
(Matohara) [Do your best, do your best] >> [This is no longer possible]
[Now] (Matohara) [Toughness]
>> [Sorry~] (Matohara) [Yes, yes]
>> [Yu! ã€‘ (Matohara) [Huh? ã€•
>> [Um...]
[Actually, me â†’
I like Yu.
(Matohara) [Huh? ã€•
>> [Who is the best? ã€•
[Don't you like me? ã€•
(Matohara) [No... I really like it but...]
>> [Really? ã€•
[Then we're lovers from today! ã€•
(Matohara) [Huh? ã€• >> [I'm happy! ã€•
At that time, I was happy to know that we both felt the same way.
(Matohara) No, but...
We talked, let's break up.
[Don't cry] >> [Sound of slurping flowers]
[Because I mean, breaking up...]
(Matohara) [No more, even if we stay together â†’
I'm in Kanako's feelings...
>> [I don't want to hear that]
(Kanako's voice) That story ended in a breeze.
He also met me normally since then.
(Matohara) That's because I thought I could have returned to being friends again...
It's actually Kanako â†’
You don't think you're dating, right?
>> I don't like friends.
I definitely don't want it unless it's her.
I'd never see him again rather than just becoming friends.
Is Yu okay with me gone?
See, you don't like Yu, right?
(Matohara) But me...
I have someone else I like right now... >> I can't break up.
I will never break up.
Yes, this story is over.
(Door opening and closing sound)
(Yuki) What's that?
(Kazuo) No... I thought I'd listen to a bit.
That's fine, I'll just drink it without doing anything unnecessary.
(Kazuo) Yes...
♪～
(Matohara) [I like Koyama-san]
[My ex-girlfriend is already broken up...]
>> [He also said that Ui-senpai proposed to me â†’
"What do you think of me?" I asked.
♪～
(Rin) Seriously?
(Rin) You could say that we haven't broken up, Kanako.
That's right.
No, Kanako isa â†’
I've always loved Yu.
(Matohara) What? (Yasda) I've been consulted frequently.
How can we stay together forever?
But your big brother likes Sena, right?
I was so worried I went all the way to Nagano.
(Yasda's voice) That's right! Did you tell Sena?
We couldn't meet over there, did we?
(Matohara's voice) I haven't said that, I don't think it's too heavy...
>> If Sena-san is important â†’
Be clear about Kanako.
(Matohara) That's right, but â†’
He was told that if we break up like this, we would never be able to see him again...
Then it's already... â†’
My head is completely white...
Why is it so scary?
>> I know it's tough but â†’
It's not good as it is now.
That's right, let's get it right.
(Rin) It's probably time for your big brother to change.
(Matohara) Yes.
(Yasda) Come on, eat quickly.
(Sena) Sakimoto is a mutual friend of Nagumo and Honoka â†’
You participated in this party held in your apartment, right?
(Sakimoto) Yes, this is â†’
It was a party to unveil the two of them' new homes, right?
Yeah.
(Sena) At this time, Nagumo puts in the lease agreement â†’
I wrote about Honoka as my wife â†’
I heard that it was a hot topic.
>> Ah, yes.
(Sakimoto's voice) Honoka was certainly talking to everyone with joy.
(Sena's voice) What was Nagumo's behavior at that time?
(Sakimoto's voice) He listened with amusement.
(Matohara) Regarding the description of Nagumo's wife â†’
That means you didn't deny it, right?
>> Yes I remember that very well.
(Sena) Can you testify about what you just said in court?
>> Of course it's fine.
(Matohara) I'm glad you could get testimony. (Sena) Yes.
(Sena) Matohara-kun.
Maybe a bit nice.
(Matohara) Yes.
(Sena) The other day, the story was in the middle â†’
I was proposed to by Ui-kun.
(Matohara) What...
(Sena) But I refused.
I'm sure â†’
the….
(Sena) Sorry, I want to hear Matohara-kun's feelings.
The one who said he liked me before was â†’
What does it mean?
(Matohara) That's... my true feelings.
(Sena) But she hasn't broken up...
(Matohara) The farewell story has been...
But... â†’
I'm not convinced.
I know this is just weird, normal â†’
Me... â†’
Being parted with someone â†’
I'm really not good at it...
(Sena) No one is good at breaking up.
I don't like breaking up... â†’
That's unfair.
If you can't date, you can say you can't date.
(Matohara) It's not like we can't date you, it's really...
(Sena) It's okay.
You don't have to force yourself to break up with Kanako.
Let's go back to being a coworker.
(Matohara) But...
(Ui) I didn't know that my mother was calling Sena too... I'm sorry.
(Sena) Sorry I don't know anything either...
(Shoko) Thank you for keeping me waiting. (Ui) Thank you.
(Shoko) I also picked up Sena's favorite young corn.
(Sena) Thank you.
(Sakura) Hey, hey, look. (Sena) Huh?
(Sakura) Tamiya-kun occasionally sends photos.
(Sena) We're still good friends now, I'm glad.
(Sakura) I want to ride a balloon again! Let's go with Dad too.
(Ui) Yes. >> That's fine!
Ah, let's go with four of us next time.
(Ui) Yes, if everyone's plans are right.
(Shop clerk) Sorry for the wait, sorry.
Wow, it's here! (Sakura) Amazing!
(Shoko) I want everyone to eat.
(Sena) It's impossible for four of us to eat all of this.
>> If it's still there, you can just take it home.
(Sena) Stop asking for it with the assumption that I'll take it home anyway...
(Ui) But I haven't eaten since morning and am hungry.
Looks tasty. (Shoko) Is it true?
Ah, are you going to eat pizza? Pizza. >> Ah, wait and take a photo!
Sorry please take a picture.
With this...
(Whisper) Preparing for a big meal.
(Shoko) Sena-chan is after all, Ui-kun and Sakura-chan â†’
You look happiest when you're together.
(Sena) Mum just wants to see it like that.
>> Mom knows!
You need Ui-kun in your life!
I'm sure I'll be happy if we can all become a family together.
You know that Sena-chan is.
In living â†’
There is something more important than love or love.
Hehe.
(Kanako) Look, this is so nostalgic!
I want to go again.
(Madohara) Kanako There's a story.
>> This aquarium was fun, wasn't it? (Matohara) Listen carefully.
(Matohara) I liked Kanako but â†’
That wasn't romantic feelings.
That's what I liked with that feeling â†’
I've never seen it before.
So I don't think we should be together.
>> So it's fine if we can't see you again.
You've never had all the time together up until now.
(Matohara) Why that's what it is...
>> Get calm.
Think again.
(Matohara) Is it a settlement? (Eto) Yes.
(Eto) If you agree, we will withdraw our lawsuit â†’
Furthermore, we will pay a settlement of 10 million yen.
(Sena) Are you sue me and propose a settlement?
(Eto) Nagumo's current status â†’
I have a married wife.
(Matohara) Marriage? >> Yes.
I got married shortly after I broke up with Honoka.
(Matohara) Nagumo is a different woman than Honoka â†’
Does that mean they were dating at the same time?
>> Yes, just like Honoka-san â†’
I was living in an apartment with my current wife.
(Matohara) It also says "wife" here...
(Sena) In other words, she rents an apartment at the same time as two women â†’
Does that mean that you wrote in both contracts with your wife?
>> For him, he writes his wife in the lease agreement â†’
It means there is no special meaning.
So, who is Honoka?
This means it wasn't a common-law relationship.
Just... â†’
As a representative of a company, Nagumo will be in court that will damage the image â†’
I would like to avoid it if possible.
If you could promise not to mention this matter at all in the future â†’
I would like to end this by paying the settlement.
I apologize for the fact that I was dating another woman.
I think the settlement amount is not bad either.
Please consider it positively.
(Sena) Nagumo was married shortly after Hoka-san broke up.
It seems that the relationship period was also overlapping.
>> What? that….
(Matohara) "Nagumo had no intention of getting married" â†’
...but you said that â†’
Has there ever been any discussion about that?
>> You can understand without talking, since we've been together for five years.
(Matohara) Doesn't it mean that you've never checked it properly?
I don't think the other party is a common-law marriage.
This lease agreement is also available â†’
It's no longer a powerful evidence â†’
Isn't it okay to reconcile?
(Sena) Matohara-kun.
>> If... if we accept the settlement â†’
That means I wasn't my wife, right?
(Sena) That's what happened in the other party's settlement proposal.
>> If so, it won't be accepted.
There are witnesses over here.
(Sena) But Honoka... >> I was my wife!
It's been said that he's been living with him for five years -
I can't accept it.
(Matohara) Are you really going to be tried?
I don't think I'll ever win.
Koyama-san!
(Sena) Ha...
I want to snuggle with Honoka.
(Matohara) But...
(Sena) Witnesses will also come.
You have to fight until the end.
(Sena) Next, we will show you Exhibit No. 2.
(Sena) Sakimoto-san At this party you participated in â†’
What did you perceive of the relationship between Honoka and Nagumo?
>> I thought it was a common-law relationship.
(Sena) Why did you think so?
(Sakimoto) Even if everyone knows that he wrote "wife" â†’
Nagumo was not denying it and was having fun.
(Sena) This makes me think that Nagumo also had a will to marry him.
That's all.
(Judge) should begin cross-examination of the plaintiff's agent.
(Eto) Yes.
You were at a party five years ago â†’
Nagumo and Honoka had a common-law relationship â†’
Did you really recognize it?
yes.
I see.
Now, we will submit new Iku No. 6 as evidence of impeachment.
picture….
(Eto) This is Sakimoto-san immediately after the party â†’
This is the email screen where you interacted with other participants.
Eh, I'll read it out.
"Honoka-chan was really happy lol."
(Participant's voice) "Is Honoka really Nagumo's wife?"
(Participant's comments) "I watched it thinking I was just a lover."
(Participant's voice) "I feel like I'm alone and excited."
(Eto) "Poor... ha ha."
And at the end of the exchange, Sakimoto-san â†’
He replies "That's true."
(Buzzing)
What is this...
(Eto) At the time, you two were in a common-law relationship â†’
Maybe you didn't think about it?
That's probably... maybe.
(Eto) Well then, once more â†’
Please remember carefully and answer.
Those who were convinced that the two were common-laws:
Have you been there?
Probably â†’
not here.
(Eto) Nagumo gives Honoka â†’
That's what I didn't think of as a wife â†’
It must have been a well-known fact.
That's all.
(Nagumo) I'm trying to choose a marriage partner â†’
I lived with the two at the same time.
I spent five years living with Honoka, but â†’
It seemed he wanted to maintain the status quo.
When you think about walking through life together â†’
Choose the person who says "I want to get married" â†’
Isn't that obvious?
What is that...
It's too bad! (Sena) Honoka-san.
>> I'm just â†’
I'm happy to be by your side...
(Judge) Please refrain from making comments unless you are being asked.
I'm proud to be able to support your work â†’
I'm happy...
So I'm going to stop wanting anything more...
Honoka hasn't said anything specific.
(Honoka) I thought he would understand without talking.
(Honoka) I â†’
You're your wife.
(Judge) Stay quiet!
That's what they thought.
Wife Wife â†’
In the end, the goal is to divide the assets, right?
♪～
(Sena) Honoka-san!
(Honoka) Even amateurs can understand it.
I'm losing already.
The possibility of this happening â†’
Did you not expect it?
If so â†’
I wish they'd stopped properly.
♪～
(Kotori) This time it was a shame.
Yes, but there's nothing I can do about it.
I know it's a difficult case â†’
Because I chose to fight.
But it taught me a lot.
Love and life â†’
There are people in all different styles in the world.
That means you can't measure someone on your own scale.
In the end, reveal your feelings â†’
Clash with your opponent â†’
We have no choice but to discuss it all.
I'll look forward to it next time.
(Sena) Yes.
>> Hey, Koyama-san.
We're all thinking about going out drinking together, what do you think?
That's right, it's time to drink and forget about it.
I'll be with you until the morning.
I'll go home on the last train, but if that's fine.
(Sena) Sorry, I'm sorry today.
(Matohara) Koyama-san. (The sound of the door closing)
(Matohara) Sorry I'm lacking in strength.
(Sena) It's not, it's all my fault.
(Matohara) Let's go out drinking.
It's sure to distract you more than being alone.
(Sena) Thank you.
But I'll stop today.
(Matohara) Everyone wants to cheer up Koyama-san.
That's true for me too.
I want you to rely on everyone more.
(Sena) Sorry.
I want to be alone now.
(Indigo's voice) It's a bit sad, isn't it?
He wants to encourage Koyama-san...
Sena-san doesn't rely on me very often.
It's better though.
Previously, I was more alone.
The wheat becomes stronger when stepped on.
That's the type of person Koyama-san is.
Service because he said something unusual and good.
Haha, I said something unusual and good! >> Unusual?
I'm sure Koyama-san is fine.
Let's drink! >> Right, let's drink it!
Okay, I'll give you the best shochu.
Oh! (Ai) Yay!
(Kozue) Oh! (Indigo) Oh, amazing!
♪～
Yu-kun is no good. (Matohara) What?
>> If you're going, go quickly.
(Matohara) Yes, thank you.
(Ui) Sena.
I heard it from my mother.
I think he's depressed.
(Sena) Hmm... sorry I'm glad I ignored it.
(Ui) Hey...
Would you like to do this together?
(Sena) Before â†’
He said, "Sena should stay like this."
Is it really okay to just stay like this?
(Ui) I think it's fine.
Sena is straight towards her goal â†’
I can support those who are worried â†’
I remember my mother...
Can I take this until morning?
(Sena) Hehehe...
thank you.
It's okay now.
(Ui) So let's make a wish.
Those who have had this sparkler lasted for a long time â†’
be happy!
(Sena) That's sloppy.
♪～
(Ui) I think Sena is doing her best.
I'm the same Sena as I am now â†’
I think it's pretty impressive.
(Sena) Is that so...
(Ui) Ah...
That's good, Sena I can be happy.
(Sena) What is that?
(Matohara) Koyama-san!
(Matohara) Haa haa haa...
Koyama-san has something I want to talk about.
(Ui) It looks like I'm tired today.
(Matohara) But...
(Sena) I'm going home now today.
(Ui) I told Sena I wanted to become a family.
Does Matohara like Sena?
(Matohara) Yes I like it.
(Ui) I want to stay with Sena forever.
Is Matohara ready to do that?
(Matohara) Me...
(Ui) If you are not prepared, act irresponsible â†’
I hope you don't make Sena sad any more.
(Kozue) What about Matohara-san?
(Ai) Today I'm on paid leave.
Wow, that's rare.
I wonder what's wrong?
Koyama-san... (Sena) Yes.
>> I want Matohara to see this one day.
It's bad, can I have it delivered?
(Sena) What?
yes.
(Sena) Sorry. (Yuki) Ah, Sena-san.
(Sena) Sorry I suddenly brought the documents to Matohara...
>> Oh, I just went out somewhere.
(Sena) Is that so... Ah.
Can I give this to you?
>> Thank you of course.
(Sena) So, I'm sorry.
>> Sena-san.
Maybe a little bit more?
Please. (Sena) Thank you.
>> It looks a bit complicated.
Me and my husband â†’
He's not Yu's real parent.
(Sena) What?
>> I took Yu in when I was five years old â†’
Her real mother â†’
He didn't seem to be very enthusiastic about raising children.
Finally â†’
He stopped leaving that child behind...
(Sena) That's it...
>> Maybe that's why that girl â†’
I'm extremely bad at breaking up with people.
Is it called separation anxiety?
Even on the way home with friends â†’
I'm worried that I won't be able to meet again â†’
I'll wave my hands forever.
That's why Kanako-chan can't break up completely.
But about Sena-san â†’
I think it's probably more important than anyone else.
(Yuki's voice) That girl â†’
I really want to change for you.
(Yuki's voice) That's all you can see if you look closely.
Sorry, this is what happens to Ne Sena.
But to that girl and Sena-san â†’
I don't want you to regret it.
♪～
(Sena) [It's unfair to say that it's not good at breaking up]
[If you can't date, you can say you can't date]
♪～
(Matohara) [I'm sure I'll get off next time]
[At that time, we'll be together somewhere]
(Matohara) [I hope I can see it with Koyama again â†’
I've always wanted to say it...
(Sena) [I wanted to talk about that too]
♪～
(Sena) Matohara-kun.
(Matohara) It's snowing.
(Sena) I heard it from my mother.
For you, parting â†’
Without knowing how hard it is,
I said a lot of terrible things.
sorry.
(Matohara) That's what it is...
(Sena) I just wanted to know what Matohara thinks â†’
My feelings â†’
I never told it properly.
(Sena) I'm â†’
About Madohara-kun â†’
I like it.
So I want to be with you.
I just wanted to convey this feeling properly.
(Matohara) I parted ways with Kanako â†’
This time it's time to be properly ï½¡ (Kanako) [Yu]
[Be calm]
[Rethink it]
(Matohara) [I have someone I like]
[About that person â†’
I want to cherish it properly.
[Stay by Kanako's side without being clear forever...]
(Matohara) [I'm really sorry]
[Thank you so much]
ã€”Goodbyeã€•
♪～
(Matohara) I really wanted to talk about that yesterday.
(Sena) That's right.
(Matohara) But today's day â†’
Should I say it â†’
I was unsure if I should say it.
He hurts Koyama again â†’
I wonder if it would make you sad...
Me too â†’
I like Koyama-san.
but….
Haa...
♪～
(Sena) It's okay.
I won't be gone.
(Level Crossing Alarm Sound)
(Madohara) Koyama-san... (Leadway sound)
♪～
(Sena) Probably â†’
I'll continue to do this from now on â†’
You can overcome one at a time.
If only they were two.
(Matohara) Koyama-san.
With me... â†’
Please stay with us.
(Sena) Yes.
♪～
(Matohara) Ah...
It's piling up.
(Sena) Right.
>> It seems like I've seen something I shouldn't look at...
♪～