=Promise in the Summer=
=Episode 17=
Auntie,
we're back.
Chuxia,
you're finally home.
Auntie,
I have a surprise for you.
Here, sit.
What surprise?
Give me your hand.
Qilu.
Mom.
I'm well now.
Chuxia?
Qilu.
Over the years,
Mom always wants to hug you.
Today the wish is finally fulfilled.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Chuxia,
you're really our lucky star.
Auntie, I was just doing my job.
Honey,
Qilu,
Qilu has recovered.
Come and have a look.
Have a look.
Mr. Han,
were you going to
ask me something just now?
Qilu,
your birthday party will be in two days.
Ma'am wants to know
if you have any special demands.
Is there anything special this year?
Or maybe
you want some
special gifts?
Special gifts?
They don't have to be expensive.
It's the thought that counts.
Did she hear me?
Qilu,
you can invite Chuxia
to your party fair and square.
Who wants to invite the fool?
Chuxia
has cured you.
The whole family is grateful to her.
Your parents
both want you to invite her.
That sounds reasonable.
Han Qilu's birthday is coming.
What gift should I prepare?
Hello, Chenchuan,
what birthday gifts
do you boys
usually want?
(Whose birthday?)
Han Qilu's birthday is coming.
(Do you have money?)
Don't you know
whether I have money or not?
(I think)
(he'll like it)
(no matter what gift you give him.)
(After all, it's your thought that counts.)
Thought?
The bossy president's way,
kiss the girl peremptorily.
(What are romantic confessions?
Seven ways to win her heart.)
This is nonsense.
No.
I have to ask for advice.
Are you Qilu?
Who are you?
Do you want to see my parents?
They are inside.
Uncle.
Hello, Mankui.
Where was
Qilu going in such a hurry?
Did I come at a bad time?
No, you think too much.
He just went out on business.
We haven't seen each other for years.
He doesn't seem to remember me.
By the way, Uncle,
this is a gift
I brought for you and Auntie.
Thank you.
Come on.
Have a seat.
What can I do for you,
Young Master?
What will you do if you're going to
confess to Mo Xiwei?
Confess?
Why do you ask about this?
I want to...
You're going to confess to Chuxia.
Come on, let me tell you.
Are you sure
she will like that?
Rest assured.
Every girl likes that.
Actually, I want to give her a surprise.
I tell you what,
you should do me a favor
at my birthday party
in a few days.
What do you think?
Little prince.
Are you suggesting that
Han Qilu is your prince?
No.
I simply think it looks good.
Whatever you make,
he'll like it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He'll definitely like it.
Even if you made a piece of shi...
he would like it.
You guys must keep it a secret
and not tell him.
Alright. I'll get back to work.
Chuxia,
remember to
wear a red dress
on his birthday.
Why?
I hear that
he's liked red
since he was a child.
OK.
Thanks. Bye.
Bye.
Xiwei,
did you tell her?
I worried that I was too clumsy
and would betray myself.
You never thought
you would betray yourself
concerning your own business, right?
What's this?
I don't know English.
Appointment letter of
a senior dessert chief abroad.
Xiwei,
it took me effort to make you like me.
How can I leave you easily?
But
isn't that your dream?
Don't worry.
I made an agreement with them.
I'll take the job after college.
At that time,
if you'd like to...
♪I will guard you quietly♪
♪Be a star♪
♪Shining on your lonely island♪
♪Wait for your response at some point♪
♪I look up at the night sky♪
♪What a dreamy scene♪
♪You're like a beam of light
generated by fireflies♪
♪Coming to me without hesitation♪
♪You are like the moonlight
reflected from the sea♪
♪Flowing silently in my heart♪
♪You're not my exclusive moon♪
♪Yet your light illuminates me♪
♪You're like the first light of morning
that comes into my dream♪
♪Illuminating my face in the dark world♪
♪Helping me with my growth in confusion♪
♪And my search for
precious treasures in the world♪
♪You're like the first light of morning
that comes into my dream♪
♪Always guiding me to my destination♪
♪With you, I no longer
feel lost about the future♪
♪I'll pursue beautiful dreams bravely♪
(The right of network communication
of this work)
(is exclusively owned by Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)