=Promise in the Summer=
=Episode 11=
The doctor said
you mustn't use your injured foot,
or it would become an uncured illness.
You need to rest for about three days.
Three days!
Then...
What about my show?
Be careful.
The show
isn't so important as your health.
I'll figure a way out.
Xiwei is definitely
unable to play her role.
Therefore,
we must choose another heroine.
Why are you looking at me?
Chuxia.
I did want to
compete for the role before,
but
I doubt it's appropriate for me
to do it now.
But at the moment,
no one but you has memorized
all of Cinderella's lines.
Moreover, we're running out of time.
But I don't know how to dance.
Chenchuan can teach you.
Come on. I'll teach you.
Let me try.
Left hand.
OK.
The first move,
right foot backward.
OK.
Come.
One.
Then right foot forward.
Forward.
Two.
Left foot backward.
Three.
I'm sorry.
No worries.
Come.
Let's...
let's do it again.
OK.
Right foot backward.
Come.
One.
Two.
You're much skilled now.
Right.
Three.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
No worries.
How much longer will it take?
If you want to dance so much,
you can practice here yourself.
Wait for me.
Chuxia.
I'll practice when I get home.
Are you going to practice or not?
Wait for me.
It sounds unsympathetic,
but Mo Xiwei's accident
actually makes me the heroine.
Does it make you so happy?
Sure.
Why are you upset again?
I was going to ask you
to teach me to dance.
Why hasn't she come yet?
Four.
I forgot I hadn't finished
the ten-minute task.
Why do you stop dancing?
Dancing is important,
but the task is also...
more important.
Waltz?
I teach only once.
I'm sorry.
No worries.
Again.
Can't you tell left from right?
A little bit.
A little bit?
Do you know
how many times
you stepped on me
since the beginning?
Forget it.
Won't you teach me anymore?
Step on my feet.
You step on my feet.
I'll tell you left and right.
Wh, wh, what?
Step, step on your feet?
You wanna learn or not?
Yes.
Hold tight.
What did you say?
Ma'am,
absolutely true.
Qilu is dancing with Chuxia
in the garden now.
That's great!
Don't stand there.
Go grab my SLR camera.
Yeah. Yeah.
Ma'am.
They're such a perfect match.
Wonderful!
Well,
thanks.
Thanks for helping me
to prepare the prop
and teaching me to dance.
Will you
go to see my show?
Not interested.
Great.
You learned to dance so fast.
Chenchuan seems to be a good teacher.
I can't take all the credit.
Chuxia learned it herself at home.
Hello?
Don't worry.
I must ruin
Cinderella's dress.
(Hurry up.)
(Don't get caught.)
What's wrong?
It's OK.
Someone is coming.
I must leave.
♪I look up at the night sky♪
♪What a dreamy scene♪
♪You're like a beam of light
generated by fireflies♪
♪Coming to me without hesitation♪
♪You are like the moonlight
reflected from the sea♪
♪Flowing silently in my heart♪
♪You're not my exclusive moon♪
♪Yet your light illuminates me♪
♪You're like the first light of morning
that comes into my dream♪
♪Illuminating my face in the dark world♪
♪Helping me with my growth in confusion♪
♪And my search for
precious treasures in the world♪
♪You're like the first light of morning
that comes into my dream♪
♪Always guiding me to my destination♪
♪With you, I no longer
feel lost about the future♪
♪I'll pursue beautiful dreams bravely♪
(The right of network communication
of this work)
(is exclusively owned by Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)