=Promise in the Summer=
=Episode 18=
Red dress?
Do I really have to wear a red dress
to Han Qilu's birthday party?
Isn't red a little flashy?
Where can I find
a red dress?
Chuxia, are you there?
Auntie, come in, please.
Chuxia, look.
Today,
I saw this
when I was shopping.
I thought it fit you well.
I really have good taste.
It's beautiful, indeed.
Auntie, I can't accept this.
Why can't you?
You've cured Qilu.
The dress is a token of my gratitude.
If you don't accept it,
I'll think
my thank-you gift is turned down.
No.
That's not what I mean, Auntie.
Then you should accept it.
Bye.
What a coincidence.
Ma'am.
Hush.
Keep your voice down.
Ma'am, how was it going?
I made Chuxia accept it.
But I was a little nervous.
I don't know if I did well.
Qilu is too proud.
I don't know who he is like.
Like me.
Like Mr. Han.
He wouldn't give Chuxia
the dress directly,
instead, he had to keep it back from her
and make me do it.
Qilu might feel embarrassed.
Anyway,
I've done my part.
As for the rest,
he is on his own.
(After the party,)
(Han Qilu should go to Xiang Mankui.)
What am I doing?
An Chuxia,
you have a conscience after all.
Mr. Han,
you're awesome.
Of course.
I'm a capable housekeeper.
Do you need a hand?
No, no, no.
Chuxia,
you look beautiful in that dress.
Really?
Qilu must like it.
Well, let me give you a hand.
OK, then.
Put it here.
Congratulations.
OK. OK.
Thank you.
I'll see you later.
OK.
Hello, Mr. Han.
Hello.
Ma'am, good evening.
Where is Qilu?
I don't know.
Wayward boy.
Maybe he's entertaining
his friends somewhere.
All the guests here
are your business partners.
People would think
it was your party.
Welcome. Welcome.
Welcome.
If I were Qilu,
I wouldn't come either.
Congratulations.
Thanks for your kindness.
How's your business going?
Ma'am.
Have you seen Chuxia?
Chuxia?
I saw her earlier.
Where is she?
The party will start soon.
Why hasn't she come yet?
I'll find her later.
Qilu.
Thanks, man.
No problem.
By the way,
have you seen Chuxia?
She should be in her room.
Xiwei went to find her.
How do you feel?
Nervous?
Don't worry.
Everything goes according to plan.
Ma'am,
it's almost time.
Get started.
Dear friends,
welcome to
Qilu's birthday party.
I now declare
Han Qilu's
20th birthday party
officially begins!
Now,
let's welcome Han Qilu
to give us a speech.
Go for it.
Today
is my 20th birthday.
First, I'd like to thank you for coming.
You may wonder why I'm holding flowers.
It's a surprise.
You'll find out in a minute.
In fact, today,
I have an announcement to make.
Chuxia is gone.
She isn't in her room.
How come?
Where would she go?
When I went in her room before,
she was still there
and had changed into the dress.
Wait.
Dear friends,
it's a good day today.
Please allow me
to introduce
my son's fiancee,
Miss Xiang Mankui.
Meanwhile,
I'd like to
announce their engagement.
They will
get married after reaching
the legal age of marriage.
That's weird.
He was planning to confess yesterday,
then today, a fiancee
showed up out of thin air.
Chuxia,
we're very grateful to you
for curing Qilu.
So,
what's your plan next?
Mr. Han,
next, I want to
take good care of my mom.
Good.
You're a dutiful daughter.
Tonight,
I'll announce the engagement
of Qilu and Miss Xiang.
If Qilu is always
with another girl,
it might be inappropriate.
Mr. Han,
I only stayed here to
help with Qilu's treatment.
Now that he gets well,
I should leave.
I don't want Miss Xiang
to misunderstand.
Is this your birthday gift to Qilu?
Qilu has lived
a carefree life since childhood.
Then suddenly,
he came into contact with
an ordinary person full of vigor.
He would feel curious indeed.
But curiosity
doesn't last long.
I understand, Mr. Han.
Thank you.
Qilu,
I didn't expect you
to be so considerate.
You even
prepared roses for me.
I like them very much.
Thank you, Qilu.
Qilu.
Unbelievable.
Han,
what's going on?
Don't worry.
Qilu is being childish.
I'll give you an explanation.
Our cooperation depends solely
on the marriage of our children.
The engagement won't be canceled.
♪I look up at the night sky♪
♪What a dreamy scene♪
♪You're like a beam of light
generated by fireflies♪
♪Coming to me without hesitation♪
♪You are like the moonlight
reflected from the sea♪
♪Flowing silently in my heart♪
♪You're not my exclusive moon♪
♪Yet your light illuminates me♪
♪You're like the first light of morning
that comes into my dream♪
♪Illuminating my face in the dark world♪
♪Helping me with my growth in confusion♪
♪And my search for
precious treasures in the world♪
♪You're like the first light of morning
that comes into my dream♪
♪Always guiding me to my destination♪
♪With you, I no longer
feel lost about the future♪
♪I'll pursue beautiful dreams bravely♪
(The right of network communication
of this work)
(is exclusively owned by Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)