ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
PLACES AND EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL
REGIONAL FORCES UNDER MARTIAL LAW
There's a chance
that the military will use force,
led by General Eun Hui-jeong,
Minister Oh Yeong-seok,
and NIS Deputy Director Ji Yun-bae.
In other words, there's a sign of a coup.
The H-hour is 11:00 p.m.
The troops near the metropolitan area will
assemble near the Capital Defense Command.
What we need to do now is appoint
someone in the military we can trust
and quell the rebel forces
before 11:00 p.m.
But do you think
there's someone reliable in the military
that will listen to the Blue House?
Someone we know for sure
is on Mr. President's side.
There's one person
who can stand against General Eun.
I'm not sure
if he'll take my side, though.
General Lee Gwan-muk
is a risky choice, sir.
General Eun
is using General Lee's dismissal
and detention to justify the coup.
That's why.
If General Lee decides
to join hands with us,
they will lose their justification
to exercise force,
and their coup attempt will lose momentum.
But General Lee Gwan-muk...
Are you sure
that he'll join hands with us?
He doesn't trust the Blue House.
He might have already agreed
to collude with General Eun.
-Then--
-Then,
General Lee will be prosecuted
for insurrection before anybody else
according to the Military Criminal Act.
It is the decision I made
as the Commander-in-Chief of the military,
Secretary Han.
At the moment,
there is no military official whom
we can trust to side with President Park.
If General Lee is a possibility,
we should give it a shot.
General Lee is the most elite member
of the ROK Army.
And President Park hurt his pride
in the most humiliating way.
Do you think he'll side with us?
What if I turn you down?
What are you going to do
if I even join General Eun?
Then this offer
will basically be suicide for you.
You don't know anything about the military
to be called Commander-in-Chief.
Where did you say we'd be meeting?
General Lee has just arrived.
MILITARY POLICE
Welcome, sir.
We were waiting for you.
General Lee has arrived
at the Capital Defense Command.
I believe he has joined hands
with General Eun.
REGIONAL FORCES UNDER MARTIAL LAW
Sir.
Would you like to issue the order now?
The Tenth Fighter Wing is on standby
as you had requested, sir.
The Special Task Force
at the Capital Defense Command
is awaiting your orders, sir.
If General Lee did indeed join them,
the troops gathered at the CDC
will be on the move soon.
We must make a move to quell them
before that happens
in order to minimize casualties.
Sir.
I have...
already given my orders.
As per the order of President Park,
the Commander-in-Chief of our military,
General Eun Hui-jeong is under arrest
for plotting a military coup
according to Article Eight
of the Military Criminal Act.
What are you talking about?
Why are you doing this?
-He should have arrived by now.
-All right.
Let's go.
Hands up!
Who the hell are you?
President Park humiliated you.
Not once, but twice!
So why?
Because the honor of the ROK Army
is more important
than my personal honor.
The most shameful moments
in the history of our army
was when we had to aim guns
at our own people.
Did you think
I'd repeat that?
I need to hear your answer, sir.
Did you think
I'd join hands with you right away
if you offered to reinstate me
as Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff?
Is that why you came all the way here?
In front of the generals under
my leadership, you took away my authority
and doubted my patriotism.
My honor as a soldier
matters the most to me,
and you humiliated me.
Are you really naive enough to believe
that I will help you?
I calculated your move.
In a clever manner.
You thought I humiliated you twice,
you neither rebelled
nor exercised force.
Hence, I thought
the law and order of this country
mattered more to you
than your personal honor.
Thus,
I believed
that you'd want our military
to be remembered honorably
by our children.
I do not know much about the military.
However,
I felt like I could tell
what kind of person you were.
Was I
wrong about you?
Mr. President.
General Lee has arrived
at the NSC situation room.
As of 22:05
on March 31, 2019,
the Military Police and prosecutors
have successfully completed
quelling the military coup attempt
led by Army Chief of Staff Eun Hui-jeong.
All associated personnel
have been sent to the DSSC.
I hereby report the progress to you,
the Commander-in-Chief of our military,
sir.
DAY 32 : THE TRAP
EPISODE 15
EUN HUI-JEONG
General Eun Hui-jeong.
When we found out that you were the mole
who leaked OP 5015-18,
you started plotting a military coup.
It was
because you were afraid you might be held
solely accountable for the bombing.
We can't condone such injustice.
Now, tell me.
OP 5015-18.
Who did you give it to?
The VIP.
I asked you who inside the Blue House
shared the plan for the attack
with you.
What do you mean by "the VIP"?
That's right.
All of us
simply followed the instructions
given to us by the VIP.
That is not something the former
head of a government agency should say.
So you simply followed
the VIP's instructions
and bombed
the National Assembly Building...
Who is it?
The VIP.
I don't know. I have no idea.
We don't know what he looks like,
what his name is, or who he is.
We
have never met the VIP.
This person was an accomplice
in the massive attack,
and yet you've never met him?
Mr. Kim.
I always met
with Mr. Kim,
the VIP's representative.
He always passed on
the VIP's instructions to us
and informed him of our requests.
He is the faithful middleman.
Who is Mr. Kim?
It's common, you know.
When the VIP has too much to lose
by revealing himself,
his right-hand man acts on his behalf.
Where is
Mr. Kim now?
That's Mr. Kim.
He was caught on a camera
near the tailor shop.
Ji-won, do you have his name yet?
I've been going through
all the security footage to find his face
since the second I got here
without even going to the bathroom
thanks to you two, my incredible mentors.
Okay, so...
You can find out
more information about him, right?
Some say he was one of our spies
sent to the North.
Some witnesses also said
that he used to do legal work
at Nadong Group's
Planning and Coordination Office.
A former South Korean spy
and Nadong Group's legal team
seem completely unrelated.
The two have something in common.
They're both fixers
who can pull off anything.
It does seem like Mr. Kim can do anything.
From personnel matters to money,
they never had to reiterate their requests
regardless of what it was
because he always resolved
them effectively
using the VIP's power.
Are you saying
that's why they could put their trust
in Mr. Kim
without knowing his name or identity
and conspired with him
to commit the outrageous crime
together?
The entire nation is shocked by the news
that the Minister of National Defense,
Oh Yeong-seok, was shot and killed
last night by an officer
from the Ministry of National Defense.
According to the police,
Minister Oh and the officer...
It's me, Mr. Kim.
I'm sorry I couldn't call sooner.
I was trying to figure out
who'd have the most to lose
if I revealed myself now.
They arrived near Namhyeon-dong.
According to witnesses, the officer...
As all of you have probably heard,
Minister Oh
was shot and killed last night,
which is truly tragic.
Was it because of a personal grudge?
Was it due to a conflict over
his presidential bid?
We have issued a press embargo,
but I'd like to share this
with the two of you
as I consider you our partners.
Last night,
there was a conspiracy
for a military revolt
led by General Eun Hui-jeong.
And Minister Oh was on his way
to participate in the conspiracy.
Hold on.
A conspired revolt?
Do you mean
a coup d'etat?
General Lee Gwan-muk
and the military prosecutors
arrested all of them at the scene.
They were all transferred to the DSSC,
and the situation has been contained.
Why wasn't it reported to the media?
Once people learn of your quick efforts
to quell the coup,
it will only give you
a bigger advantage in the polls.
Those who plotted the coup
were also involved with
the National Assembly Building bombing.
Minister Oh,
General Eun Hui-jeong,
and even Director Ji Yun-bae.
Oh, my.
My goodness.
When the NIS Terrorism Task Force
got closer to the truth,
they believed their involvement
will soon be revealed.
That's why they plotted the coup.
Currently, we've yet to uncover
the true culprits behind the bombing.
If news of the coup got out,
it'll only aggravate the people's anxiety.
We believe he is one of the main players
of the bombing and coup d'etat.
You two are not only delegates
of the opposing and majority party,
but also the top presidential candidates.
That is why
I earnestly ask this of you.
Please do not let this
be turned into a political issue
or used to aid your campaign.
Will you please
keep this confidential?
Why do you think
Minister Oh made such a choice?
He got involved in the bombing
and even decided
to join the military coup.
He was probably desperate
and believed that
without taking such extreme measures,
there was no hope for this country
ever since the Battle of Baengnyeong.
Then you could say that
I was behind the bombing.
The practical politics
that only further discouraged him
has always been what I promoted.
During that Baengnyeong Battle,
where were you?
When the ones who survived
were suffering in pain
of the wounds
and the people's indifference,
where exactly were you?
-Mr. Oh--
-You were a member
of the National Defense Committee.
However, when we asked for your help,
you were never present.
Not even once.
Living in South Korea
only ends in two ways.
You either become a victim one day
or the bereaved.
Due to ethnic background,
disability, nationality, affiliation,
race, religion,
and even beliefs...
In every way,
people have found a way
to discriminate against others.
It's how one can be at a slight advantage
in this dog-eat-dog world.
Underneath our masks, we're selfish beings
who support discrimination
and oppose equality.
That's the ugly face
of the power
that propels the world.
GENERAL ELECTION POLLS
I thought there would be
a huge fluctuation in the polls
now that front-runner Minister Oh
was excluded.
I'm glad President Park is in the lead,
although it's only by a small margin.
This isn't a number we can be happy with.
Once supporters
of the major parties gather,
as an independent candidate,
President Park will be fighting
with one arm tied behind his back
against Mayor Kang and Ms. Yun.
Still, he has achieved something
no one can deny.
For a month since the bombing,
he completed an internship
in administration.
He passed given the circumstances.
All right.
His term
ends in four days. That's including today.
Please
handle the reporters
and the media well until then
so that he can finish up his duties
and end his term successfully.
I'm counting on you.
The polite Mr. Cha
isn't a douchebag,
but at the same time, he's not very fun.
Don't worry though.
You're not the only one
who supports President Park.
What does he want from me?
I saw the latest polls.
You've made progress.
Didn't you promise Secretary Cha
that you'd join the campaign
if I became the front-runner in the polls?
You don't have to keep that promise.
Join my campaign
when you finally see me as a candidate
who can win the election.
Is that confidence I detect in your voice?
You were right
to choose General Lee Gwan-muk.
When we first met,
I asked you to prevent
a military coup d'etat,
and you kept your promise.
Thank you, President Park.
CHA YEONG-JIN
Call Mr. Kim.
They will contact you soon
since they'll need your help.
Are you saying
that Ms. Yun is involved with the bombers?
The photos indicate its possibility.
Who sent these photos?
They were sent to the office,
but there was no return address.
I'm sure they have an agenda.
Either it's to disclose her corruption
for the interest of the public,
or it's a political attack
designed to make the Blue House
suspect Assemblywoman Yun.
There's someone who could answer that.
The man in the photo is Mr. Kim,
one of the people behind the bombing.
During your internal investigation,
has Assemblywoman Yun come up
as a person of interest?
Not yet.
However, I believe
that nothing can be easily assumed
or stated about this Mr. Kim.
We do not know anything about this man
including his name and identity.
However, General Eun, Director Ji,
and even Minister Oh
trusted him fully and followed his orders
because they were blinded by the wealth
and power the VIP could give them.
Then,
in your opinion--
Assemblywoman Yun
is also someone who needs
the wealth and power the VIP can provide.
I don't think we can rule out
the possibility.
I'd like to ask you for a favor.
Until you're done
investigating Assemblywoman Yun,
I'd like these photos
and what we know of Mr. Kim
to be kept a secret.
Speculations
of a presidential candidate
colluding with the bombers
will cause irreparable harm
even if it's later proven to be false.
I'll try, sir.
They met at a Korean restaurant
in Gangnam,
and their meeting occurred
on February 21 at 5 p.m.
That's all the information I can get
from these photos.
We should check
if there's anyone in her circle
who has a connection to this Mr. Kim.
Na-gyeong.
Could Assemblywoman Yun
be this so-called VIP?
Just think about it.
She left the National Assembly Building
just before the explosion
due to a sudden boycott
and got out of harm's way.
Who has the ability and authority
to control the political arena
other than her?
Mr. Kim, it's me.
Thank you for the photos.
I'll cut right to the chase then.
Is this your way of saying
you'll expose me?
Now?
By now,
those photos are probably in the hands
of Acting President Park as well.
I'm considering sharing these
with every media company
as the next step.
Could you handle that?
He must have sent these photos
to President Park as well.
Sorry?
-Then...
-I only have
one option now.
But ma'am...
-Secretary Han.
-Yes?
The media is reporting breaking news.
Last night, a coup d'etat conspiracy
led by Army Chief of Staff Eun Hui-jeong
was quelled by the joint forces
of the military prosecutors,
DSSC, and the military police
under Joint Chiefs of Staff Chairman
Lee Gwan-muk's command.
Division equivalent forces
near the metropolitan area
were supposed to assemble
at the Capital Defense Command
along with the Special Ops
and the Army Air Command.
They were then planning to station
the mechanized infantry division,
-the armored brigades, and tank forces...
-Sir.
It was either Mayor Kang
or Assemblywoman Yun.
You should summon them over.
We must hold someone responsible.
The public sentiment will be important.
Quelling the coup could help your image
and that of this current administration.
President Park and the Blue House,
despite this being a coup d'etat
that poses a serious threat
to national security,
disregarded the people's right to know
and were only bent on
covering up the truth.
One can only assume
that the current administration
were only focused on how it'll effect
President Park's approval ratings.
-He'll be blamed instead of praised.
-How the people will react...
The press will be out for blood yet again.
-Over here!
-Here!
-Mr. Kim!
Why did you hide the coup d'etat
conspiracy?
Was the administration worried
about it being
directly tied
to President Park's competency?
Was it because President Park
is running for office?
In case it would affect the polls?
Is the Blue House more concerned
about a candidate's standing
at the polls
than the people's right to know?
We'd like an answer.
-Mr. Kim!
-Here!
-Over here!
-Mr. Kim!
Please answer the question.
-What's the answer?
Ever since the bombing,
the Blue House has
continuously followed one principle.
National security
takes precedence over
the people's right to know at times.
That is why the administration
also could not tell the people
about the conspired military revolt.
Are you saying
that the government
is hiding other matters as well?
Was it President Park
who decided to keep this from the public?
-Please tell us.
-Please answer the question!
-Mr. Kim!
-Is any of this true?
-Please answer us.
-Mr. Kim, what's the answer?
Aren't you leaving?
Of course I am. Let's go.
Ms. Woo.
Don't you think they're hiding more
than the conspired coup?
-Another great job today.
-I'm getting a strong feeling.
I'm not sure.
If you know anything, do share.
Excuse me.
-I'll wait.
-Good job today.
Ms. Woo, just a moment.
Do you know
who the source is?
Well,
it's linked to national security.
I believe
that the public should've been told
about the coup d'etat
as soon as it was quelled.
The authorities haven't figured out
who was behind the coup d'etat.
It would only lead
to unnecessary speculation.
That'll only shake
the stability of this nation
which we're trying to restore.
Yes, but the media and the people
would've distinguished rumors
from truth over time.
It may be noisy and chaotic,
but that's the process of democracy.
It's not like I don't understand
the Blue House's position.
Still, you shouldn't
have asked for our source.
It sounds to me
like you're trying to control the media.
How could you say something
so frightening?
When did I do that?
Just accept whatever the people think.
It's how one takes responsibility.
I think you should get going.
"They always say it's national security.
Don't they care about the people?
Now, they're even concealing coup d'etats.
Where is the truth?"
"Concealing a coup d'etat
and suppressing the people's rights.
President Park's administration
is an absolute failure."
Unbelievable.
This is like catching a burglar
that entered my home
but being criticized
for not reporting it to the police.
The media was kind enough
to give us a guideline.
They're saying that this administration
ignores people's rights
and harbors too many secrets.
President Park is scheduled to resign
in four days.
Just like a soldier
days before his discharge,
he should be careful of every action.
I can't believe his bad luck.
This will probably affect
the General Election Polls,
right?
Secretary Min,
are you worried about President Park?
Are you worried about
the independent candidate,
President Park's standings in the polls?
You're the one who was worried first,
so I thought that was the trend.
You see,
I'm very conscious
when it comes to trends.
Sure. Okay.
These are the poll results
of the presidential candidates
after the press reported about the coup.
GENERAL ELECTION POLLS
Assemblywoman Yun Chan-gyeong
has passed you and taken the lead.
Now, it's clear
who tipped off the press
and why that person took such a risk.
Are you saying Assemblywoman Yun
tipped off the press
to beat the President?
Let's not jump to conclusions.
We don't have time.
We have three days
until the President resigns,
and we must fix this within that time.
So what alternative do you suggest?
I suggest we turn the internal
investigation on Assemblywoman Yun
into an open investigation.
You want to turn it
into an open investigation?
If we do that,
the press will be busy
talking about Assemblywoman Yun.
The suspicion is regarding the bombing.
The votes that went to her
will naturally go to you, Mr. President.
Above all, no one will blame us
for our political attack on her.
We have a good cause.
We're responding to the people's request
for a transparent government.
You're wrong.
It's definitely a political attack.
You want to sway the votes
using an unconfirmed suspicion
against the leading candidate.
We can't betray our own principles.
-I'm against this, sir.
-But, sir--
Both of you.
Could you give us a moment please?
Mr. Han can't just
exclude us in the middle
of the discussion--
Obviously, he's making a mistake.
It was just two presidential secretaries
making counterarguments.
-It wasn't a quarrel--
What are your plans after this?
I don't have any special plans.
Why do you ask?
Do you want to go another round?
No.
There are some things in my office
that I can't handle myself.
What are they?
Ramyeon.
Would you like to have some?
I do not.
Is it that hard to decide whether or not
to open the investigation
on Assemblywoman Yun?
I was the one who begged
her and Mayor Kang
not to make national security
a political issue this morning.
Just because my rating dropped,
I can't betray the principles
I have set myself.
Those who play in the Olympics
don't compete in order to obey the rules.
They put in their best efforts
in order to win the medals.
Even after you lose in the elections,
will you be proud of yourself
for sticking to the rules?
I heard...
you said
you would enact the Discrimination Act
when you become President.
Does that promise...
mean less than your principles?
Would you call
Assemblywoman Yun Chan-gyeong in?
Have you made up your mind, sir?
I don't know if this will
sufficiently explain these pictures,
but it was just a meeting
with my supporters,
which is common during election season.
Some call them election brokers
and some call them
self-employed politicians.
If you blame me for not being
careful enough, I'd accept that.
But the claims
that I'm behind the bombing is ridiculous.
Even if it weren't for the bombing,
I would have successfully changed
the government through the election.
You're suspicious of me, aren't you?
Is that why you called me in?
The NIS Terrorism Task Force is conducting
an internal investigation on you.
And I'm planning to ask them to turn it
into an open investigation.
Every media outlet
will make this picture public.
They will persistently question
everything you have done
after the bombing.
Your credibility
as a presidential candidate
will drop to the point
where it can never recover.
Why are you saying this to me?
It's not like you need
my permission to do that.
You are still
a partner
in this government administration.
Do it. Make it an open investigation.
Even if you do so,
they won't find anything on me
because I'm innocent.
But turning it into an open investigation
will only show
you're admitting to yourself
you want the downfall of Yun Chan-gyeong
more than a truthful investigation.
I have sent the same picture
to President Park and Assemblywoman Yun
just like you have ordered.
I can't wait to see
what kind of decisions
these two will make.
Mr. Cha.
Yes, sir.
We're turning the investigation on Yun
into an open investigation tomorrow.
I'll relay the message.
SEONJIN REPUBLICAN PARTY DELEGATE
Call Mr. Kim.
Ma'am.
I must make him flee the country tonight.
KILLED MYUNG HAE-JOON,
ABDUCTED HAN NA-GYEONG
-I found him.
-What?
I identified Mr. Kim.
It wasn't a lie.
Mr. Kim was a part of
the Military Intelligence Command,
and he used to be an anti-North spy.
Are you sure?
At first, I thought
the bomber was just bluffing,
but I gave him the benefit of the doubt
and searched the entire network.
Then I found him. Mr. Kim.
Age, 38. Name, Kim Su-hyeon.
What has he done as a spy?
In 2010, he got selected
for the anti-North spy project.
He performed the best among his peers
in every skill.
For the anti-North spy project,
those with big builds aren't preferred.
He was perfect for the job.
2010. 2010 means...
It's when the inter-Korean relation,
strained by the Asan Port bombings,
suddenly improved significantly
right before the general election.
You're right.
At the time,
our government denied the existence
of anti-North spies. At the time...
KIM SU-HYEON
...Mr. Kim had already been
sent to the North.
He was abandoned by our government
while in dangerous circumstances.
LEE GYEONG-PYO
KIM SU-HYEON
These people here
have something in common.
They dedicated themselves
to Korea in their respective roles,
but...
they were all abandoned.
Do you think they wanted
to get revenge on Korea?
We should ask them in person.
Mr. Kim will do everything he can
to get help from the VIP.
I'll leave now, ma'am.
You can't make any mistakes.
My political career is on the line.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm here.
Where are you, Mr. Kim?
I will go and escort you.
Check him out.
Get him.
Mr. President,
we have succeeded in arresting Mr. Kim.
Thank you.
We arrested Mr. Kim thanks to you.
I'll give you a chance
to prove your innocence.
If you are innocent,
would you become a trap for us?
A trap to catch the mastermind
behind the bombing.
It couldn't have been easy.
Did you believe I was innocent
from the start?
Ever since you saved yourself
from my trap of an open investigation.
First, I'd like to ask
for your understanding.
There was a reason why the Blue House
decided not to make a statement
about the conspired military coup
led by Army Chief of Staff Eun Hui-jeong
reported by the media yesterday.
Some of the people
that plotted the coup d'etat...
were accomplices of the bomber
of the National Assembly Building.
-Mr. Kim.
-Mr. Kim!
-I have a question.
Then are you saying
those involved in the coup d'etat
were behind the bombing?
Was the military involved in the bombing?
While this is a time
where all things are possible,
it is also a sensitive time where
we must refrain from making assumptions.
However,
we will share with you the progress made
with the investigation today.
Kim Su-hyeon, also known as Mr. Kim,
who is believed to be
one of the masterminds behind the bombing
was arrested immediately before
he fled the country
by the NIS Terrorism Task Force
and the Joint Investigation Team.
As one of the main people
behind the bombing was arrested,
we believe we are a step closer
to the truth about the bombing.
Here you go.
Every time there is progress
in the investigation,
the Blue House will share it
with you quickly and precisely
to satisfy the people's right to know,
while doing its best
to create a transparent government
that communicates with its people.
The Blue House will do everything possible
-to settle the coup d'etat...
-Now the media
won't be able to say the Blue House
is concealing information, right?
You never know.
The number of views is more important
than the number of subscribers.
Some could criticize
that the government is all show
as it released a statement
when there hasn't been any progress
in the investigation this afternoon.
How were you able to stay
at the Blue House for over a decade?
You can't survive elsewhere
once you get used to this battlefield.
You'll get too bored.
Bored?
I have nothing else to give you.
This is nice.
President Park is a very weird person.
Why?
Isn't he whom you were looking for?
Someone who knows how to win.
That's right.
Until now,
I thought politics was all about winning.
That there was a clear-cut
winner and loser,
and that the winner takes it all.
A world monopolized by the winner.
That was what I believed.
What about now? Has it changed?
President Park's politics...
is different.
He is always the winner, but it's weird.
No one loses,
including Chief An last time
and Assemblywoman Yun.
Secretary Han,
do you still think he isn't qualified
to be the next President?
Let's not...
talk about that.
If it's President Park,
wouldn't it be possible?
A different government
and a different Korea that you
and President Yang Jin-man
dreamed of.
Can't we hope for it again?
Must I, at this age,
dream of such things again?
The belief that it is possible to create
a good world with a good person.
Must I put everything I have on the line
to torment myself with false hope
and ride on
that emotional rollercoaster again?
I've already learned...
that those fairytale endings
don't exist in real life.
You're...
very cruel.
I issue an executive order
to carry out my duty
to maintain pre-existing orders.
If you wish to issue an executive order,
you will have to fire me.
Wait, Secretary Han.
Make your choice, sir.
Secretary Cha,
call a Cabinet meeting.
The agenda
is the issue of an executive order.
As of now,
Secretary Han is dismissed from his job.
Why me?
Why did you recommend me to the President?
Why did you bring me here when I had plans
to go back to school?
Did something happen?
Didn't you say I just needed to fulfill
my duties as a citizen?
Then why...
Why am I put in a position where
I take people's lives?
Why?
Why do I have to do this because of you?
Isn't the hearing
a verification process
of candidates by the National Assembly?
The opposing party
asked for a verification,
and I just faithfully complied to it.
Have I created a controversy
that you have to object to?
Just to be lauded by the public,
must I push my son into hell?
Is that what politics is?
Someone commits these attacks,
and others sacrifice themselves
to stop the attacks.
What does Korea mean to them?
Do they even think of it
as the same country?
What kind of country is Korea...
to you, Secretary Han?
When you failed,
I thought...
we no longer had hope.
Tell me!
Was I wrong?
Did you say to join your campaign
if I decided
you have a chance at winning?
-Secretary Han.
-I've lived too long
and been in politics for too long
to be naive enough to believe
things will be different this time
and that you'd be different.
This place
is hell, where nothing ends until everyone
becomes a monster.
Do you still plan
to run for President and stay in politics?
I found one person here.
You still haven't turned into a monster.
You were the one who taught me
about a citizen's duty.
You taught me
how to use my power and not be pressured
by my position.
Won't you help me?
So that I won't turn into a monster.
Help me
sit behind that desk
and govern this country as a civilian.
Once the election campaign starts,
we should do something
about the color of your tie.
The length of your pants
needs some work as well.
You need to look
as conservative as possible.
Does that mean you will...
Let's do this.
We may be late,
but let's try it again.
Resident registration number.
820517-109467.
Kim Su-hyeon.
Addressed as "Mr. Kim"
or "Mr. Kim, the Tailor."
You're incredible.
Everyone from Assemblymen
to the Army Chief of Staff
followed your orders blindly
without even knowing your real name.
Do you know why?
It was because of the VIP
who was supporting you.
Tell me.
Who is the VIP?
Who is this person that is behind
the attack on the National Assembly
and can go back and forth from North Korea
to recruit Myung Hae-joon?
Who is this person
with immense wealth and power
who can easily grant requests
made by anyone?
Whose gopher are you?
Who...
is the VIP?
President...
Park Mu-jin.
Bring him here.
That is, if you want me to tell you
who the VIP is.
What?
Until then,
I won't say a single thing.
Mr. Kim knows very well
whom he needs to grab onto to survive.
It won't be easy to make him talk.
MILITARY INTELLIGENCE COMMAND
KIM SU-HYEON
I thought I should report this to you.
I don't know why,
but he's demanding to see you.
Why does he want
to see me?
He's adamant about disclosing the identity
of the VIP,
whom we believe is the mastermind
of the attack, in front of you.
Taking into consideration the protocol
and the current political situation,
I understand that
this isn't an easy decision to make
for both you and the Blue House.
Feel free to discuss it and let me know.
Agent Han.
Tomorrow
is the last day before my resignation.
It's my last day as the Acting President.
You might have assumed it already,
but the secretarial staff
of the Blue House
will most likely oppose this.
Unnecessary speculations
wouldn't help my election campaign.
There's nothing I can do if they oppose.
Yes, I understand.
That's exactly why I should see him
right now.
I won't discuss this with my staff.
-Sir.
-Mr. Kang.
Which article was it again?
"No public official
of the Security Service..."
Article nine.
"Shall divulge confidential information."
Please, Mr. Kang.
I heard that you wanted to see me.
Why is that?
Why did you say
that you'd only disclose it to me?
Because you have power,
and I need someone with power.
Then keep your promise.
The VIP.
Who is the mastermind behind the attack?
The VIP is...
me.
What did he say?
It's me.
It's no one else.
It's me,
the person sitting in front of you.
Are you saying that
you single-handedly came up with
the Assembly Building bombing
and put it into action?
How was that possible?
It was possible...
because you were
at the beginning and the end
of the attack.
Park Mu-jin.
You helped complete the attack.
What do you mean?
How did I help complete the attack?
That person completed the attack
through you.
Who is this person?
Should we request help from
the police and prosecutors
and investigate openly?
If it hadn't been concealed,
it may never have happened.
We could experience trial and error.
Isn't all of that what we call
history?
Subtitle translations by Sun-young Baek