ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
PLACES AND EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL
Now, please take an oath.
"Oath.
As a candidate
for a voter-nominated office,
I solemnly declare and affirm
that what I state shall be the truth,
the whole truth and nothing but the truth.
March 22, 2019.
Candidate Oh Yeong-seok."
The confirmation hearing
for the minister nominee
is going well.
The nonparty cabinet is the result of
a joint effort between the ruling
and the opposition parties.
Most importantly, it shows
the government's strong determination
to ensure a fair, seamless
presidential election,
which will take place in 40 days.
CONFIRMATION HEARING WELL UNDERWAY
When the cabinet reshuffle is completed,
people will realize that President Park
was like a relief pitcher who took
the mound in the midst of a crisis.
Mr. President
will outrank all other candidates
by a wide margin.
A pitcher who takes the mound
before he's warmed up
is highly likely to get injured.
It'll only cut his career short.
To run for President,
he'll have to resign from office
at least 30 days prior to the election.
He can't run
as a candidate this time.
As for the Acting President role,
the newly appointed ministers can fill in.
Is President Park in agreement with you?
Has he agreed
to run
for President?
Would you consider
running for President, sir?
Not as the Acting President,
but as the president
of the Republic of Korea.
Do you think
I'm suitable for that position?
I think you can win.
As far as I know, you're the candidate
who is most likely to win the election.
Mr. President.
About the bomber, Myung Hae-joon...
Where is he now?
I cannot disclose that information
for national security's sake.
Are you sure that he's alive?
What?
That's...
Is the rumor true?
Some are saying that the bomber,
Myung Hae-joon, is dead.
-What?
-He's dead?
-Myung Hae-joon?
-Seriously?
Did something really happen?
There's a witness who saw his corpse
being transferred
from the DSSC to the NFS.
-What?
-To the National Forensic Service?
We received a tip
that one of the four corpses,
which hasn't been collected
by the bereaved,
is Myung Hae-joon.
Is it true?
Did he die during the interrogation?
Was he tortured or abused in any way?
-Please tell us.
-What happened to Myung Hae-joon?
-Tell us.
-Is he dead?
-Tell us the truth.
-Please make a comment.
-What happened during the interrogation?
-Tell us the truth.
Myung Hae-joon...
During his interrogation,
he was neither tortured
nor abused in any way.
Are you saying he's alive?
-Tell us.
-Is he alive?
-Then where is he now?
Raising groundless speculations
regarding him
may pose a serious threat
to national security.
I can't say anything else.
-Then is he alive?
-He wasn't tortured at all?
-Tell us the truth.
-Answer the question.
THE BLUE HOUSE
NCND.
"Neither confirm nor deny."
Their strategy is the Glomar response.
I have to say, the tip is quite detailed.
Well, the fact that they can't
firmly deny the speculation
means that it's true. Right?
Myung Hae-joon was murdered?
By who?
Well, we'll have to find out.
Hey, Sin-yeong.
You're no longer
in the Blue House press corps.
I can't wait until they call me
and tell me that dinner is ready.
I'm hungry,
and I can already smell the food.
The reporters have caught on to it,
so there will be all sorts of speculations
regarding Myung Hae-joon.
Yes, probably.
I always thought
freedom of the press
would be guaranteed in the South,
unlike the North, where I was born.
However, all I can do now
is saying that we can't confirm it
at the moment
with a stern face
in front of the press corps,
who insist that the people
have the right to know.
I'm an incompetent communications officer.
A press secretary who's a coward.
If we tell them
the truth,
will it help us catch the one
behind Myung Hae-joon's murder?
Broadcasting the details
of our investigation in real time
will only tell the bombers
how they can flee. Am I wrong?
At the moment, national security
matters more
than the people's right to know.
It's for the public good.
You're able to judge situations quickly,
and you can handle crises well.
Who can do a better job
than you?
Well...
I do have to say that you whine more
than I thought you would.
What do you think of a man
who likes to whine a little?
Go on in.
The reporters aren't the only problem.
The opposition party will make
a big fuss over it if it's made public.
You saw what Ms. Yun did.
She won't even hesitate
to get you impeached.
She'll launch
a full-on political attack against you.
But this is about national security,
which both she and the opposition party
consider the number one priority.
It is also their favorite card
because it can help them
bring their supporters together.
Whether you want
to take part in it or not,
they're getting ready for the election.
It's like a black hole.
They'll turn every situation
into a political strife.
In Ms. Yun's eyes,
the Blue House will look like
a presidential candidate's
campaign office.
Her competitor, whom she must beat
at all costs.
Then our priority should be
finding out who killed Myung Hae-joon.
To ensure national security
as well as to win the political battle.
I'll contact the NIS right away
to see if they've obtained any clues
regarding the killer.
Na-gyeong!
I found him.
Room 119.
I found him in the security footage
from the camera in front
of the air-raid shelter.
Do you see him?
Zoom in on the face.
Look at my eyes.
I found him in the security footage
recovered
by the Digital Forensics Center.
And thanks to that,
my eyes are all bloodshot now.
Don't you see it?
Dedication isn't a virtue.
It's our duty.
Goodness.
Do you take classes or what?
Who taught you to talk
like a stuffy old man?
Right here.
At 3:14 p.m.
It was right before the explosion.
This is him, right?
Assemblyman Oh Yeong-seok.
Mr. Chairman
and all members of the Committee.
I am here today
to prove to you all
that my capabilities and moral standards
are well suited for the role of
the Minister of National Defense.
We found it.
It's firm evidence that shows
the bombers had designated Assemblyman Oh
as a survivor before the attack.
Assemblyman Oh was caught on
the camera in front of Room 119
at 3:14 p.m.,
which was right before the explosion.
We must report this to the Blue House
immediately,
before the confirmation hearing ends.
The DSSC, which is partially responsible
for Myung Hae-joon's death,
operates under National Defense.
If Oh Yeong-seok is appointed
Minister of National Defense,
he'll try to bury this case.
We were waiting for you, Agent Jeong.
How is the investigation going?
Any progress?
We found
the killer, sir.
You found the killer?
Who is it? Where is the killer now?
Agent Jeong?
Who is the person
that killed Myung Hae-joon?
It's me, sir.
I killed Myung Hae-joon.
What did you...
just say?
I killed Myung Hae-joon,
Mr. President.
DAY 42: DOUBT
EPISODE 8
State your team, name, and position.
I'm the chief of
NIS' Counterterrorism Task Force,
Jeong Han-mo.
You said
Agent Jeong is well respected
within the NIS, right?
Yes, I'm sure he is.
From the Counterintelligence Task Force
to the Counterterrorism Center,
he's been on the so-called elite path
at the NIS.
Then why do you think he did
such a reckless thing?
If he thought about the career he's built
or his family even just once...
It couldn't have been an easy decision,
considering his age and the fact
that he has a family to support.
Why do you think Agent Jeong
killed Myung Hae-joon?
He deserved to die.
Our President and many innocent civilians
lost their lives because of the attack,
and yet he neither repented
nor begged for forgiveness.
I...
I did
the best thing that I could do.
Something's wrong.
You know
he'd never do something like that.
I'm his witness and his alibi, sir.
I was with Han-mo
the whole time we were investigating
Myung Hae-joon at the DSSC.
If it's actually true,
there's no way I wouldn't know about it.
I'm just as frustrated as you are.
They're saying he has confessed to it!
It's not like he was tortured or coerced.
He walked in there
and confessed to the murder.
What else needs to be said?
What are you doing now?
Agent Han?
From this moment forward,
all the data regarding Myung Hae-joon case
will be transferred
to State Bureau of Investigation.
You can't just do that
without any discussion--
You've been suspended, Agent Han.
Would you please come with us
to the office?
According to the regulation,
there will be an interrogation to find out
if you're Agent Jeong's accomplice.
Accomplice?
Please cooperate.
Otherwise, we'll force you to.
Hey, don't forget
to take things like USB sticks.
Get her!
Agent Han!
Stop!
Stop there!
Hey! Han Na-Gyeong!
Damn it.
Hey, Han Na-Gyeong!
Stop there right now!
Hey, stop!
Damn it!
Stop, Han Na-Gyeong!
Hey!
Stop her!
You stop there!
Hey!
Hey! Stop!
Stop the car!
Damn it!
You won't have to worry about
being tracked for a while.
This is a stolen car that has been
in the office parking lot for ages.
These are a copy of the things
Han-mo tried to report to the Blue House.
Stop the car. I'll go by myself from here.
If you're away for too long,
you might get suspected too.
Promise me
even if things go wrong,
you won't mention my name
during the interrogation.
What?
I can't trust you.
Oh, well. Na-Gyeong.
You might as well just make this work.
You must make this work.
Don't get caught and don't get hurt.
Be careful. Please.
Ji-won.
Thanks.
Mr. Oh.
You defeated the North Korean army
seven years ago
at the Battle of Baengnyeong, right?
That was the first battle we won
ever since the Korean War.
Am I right?
We did defeat the North Korean army,
but we didn't win
the Battle of Baengnyeong.
Fourteen members of my troupe
lost their precious lives.
As the commander of the battle,
I think about my responsibility...
for the defeat every single day.
Agent Han?
You wanted me to call you once
I was certain about the bomber.
Assemblyman Oh
must not become
the Minister of National Defense.
Are you saying he's unqualified somehow?
Is this related to the blueprint
of the National Assembly building?
We'll talk about the details in person.
I'm on my way to the hearing.
Mr. Oh.
-Here's the next question.
-Sir.
May I suggest we take a short break?
Before we confirm the hearing report
about Mr. Oh,
there's something I'd like to discuss
with our party members.
Please, sir.
As Ms. Yun suggested,
we'll take a short break.
It's getting too late.
It's almost time.
Do you think it's reliable information?
I proposed her a deal with the blueprint.
Usually, people would say yes
even if they didn't mean it.
There's nothing to lose.
She got an offer from the opposing party
when the administration
is about to change.
But Agent Han turn the offer down.
I trust her.
AGENT HAN NA-GYEONG
Please stay away.
There was an accident here.
-There's been an accident.
-Please step away.
Excuse me.
Ma'am. Ma'am.
Have you heard from the informant yet?
It's been an hour already.
We need to finish it up by today, ma'am.
She said he's unqualified for the position
of Minister of National Defense.
Security is important now more than ever.
This is about...
appointing Minister of National Defense.
Please just trust me
and give it some more time.
I trust you.
But will the other members
trust you as well?
You failed to scout Assemblyman Oh,
and everyone in there knows that.
You were against establishing
a nonparty cabinet too.
If it gets any more delayed,
they will say things
like you're trying to ruin the hearing
and besmirch him out of personal reasons.
Ma'am, can you hear me?
Ma'am.
Ma'am, please stay...
where you are.
You did great.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
I'll see you around.
Congratulations, Assemblyman Oh.
Your hard work didn't go unnoticed too.
You managed to survive not only
on the battlefield but even a bombing.
That kind of luck
never strikes a person even once,
but it happened
to you twice.
Luck?
Do you believe
you'll always be this lucky?
At least for today, it seems like
Lady Luck is on my side,
not yours.
I'll see you then.
Assemblyman Oh's confirmation hearing
just ended, sir.
His appointment was accepted
without any specific hitches.
CERTIFICATE OF APPOINTMENT
Is it too far into the night
to meet Assemblyman Oh?
What is it about?
He was here on that day.
PERSONNEL FILE
JEONG HAN-MO
The day Agent Jeong came here
to debrief me on the interrogation.
Something about him felt off.
Agent Jeong?
Yes.
He said he had a lead
on the Myung Hae-joon Case,
but quickly changed his word.
It's as if he had become
a different person.
I want to know
if Mr. Oh thinks the same way.
What's there to be curious about?
The answer is clear as day.
A witness who holds
the key to the investigation
suddenly changes his or her statement?
That only happens when
someone who shouldn't hear it is present.
Who was in the room with you?
Do you have any leads?
Yes, I believe so.
This way.
I'm glad to hear that.
It's a relief.
I had no idea you'd be here too.
CURRENT AFFAIRS CHANNEL
HOW DID THE SURVIVOR OH YEONG-SEOK
BECOME THE NATION'S HERO?
Yes, over here.
Make sure it's in line.
Nice.
-Ms. Kim.
-Yes?
No one will give you a merit badge
for saving duct tape in the Blue House.
Don't you know that
this is President Park's first time
at an event like this?
Look where you marked, for example.
All right. One, two, three.
The spot...
I see you marked the right spot.
Secretary Cha, did you call for me?
Gosh, look at the dust on your suit.
And who are you again?
-Sorry?
-Let me ask you all this.
Raise your hand
if you heard me calling for him.
No?
Ms. Kim, you're doing a great job.
CERTIFICATE OF APPOINTMENT
OH YEONG-SEOK
ACTING PRESIDENT PARK MU-JIN
CERTIFICATE OF APPOINTMENT
OH YEONG-SEOK
Minister candidate Oh Yeong-seok's
approval rating has skyrocketed.
With a rating of 19.8 percent,
he's even ahead of Yun Chan-gyeong
in the presidential race.
He's in second place
right behind President Park.
He must've
won over the public
at his hearing yesterday.
His rating has been measured
ever since he gave his eulogy,
and it's been on the rise.
It's quite funny if you ask me.
The two with the highest approval ratings
are both survivors of this recent attack.
It reflects how much
the people were terrorized by it.
That fear had them
make heroes out of the survivors.
It was one heck of a move
to have Mr. Oh join the nonparty cabinet.
I'm sure it'll immensely help
President Park run the government.
Good job.
I had a tip
that implied how Assemblyman Oh
is unfit to be a minister.
The tip came from Agent Han Na-gyeong
of the NIS Terrorism Task Force.
Please have a seat.
What disqualifies him of being appointed?
What was the tip?
I don't know yet.
She called me on the road
and asked me to stall the hearing.
I haven't heard back from her
even up until this moment though.
Around the same time,
a big car accident occurred
near where the hearing was being held.
Odd, right?
However, no one with injuries
from a car crash
was admitted to
any of the hospitals near the site.
Do you think that
Agent Han was a victim of the accident?
I don't think it was an accident.
Agent Han told me
that she had definitive proof regarding
the National Assembly Building bombing.
She was even adamant about
Assemblyman Oh being unfit for Minister.
But then she disappeared
without a single trace.
Do you suspect Assemblyman Oh?
And you're suspecting me.
Mr. Oh
has devoted his life to this country.
And you think I'm crossing into
a dangerous territory by accusing him.
I'm here without any proof after all.
You must think it's to put a dent
in your nonparty cabinet.
I didn't actually think
you'd agree with me easily.
Why not?
You're probably scared
because I could be right.
It would be even scarier to admit
that you were wrong
in appointing him as Minister.
Aren't I right?
Please take care of this. Thanks.
You're actually
more competent that I gave you credit for.
President Park
has become a true politician.
Secretary Cha, call the NIS.
I need to verify something.
I heard that Agent Han
found definitive proof regarding
the National Assembly Building bombing.
Is this true?
Sorry?
What do you mean by definitive proof?
Oh, I must apologize, sir.
Chief Jeong and Agent Han
were asked to debrief you in person,
-so I am not aware of all the findings--
-Agent Han.
Where is she right now?
There's an issue with Agent Han
at the moment.
The State Bureau of Investigation
informed her
that they'd be looking into her
being Agent Jeong's accomplice.
She must've gotten scared
because she's gone AWOL.
The agency
is doing its best
to locate her as we speak.
Please report back to me
as soon as you find her.
I need to ask her something in person.
Yes, Mr. President.
Hey, you're up.
Drink this.
What happened?
How did I get here?
You took the words right out of my mouth.
I received a call.
They said you were in an accident
and asked me for my address.
A call?
From whom?
Let's check the caller ID.
What's the number?
It was from a payphone
somewhere near
the Seoul Metropolitan Council.
A payphone?
Who could've been?
The bell rang, so I opened the door.
You were the only one outside.
Don't you remember?
Do you remember who it was?
No.
MS. YUN CHAN-GYEONG
Why aren't you answering?
The only person who knew
I was headed to the hearing
was Ms. Yun.
So the car accident wasn't random.
CALL HISTORY
POWER OFF
Ji-won, we can only
trust each other right now.
What about the hearing?
Was Assemblyman Oh's appointment approved?
Congratulations.
I heard that
your appointment was approved
with a unanimous vote.
Thank you.
I'm guessing you didn't
hear the news though.
The head of the congressional hearing
informed me
that Agent Han of the NIS
tipped Ms. Yun off
about there being
a reason for disqualification.
Although, it turned out to be nothing.
Why do you think Agent Han said so though?
She's not exactly in a position
to make false accusations like that.
Agent Han
lost a loved one
in the attack.
I was told she lost her fiancé during
the National Assembly Building bombing.
He died
while I lived.
She's been suspicious of my survival
from the get-go.
No matter how many times it's explained,
even though it's the truth,
it'll be hard for her to accept.
I've been there myself.
After the Battle of Baengnyeong?
Living in South Korea
only ends in two ways.
You either become a victim one day
or the bereaved.
That day at sea,
I asked myself over and over again
why those innocent young souls had to die.
I just couldn't accept the truth.
I couldn't believe it.
However,
nobody gave me an answer.
The conservatives
who uses national security to score votes
took advantage of us,
and the progressives
who cry peace for their votes
turned a blind eye.
Is that why
you got into politics?
I chose a path
where I could find the answers myself.
And Agent Han
is one of the people
that I wish
to speak for.
What time is the investiture
for the new ministers?
It's at 2 p.m., ma'am.
Will President Park appoint
Assemblyman Oh as a minister?
I don't know,
but it feels like I'm being evaluated.
Excuse me?
If he trusts me as a politician,
he'll reconsider.
If he appoints Assemblyman Oh,
won't that mean he doesn't trust me?
I wonder
what kind of choice
President Park will make.
I've chosen to answer myself.
It's time to leave, sir.
The investiture will start soon.
Okay.
You'd like to postpone the investiture?
If you do that now,
wouldn't the media
come up with wild speculations?
Rumors about your health,
conflict within the Blue House,
the Blue House playing a power game...
There will be various rumors.
Please help me out here.
Mr. Kim.
I need time...
to verify the candidates.
I'll leave...
the media up to you.
Do you plan to withdraw
Assemblyman Oh's nomination?
You can't do that, sir.
Assemblyman Oh
is a symbolic member
of the nonparty cabinet.
Withdrawing for any reason,
would only mean the Blue House
failed in personnel verification.
The opposing party will use this
as an excuse to annul the nonparty cabinet
and say it was bad government.
You're the biggest threat
to Assemblywoman Yun
as a presidential candidate.
Other than Assemblywoman Yun's claim,
we currently have no evidence
on the suspicions of Assemblyman Oh, sir.
Assemblywoman Yun
was trying to get you impeached
just a few days ago.
She's a master in politics.
She may have other intentions, sir.
What should I do?
Should I call the ceremony hall?
It isn't too late yet.
Let me ask you one thing.
Isn't the hearing
a verification process
of candidates by the National Assembly?
The opposing party
asked for a verification,
and I just faithfully complied to it.
Have I created a controversy
that you have to object to?
Then
when you met with Assemblyman Oh,
did you find him suspicious in any way?
It's the opposite.
Then why are you taking such a big chance?
Don't you see
what Assemblywoman Yun wants?
Assemblyman Oh is someone everyone--
I don't know what Assemblywoman Yun wants
or what kind of person Assemblyman Oh is.
I want to trust them, but can't.
As for now, I don't even know
whether they are friend or foe.
So I've decided to choose neither of them.
-Mr. President.
-What I believe in...
are the principles and system
of our administration.
It's controlled our nation so far.
Until Assemblyman Oh is verified,
I don't plan to appoint him
Minister of National Defense.
The nonparty cabinet
was a test to verify
your administrative ability.
If you postpone the investiture
and withdraw his nomination,
that will clearly become
your error and misadministration.
Your approval rating
will definitely plunge.
Are you okay with that?
You want me to be
a presidential candidate?
Yes.
I can't be the candidate that has
a good chance of winning
like you want me to be.
That's my answer.
Yes, sir.
I'll have the investiture...
postponed as you wish, sir.
What did he say?
He just isn't used to this.
Taking chances on political matters
or how the Blue House works.
He isn't used to it?
The President isn't desperate enough.
I
think every day
that during the previous government,
we should've used the power
we had to fight and win
against the opposing party
or anyone that were against us
by any means.
If we didn't give them an excuse
or even the smallest reason to attack us,
if we pushed back harder,
if I just insisted to the President...
more strongly...
Then...
he wouldn't...
have been ridiculed...
throughout his entire term,
nor...
would he have gone down in history
so pathetically.
President Yang Jin-man...
was the kindest person I've ever met.
That's why we failed.
I really don't understand.
Why did Han-mo confess
that he killed Myung Hae-joon?
I need to ask around
to find out what happened to Han-mo.
You can't be careless like that.
Don't you get it?
We've all fallen into a trap.
Han-mo went to the Blue House
to report Assemblyman Oh
to higher authorities
and got locked up as a murderer.
You almost died
on your way to the hearing.
I followed your orders,
and now I've been suspended
indefinitely without pay.
I haven't even paid off my car yet.
Are you trying to make me feel bad?
No, I'm not.
I'm saying an agent's commitment
isn't a virtue,
but an obligation.
It's what you said.
Something this cliche should be
engraved in stone for the NIS.
Who in the world said that to you?
The agent who trained me.
Kim Jun-o of Espionage Team Two.
This is Myung Hae-joon's killer.
Is he the one that attacked you yesterday?
It's him.
Tae-ik.
Do you work out?
You've lost weight.
Golf isn't much exercise.
I can't seem to lower my score.
It's always above 80.
Maybe I lost weight
because I have much to worry about.
Two of my men...
I'm really sad, Mr. Kim.
Make sure I don't have to worry.
I told my men in the State Bureau
of Investigation to find Na-gyeong.
The Blue House wasn't doing anything.
Would you like cuffs this time?
You have to find her first.
Don't have others do it,
but find her yourself.
Outsourcing causes problems.
Isn't that right, Mr. Kim?
You need to learn how to wait
after giving orders
for your men to grow.
Is that how the VIP taught you?
He trusts you too much.
Those that are in charge
of state affairs don't even meet.
We don't know each other's names or faces.
How will we get anything done
without being connected?
Isn't it better not to know...
for everyone?
Did I keep you waiting?
They must get chatty with age.
Director Ji...
seemed to be hoping you'd meet with him.
He works in the shadows
but wants to stand in the light?
Silent commitment.
I wonder why people engrave
that on stone...
when they can't live up to it.
President Park seems to be looking
for Agent Han.
Director Ji will take care of her,
so the investiture
for the Minister of National Defense
goes smoothly.
Is the investiture that important?
I think we got everything we needed
during the hearing.
I saw
that your approval rating soared
after the hearing,
and you are up there with President Park.
Now, everyone will move
with the presidential election in mind,
including Assemblywoman Yun
and the Blue House.
Those people...
How great a world
are they trying to create?
If we could change the world
with an election,
humans...
would have done everything
to get rid of elections.
And a long time ago at that.
Don't you agree?
That's why elections are like
Santa Claus to adults.
It's a lie we want to believe in.
Don't you think you can give people
their gift?
President Park won't be registered...
as a presidential candidate.
What should we tell the press
about the postponement?
Let's say it's a problem
in administrative procedure.
It's a first with an acting president.
Whom do you have in mind?
The presidential candidate registration
is in 10 days.
President Park turned you down.
But...
I'm sure someone new
will show up
as the presidential candidate.
Good luck!
Nothing in this house is off the record
nor do embargoes work.
-Is this true?
-Please answer us!
What is it?
Who could it have been?
Why bother now?
It's a scandal
regarding Yang Jin-man's ministers.
Why would they release a scandal
about those who are already dead?
Why do you think they tipped off
the press?
How is the press responding?
So you're saying that the same tip
was given to Joongang Daily,
the public TV, and the news channel,
right?
That's an internal document
with the Blue House's mark on it.
Was there a whistle-blower? Who was it?
Do you have no clue either?
Even Jang-hyun, the chief
of the Blue House, had no idea either.
Based on the tip,
I'm certain it was a whistle-blower.
The tip is...
JANG GUN-HO'S
INVOLVEMENT IN CORRUPTION
I can't believe them.
"Jang Gun-ho, Former Minister
of National Defense's Involvement
in Corruption.
Choi Jong-bok, Former Minister
of Construction and Transportation's
Investment in Real Estate.
Park Ji-yoon, former Minister
of Gender Equality
and Family's husband's sex scandal."
Also, "Former--"
Was the Chief Office already aware
of this?
It is our duty to monitor
our public officials.
We now know that the tip wasn't fake.
So now, we need to know who released
these documents to the press.
This was top secret information that
only the Chief Office knew about.
So? Are you accusing me?
Just be blatant and tell me
that you're suspecting me.
Don't beat around the bush.
It feels like crap.
This is a logical inference.
You've done this before.
If that's the case,
you're not that innocent either.
Remember Myung Hae-joon's video?
In order to gain political wins,
there's nothing you can't do.
I'm sorry to interrupt
your passionate debate,
but this is odd.
This tip has all the big and small issues
regarding Yang Jin-man's men.
But why isn't there anything
about Mr. President?
Not even one bit.
The anonymous whistle-blower has claimed
that they also have scandals related
to Acting President Park Mu-jin.
They weren't after Yang Jin-man's cabinet.
President Park was their target.
Why did they reveal scandals
regarding the cabinet?
They've all passed away.
Because the scandals were proven
to be true.
They're warning all of us
that President Park's scandal
is also true.
They also have scandals related
to Acting President Park Mu-jin.
If this information proves to be true,
it is likely to cause a great commotion.
Sir.
Is there anything
you can think of?
Whether it's related to your work
or your private life.
What kind of information do you think
the informant has?
He was evaluated during the hearing,
and he had the best reputation in Sejong.
Since he's always been at school,
it can't be anything too serious, right?
If it's related to school, it could be
his thesis, position, or research funds.
If it's his ministry,
collusion with the local government?
-Come on.
What? It's better to predict
such things before they hit you.
But it's best to prevent them.
"Collusion with the local government"?
Why are you writing that down?
If you tell us first, it'll be better.
If we make a move first,
we can prevent this from blowing up.
In addition, the whistle-blower stated
that they will release the scandals
related to President Park Mu-jin tomorrow.
Sir.
Will you please tell us?
The public is in commotion
about how President Park's scandals
will affect this country.
Someone who has claimed to know
about his scandals appeared.
This is ridiculous.
Is this true?
Agent Han is not someone who would
commit such a crime.
Am I to push them into the gates of hell
so that I can be commended?
I wonder how Mu-jin will react
once he finds out that he was a part
of the bombing.
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi