x: smolsannie
[ Healing Kiss ]
Live streaming guy × Tired girl
I truly believe...
That we were destined to meet.
Like always
I came home tired from work.
If you're asking how it became like this...
I'm home...
My life's only healing is this.
As expected, he's cool.
Alright!
Today is the beloved program,
"Surprise! Real-Life Princess Next Door!"
Let's get started right away.
To the princess out there, please do me a favour,
And send me a direct message.
You have five minutes.
Then I'll immediately intrude into your room.
This super popular program will indulge your every desire.
It's the real deal, no trickery.
This project, as I've mentioned before,
Is a personal dream of mine.
As for what that dream is...
I'll keep it a secret from you all until it comes true.
Thanks for watching.
And... send.
Applying is my daily routine.
Actually, I just do it out of habit at this point.
[You have a new message]
I don't actually think I'll win.
Cleaning someone else's house somehow boosts your mood, don't you think?
I actually like household chores like this.
Ah, it's so clean. Incredible.
I won
Sorry for intruding~
I've arrived~
You're our princess this time.
Wave.
How is it?
It feels good.
That's a relief.
But... I'm embarrassed.
Alright~
Then, please lie down on your side.
It's like a moment from a dream...
It's like a dream...
It seems like a dream, doesn't it?
However, it's not a dream!
Yes, this is "Surprise! Real-Life
Princess Next Door!"
I wish I had dressed up better...
You didn't know you would win.
But...
You also look very lovely the way you are right now.
Lastly, let's make a toast to our chance encounter.
- Cheers.
Well then, that's all for today.
We've decided that this episode,
Will be the final episode of this program.
So... stay tuned for the next episode.
If you liked this stream, please subscribe!
Bye-bye.
The dream is coming to an end...
Do you understand why I was doing a program like this?
Huh?
It was... a dream of yours?
...Is that right?
What do you think my dream is?
I wonder what it is...
I...
Wanted to experience love at first sight.
Huh?
I guess I was drawn to the idea of love at first sight.
I wanted to try to have a
fateful encounter in my life.
So I thought, there's no choice but to take action.
That's why...
The program ended today.
Huh?
Huh?!
Today...
My dream has finally come true.
Huh?!
Because I truly believe...
That this is a fateful encounter.
Okay...?
Is this...
Hmm?
...A dream?
I don't want to wake up from this dream...
You won't.
Why not?
Because it's real.
It is a dream.
No, it's not.
Yes it is.
Nowadays, even dreams can come true out of nowhere.
This look is also cute.
- It's not cute...
- Yes, it is.
- No, it's not.
- It is.
Glasses don't suit me...
Again.
Five left.
Alright, I get it!
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
meow :3