[English subtitles are available]
Continue the story.
Where we left off:
Guo and Gu visited the ghost market.
Ding Mao went to the police station to check for missing persons.
Two clues point to one.
Xue Yuanyuan, a young lady from the Xue mansion, had just given birth.
Recently, both Xue and the kid died.
Guo Deyou swindled Ding Mao,
on the grounds of condolence to investigate.
Master Xue Qingyang thought that the adulterer came to the house
and caught Ding Mao.
Guo and Gu arrived in time.
Xue Qingyang told the previous situation.
Xue Yuanyuan had an affair with someone and conceived a child.
Xue Qingyang put her under house arrest.
But Miss Xue ran away with the child
and fell into the river and drowned.
Guo Deyou asked the Xue family to bring back the dead baby
and bury the mother and baby together.
Junior Tientsin Mystic perceived that
there must be more than that.
This brings:
Tientsin Mystic's discernment of grievance and criminal suspect to justice.
Men in black stole the coffin and the body.
Guo Deyou explored the Haihe River at night.
The case of the floating body disturbs Tianjin.
You've been living in the deserted temple for two days.
Are you used to it?
Yes.
It's a lot more peaceful than the chamber of commerce.
You don't know how to do this,
so stay out of it.
I'll learn.
When I first went abroad,
I could do nothing either.
But the only good thing about me is
curiousness.
Uncle Gui,
do you have a cigarette?
Because just now I held the red umbrella,
in order to let the body not see three light
and gather the soul.
But it was you who carried the coffin.
All this bad luck has come to you.
If you don't mind,
I'll light a cigarette
and smoke it for you.
Thank you for your kindness.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Do you want to learn lighting-up to analyze grievances?
Of course I do.
But I know that
I just joined the faculty.
I can only learn it after my brother learns.
He won't learn in his life.
Why?
He couldn't touch
anything that had a whiff of irritation.
Not to mention smoking and drinking,
If his clothes aren't washed clean,
they will tickle all over him.
His condition is called anaphylaxis.
People choke and cough when they smell smoke.
It's a protective mechanism in the body.
Because of their constitution,
some people are more sensitive
and have a greater reaction to smoke.
Because of the stimulation,
some people even become delirious,
hallucinate, amplify the senses,
and even have a choking reaction,
resulting in death.
Are you not feeling well?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Let me show you to the front room for a rest.
Don't bother.
The jade earrings...
Yuanyuan was wearing them
the day she was found.
Young master.
Uncle Hu.
Are you...
What's the matter?
A trivial matter.
The daughter of the secretary general of the municipal government,
Xiao Lanlan, is going to be engaged.
You will attend on behalf of the canal transport Chamber of Commerce.
Don't we have a problem with the Xiao family?
That was a generation ago.
This is the best time to defuse the relationship.
This is a red-letter day for you.
Why do you have time to come to me?
Have some tea, please.
I haven't seen Qian Zixian
for a week.
Miss Xiao,
please think again.
Maybe Childe Qian has been busy with other matters
and forgot about this.
I have a hunch.
He won't show up at the engagement party tonight.
Childe Qian
was usually playful. It's fine.
But how can he...
This is missing,
not playing.
Don't be angry.
Childe Qian
is the best in Tianjin.
And after tonight,
he'll be Secretary General Xiao's son-in-law.
It's normal to go out and relax before getting engaged.
How about this. I'll get a couple of people
to go door to door
to see which venues Childe Qian usually likes to go to.
I'm sure I'll find out.
When we get him,
we'll give him back to you.
Captain Fu,
people of Qian family are sensitive about their reputation
and can refrain from reporting the case for a few days.
But I, Xiao Lanlan, don't care.
Since the person has been lost,
there is no fear of shame.
I just want you to be clear about this.
Take it
seriously.
Miss Xiao,
your engagement party tonight...
As before.
Vice Mayor Xu.
A set of diamond jewelry.
Colonel Luo of the city defense regiment.
A pair of ivory screens.
Feng shopkeeper of Suxin Fang.
Ten gold bars.
President Sun of the Charity Hall.
An imported car.
It looks like their money grows on trees.
Hurry up.
Captain.
What's taking you so long?
Have you gone shopping in Peiping?
I really put my heart into it.
It's cheap and fresh.
And distinctive.
Your satisfaction is guaranteed.
If you take it out,
no matter who is talking about it,
you'll absolutely gain face.
All right, let me take a look at it.
Captain, here you go.
How's that?
You said fresh, didn't you?
They were just out of the water.
How fresh!
One is fatter than the other.
You want me to be the joke of the whole city?
No, Captain.
Let me explain to you, Cap.
I'll kick you to death.
Captain Fu.
Mr. Xiao.
Here comes Captain Fu.
Inside, please.
Don't bother.
We're still on business over there.
Miss Xiao also asked us
to go and find Childe Qian.
What's this?
It's...
Crabs for gifts.
They're really fat.
Good stuff.
Our Miss Lanlan likes to eat crab cream.
These were
chosen one by one by our captain.
In Peiping.
Sorry to make you laugh.
It's too shabby to give.
It's very kind of you.
We're family.
Don't tell anyone about finding Childe Qian.
Otherwise, if the news gets out,
there will be trouble in the market.
Today is Miss Lanlan's red-letter day.
Don't upset the Secretary General's mood.
For sure.
Please rest assured.
No matter how busy you are,
we should be given some face.
Inside, please.
Obedience is better than politeness.
Please.
Where are you going?
Aren't we supposed to go in?
Mr. Xiao just gave orders.
Take care.
Keep watch at the door.
Give me the present.
Well, Captain.
That's it.
Captain, do we still need to find Qian?
Please.
After you.
Captain Fu of Tianjin police station.
A basket of crabs.
Inside, please.
Come on, come on, come on.
You're...
You don't know me?
Are you on the guest list?
Let me check.
We come here just for dinner and you have to verify our identities?
I'm sorry, it's the rule.
Don't fool me with your son of a bitch.
Mum.
You can go all over the city to inquire about it,
which restaurant does not know me, the fairy grandmother.
Don't make me angry.
If I get angry,
I'll put a diarrhea spell on you,
putting you out of work.
What are you doing?
We don't have an invitation in hand,
at least we should be dressed properly.
You see what they're wearing.
How can we blend in?
Let's go. I'll get you some wine.
You think I'm freeloading?
I'm trying to help them.
Tell you what.
Heaven, man, god and ghost have their own way.
I got your master a hexagram,
and the message was not very good.
I have come to interpret the hexagram today.
You don't even have that kind of piety.
I'm not cursing you,
your bridegroom is going to have a big trouble.
Do you know that?
Young master Ding, inside, please.
They're with me.
Did you hear that?
Hear that?
Get out of the way.
See you later.
Young master Ding of canal transport chamber of commerce.
500 silver dollars.
He's just a big spender.
Brother!
Calm down.
You promised me the fifty dollars.
You're not going to beat the bill, are you?
I wonder if Agent Ding is free tomorrow morning,
to come with me to the Xue mansion.
Pay the bill tonight,
and the case will be solved tomorrow.
It's time.
Move the coffin to the graveyard.
All three of you, please stay.
You can't go in there.
Guys,
my daughter is going to be buried today.
What do you want?
Don't rush to the burial.
Milord Xue,
there's something you haven't come clean about.
Young master Ding.
Although your canal transport chamber of commerce is rich,
you‘re rampant like this without any scruple,
isn't it a bit too much?
Let me ask you: Xue Yuanyuan died in her boudoir,
how would she feel?
Show your respect for the deceased.
Don't talk nonsense here.
In the previous dynasty there was a form of torture.
The waterlogged rice paper
is affixed layer by layer to the prisoner's face,
separately sealed his eyes, nose and mouth,
so that the prisoner can not see or speak,
but can only continue to struggle until death.
Besides,
What a cruel person one would be
to not let go of a woman who had just become a mother.
I... I don't know what you're up to.
But you should know
the consequences of framing the Xue family.
Milord Xue should have known
what would happen if one did that.
Are you crazy?!
Even a vicious tiger will not eat its cubs.
You tell me,
who's crazy?
You’re talking nonsense.
Somebody, get them out of here.
The weapon used to kill Xue Yuanyuan is in the mansion.
Mr. Xue.
You haven't had time to deal with it, have you?
Although she had repainted her nails,
it was clear that, just before she died,
Xue had hurt her nails by scratching at something hard.
Judging by the extent of the damage,
it's not metal or rock,
most likely wood.
To be precise,
it's varnished mahogany furniture.
Uncle Gui.
In the room where I change my shroud,
you can check there.
When a man is drowned in a river,
his nose and ears
will be more or less filled with mud.
But Miss Xue's body was very clean.
Large families are fastidious.
That's all right.
But in Miss Xue's hair,
I smelt the good Longjing picked before Grain Rain.
And the jade earrings she wore before her death
still had bits of rice paper soaked in tea.
In the river,
how can there be tea and paper?
If you ask me,
Miss Xue must have died
in her boudoir.
The courtyard of the Xue House was built with high walls,
and has men on duty at night.
If the murderer wants to sneak into the house to commit murder,
it's much harder.
But if the killer was from the house,
that would be a different matter.
Milord Xue,
what do you think?
If you still don't agree with what I'm saying,
come down to the police station with Agent Ding.
I promise we'll get to the bottom of it.
No matter how,
you shouldn't kill your own daughter.
In distinguished families,
the slightest mistake
may destroy a family.
The daughter of the Xue family
conceived an evil child outside,
which brought disgrace to my family and ruined my reputation.
She should have died outside.
Sit.
You're like this,
and you're running out.
Dad.
I brought you up.
But you're leaving.
You don't want this home anymore?
Listen to me, Dad.
How can you be so shameless?
Dad.
I went to  all this trouble
to keep you hidden,
because I was afraid it would come out.
I wanna cover it up. Cover it up!
But if you run out with the baby,
and someone else sees you,
then my family will be disgraced!
Dad, I'm begging you.
I have to find him.
I beg you to let me go.
Please forget me as your daughter.
Shut up.
You're still looking for the beast, aren't you?
Give me the baby! Give me the baby!
Give me! Dad!
Dad! What do you want?
Dad!
See if you can still run.
It's not gonna work, Dad.
It's not gonna work.
I will go for sure.
See if you can still run!
Uncle Gui! Uncle Gui!
Silence!
Even if you don't let me go,
he will come to pick me up.
Are you still going?
It's not gonna work.
See if you can still run away!
Where's the baby?
He was taken away.
You, you just keep making it up.
Things have come to this.
What's the point of making up?
Let him.
Go, go find him, go, go.
You must get him back!
Yuanyuan was sitting there,
very quiet.
Don't move!
Who?
Hand over the baby.
You... Who are you?
As long as you hand over the baby,
no one will know what you have done.
What do you want?
Rest assured.
It has nothing to do with the Xue family.
How can I believe you?
You don't have a choice.
Move.
Do you remember what the man looked like?
His face was covered and I couldn't see it.
Well, you have to remember something about that person, right?
He seems to be a little lame.
Gu Ying.
Catch them!
Got it.
You keep an eye on Xue Qingyang.
What are you gonna do after you have killed a person and hidden the body?
Young master Ding.
Those people are not from the Xue family.
Who are they if they are not from the Xue mansion?
My master was afraid of publicity,
so I hired some porters from the docks.
Not to mention my master,
even I don't know them.
It was the brute who raped, raped Yuanyuan!
Besides his lame,
what other features does he have?
It was so dark. I can't see clearly.
You must have heard his voice.
Is he an acquaintance of yours? Is he a local?
I don't know the accent.
He is not an acquaintance.
I heard him coughing a lot.
Who are you?
Such a narrow road for moving the coffin.
Thank you for your hard work.
Need a hand?
Excuse me.
Why did he open the coffin?
Run.
You're good at running, aren't you?
You can't run as soon as the sun goes down?
In those days, my second elder brother Guo
was chased by me for a day and a night.
Who sent you here?
Why are you looting the body?
I don't know.
So stubborn, huh?
I...
As robbers, we can only see the money, not the faces of the buyers.
Why don't you ask me about something else?
So where are you going to take the body?
We were only asked to transport it to Yaowa Wharf.
Then someone will take care of it.
Stop.
Now let's welcome Captain Fu of the Jinmen police station
to give a speech.
Applause.
Young master Ding has just joined the police station,
and personally cracked a big case,
and brought Xue Qingyang who was cruel enough to kill his own daughter to justice.
It's really delicaces!
Well, it's delicacy then.
Yeah. Delicacy.
Captain.
You mean affording general satisfaction.
Delicacy means eating.
Yeah, I'm talking about eating.
For the morale of our department,
we need to celebrate.
You have worked hard together with me for so many days
and have settled such a big case.
Of course, we need to have some good food and drink.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It shows how much I, the captain,
care about my men.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
We can't close the case now.
How about a sheep's head?
Sheep soup with pancakes, warm our heart and stomach.
You've been getting inflamed recently, cap.
The bodies of Xue Yuanyuan and the baby
are now missing.
Then instant-boiled mutton.
Hand cut lamb of Yongyuande, north of the city,
is particularly smooth and tender.
Mutton gets people inflamed easily.
Better not to have instant-boiled mutton.
We must find out who these people are
and what their purpose is.
Then we'll have fish.
Sweet and Sour Mandarin Fish of Shunfu Restaurant.
With shredded tofu and fried pork offal.
I'll heat up a pot of wine for you.
And ask a girl to sing a song.
I'm short-handed now.
I need extra police.
Give me permission.
Drink little but know much.
A little pot will do.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
What did you say you wanted to eat?
Where are they? Did you catch them?
How can you not even catch up with a coffin?
I did catch up.
It was empty.
One of them jumped into the river
with Xue Yuanyuan's body.
Jumped into the river?
What about the baby? Where's his body?
I didn't see him.
What about the undertakers?
They ran away.
All this time, you haven't caught up with anything?
Go for them if you can.
I should have gone after them then.
You should have stayed with Xue Qingyang.
You...
Who are you blaming?
If it weren't for me and Brother Guo,
you would have been dragged to martyrdom!
I have an idea.
Roast duck!
He's so firm.
Love is so great.
You mean
it was her man who looted the body.
If their feeling is not deep,
this won't worth it.
Didn't I just
hound them to death today?
This is called destroying the corpse and the evidence.
Not die for love.
Do you jump with the body when you dump it?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Right here.
He jumped off without looking back.
Didn't they rise to the surface?
No.
But it was dark,
so I'm not sure.
Let's go.
And eat something warm.
We're here to investigate a case.
How?
You already said that
the murderer jumped in with the body,
didn't you?
They're all in the water and they haven't surfaced.
Then go into the water and have a check.
That makes sense. Go ahead.
You're from the corpse-retrieval team.
Yeah.
Where's the bodies?
How do you know if you don't go down there?
When you treat people,
you cut them open
before you find out what's wrong with them, right?
I majored in forensic medicine, not Western medicine.
I pulled bodies out of the water,
not wind.
Didn't I give you 50 silver dollars?
That's money for investigating the case, not for fishing bodies out.
How much do you want?
What's the matter?
It's like gambling on stones.
One cut,
and if there's nothing, you'll have to blame nothing but your bad luck.
If there's anything, it's a big case.
Then you'll make contributions, Detective Ding.
Okay. Let's do 50 dollars.
50 dollars is the price for one corpse.
If I had two down here,
I'll charge 100 silver dollars.
Okay.
Xiaoying will bear witness to me.
If there is nothing in the river,
pay me 50 dollars all the same.
Hurry up.
I still don't believe it.
How could he hold his breath in the water for so long?
That's because you can't.
Brother.
You won the bet.