After Pop Dance Club's performance,
let's welcome the Rock Club
to bring us the most lit
recruiting show ever!
♪ When I set sail ♪
♪ Riding the waves ♪
♪ I will not be afraid to lose my way ♪
♪ Looking into the faraway light ♪
♪ Would you join me on my voyage ♪
♪ To where the stars have fallen ♪
♪ When I step on ♪
♪ This stage ♪
♪ The dazzling lights illuminate me ♪
♪ I will shine bright for you ♪
♪ For your eyes to see ♪
♪ Waiting for you to ♪
♪ Sing with me ♪
Thank you all! We are...
Zhonghe Rock Club!
Newbies, line up with your admission forms.
♪ I want to stand on the stage with you ♪
♪ Just like that day when you sang ♪
♪ A little closer, I may be more like you ♪
♪ Maybe I can shine a little brighter ♪
♪ From that day on ♪
♪ I've been looking for you everywhere ♪
♪ Pick up the guitar
play the first chord ♪
♪ And so I made up my mind ♪
♪ To practice with you ♪
- How do you play Bm?
- ♪ Take me forward together ♪
You don't even know this?
- I've been practicing.
- ♪ You are the one I've always longed for ♪
- I've really been practicing!
♪ I want to stand on the stage with you ♪
♪ I want to sing loudly with you ♪
♪ I think I won't give up ♪
♪ Until I sing your melody ♪
♪ Whenever I'm by your side ♪
♪ And you smile tenderly at me ♪
♪ Makes me believe that ♪
♪ I can be the one on stage too ♪
♪ I want to stand on the stage with you ♪
♪ My feelings for you are not just longing ♪
♪ I wish to express my heart ♪
♪ And all my feelings to you ♪
♪ I want to stand by you ♪
♪ And sail with you to the faraway light ♪
♪ From now on ♪
♪ Only sing the melody that you sing ♪
♪ Singing with you ♪
"First Crush"
We used to give the best show.
You satisfied with how you did?
Performing is to accept that some
will like it, and some won't.
No one has heard your song,
so they won't resonate.
This is very relevant to the club ranking.
Self-composed songs have advantages.
We can improve our performance.
Would it be better
if you play difficult solos,
and blow it up on stage?
But the audience have
no interaction, no reaction.
Who's gonna rock with you
with your own song?
Lin Yu-jia, why did you quit the club?
The president won't let me perform my song.
So I don't want to be there anymore.
But... you can't do that.
You almost complete your song.
There must be another way.
This isn't the only club, right?
Or I can perform your song.
Okay, I'll just...
I'll practice more and get it right.
Just pretend it's my song first.
You know, even if I do finish writing it,
I probably won't go to see your show.
Why?
Are you serious or just trolling?
I'm serious.
I don't want to see the president.
Plus...
I can't bear to see you play so badly.
No way! I've been practicing hard, okay?
Really?
- Come on, then.
- Why not?
Ready?
A minor.
Start it over for me.
- You wrote all this?
- Yes.
Impressive.
I... I think you have
some chords written...
a bit strange.
Your guitar arrangement
and the vocal part...
They are incompatible.
It's okay. Let's try it out.
Okay.
Hey!
Don't lose my pick again!
I won't.
I'll take good care of it.
Okay, stop writing.
- What's up?
- Let's go!
Are you dumb? What if we get caught?
Don't worry.
I've sneaked in many times before.
So pretty.
Right?
What are you doing?
I nearly got choked!
Take it easy.
Why did you push me?
When I was feeling down,
I would always come here alone.
Come here for what?
I don't know.
I just felt...
It's so relaxing.
To float on the water like this.
It's like...
Like floating in the vast universe.
♪ As a child, going to the planetarium ♪
♪ I remember
in the Universal Dome Theater ♪
♪ Seeing the stars
and the Milky Way in the sky ♪
♪ I realized the universe
is not just black and white ♪
♪ Like the strokes of a paintbrush.
- Gold, blue ♪
♪ There were many twinkling stars on it ♪
♪ Truly beautiful ♪
♪ From that moment on ♪
♪ I wanted to be an astronaut ♪
♪ I wanted to be closer to the stars ♪
♪ As I grew up,
I realized it was hard to be an astronaut ♪
♪ I hated studying ♪
♪ So I didn't dare to say again ♪
♪ That I wanted to be an astronaut ♪
♪ Instead, I joined the swim team
in junior high ♪
♪ Floating on the water
was like losing gravity ♪
♪ I felt a little closer
to the universe again ♪
What do you want to do in future?
♪ As a child, everyone praised me
for my beautiful voice ♪
♪ But I wasn't sure myself ♪
♪ I just thought that if people liked it ♪
♪ I would keep singing ♪
♪ And I like singing very much ♪
♪ In my mind ♪
♪ It seems that only when I'm singing ♪
♪ I'm more comfortable with my life ♪
I'm having a better time.
I still remember that one time,
a senior came to give a music lesson.
He played a song that he wrote himself.
I don't know why,
he only played four chords,
but I felt so greatly moved.
From that time on, I knew.
Music can have this kind of power.
♪ So I started to write songs ♪
♪ Felt like I can be a singer-songwriter ♪
♪ This is something I can do ♪
♪ And something I like to do ♪
♪ That's why I keep writing songs ♪
♪ I like to listen to you sing too ♪
♪ It is not as great as a dream ♪
♪ This is just what I want to do ♪
♪ I love to hear you sing ♪
♪ So I'll keep on singing ♪
♪ It is not as great as a dream ♪
♪ It's just something I want to do ♪
♪ A little thing ♪
I think your song are written badly.
No audience will like it.
It's not that bad.
But perhaps a different expression?
Like adding some funk?
For a tacky piece,
it's still tacky
however you change the arrangement.
I think it's not bad.
He just have a bad taste.
So you know about good taste in music?
Write it yourself if you're so good!
Anything I write will sound
better than yours.
I'm right.
G is to be followed by Bm7.
- But the whole thing is off key!
- Enough!
Jian-kai.
Can we save your song for next time?
Even you are like this!
Hey!
Quit secretly recording me!
(How's the rehearsal?)
(Sorry Yu-jia,)
(we've decided not to play
self-composed song...)
(Hahahahahaha...)
(It went well.)
(National Student Songwriting Contest)
It's almost time. You may want to go in?
Sure.
Bye!
Lin Yu-jia.
Welcome to the freshmen show.
Still welcome after I quit?
Of course.
Don't miss my grand finale.
I'm gonna lit the stage.
Are you in tune?
Not yet.
Let's talk outside.
Have you seen the program list?
Yes.
Is that a misprint?
No, it's not.
Then why my song is not on the list?
The band members decided
not to play the self-composed song.
They decided to just do cover songs.
So when you told me before,
that you've been practicing well,
that you're almost ready.
That's all a lie?
No, that's not true.
You think I'm bad at writing songs?
No, I think those songs are great.
- I love the songs.
- Do you?
- I really do!
- You don't!
Yu-jia...
You're just like them,
thinking that my songs are shitty!
No, I don't.
Let me ask you...
Why did you ask me to write a song?
You made me think that
someone would really like my songs!
Because I like you!
Because I didn't want you to leave.
I like the way you sing and play guitar.
The way you write.
I just really like you!
Lin Yu-jia!
♪ Dream and belief ♪
♪ What am I left with ♪
♪ If I cry alone now ♪
♪ No one else will find out ♪
- (Sorry Yu-jia, I shouldn't lie to you.)
- ♪ Maybe I should admit my defeat ♪
- (Can we still be friends?)
- ♪ If I didn't say it out loud ♪
- ♪ It wouldn't be like this now ♪
♪ I just wanted to be with you ♪
♪ Watch you glowing on the stage ♪
♪ With feelings that I shouldn't have ♪
♪ Now I can't even be honest to myself ♪
♪ I just wanted to be there for you ♪
♪ But I screwed it all up ♪
♪ Maybe I shouldn't have said it ♪
♪ Perhaps we can still go back
to the old days ♪
♪ Did I really want to help you ♪
♪ Or just to hold on to you selfishly ♪
♪ I want to be by your side ♪
♪ To hear your voice ♪
Hey, congratulations!
Here comes our super star!
Lin Yu-jia, this is you, right?
- Where did you find this?
- Huh?
Just look at the view counts!
Sing for us!
View counts?
- Lin Yu-jia!
- Champion!
When did you sign up? Sneaky boy!
I don't know.
I don't even remember when I signed up.
You have amnesia,
or someone else signed you up?
Where's Jian-kai?
Why isn't he here?
He quit the club a while ago.
Don't you know?
Oh...
I'm back in the Rock Club.
I know.
Congrats, you won the contest.
You signed me up, right?
Yes.
Come to the next show? I'll perform.
Jian-kai.
Where are you going?
♪ Dream and belief ♪
♪ What am I left with ♪
♪ If I cry alone now ♪
♪ No one else will find out ♪
♪ Maybe I should admit my defeat ♪
♪ When I thought I still had music ♪
♪ Didn't expect there was nothing left ♪
♪ I left my club ♪
♪ I left my best friend ♪
♪ But I ended up with nothing ♪
♪ I got used to your company ♪
♪ And the moments we spent together ♪
♪ Singing and talking over meals ♪
♪ Get used to the way you look at me ♪
♪ Did I really not realize your feelings ♪
♪ Or am I just afraid to admit my feelings ♪
♪ Missing your smile ♪
♪ The dream you sang in the water ♪
♪ But I'm no longer worthy ♪
♪ To desire your company ♪
♪ You are not with me ♪
♪ Who else can hear my voice ♪
♪ I think I'm in love with you ♪
♪ But you're not with me ♪
♪ Clearly aware of your feelings ♪
♪ But I'm too cowardly to respond ♪
♪ I wish to express all my heart to you ♪
♪ Our songs and little talks ♪
♪ Are the joy I can no longer have ♪
♪ I miss your smile ♪
♪ The day you floated on the water ♪
♪ Maybe that was the day ♪
♪ I fell in love with you ♪
♪ I've fallen in love with you ♪
Let's welcome the frontman, Lin Yu-jia!
This song,
is written by me and my most important one.
♪ How are you doing lately ♪
♪ In the life without you ♪
♪ The words I want to say ♪
♪ Were left by me in the hidden corner ♪
♪ On the crumbled draft paper ♪
♪ I couldn't find the right words
to answer ♪
♪ The truest voice from your heart ♪
♪ Your presence drives away
the uncertainty in my heart ♪
♪ The notes you bring floating
on the pool water ♪
♪ We break the waves ♪
♪ Like turning the next page ♪
♪ I picked up the music sheet
and that guitar ♪
♪ Started to sing out loud ♪
♪ This one song ♪
♪ Was with me in the corridors at dusk ♪
♪ Through the starry night sky ♪
♪ There may be many memories ♪
♪ That I can no longer recall ♪
♪ But only you ♪
♪ And our every little talk ♪
♪ All the time I will never forget ♪
♪ Waiting for you to come ♪
♪ To take my hand ♪
Make some noise!
♪ You made me fall in love
with music again ♪
♪ In a world without you ♪
♪ How can I move on ♪
♪ All my heart and feelings ♪
♪ Are now presented to you ♪
♪ So I picked up the pen ♪
♪ Just want you to hear ♪
♪ This one song ♪
♪ Day or night ♪
♪ As long as you're in the seat ♪
♪ I want to share with you ♪
♪ The way I see the world ♪
♪ Everything about you ♪
♪ And the smile on your face ♪
♪ Are the memories I can never forget ♪
♪ This time it's my turn ♪
♪ To take your hand ♪