[tense music playing]
ABUSE RAMPANT AT
CHIBA NURSING HOME
[Yamashiro] What the hell is this?
And they have videos.
[altered voice] Hello. Mr. Udagawa.
- Delicious, huh? Open your mouth.
- [Udagawa] No!
MR. A: (SOUNDS LIKE HE'S IN PAIN)
- Don't you dare waste it. Eat up.
- [Yamashiro] This isn't good.
The source is either
the family of that guy
or a member of the hospital staff.
Yamashiro, do what you have to
to make sure we don't get fined for this.
[music fades]
[Yamashiro sighs]
Mr. Sugawara,
you should know better than
to talk to me like that.
[tense music playing]
I'm sorry.
I got carried away.
Now that the media's got a hold of this,
the government's not gonna have a choice.
They're gonna have to take action on this.
At the very least,
they'll suspend our license.
[Sugawara] Sir…
You know we forced that guy Iemori
to write out his last will
and testament over and over?
What would happen
if a video of that got out?
Of you forcing him to write his will?
What'd you film that for?
It's a hypothetical question.
Goddamn kids with their phones.
They can't jerk off without filming it!
No, sir, please calm down.
Hypothetically.
If a video like that ever got out,
it wouldn't be just a… fine or something!
We'd be finished!
[sighs]
I want… you to find out who was filming.
I think…
I have a pretty damn good idea
who's pulling the strings.
Dammit, Kujo.
- Little shit!
- [music ends]
Ow! [groans]
[altered voice] What's the matter
with you, anyway?
Just swallow it.
This video was on the USB you got
from Mr. Mibu the other day, huh?
Uh-huh.
But how'd you know
he'd be able to get his hands on it?
I remembered someone I'd met before.
What do you mean?
You know, you should eat, Mr. Karasuma.
Junk food in the morning?
What, no more fasting?
Yeah.
Because today's gonna be busy.
Is it? Why's that?
Mr. Karasuma, I wanted to ask.
Could you contact the reporter
who wrote the news article again?
[theme music playing]
- [breathing heavily]
- [Sugawara] Kuga.
Are you the one who leaked the video?
I think very highly of you, you know?
So I'd rather you just fess up.
[coughs]
I told you.
I don't know anything.
[panting]
But you
didn't believe me.
So, Mr. Sugawara, I'm at your mercy.
Do what you want.
[ominous music playing]
[Sugawara] I see.
The reason the government created
the medical system and social supports
wasn't to save lives
or to reduce people's suffering.
It was to keep people healthy
so they could work harder,
increasing the strength of Japan.
[dramatic sting]
It isn't like that today, though.
Our numbers are out of control,
and the useless are discarded.
[dramatic sting]
[Kuga screaming]
[grunts]
[music fades]
Hello, Mr. Kuga.
We're from the Honjo Police Department.
Your doctor filed a report,
so we'd like to ask you some questions.
[Kuga groans]
Sorry, I don't…
I was drunk and I passed out so…
Then I woke up here like this.
- So you don't know how you got hurt?
- No, it's just a blank, so yeah.
[inhales sharply]
[cop] Please contact us
if you remember anything.
Yes, sir.
All right.
Doctor, can you tell us more
about his injuries?
[doctor] Absolutely. Follow me, please.
[Kuga] I figure Sugawara bugged
the hospital room,
so I'm texting you instead.
They still think it was me,
but… I'm out of the woods for now.
[scoffs] The article
about Iemori is crazy.
Fuckin' Sugawara was so pissed.
[phone buzzes]
GOOD JOB, KUGA.
HOW ARE YOU? HURT TOO BAD?
[chuckles]
[Kuga] Hurts like hell.
[dramatic sting]
Mibu.
[chuckles]
[upbeat music playing]
[Yamashiro] Hi. Sugawara?
[Sugawara] Yeah?
Did you figure out
who leaked those videos?
No, not yet.
I just put my prime suspect
in the hospital and then bugged his room.
What? You put him in the hospital?
What's the matter with you?
Are you insane?
These videos were on the news
for everyone to see.
The media's gonna be all over you.
Tell me about it.
There's already a swarm of them
outside the care home. It's gotten crazy.
I can't get close to my house
or my girlfriend's either.
[sighs] What are we gonna do?
[Yamashiro] The police have no choice.
They have to investigate
'cause of those videos.
If they find out
that the place is being run by a thug,
it'll make things even worse.
What do we do about
the staff member in the videos?
[Yamashiro] If it was just him,
he would just get charged with assault,
and that'd be it.
However,
if they suspect the whole facility
of abusing patients, then
even you would be in
a precarious position.
And if there's a video
of you forcing someone to write a will,
then you're finished.
You and I would both get arrested
for fraud and breach of trust
among other things.
[music fades]
[woman] Attorney Yamashiro.
May I have a moment?
I'm Ichida from the Toei Shimbun.
You're… retained by the Kikogi Association
that runs the residence, am I right?
I have some questions for you
regarding a coerced will.
Uh, sir!
Could you just give us a few words?
Goddamn reporters!
Who do you think you are?
[growls]
If you spread lies about me, I'll sue you.
Are you prepared for that?
Stop following me!
It was a great article.
I'm glad it went viral.
[chuckles]
[Ichida] Thanks for the scoop.
As soon as it hit,
all the major outlets picked it up.
And if I post my next one
all about a big-time lawyer
aiding and abetting a gang,
it'll go even more viral.
[indistinct chatter]
[Karasuma] Ms. Ichida from Toei Shimbun
is very happy, Mr. Kujo.
Is that so?
You know, Mr. Karasuma,
you sure are well-connected.
Huh?
Not as well as you are, sir.
Yeah, no.
All of my contacts are
scary-looking characters
covered in tattoos and piercings.
[both slurping]
Conversely, you, Mr. Karasuma,
know very approachable people,
most of whom, I've noticed, are women.
Hmm. Yeah, I guess that's true.
We're both lawyers.
Why are we so different?
[Karasuma] Mmm…
- Our looks.
- Huh?
[laughs] That's what you're thinking.
[laughs]
You… you said it, not me.
It's just a coincidence.
It's not a coincidence.
Yakushimae just ignores me
whenever I ask her out.
But she goes to that Chinese restaurant
with you all the time.
The only time you asked her out
was for Japan's number one takoyaki.
That doesn't count as asking someone out.
Sure it does.
Oh my God, how did you ever get married
with an attitude like that?
That explains the divorce.
[chuckles] It's written
all over your face.
[laughs] Again, you said it, not me.
- [door slams open]
- [Yamashiro] Hey, Kujo!
[Kujo] I've been expecting you,
Mr. Yamashiro.
Expecting me, huh?
[Kujo] I figured it was about time
you showed up.
Hello. My name's Shinji Karasuma.
Shut it!
You used the media to try
and put me in a corner.
You got me.
I taught you well, Kujo.
You got me good.
I don't know how much evidence
you've got, but
I'll make you a deal.
It's not as if you enjoy
any of this, right?
Look, I'll pay back
all of Mr. Iemori's estate.
Okay? You win, Attorney Kujo.
[Kujo] All right. I'll end it.
But in exchange,
you will…
surrender your license today.
Huh?!
[upbeat music playing]
You have to quit practicing law for good.
You son of a…
I did you a favor coming here,
and you treat me like this?
You're telling me to quit?
Me? I was your second father. [laughs]
Who do you think you are?
I'll crush you, kid.
Have you forgotten who you're talking to?
Maybe, yeah.
I think I did. Why don't you remind me?
[music ends]
[Yamashiro] Come and get me!
I'm not finished yet.
[liquid pouring]
[Yamashiro] It's stupid to think
that lawyers have any power.
[hiccups]
It's only ever the rich
who have any power. Am I wrong?
It does make you wonder.
Lawyers with any brains
only take on clients with deep pockets.
The poor are stuck
with court-appointed lawyers.
They don't have any choice.
And if they get one
that doesn't give a shit,
they end up losing
when they should've won.
[laughs]
We're supposed to be equal under the law.
Obviously money turns that
into a friggin' fantasy.
Am I right, Kujo?
[groans]
I charge everyone 330,000,
regardless of whether
the client is rich or poor.
- I don't care about social status.
- 300,000 yen?!
And I don't take a percentage
of bail either. That's my policy.
But I'm still too expensive
for a lot of people.
[Yamashiro] What the hell?
You're not running a charity.
It makes sense to charge more for the rich
in, let's say, complicated cases.
But I've never heard of a lawyer
being such a pushover.
It's something to think about.
It reminds me…
“He who fights with monsters should
be careful lest he thereby
become a monster.”
“And if you gaze long into an abyss,
the abyss will also…
gaze into you.”
[chuckles]
[groans]
Nietzsche's Beyond Good and Evil?
That's a pretty overused quote,
don't you think?
[somber music playing]
I'm grateful to you, sir,
for everything you did for me
and everything you taught me.
[music fades]
[Sugawara] One of your guys filed
a complaint for assault.
Well, that's because a video
of you beating us up went viral.
The cops told us to file a report,
so we did.
[Sugawara] Uh-huh.
Withdraw it. Now.
Sure.
Yeah, I'll get right on that.
You're the one behind this whole thing,
aren't you, Mibu?
Sorry,
I don't know what you… mean.
Mark my words.
One day, I'll make you pay for this.
[Kuga sighs, chuckles]
Did Sugawara find out about me?
No, he didn't.
[both laugh]
Good.
Ah, I wanna tell you,
you're amazing, Kuga.
You infiltrated their operation
and didn't get caught.
[Kuga] No, you're the one
who knew exactly what to do.
You knew if I snuck into the facility,
I'd find Sugawara's weakness.
[Mibu] Weakness?
That's not what I was after.
I don't give a shit about Sugawara.
I just used him to increase my reach,
that's all.
[lighter clicking]
[Kuga] Okay.
Thanks.
[mellow music playing]
I was wondering…
How'd you manage to get those videos?
Uh, well…
[phone smashes]
[Kuga] We were lucky
the damage didn't reach the data.
[Mibu] Yeah, lucky.
Thanks to that, I got rid of Sugawara
and paid my debt to Mr. Kujo.
[blows smoke]
[Kuga] I'm surprised
Mr. Kujo recognized me.
I think we only met once at your garage.
Yeah, he's like that.
Anyway, I owe you one, Kuga.
Go sit in a hot spring for a while.
Thank you.
But seriously, Mibu, anything you need,
just give the word, and I'm there.
Is that right?
Yes sir.
Well,
how 'bout we find some time to go bowling?
What do you think?
- [laughs]
- [chuckles]
Come on, I just got my nose caved in.
Give me a chance to recover.
[music fades]
LAND FOR SALE,
FEEL FREE TO CONTACT US
[car door closes]
[Ms. Iemori] Now that it's a vacant lot,
I feel better.
The land our father left behind.
Sorry you had to deal with all of this
when you're so busy.
[Ms. Iemori] That's okay.
Anyway,
that lawyer you found is really good.
Well, we paid good money for him.
So, he better be good.
Still, it was a bargain.
His rate was super cheap.
I was really shocked.
He got the whole 400 million back.
The standard cut is 10%, so 40 million.
But he didn't even ask for half.
Only ten, right?
That's amazing. Totally unheard of.
[car horn beeps]
[inaudible]
What is it?
[Keisuke] Oh no. I mean…
Sorry, this is awkward.
The 25 million you received
as an inter vivos gift from Dad…
Can you include that in the distribution?
[Ms. Iemori] Saeko wanted you
to ask me this, didn't she?
Sure, whatever.
I'm not obsessed enough with money
to fight over it.
I'm sorry.
I don't care.
Now that the house is gone,
I don't expect to have to
talk to you two anymore.
You know, that reminds me of something.
Dad said something to me at Mom's funeral.
He told me that you hated him
since you were little.
What do you mean?
[Keisuke] You don't remember?
You used to spend a lot of time
doing homework in the kitchen.
[Ms. Iemori] I could concentrate
better there.
[Keisuke] That's when Mom
and Dad were at their worst.
[Mr. Iemori] You're still up?
[Keisuke] Dad wasn't home much.
He'd stop at the bar every night.
When he'd get home… drunk,
you would get up and leave
as soon as he came in.
[poignant music playing]
[Keisuke] He said you've hated him
all this time.
Yeah, I was just reminded of that
for some reason.
No offense.
None taken.
How much longer will this take?
I'm coming, honey.
Well, I'll leave the distribution to you.
[car door opens, closes]
That is not the reason
that I was in the kitchen.
[music fades]
[door opens]
[Yakushimae] Hi, you two.
[humming happily]
[Karasuma] Yakushimae?
[Kujo] Is it Halloween?
No, it's not a costume!
[sighs]
Bet you were always a big hit
with the girls.
Never.
So, how can I help you?
Karasuma told me I should come over.
Because you… wanted to go out with me. So?
- Go out?
- Yeah.
[Karasuma] That's what you said.
You said that every time you ask her out,
she just ignores you.
Really? Is that what I said?
I don't mind going out with you.
But… I'd like to go somewhere classy,
like maybe counter-only sushi
or teppanyaki
where they cook in front of you.
Sorry. We have a lot of work left
from the Iemori case.
Hmm?
But you already finished that case.
A neighbor of hers said
the house was torn down,
and she split the inheritance
with her brother.
All of it?
Uh-huh.
The neighbor told her,
“You did most of the caregiving."
"You should've taken all of it.”
And she said,
"We're family."
It seems like
she really put her family first
until the very end, you know.
So, have you chosen a restaurant?
I don't wanna go anywhere
with fewer than a four-star rating.
Maybe you can go
with Mr. Karasuma instead?
[Yakushimae] What?
- Where are you going?
- [Kujo] Somewhere.
[Yakushimae] Oh, oh!
Hey! Not so fast, you crooked lawyer!
- Treat me to dinner!
- [door closes]
[Kujo] Ms. Iemori.
Hello, Mr. Kujo.
I'm sorry for calling out of the blue.
That's okay. So, what's this about?
I wanted to give you the receipt.
Oh, you could've just sent it
to me in the mail.
Yes, that's true, but…
Here you go.
All right.
Thank you very much.
[Kujo] Ms. Iemori.
Can I ask a personal question?
I was wondering if you regret
how it turned out?
[laughs]
Regret what?
That you weren't able…
to take care of your father
right until the end.
[mournful music playing]
I don't think you ever really cared
about getting the money back.
But it was the only way you had
to try to make peace with yourself.
According to your neighbors…
you cared for your father
with such devotion…
they were worried
you might just collapse one day.
There's something my mentor
used to tell me.
No matter how difficult things can get,
no parent wants to burden their children.
You can be sure of that.
Even if your father
never said it out loud,
I'm sure he was so very grateful to you.
You did your best, Ms. Iemori.
[sobbing]
My dad…
He put up with my selfishness
and all kinds of unfair demands
whenever I was sad or lonely.
He never said anything bad
about my mother even after she left us.
Now I see…
he was a good dad.
[sniffs]
And now…
I just found out
he thought that I hated him.
But no…
I waited
for him every night
'cause I was so worried…
- [Mr. Iemori] Hanae, you're still up?
- …that he wouldn't… come home.
That's why I waited for him.
[sobs]
I didn't know he thought I hated him.
I must not have given him enough.
And now he… Now my dad's dead.
[sobbing]
[music fades]
[Karasuma] Is this the right castella?
The one you and Dad liked?
It's okay, you know, Shinji.
You've got a lot going on.
You don't have to come visit so often.
[Karasuma] But I'm worried.
Don't worry.
I'm not likely to fall
and break a hip just yet.
[Karasuma] That's a good sign.
A good sign?
That you're well enough to joke like that.
Here.
So? Is it good?
It sure is.
I know, right?
[curtains sliding]
[window unlatching]
Hey, please don't open it.
You should let some air in.
If you open the window,
people outside will hear us.
No, they won't.
[Mrs. Karasuma] Just close it. Please.
Okay. Right away, ma'am. There.
Done.
[sighs]
But you know, Mom,
Dad wasn't the only victim here.
You and I are too.
So, we don't have to live
like we did something wrong.
It's not too late, you know,
for us to start over.
Okay?
I don't know if I can.
Sure you can.
You can do anything.
[sighs softly]
Mm-hmm.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Lie down.
Okay.
You're so good.
- Mr. Kujo. Mr. Mibu's here to see you.
- Oh.
[upbeat music playing]
Hello, sir. I finally found someone
to take the dog off your hands.
[Karasuma] Good. Now the office
won't get torn apart anymore.
Hey, uh, Mibu?
[Mibu] Yeah?
Would it be okay if I became
Black Thunder's new owner?
You telling me you wanna keep her?
Well, she's already
kind of like family to me.
[Mibu] Sir…
You know, having a dog…
means being responsible for a life.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Do you really understand?
You have to walk her every day and pick up
after her. You know, she might bite you?
And you have to brush her
and brush her teeth. It's a lot.
I know how much you still miss
your dog Omochi. I really get it.
[cell phone rings]
[music fades]
Excuse me.
Hello?
Yeah.
Who's Omochi again?
Uh…
His dog, who unfortunately passed away.
So that's why he's so different
when it comes to dogs.
Yeah.
But he's right though.
A dog is a lot of work.
What if you have to go away on business?
In that case…
- I guess you'll have to take care of her.
- [groans]
[chuckles] Yeah.
I mean, why not, huh? We're both single.
We're practically family.
Well, who's to say
I'm gonna stick around here forever?
[Mibu] Mr. Kujo,
I need your help with something.
A guy who's helped me out in the past
just got pinched.
So, he needs a lawyer?
Is he a friend of yours?
A Fushimi-gumi boss, actually.
Kiyoshi Kyogoku.
[tense music playing]
[cell door slams]
Finally.
This doesn't make any sense at all.
I'm the one
who almost got my watch stolen.
So why did I get arrested?
[Karasuma] On our way here,
we asked the arresting officer
to explain the charges.
According to them,
you were approached by a Kenichi Sakuma.
[grunts]
[Karasuma] While it's true
that he ran toward you,
he didn't intend to steal from you…
[Sakuma] What the hell?
…nevertheless,
you inflicted serious injury on him.
While the bodyguards were
the ones who acted,
you are also held liable
as their employer.
As a result, you've been charged
with assault, Mr. Kyogoku.
But it was a robbery.
I was protecting myself.
You're a yakuza leader, Mr. Kyogoku,
so this is likely an excuse
to arrest and question you.
I understand you want to settle this
and secure your release quickly.
The victim won't agree.
The yakuza are being underestimated.
I saw the footage from the security camera
at the parking lot.
I believe your bodyguards will be found
to have acted in self-defense.
You won't be prosecuted for this.
I heard you got some thug out
after only 20 days, so I asked for you.
I need you to get me out of here.
How quickly this goes depends on you.
That's it.
I need your phone.
I better get my guys on.
You can't. That would go against
the purpose of this meeting.
Lawyers have been disciplined
for doing less.
[Kyogoku] Don't give me that bullshit.
Fine. Give Mibu a message, then.
You're just courier pigeons,
aren't you?
[music fades]
If you want a messenger,
you can go get a new lawyer.
All the money in the world
doesn't make a difference
in the face of the law.
[tense upbeat music playing]
[whimpering]
- Sakuma.
- Yes?
Do you know who I am?
Yeah, of course. Mibu.
Then
you must know how this world works?
The… This world?
[whimpering]
Listen.
I'm afraid you stepped in shit
that you shouldn't have stepped in.
Withdraw the report you filed.
[Sakuma stammering] Yes, sir.
[music fades]
You said
you don't judge your clients
based on status
or whether or not they're good people.
Mr. Kyogoku is dangerous.
It won't end with you
just losing your license.
One day,
you could lose your life.
[siren wailing in the distance]
[indistinct chatter]
- Good morning Mr. Kyogoku.
- Morning. I'll stop by again soon.
Thank you, sir. Looking forward to it.
- Good morning!
- Good morning.
- [man] Morning, sir.
- Hello there. It's been a while.
You're popular here.
[exhales] It's my wallet that they like.
So, listen.
I wanted to talk to you about
that lawyer of yours. He's interesting.
[Mibu] Oh yeah?
Yeah. Why didn't you introduce us earlier?
I don't appreciate you hogging
a lawyer that quick on his feet.
I felt like it would be presumptuous of me
since the Fushimi-gumi
already have a lawyer.
Yes, but the problem is
our lawyer lent me his phone
without a second thought.
Mr. Kujo, on the other hand…
[Kujo] Mr. Kyogoku.
You're aware that the police
regularly check the call history
of known yakuza members, right?
If I were to let you use my cell phone,
it'd be a disadvantage not just for me,
but for you too.
Even if the other party
doesn't agree to settle,
I think we can
successfully argue self-defense.
If you and your bodyguards remain silent,
in 20 days, you'll all be cut loose.
[Kyogoku] As it turned out,
that little punk agreed to settle
before the 20 days were up.
[sighs]
You know, Mibu… [smacks lips]
Something's bothering me.
This was the first time I've ever been
the target of a snatch-and-grab
in this city.
And you know what I think?
I think that someone out there
is maybe looking to frame me.
Pretty paranoid, huh?
[chuckles]
What do you say, Mibu?
Well? Was it you?
[dramatic music playing]
You haven't forgotten
how sideways things can get?
[groaning]
[Kyogoku] Mibu…
I'm afraid… you guys screwed
with someone you shouldn't have.
You stole proceeds from one
of the gambling dens we look after.
Are you crazy?
[Mibu groans]
The guy we caught first
ratted you out right away.
Said it was all your idea.
Thugs have no loyalty to their superiors.
[Mibu groans]
Yakuza don't rat out their superiors.
But we all…
look out for number one, right?
The search for love is
a search for ourselves.
[sighs]
You know, this heater is used
to dry the paint on cars.
If you get too close to it,
your blood'll boil, and you'll die.
It's pretty dangerous.
[heater creaks loudly]
[grunts, groans]
Are you okay, Mibu?
Is it hot?
[groans]
Don't worry.
You're too valuable to die like this.
You know what we're gonna do?
If you show your loyalty,
I'll let you live.
What do you say?
[groans]
I'm sorry.
I'll do anything.
Okay. Show me your loyalty.
[groans]
Your dog, what's its name again?
Huh? What is it?
Omochi! Don't touch him! No!
Oh, Omochi!
Omochi, the dog you've had
since you were a little kid.
- No!
- Yeah…
[struggling]
I want you to kill it.
[dramatic sting]
There's no way! I can't do that!
[grunting]
Ah, then you'll
die.
[Mibu screaming]
[music fades]
[dog groans]
- [bang]
- [Omochi whimpering]
[ominous music playing]
Mibu.
Remember, you chose to kill it.
If you'd done it on my orders,
you would've held a grudge against me,
and we can't have that.
This way, the guilt is yours to bear.
[music builds, ends]
[indistinct chatter]
[Kujo] Are you all right?
Yeah, why?
I'm Mr. Kujo. I'm an attorney.
Please get in touch if you ever need to.
[closing theme song playing]
[music fades]