It's been a while since I've been to school.
Hey.
Are you and Iijima Hinata close?
Huh?
Well, look.
You two have been walking to school together a lot lately.
Alright everyone,
let's decide what we're doing for this year's school festival.
Yeah!
It's that time already?
Any ideas?
A cafe!
A haunted house!
A petting zoo!
How are we supposed to pull off a petting zoo?
Oh!
How about a play?
A play?
Hey, that's not bad!
I want to be in it!
Really?
Oh, that's a great idea!
And look!
Kono-kun is so handsome!
Wouldn't he be perfect for the lead role?
Exactly! I second that!
Right?
No... I...
Come on, please!
"Brother,"
"You're so unfair!"
Alright! It's settled.
Kono Mizuki will star in our festival play!
Yeah!
I want to play the lead actress!