This room is all yours.
It used to be my dad's office.
But he doesn't come around anymore.
The furniture is still in great shape.
Right.
And feel free to use the TV, too.
Sure.
Hey.
Can you try talking like a normal person?
What's the point of that?
Living with you is going to be impossible.
I'm telling my mom to kick you out.
Which one is your room?
Don't touch that!
Give it back!
I said give it back!
Who would've thought the school's golden boy was into this?
You wouldn't...
You're not going to tell everyone at school, are you?
If you don't want me to spill the beans...
Stop it!
Call me big brother!
Fine, fine.
I'm just messing with you.
I'll be moving out after graduation anyway.
Let's just keep our distance until then.
Deal?
This guy...
He's a completely different person than he is at school.