There was a time
when my mom, my brother, and I
had to sleep on the street.
We have a demolition order!
I promised that I would
give them a better life,
a house we can call our own.
Marj, congrats!
You stole the clients
I worked hard to get.
Thea, I didn't need to steal
your clients to get ahead.
Well, I'm this man's wife!
You turned me into a mistress!
It will affect the image
of our company.
That's why I decided
to let the two of you go.
Why don't you try applying
to the company
I'm transferring to?
At Torrecampo Realty.
- Am I late?
- You'll be fine.
Everyone's willing to wait
for the golden boy.
You'd better watch your mouth,
Edward.
Don't embarrass our family.
Mr. Valderama is looking for
a new house for his daughter.
There's something else I want.
Excuse me, I need to get
something upstairs.
Pervert!
You no longer work here!
Why did you follow us
here in our own home?
My brother
is in a critical condition.
I'm begging you to help me,
please.
Please leave, Miss Castillo.
You can go ahead
with the surgery.
I will take care of everything.
Once he's fully recovered,
you can go back to work.
Thank you so much.
I will never forget
what you did to help us.
Sir, this guy is throwing a fit
earlier.
I understand, but you shouldn't
abuse your authority.
Have more patience.
I don't want this
to happen again.
Okay, Sir. I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize
to me. Apologize to them.
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
- I'm so sorry.
- Go on.
Are you okay?
Sir Paolo.
Thank you so much, Sir.
You're a good guy.
A good guy.
Thank you, you're kind Sir.
Thank you.
Jobert!
Sis!
Mom, why didn't you tell me
that you're coming here?
You didn't receive
my text message?
My phone died.
Are you okay?
Did the guard hurt you?
It's okay, they're safe now.
I have already
handled everything.
They have nothing
on these muscles.
I was almost impressed.
A hero, but an arrogant one.
Did you say something?
Oh, nothing.
I was just saying,
you're starting to make a habit
of saving my family.
Aside from the money I owe you,
I feel like I'll be forever
indebted to you.
You know, next time,
let the guards know ahead of
time that you're expecting them
so they can get in
without a problem.
Being your knight in shining
armor can get tiring too.
- Thanks again,
- Sir. You're welcome.
I'm going to get going now,
Mrs. Evelyn.
Thanks again, Sir Paolo.
Jobert, I'm going to go, okay?
Big bro will go now.
- Bye, Paolo.
- Okay, bye.
Girl, I'm going to go, okay?
Auntie, sit down, come on.
Thank you.
Timmy, come with me.
We have a lot of papers
to submit, come on.
Wow, that's a big turtle.
Marj,
if I had known that we would run
into Sir Paolo earlier,
I would've made
some rice cakes for him.
I could've given it to him
as a way of saying thanks
for helping us
with Jobert's operation.
Oh, Mom, it's not like
he's going to eat rice cakes.
He's a rich kid.
You never know.
And wait a minute.
I noticed something
about your boss.
Yeah.
Why does your boss
seem so nice to you?
Could it be that
he likes you?
What?
He likes my sister?
Hey, what are you talking about,
Jobert?
Here, watch the turtle.
Come on, Mom.
Don't pay attention to
what she's saying, okay?
Mom, don't make a big deal
out of Sir Paolo's help.
And don't give Jobert
any ideas, okay?
All right, go ahead
and sit there, Mom.
I just need to submit a few
files. I'll be right back.
And then we'll go home, okay?
Excuse me, Ma'am.
Good afternoon.
Are you Marj's family?
That's right.
I'm Edward,
I'm your daughter's friend.
Oh, so you're Edward.
Marj told me about you.
Really?
Yes.
Actually, your daughter
always talks about you, too.
And that's Jobert?
Yes.
Jobert?
Jobert, what are you watching?
Turtle.
Did you know that turtles
have a long life?
They can live up to 50 years.
Wow, big bro Edward
didn't know that.
Big bro?
Like my kind big bro?
Kind big bro?
Who is that?
Oh, that's what he
calls Sir Paolo.
He likes Sir Paolo because
your brother helped us.
He likes my big sister.
Jobert, that's enough, sweetie.
Don't talk like that.
I'm sorry about that, Sir.
He doesn't know
what he's talking about.
It's okay.
Jobert,
just watch TV, sweetie.
Look, look how big
that turtle is.
Is everything all right,
sweetie?
Yeah.
I just remembered...
When I was a kid,
I would stay up late
every night studying.
And I joined every sport
there was,
because I wanted to at least win
some kind of award.
To be displayed here.
Just one, I'm happy with that.
Sweetie, awards
are not important at all.
That's not the measure
of your worth.
And you shouldn't be competing
with your brother.
I have to.
Because that's the only way
I can earn my place.
So you would notice me, too.
Why is it like that, Mom?
With Paolo, it seems like...
winning comes so easily to him.
And...
he gets whatever he wants.
Wait a minute.
Did you and your sibling
have an argument again?
No.
Not really, Mom.
I'm just tired
of always being the loser.
I'm so tired of losing
and not getting what I want.
Right now, Mom.
There's this girl that...
I really like.
And...
I will do everything to win her.
Because I don't want
to lose her.
Okay.
Oh my goodness, sweetie.
Sir, Miss Castillo's here.
Sit down.
You called me here.
Do you need something, Sir?
I just want to discuss
the incident with Mr. Valderama.
I understand
that you felt offended
about what happened.
But I've known Harry
for a long time.
He's a devoted husband and a
loving father to two daughters.
What did I have to do with them?
What I mean to say is...
What happened could have
been just an accident.
Perhaps Harry just
accidentally brushed...
onto your buttocks.
He will not risk his name
and reputation
by doing such things.
You must have just overreacted.
But Sir...
You could have been...
stressed or exhausted
when that happened.
And you have misinterpreted
the client's intention.
Listen,
I don't want this to go
any further, Miss Castillo.
I want to retain Mr. Valderama
as our valued client.
That's why I want you to go to
him and apologize in person.
You're not going to decline
my request, right?
After all,
you're indebted to us,
since my son helped you save
your brother.
Remember?
I will go to him to apologize.
Good.
I didn't come here
to argue with you.
I came here to apologize.
I've hurt and accused you.
I hope you can forgive me.
And that it won't affect
your business deals
with Torrecampo Realty.
I also want to apologize to you,
Miss Castillo.
You almost lost your job
because of that incident.
You don't need to worry
about that anymore, Sir.
I'm back at work now.
The important thing is,
we got this straightened out.
Well, I'm glad
we can put that behind us now.
Well, we should celebrate
this moment.
No, thank you.
Sir, they might look for me
at the office.
Thank you,
but I'm going to have to pass.
It's just one drink.
You won't get drunk.
Come on, Miss Castillo.
Please grant my request.
Cheers?
Cheers.
Good morning, Gemma.
Could you please get me
a cup of coffee
and cancel all my appointments
for today?
I had a bad hangover.
Okay, Sir.
And...
can you call Miss Tough Girl?
I mean, Miss Castillo
from her cubicle.
Sir, as far as I know,
Marj is out of the office
right now.
We don't have
an open house today.
Your dad asked her
to go see Mr. Valderama.
Sir, what's the matter?
Thank you, Sir,
but I have to get going.
Are you sure you
don't want to stay?
So we can talk more.
Thank you for your time.
But they need me
at the office.
Are you sure?
Are you all right,
Miss Castillo?
I just felt a little dizzy,
but I'm okay.
Please, don't.
Sir, please, no.
Good afternoon, Mr. Torrecampo.
Mr. Valderama!
Get off of her!
There are so many bars out
there if you want a good time.
If you want,
I can accompany you.
Stay out of this, Paolo!
I can't!
You drugged my employee!
If you want,
let's just take this outside.
If you want me
to break every bone you have.
You're insane!
You bastard!
I will pull out all of my
investments in your company!
Don't threaten me!
Because I can file a case
of attempted rape
and acts of lasciviousness
against you!
And I have a witness!
So don't even try me!
Sir? Sir Paolo.
Don't worry, you're safe now.
- How is your brother now?
- He's okay now.
-I'm glad Sir Paolo helped me.
- Who's that kind big bro?
That's what he calls Sir Paolo.
He likes my big sister.
Sir!
It's Marj, Sir!
Something happened to her!
What happened?
Thankfully, she only ingested
a small amount
of depressant drugs.
All her vitals are normal.
So there's no need
to confine her.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
Sir, thank you,
that you came.
If you weren't there,something
bad might happen to me.
Mr. Valderama got nothing on me.
And I had a bad hangover.
Sir, thank you so much.
I was so scared.
My mom, my brother.
They're the only ones
I think about.
I'm the only one
they can count on.
What if something
bad happened to me?
I don't know what I'll do.
I couldn't bear it.
Don't cry, don't cry.
Don't cry, stop crying.
Aren't you Miss Tough Girl?
Nurse, excuse me.
Where is Miss
Marjorie Castillo?
That way, Sir.
Sorry, sorry,
I'm sorry, Sir.
Sorry for what?
I hugged you.
I'm sorry.
I just got carried away.
I know I always have
that affect on you.
Thank you, Sir Paolo.
Thank you, Sir.
You're welcome.
Okay, Ma'am.
We're good to go.
Let me give you a lift.
Thank you, Sir Paolo.
But you don't need
to give me a lift,
I can take care of myself now.
Just call me Paolo.
And...
it's the least
I could do for you.
After everything happened.
I'm still a gentleman.
My mom might see you, Sir.
Paolo.
I'm sure she'll
wonder what happened.
She'll ask questions,
and I don't want them
to find out about this.
I don't want them
to worry about me.
Fair enough.
Okay, just...
don't forget what the doctor
said, all right?
The drug they gave you
will still affect your body
for the next 6 to 12 hours.
So you still need to rest.
Until it completely wears off.
And when you're ready,
let me know, okay?
I'll go with you to file a
complaint against Mr. Valderama.
No, please.
I don't want to add
to your problems
or your expenses because of me.
You already have so
much on your plate.
And besides,
he's a powerful man, the kind
you don't just go up against.
Okay.
It's up to you.
But remember this, okay?
I always got your back.
And I will make sure
that we won't be making business
deals with him anymore.
You can trust me on that.
Thank you, Paolo.
You're welcome.
Stop crying. You're Miss Tough
Girl, remember?
Hi, Jobert.
Marj, why do you look like that?
Did something happen, sweetie?
Nothing, Mom.
I'm just exhausted.
Come, sit down, it's
time for dinner.
I'm going to set the table,
okay?
I got that, Mom.
Jobert, what
are you doing?
Big sissy's not okay.
You look scared.
I'm just worried.
I'm thinking if you're
behaving while I'm at work?
Jobert's a good boy, right?
Sis,
if they're being mean to you,
you tell Jobert, okay?
I will fight for you.
I will defend you.
I will.
They'll get scared if they
find out you'll fight for me.
Hi, Weng.
Hey, what's with
the serious face?
I saw you.
What?
I saw you and Marj at the ER.
What was that about?
Oh, come on.
It's not like you haven't
seen me with other girls before.
What's the big deal?
What happened to her?
Mr. Valderama tried
to take advantage of her.
But don't worry, she's safe now.
I handled everything already.
Are we good?
Did I answer all your questions?
Do you like her?
Wait.
Are you acting like this
because you like her?
Do you like her?
What if I tell you
that I like her?
I like Marj.
I really like her a lot.
What about you?
Do you like her, too?
Mom, who's that?
It's nothing. Nobody.
- Who's that?
- It's nothing, Marj.
- Here, I got it.
- Marj, I got it.
Marj.
Why are you hiding your phone?
Who is it?
Mom!
You're texting Dad?
This is just
the initial presentation.
I didn't expect
that they would send you.
Why did you have to lie?
Mr. Fuentes didn't request
that I do the presentation.
The Paradiso Escano deal needs
the best person for the job.
And that's Paolo, and not you.
Thanks, Dad.
That's my chance
to impress Marj.
Don't be nervous. We got this.
You got this.
You're Miss Tough Girl, right?
Does that mean Premium Homes
Realty is here, too?
Love.
Randall, I'm here to work.
Please don't bother me.
And we have nothing
left to talk about.
Leave me alone.