I agreed to marry Edward
because I wanted my child
to be a legitimate Torrecampo.
You should be thanking me.
You won't be separated
from our child.
They said I'm bad.
Paolo's mom said
I'm bad for Baby Jasmine.
What if you just agree
to what they want?
Just don't let Jobert
get close to Jasmine.
That way he'll still be here...
but there won't be
any more trouble, Marj.
I hope they agree.
Sorry, Paolo,
for what I did.
My teacher said...
the dove means peace.
Paolo...
I don't want to hurt
Baby Jasmine.
No.
I know.
Don't you want me anymore?
It's not like that.
I'm not mad at you, Jobert.
I just want to protect
Baby Jasmine.
And to keep her safe.
Always.
Do you understand?
I want to protect Baby Jasmine.
Then you'll do everything...
for Baby Jasmine, right?
Yes, Paolo.
Marj, just tell me if you need
help watching Jasmine, okay?
Just tell me. Don't be shy.
Yes, Mom. I will.
Mom! What's the problem?
It's nothing, Marj. Nothing.
- No.
- Marj, it's nothing.
Mom, what hurts? Lift your arm.
What is this?
It hurts, Marj!
Did dad do that to you?
Marj...
Your dad is cheating again.
I got mad at him last night,
and...
this is what I got.
Mom!
If you had just listened to me!
I thought he had changed, Marj.
- Forgive me.
- Mom, listen to me.
Sorry isn't going to fix this.
Leave dad.
Just leave him. Please listen.
Please, listen to me.
I know.
It's my fault.
I went back to Lito again.
I chose him again.
That's why our family
is falling apart, Marj.
- I deserve this.
- Mom, listen to me.
You don't deserve this.
You don't deserve this, okay?
No one who truly loves someone
would do this to them.
So leave. Pack your things.
Leave dad.
He might do something
worse next time.
Are you listening?
What else did dad do?
I'm sorry, Marj. I'm so sorry.
Hello, Hannah?
How's mom?
She's exhausted.
She's okay, though.
I'll take care of your mom here.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
I'll send extra for rent
and whatever food she needs.
Sorry for all the trouble.
What are you talking about?
You are family.
Thank you again, Hannah.
Bye.
Marj,
can Baby Jasmine play with me?
Maybe later, Jobert.
Jasmine needs to sleep.
Go play with Yolly
and Weng for now.
Are you mad at me?
I'm not mad.
Paolo is mad at me.
And Paolo's mom.
And you.
Jobert, I'm not mad.
Stop crying now. That's enough.
It's because I'm bad.
Bad. Bad.
- Bad! Bad!
- Jobert, stop it.
- Jobert, stop!
- Bad! Bad!
- Jobert!
You don't want me anymore!
Jobert, enough!
You're going too far! Stop!
Enough!
Jobert!
Where's Jobert?
He's still locked in his room,
Ma'am.
He keeps calling
for your mother.
He wants to see her.
Then why don't you just take him
there?
If that's what he wants,
give it to him.
So we can finally have
some peace in this house.
I did suggest
maybe Jobert should stay
with Mommy Evelyn for now.
It's painful for Marj and me...
but we'll all have more peace
of mind knowing Jasmine is safe.
I'm so sorry about this, Marj.
I know I promised
when you and Paolo got married
that you and Jobert
were a package deal.
But I have no choice but
to agree with Regina and Paolo.
Dear...
Jobert needs to go.
Mom, I don't have anyone
on my side here.
I'm really struggling
with what they want.
Marj, can't they be reasoned
with?
What if Jobert promises
to stay away from Jasmine?
That's not fair.
It's as if Jobert is sick
that he's not even allowed
to be near my daughter.
That's not right, Mom.
If they all don't want him...
maybe it's not good for Jobert
to stay here.
So what are you going to do,
Marj?
Mom, I'm begging you and Hannah.
Please take Jobert in.
You're the only ones he trusts,
aside from Paolo and me.
Please, Mom.
Don't cry, Jobert.
I'm not abandoning you.
- I'll take care of you.
- No.
I don't want to leave.
I'll stay here with my sister.
Jobert, we have to do this.
You'll come back when Jasmine
is stronger and healthier.
When she's tougher,
you can play together.
You have to understand that.
You understand, right?
I'll do it.
I'll leave...
to protect Baby Jasmine.
Very good.
Yolly, why are you crying?
Yolly...
It's nothing.
I just got attached
to that child.
You haven't even known Jobert
that long,
but you miss him
so much already.
He reminds me of my son.
If he were still alive,
he'd be the same age as Jobert
by now.
Oscar and I will miss him, too.
He's such a joy to be around.
I just feel bad.
Our employers don't see
what we see in that boy.
He's so kind.
So hardworking. So loving.
Just because he's different
doesn't mean it's his fault
the baby almost got hurt.
I'll listen to my sister
so she won't be mad anymore.
Jobert...
I'm not mad.
I will never be mad at you.
I love you so much.
We just have to do this
for Jasmine.
Okay?
Marj...
Give me a hug.
I love you, okay?
I love you.
I love you, too, Marj.
Yolly, we can't really
blame them either.
Yes, Jobert is very kind.
But we can't predict
when he might have an episode.
Like last night,
he was screaming, remember?
- It was scary.
- What's scary about that!
He doesn't just have
episodes out of nowhere!
He was triggered!
And do you know why
he gets triggered?
Because of the nasty attitudes
of the people upstairs.
Yolly, they might hear you.
If they hadn't questioned
that boy's worth,
he wouldn't feel the need
to prove himself in this family.
He wouldn't have tried so hard
that he accidentally
put Jasmine in danger.
Those people are the ones
at fault.
They're the ones to blame.
Yolly, let me get
you some water.
Here, drink.
That's enough.
We're leaving.
Thank you so much
for letting Jobert stay here,
even just for a while.
I believe
he can come back someday...
when Jasmine is older.
Maybe not.
I don't want my son
causing trouble for you again.
And it's hard living with...
people who aren't normal.
Marj.
- Mom.
- We're going now.
Take care.
Jobert.
I'll call you, okay?
I promise, I'll call.
Look at me.
Don't forget that...
I love you.
Jobert, let's go.
Let's go home, son. Let's go.
Jobert...
Come on, we're going home.
Jobert, let's go home.
Bye, Marj.
Jobert.
Come on, what are you doing?
Marj!
I want to stay here.
I'll stay here.
I'll stay here, Marj.
I'll stay here!
- Marj.
- Jobert, don't be stubborn.
- Come on.
- Marj!
Marj!
Don't send me away.
Marj, please don't send me away.
I'm such a terrible sister.
No, Love. Okay?
You're being a good mother
to Jasmine.
That's the right thing to do.
Don't worry, Jobert.
Just hang in there
a little longer.
Someday we'll live
in our dream house.
You, me, and mom.
And Pong.
Of course, Pong comes, too.
He can't be left behind.
And I will give you everything
you want that's good for you.
Because I love you.
I love you, too.
Baby...
look at this.
Your Uncle Jobert made it.
Jasmine, your Uncle Jobert
loves you so, so much.
It's just a shame we can't
have him with us right now.
I didn't want him to leave.
But...
I had to.
To protect you.
Because I love you so much,
my child.
So much.
Jobert!
Hey!
Hannah missed you!
Jobert, hey!
I bought snacks for Pong.
Do you want to give them to him?
Is there anything
you want to eat?
Come on, let's buy something.
We'll order.
Hannah...
I'm sorry.
He just really doesn't want
to leave his sister.
Jobert, go upstairs to your room
for now.
You know the drill.
Same as before. Come on.
Yeah, let's put Pong here.
Let's set Pong down.
Enjoy.
How are you holding up?
Here...
My heart is breaking
for my children.
Maybe if I had been
a better mother...
this wouldn't have happened.
Auntie, please don't pity
yourself like that.
Hannah...
it's true.
I put myself first,
and I neglected Jobert.
That's why Marj ended up having
to take him to the mansion.
But...
I've woken up now.
After all my foolishness
with Lito.
I'll do everything I can
to make it up to my children.
Marj has her own family now.
It's not her responsibility
to take care of Jobert anymore.
That's right, Auntie.
I just hope...
it's not too late.
I hope...
I can still fix my mistakes.
I can still take good care
of my children.
I hope...
our family
can still be whole again.
It will happen, Auntie.
Now you're making me cry.
Okay, I'll take care
of Jobert's things.
Please, have a seat first.
Here, have some water.
Your baby is looking healthy
at two months.
Doctor...
is that the baby's heartbeat?
Yes,
that's the baby's heartbeat.
Doctor...
where's my baby on the screen?
I can't really see anything.
Right now, the baby's only about
half the size of your thumb.
Give it a few months,
and you'll see more clearly.
But, Doc, the heartbeat...
it's supposed to be
that fast, right?
Yes, that's completely normal.
There's no problem, right, Doc?
Hon...
the doctor said
our baby's healthy.
Don't worry.
I just want my baby to be
perfect when she comes out.
I have very big dreams for her.
Don't worry.
I won't let anything happen
to you.
Our baby's going to be healthy.
I'm just demanding
what I deserve.
You think you deserve Paolo...
even though
you already have Edward?
I deserve for my child
to have a father.
I'm pregnant,
and he's the father.
You're going to make it look
like Edward is the father.
That way,
the baby will still be
a legitimate Torrecampo.
You know,
I think it would be better
if you moved into the mansion.
It'll be better for your child.
I actually love that idea.
Do you think that's a good idea?
Don't tell me
after all this time,
you still have feelings for him?
She has bronchopulmonary
dysplasia.
If she's not carefully
monitored,
the condition could persist.
Jasmine?
It's like she's not breathing.
This is your fault!
If you had taken better care
of Jasmine,
this wouldn't have happened!
I'll never forgive you!
Your niece is beautiful
and healthy, Paolo.
And don't you ever forget that.
She's Edward's daughter.