Hello, Edward!
Look who still remembers
the address.
You're starting something?
A web development company?
If he wants to prove himself,
he should do it without asking
for another check.
Forget it.
You shouldn't have offered help
in the first place.
Edward, are you really sure
about Thea?
She said you were the one who
spread her video scandal before.
- Is that true?
- Yes.
If I could turn back time,
I wouldn't have done it.
So Rodriguez really left?
Love, they even took Velasco and
our Santos accounts with them.
I've got someone
who could help you.
And who exactly would that be?
Hi, Paolo!
What is she doing here?
We'll be working together again.
Mr. Orbos?
Let me make you an offer.
Better property. Better terms.
I know something else that could
close the deal faster.
Your choice.
My child.
Where's the money I gave you?
All my savings.
Everything I worked for.
Dear...
I'm sorry. Something went wrong.
Sorry?
You used my body
to pay your debts!
You wasted all the money
that was supposed to be
for your medicine.
You chose gambling
over staying alive.
I had no other choice.
You had a choice, Dad!
I'm the one
who had no choice!
I'm always the one
who has to sacrifice.
I'm always the one who has
to get dirty just to save you!
It's my duty to save you
because I'm your daughter.
But that was the wrong kind
of obligation, Dad.
I'm tired of getting dirty
just so you can live.
My child...
I promised myself...
I'd never use my body again...
for money and ambition.
But I couldn't rely on Edward.
So this was the only way...
to impress the Torrecampos.
To get into their world.
So, good news, everyone!
We've officially regained
the Orbos account.
Signed, sealed,
and confirmed this morning.
Wow! That was fast, Thea!
We thought it was impossible,
but you managed to pull it off.
Seriously impressive.
Hey, come on.
That's incredible, Thea.
We've been trying to win them
back for weeks.
How did you manage
to convince them?
Well...
just a lot of follow-ups, Paolo.
Talk it out, read the room,
and maybe a little charm.
Now, that's initiative.
Even Marj...
couldn't get Orbos back.
But you did.
Looks like we found ourselves
a new lucky charm
in this company.
Thank you.
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe it was just luck.
Or maybe they just preferred me
this time.
But Marj's still amazing.
Right, Marj?
Congratulations, Thea.
Well then, here's to new wins,
and to Thea Villarreal.
Let's keep this momentum going.
Thea's amazing, right?
We chased Orbos for weeks
to no avail.
She met him once,
and boom, deal done.
Exactly.
It's almost too good to be true.
Well, whatever she did,
it worked.
Let's just hope she keeps it up.
At least the company's finally
making progress, right?
Aren't you curious, Love,
how she did it?
We all know
Mr. Orbos is stubborn.
Why'd he change
his mind overnight?
Maybe Thea's just that good.
And can we not overthink it?
Please?
Work talk again.
Office hours are over.
Love, I'm exhausted.
It's been a long day.
Exhausted?
That's what you said last night.
But you still managed,
didn't you?
Yeah, we just did it last night.
Then let's do it again.
And dad's been waiting
for a grandkid, right?
Come on.
Love, Love, Love.
Can we make the Torrecampo boy
next time?
Please?
Just one more.
Promise.
Chloe, what time's my meeting
with Mrs. Sanchez?
- 10:00 AM, Ma'am.
- Okay.
And the Yakap Bata Foundation?
- 1:00 PM.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Ma'am.
Marj.
Thea.
Hi, Auntie!
I just came by
to congratulate you personally.
You got the Orbos account
so fast.
Very impressive.
Oh, thank you, Auntie.
Maybe it was just luck
that Mr. Orbos trusted
Torrecampo again.
It's not just that, dear.
You've got something special.
Smart.
Composed.
Decisive.
Edward's lucky to have you.
Thank you.
You know what?
I really admire women
who walk into a room
with charm and grace.
Not the kind who overreact
or bring drama.
Oh, Auntie, Marj
was a great mentor to me before.
I learned a lot from her.
Really?
Then keep learning
from her mistakes.
Excuse me. I have a meeting.
Marj's actually doing
really well, too, Auntie.
She's handling a lot right now.
- Maybe she's just...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sure she's doing her best.
And so am I, Auntie.
I'll do my best to make
things easier around here.
That's what I want to hear.
Maybe next time you can convince
Edward to come back.
Let's have lunch
at the house soon, okay?
Yes, of course.
All right, I'll head out.
Chloe.
Marj, are you okay?
You look pale.
I'm not okay. But...
I'll manage.
Marj, I just wanted to say,
don't take whatever
Auntie Regina said seriously.
You know how she is.
She can be blunt.
She didn't mean
anything personal.
You don't need to defend me.
I don't need a lawyer
against my mother-in-law.
That's not what I meant.
- I just wanted to say...
- I know that tone.
"I'm just being a friend" tone?
Enough, Thea.
Can you stop pretending?
Stop acting nice.
Marj.
What do you want me to do?
I've tried everything,
so you'll forgive me.
- What else do I need to do?
- Nothing.
I don't want anything from you.
Marj.
Wait.
What now?
Your dress.
Marj, you're bleeding.
We need to get you
to the hospital.
I'll take you.
Doc, am I pregnant?
Almost three months.
Congratulations,
Mrs. Torrecampo.
Mom-to-be.
So that's why I've been getting
tired and dizzy so easily.
That explains
the mood swings, too.
Oh my God.
But, Doc,
I was bleeding earlier.
Is my baby okay?
It's a good thing
you came in right away.
If you'd waited any longer,
there could've been
complications.
But for now, the baby's stable.
I'll be back with the rest
of the test results.
Just get some rest
and avoid stress, okay?
Okay, thank you, Doc.
You're welcome.
Paolo's on his way.
He's almost here.
If you hadn't come and kept
pushing me to forgive you,
who knows what could've happened
to my baby and me.
Good thing I'm persistent.
Like how a sales agent
should be.
But, Marj,
what matters is you're safe.
Both of you.
I don't know if I'm ready
to forget what happened before,
but...
thank you.
I'm not asking you to forget.
I just...
I just want a chance
to make it right.
I don't know.
But...
maybe someday.
That's all I need.
One day,
when you finally trust me again,
it'll be easier for me to decide
when and how to break you
in front of the Torrecampos.
Is this it? Is this...
What is this? The legs?
Kind of.
I'm sure dad and mom
are going to love this.
So after running some tests,
we saw that the baby's heartbeat
is strong.
However, the placenta
is implanted a bit low.
So we need to be careful.
Doc, what does that mean?
It means there's a higher risk
of bleeding or miscarriage
if you get too tired, stressed,
or overly active.
You'll need complete bed rest.
So avoid strenuous activities.
Heavy lifting.
And even sexual activity, okay?
At least until
your next checkup.
How serious is it, Doc?
As long as you follow my advice,
everything should be fine.
What's important
is that you avoid stress.
And that you have someone at
home to help take care of you.
- I'll head out now.
- Okay.
- Thank you, Doc.
We can do this.
We've got this, okay?
- Hi, Ma'am Marj.
- Hello.
- Hi, Sir.
- Marj!
- There's my grandkid!
Hi, Paolo.
Marj...
you know I've been waiting
a long time for this news.
The first grandchild
of the Torrecampos.
What a blessing.
Thank you so much, Dad.
But the doctor said
my pregnancy's a bit delicate.
So I really need to rest.
Of course, of course.
No overexerting yourself.
Tell us anything you need.
You're carrying our legacy.
The future of our family.
And family comes first.
I'll take care of my sister.
If she gets tired,
I'll make sure she rests.
I'll protect the baby.
Promise, Uncle.
Well, look at that.
The mom already has a bodyguard.
Good job, young man.
I hope the child gets
the best of both families.
Hopefully not too much of the...
uniqueness of his special uncle.
Mom...
the doctor said
Marj's pregnancy is sensitive.
And she also said
to avoid stress.
Okay?
So maybe, temporarily,
let's call a ceasefire.
For the baby.
Yes. Yes, of course.
I mean, I don't want
to stress Marj out.
Especially since she's not used
to our lifestyle yet.
And I don't want to stress
the baby either. So yeah. Okay.
Mom, for the baby.
Okay.
I'll keep the peace.
I care about the child.
No matter who
the mother is.
That's enough!
All right?
Let's not ruin
a beautiful day with drama.
Today, we celebrate.
The Torrecampo legacy lives on.
Well, look who finally decided
to come home.
I thought you were
going to sleep at the bar.
By the way,
I've got good news for you.
Marj is pregnant.
And believe it or not,
we made up!
You know,
I feel like she's going to ask
me to be the baby's godmother.
Good for you.
What kind of reaction is that?
What now?
What happened this time?
Some investors pulled out
from my start-up.
I need to find new ones. ASAP.
Well then, talk to your dad.
Make peace already, so you can
go back to the family company.
At least you'd be secure there.
For what?
So I can beg him?
- No.
- So I can admit he was right?
No!
So you can demand and reclaim
your position.
Edward, you're good.
You know that.
Oh, perfect timing.
I'm going to your house later.
- Come with me.
- No.
I'm not going back there.
Do you want me to beg them?
I'll figure this out. On my own.
Okay.
Fine.
I won't ask your dad
for help anymore.
But at least come with me
to your place, okay?
Marj invited me, too.
Just to show support.
And maybe you want to see
your future niece or nephew?
Edward...
come on.
It won't take long.
Let them see
that their rebel son...
still cares about his family,
even if his bank account
is full of pride.
Come in!
- Hi, Marj.
- Hi, Thea.
How are you feeling?
Oh, Edward's with you.
Yeah, we just dropped by.
Thea wanted to see you.
Good thing you met Thea.
I got the chance
to reconnect with her
and even work with her again.
I wanted to apologize
for judging her before.
And thank you
for standing by her.
So, let's get back
to the agenda.
- Oh, yeah.
- What are you turning over?
Here it is. These are the...
- Sorry.
- I'll help you.
These are the accounts
I'm handling.
You'll take over for now.
I can't really monitor
them anymore.
The doctor said
I need to rest.
Oh, Marj,
don't worry about work.
I'll handle everything.
Thank you, Thea.
You know,
I'm worried about Paolo.
He's dealing with so many
problems right now,
and I can't even help him.
Don't think about that.
Don't think about that now.
Focus on your baby.
I'll take care of Paolo.
I'll take care of everything.
Right, Hon?
Maybe just focus on the tasks
Marj assigns you.
Leave Paolo alone.
He's a grown man.
Exactly.
Anyway, Marj,
I'll handle everything, okay?
You can trust me.
Hey, you've been showing up
at the mansion a lot lately.
I thought you were happy?
Your boyfriend's right there
with you.
I don't even know anymore.
You know,
working on Edward isn't easy.
He's stubborn, full of pride,
and he refuses
to make peace with his dad.
And we both know he needs help.
Then why don't you just
go straight to the dad?
Sir Greg.
You've got influence, right?
Of course!
Honestly, I'm even closer
to Greg than Edward is.
But I don't really want
to get in between them.
The rift between father
and son runs deep.
I knew it!
You picked the wrong
Torrecampo to date.
You should've gone
for the older brother.
Guaranteed win.
Future CEO.
But then Marj got pregnant.
And if the first baby's a boy?
Huge points!
He'll carry the family name.
What?
Is it too late now?
So what if he's married
and has kids?
That's easy for me.
Piece of cake, girl.
Girl, don't tell me you're
going to go after both brothers?
Hey! That's low, Lalaine!
Marj's my best friend.
I'm not stealing anyone's man,
okay?
That's disgusting!
But if blessings come
knocking on my door...
then thank you, Lord.
I won't say no.
That was impressive,
Ms. Thea.
Everyone, thank you.
Meeting adjourned.
I didn't know you were
that sharp with numbers.
I've had good mentors.
And I've learned how to adapt.
Especially when
I need to prove I belong.
You don't need to prove
anything. You're doing great.
Thanks, Boss.
But hey,
this is strictly work, okay?
I don't want people thinking
I have special favors with you.
Don't worry. No, no.
I won't let this reach HR.
I'll go ahead.
Yes?
Love...
you've been resting all day.
Maybe we could have
a little...
cuddle time?
The doctor said we can't yet.
My pregnancy's delicate.
I'll be gentle.
Come on, I just
really miss you.
I know, I know.
But I don't want to risk
our baby.
So please, just be patient
for a bit, okay?
Love.
I just want our baby to be safe.
I've been feeling
a little guilty lately.
It's been a long time
since we did it, you know.
I know all you care
about is the baby's safety.
So that's why
you've been so irritable, son.
If you can't have it at home,
look for it somewhere else.
Simple as that.
Are you coming home
for dinner tonight?
I cooked all your favorites.
I'll wait for you, okay?
The country manager
of NextConnect Global Services
messaged me.
He's willing to meet tonight.
No matter how hard you try,
if there's already a wall
between you and your husband,
it's not going to be easy
to tear it down.
You decide.
If you're coming, I'm game.