[DRAMATIC TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Thea, Ashley and Jasmine
are a match!
Marj, I am sorry.
We did not agree to the test.
Edward, they already got tested.
What kind of mother are you?
You had her tested without even
telling me?
Because you would not agree.
Besides, Ashley
wanted this too.
Are you not tired of people
getting hurt because of you?
- It is all your fault!
- [SLAPS]
People only change their minds
when they are forced to face
what they avoid.
When will the operation be
so our family trip
can finally happen?
Soon, my child.
They are just finalizing
the procedure.
What if there is really
something they need to face?
Go on, my grandchild.
I am listening. He will be
Marj's lawyer
if she files a case against you
for what you did to Jobert.
Let us settle this.
Fine, what are we settling?
Allow Ashley to donate
to Jasmine.
- Unbelievable!
- One hundred fifty
million pesos.
What?
One hundred fifty million pesos?
Did you hear that, my child?
You have a donor now,
you and Ashley are a match!
So there really is a chance?
Not just a chance,
you will get better.
But
test consent is different from
the actual extraction.
What about Ashley then?
What if she suddenly backs out
or Aunt and Uncle refuse?
No, no, that will not happen,
my child.
We are almost there.
We will set your procedure soon.
I do not know, Mom.
Sometimes I feel
my life is full of almosts.
Almost healed,
almost normal,
almost okay as a family.
It is tiring to hope
when nothing is certain.
My child, do not think that way.
Think instead that
once you get better,
we will leave this place.
You will go home.
Do you want to go to the beach?
Anywhere, wherever you want.
Nature trekking?
Stargazing?
Road trip?
Anything you want.
Can I drive already?
Jasmine,
you really are something,
of course!
Just take driving lessons
and get a student permit. It's
not that easy.
I will teach you how to drive.
Manual transmission, for real.
Will you come with us on
the stargazing trip, Dad?
Yes.
The three of us together.
We will bring a tent
and all your favorite snacks.
We will go somewhere
with little light
so we can see the stars.
No phones,
no hospital, no problems.
Then we will wait
for a shooting star.
We will make a wish.
No need to wish
because we are together
and happy.
Best wish granted ever.
[DRAMATIC]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
How long are you
checked in here?
I do not know.
I am still looking for a place.
[PHONE RINGING]
[UNSETTLING]
Are they still pressuring you
about the test?
Maybe
you are still giving them hope
and accommodating them.
Edward,
can you endure Jasmine's
condition getting worse?
If Ashley were the one who
was sick,
I feel Paolo would not hesitate.
Because what?
Even Marj
would help Ashley if she
were in Jasmine's situation.
Dad,
are you not worried
about Jasmine?
[SIGHS]
My heart aches for Jasmine.
I can't watch what is happening
to her, but, my child.
But you are my responsibility.
You are my priority.
So we will just let it be?
Thea,
one mistake
in the operating room,
one mistake, one complication,
we will carry that for life.
Do you want Ashley to be harmed?
Can you live
knowing you decided that?
If they do not match,
life goes on.
But if they match,
she will donate to Jasmine.
This is the last time
I am going to say this .
Ashley's body is off limits.
They cannot touch Ashley
as if they have a right to her .
Dad!
[INTENSE]
Thea!
Are you avoiding us?
Did you not receive my text?
Ashley and Jasmine are matched.
[SIGHS]
I received your messages.
But Edward refuses.
I will talk to him again.
I am just waiting
for the right time.
Thea, I do not have tomorrow!
I do not have right time.
I do not even know if my child
has a tomorrow.
Why are you so demanding?
You are the one asking
for a favor.
Marj, my child
is also involved here.
Do you think I want to talk
to you?
It is against my will to beg
someone like you,
but I choose to be a mother
rather than a betrayed spouse.
Thea, if I need to beg Edward.
Not now, it is chaotic.
Marj.
Edward.
Marj, I am sorry.
We do not agree to the test.
I already told Paolo that.
Edward, they already got tested.
[INTENSE]
What?
You got tested behind my back?
Edward, Ashley and Jasmine
are matched.
I am begging you.
The doctor needs a schedule
for the transplant
as soon as possible.
Please, allow Ashley
to help Jasmine.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Go upstairs now.
- I will take you, lets go.
- Edward, please, please.
No more.
I am not agreeing.
Edward, my child's life
is at stake.
And my child's life
is also at stake.
If I have to be seen as cruel
in everyone's eyes,
I will do it!
As long as I do not allow
my child to be used
especially without my consent!
Marj,
They silenced me for so long
in this family, but this time,
I will decide.
I will not allow it.
- I am begging you.
- Ashley,
- let's go.
- Please, I am begging you.
Let Ashley help.
Marj, it is not allowed!
We cannot help you, I am sorry.
Please leave.
I thought you were different.
I thought you had a heart.
But you are selfish too.
[INTENSE]
What kind of mother are you?
You had her tested
without even telling me?
You would not agree anyway.
Besides, Ashley wanted it too.
And Jasmine deserves
compassion too.
Hey, why is that?
Are you still hoping to return
to my family if you help?
Edward, not everything
is about you.
I am also Ashley's parent!
I did not force her.
I did not use her.
I listened to our child.
I do not believe your reasoning.
You would not do that without
gaining something.
Why do you still refuse?
I already matched, right?
What about Jasmine? What if
something happens to Jasmine?
If I have a chance
and do nothing,
I would not be able to live
with that.
My child,
that is not just a simple test.
There is a process
and there are risks.
And as your parent,
it is my responsibility
to not let you be harmed
by anyone.
Dad, I can survive this.
Knowing I did
something meaningful.
My child, I could not bear it if
something bad happened to you.
So we are just going to let
Jas be?
We are just going
to let her die?
[SIGHS]
No.
They will find another way
if needed.
What if I am really the way?
Mom,
after everything,
is this not the least we can do?
Ashley...
Are you not getting tired.
Are you not tired of people
getting hurt because of you?
Ashley, do not talk like that.
Why not?
It is true.
If not because of you,
everything would not be
in chaos.
This is all your fault!
The cheating, everything,
even what happened
to Uncle Jobert!
- [SLAPS]
- Enough!
Thea!
[INTENSE]
- [SOBBING]
- My child, I am sorry.
My child, I am sorry.
I understand now.
Maybe I really was a mistake.
If I had not existed
from your lies,
you would not be like this.
[INTENSE]
This is my only chance to do
something right even just once.
To have value.
So please,
do not take this away from me.
Ashley, my child.
Do not follow me anymore
if you still want me
to come back.
[INTENSE]
I am tired.
Everything is always forbidden.
Not allowed.
You are still young.
Others will decide for you.
This is my body.
My rules.
When can I decide for myself?
Without anyone getting angry
at me?
Without hurting anyone?
It feels like everyone
has a say over my body.
In my life.
If I help,
it is drama.
If I do not help,
I am selfish.
That is how they see me!
I am selfish!
Do you want to help, Ash?
[DRAMATIC]
But it is unfair.
When I choose,
someone still gets hurt.
You choose to love.
You choose to care.
That is why I like you, Ashley.
I just do not want
to see you suffer.
Xander,
thank you.
Thank you for being here
with me.
You know,
you are the only one I know
who does not see me only
as a donor.
Or a child who needs protection.
That I am not a problem.
Thank you.
Thank you, Ashley.
[DRAMATIC]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
This is just a teaser.
So when you are discharged,
you will not be surprised.
This feels like stargazing
on an outer space level, Dad.
Your dad is really amazing.
Mom.
[DRAMATIC]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
When will the operation be
so our family trip outside
this hospital can happen?
Are you excited?
Soon, my child.
They are just finalizing
the procedure.
[DRAMATIC]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Dear, breathe.
Breathe.
[DRAMATIC]
I really just wanted to help,
Grandmother.
I truly just wanted to help.
But it feels like Dad
is not listening to me.
- [SIGHS]
- But you know,
your grandfaher and I
are on your side.
We understand you.
And you are so brave
and generous
for offering your help
to Jasmine.
I tried
to convince your mother,
I even offered help.
But
what do you think
your father did
to make Thea so stubborn?
Greg, not in front of our
grandchild, please.
Honestly, Ashley,
your mother makes decisions
when she is cornered.
When there is something
to protect,
when there is something to hide.
Greg!
What I am saying is,
people only change their minds
when they are forced to face
what they avoid.
But
it is not your obligation
to do that to your parents
just to get what you want,
Ashley.
You are still young.
I am not a child anymore.
What if
there really is something they
need to face?
Go on, my grandchild.
I am listening.
[TENSE]
I do not want to say this to
ruin her reputation
or anything like that.
I also do not want
to embarrass her.
But if Jasmine's life
is at stake,
I can no longer stay silent.
Ashley, what are you saying?
If there is a way to correct
my mother's mistakes
even little by little.
If I need to tell the truth
to save Jasmine,
I will do it.
[INTENSE]
Don't worry too much.
Ashley might just be
cooling off.
I am sure she will
come home later.
I hope Ashley understands
that we are being strict
because we want to protect her,
so she does not get hurt.
[PHONE BEEP]
[INTENSE]
Dad texted.
Ashley is there, apparently.
He wants us to go there.
Why did she go there?
I do not know.
- Let us just pick her up.
- Wait, for him to text us?
He would not just text
about where his grandchild is.
He has something planned.
He is going to interfere again.
[INTENSE]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Thank you for coming.
We are just going to pick up
Ashley.
Why does this feel like
a family meeting?
And who is he?
[CHUCKLES]
Aren't you familiar
with Attorney Mamucod?
Part of Torrecampo Realty's
legal team.
He will be Marj's lawyer
if she files a case against you
for what you did to Jobert.
[INTENSE]
Ashley.
- Whatever Ashley said...
- Stop it!
[SIGHS]
So, you just called us here
to threaten us?
- Come here!
- Sit!
Sit down!
[INTENSE]
Personally,
I do not want this
to reach court.
Bad publicity.
That is why it is better
to settle this.
Fine, what kind of settlement
is that?
It's where only your favorite
child benefits.
Edward, you know that
is not true.
Allow Ashley to donate
to Jasmine.
[HUFFS]
In exchange for not filing
a case against me?
My job, my support for Ashley?
What else?
- Unbelievable!
- One hundred fifty
million pesos.
What?
One hundred fifty million pesos?
[INTENSE]
Cash settlement.
No case, no hearing,
no scandal, and you walk away
with security.
Thanks again
to your loving mother.
Edward,
we will make sure
that Ashley is protected.
We will not put her in danger.
So
you are paying us
to give you my child?
We are not desperate!
And I am not stupid!
Do you think I do not know
how much you are paying
for the hotel?
How many credit cards you cycled
just to maintain your image?
You have no stable jobs!
All start-ups that do not earn!
All plans that never succeed!
Greg, that is too much!
Edward, my child!
Just think of it as a reward
for saving Jasmine's life.
[INTENSE]
A child's life is at stake!
I have made my decision.
I will not trade my child
for money.
And I will not turn my child's
body into a transaction.
[INTENSE]
What kind of person are you?
You had the chance to help.
You had the chance
to save Jasmine.
And you chose
to protect yourselves.
I have no one else left
to protect.
There is nothing left for me!
I lost everything!
The respect I worked hard for,
my family,
my home!
Ashley is my whole world now.
And I will not allow my world
to be traded
just to fix yours!
Enough!
This meeting is over.
Ashley.
Ashley, let's go!
[INTENSE]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why is Attorney Mamucod's
associate here
when there was no legal
settlement?
I just fixed something.
I revised the will.
I removed Edward.
What?
You removed your own child
from your will?
Edward refused to sell
his child!
That is not disrespect.
That is parenting.
That is not my point.
Then what is your point, Greg?
Does Edward know about this?
Edward and I
have different views
on what is best for Ashley.
And as her mother,
I need to make the decision.
Are you sure about this?
Nothing is certain in our lives
right now.
But I can stand by this more
than living with guilt.
Because there is a child
I would be allowing to die.
We can finally leave this mess.
Our lives will be better even if
it is just the two of us.
They will not take you
from me so easily.
I am scared, Mom.
Ashley.
What you mean is,
when you do not get your way,
you make him feel that he has
no right to be your son!
He really has no right
to be included in my will.
What do you mean?