Ash? Xander?
Don't you know I told
Xander to stay away?
And you're the one
who brought him there?
Did you know Jasmine
had a seizure?
Hey, Marj!
What are you doing
to my daughter, huh?
Next time you go after my kid,
I won't hesitate to hurt you.
You booked a flight
to Hong Kong?
The meds aren't working on her.
I'm not agreeing to your plans!
No one can stop me
from curing my daughter!
You convinced my wife
to go to Hong Kong!
Are you doing this on purpose?
Are you doing this to spite me?
You never do anything right!
Is that really how
low you think of me?
That's how everyone sees you.
Even Marj.
That's why she didn't
choose you, right?
You want me to go
against my own brother?
If you help me beat him,
wouldn't that be your revenge,
too?
I expected my daughter's
condition to improve,
just like the other patients
on this treatment.
But why is it like this?
Why is she getting weaker?
Why isn't the pain going away?
Several of our patients
also needed time to adjust
because of the extreme pain.
Just hang in there
a little longer.
My team and I are expecting
good results.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me,
I need to do my rounds.
Am I still doing
the right thing?
I'm the reason your suffering
is lasting longer, sweetheart.
I thought I was fighting
for you.
I thought I was choosing
what was best for you.
But maybe I'm the one
causing you pain.
I made the wrong decision.
I'll never forgive myself.
How do you like it so far?
Please feel free to look around.
-Okay.
-Orly, take care of them
- for now.
- Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Paolo.
I know you're having
a hard time.
But for what it's worth,
I don't think Marj has bad
intentions for your child.
Jasmine should be okay with her.
But right now we're at work.
Forget about Marj and the fact
that she disobeyed you.
You don't understand
because you're not
in my position.
Maybe not.
But I'm sure about one thing.
Things will only get worse
if you let Aldrin beat you.
Is that what you want?
Of course not.
I will never let that happen.
You've been taking that
for a week now, Manang.
Has your eye improved?
Nothing happens.
My eye just stings from putting
that oil on every night.
And she told me to drink
this three times a day,
but nothing's happening.
You should go back
to that faith healer.
Yes, Manang Yolly.
So you can get your money back.
Wasn't that the promise?
Yes.
She said she'd return it
if it didn't work.
That should be.
Manang Yolly, do you want us
to go with you?
Just to make sure that person
doesn't scam you.
It's going to be okay.
Hey! Be careful!
- What the!
- Sorry.
Oh, my legs!
I'm really sorry.
I'm so sorry.
What are you even doing here
now?
Do we need to fire the guard?
They're letting just anyone in.
I went to the skate park,
so I decided to drop by.
You do skateboard?
There's a lot more you
can learn about me.
Just like there's a lot
I still want to know about you.
Like, why do you look so sad
today?
Nothing.
I just miss Jas.
I'm worried about her.
I read about experimental
leukemia treatments...
It got me scared
because they said they're really
painful.
Hey, everything's going to be
okay.
We know Jasmine.
Even if she's sick, she's tough.
She's a fighter.
She's not just my best friend.
She's like a sister to me.
I just don't want to lose her.
Hey! You're not going
to lose her.
Everything's going to be okay.
Manang, I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
It's my fault, Manang.
- It's all my fault.
- Manang Yolly!
I'm so sorry, Manang.
Manang Yolly, calm down.
Our boss might hear you.
What happened?
My 100,000 pesos
savings are gone!
We went back to Madame Elsa's
house to get the donation back
because the oil she gave me
didn't work.
But when we got there,
she was gone.
All her things were gone, too!
Oh, no!
See? I told you!
You! You know what?
This is your fault!
That faith healer was
obviously a scam!
Why did you insist on
taking Manang Yolly there?
- It's your fault!
- Okay, fine!
It's my fault!
That's why I'm apologizing!
That's enough!
Blame me!
It's all my fault!
Manang, I'm sorry!
Hey, quit it.
Manang.
Let's find her.
She can't just run
away with your money.
How?
Where do we even start?
Let's report it
to the police.
That money's gone.
It's really gone.
Doctor, I'm sorry.
When I agreed to the
experimental treatment,
I didn't expect my child to go
through something this hard.
We've already had several
rounds,
but there's still no change
in her condition.
Mrs. Torrecampo,
you have to be patient.
We're doing our best
to cure your child.
I can't bear watching my child
suffer anymore.
I'm sorry, but we won't continue
the treatment.
We'll go back to the Philippines
and consider other options.
I respect your decision.
I'll make the necessary
arrangements.
Excuse me.
Mom...
I'm sorry.
I really wanted to get
better for you, but...
The pain is just too much.
It's okay. I understand.
And I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, my child.
I should be the one apologizing.
Please forgive me.
I shouldn't have forced you
to come here.
Your dad was right.
I'm so sorry.
Let's go home.
Is this going to stop now?
Yes.
Yes, it's going to stop.
I'm taking you home.
I'm sorry.
Jasmine!
- Sorry, Auntie.
- Ma'am Marj.
How are you?
Are you feeling better?
Did the treatment work?
Jasmine!
Jasmine, sweetheart!
It's so nice to have you home,
my granddaughter.
Jasmine...
Oscar, please take Jasmine
to her room.
She needs to rest.
- Jasmine!
How are you?
I'm glad you're back.
Go ahead.
You always think
you know better!
What happened to all
that showing off, huh?
You put my granddaughter's
life in danger!
I understand you just wanted
Jasmine to get better.
But it was a huge mistake, Marj,
to decide everything
on your own.
You're not the only one
who wants the best for Jasmine.
We do, too.
Especially Paolo.
You didn't just disregard
your husband with what you did.
You also disrespected us.
I'm sorry I didn't inform
everyone properly.
But I never regretted trying.
I wanted to exhaust every option
for Jasmine.
Marj, just apologize.
You already admitted
your mistake.
Being proud right now
won't help.
Why?
If your child were sick,
wouldn't you do the same thing
I did?
Be honest.
No pretending.
Honestly?
If Ashley were in
Jasmine's position,
I would never risk her safety.
For what?
An experimental treatment
with no guarantee?
What are you trying to say?
That I harmed my own child?
- Yes. Why?
- Thea!
That's enough!
Why? It's the truth.
You risked Jasmine's life.
If anything bad had
happened to her,
you would be the only one
to blame!
Fine. Blame everything on me.
But deep inside, I know I did
the right thing!
That's enough!
Come with me.
Come with me!
Don't grab me like that!
I'm really sorry about
what happened in Hong Kong.
There must be other
treatment options.
This isn't the end, okay?
I can still feel it, Ash.
All those injections
they kept giving me.
The burning feeling
from the medicine.
I tried to endure it
as long as I could.
Because I felt so sorry for Mom.
I could see how badly she wanted
the treatment to work.
But in the end...
I was the one who gave up.
I failed my mom.
I should've been stronger.
I should've fought harder.
Jas...
So they wouldn't blame Mom.
So they wouldn't be angry
at her anymore.
It's okay to cry, Jas.
Just not too much.
Stress is bad for your body,
right?
So little by little...
just relax, okay?
I'm tired, Ash.
I just want this to end.
I just want to get better.
You will.
You're going to be okay.
Don't lose hope.
Just keep fighting, all right?
So many of us are
rooting for you.
Even Xander.
Did you know he visited
while you were gone?
He kept asking how you were.
Really?
What did he say?
What did he do?
Did you guys talk?
Yes, cuz.
He was really worried about you.
Turns out he's not
a total bad boy.
He's actually nice to talk to.
Good listener, too.
And caring...
especially toward you.
Wow.
I was only gone in Hong Kong,
and suddenly the wind
had changed.
Weren't you the one who didn't
like him before?
I'm not on team bad boy
or team good boy.
I'm on team
Jas-deserves-happiness.
So if Xander is what makes
you happy, I'll support it.
Let go of me!
What are you doing? Let go!
Let go!
After you let your whole
family gang up on me,
now you want to talk in private?
Don't make this about me!
Why not?
Ever since you opposed
Jasmine's treatment,
isn't that exactly
how you made me feel?
And you know why I opposed it!
Do you think anyone here
feels worse than I do?
No one, Paolo.
No one is angrier at me
than I am at myself.
Because our daughter's
treatment didn't work!
Yeah, you're right.
You should be mad at yourself.
You only exhausted Jasmine
because of what you did.
You weakened her body even more.
For what?
So you could say you did
something as a mother?
How dare you!
How dare you say that to me
after everything
I've been through
since Jasmine was a baby!
That's always what you say,
right?
That you're the only one
who struggled raising her.
That I never helped.
That you're the only one
who has the right to our child.
who understands her!
For what, huh?
The truth is,
you're the one making our
daughter's condition worse.
It's like you're the one
killing her.
Just like how you killed
our relationship!
I made all those decisions
because I love our daughter
so much.
Paolo, I was desperate
to save our child!
So don't you ever say I did
all this to Jasmine
because I'm careless!
What about you?
You always want things your way!
You only care about what
you think is important
instead of listening to
what she actually needs!
That's not true!
Really?
Can you control
Jasmine's condition?
Can you control the exact time
she needs her medicine?
Can you comfort her
when she cries in pain?
Can you calm her breathing
when she wakes up scared
in the middle of the night?
You can't!
Because you're not there!
You shouldn't have fought
with Marj like that.
So you're really defending Marj?
Edward, I'm your wife.
You should be taking my side.
You know what
she's going through.
Their child is sick.
She doesn't need more
stress from you people.
Marj disrespected your family!
And you're just okay with that?
Then again...
you can't even stand up for me.
What more your own family?
No wonder you're such a loser
in this family!
You shut up!
While our daughter is suffering,
you're busy with meetings.
With your damn responsibilities
at Torrecampo Realty!
The same company that's keeping
her alive!
All her medicine,
all her hospital bills!
Every single thing she needs
comes from that company
you hate so much!
Don't act like you're the only
one sacrificing here, Marj!
Don't paint me as the villain
in your story!
You were the one who shut me off
in the first place!
You make decisions on your own!
You never listen to me!
You decide everything,
but never include me
as your husband.
As Jasmine's father!
This has nothing to do
with my family or me.
This is about how you acted
earlier!
Go ahead!
Go on, hurt me!
Just because of Marj,
you're really going to hurt me?
Go ahead.
Do it!
Hit me!
So I can finally think
that I married the wrong man!
Yes, you became a mother.
But you failed as a wife.
So yes, I blame you.
Because while Jasmine's health
keeps getting worse,
our relationship is slowly
falling apart
because of everything
you've done.
Marj, have some tea first.
It's a little hot,
but it'll help calm you down.
I'm so exhausted, Manang.
I try to stay strong...
but sometimes I don't even know
if I'm still doing
the right thing.
You know, sometimes
we make decisions
when we're already desperate.
Especially when we feel like
we don't have any other choice.
I made a huge mistake myself
once.
I trusted something I thought
would solve my problem.
But it didn't.
I just ended up
hoping for nothing.
So now...
the only thing I can do
is get back up and move forward.
So, Ma'am...
I hope you can do the same.
Jasmine gets her strength
from you.
From you and Sir Paolo.
When the two of you are
not getting along,
it becomes even harder
for your daughter
to keep fighting every day.
So I hope...
I really hope you and your
husband can make peace.
Don't paint me as the villain
in your story!
You were the one who shut me off
in the first place!
You make decisions on your own!
You never listen to me!
You decide everything,
but you never include me
as your husband.
As Jasmine's father!
Jasmine gets her strength
from you.
From you and Sir Paolo.
When the two of you are
not getting along,
it'll be even harder
for your daughter
to keep fighting every day.
So I hope...
I hope you and your husband
can make peace.
Pao?
Love.
Let's not talk right now.
What are you doing?
Love?
I'll sleep in the guest room
for now.
What?
Please, can we talk, Paolo?
I can't talk right now.
Love...
Love.
What's this for?
Why are you giving me money?
I want you to be my eyes
and ears in this house.
Spy on Marj.
I want to know her every move.
And do everything you can
to make sure she and Paolo
never reconcile.
You know what's funny?
They can't even fix
their own family.
How are they supposed
to run a company?
Shut your foul mouth!
Paolo!
Paolo, I know you're
going through a lot.
You don't have to face
everything alone.
I'm here.
At least you're here for me.