Hi, Marj!
I didn't even get to hug you
last night because...
Paolo wouldn't let you go.
Because he feels guilty.
That he wasn't here when
we delivered the baby.
You probably think I told
some sob story?
Why would I do that?
Marj's already vulnerable
as it is.
Thea, she doesn't need
to know that.
Let's not ruin both our lives.
Just stay strong, baby,
I love you.
Do you still have feelings
for Marj?
What kind of question
is that, Mom?
I already have Thea.
You didn't answer my question.
Why don't you just focus
on Thea?
You don't even realize how lucky
you are to have her.
Paolo avoids me even at work.
You have Edward, though.
He's still a Torrecampo.
But he's not the golden boy.
It just annoys me
that I met Paolo too late.
Right when he was already taken.
It seems...
It seems spoiled.
My suspicions are right.
You and Edward
are having a baby?
This baby isn't Edward's.
If I'm eight weeks pregnant,
then this baby is Paolo's.
Hon?
I've been trying to call you
for a while.
I think your phone was off,
I couldn't reach you.
Sorry, Hon, I had to work
overtime.
No, I called your office
earlier.
They said that after you
went out for lunch,
you never came back.
Oh, we had an open house.
Tons of prospective buyers,
that's why I stayed out so long.
And there was no signal there,
so I didn't get your calls.
Wait.
What is this?
An interrogation?
I've been working all day,
and this is what I come home to?
Hey, Hon, hey, hey.
No, no, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Hon, I know I'm asking a lot
of questions.
I'm just worried about you.
What if something happened?
That's all.
Hon, don't be mad at me, okay?
You're the most beautiful baby
in the whole world.
Daddy loves you so, so much.
I will never let anything happen
to you.
And I won't let anyone hurt you.
Because if someone does,
they're dead.
Hey, Love.
There's a line.
I'll be the first one throwing
hands if anyone hurts our baby.
You better take after your mom.
Brave.
Come here.
You know, I think...
our baby really takes after you.
Brave,
smart,
healthy.
Maybe even good at sales talk?
Then she takes after both of us.
There you go.
Love?
Is it okay if...
I don't go back to work
after my maternity leave?
I want to stay home for now
and take care of Jasmine.
Of course.
And Thea's been handling your
accounts really well anyway.
Why?
What's wrong?
Tell me.
I'm thankful Thea took over
my listings.
And I'm grateful she was there
when I was bleeding.
But honestly...
I want to trust her completely.
I thought you two were already
friends?
Love, yeah, I'm happy
when she's around.
She makes me laugh.
But...
I can't forget
what she did to me before.
Okay.
So...
what would you like me to do?
You don't want to give her
your listings anymore?
I just want to be careful.
I know she's nice
when she's in front of me.
I just don't know what
she's like behind my back.
So if it's okay,
maybe just give them to Hannah
instead, Love.
Okay.
I understand.
I'll take care of it.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
You're really good at
putting her to sleep.
Thanks.
Wait.
We need to talk ASAP.
It's very important.
Wow.
Those drawings are beautiful.
Let me see, Sweetheart.
Is this your assignment?
It's for Baby Jasmine.
I'm going to put it in her crib
so she'll be happy.
I'm sure she'll love that
when she sees it.
I hope my sister likes
what I made, too.
Oh, I'm sure she will.
She loves Baby Jasmine.
Of course.
She loves her so much.
Pong and I are leaving.
Wait, wait, why?
Hold on, why'd you stop?
You were still drawing.
Why, Sweetheart? What's wrong?
What if my sister gives all
her love to Baby Jasmine?
There won't be any left for me.
- Oh no.
- It'll all run out.
That's not going to happen,
Jobert.
You know, your sister,
has the biggest heart.
She has more than enough love
to give.
Plenty for you.
Plenty for the baby.
And..
she will never run out of love
for you.
Really?
That's true.
Okay, I'll go back to drawing.
- All right.
- I'll now focus.
- Focus, all right?
- I will.
Let's put this away.
- Hey!
- Oh my gosh!
What's that?
What are you doing?
Nothing, Yolly just has such
a wild imagination.
Yeah, Yolly.
We're nice people, right?
Him? Oscar? Nice?
I doubt.
You better be careful.
I'm warning you.
He's just like Sir Paolo.
Smooth with the ladies.
Just ignore her, well,
it's because...
What?
Nothing, I'm leaving.
Hey, hey, where are you going?
Stay here.
- Okay, Yolly.
- Work's here.
I'll go wash the dishes.
Marj, don't forget
what I taught you, okay?
Just gently pat her back,
and Jasmine will burp.
Okay, Mom.
My problem is her diaper rash.
Oh my, Marj.
Good thing you reminded me.
I bought some coconut oil.
It's from Quezon.
I got it at the market.
Rub that on her
before you put the diaper on.
So she won't get chafed,
poor baby.
Absolutely not!
I bought diaper cream
for her rash.
That's what we're using.
That stuff's too expensive.
This is way cheaper.
It's not like money's a problem
in this house.
Just because it's expensive
doesn't mean it works.
People have been using this
for hundreds of years.
Exactly, that's outdated.
Things are different now.
Mom, they're both fine
for Jasmine.
Both are okay.
I swear.
So fussy.
Excuse me?
Fussy?
I'm just being a mom.
If you're used to being
careless with your kids,
don't get mad at mothers
who actually do things right.
Oh, really?
Are you saying
I was a careless mother?
Well, who has a kid she couldn't
even get along with,
so that child ended up
leaving her?
Mom!
Please, let's not fight, Mom.
We all just want what's best
for Jasmine, we all love her.
So please, can't we just
get along?
Good thing you were able
to drop by.
Mom's been waiting for you
for a long time.
But when you finally came,
she wasn't home.
No.
I just made sure dad
wasn't around.
And...
Marj, I really came here
for you and Baby Jasmine.
Thank you.
We want you to be Jasmine's
godfather at the christening,
okay?
What?
Really?
Yes.
That would be a blessing.
I wouldn't say no to that.
There's no one more deserving.
You're Jasmine's dad's brother.
You're like a father to her,
too.
How are you?
How are things
with you and Thea?
Is there a problem?
Thea?
I don't know.
She's acting differently.
What do you mean?
When she came home,
I could tell something
was wrong,
but she said she was fine.
Just tired.
But I know her,
I know when Thea's...
forcing a smile.
And...
I don't want to think she's
hiding something from me.
Excuse me, Sir.
Miss Thea says
she needs to talk to you.
Tell her I'm working on
something very important.
I don't have time to talk
to her.
Okay, Sir, sorry.
Thank you.
Miss Thea.
Sir Paolo's really busy.
- Sir.
- What the...
Didn't I tell you I needed
to talk to you?
Sir, I'm sorry, she insisted.
It's okay, Gemma, you can go,
thank you.
Why aren't you answering
my messages?
I can't even call you.
Obviously, I don't want to talk
to you.
What part of that was unclear?
didn't you get it?
Maybe she's going through
something.
Maybe she just doesn't
want you to worry.
I don't know.
You know, Edward, I don't really
know Thea that well.
We only just recently started
getting along.
I'm still figuring out
our friendship.
But...
I'll say this.
We, women, sometimes don't admit
we're hurting...
because we don't want the man
we love to worry.
And sometimes we don't
want you thinking...
we're weak.
You can't push me away.
Not now.
We only had sex once,
and you're already attached?
Paolo, that's not my issue.
Then what?
I'm pregnant.
And you're the father.
And sometimes, even if I don't
want to admit it,
we're just moody.
So don't worry.
Whatever Thea's going through,
I'm sure she'll tell you
eventually.
I hope so.
I hope she doesn't have
a problem.
I hope...
she's not hiding anything
from me.
You think this is the first time
a woman claimed she's pregnant,
and I'm the father?
I'm eight weeks pregnant.
And you're the only one
I slept with eight weeks ago.
Edward and I
only recently started sleeping
together again.
Paolo, this is yours!
How can you be pregnant?
We only had sex once.
Wow.
Sorry, okay?
So should it take three times
before a woman gets pregnant?
Oh my God.
Baby, sorry.
Maybe you should go back
to your dad's private part.
Because apparently once
isn't enough to...
That's enough!
Someone might hear you!
Why won't you believe me?
Fine.
If you're really telling
the truth,
I want proof.
We're getting a paternity test.
Fine!
You think I'm lying?
You want to come with me
to the doctor?
So we can finally settle this.
Love!
Hi.
Have you eaten?
I'll fix you a plate.
Love, later.
Let's just stay here for now,
this day was just...
exhausting.
I just want to be here
with you and Baby Jasmine.
So I can forget about
the stress...
and everything on my mind.
Love,
I'm sorry if...
I've been neglecting you
these past few months.
I want you to be okay.
I'm willing to do anything
to make you feel better.
Now that I've got
my strength back...
let me make it up to you, okay?
It was nothing.
It was just a moment
of temptation.
It doesn't mean anything.
And it can't ever happen again.
No one knows.
I'm pregnant.
And you're the father.
Sorry, Love.
I'm just tired, okay?
Maybe next time?
Why?
Is something wrong?
Are you having problems at work?
There is a big...
problem.
But, Love,
don't think about it, okay?
I'll handle it.
Don't worry.
I'll fix this.
Weng, after you wash
and sterilize
Jasmine's baby bottles,
just put them back
in the nursery, okay?
Yes, Ma'am Marj.
- Thank you.
- I'll head out now, Ma'am.
So how's the new mommy?
- Hi.
- Hello.
What are you doing here?
Oh, Mom Regina asked me
to help her...
plan her birthday charity event.
But our meeting's still later.
I just came early because
I wanted to catch up with you.
Me?
Nothing new, same as always.
The doctor said Jasmine
gained weight.
- Good.
- And Paolo's...
fine, too.
That sounded a little forced.
Are you sure you guys are okay?
I can feel that my husband
has a problem.
Even if he's not telling me,
I'm determined to find out
what it is.
Of course, I want to help him.
Be there for him.
Back when I was the one
struggling, he supported me.
So now, I want to do the same
for him.
I'll do whatever it takes
to make his problem go away.
You can't just make his problem
disappear that easily.
What?
What do you mean?
Do you know something
about his problem?
Well, isn't Paolo
under pressure?
You know trying to win
back the...
accounts he lost at the company.
So that's probably it,
I just think...
that kind of problem doesn't go
away that easily.
I still have a client meeting.
It might take a while,
maybe 30 minutes.
Just come back for me.
Thirty minutes, Sir?
I'll just wait for you.
No, just go ahead.
I'll call you when I'm ready
to be picked up.
Yes, Sir.
Paolo!
What is this very important
thing you needed to tell me?
Why did we even have to meet?
I'm just excited for you to see
the lab test results.
It's still sealed.
I haven't looked inside.
I wanted us to see the findings
together.
Just give it to me!
Let's end this nonsense
once and for all.
See?
I'm telling the truth, Paolo.
Congratulations.
You're going to be Daddy Paolo.
And we're going to have a baby.
No, no, no.
No, this can't be happening.
If Marj finds out about this,
it will destroy her.
I promised her I would never
be like her dad or her ex.
So what are you saying?
You're going to deny this baby
I'm carrying?
You're not going to step up?
You're not going to acknowledge
my child?
I love Marj.
Oh, come on!
This was one huge mistake.
One I completely regret.
And I'm not about to add to the
damage I've already done...
to my wife.
Oh? What about our baby?
What, you're just going to walk
away from us?
Just like that?
I'll support the child, okay?
Just...
Just stay away from me.
And stop bothering me.
As for Edward,
you should leave him before
your belly starts showing.
And resign from Torrecampo, too.
What?
You got me pregnant,
and now you want me
to lose my job, too?
That's not happening.
You don't get to just
throw us away, Paolo.
My child has rights.
We're not leaving
just because you want us to!
Whether you like it or not,
the baby I'm carrying
is a Torrecampo.
So you're going
to take responsibility.
And you're going to acknowledge
this child.
Yes, son?
- Problem?
- Sorry,
but they won't be able
to push me aside.
I'll destroy them first before
they try to control me.
Thea's pregnant.
Edward isn't the father.
I am.
I just happen to be attending
a Torrecampo charity event
tonight.
That's where I'll expose
everything...
that happened between Paolo
and me.
That he's the father...
of my baby.
His wife and his family
will spit him out.
But how can I do that if you're
not being honest with me?
I was planning to tell you.
The truth is...
I'm pregnant.
And he's the father.
Because of what you did,
you've only made our sin worse.
It will ruin our family!