You're different from all
the women I've ever met.
You men are all the same.
Just because she's the help
doesn't mean you get
to treat her like that.
Fine. Go ahead, be the hero,
Marj.
I'll just keep going
after your husband.
Hello?
Let's take a raincheck.
What?
I'm with Marj.
You need all the help
you can get.
Why don't you ask Evelyn
and Jobert to come back here?
Thanks dad.
This really helps me a lot.
Hello!
It's easier to move
when you don't have that much
stuff, right?
Oscar, take their things
to the guest room.
The one near the laundry area.
Maybe it's better
if we don't force ourselves
to stay here.
We'll just leave, Marj.
Paolo, just let them go.
Let them do whatever they want.
Mom, please stop.
What's going on here?
Evelyn, why are you leaving?
Regina...
What did you do?
Did you tell them to leave?
No, I was just welcoming them.
Maybe they realized
they're not comfortable
with the setup.
I even told Evelyn they
could stay near the laundry area
so she'd feel more at home.
She's the one who decided
to leave.
I didn't tell her to go.
Well, they're not leaving.
And they're definitely
not staying
next to the laundry area.
They're staying in the proper
guest rooms.
But Greg, those are
for special guests.
Exactly.
They're Marj's family,
so they're special guests here.
Marj and I already agreed
on this.
And as the head of the family,
I want everyone to feel welcome.
From now on, I don't want
to hear any more insults
or disrespect toward them.
Is that clear?
Yes, Sir.
Marj, go on.
Okay.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
- Let's head to the guest room.
- Oscar, take their things back.
- Hello, Yolly.
- Let's go.
Thank you.
We're not done yet, Evelyn.
Sis, I'm scared.
Mom, bro.
Mom, just bear with them.
You're right, Marj.
Let's just bear with them.
So they won't have anything bad
to say about us
especially about you.
Mom, thank you.
Honestly, If I didn't
feel sorry for you,
with everything
you're going through,
we wouldn't insist on staying
in this house.
Your mother in law really
makes us feel
like we don't belong here.
Mom, thank you so much
for being here.
Now that you're beside me,
I know I can handle everything.
Thank you for coming with me
earlier
and standing up for Mom
and Jobert.
Can we get some rest now?
I've got an early
meeting tomorrow.
All right, let's go to the room.
But give me a kiss first.
Sorry!
I was texting.
Oh my gosh, I almost fell...
By the way, Paolo...
your client was waiting
for you at the hotel earlier.
You had a client meeting today?
Yes.
He canceled last minute.
The client was pretty upset,
he was expecting that Paolo
will be there.
All the client's effort
went to waste.
But you said you were
going to the gym.
Yeah...
I forgot I had a client meeting.
I already apologized via text.
I only remembered when
we were on the way.
But I chose to go with you
to pick up your family.
Because I know that's more
important to you.
Paolo, you better better
make it up to that client.
If they get mad, that's on you.
Evelyn...
What are you doing here?
Someone might see you!
Can you just leave?
I'm not leaving until we talk.
You've been avoiding me
for weeks.
What do you really want?
Why are you insisting
we stay here?
What are you doing?
I just want to be with you.
You keep avoiding me.
I've tried talking to you
so many times.
But there's no chance at all.
This was the only way
I could see you everyday,
where you can't avoid me.
Is that how you see me?
You think I'd agree to be
your mistress
under the same roof
as your wife?
Weren't you supposed to stay
overnight
with Lalaine and your friends?
No, I didn't go.
I worked overtime to fix
the company's problems.
You know things are a mess
right now, right?
Really?
Or are you fixing
the mess Paolo made?
You know, Thea...
sometimes I don't understand
you.
You spend more time helping
Paolo fix his problems
than being with this family.
You're forgetting
your responsibilities here.
With me as your husband.
Sometimes it feels like you'd
rather be with Paolo than me.
Oh please, Edward.
Don't tell me you're jealous
of your own brother.
What is all this to you, Greg?
A game?
This isn't a game.
I like you, Evelyn.
And stop pretending
you don't feel anything for me.
Please, just stop!
Don't drag me into your mess.
I'm here because of Jasmine.
Because my grandchild
and my child needs me.
If you still have any
respect for me, please...
stay away from me.
Please!
I'm only doing this to make us
look good in Dad's eyes.
I have no choice but help Paolo.
If the company recovers,
we all benefit, right?
Why are you sure Paolo's
going to succeed?
Of course.
I believe in him.
Wow, you really admire him.
I wish I could feel
that from you sometimes.
That you actually
believe in me.
Because in case you forgot...
I'm your husband.
Not him.
Drama!
You guys are actually
fun to watch.
Looks like you're really
enjoying yourselves,
and it's just a simple
breakfast.
Feels like a whole feast
for you.
We're just appreciating
the blessings, Ma.
Well, you've got a point.
I mean, if you suddenly
moved into a nicer place,
you'd probably be thanking
the Lord too, right?
But I'm really happy you
adjusted quickly here.
Regina, please...
Just let them eat in peace.
Anyway dad, I'm holding
an open house party tomorrow
at Menagerie.
It's to attract more potential
buyers for the units.
Love, can I come with you?
I can call some of
my former clients.
I'm sure they'd be interested.
They might want to get a unit.
Love there's no need.
Thea and I can handle it.
Paolo, please, let me do this.
So we can reconnect again.
I just feel like you're slowly
drifting away from me.
Marj, just stay here.
Don't leave Jasmine.
She needs you here
more than that party.
Going to that event wouldn't
make me a bad mom.
Don't be so defensive.
I'm just concerned
about Jasmine.
Then why don't you focus
your concern
on your own child and husband?
Aren't you the one who's always
away from home?
Thea, that's enough!
You have to stop!
Even you, Edward?
Why are you siding with Marj
instead of me?
Stop it!
We have guests here.
At least let me keep a little
dignity in front of Evelyn.
Please!
How many times do
I have to tell you?
Stop attacking Marj!
You're just looking
for trouble.
You're trying to create cracks,
so we get exposed!
But Paolo, I can't help it.
I'm upset.
It's been so long
since we made love.
You always leave me hanging.
Can you stop, Thea?
When we started this,
I told you, no demands,
no drama.
So can you get it together?
Fine.
I'm not demanding anything.
It's just a request, Paolo.
Don't bring Marj along,
so we can be together.
That's not possible.
You saw how determined she
is in front of Dad, right?
If I stop her,
she'll get suspicious.
We'll lose our chance even more.
Mom, look.
- Does this look okay?
- Wow!
- It's beautiful!
- It looks good, Marj!
It suits you well.
I just want Paolo
to notice me, Mom.
I want what we had before.
When we were happy...
getting along,
helping each other,
giving to each other.
It feels like he's still distant
from me.
Our relationship still
isn't normal.
It's actually a good thing
he allowed me
to come with him today.
You know, Marj...
maybe he really does want
to fix your relationship.
Maybe you should go too.
Your sister in law might try
to ruin your image there.
You know, Marj...
something is off with her.
Don't worry, Mom.
I'll do everything I can
to fix things with Paolo.
Jasmine really misses
how we used to be.
She's hoping her dad
will be okay again.
Sis...
Don't worry about Jasmine.
Have fun at the party.
I will take care of her.
Paolo!
What are you doing here?
Marj might see you,
she'll get suspicious.
Relax.
Your wife took Jasmine
for a check up.
They won't be back for a while.
So...
we've got time for a little
afternoon delight.
You're so naughty.
Admit it...
You like the thrill.
Yeah.
Hush, keep it down.
Come on, this place is huge.
No one's going to hear us.
Oh my God!
Oh my goodness!
Seriously?
Sir Paolo, I'm sorry,
I didn't know you were here.
I thought the room was empty.
- Sorry.
- Next time, knock!
Don't just walk in like that!
I'm sorry, Sir.
It won't happen again.
What are you waiting for?
Get out!
I was just going to
take the trash, sir.
No, don't!
Don't touch that!
Why? I'm just taking
the trash...
No, no, it's barely full.
Just take it out later, okay?
Go on, get out.
I've got a lot to do.
Go on.
Yes, Sir.
Sorry again, Sir.
All right.
I'm sorry, Sir.
Good thing we didn't get caught.
So can you leave now?
No way.
You've left me hanging way
too many times already.
Let's just be quick, okay?
Nurse, I don't want that.
It's bitter, I'm going
to throw up if I take that.
But Jas, you need to take it.
To make you feel better.
It just makes me feel worse.
Excuse me.
Baby Jasmine, you need
to take your medicine.
Uncle, I can't...
It's really bitter.
I know how to swallow medicine
easily.
My sister taught me how to take
medicine like this.
This is what you have to do.
You have to pinch your nose,
like this.
Then swallow it.
That's it. Just hang in there,
Baby Jasmine.
You can do it.
You have to bear it.
Nurse, she's ready
to take her medicine.
Pinch your nose.
Good job, Baby Jasmine!
You did it!
See? She did it!
You're such a good teacher,
Uncle.
I did it because of you.
Baby Jasmine,
once you get better,
Uncle Jobert will treat you,
okay?
I'm a big boy now,
I've got a job.
I can treat you!
I'll get better
as fast as I can.
So we can hang out.
We'll eat ice cream,
fried chicken...
Ice cream!
- I like that!
- Let's go out, okay, Uncle?
Chocolate ice cream...
so good!
- Take me with you too!
- Ashley can come!
Good job!
Thanks, uncle.
Go ahead and eat, Pong,
it's good!
- You don't want it?
- Hi!
You're Jasmine's Uncle, right?
Yeah.
I'm Jobert, Jasmine's uncle.
I'm Ashley.
Jasmine's cousin,
and her best friend.
It's so nice to finally
meet you.
She always talks about you.
If you're Jasmine's friend,
then we're friends too.
Yes. Even if we just met,
we both care about her.
You're Pong's friend too...
Wait!
I don't want to!
- He's nice!
- Mommy, no, wait!
Mommy, wait!
-You're scaring her, aren't you?
-Mommy, no.
He's not hurting me!
I just got surprised
by the turtle.
Stay away from her!
Mom, please, stop!
You two shouldn't be together!
You might catch his craziness!
What is going here?
Sis...
Why are you picking
on my brother?
Who gave you the right to yell
at my brother?
Hold on, Marj.
Calm down.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I was just asking why Ashley
and Jobert were together.
No.
She was yelling at me earlier!
You told me to stay away!
You were yelling at me!
Jobert, just calm down, okay?
Jobert, I'm not mad.
I just naturally
have a loud voice.
It's not my fault
you misunderstood
and you're being overly
sensitive.
You can even ask Ashley.
Thea, I know you.
And I know my brother,
he doesn't lie.
If you've got a problem with me,
then face me.
Take it out on me.
Goodness!
But the moment I see you
mistreating my brother again,
you'll be dealing with me.
Jobert, let's go.
And you...
I don't want to see you
talking to that idiot,
do you understand?
Stay away from that family.
Yes, Mom.
Yes, Ma'am.
Ma'am Marj really went off
on Ma'am Thea.
So that's how she is...
when it comes to her brother,
she turns into a tiger.
I knew it.
They haven't even been
here that long,
and Marj's family is already
creating trouble.
I won't allow them to destroy
the peace in my household.
I want you to keep an eye
on Evelyn and Jobert.
And if you see them doing
anything wrong,
report it to me immediately.
Do we understand each other?
Ma'am, are you asking me
to spy on them?
Do you have a problem with that?
No, Ma'am.
All right, yes, Ma'am.
We need to find something
against them a mistake.
So Greg will be forced
to kick them out.
Hi, Marj.
To be fair, you look
presentable tonight.
But the question is...
can you keep top socially?
Or you have gotten rusty staying
at home or the hospital.
You know, no matter how long
I've been out of the scene,
I'll never forget my manners.
It's tough when all you
have is beauty but no class.
I guess that's what happens
when you're full of envy.
No matter how expensive
your outfit is,
your attitude
still makes you look...
cheap.
I don't see anything wrong
with what I'm doing, Evelyn.
You've spent your whole
life enduring a husband
who gave you nothing
but pain and heartbreak.
I just want you to feel
that you deserve more.
Oh, no...
Ma'am Evelyn is doing
something wrong.