I've decided
who Paradiso Escaño's
exclusive realty partner will be
the Torrecampo Realty.
Your shoulder's dislocated.
Must've gotten hit earlier.
Let's get a drink,
it'll numb the pain.
I just want
to lose control right now.
Edward, why don't you just give
your brother
the benefit of the doubt.
and focus on how you're going
to court
Marj when they get back?
You don't owe me anything.
I'll forget what happened
between us.
Just like you want.
Mom's going out for a bit, okay?
But I'll be back soon.
Where did my mom go?
If your sister calls,
don't say anything, alright?
Beats me, when I got here,
she was already gone.
Even Jobert stayed up all night
waiting for her!
Thank you, Miss Rona.
If you see Mom,
please call or text me
right away.
Okay, thanks so much.
I already reported to the police
that Auntie Evelyn is missing.
Do you have any idea
where she might've gone?
I can't think of anywhere
right now.
Mom!
I'm going crazy worrying about
what happened to you.
Where have you been?
And I told you
not to leave Jobert alone.
Mom, I told you to watch Jobert.
Dear, I just couldn't
help myself
I had to talk to him.
Who?
Mom, I don't understand.
Who are you talking about?
Ah, Marj,
my child.
What is he doing here?
Your dad and I talked, Marj.
We decided
to give our relationship
another chance.
Mom!
Are you falling for it again?
Marj, it's not like that.
Your father has changed.
Mom! That's the same old story!
He always pretends he's changed,
but we all know how this ends!
Marj, please listen first.
I almost got mugged last night.
My phone even got destroyed.
If it weren't for your dad,
who knows what would've
happened to me.
Dear, I promised your mom
I'd be better.
I'll make it up to her
and to you and Jobert.
Please, give me one more chance
to prove I can be
your father again.
- Please, my child.
- Please, sweetheart.
He's just gonna fool you again.
Mom, use your head for once!
Stop letting your emotions
run everything!
Marj.
Don't raise your voice
at your mother like that.
Don't tell me what to do!
You lost that right after
what you did to us!
Noise.
- Noise! Noise! Noise!
- Marj!
Mom!
So loud!
Jobert. wait.
Please just leave!
Stop bothering us!
Enough! Stop messing
with my mom's head!
We don't need you!
Get out!
So loud!
- Lito!
- Mom!
Mom!
Noise!
Manang, how is he?
He's still upset...
because Sir Greg sent you
to Batangas instead of him.
Bro, how'd your...
meeting with Mr. Fuentes go?
How is it?
Did you close the deal?
I was calling you last night.
You didn't answer.
Sorry, I didn't hear it.
Marj was drunk
when I talked to her.
And I heard you.
You offered to take her
to her room.
I couldn't just
leave her there, could I?
And then what?
What do you mean, "then what"?
You undressed her?
You laid her down?
You kissed her?
Dude...
your mind's filthy.
When did you start
thinking that way?
Paolo, I know you.
I know how you are with women.
Just tell me the truth.
Did something happen
between you and Marj?
Don't try
to say anything, Paolo.
Just don't.
You told me
you didn't like her!
You said I should go for her!
I was about to tell Marj
I liked her!
Then what?
What did you do?
You had to try her out first
before handing her over to me?
Good job, Paolo.
Glad I trusted my gut
and sent you to Batangas.
Actually, Dad, you should be
congratulating Marj.
If it weren't for her,
we wouldn't have closed
the deal.
I was wrong about her.
I thought she'd just be trouble.
But now, I can see
she has a great potentials.
Mr. Escaño said the same thing.
He believes in her.
She's not just pretty,
smart and, capable.
She's also kind.
Yes, Marj's kind.
And too trusting.
That's why people
take advantage of her.
Like who?
Please have mercy on us
- for our child.
- Mom!
For our kids' sake, Lito.
We have nowhere else to go.
Please have mercy on us, Lito.
I don't need them!
Ever since your father
and I separated,
I became weak, sweetheart.
Please forgive me.
Sis?
Are you okay?
I don't understand.
I really don't understand
my mom.
Instead of helping me
build a life,
she brings trouble back
into this house.
I already told her
not to take him back.
But what can we do?
Your mom's just really weak.
How many times do I have
to tell her that?
It's exhausting.
I'm the one holding
everything together.
Me, always me.
Everyone depends on me,
and I'm not made of stone.
I get tired, too.
I know.
Nothing about this is easy.
Hey, can we talk
about something else?
Anything but Marj,
okay? Please?
It's rare that I get impressed.
My standards are high.
But Marj?
She's approved.
That's the kind of woman
you should be dating, son.
You two will make a great pair.
Excuse me.
This is for Ms. Marj Castillo.
Ah, that's sweet!
Who's it from?
What happened between us
wasn't nothing to me.
I know you're going through
something right now.
and I hope everything works out.
I just want you to know that
I'm thinking of you.
I'm just here.
Jobert.
Why is my little brother
so quiet?
Sorry, Sis.
What for?
You and Mom are fighting.
I don't know how to fix it.
I'm sorry, Jobert.
Sorry, you're stuck
between Mom and me.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to fight
with her either.
But if I don't say anything,
she'll be the one who gets hurt
in the end.
Jobert, don't worry
about it, okay?
What matters is
I love you.
Okay?
I love you too, Sis.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Mom, wait.
Don't tell me you're leaving.
I am, Marj.
I want to give your father
another chance.
I want this family
to be whole again.
If you can't accept him,
then Jobert and I will leave
this house.
Mom, are you serious?
Yes.
Because I feel like
I have no freedom here.
No right to be happy.
No right to love.
Mom, what did I do wrong?
All I did was care!
If there's anyone here who's
been unhappy her whole life,
it's me!
I never got to enjoy my youth.
I sacrificed everything for you,
and now I'm the bad one?
If you can't live without Dad,
then leave!
But don't take my brother!
Jobert is your father's son.
He's our son.
I'm taking Jobert!
Mom, didn't you see yesterday?
He didn't even go near Jobert!
Because you kicked him out!
Mom, come on!
Seriously! Did you forget
how he hurt Jobert?
How he said Jobert
wasn't even his kid?
Because he couldn't accept that
Jobert is different!
Mom, don't leave.
- I don't want.
- Jobert.
- I don't want, I don't want.
- Let Mom go.
- I don't want.
I don't want Mom to leave!
She chose Dad.
- Let Mom go.
- No, I don't want.
Mom...
- I don't want Mom to leave!
- If that's how she wants
to get treated,
then let her leave!
Don't take my brother!
No...
Mom...
Mom! Mom!
Jobert, stay here.
Mom!
Here, here,
just a little more.
That's it, just a bit.
Very good.
Where's Mom?
Jobert misses Mom.
I miss her.
I miss Mom, too, Jobert.
Don't worry,
she'll be back soon.
How about I buy you a turtle
keychain later?
Turtle keychain!
Jobert wants!
Just like Pong!
Pong.
Girl, thank you.
Thanks for helping me
take care of Jobert.
I'll be back right
after my presentation.
I should be here by lunchtime.
Yeah. Sis, we've got
a big problem.
Sir Greg called me. He wants me
to edit the presentation.
But it's all
on the office computer.
I can't do anything about it.
I won't be able to watch
Jobert this morning.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey, hey, sis.
Relax.
Just relax.
I'll just file for emergency
leave later.
What?
You have big time client.
That's a big account, right?
What if they give it
to someone else?
That'd be such a waste.
If only they would give it
to me, then that would be great.
Remember this place, Jobert?
Look, there's Hannah.
- Hey, Jobert.
- And there's Mikee.
Come on, sit here for now.
There you go.
There.
Oops.
Here, watch this
for a bit, okay?
While I talk to someone.
- Behave, all right?
- Girl...
it's 9 o'clock,
your client.
Oh, right.
Can you watch Jobert for me
for now?
Yes, I've got him.
Thanks.
Bye, Jobert.
Stay right here, okay?
Behave.
Here.
And this house in Tagaytay,
it has three bedrooms
and three bathrooms
with a 360 degree view,
and it is safe for kids.
You have two children, right?
That's right.
I'm glad you're considering
my kids.
Of course, Ma'am.
That's why we build good homes
for our families.
What's the total floor area
of the property?
Is everything okay?
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
My younger brother doesn't have
a babysitter today,
and I'm the only one with him.
He has autism, so I'm worried.
Anyway, the total floor area...
Ah! We don't have to do this
right now
if your brother needs you.
I understand.
I'm a single mom
with little kids,
and I'm the breadwinner, too.
Then you know how hard
it is to juggle work and family.
Of course.
It's really hard
when you have no one to share
the responsibility with.
So, let's just reschedule?
Ah, how about Wednesday
afternoon?
Yes, yes.
Thank you so much, Ma'am.
Ah, I'll go ahead now.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Jobert?
Oh my god.
Gi, did you see my brother?
No, I didn't,
I just got back.
Cindy, Cindy!
Did you see my brother?
Sorry, Marj,
I just came from a meeting.
Mikee! Did you see my brother?
it's Jobert.
No, I didn't see him.
Are you sure?
Hannah left him here earlier.
I really didn't see him.
Jobert?
- Jobert!
- I feel bad for that teenager.
It's awful,
there's so much blood.
I wonder how he is.
Jobert!
Sis!
Jobert.
My god, I thought you were
the one who got hit.
Ah, sorry.
I was trying to call you.
I saw Jobert walking alone
in the hallway.
Kind Big Bro bought me
ice cream!
Yummy!
- Look, look!
- Jobert, I told you
not to leave my desk.
I finished watching the videos.
I got bored.
Paolo, thank you.
And sorry if I scared you.
I thought he'd get less agitated
if we got some air and a snack.
And it turns out
he loves ice cream.
Oh, Jobert.
Anyone who doesn't like ice
cream isn't normal.
Well, I hope that guy is okay.
That's why, Jobert,
don't cross the street
by yourself, okay?
Okay.
Ice cream.
- Heading home now, Jobert?
- Kind Big Brother.
Thank you again for finding
Jobert earlier.
If you hadn't, something bad
could've happened.
I know he'll be fine.
Jobert's tough, right?
Jobert strong!
Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
Come on, tell me.
A lot happened today,
but for some reason,
it doesn't feel as heavy.
Thanks, by the way,
for being Jobert's
babysitter for a bit.
Kidding.
You know, sometimes
you just have to admit
to yourself that you need help.
I know you're Miss Tough Girl.
But you get tired, too, right?
You're right.
So this is what it feels like
to have someone share the load.
Someone who helps
without being asked,
given willingly
out of good intentions.
Even if it's not obvious.
- Oh.
- Sis, message.
Marj, can we talk for a moment?
I got a message from Edward.
He wants to talk.
Go, talk to him.
That's important.
Do you know what this is about?
I have an idea,
but I don't want to assume.
You sure you don't want
to go inside?
No, it's okay.
It's actually better out here.
No one can hear us.
Are you okay?
You don't look like it.
Sorry.
Is it obvious?
Is this because you
and your brother fought?
How did you know?
He didn't tell me everything.
But Paolo said you two
had a disagreement.
I'll be honest with you.
It's not just
a misunderstanding.
I'm really mad at Paolo.
He admitted to me that something
happened between you two
- in Batangas.
- What?
What?
- He told you that?
- Yes, he did.
To tell you the truth, I've...
I've felt so betrayed.
Because Paolo knows that...
I like you.
What?
Marj, I like you.
Edward, are you serious?
I am.
I like you.
That's why it hurts seeing you
fall for Paolo.
What was that?
Did he get you drunk
on purpose just to take
advantage of you?
No, no,
that's not it.
No, we both wanted it.
But it didn't mean anything.
That's exactly
what he wants you to see.
what he wants you to believe.
That it was nothing.
That you shouldn't
expect anything.
That's just how Paolo is.
He'll do whatever it takes
to make you like him.
And in the end,
he'll just leave.
He'll let go.
And you're the one who gets hurt
in the end.
That's the kind of guy he is.
But the Paolo I saw
in Batangas was different.
I got to know him better.
Marj, don't let him fool you.
He's not a good guy.
Look, he already blabbed to me
about what happened
between you two.
Who knows?
who else he'll tell?
But me...
I'm serious about you.
I'm serious about how I feel.
I'll take care of you.
I won't leave you.
I'll give you everything
you want.
I'm begging you...
leave Paolo.
Forget about him.
I don't want to see you
get hurt.
Marj, we belong together.
I just...
I hope you choose me.
What did you say to Marj?
She suddenly started avoiding me
and won't reply to my messages.
What did you tell her?
What did I say?
The truth! That she's just
another conquest to you.
Your flavor of the month.
You just have to choose one.
Either way, you win.
So which one do you want?
I didn't raise you
to be a loser.
Don't let your brother beat you.
If there's anyone
I want you to marry,
it's someone like Marj.
Why are you telling me this?
Sorry, I'm into someone else.
Marriage is serious.
That's a lifetime commitment.
Don't joke about something
like that.