How about we meet at 9:00 p.m. tomorrow in front of the Comm Arts building?
Are you into Lynn?
I don't want to cross the line, but I think you should get over her.
Why should I? I came first.
Have you ever told her that?
This might be his plan of confessing his love to you.
No, I've tried but got no vibe.
I flirted, I asked him to kiss me on the cheek.
I let him ride Chawee.
I even sang him a song in the restaurant.
If it were somebody else, they'd be all undressed and ready to bang.
Fuck...
I think Third has feelings for you.
No, I've tried but got no vibe.
He's not showing anything.
I flirted, I asked him to kiss me on the cheek.
I let him ride Chawee.
I even sang him a song in the restaurant.
If it were somebody else, they'd be all undressed and ready to bang.
I feel like I'm in a film with a major plot twist.
The scene where the main character realizes that what they've been led to believe is not true.
Every nice gesture that Khai gave me...
Everything that happened...
It was just to prove a stupid assumption.
For three years, I've repressed my feelings.
I've put up with his awful behavior.
Now I end up being hurt all by myself while he's blissfully ignorant.
I sometimes have this urge to shout out my feelings to his face.
But I don't have the guts to do it.
Instead, I come home and cry,
letting him treat me like I'm a clown, and leave when he's satisfied.
Am I worth only that much...
to him?
Where have you been?
Nowhere.
Let me repeat. Where have you been? We've been trying to call you all night.
Why didn't you pick up? Do you have any idea what time it is?
Why the fuck would you care?
What is wrong with you? Tell me so I'll know how to act.
You played with my emotions.
What the fuck are you talking about?
If you don't know any better, just leave me the fuck alone.
[Theory of Love]
[Ep. 05: Ten Things I Hate About You]
Khai, what are you doing?
Huh?
First thing in the morning?
You are a real piece of work.
I said I was cleaning my glasses.
Or I can do what you think I was doing.
Whatever.
Get out after you're done. I'm going to brush my teeth.
Don't forget to mouthwash after brushing your teeth.
You'll have fresh breath like me.
It's not like I'm going to go and kiss anyone today.
So, what was up with you last night? Will you tell me now?
Nothing.
You raised your voice to me. It's not nothing.
You also said some weird stuff.
I was drunk.
Pay no mind to the drunk.
Don't overdo it next time.
You know that you get hives when you drink a lot.
Look. They're all over the place. Let me apply some medicine.
No! I'll do it myself.
Just get out.
Okay.
Dudes, you skipped class again. Bad students.
Look who's talking.
You ditched editing class yesterday. The professor kept asking about you.
I will go eventually.
Let's talk about you, Third.
You've never skipped this class before.
It's nothing. I'm just being lazy.
Why didn't you ask Khai to come with?
Khai called me to vent how you've been acting strange lately.
I don't know what's going on between you two. But make up already.
I've already asked Khai to come here.
Hello, here I am.
How are you guys? Any hangover?
I'm a heavyweight.
No. All the girls were damn hot. My eyes were wide open.
You're right. Especially the chick Two was hitting on.
Big boobs.
You're exaggerating.
You were getting it on quite hot and heavy.
Bathroom.
Then, on your bike. Did she end up in your bedroom?
What about you? Did you take nude photos of her?
I'm moving to Two's place.
Third, why won't you tell me what's wrong with you?
I just want to move out.
I'll see you at your apartment tonight.
Hello.
[Third]
I don't know why he's mad at me.
Is it about girls?
You know how much I give to my friends and the girls.
I care about him.
But I see you being mean to him plenty of times.
I admit that.
But if he told me to stop, I'd stop.
For what?
So I won't lose him.
How can I stop liking you after you've said things like that?
Tell me.
[London, Tokyo, New York, Paris, Chicago, Los Angeles, Dallas, Beijing, Frankfurt, Hong Kong]
Third, I'm asking you for the last time. What's going on with you?
Answer me.
Third.
Are you still mad because I brought girls here?
Since Fahsai did that shit to you, I've never brought anyone here.
Isn't that enough?
I'm doing all I can.
Are you just going to be quiet?
Fine! If you don't answer me today, don't call me your friend again.
I haven't wanted to call you a friend for a while.
Did Khai and Bone join hands to dupe you?
I'd be pissed, too.
This is it.
This is why I can't stay with him any longer.
Can I stay here for a while?
Sure, you can. Make yourself at home.
Let's talk about this.
What are you going to do with Khai?
I'll back out and get over him for real.
What about us four? Will things be the same?
Don't worry.
Everything will be the same.
I just need some time.
Hang in there. I'm here for you always.
I need to go out and do some work with a senior.
If you're tired, just go to bed.
Pillows and blankets are in the cabinet.
Make yourself at home.
Thanks.
Trust me.
It's for the best...
for us both.
Hello.
This is probably the last clip of the Movie Seer page.
Today, I'm going to review a real oldie.
It's called "Crazy, Stupid, Love."
I selected this film because...
it speaks to what I'm feeling now.
I feel crazy and stupid because of love.
I spent around 15 minutes...
to tell my story through words and tears.
It's stored as a memory,
and it will be kept here forever.
[Create Post, Photo/Video, Live Video, Life Events]
[Only me]
Bone, you went to the movie with her the other day.
Did you do anything afterward?
How could I?
She didn't even show up.
No wonder you look grumpy.
You were dumped.
It's not that. I just felt bad that I didn't see the film I wanted to see.
Oh yeah?
Shit, she's here.
Don't try to fool me. I'm on to you.
It's like a scene from a movie.
This is real.
One iced espresso, please.
[Cafe Ton-Cha-Bub]
Bone, please tend the shop.
I have a fish bone stuck in my throat. I have to get it out.
Bone, I'm sorry I didn't see the film with you the other day.
Something came up, and I didn't know how to contact you.
That's fine. Something came up for me, too.
What a shame! Good films don't come by too often.
This film was from like 50 years ago.
Don't know when the next opportunity will come.
Don't worry. There are several film festivals here.
You'll get to see it at some point.
I guess.
[Chobjai Condo]
What are you doing?
I just finished "10 Things I Hate about You."
The lead listed out all the flaws of her crush to get over him.
I'm going to list Khai's.
How many have you got?
Just one.
He drives too fast.
This is nothing. Why would it make your list?
It's not nothing.
Do you know what happened when I was on Chawee for the first time?
- Third, hang on tight.
- Why?
That guy is looking for trouble.
I'm going to show him he's messing with the wrong guy.
Khai, drive slowly!
Khai!
I thought I was in "Fast and Furious."
I was having flashbacks and thinking of my parents. I thought I was going to die.
Even after I told him to stop, he wouldn't.
The first item on your list got you so worked up.
I think this is working.
Keep on doing it. I'm going to go out for a smoke.
I got the second one.
His second flaw is he gives up easily.
Come on, they have a discounted promotion today.
Just a few minutes in the queue and we'll be served.
- You can wait, right?
- Right.
I eat right on time at 12:00 p.m.
I need to eat at exactly noon. Let's go somewhere else.
No, I came all this way for this. Let's eat here, please.
You're welcome to wait here by yourself.
I'm a sharp person. Food needs to reach my mouth at 12:00 p.m. sharp.
Hey, Khai!
You're punctual only for your eating habits.
You never are when we have an appointment.
You asshole!
This gets me thinking of another thing.
The third flaw is he's not smart.
Hey.
[I...]
[like...]
[you.]
Now you know about my feelings.
- I...
- Third.
This is awesome.
Did you just come up with a way for me to make up with Nong Milk?
But I thank you.
Love you, dude.
This really gets me angry.
I worked up the courage to confess.
And he didn't get it. That's crazy.
Geez! The more I think about it, the more I get frustrated.
How could she write 10 things in that film?
[Lyn Lalita]
[Lyn Lalita updated her cover photo]
These photos are great.
Thank you.
They could be better though.
Once I get a new lens, they'll be better than this.
Are you okay?
It's nothing.
Are you having trouble with P'Phon?
I see you've changed your profile picture to plain black.
If you're upset about anything, you can talk to me.
I had a little fight with P'Phon.
But it's not a big deal.
P'Phon has been hanging out with his friends a lot.
He spends most of his time with his friends,
either watching a soccer match or playing soccer.
But never mind.
How about this?
I'll invite you to play soccer with me. So you'll be even.
Me playing soccer? You're crazy.
Why? I even came up with the title of your soccer club.
Lynn-verpool. The slogan is "kick nothing but a boyfriend."
How's that?
This is getting out of control.
But good, huh?
That's actually a good idea.
Good name.
Kick a boyfriend.
Lynn-verpool.
[UN Fre...]
[UN French movie]
[The Untouchables]
I don't remember the name.
It starts with "UN".
"Unforgiven".
No.
It's longer than that.
Or is it...
"Unforgettable"? 5 syllables.
No, Professor.
It is a French film.
"Un plus une."
No, Professor. Not this one. It doesn't sound familiar.
I think you should find out about the title and then come to see me.
I'm so sorry.
It's the one that was screened during the "Movie in the Yard" event.
It starts with "UN"...
and then h-o-m-e.
It's pronounced as...
un... home.
"Un Homme et une Femme"!
Exactly! That's the one! How do you pronounce that?
Un-homme-et-une-femme.
Do we have it?
[Cafe Ton Cha Bub]
Excuse me, have you found a film you're interested in yet?
No, I don't know what to watch.
In that case, I have one recommendation.
This is "Un Homme et une Femme."
How did you find it?
It's not commonly available.
I borrowed from a friend.
It's a shame we didn't see it the other day.
So, I thought I should have a special screening here.
[Lyn Lalita updated her cover photo.]
Shit!
[The gang from Accounting on the right is freaking cute.]
Guys, where should we go for dinner?
I can't go.
I can't either.
I don't know if it's just me.
But I feel that the four of us aren't as close as we used to be.
I have to go.
I'm going, too.
What's up with those two?
Screw them, I can go with you, just the two of us.
I can't either. I have to do some shopping. See you.
Hey!
[Great photo.]
[You look great in this photo.]
[Who took this photo?]
What the hell did you do?
What are you talking about?
This.
Did you send her this photo?
They had a little fight and you saw an opportunity to swoop in.
- You're opportunistic.
- Opportunistic?
I came first. I've known her since high school.
So?
They're dating right now!
Screw that! Whatever I do is my business.
If you have all this free time,
spend it to remind your friend to take care of his girlfriend.
You've got a good eye.
This lens is great.
It makes the model's skin shine like a diamond. It makes the background blurry.
Blurry? Like my bank account?
Come on. This is a good product. It's worth the price.
Want it?
Girls like it.
Don't hesitate. Just get it.
- Fine. One of these, please.
- Attaboy.
[Lyn Lalita updated her cover photo]
Here.
I don't want it anymore.
No?
Who will I sell it to now?
Two!
What the hell are you doing?
What is this?
What are you doing dragging me like this?
- I'm saving your life! Why are you suicidal?
- I'm not suicidal.
I threw my stuff in the water, but then I had second thoughts.
So, I'm trying to find it. Let me go!
This is none of your business.
You keep a lot of Lynn's things.
Are you enjoying this?
I'm pathetic.
I saw them having a fight, and I got a glimpse of hope.
In the end, I'm still an outsider.
I'm so stupid.
Yes, you are.
But as they say,
people who are in love...
are all stupid.
But I don't want to be anymore.
The only way...
The only way to forget about your old love...
is to find someone who loves you.
[ICON Cineconic]
Be careful. Watch out for the steps.
Have a seat.
Are you okay with these moving seats?
I'm fine.
After the movie, can I go to your place?
Of course.
I can think of his fourth flaw.
He likes to flirt around. He's a player.
I love you, Som.
Yes.
You'll break up with her soon enough. Just watch.
Then, you'll avoid her, and you'll use me as a buffer.
Do you like this?
Yes.
Another one. The fifth flaw is he causes me trouble after his breakup.
What's worst is the sixth flaw.
He never feels guilty.
Third.
Hey, are you here to see a movie?
No, I'm here to see you.
Two told me you were here.
What's up?
I want to apologize to you.
For what?
That day at the bar, you heard me and Khai. Right?
I'm sorry.
We were assholes.
I didn't think things would get this bad.
No.
I was the one with the hidden agenda.
It serves me right.
But because of me, Khai...
He didn't have to believe you,
but he did.
And he chose to treat me like shit.
Third...
Don't worry about me.
I'm trying to get over him.
Thanks to you, I could come up with Khai's biggest flaw.
That is...
He never really loves anyone.
I'm his friend,
and he plays me like a fiddle.
An asshole like him... why is he so hard to get over?
Just cry it out. I'm right here with you.
I don't know how many times I've done this.
But I end up crying because of him again.
Khai.
Where are you?
Come and help with the report now. I've already closed the shop.
Okay.
Are you okay working with Khai?
I can do it for you.
I'm fine. I'm over it.
Hi, friends.
I'm here. Sorry, I'm late.
I stopped by to get some beers to smoothen our conversation.
I forgot to tell you. Here's Nong Som.
She can help us with the report and give us ideas.
Okay?
Bone, put them in the freezer, please.
Please wait a moment. I need to do some work here.
Then, we can go home. Okay?
Good.
Som, here are my friends.
We've been close since we were freshmen. We did a short film together.
This is Bone, the no. 1 editor of our class. He's very good.
He doesn't pay attention to class because he already knows everything.
This is Two, the master of photography.
He makes his model tenfold more beautiful.
This is Third, the screenwriter.
He writes about romance and love.
He loves to imagine...
That was before.
Now, I don't believe in love anymore.
Do you ever believe in anything?
Unlike you who believes it so much that you whore around.
Third, let's just go to that table.
I'm going to find some film to use as a reference for our report.
Come on. Up.
P'Khai, don't drink too much or you'll get drunk.
Okay, I'm going to go out for a smoke for a little bit.
No smoking either.
Okay.
Good boy.
You will be rewarded for your obedience.
What kind of reward?
Do you really think he's listening to you?
After he has you, he'll dump you in no time.
Third, you asshole.
- Third, I think you're drunk. Let's go home.
- I'm not drunk.
I'm just telling the truth. Is that wrong?
Douchbag, so what if I whore around?
At least I know how to love.
Do you? Is this what you call love?
Just mind your own damn business.
- You're an asshole.
- Don't fuck with my life.
Shut up! You, asshole.
Do you call what you're doing love?
Yes, and I know whom to give it to.
It's not a shitty friend like you for sure.
Khai, talk to him nicely.
He's not in a good place right now.
Screw him! He's not my wife.
You're being too harsh.
Only when he's my bitch, then I'll talk nicely to him. Okay?
Asshole!
This is your friend. A friend who loves you.
- Do you know Third...
- Bone!
Enough!
I'm sorry.
This is my fault.
[Chobjai Condo]
Third!
Let me in, please.
Let me be alone.
Khai says shitty things.
I don't blame you for getting angry.
I'm not angry at him.
I'm angry at myself.
Tonight, I planned to be Third, Khai's good friend.
But in the end, I couldn't help myself.
I turned into Third who loves Khai.
I suck.
But here and now, you can be Third who loves Khai.
Hey, where is Third?
Do you really have to ask? You know what you did.
What do you want me to do?
Third finished his part of the PowerPoint presentation.
You add yours to his.
This is the file.
Hit "edit" here.
Yeah, yeah! I know how to do it.
He's the man. Just let him do it.
Let's go.
[Chobjai Condo]
Third.
I'm here to return the laptop.
Thanks.
Can I come in?
Sure.
That's not the only reason I'm here.
I also want to apologize to you for yesterday.
I didn't mean to say that shit to you.
That's fine.
I'm sorry for making you mad yesterday.
Can we go back to being friends like before?
Of course.
It's not fun being mad at you.
Same here.
I feel good now.
I'm going to go.
Thanks, dude.
See you later.
Thanks for still seeing me as your friend.
I will try to think of you as a friend, too.
You've taught here for almost a month. Have you started to get the hang of this place?
It's been good. The students here are awesome.
They are very attentive to my editing class.
I have Prof. Sujitra to thank.
If she hadn't taken a maternity leave, I wouldn't have had such a good experience.
Any issues that you'd like to talk to me about?
There's one about some students who haven't come to class.
For example, Mr. Boriphat.
Since I started here, he hasn't been to any of my classes.
Do you know him?
I do.
He goes by the name of Bone.
This is him, Professor. Here's Boriphat.
Why are you taking so long to set this up?
You are an asshole.
I heard you were sick.
I got you porridge and some medicines.
I think you're out of it.
This is Praew, my girlfriend.
Hello.
- I have to go.
- Third!
- Where is Third?
- I don't know.
Third has gone out of my life.