MkvDrama.me
11 MONTHS LATER
Yes, make a pose, please.
Ready? One, two, three.
For colon cancer treatment,
we start with surgery
to remove the malignant tissue.
Then, we proceed with chemotherapy
to destroy any remaining cancer cells
and prevent them from spreading.
However, side effects are common,
including hair loss and nausea.
I think I'll trim this part
to tighten the flow.
But this is important information.
We can wait to add a caption
to keep it engaging.
The clip is only a bit over a minute,
we can't fit everything in, Dao.
Then can I trim something else instead?
I'm doing this show to spread awareness.
Okay. Let's keep the whole thing.
Let's play the next part.
- How is it?
- Looks okay.
I think we should brighten it a bit
so the energy-saving label pops more.
Sure.
Make it look nice. This client is lovely.
Alright, let's try this.
- How is it?
- Great, much better.
If we run it until the year's end,
it will be more cost-effective.
I'll also plug your product
in other programs
on the Better Together channel.
It's worth it.
Our channel engagement keeps rising.
Thank you.
I'll have accounting
send over the details.
- Another job closed!
- For real?
Yeah, just now.
The Protex campaign we shot
is already on billboards.
Awesome!
Let me see.
Just now,
the client personally approved
Dao's Fighting Cancer campaign.
Amazing!
Health content
is really trending now, Dao.
Your show gets more views than any other.
Honestly,
I didn't expect it to get this popular.
I made it just to learn more,
and turned it into content.
Babe,
then let's find something relatable to us
and turn it into content too.
You should do a series called
"How to Win Her Back."
I think it's gonna take a while.
You've been trying for six years
and still no luck.
Oh, Babe.
Dao,
are you cold?
How's this round of chemo?
Not too bad.
It was less painful than surgery.
And I think there are
fewer side effects this time.
Hang in there, Dao.
This is round eleven. Just one more to go.
Don't worry. It's all about moral support.
Ugh, so much love.
Do you want to see even more?
- Why?
- What now?
Come here.
- Hey!
- Look.
- Gorgeous.
- Stunning.
I booked Mew's hotel for you two.
You can go on your honeymoon.
And make content while you're at it.
- Cut it out, you're always like this.
- What?
The hotel just reopened after COVID.
- They need tourists. Be understanding.
- We're friends, come on.
Yeah, friends.
But it's in less than two months,
will you really be okay?
What if the last chemo hits hard?
Stop. Don't think like that.
I will be fine.
Alright, back to work, everyone.
- Hey, Dao!
- Dao!
Sit down first.
Let's go.
Why didn't you let Dao
stay at the hospital?
It's just nausea and dizziness, Mom.
The doctor said it's nothing serious.
But we've talked about this, Dao.
If anything happens, you have to tell us.
And no pushing yourself.
I wasn't. I really felt fine this morning.
You're stubborn again.
I'll work at the studio.
And for the wedding,
will she be okay?
I'm trying to keep things quiet.
You can wake me up.
Dao, let's get you changed first.
I'll take care of the laundry.
I'm sorry.
You had to stay up with me.
It's okay.
We've still got
two more tie-ins this month.
And for the new ad campaign,
please help find a model
with a modern Chinese look.
- To match the product's target.
- Got it.
Some viewers say
the Taste & Share show feels a bit slow.
I'm thinking of tightening it up
and adding more upbeat music.
You think that will help?
Try it. Whatever feels fun for you.
Dao.
How are you doing?
I brought snacks to cheer you up.
Dao.
I told you to rest at home.
Why did you come in?
I've been resting for days.
We gotta deliver
the invites to the elders.
So you don't have to come back for me.
- I'm not going.
- Why?
What are they talking about?
- No idea.
Why postpone?
Don't you want to marry me, Ran?
I'm just worried about you.
But we agreed you wouldn't do this.
Can you make things feel normal, Ran?
Stop treating me like I'm about to die.
Get well first.
Once you're healthy, whatever
you want to do, I promise I'll take you.
I don't know
how much time I have left.
I want to marry you, Ran.
But this is torture.
It hurts so much.
I'm scared.
You have to fight through it.
Better Together, right?
And we are together.
I feel bad for Ran and Dao.
They took forever to get together,
and now this.
Yeah…
Hey.
I talked to Dao.
We'll wait and see
how she reacts to the final shot.
If it's too much
and she really can't handle it,
then we'll postpone the wedding.
Just one more shot. You'll make it, right?
The produce looks really fresh.
- Did it come in today?
- Yes, this morning.
- Then I'll take one papaya.
- Sure.
And three apples, please.
- Okay.
- Here you go.
This one.
- Put them in this bag, please.
- Got it.
Here you go.
Ran, tonight I'm making
steamed fish with milk.
It will help soothe Dao's throat.
If she wants anything else,
just let me know. See you later.
It's nothing. See you at home.
It's me.
For the newly edited
Taste and Share episode,
I watched it. It looks good.
As for the budget on Ning's show idea,
please set up a team meeting.
I want to trim a few more things out.
Okay.
Mon…
Mon, wait.
Why are you back?
I'm sorry, Mon.
How could you do this to me and our child?
Do you even know what we've been through?
I take full responsibility.
It's all my fault.
- I thought I could fix everything.
- With a stupid method like that?
I know everything now.
I know why you took out the loan.
What were you thinking?
At the time, I didn't know what to do.
I just wanted to find money
to help the company.
At first, it worked.
But before I knew it,
everything collapsed.
It wasn't just your life that fell apart.
Mine and our child's did too.
Why did you do it?
Why?
Why? Why?
You didn't care about me
or our child at all?
No calls. No letters.
Why didn't you reach out?
It's not that I didn't want to.
I was ashamed.
You know…
I haven't had a night
of peaceful sleep since.
But I've quit everything now.
I'm working hard to pay off the debt.
Our child is stronger than I was.
In just a few years, he paid it all off.
Is that the reason?
Because the debt is gone?
That's why you came back?
No.
Why aren't you coming inside?
I was just thinking about something.
Alright.
- Tonight, Dao will sleep at her place.
- Okay.
I just dropped her off.
Tomorrow, she has a meeting about
the new collection of Mr. Stone Face.
So let's save the meal
you planned for her for tomorrow.
Are you alright?
Yes, I'm fine.
Here you go.
No worries. I'll go myself.
Ran, it's okay. I'll check.
- It's fine. I can go.
- It's fine.
Mom.
What is it, Nay?
Hold on.
- There's a delivery for Mr. Paran.
- From where?
It doesn't say.
Please sign for it.
Thank you.
I sent you the email.
Check it when you can.
What are you doing, Mom?
Nothing, Dear.
Just some creep sending stuff.
Let's go inside.
GRANDMA SAMAI RESTAURANT
Do you want anything from Chiang Mai?
Jew will bring it after his site visit.
We haven't even finished the last batch.
Jew looks happy with his new job.
Of course.
When a man can ease his family's burden,
he feels proud.
- Mom.
- Hmm?
- Duen.
Is wedding planning
really that exhausting?
Everyone keeps telling me to postpone.
Before the wedding,
you have to visit venues,
make sure everything's ready,
outfits, makeup artists,
party favors, everything.
The night before,
you'll be too excited to sleep.
Then you have to
get up at 3 a.m. for makeup.
On the day, you'll be busy with
the ceremony and greeting guests.
But there's one part that isn't tiring.
Which part?
Counting envelopes.
Mom.
No, no.
Come here.
Are you okay?
Hey, I know my food is good,
but you don't have to eat until you vomit.
Actually, it's good.
You'll be slimmer
and look gorgeous for the wedding.
Thank you.
You and Duen never treat me like I'm sick.
Because you're stubborn.
- Let's go to bed.
- Come on, Dear.
Let's go.
Once I'm married,
we won't be sleeping here
like this anymore.
If you miss it,
just bring Ran to stay over.
I'll keep your room exactly as it is.
Time for bed, Dear.
- Sweet dreams, Dao.
- You too.
MR. PARAN WATCHAWONG
7,000,000 - SAK
MR. PARAN WATCHAWONG 7,000,000
As for the money…
We'll need to ask the investor
how much he's willing to
lend a couple of fresh grads like us.
How much again?
Ran, I've prepared food for you.
Is Dao staying over tonight?
Yes.
- Pueang, can you leave first?
- Of course.
Mom.
Yesterday when you came back
from the market, you were acting strange.
Did something happen?
Why do you ask?
You met Dad, didn't you?
He just got back to Thailand.
Where has he been?
In Hong Kong.
Yesterday,
he waited at the market to see me.
But don't worry, Ran.
I won't let him
interfere in your life again.
Aren't you happy he's back?
You've waited all these years.
But I'm more worried about you.
About me?
Not long ago,
I spoke to Uncle Nui.
About the bank loan your father took,
part of it…
He used for online gambling.
Dad?
When the company ran into problems,
he tried to find cash flow.
Then,
Uncle Kitja from his golf group
gave him the idea.
At first,
he actually won some.
So he… and in the end…
Ran…
Online gambling? Seriously?
Your dad made a mistake.
I don't understand.
How could someone
as smart and capable as him
choose to solve things like that?
Ran, listen.
I don't want to make you hate him more.
But I'm telling you
because I don't know
if he's really quit gambling.
He told me he has.
And I don't want him
to cause any more trouble in your life.
Why did he come back?
He heard from Uncle Nui
that you're getting married.
So he wanted to come to your wedding.
- Are you okay, Dao?
- Of course.
The final shot is finally done.
Others got vax marks on their arms,
I got chemo lines.
Isn't it cool?
You did great.
Do you wanna grab snacks
from downstairs again?
Last time was pretty good.
What kind do you want?
This one? One or two pieces?
- One strawberry, please.
- Sure.
And two chocolate ones, please.
Got it.
And two brownies.
Sure.
Anything else?
No, that's all.
- One moment.
- Sure.
Anything else?
- How much?
- It's 650 baht.
Excuse me.
Are you Nubdao?
Yes.
I really love your Mr. Stone Face!
I brought it too!
Can we take a photo, please?
- Please.
- Of course.
- I'll take a lot. One, two, three!
- Again! One, two, three! So pretty!
- My turn!
- Let me take one first!
- Me first.
- How about one group photo instead?
- Sure!
- Sorry to trouble you.
- No worries.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
- Thank you so much!
- Thank you!
I'll wait for your new collection.
- Alright.
- Thank you.
How do I look in the photo?
- If you're tired, you can say no.
- It's fine.
It feels good.
It feels like I still matter to people.
Dao hasn't come down yet.
She must still be sleeping.
She was throwing up all night.
Probably needs to rest all day.
Please look after her. Once I'm done
with work, I'll come right over.
I thought you had meetings
with Mira until evening?
She rescheduled.
She even told me to go home.
- Dao!
- Mom!
- Ran!
- What happened to Dao?
She fell down the stairs. I gotta go.
Dao.
Are you okay, Dao? Dao?
Pueng! Pueng!
Pueng, Dao fell down the stairs!
Pueng!
Help!
Security!
Mon, what happened?
Sak, Dao fell down the stairs. Help me.
Hurry up.
How is she, Mom?
We're heading to the hospital.
Your dad showed up to help.
Where is Ms. Nubdao Paitho?
Bed three, Sir.
Oh, Mr. Paran.
- Hello, Doctor.
- Hello.
How is Dao?
We've done the X-ray.
There's nothing concerning.
She's just weak from the chemo.
Still, I'd like to keep her
overnight for observation.
Alright.
Don't worry, Mr. Paran.
Thank you very much.
A nurse will bring her
to the recovery room soon.
Excuse me.
- Thank you so much.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Come on.
And…
Where is he now?
I asked him to leave.
Or do you want to see him?
I'll check on Dao's room.
Dao's awake.
She's okay now.
Please handle work today.
I won't be coming in.
Got it. I'll tell her.
Kae and everyone send their well wishes.
The day I had my final chemo,
you saw your Dad, didn't you?
I saw him staring at you for a while,
hoping you'd turn around and speak to him.
Don't think about anything now.
Just rest and get better.
I understand
you're still angry at him.
But if he hadn't been there today,
things might have been worse.
Please forgive him, Ran.
He stole six years of my life, Dao.
And the 20 years he gave before that,
do they mean nothing?
I'm not mad that he caused debt.
People make mistakes.
But I'm mad that he was selfish.
He chose to run away
instead of staying to face it with us.
I still remember
how devastated Mom was
the day he disappeared.
And in the end,
it was Mom and me
who had to clean up the mess he made.
But today, you've made it.
The day I found out
that my Dad had someone else,
Mom told me
there are still good things about him
worth keeping as memories.
No one is perfect.
I hope you can do the same, Ran.
Life is short.
We never know when we'll die.
No, Dao.
Don't say things like that.
It's the truth, Ran.
That's why I want you to forgive your Dad
before it's too late.
But I don't want to be hurt by him again.
Dodge! Throw a punch!
Again.
Same side! Jab!
‪Here.
Your film camera?
You said you wanted it, right?
I'm giving it to you so you can
take pictures at the club building.
One, two, three!
- I've got another medal, Dad.
- Good job!
Hey, I think
I need to buy a new medal cabinet.
- The old one is full already.
- Great job!
Thank you.
Come on, let's take a picture.
- Alright.
- Come on.
One, two, three.
It turns out your ride-hailing feature
is making more money
than the food delivery one.
But this year, be ready to hustle.
I spoke to Mira. We're adding hotel
and flight booking features.
It will become a one-stop service.
Dev is currently doing the research.
Once we've finalized everything,
we'll share the summary with the team.
You seniors are so productive,
it makes us look lazy.
Right? I was planning to use lunch break
to find some clothes for Ran's wedding.
No need to nudge. Just go.
Alright, that's it. Meeting dismissed.
- Tle.
- Yes?
Can you grab the stuff from my office?
Oh, sure.
How's Dao doing lately?
It's just a few more days
until the wedding.
Is she okay?
Her body's not at 100%,
but her heart is more than ready.
If she could reschedule it
for tomorrow, she would.
Dao must really love you.
Here.
This is our gift, from me and Tle.
Congrats, Ran.
Thank you.
We won't be able to make it
to the wedding day.
But we wish you and Dao so much happiness.
Thanks again, Mira.
And Tle too.
We'll head off then.
- Let's go.
- Alright.
Hey, put it properly!.
Don't let it go crooked.
Alright, kids, step out for a bit.
- I'll take a photo before the guests come.
- Move aside.
Sure, go ahead.
- Let me get one first.
- Of course.
Let me take one first.
Please do a mini heart.
- Like this?
- Show her how.
One, two, three. Alright.
- Nice.
- Duen, come here.
- Friends' turn?
- Wait. Hang on! Let Duen go first.
- Oh?
- Yeah.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Easy now.
Two, three.
Give us some love signs too.
Great! Everyone, look at the camera.
One, two--
Mon, wait.
Mon, move Jew this way.
Just the two of us here is better.
Thank you.
Mon, are you waiting for Mr. Sak?
Actually, I wanted to thank him too,
for helping Dao that day.
No need to thank him.
It was just a coincidence.
And no, I'm not waiting for him.
I just don't want him ruining
the happiest day of my son's life.
All done, thank you!
- Thank you.
Shall we get a chair for the photos, Dao?
No. It won't look as good.
You'll look beautiful
whether you're sitting or standing.
- Can I get a chair, please?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- I'll help.
Alright.
Please.
Thank you.
You okay?
- You alright?
- Yes.
Okay.
- Ran.
- Nam.
Thanks for coming.
I really admire Dao.
She's completed 12 rounds of chemo.
Are the cancer cells gone?
We still don't know. We'll have to wait
and consult with the doctor.
What if it's not all gone?
Then she'll need another chemo set.
Will she be able to handle that?
The first round was already brutal.
Exactly.
And where the hell did Zen go get water?
He's been gone for ages.
Hey, Ning.
I'll go get water for you.
Just stay here.
Ning. Ning.
Babe, today is Dao's wedding day.
Is it gonna be Zen's funeral day too?
- Don't even try to copy that.
- I won't.
Sorry, June. I forgot to shift to neutral.
- I was in a rush.
- It's okay.
See? I remembered it was your car.
I saw it on Instagram.
- Are you back with Ning?
- Yes.
That's impressive.
She finally forgave you.
I just got a new phone.
Can I have your LINE again?
If you need to reach me,
you can message through Ning.
Okay.
Did you come after me?
Come on. Let's go in.
I met the groom back
when he first started walking.
There was a little boy
who always ran around the print shop.
And when he got to middle school,
he brought a little girl, his friend,
to run around with him.
I'm truly happy to see
that boy and girl, once childhood friends,
grow up and care for each other now.
I'm confident
they will take care of one another well.
- Right, Ran?
- Yes.
Why are you here?
I told you, didn't I?
Don't make our child suffer again.
I just wanted to see him.
I promise I won't get in the way.
You've seen him now. You can go.
Thank you
for helping Dao that day.
Ran probably wants to thank you too.
But that alone
doesn't make up for what you did to us.
I know.
If you want to watch, watch from here.
Just don't let him see you.
Let's raise a toast
to the bride and groom!
- Cheers!
Thank you to Mr. Nui, Patipak Iam-in,
former editor of Add-On magazine.
And now, let's hear a few words
from the bride and groom.
Let's begin with
the bride.
Thank you all
for making our wedding
so warm and full of love.
Thank you to my mom,
Duen, Jew,
Ran's Mom,
and I believe my grandma
is smiling down on me today, too.
She was our first true fan.
But the one I want to thank most
is Ran.
Ran has always been
my inspiration, my driving force,
and the one who always believed in me.
Many of you already know,
this Mr. Stone Face you all admire
comes from Ran.
Do they look alike?
- Oh.
- Yes.
On my toughest days,
just turning to look at Ran,
even with that blank face,
he always made my heart feel lighter.
Ran is my secret edition
of Mr. Stone Face.
Thank you.
Now that we've heard from the bride,
let's hear from the groom.
Thank you, everyone.
Dao and I missed each other many times.
Kae once joked
that maybe my guardian angel
didn't want us together.
Without Dao,
I got by,
but it was harder.
With her, it's better.
Dao is my friend,
my girlfriend,
and soon, my life partner.
Whether it's joy or sorrow,
even if the guardian angels disapprove,
I promise, we'll always have each other.
And now,
the moment you've all been waiting for…
- Kiss! Kiss!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
This couple right here
is sweeter than the cake in front of them.
Next up,
the bride and groom will now cut the cake!
Wait.
Just one more moment.
There's someone else
I want up here with me today.
Dad.
Please give your blessing to me and Dao.
Thank you all
for loving and supporting my son.
He's far more capable than I was.
When he was little,
he once told me
he didn't want to work at my company.
He feared people would say
he got the job because of me.
But he's proved himself.
He's where he is today
because of who he is.
I'm proud of you.
I wish you and Dao
a life filled with love and care.
Hold each other's hand tight.
You'll get through anything.
I love you.
I'm sorry, Ran.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay, Dad.
Get ready to catch
the bouquet from the couple!
Let's make some noise!
On the count of one, two, three!
Zen!
Ran, this exhibition means a lot to me.
Dao!
- Dao.
- I know you've got the heart of a fighter.
But if your body can't keep up,
willpower alone won't get you through.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon