Master, you won.
[Sandstorm]
[Episode 11]
They are matched!
A duplicated one.
Yes.
Why does it need to be duplicated?
To steal coal.
Stealing coal?
But, why is it thrown
to be burnt in the furnace?
Maybe something shady was done.
Destroying evidence.
Hello, Kulu County Police Station.
Who is this speaking?
Police officer, I want to make a report.
My husband's name is Liu Dazhi.
He's from Kulu.
I think something happened
to my husband.
Didn't Liu Dazhi go back two days ago?
I'm not sure either.
But, I couldn't reach him.
Don't panic, please tell me slowly.
He didn't come back.
I...
A few days ago, he wanted to return.
But, I kept persuading him
that his father hadn't buried yet
and it would be better
to return after the funeral.
However,
he excitedly called me two days ago
saying he was coming back.
Then, after a while,
he called again,
telling me that there was
still something he hadn't settled
and couldn't come back yet.
I didn't think much of it.
At 6:00 PM the night before last,
he called me again...
He called me again,
saying he was on the way back.
But, before he finished speaking,
the call hung up.
I...
I didn't finish what I was saying before
it hung up, and I was apprehensive.
Then, I tried calling him twice more.
He picked up the first two times,
saying he was on his way back
and told me not to worry.
But,
I couldn't reach him anymore after that.
I thought maybe he had entered
a desert region and lost signal.
Then, I didn't think too much of it
and went to bed.
But then,
when I woke up,
I still couldn't reach him.
Police officer, do you think his car
might have broken down in the desert?
But...
But I waited all day,
and there's still no news from him.
I didn't know what to do.
I...
I called the police station
to make a report.
They let me contact you,
the Kulu County Police Station.
So I...
I got it. Don't worry.
We will start looking for him now.
Keep your phone on.
We'll stay in touch.
Thank you.
Chen.
I saw Liu Dazhi safely leave this town.
You told me to come back.
Could it be like his wife said?
The car broke down in the desert
and he lost the signal?
Something happened.
Immediately report it
to headquarters
and request support.
Keep close surveillance
on Wang Liang and Liu Yingying.
Extract Liu Dazhi's call records
from that day.
Get all the surveillance footage
along the route.
Got it.
Let's take action now. Hurry up!
This was the room, right?
Yes.
He was always yelling at us,
and even had me move him
from the fifth floor to the seventh
because of a room issue.
I had no idea what was up with him.
He especially wanted a corner room.
How long did he stay here?
He stayed for
about three or four days.
He didn't go out much.
And, it's very rare
to see someone visit him.
A woman came to see him.
She said she was his sister.
When did she come?
On the day he checked in,
and two days before he left.
I don't remember the exact times.
Do you remember
when he left?
He...
Is this security camera newly installed?
Why is there a camera here?
I don't know about this.
We found Liu Dazhi.
Liu Dazhi left the hotel
at around 7:21 PM that night.
I followed him along the way.
At around 7:50 PM,
he left Kulu.
When we found Liu Dazhi's car,
we discovered someone
had tampered with it.
The engine oil was leaking.
This was my fault.
As soon as I saw Liu Dazhi
leave Kulu safely,
I withdrew from following him.
If I had stayed with him,
maybe this wouldn't have happened.
Don't blame yourself.
I told you to withdraw.
You were standing so close
and watching it for so long.
I thought you would be fine.
I tailed him for two days,
worrying that he might escape.
When Liu Yingying hit him,
I still didn't believe Liu Dazhi
was in danger.
The dark side of human nature.
Everyone has it.
It's just a matter
of when it is activated.
If nothing happens,
no one knows
when it will be activated.
Bring Liu Yingying
and Wang Liang in for questioning.
Yes.
At the time of the incident,
both Wang Liang and Liu Yingying
had solid alibis.
Yes.
Liu Dazhi's call records show
that Liu Yingying
called him that day,
The phone call lasted 19 minutes.
It started at 6:15 PM,
and ended at 6:34 PM.
Afterwards,
Wang Liang called Liu Dazhi,
from 6:38 PM to 6:42 PM.
Five minutes later,
Liu Dazhi left the hotel
and drove out of Kulu.
There was an added camera
outside Liu Dazhi's room.
He was safe as long as he stayed inside.
What did those two
say to him on the phone
that made him leave the room?
Liu Dazhi was always
in a hurry to leave Kulu.
Luo, watch this video.
This is the nearest surveillance camera
to Wang Liang's home.
At 6:13 PM,
Wang Liang and Liu Yingying
passed by here
and went straight home.
Chen went to their place
at 7:05 PM
and left at 7:30 PM.
Theoretically, they didn't have time
to commit the crime.
These two people provided
a very solid alibi.
You are the solid alibi.
I'm a fool.
Yes, I called my brother.
My daughter has passed away.
My father's case is still unresolved.
I'm heartbroken.
In this world, my brother
is the only family I owned.
But, at that moment,
he was eager to go back home.
I was a little mad at him.
So I called and blamed him.
He comforted me a little,
and that was it.
That's all.
Do you get along well with your brother?
Yes, we do.
Our mother passed away very early.
I practically raised my brother
since he was young.
Even though I'm only
two years older than him,
sometimes I feel like
I am his mother.
From what I understand,
Liu Dazhi doesn't
come back to Kulu often.
And, you both don't
keep in touch either.
That's right.
He's busy with work
and seldom come back home.
We talk on the phone.
You mentioned that Liu Dazhi
is your only family now.
So, what's your relationship
with Wang Liang?
He is my other half.
Both of you didn't have
a marriage certificate, right?
And you don't recognize Wang Liang
as Duoduo's biological father either.
You were always a top student,
the pride of your family,
and a graduate
from the provincial university.
Someone like you
could have stayed
in the province
for a better future development.
But Wang Liang is
an illiterate furnace worker,
and a street child
that your father, Liu Sancheng
adopted from the grasslands.
You gave up a promising future
for Wang Liang.
Is that love
or hate?
What are you implying, Officer Luo?
Answer the question.
I was pregnant.
With Wang Liang's child.
So, do you think it is love or hate?
That's right.
After Yingying called him,
I gave him another call
talking about something.
What did you say to him?
After Duoduo passed away,
Yingying hasn't been able to move on.
My father's case
impacted her a lot too.
That's why I wanted
to convince Dazhi to stay,
to help comfort Yingying more.
After my father died,
my brother kept thinking
that someone was trying to harm him.
I found it strange too.
I'm not sure when it started,
but he just always felt
someone was trying to harm him.
I'm from a medical background.
I think he might be suffering
from paranoia.
Maybe...
It was a series of incidents
that happened in his family
which brought him a huge stimulation.
I'm very worried about him.
I tried to convince him over
the phone for a very long time.
I talked to him over the phone.
But he insisted on going back.
I let him consult a doctor
when he returned.
That night, Chen came
to my house around 7:00 PM.
We talked for about half an hour.
Officer Chen
left our home
around 7:30 PM.
After he left,
I went back to the station.
- Wang Liang went to his night shift.
- I was on night duty that day.
I wasn't feeling well that day.
So I stayed at the station all night.
I stayed at home the whole night
and didn't attend work.
Liu Yingying.
Please check the record.
If there are no issues, please sign it.
Thank you for your cooperation.
We had already allowed
Liu Dazhi left Kulu.
So why did he stay two more days?
After two days, he suddenly fled
and ended up being murdered
in the desert.
Why?
Liu Yingying and Wang Liang
didn't have time to commit the crime.
There must be another person
involved in this case.
Zhang Yuan.
Check the call records
of Liu Yingying, Wang Liang,
and Liu Sancheng.
But, wasn't Liu Sancheng
already burned in the furnace?
Liu Dafu. Liu Dazhi.
Yes, we checked all of them.
Check the call records with anyone else
for the three of them.
How about we go have some lamb soup?
Let's go.
♪We wanted♪
♪We lost♪
♪We've had♪
How much time do we have?
♪Enough♪
♪I prayed♪
It's okay.
♪I tried♪
The people who know these things...
♪Again♪
There's only one person left.
♪It's destiny♪
♪I need you to tell me
what you're hiding from♪
♪And what's been keeping you so down♪
♪My lover♪
♪It's getting deeper♪
♪I've got a secret♪
Please go ahead to work first.
♪We need to keep it silent♪
♪We make sure it never happened♪
♪I've got a secret♪
♪We leave it under surface♪
♪Then we uncover after decades♪
♪We wanted♪
♪We lost♪
♪We've had♪
♪Enough♪
♪I prayed♪
♪I tried♪
♪Again♪
♪It's destiny♪
♪I've got a secret♪
♪We need to keep it silent♪
♪We make sure it never happened♪
♪I've got a secret♪
♪We leave it under surface♪
♪Then we uncover after decades♪
Your lamb soup is served.
Enjoy!
You've mastered it.
Not afraid of the heat, huh?
I learned this from you.
I don't eat like this anymore.
Are you regressing?
I follow the given advice.
Eating hot food too frequently
is bad for the oesophagus.
Who owned the ability to convince you?
My daughter.
The methods of solving cases nowadays
are so varied.
Checking surveillance, call records,
and location tracking.
I remember back
when I was with my master,
we surveyed human relationships,
social connections, and the motives.
Are we relying too much
on modern technology?
The old skills and knowledge
shouldn't be abandoned.
You mean we need to look
at the cause and effect?
Cheng Chun was murdered by Liu Dazhi.
Liu Dazhi's crime changed
many people's fate,
and it earned him hatred.
Who...
would hate him so much
to torture him to death
in such a brutal way?
Chen. Luo.
You're just in time.
I've got a discovery.
Come check it out!
Alright!
Qin.
Bring the beef noodles for everyone.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Commissioner Liu.
Both of you are here.
[Kulu County Police Station Surveillance Center]
Play the footage from Wednesday afternoon,
outside Haotai Hotel.
Okay, pause.
Look at how he rides the bike.
He seems to be Ding Baoyuan.
He has appeared
near Liu Dazhi's hotel several times.
Now play the footage from the exit road.
Okay, pause.
At 5:11 PM,
Ding Baoyuan left the town on his bike,
heading toward the province.
Ding Baoyuan is involved in the case.
What about Wang Liang and Liu Yingying?
Play the footage from Tuesday
at Wang Liang's house.
Okay, pause.
He was spotted near Wang Liang's place.
They have had private contact.
When did we tell Liu Dazhi
to go back to work?
Monday afternoon.
Liu Dazhi...
Why did he stay?
He stayed for two more days.
Commissioner Liu.
I've checked the call records.
On Monday at 3:21 PM,
Liu Dazhi called Liu Yingying.
Shortly after, at 5:05 PM,
Wang Liang called Ding Baoyuan.
The call lasted just over a minute.
So far, this is the only call
we have found between them.
Liu Dazhi decided to stay,
and made a call to Liu Yingying.
Then, Wang Liang contacted Ding Baoyuan.
And, Liu Dazhi
ended up dead.
Didn't I ask you to keep an eye
on Ding Baoyuan?
I did, Commissioner Liu.
I let Wei follow him.
He has been hanging out
with Sun Caiyun recently,
playing mahjong and dancing
in the public square.
Everything seems normal.
Ding Baoyuan is good
at managing his facial expressions.
Has anyone seen Guan Qiao
these two days?
Guan Qiao?
Hi.
We are from Kulu County Police Station.
Are you Guan Qiao's sister?
Yes.
We will take a look around.
Where is Guan Qiao?
He is not here.
He went out to look for a job.
When did he leave?
Where did he go?
What kind of job he is looking for?
How should I know?
You better tell the truth,
where is Guan Qiao?
What happened to him?
Just answer the question.
He came by here three days ago,
saying a man named Ding Baoyuan
offered him to be his lawyer,
and also mentioned
that the state compensated
Ding Baoyuan a large sum of money.
That's all I know.
Alright, we got it.
We will contact you if any update.
Okay.
Hello, Luo.
Guan Qiao has gone to meet Ding Baoyuan.
Ding Baoyuan.
Investigate.
Hello.
Sun Caiyun.
Luo.
Where are you?
I'm at home.
Is Ding Baoyuan with you?
He is not at home.
He went out.
How has Ding Baoyuan been
since he returned home?
He's been fine.
He stays with me every day,
dancing in the public square
and playing mahjong.
He is doing well.
I am just asking.
These two days, you two could
come to the police station
to discuss the compensation matter.
Alright, Luo.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Bye.
Have some water.
You look tired.
Why do you men
always like hitting women?
Did you hear earlier?
Luo thought Ding Baoyuan
was going to kill me.
Yeah.
People like them
think they are so clever.
For them,
I am just a small person.
But they don't realize,
people like me
can do anything.
Wang Liang,
have an apple.
You didn't even drink the water.
Aren't you thirsty?
It seems I made the right choice.
I picked you back then
to help me send Ding Baoyuan
to prison was the right move.
Was it necessary to go that far?
That's pretty ruthless.
Caiyun, I'm sorry,
but you must die.
Once you are dead,
no one in this world
will know the truth.
I'm sorry, it will only take
two minutes, and you won't feel pain.
Wang Liang. Wang Liang.
You can't kill me.
You think killing me
will keep you and Liu Yingying safe?
Wang Liang,
you don't understand women.
You don't even understand your mother,
let alone Liu Yingying.
Wang Liang.
Your mother and mine
both came from other places.
Do you know why
their fates were different?
Because my mother chose to obey.
Your mother chose to resist.
What about Liu Yingying?
What do you think
about Liu Yingying's choice?
A woman's thought
is always hard to understand.
You don't understand,
but I do.
Let me teach you.
I know I am going to die.
I'll die at your hands sooner or later.
But, don't you have a lot
of questions to ask me?
I can help you answer them.
Let's take some time for it.
It won't be too late to kill me
after we talk about that.
Well.
It doesn't matter
if we wait a bit longer.
What do you want to talk about?
What I want to talk about
is not important.
What matters is
what you need to talk about.
Don't you have any questions?
Tell me,
and I'll help you figure things out.
Why did you
come from Luoche to the county?
Why did I come here?
When I was on the grasslands,
I had no home.
I felt unsafe.
But after I got to Kulu,
I found a home.
Do you get it?
You are pitiful.
I feel very sorry for you.
We are different.
I live for myself.
I just want to get out.
I always
want to get out of there,
aiming to a higher position.
But after I got to the county,
I realized that the people here
are so fake.
They flatter you superficially.
But deep down,
no one respects you.
It doesn't matter, I don't care.
That's why I have to keep stepping out,
heading to a higher position.
Do you know why I sent Ding Baoyuan
to prison?
Because he never treated me
like a human being.
He treated me like an animal.
I'm a realist.
I love money.
Money is everything to me.
But then I slowly realized,
as a human,
once we are satisfied materially,
we feel spiritually empty.
Li Rui.
Yes.
Have you found Ding Baoyuan?
No, Chen.
All the major road surveillance
were checked,
but no discovery.
However, I did find something new.
Wang Liang left the county at 9:03 PM
and returned at 12:21 AM.
Check for Ding Baoyuan's vehicle
along the road in the province.
Send people for that.
Wang Liang,
have you ever heard the saying,
"literature
is the salvation of humanity"?
Guan Qiao is just great at this.
I think
that is also the reason
why you are with Liu Yingying.
Guan Qiao and you,
and Liu Yingying and I, are different.
Don't compare us to you.
I love Yingying.
She's my everything.
She's your everything.
But, what are you to her?
You are nothing to her,
not even a fart.
Maybe not even that.
Are you mad now?
Don't be mad, Wang Liang.
I know you don't like hearing this.
Wang Liang,
we are both
from Luoche.
You are the wild grass
of the grasslands,
and I am the wildflower.
You can grow anywhere,
and I can bloom anywhere.
We are the same kind of people.
Liu Yingying never cared about you.
All these years,
has she ever looked at you properly?
She looks down on you
from the bottom of her heart.
Neither does her father.
Their whole family looks down on you.
Their family
treat you like a thief,
like a free labor.
They've been using you.
Do you even know that?
So,
why should we die?
They are the ones who deserve to die.
I know
you killed Liu Sancheng.
You did well.
You should have killed
Liu Yingying too.
Killing that wife
who ever looked down on you.
Am I right?
Why are you laughing?
Am I wrong?
Shouldn't you kill her?
Caiyun.
Have you ever loved someone?
Yes, I have loved someone.
Who did you love?
Myself.
Besides me,
who else is worth loving?
How about you?
I have loved someone before.
When I was a kid, I loved my mother.
When I grew up, I loved my master.
I love Yingying.
Even if they don't care about me,
even if they never look at me properly,
I still love her.
Because you are a fool.
You are not allowed to say so.
I love her.
But you don't love anyone.
So you are the one who deserves to die.
Die?
I knew it. I won't die.
I won't die.
Even if you kill me,
I'll still come back to life.
Go die, you!
I'm someone strong who won't die...
What are you doing here?
Aren't you supposed to be at work?
Leave here!
The police are now
looking for Ding Baoyuan.
They will track me down soon.
I've already killed Sun Caiyun.
There's no one left in this world
who knows what happened anymore.
Remember,
everything that happened was done by me
and has nothing to do with you.
Understand?
Leave here now!
Leave now!
Yingying, what are you doing?
Please leave here.
The police will arrest me soon.
It will be hard to explain
if you stay with me.
Let's go around
and see.
Don't you want to come with me?
There is a motorbike over there.
Hello, you can speak.
Hello, Luo.
We found the car and the people.
Wait a minute.
You can speak now.
We found the car and the people,
in the desert outside the province.
The body is decapitated,
and we found a bundle of steel wires.
Got it.
Let me send you off.
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
What's wrong with her?
She's feeling a little unwell.
I'll go check on her.
Yingying.
Chen.
Arrest them?
Arrest!
Ma!
Bring people to the hospital
to arrest Liu Yingying.
Got it.
We are heading to the heating station.
Let's go, Dayong.
Alright.
[Outpatient]
Keep up. Hurry!
Is Liu Yingying in the hospital?
She took leave today and left early.
Alright, thank you.
Go take a look around.
Let's go.
Hello.
Liu Yingying is not at the hospital.
Where did he go?
Alright, you guys check again.
I don't know.
Did he come here yesterday?
No, he didn't come here
yesterday either.
Liu Yingying hasn't been to work.
She didn't go to work?
Could they be trying to escape?
It is possible.
Hello?
Hello, Luo.
That villain, Wang Liang.
He wanted to kill me.
Wang Liang wanted to kill you?
Where are you?
I am at home.
He had colluded
with Ding Baoyuan long ago.
They teamed up to murder Guan Qiao,
and then he killed Ding Baoyuan.
Now, he wanted to kill me.
Where is Wang Liang now?
He has already left.
Why are you asking so many questions?
When did he leave?
He's been leaving for a while.
Why are you only calling me now?
I had to make sure I was safe
before I called you.
Oh, right!
He drove away my car.
The car is worth over 200,000 yuan.
You have to get it back for me!
Hello?
Luo?
Wang Liang tried to kill Sun Caiyun
but he failed.
He took away her car keys.
They are trying to escape from Kulu.
Chase them!
The police are catching up soon,
and you are still very happy?
Of course.
Why wouldn't I be happy?
Everything that needed
to be done is done.
What could be
more satisfying than that?
Where are we going?
Keep driving.
Leave Kulu.
Then?
Then...
It doesn't matter where we go.
Even if we just take one step
outside of Kulu, it's enough.
Wang Liang,
have you never left Kulu
your whole life?
Haven't you ever thought
about going out and exploring the world?
Why do you all want to leave here?
Who else?
Mr. Chen.
Last time, he took me
to get a DNA test,
saying that he wanted to help me
find my relatives outside.
That's a good thing.
Why don't you go?
My family is here.
Just keep driving.
Make this journey as you accompany me.
Alright, I got it.
They have tracked them.
Wang Liang took Liu Yingying
left the county 20 minutes ago.
Your stomach hurts again?
Do you want to try one?
Sure, give me one.
Here's a small one for you.
Okay.
Just spit it out if you can't stand it.
What a big piece of this!
It is salty and sour.
It is the taste of my childhood.
I am used to it.
It is completely different
from what I imagined.
Just spit it out if you can't stand it.
Don't waste it.
[Kulu]
Why do you stop the car?
Yingying, I've already
reached the outside.
Let's keep driving forward.
You should leave.
The police will catch up soon.
What about you?
Yingying, do you still remember the
field of flowers that Duoduo was buried?
The other kids had toys,
but Duoduo didn't.
But, I didn't think
she was any worse off
than the other kids.
She loved playing hide-and-seek with me
in that field of flowers.
I want to go accompany Duoduo.
Take care of yourself.
Get in the car.
Wherever you go, I will go.
Something amiss.
They left not long ago.
Why haven't we caught up yet?
Could there be a mistake?
There's only one road leading
out of the county, right?
Stop it.
Everyone, please stop moving.
Head to Luoche.
Please stop moving, and head to Luoche.
[Kulu]
Wang Liang was born in Luoche,
and grew up in Kulu.
I have mentioned to you before,
Wang Liang's mother
tried to escape from Luoche, right?
[Kulu]
Back then, Wang Liang's mother
was ready to escape from Luoche.
She wanted to take Wang Liang with her.
Wang Liang was seven years old.
He told his father about it.
The escape failed.
Do you know
what motive is behind Wang Liang?
What is that?
He thought the family couldn't
be complete without their mother.
But his mother was not happy.
You're right.
But the child understood nothing.
He must be trying to go back
to that once-happy and carefree Luoche.
And, Duoduo is there now.
All these years,
deep down, you've always known
I feel hostile towards you,
I hated you, didn't you?
I know.
Then, why have you still been
so kind to me?
You should know,
no matter how kind you are to me,
I'll never look at you differently.
Have you heard about my mother's story?
I've heard the old man
mentioned it once.
My mother came from outside.
She was like you.
She always wanted to escape from here.
When I was little, she hated me.
But, she was my mother,
the only relative I have in this world.
No matter how much she hated me,
I think...
I hope
that she still feels sorry for me.
♪A dying fire♪
Mother, does it hurt?
So, I've always hoped
that someday you would see me.
♪Repeatedly filtering old stories♪
♪Toss and turn restlessly♪
♪Let go of all gains and losses♪
My mother told me
that there's a kind of flower
in the desert
called the black mandala.
If you want it to bloom,
you have to water it with blood.
Perhaps, to me,
both you and my mother
are like the black mandalas.
♪To go on, to break free, to run away♪
Chen,
I heard
your wife left
because she was not willing
to stay with you in Kulu.
Did you ever think of leaving
with her at that time?
Yes, I did.
Why didn't you leave then?
Because of your master?
It's also because of myself.
I was born in Luoche,
raised in Luoche too.
Before I got divorced,
I tried to save my marriage,
and therefore traveled back and forth
between Kulu and the province.
One day, I realized that being led along
and deciding it for myself
were different.
What was the difference?
Let's stop chatting nonsense. Hurry up!
Alright, no more idle talk.
It's Sun Caiyun's car.
Wang Liang.
Ever since the old man
handed me over to you,
do you know how I've been
living all these days?
I know.
But, I've always wanted
to build a home with you,
and stayed together with you.
From the first time I saw you,
I knew
that apart from my mother,
you were
the most important person in my life.
Because of all this,
you've ruined my entire life.
I hate you.
I hate you for causing me to be
unable to leave this place
for my entire life.
And, I will have to die here.
Just because of you,
my hope,
my life,
and my other half
were all ruined.
I feel like I've already died inside.
I don't have any emotions left.
Because of you,
I even hated my own daughter.
I abhorred my own daughter.
I don't know why I'm still alive now.
Yingying,
it is my fault.
Is there anything I can do for you now?
You've already done enough.
Remember,
I'm the one who killed everyone.
Quickly run now.
Go accompany Duoduo.
Yingying.
If only one of us can survive,
I hope it is you.
Yingying,
just listen to me this once.
Wang Liang.
There's quicksand up ahead.
Don't let them follow us in.
Got it.
Wang Liang!
Liu Yingying.
You are suspected
of intentional homicide.
We are arresting you
according to the law.
Yingying,
come here.
He is Wang Liang.
From now on, he will live with us.
We are family now.
You need to get along like a sibling.
Why are you staring at me?
Close your eyes,
or you will get hair in your eyes.
Yingying,
you should marry to Wang Liang.
I will treat you well
for the rest of my life.
Let's live a good life together.
Yingying.
Don't touch me.
This child is so adorable.
Have you thought of a name yet?
Not yet.
Duoduo.
Liu Duoduo.
Aren't you the father of the child?
He is the child's uncle.
Yingying,
if only one of us can survive,
I hope it is you.
♪Silence♪
♪After the sandstorm♪
♪Thunder♪
♪Knocks on the cloud♪
♪Whisper♪
♪Before the dawn♪
♪Criminal♪
♪Through it all♪
♪Silence♪
♪After the sandstorm♪
♪Ruins♪
♪Throughout the ground♪
♪Darkness♪
♪Suddenly comes♪
♪I know♪
♪Where to leave me alone♪
♪Far away safe and sound♪
♪Night's so far so long♪
♪Faint light shining front♪
♪Guide me to hometown♪