[Pinghai University]
Here you go.
Try this.
Come on.
Thank you.
You guys try it, too.
I brought the goat milk
straight from the farm.
They are fresh.
Come on.
Try it. Here you go.
Thank you, Mrs. Liu.
Don't call me that.
Dafu...
Dazhi
calls my sister-in-law.
You can call me that, too.
Thank you, sister-in-law.
You're welcome.
Which one is Dazhi's bed?
This is Dazhi's bed.
Sure.
Oh, my. Why didn't he fold his blanket?
Liu Dazhi, your sister-in-law is here.
Dafu, did you just finish your lecture?
Why did you come here?
I came to visit you.
Sit.
She's my relative from my hometown.
We know.
She's your sister-in-law.
Right.
You've lost some weight.
Oh, right.
Here.
Take off your shoes.
What are you doing?
I sewed a pair of soles for you.
Try them.
Look, they fit well.
Sister-in-law,
I want a pair, too.
Sure. I'll make a pair for you later.
Hey,
you haven't put this one in yet.
Come.
You haven't put this in yet. Oh, my.
Why... Why didn't you tell me
you were coming?
My bad.
I wasn't thinking.
Well, I don't have much to do at home.
You've left for a few months,
so I was thinking of checking on you.
When are you leaving?
Oh, right.
I asked the dorm warden just now.
She told me there's a vacancy here.
I'm thinking
of staying here
and working as the warden.
I can also take care of you.
Wait for me here.
Dafu.
What's this?
Well, I have to attend lectures
every day.
I'll get distracted if you're here.
Mister, the terminal station.
Okay.
Is 50 yuan enough?
Yes, that's enough.
Freeze!
Everybody stay where you are.
Name.
Put your clothes on.
[Sandstorm]
[Episode 8]
Where are you going again?
Cyber cafe.
But the meal is ready.
Can't you go after eating?
Dafu.
Dafu!
Dafu. Hey!
Why are you back?
I don't feel like going.
Are you leaving or not?
Stop asking. I'm not leaving.
Since you got back
from the provincial town,
you've been holing up here.
Your dad doesn't say anything about it?
He goes to work.
He's busy.
I see.
I'm leaving, then.
My mom gave me a beating a few days ago.
Dafu?
Dafu.
Dafu, stop running. Dafu!
Dafu!
Stop running, Dafu!
Stop right there!
Stop, Dafu!
Stop calling my name.
People might hear that.
What do you want from me?
Why do you keep avoiding me?
I was busy at school.
I finally came back home,
so I stayed at home with my dad.
It's getting late.
If there's nothing else,
I...
I'm heading home.
You gave me 20,000 yuan
before I went to college.
I'll pay you back
once I start making money.
Don't go.
What's that supposed to mean?
You...
Let's stop meeting each other.
What do you mean?
Dafu,
haven't we agreed on this before?
Once you graduate
and start your own family,
I'll come over to babysit your children.
As long as you can
take me away from here,
I'll do anything you ask for.
Sister-in-law,
if you want to leave this place
or go somewhere else,
you can go at any time.
You don't need me to take you.
I'm all alone.
I don't know much.
How will I survive out there all my own?
What about me?
I'm not even sure
whether I can stay in the provincial town
after graduation.
How can I take you with me?
You will.
You will, Dafu.
You're good at studying.
You're smart.
You're not like those men
who always see me...
Let go.
Sister-in-law,
we shouldn't have come together.
Let's not meet anymore.
Dafu.
Stop calling my name.
Dafu, no.
You can't do this to me.
I've been nice to you.
You can't just throw me away
like a rag
- like those men did.
- What are you on about?
Don't talk nasty about me.
You can't do this to me.
No.
- Let go.
- Please take me.
- Stop yelling.
Stand up.
Stop pretending.
Sister-in-law.
Answer me.
Master.
You're here.
I've added the charcoal.
You finished the work all by yourself.
Come and wash your hands.
I baked you some flatbread.
There aren't a lot.
I can finish them myself.
Hello?
Dad.
Dafu.
I think I killed someone.
What?
Chun.
A second.
Dafu,
was what you said true?
No way.
Dad.
Why... Why did you do that?
I don't care.
Please help me.
I don't care. Nobody...
Nobody saw me.
I'll just leave her here.
You can't do that.
If the body is found,
the police will track it back to you.
Stop crying.
Don't cry.
Let me think.
Stop crying already.
Listen.
Now,
find a place
to hide the body.
After twelve,
carry her to the boiler room
and put her into the furnace.
Master, you're back.
The door.
Master, close the door.
Master,
the manager went out.
Before he comes back,
I'll cover for you.
You can go home.
Dafu rarely comes home.
You should spend more time with him.
No need.
He's probably still at the cybercafe.
Wang Liang, since we're free,
let's play the Xiangqi.
Again?
You lost three rounds yesterday.
I was cutting you some slack.
Sit over here.
I'm old now. I can't stand the coldness.
All right.
Manager.
You're playing?
Have you added the charcoal?
Yes.
Don't just focus on the game.
Make sure to check
the water gauge regularly.
Oh, right.
Keep an eye on the charcoal in the yard.
Don't worry.
I...
I'll do routine checks.
I do that every day.
Dafu.
Stop yelling.
Dafu, you can't do this.
You can't do this to me.
I've been nice to you.
You can't just throw me away
like a rag
- like those men did.
- What are you on about?
Don't talk nasty about me.
You can't do this to me.
No.
- Let go.
- Please take me.
- Stop yelling.
Dafu,
you're so cruel.
Please take me.
Check.
Well,
I lost.
Wang Liang, you've improved a lot.
Whose turn now?
It's your turn, Master.
Check.
Master,
someone's out there.
Again, check.
Master, I think there's a thief.
I'll go and take a look.
What's there to look at?
I checked just now.
Come. You won again this time.
Let's have another round.
Will you treat me well?
I will.
I will treat you well.
[2012]
[Haotai Hotel]
Officer Luo.
Where are you going at this hour?
It's been a while since I've come back.
I want to drive around here.
With luggage?
Why? Are you leaving Kulu?
No,
of course not.
Well, I came back
and bought a lot of things
for my relatives.
I was about to head over.
That's a lot.
Right.
Dafu.
Ms. Luo, you're here, too.
Oh, Wang Liang.
Dafu, what took you so long?
Yingying is waiting for you at home.
What's wrong with you?
You finally come back.
Why did you stay at a hotel?
Ms. Luo might think we're absurd.
I happened to run into Officer Luo.
We were chatting a little.
I was about to head over.
Good.
Well, Ms. Luo.
After Duoduo left,
Yingying has been upset.
Dafu rarely comes back,
so I was hoping he'd
talk some sense into her.
Go ahead, then.
Let's go, Dafu.
Sure.
We're leaving.
I was tied up,
and my superior kept pressuring me.
I honestly had no choice.
You haven't been back for long.
You must've forgotten about your sister.
That's impossible.
Yingying raised me by herself.
She's the last person I'd forget,
right?
We'll see when we get home.
Go inside. Yingying's waiting for you.
She's in that room.
You're back.
Come on in.
What's that smell
in this room?
Something's rotten.
I wonder how you managed
to put up with it.
I can only stay here, you know.
What are you doing?
Did you forget?
Tomorrow is Duoduo's burial.
I'm sewing clothes for her.
Well,
you can buy anything
from commercial stores.
Why bother doing it yourself?
Yingying,
we talked about it last time.
Dad's body
can't always be left
at the police station
without a burial.
This makes us look bad.
The cops can continue
their investigation,
but since the autopsy is done,
can we take the body back
for the funeral?
Are you back only for this?
Duoduo was your niece.
Her funeral is tomorrow.
You only met her once.
Have you never thought of her?
Of course, I miss her.
But she's gone.
Yingying, you're still young.
You'll have more children.
I've done living with Wang Liang.
That won't do.
Why not?
He's been good to you, no?
What more are you looking for?
I'll wire you 30,000 yuan
when I get back.
Treat yourself to something nice.
Get some supplements.
Women stop overthinking
when they have children.
50,000 yuan.
Is that enough?
Why are you staring at me?
Dafu.
Don't call me Dafu.
I've changed the name on my ID.
Okay.
Dazhi.
Is 50,000 yuan
the price you set for me and Duoduo?
That's harsh.
Haven't I done enough for you both?
Yingying,
you've always been kind to me
when we were kids.
Yes,
I have.
Mom passed away when we were little.
I'm only two years older than you,
but I've always felt like your mom.
Exactly.
The elder sister has the duty of a mom.
Does that mean
I have to sacrifice for you,
right?
It's not that.
Yingying,
stay with Wang Liang.
I'll take care of you when you're old.
What do you mean by that?
You want me to waste my whole life,
huh?
Yingying,
you're my sister.
don't worry.
I'll provide for you.
If you need anything,
call me anytime.
I'm leaving.
Dafu.
What else?
Mom died early.
I was eight,
and you were six.
Mom called me to her bedside
and told me
to look after you
after her passing.
I was terrified.
I told her, "I can't.
Mom, I can't."
But she was strict
and said I had to, no matter what.
Then, she died.
Over the years,
I don't remember
much of what Mom did to me.
I just remember that.
I...
What's the point of bringing this up?
Is 50,000 not enough?
It's enough.
What I'm saying is
I've done more than enough
as a sister.
You can go.
Dafu,
offer incense for Dad.
After Duoduo's funeral tomorrow,
you can go back.
I'll take care of Dad.
Duoduo,
do you hate me
when I sent you over
to Great-grandma's place?
Mom, what does hate mean?
[2011]
Duoduo, wait for me here.
No. I want you to hug me.
It only takes a few minutes.
Wait here, all right?
I don't want to.
Well, sit here.
Be good.
Stay here.
Don't run around.
Excuse me.
I'm very sorry.
Your child has been diagnosed
with leukemia,
and it's quite severe.
It's reached the mid-stage.
Is it curable?
If it's in the early stage,
the chances of recovery are higher.
But now that it's in the mid-stage,
it's not totally hopeless, though,
but the best solution is
to get a hematopoietic stem cell transplant
as soon as possible.
And that requires a compatible donor.
Also,
I have to let you know.
The costs will be hefty.
The initial expenses
are thirty to fifty thousand,
and the later ones are unknown.
In some lucky cases,
it costs around tens of thousands.
Well, for her case,
will you agree to treat her?
Mom.
Dr. Wu, you can come up
with a treatment plan.
Our family will take the matching tests.
Neither of you is a match.
Even her birth mother isn't a match?
Mr. Liu, it's very common
for the mother not to be a match.
Liu, where's the child's dad?
Get him tested quickly.
May... Maybe I can talk to him
to give it a shot.
The child's health is the priority.
Let's not worry about anything else now.
Right.
Not just the child's dad,
but any potential donor
can be tested,
like relatives and friends.
Anyone willing to help can come.
Do you have any other family members?
Yes.
I have a younger brother.
He's busy. Don't trouble him...
Mr. Liu,
there have been cases
where the uncle is a match,
even when the mother isn't.
Anyway,
it's best to have
any potential donor tested.
Thank you so much, Dr. Wu.
Hello, Yingying?
Yes?
I need your help.
Duoduo is sick.
Leukemia.
She needs a bone marrow transplant.
Dad and I aren't a match.
Can you find the time
to come back and get tested?
Dazhi, please listen to me.
It won't take your bone marrow.
If you're a match,
it just requires a tube of your blood.
We'll extract
the hematopoietic stem cell from it,
and Duoduo can be saved.
Please find time to come back.
If you're busy,
I'll bring Duoduo to you.
Duoduo?
Wait.
Yingying, I thought
you didn't care about her.
She's my daughter.
I gave birth to her.
She's sick
because I neglected her.
Just thinking about it
makes me feel guilty,
so I have to save her.
I have a feeling
that you can save her.
Yingying.
Just arrange a time, yes?
I'm working on several projects.
Every one of them is a major project.
I really
don't have time.
If you're busy,
I'll bring Duoduo to you.
- City hospitals are more experienced.
- No.
Yingying, you don't have to come.
You know
I can't be the matching donor.
Dazhi, listen.
I see this illness
as a punishment.
If you save Duoduo,
you're saving me, too.
You have to come back.
Yingying,
I'm in the middle
of a meeting.
I can't step out for long.
I'll get back to you
once I'm free.
I'm begging you.
Come on, let's drink.
It's my family.
They called me.
Duoduo.
Mom, hug!
Come. Let me hug you.
What's Wang Liang's relationship
with this child?
He's Duoduo's god uncle.
Here's the thing.
I've told you about this before.
The chances of a match are higher
among family members.
Am I clear?
Where's the child's dad?
Is Wang Liang's result out yet?
Not yet.
Didn't you mention you have a brother?
Can he come?
He can.
I'll give him a call.
Dr. Wu,
if no one in the family matches,
what else can I do?
Given Duoduo's current situation,
a bone marrow transplant
is the best treatment plan.
Of course, if you're not confident,
take the child to hospitals
in the provincial town
and get a second opinion.
Thank you.
Dazhi,
it's been so long since I called you.
When are you coming back?
I'm busy.
I can't.
In that case,
I'll bring Duoduo over tomorrow.
Wait.
Don't come, Yingying.
I'm going on a business trip
tomorrow morning.
I'll be away for a month.
Duoduo can't wait for that long.
Dazhi,
please help Duoduo.
I'm begging you.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have had her.
She's your niece.
Enough said.
She's a living person.
Just stop it.
Is she really related to me by blood?
You know the reason.
I won't be a match.
Well, that's it.
We'll talk
when I get back from the trip.
Bravo!
You sing so well, Mr. Zhang.
Answer me.
Didn't you always
not care about the girl?
Whether I care about her,
she's still my daughter.
I have to save her.
Go and get Dazhi back today.
He's right.
You're adopted.
He won't be a match.
I want to give it a try.
I'll give up if it doesn't work.
What if it works?
What if...
What if it does work,
are you going to take his bone marrow?
I don't want his bone marrow.
I only want a tube of blood
to exact the stem cells.
Don't worry.
It won't affect his body.
It won't affect?
If so, why doesn't anyone donate?
What do you mean?
Is Dazhi's blood
really more important
than my daughter's life?
Don't you forget
how he managed to get this far.
I didn't mean that.
I didn't say anything.
Fine, I'll go.
I will go, okay?
He's busy with his work.
Why do you want him
to come all the way back?
He must come back today.
If not, I'm not sure what I will do.
What do you want to do?
Do you want to ruin our family?
I may
if my patience runs out.
I'll wait for your update.
Duoduo, don't move.
Hold on, Duoduo.
All right.
Almost done.
Duoduo, it's almost done.
Liu.
His bone marrow
doesn't match, too.
You have a brother, right?
Get him here
for the matching test quickly.
It didn't match.
How could that be?
Dr. Wu, is this a mistake?
How could we not...
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
I'll have my brother come.
Sure. As soon as possible.
Hello?
You're back?
I'm in the yard.
Where are you?
I'm here.
Where's Dazhi?
Why isn't he here?
Why didn't he come with you?
Don't yell.
Keep it down.
It's not that he refused to come,
he's too busy.
He's on a business trip now.
His job is important.
His superior wouldn't let him leave.
That's a good thing.
Oh, right.
He asked me...
He asked me to bring you some money.
I'll give you all the money.
Buy something for Duoduo...
I don't want his money!
You...
His job is more important
than Duoduo's life?
It's not that, Yingying.
Let go.
No, Yingying.
Please listen to me.
Well,
many years have passed.
You can't drag Dazhi
and me into this
because of your daughter.
Our family will be ruined.
So be it.
But...
♪I'm going to sleep♪
♪I will learn magic in my dream♪
♪To freeze my mom and dad's♪
♪Most beautiful face♪
Many years have passed.
You can't drag Dazhi into this
because of your daughter.
♪Without fear♪
Duoduo?
Wait.
Yingying, I thought
you didn't care about her.
She's sick
because I neglected her.
Just thinking about this
makes me feel guilty,
so I have to save her.
I have a feeling
that you can save her.
♪To the warmest palm♪
I'm begging you, Dazhi.
Please come here.
Please help her.
Doctor, is there any other method?
Doctor, please get me tested again.
Manager Wang, please calm down.
♪Light up all the fairy tales♪
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have had her.
She's your niece.
She's a living person.
Enough said.
The test result won't lie.
There's nothing we can do
if you are not a match.
Is she really related to me by blood?
You know the reason.
I won't be a match.
Mom, can you hold me a little longer?
Duoduo, be good
You need a complete rest alone.
Mom, I had a dream just now.
It was about the flower
Uncle talked about.
Black and huge.
So beautiful.
Let's go to bed.
Mom, have you seen the flower
Uncle talked about?
Duoduo, do you hate me
when I sent you over
to Great-grandma's place?
Mom, what does hate mean?
Mr. Liu,
I'm so sorry about that.
Are you all right?
The technician was installing
the surveillance in your room,
and the breaker tripped.
It's fixed now.
I'm truly sorry about that.
The camera is installed.
Well, you see...
Sure. Thank you, Mr. Liu.
Wang.
Have you done installing?
Yes.
All right. Good.
Mr. Yang.
Good job.
You see, the camera is installed.
I knew it.
Thank you, Mr. Yang.
Sure. Off you go.
♪Silence♪
♪After the sandstorm♪
♪Thunder♪
♪Knocks on the cloud♪
♪Whisper♪
♪Before the dawn♪
♪Criminal♪
♪Through it all♪
♪Silence♪
♪After the sandstorm♪
♪Ruins♪
♪Throughout the ground♪
♪Darkness♪
♪Suddenly comes♪
♪I know♪
♪Where to leave me alone♪
♪Far away safe and sound♪
♪Night's so far so long♪
♪Faint light shining front♪
♪Guide me to hometown♪