Don't you know
your own status?
Going to a
slum like that.
Don't you know
how dangerous
it is?
Are you looking
down on me
right now?
What do
you mean?
You probably
don't
know, do you?
That my
father also
grew up
in a slum.
Since you look
down on Luna,
look down on
people in
the slum,
that means...
you look down
on me too.
Sorry.
I... I
didn't know.
You were born
into a rich
family from
the start.
There are
still many
things you
don't know.
Even about
Thanya...
you probably
just want her,
but you don't
really care
about her
feelings, do you?
I am at my wits'
end with you too.
Wait.
Give me the
invitation too.
(How can he
act so relaxed)
(in a place
like this?)
Oh.
Are you ready?
Fight,
fight, fight!
Is anyone
ready to fight?
Whoever
gets pushed
out of the
circle...
loses.
Begin!
Come on!
Fight a bit!
Fight!
Great, great!
Hey!
Someone
like you...
has to face me.
Hey!
Here we go!
Go for it!