Don't get
frisky tonight.
Relax, I'll
behave.
(Philip)
Logic,
long time
no see.
You're still
as boring
as ever.
Philip,
you're even
more annoying
than in the
tabloids.
And who are you?
Leo,
Logic's date?
You'd look
better if you
were on my
arm instead.
Philip,
this is an
official event.
Please conduct
yourself
properly.
Don't
lecture me,
you Prime
Minister's son.
Next year's
the election.
You and
your father
will be
crawling to me.
Don't forget
how much
my country
has invested
here.
So confident
in yourself,
aren't you?
But Leo,
I want to…
Don't you
dare touch me.
Hey.
Leo,
if you act
like this,
I can't
protect you.
A coward
like him
isn't worthy
of you.
And what business
is it of yours,
Prince Philip?
Logic
belongs to me.
He surpasses
you in every way.
Do you really
believe that?
Leo,
I told you,
he's useless.