=Hold a Court Now=
=Episode 17=
Want me to give you a lift?
No, thanks.
I'm meeting a client.
I'm actually running late.
I'll drop off your grandma's cured meat
at your place tomorrow.
Just keep it for yourself.
Grandma meant for you to have it.
Don't use too much salt
when you cook it.
(Heavenly Goddess,)
(when I broke my leg at six years old,)
(I prayed for things to go my way.)
(I asked for a divine warrior
to come save me.)
(And then,)
(over twenty years later,)
(you sent me Machine Shen?)
(A Machine Shen bound
by conflict-of-interest rules, no less.)
Hey, you scared me!
How long have you been there?
I said hello to you
the second you walked in.
You did?
When you got back,
I asked why you were home so early.
You said you took
a taxi straight from the airport.
You're way too young
to be having memory loss.
At this rate,
I'll be the one
looking after you in your old age.
Aren't you playing ball today?
I was supposed
to play one-on-one with Mr. Xu,
but of all things,
he had to go and sprain his ankle.
I think he chickened out,
but he wouldn't admit it.
Since I was already out,
I figured I'd stay out.
So, I came here to kill some time.
Am I bothering you?
Yes.
Fine.
I'm leaving.
Remember, you're kicking me out.
Don't call me irresponsible.
Do you even have anywhere to go?
I'll find a random game at the court.
If your sister-in-law calls...
Just...
I'll tell her
you're closing a big deal.
A billion-yuan deal.
Let's not exaggerate.
Keep it realistic.
But you know,
you can find leads at the court.
That guy who pulled an arm?
His case is still ongoing.
Too bad Old Li beat me to it.
Did you pack my heart pills?
Here, take these.
They're specialties from back home.
Take some.
In case your blood sugar drops,
you can have one right away.
Thanks.
Take it easy on the court.
Don't go spraining an ankle.
Always so exasperating.
Dried chrysanthemums...
Sausages...
Why'd you buy so much local stuff?
None of these even has labels.
What do you mean "no labels"?
I bought them at a farmer's market.
Fine.
Since when do you eat candy?
You've never had a sweet tooth.
Not mine. I grabbed the wrong bag.
Then whose is it?
Who was with you
on this business trip?
I told you already.
I went alone.
Well, a local court clerk helped out.
I just saw the villagers at the market
and picked up a few gifts on a whim.
Some are for my colleagues too.
You?
Buying gifts for colleagues?
Don't try to fool me.
I'm your mother.
What reason would I have to lie?
Please.
The over-explaining
tells me you have something to hide.
But I'll stop asking.
I'll just wait for you
to slip up on your own.
Right.
I'll cook these for dinner tonight.
I'm not staying.
I have to head out soon.
Your skewers are ready.
I tweaked
the sauce a little.
Give me some feedback.
Try it.
The girls need to talk.
About your job?
Got it. Protocol first.
I'm recusing myself.
Enjoy your food.
Thanks, Yongjiu.
This drawing is incredible.
This baby definitely likes bold flavors.
Stop calling it a "baby."
To me,
it's still just a fertilized egg.
Thinking of it that way
is too much pressure.
Look, if you genuinely
didn't want kids,
I wouldn't say a word.
But you clearly love kids.
You're just too hard on yourself.
You want everything to be perfect.
We can't control
if they'll even be successful.
But giving the child a home full of love
is entirely up to us.
And you and Xiao Bing?
You're the gold standard for couples.
You'll give that child
100% of your heart.
There's nothing to worry about.
But as judges,
we see the worst-case scenarios.
It makes me over-analyze everything.
I worry that if I mess up
even one step,
I'm the one failing the child.
Don't get inside your own head.
It's obvious Xiao Bing is
going to be a softie.
He claims he doesn't mind
and will follow my lead,
but in reality,
he's read every parenting book
cover to cover.
He's even started
planning the nursery.
That just shows how much
he values you and the baby.
He's going to be a great father.
If you think of a person's life,
from start to finish,
as Version 1.0...
then parenthood
is like Version 2.0.
Because
it gives you a chance
to re-examine your own childhood.
You get a second chance
to make up for all the regrets
you had while growing up.
If you're lucky enough
to have grandkids,
that's when
you get to fix the mistakes
you made while raising your own kids
in your middle age.
So, basically an upgrade to Version 3.0?
Jing,
do you think I'm just being selfish?
Don't mind my rambling.
The truth is,
everyone is handed
a different script in life.
But having children
isn't just about pressure and duty.
It's a life experience
that simply can't be replaced
by anything else.
A child is the glue
that holds a marriage together.
For the grandparents,
they're an elixir of youth.
Think about it.
Just seeing Fei sitting there,
perfectly still.
She looks so tiny.
My whole world
just lights up instantly.
Is it a total loss of humanity,
or a complete moral collapse?
Let's find out together.
You don't want to miss this.
Follow Rui's Legal Lens.
That's all for today's segment
on AI-generated rumors targeting women.
In our next episode,
I'll be covering
hidden cameras in female locker rooms,
investigations into
gender-biased hiring,
and victims of online dating scams.
As my followers already know,
the details of the investigation
or the specific
sentences the criminals receive
aren't the main focus here
at Rui's Legal Lens.
We care more about women's safety
and protecting their fundamental rights.
Alright.
Lian is calling me for dinner,
so that's it for today's show.
Don't forget to
like, save,
and follow Rui's Legal Lens.
Hello.
Are you guys closed yet?
Not yet. Please, come in.
Thank you.
Oh, you're injured.
Yes.
It looks pretty serious.
I'm okay. I can manage.
Take it slow.
Have a seat. I'll get you some water.
Thank you.
And your name is?
I'm Lu Huilan.
Let me help you with that.
Alright, thank you.
So,
what happened?
I was on my e-bike,
taking my father to the doctor,
and I hit a car.
Who was found responsible?
I was.
I imagine the medical bills are high.
Over 30,000 yuan so far.
My leg is fractured.
The doctor says
it isn't healing well,
so I might need more surgery.
And as for the driver
and the car,
there might be other damages.
Were you at fault,
or was it shared liability?
I'm fully liable.
Are you planning to sue the police
for a wrongful fault determination?
Did you file for an administrative review?
No, that's not...
Look,
I really was 100% at fault.
I ran a red light.
Then, why have you come to see me?
My two brothers are suing me.
Wait,
the car you hit
belonged to your brothers?
No.
I was on my e-bike,
taking my father to see a doctor.
When we crashed,
my father died.
Now I'm facing a lawsuit.
They want me
to pay 300,000 yuan.
Please,
you have to help me.
I really don't know what to do.
Take a breath, Ms. Lu.
It's not that I won't help you,
but look at the facts.
This is a traffic accident.
It's crystal clear.
A judge will see that instantly.
The judge just needs to figure out
how the law applies here.
Honestly, any judge
with a shred of conscience
will reduce your liability anyway.
You don't necessarily
even need a lawyer.
I'd hate to see you
waste your money here.
But I've never been in a courtroom.
I'm so nervous.
What am I even supposed to say?
Most people haven't been to court.
It's enough to make
anyone's blood pressure spike.
Tell you what.
If you're really that anxious,
feel free
to just stop by.
We'll have some tea together
and calm your nerves.
Because if you sit here any longer,
my conscience
won't be able to hold back my ambition.
I'll fast-talk you
into signing a contract.
Trust me.
Just let the judge handle it.
And once you leave,
don't go running off
to some other law firm.
It takes two to make a baby, you know.
You should at least consider
how Xiao Bing feels.
I know the logic.
But it's different
when it's your own life.
I'm just completely lost.
You're always calling us indecisive.
Look at you now.
You're overthinking every little thing.
This isn't your usual self.
How are things with Yongjiu?
Are you two back on track?
Hardly.
He've been home for two hours,
and still reeked of mutton.
But it's okay.
A few years ago,
he was the rising star
at the Intermediate People's Court.
And years later,
and he's the local legend
of grilled skewers.
Right before you got here,
he was unclogging a sewage pipe.
God, the stench was unbearable.
Shh! Keep it down.
But back then,
he didn't exactly have a choice
but to leave the court.
He talks about it all the time.
He blames himself
for not taking care of Fei.
Otherwise,
none of it would've happened.
Has he considered
returning to the legal field?
Actually,
we were just talking about that.
After the incident with Fei,
she needed
round-the-clock care.
I offered to quit my job,
but he wouldn't let me.
He ignored Chief Judge Feng's objections
and handed in his resignation.
He spent six months at home.
Aside from speaking
to Fei for her therapy,
he barely spoke at all.
I know him.
Walking away from the job he loved
and from his entire career
is eating him alive.
One of my seniors
is the Legal Director
at an energy company.
He's a fellow alum.
He reached out the other day
looking for a Legal Supervisor.
They want someone
doing the internal audits,
specifically someone
with experience in economic crimes.
Could you ask Yongjiu for me?
See if he'd be interested.
Sure. I'll bring it up when I get home.
It's too chaotic
to have a real talk here.
(You're afraid to look at me right now.)
(Is it because you're having)
(second thoughts about us?)
Hi, Judge Shen.
Remember me?
We just saw each other this morning.
This is for you.
What do you think?
I honestly believe that
when it comes to raising a child,
money isn't the most important thing.
They need someone who truly loves them,
someone who's actually there
so they can feel cherished.
That's a gift that lasts a lifetime.
(Take your medicine
exactly as prescribed.)
(Once Grandma finishes this month's supply,
I'll make sure to mail the next batch.)
Are you okay?
♪Let me be your safe haven♪
(I want to be the one
who takes care of you.)
(But I'm in a dilema.)
(I don't want us to repeat)
(the same mistakes
as Jiang Feng and Ms. Lou.)
(He usually looks)
(so cold and detached,)
(but he's surprisingly empathetic.)
Can you send me your ID number?
I want to sign you up
for one of those unlimited
flight passes.
♪ In your world ♪
♪I want to be in your world♪
♪I'll be there for you
until the very end♪
How can you sleep
with your clothes on like that?
Come on, stop being lazy.
Get up and eat.
Not even food can tempt you today?
What's wrong?
Still haven't adjusted
after getting back from home?
Shen Xiezhi confessed
his feelings to me.
So,
what did you say?
What else could I say?
I turned him down.
Impressive.
What's so impressive about it?
I'm brilliant
with a bright future ahead.
I'm going to be
a top-tier lawyer at a top-tier law firm.
In my position,
do I really have a choice?
Am I supposed to
throw my career away for him?
I get it.
So you're basically
married to your career.
In that case,
just don't come crying to me in regrets
when you're old and alone.
Smells amazing.
What is that?
See? I told you
I brought back something good.
Since you won't get up, fine.
You can eat in bed.
Happy now, my lady?
Hurry up.
You'll feel better once you eat.
You're the best.
Exactly.
How could I possibly end up alone
with you around?
Think about it.
If you're turning down
a guy like Shen Xiezhi now,
what's going to happen
once you're at the top
of the food chain?
Who'll be good enough for you then?
When I'm at the top,
I won't need to look up.
There'll be plenty of fish
in the sea below me.
Do you think
Shen Xiezhi is going to wait around
pining for you, do you?
I'll just find someone else then.
Seriously?
Why not?
I don't even
recognize you anymore, Qin Rui.
What?
Now you're talking back?
You're clearly crazy about him,
yet you still said no.
Let me guess what's actually going on.
Stop guessing.
You're just hungry.
Just go. I want to sleep.
I've got it.
There's only one logical explanation.
He's a judge and you're a lawyer.
Conflict-of-interest rules mean
you can't practice
in the same jurisdiction.
He's at a lower court for now,
so you could just switch districts.
But if he ever makes it
to the High Court,
or even the Supreme Court,
you'll end up just like Lou Yue.
Shut up.
I'm telling you,
I am not walking away from my career.
It's alright.
You got a lecture
and a rejection.
Look at me.
I've been through it.
But I'm still alive.
We are nothing alike.
I've been thinking about it.
Qin Rui isn't actually wrong.
She's just not the type of person
to choose love over her career.
I blame myself.
I couldn't help myself,
I've made it awkward for her.
I get it,
but since you two have hit the brakes
and there's no future there anyway,
I've got some news
that might help you snap out of it.
The High Court
just posted a notice
for a lateral transfer.
Three openings in the criminal division.
It's open to the entire city.
If you're qualified, you can apply.
Competition will be a bloodbath,
but I think
you've got a real shot at it.
What?
Why are you hesitating
on a chance like this?
I just don't know
if my odds are that great.
Stop overthinking it.
Your love life is dead,
so you might as well
go all in on your career.
That old scoundrel is playing my mother.
He's in his forties. My mom's over sixty.
He's a year younger than I am!
Plus, my mom's health is failing.
What could he possibly want?
Money.
What else can it be?
It's plain as day.
But middle-aged women
always fall for that act.
He's what people call
a real ladies' man.
Actually,
is our judge
a man or a woman?
If it's a middle-aged woman,
he might get her
with his smooth talk.
That would be a disaster.
That's impossible.
The guy can't be that charming.
I'm not sure which judge
we've been assigned to.
But if it is a woman,
it'll likely be Judge Shu.
She sees right through people.
She's reliable.
He won't be able to fool her.
Is this womanizer...
What was the plaintiff's name again?
- He Xiuguang.
He Xiuguang.
Don't worry, your mom won't fall for it.
Wait, that's not the judge
you mentioned earlier.
It was a three-character name.
Right.
Three characters.
Ying Danian?
No.
The name was kind of a tongue-twister.
I think the surname
started with a Chen?
No, it wasn't Chen.
Actually, at Qingcheng Court,
there aren't any judges named Chen.
Hold on, let me double-check.
Yeah, take a look.
It's Shen.
Shen Xie...
- Shen Xiezhi. Yeah, that's the one.
- Right.
Quite a mouthful.
By the way,
are you two close?
Not really.
We've met. I know him.
Don't sweat it.
He won't fall for He Xiuguang's tricks.
Judges have seen it all.
I hope you're right.
Just hearing his name
makes my skin crawl.
Good morning, Judge Shen.
Judge Shen.
(Courtroom 2: Shen Xiezhi,
Chen Xianghui, Qin Rui)
(Family Court)
I will now read the rules of the court.
To maintain order
and ensure the integrity
of these proceedings,
per the Court Rules
of the People's Republic of China,
the following persons may not attend.
One, minors,
unless authorized by the court.
Two, intoxicated
or mentally ill persons.
Three, those deprived
of their political rights.
All parties, participants,
and spectators
must adhere to the following.
One, everyone present
must follow the directions
of the Presiding Judge.
Two,
objections to the collegial panel or its members
may not be raised during the hearing.
Four,
(Proof of Service. Long-term Civil Cases...)
do not move around the courtroom.
Five, spectators are forbidden
from asking questions.
Six, no applauding
or creating disturbances.
(Litigation and Proof)
Seven, smoking is prohibited.
Eight,
before entering,
all mobile devices must be switched off.
Spectators with comments
regarding the proceedings
may submit them in writing
to the People's Court
after the session has adjourned.
The reading of the rules is complete.
All rise.
And now,
please welcome the panel.
♪Sweeping away the dust between us♪
You may take a seat now.
♪Searching for the warmth we had♪
♪Like a migrating flock♪
Judge Shu...
Please, stay seated.
Careful, you might fall.
Thank you.
Sit down.
(Tianhai City People's Court)
Court is now in session.
(In session)
"Entering the gate of my longing,"
"one learns of my sorrow's depth."
(Defendant, Authorized Representative)
"Long is the longing, long is the memory."
"Brief was the spark,
yet the yearning is infinite."
Excuse me, Plaintiff.
My classical Chinese is a bit rusty.
(Authorized Representative, Plaintiff)
Sorry, Your Honor.
Let me put it in plain English.
It was a bright spring day.
Back then,
I had truly hit rock bottom.
The double blow
of losing my love and my career
left me utterly hopeless.
In fact,
I had even begun
to contemplate ending it all.
But I never could have imagined
that the day
would become
the luckiest day of my life.
Because it was the day
in the park
when I met her.
She was so delicate,
so incredibly gentle.
She just sat there,
listening to my grief,
soothing my very soul.
When I reached the most painful part,
she held my hand.
She felt so much for me,
she was literally trembling.
My mother had just
had surgery for a stroke.
She was still in recovery!
When I behold the violet past prime,
and sable curls
all silvered o'er with white,
when lofty trees I see are
barren of leaves.
It only recently
offered shade to the panting herd.
Who are you calling names?
Who's a herd?
Summer's green,
bundled up in sheaves,
is carried away
like an old man to his grave.
And so I must
worry for your beauty.
For one day
you'll end up in the scrap heap of time.
You're the piece of junk here!
Calm down.
My mom picked you up
from the trash heap.
Defendant,
control yourself.
Your Honor...
How about Your Majesty?
Speak like a normal person!
Sun Daming!
Ms. Qian, try to stay calm.
Your children aren't
against you getting remarried.
They just don't think
Mr. He is the right choice for you.
Why exactly am I not the right choice?
Just because
she's a little older than me?
Twenty-three years.
What's wrong with that gap?
Does age really matter
when it comes to love?
If an older man
can be with a young woman
and call it a perfect match,
then why can't we?
Or is it that it's only true love
when the man is older?
Does the reverse not count?
Now that you're older,
do you think
you're no longer worthy of being loved?
If women keep
devaluing themselves like this,
we'll never see true gender equality.
Forget the mediation. We're done here.
Look at her, she's been sobbing all day.
Judge Shu,
just give us a ruling already.
Whatever you decide, we'll accept it.
Exactly. Just rule on it.
We're waiting for
the inheritance to be split
so we can finally bury our father.
We want to buy him a decent plot.
It's the least we can do
to show our respect.
Losing your father
has been devastating for you.
But your own sister
was seriously injured
and is still in a wheelchair.
Aren't you concerned about her future?
That's a completely separate issue.
Once the assets are divided,
even if she
hits rock bottom later on
and comes to us for help,
we won't just turn our backs on her.
Right.
But she has to take responsibility
for the mistakes she made.
A life for a life, a debt for a debt.
You're a judge.
I'm sure you see things
on a level we don't.
We can't let family ties hijack the law.
We shouldn't let sympathy
get in the way of justice.
Don't you agree?
Hold on.
A life for a life?
Who exactly are you accusing?
Who else?
Her.
She's the one who killed my dad!
Calm down.
Look, as her brothers,
it's not like we want to
see her behind bars.
But the fact remains that
she's the reason Dad is dead.
Dad's face was literally turning purple!
I called for an ambulance.
They told me
it'd take an hour to get there.
Our road is so narrow that
the vehicle couldn't
even reach the house.
I panicked. I didn't know what to do.
So what if it was an hour?
You couldn't have just waited?
If it was really too late,
then it was just meant to be.
If the ambulance was delayed,
we could've sued
the emergency center for damages.
A payout from a government agency?
That wouldn't have been a small amount.
It'd be over a million, right?
Exactly.
Leave professional matters
to the professionals.
My wife is a nurse.
She says if you don't know
the extent of the injuries,
you have to keep the person still.
Just think.
If you'd given him his meds
and waited for help at home,
our dear father
wouldn't have been run over by a car!
Unbelievable.
The death certificate
explicitly states
that he died of sudden cardiac death.
It was an illness.
He didn't die from the accident.
But...
But my dad only died because her crash
scared the life out of him!
Exactly. She can't
just walk away from this.
Not a chance.
Am I right, Judge?
If you still have
objections regarding the liability
or the cause of death,
I suggest you call the police.
Let them conduct a formal investigation.
If it's a criminal matter,
it will be moved
to the Criminal Division.
As a Family Court judge,
I have no jurisdiction
to settle that for you.
Look, we aren't heartless.
She is our sister, after all.
You make it sound
like we're desperate
to throw her in prison.
Exactly. There's no need for that.
If there are no objections,
we will proceed
with the cause of death on record.
But what about her neglect?
Fine.
Let's stick with sudden cardiac death.
Mr. He,
I truly admire your passion
and your absolute devotion to love.
But love and marriage are
two very different things.
Love
can be a sudden, impulsive rush.
But marriage cannot.
Marriage is about the daily grind,
the chores, and the bills.
It requires shared values
and compatibility.
But from what we've gathered,
you have no stable job,
no permanent residence,
and certainly no steady income.
Ms. Qin,
are these
mainstream marriage values?
Your thinking is so traditional.
They are ancient and rigid.
Have you really never
experienced a love
worth risking everything for?
If so, I honestly feel sorry for you.
When true love finds you,
it leaves you breathless.
It leaves you completely distracted.
Even a single day apart
makes you lose your appetite.
For her sake,
you no longer fear aging or death.
For her, you'd take on the whole world.
I don't blame you
for questioning me.
That's the tragedy of your own lives.
Because you've never experienced
how sacred and beautiful
a love like this can be.
You've never tasted
fate's sweetest nectar.
I can't take this anymore.
This is disgusting.
Judge,
didn't you say
you wanted to see evidence?
I have one more piece here.
Please, take a look.
Sister,
let's think back for a second.
Three months ago,
I told you to get a critical
illness policy for Dad.
At the time,
(Critical Illness Insurance Contract)
that agent, Mr. Zhao,
came by the house several times.
The paperwork was all filled out.
Even you thought the price was fair.
I left the purchase to you.
I trusted you.
Now, three months have passed,
and Dad died from sudden cardiac death.
The insurance company
should be paying out.
I think it's time
you gave us a real explanation.
He is asking you a question.
Speak up!
I picked out a policy
with 500,000 yuan
in coverage for Dad.
(Chat History)
Sudden cardiac death
was definitely covered.
Sister.
That's 500,000 yuan!
Because you were too cheap
to pay the premium,
we're out half a million!
Do you even realize that?
I...
I just got busy and forgot.
You're a housewife with no children.
Your only duty
was taking care of Dad!
So what have you been doing?
Judge, you heard her yourself.
She just admitted it.
She forgot to pay.
And now we're out 500,000 yuan
because of her.
She has to compensate us for that.
We aren't asking for much.
That 500,000 yuan should be
split three ways.
I'll even round down the change.
Just pay the two of us
160,000 yuan each.
Wait, I thought it was 300,000?
That was
for killing Dad in the accident.
The Judge told me to drop that for now.
Let's keep these issues separate.
Did you or did you not
make a mistake here?
You need to
take responsibility for this.
Honestly, the money is the least of it.
My brother and I
haven't even made you
pay for Dad's life yet.
Exactly.
We didn't even get to say goodbye.
Yeah.
Wait a second.
Look at this.
(Coverage Scope)
Sudden cardiac death isn't
listed under the coverage.
Acute myocardial infarction
isn't the same thing
as sudden cardiac death?
Sorry to interrupt,
but I should clarify.
A friend of mine lost his father
to sudden cardiac death as well.
He had critical illness insurance too,
but the company refused to pay.
There are many triggers
for sudden cardiac death,
including myocardial infarction.
So even if you'd bought the policy,
it might not have paid out.
Now hold on, young lady.
Explain yourself.
Just because
your friend's father got denied,
what makes you think they'd deny my dad?
I only said it was a possibility.
Possibility?
Don't just make things up.
There's an easy fix.
We'll just order an autopsy.
Lu Huilan,
do you have the guts to let them
perform an autopsy on Dad?
If the results come back
and the insurance denies us,
then we will drop this.
But if
it was covered under the policy,
then we want that 500,000 yuan.
- Not a penny less.
- You'll cough it all up.
Do you accept it?
Mr. He.
Let's put the essence of love
and the signals of its arrival
aside for a moment.
These topics are far too grandiose.
Let's discuss
what you're actually after
in this relationship.
Before you and your love showed up,
Ms. Qian lived a blissful,
harmonious life with her children.
But since you arrived with this love,
it's true
that my clients were initially opposed.
But as of now,
they've consented to your marriage.
They even let you
move into Ms. Qian's apartment
within the Second Ring.
Normally, you'd be satisfied
and simply enjoy
the fruits of your relationship.
So why did you
pressure Ms. Qian to sue her children
to revoke the deed to six properties?
Mother only gave them those houses
on one condition.
They had to be filial.
How have we not been filial?
Mom, tell him!
They interfered with her marriage,
destroyed her happiness,
and withheld her income.
They constantly criticize
the man she loves,
leaving her in tears day and night.
They turned their backs on her.
We're just returning the favor.
Everything I do
is purely to protect my darling.
I don't have a selfish bone in my body.
Ms. Qin,
why do you always equate love with money?
Do you really believe
that people without money
aren't entitled to love?
Mr. He,
in my opinion,
those who can't put bread on the table
have no business talking about love.
How hideous.
How vulgar.
How materialistic.
Birds of a feather flock together.
If a lawyer has such a hideous soul,
her clients can't be much better.
Say that again!
Plaintiff.
Watch your tone.
No personal attacks.
You're all still so young.
If you had the perspective
that comes with age, you'd understand.
There's always more money to be made,
and another ladder to climb.
The hurdles of reality never end.
But life is fleeting.
In this short existence,
love
might be a fleeting moment,
a mere drop in the vast ocean.
If you don't seize it,
it's gone forever.
Even if you're drowning
in wealth one day,
what's the point?
Am I right, Judge Shen?
So, tell me.
What did Guixiang and I do wrong?
We just chose to be brave
and give love everything we had.
In this dry, empty life,
when you
find a soulmate like Guixiang,
would you really walk away?
If you were drowning in darkness
and saw a ray of light,
wouldn't you reach for it?
If you knew
that letting her go meant
never feeling that spark again,
could you still turn your back on her?
Would any of you?
Could you?
Ms. Qin,
why do you always equate love
with money?
Do you really believe
that people without money
aren't entitled to love?
(There's always more money to be made,)
(and another ladder to climb.)
The hurdles of reality never end.
But life is fleeting.
In this short existence,
love might be a fleeting moment,
a mere drop in the vast ocean.
If you don't seize it,
it's gone forever.
Come in.
Oh my goodness.
It never ends.
What happened now?
The same two mama's boys.
Who else?
I seriously don't get it.
They can barely take care of themselves.
Why on earth do they have to have kids?
And both sets of parents too.
They've failed one generation.
Why are they so eager
to mess up the next one?
In that whole family,
excluding the baby in diapers
in the stroller,
not a single person is sane.
Do you know how badly
I wanted to scream at them today?
"I'm begging you,
leave the child out of this!"
If you can't raise them,
at least take some responsibility
once they're here.
Can't they just learn?
Honestly,
I'm so fed up!
I feel much better now.
Jing,
how are things with Yongjiu?
What do you mean?
About having a second kid.
When did I ever say
I wanted another one?
Well, you're burning
the calories anyway.
Might as well get a baby out of it.
A happy couple like you should
do your part for society.
We aren't burning any.
None.
What do you mean by that?
He isn't in the mood.
Maybe it's just our age.
It didn't happen.
That's nonsense. You aren't old at all.
This definitely isn't normal.
Jing,
if I were you,
I'd take him to see a doctor.
You know,
even just some medicine
to get things back on track.
Never mind.
Come on.
Fei's class is almost over.
I have to pick her up.
I'll come with you.
What for?
I'm taking her home with me today.
♪All the little things
between you and me♪
♪Woven into our lives♪
♪The building blocks of life♪
♪Shape the sky above us♪
♪Are you doing alright?♪
♪What are you struggling for?♪
♪Some questions weigh like mountains♪
♪How do we piece life back together?♪
♪So hate can fade
and love feels new again♪
♪Reclaim the barren parts of life♪
♪Walking this road
together, still hoping♪
♪Let me be the wind at dawn♪
♪Blowing away all the pain♪
♪Let me be the balance
that holds the weight♪
♪Where fairness stands♪
♪Within every heart♪
♪So many voices calling♪
♪Struggling, lost,
waiting for an answer♪
♪Light up the lamps♪
♪To answer those voices♪
♪You deserve to be happy♪
♪Loud and clear♪
♪All the little things♪
♪Woven into our lives♪
♪The building blocks of life♪
♪Shape the sky above us♪
♪Are you doing alright?♪
♪What are you struggling for?♪
♪Some questions♪
♪Weigh like mountains♪
♪Let me be the wind at dawn♪
♪Blowing away all the pain♪
♪Let me be the balance
that holds the weight♪
♪Where fairness stands♪
♪Within the law♪
♪And within every heart♪