=Hold a Court Now=
=Episode 15=
Hello, Ms. Ding.
Is your right hand
any better?
I'm sorry.
I burned you when you were at my firm.
I promised to reimburse
your medical fees.
Show me the receipt.
(Family Court)
Plaintiff's lawyer, this is unrelated...
Let her ask.
Plaintiff's lawyer, continue.
Ms. Ding.
I misspoke.
I remember it was the left hand.
Judge Shen.
I have reason to suspect
that the plaintiff is not my client.
Your Honor!
She's lying.
This lawyer is disrupting the court.
Aren't you going to stop her?
Ding Yajing.
Date of birth?
March 9, 1995.
What's your Chinese zodiac sign?
The Pig.
And your lunar birthday?
I never go by the lunar calendar.
My birthday is March 9.
Who was your university chancellor?
I studied accounting
at Tianhai University.
I asked for the chancellor's name.
It's...
The name is...
Miss,
I have reasons to suspect
you aren't the plaintiff, Ding Yajing.
Ms. Qin.
Hello, Ms. Ding.
Ding Yawei?
Ding Yawei, what is going on?
Why are you with Cheng Kuiyuan?
Talk to me!
Look at me and start talking!
What's the deal with you two?
Explain yourself right now!
Ding Yawei!
Not those. Don't pack those shoes.
Why not?
Take the black ones.
The ones with the cracks. Not these.
It's just for the hospital.
We'll toss them afterwards anyway.
Why are you worrying about this?
Can we just focus for a second?
We're on a tight budget, remember?
Look,
Dr. Bai has amazing reviews online.
They say his cosmetic stitches
are incredible.
You won't even see a scar.
Really?
Yeah.
I was thinking,
after the surgery,
we'll hire a caregiver.
One caregiver covers a few patients,
so it's not expensive.
You can just call her
if you need anything.
That way, she isn't hovering over you.
And it won't affect your work.
You can keep doing your thing.
Don't keep all those people
waiting on their lawsuits.
What do you think?
Honey?
I want to talk to you about something.
Go ahead.
Can we wait a bit
for this surgery?
Why?
Yeah.
I don't think
it's that important either.
We can't let it get in the way
of Nian's studies abroad.
That's not what I meant.
Maybe we can
find a different doctor?
But this doctor is fine.
Yeah, Dr. Bai is decent enough.
But this is just a crazy coincidence.
Dr. Bai is in a lawsuit in our court.
Did you know that?
The case is sitting right on my desk.
I've looked over the file.
The facts are black and white.
As the presiding judge, I don't have
much discretion here.
I'd likely grant his claims anyway.
But with this personal connection,
it's hard to explain away.
Exactly.
Let's find someone else
to avoid any suspicion.
Okay?
Forget it.
I'm not doing the surgery at all.
Switch hospitals, switch doctors...
Who knows what issues
the next doctor will have?
Honey,
don't say things you don't mean.
You have to have this surgery.
And I refuse to believe
that in a city as big as Tianhai,
he's the only expert available.
I promise you,
soon,
I will find a doctor
even better than Dr. Bai.
Trust me.
In all our years of marriage,
have I ever broken a promise to you?
It was obvious Ms. Qin
was getting suspicious.
Something felt off to me, too.
I've seen fake divorces
where people are polite,
but never a real one
where they're both this happy.
So I bluffed.
When she started stammering,
I knew I had her.
Ms. Qin finally got a hold of
the real plaintiff, Ding Yajing.
And get this.
The imposter's name
is Ding Yawei.
She's Ding Yajing's
identical twin sister.
She's been living off her sister for years.
She was in cahoots with the defendant.
She actually
stole the plaintiff's phone,
messaged the lawyer
to change the hearing time,
and then showed up
for the online trial!
My goodness, what a mess.
Sounds like you and Ms. Qin
actually make a pretty good team.
That's just because I'm brilliant.
I deliver results with
everyone I work with.
True enough.
Master,
Don't use that sincere tone with me.
I'd feel better
if you just chewed me out.
Have I ever chewed you out?
I was kidding.
I'm sorry.
Master, why are you being so serious?
I was really just joking.
To be honest,
I once saw you
as a product of a legal dynasty,
an assembly-line exam machine.
No empathy, no sense of responsibility,
and always stuck-up.
Just putting in your time
until you could bail.
Regarding those charges,
other than being stuck-up,
I plead not guilty.
That's mostly because I'm tall.
Not just the height.
You've got the brains,
the charm, and the talent.
Good-looking and kind-hearted, too.
"Flower of the Family Court."
And to Fei,
you're like the legendary Nezha.
Shen Xiezhi is actually pretty good.
In court today,
he fired off
a string of questions with us watching.
Out of nowhere, he asked her,
"So, who was
your university chancellor?"
She couldn't even get a word out.
I immediately video-called
the real Ding Yajing.
Guess who
the imposter was?
Look at you, Sherlock.
I can't believe you figured it out.
Waitress!
A glass of warm water for me, please.
Sure.
Oh, and I have more good news.
My channel just got more followers.
Thirteen of them!
Once I get
all the case files organized
and post them online,
I might actually
become a micro-influencer.
Not bad, right?
Ms. Qin, here's your water.
Thank you.
Don't you think
Ms. Ding now owes me
a huge bonus for this?
Wait.
Hold on.
It's Ms. Ding. She's calling.
Okay.
Yeah, just get over here quickly.
Ms. Ding?
What kind of lawyer
can't even recognize her own client?
I am so sorry, Ms. Ding.
Please, try to stay calm.
It was my mistake
for not realizing it sooner, but...
Well,
this has never happened before.
I couldn't have anticipated this.
If you're this incompetent as a lawyer,
what are you even doing?
Look...
She is your biological
identical twin, isn't she?
You never mentioned to me
that you even had a twin sister.
I really couldn't tell.
What kind of nonsense
are you spewing now?
She's timid and weak!
How is that anything like me?
She's at least five jin heavier too!
Can't you tell?
No, wait.
Ms. Ding,
I'm also very confused.
She used your phone to call me.
This is your mess.
And now, you're trying to blame me?
You're pointing the finger at me?
- If it wasn't for me, this case...
- You're out of your mind!
Hello?
Hello?!
I ran all the way, but I'm still late.
What's the word?
Did you get that bonus?
What's wrong?
Don't scare me.
Talk to me.
There is no bonus.
My entire career is hanging by a thread.
Wait, what happened?
Look, objectively speaking,
we're not perfect at everything.
But,
when it comes to handling a crisis,
we've never backed down.
It's okay, don't be upset.
If it weren't for me,
her husband would've
stripped her of every cent.
Besides,
do you have any idea
how hard I worked
just to get her trial date moved up?
Don't cry. It's okay.
I'm not even upset!
I'm turning this anger into an appetite.
We're eating to our hearts' content!
Waitress! Can we order?
Sorry, hold on a second.
I just remembered something.
Remember those
discounted groceries I mentioned?
They arrived today and are very fresh.
Look,
I'll head back and whip up
a feast for you.
There's nothing a good meal can't fix.
Leave it to me.
Come on, let's go home.
No way.
What?
I promised to treat you
to something good.
You think I can't afford a meal?
That's not what I meant.
Listen,
I was supposed
to be celebrating a win today.
I know.
But I still have enough
to take you out for dinner.
Waitress!
Hey, stop it.
Sorry!
Give it a rest.
I can't let you spend
your grandma's medicine money on me.
Besides,
didn't you say the other day
that it's her birthday soon?
Aren't you going to see her?
You convinced me even more
that I can't go back.
Just use the money to buy her a gift.
We can save some travel fare.
Look...
That's enough. Just listen to me.
Let's go home.
Come on, let's go.
When I make big money,
I'll buy you something nice.
I'm holding you to that.
Let's go. Home, now!
Sorry, waitress!
I'll order extra cake next time!
By the way, Xiezhi.
Feng Shengli's father is
coming tomorrow
to present a thank-you banner.
Feng Shengli's surgery was a success,
and he's being discharged soon.
The public has been following
this case very closely.
Xiezhi,
such a positive response
from the community
is all thanks to how well
you two worked together.
But more importantly,
you truly helped those families
when they needed it most.
Morning.
Hello.
Hello, Judge.
Judge Shen is in a hearing.
I'm the court clerk, Chen Xianghui.
Please, have a seat.
I remember you.
Judge Chen.
When do you think
Judge Shen will be back?
Also,
when is the next hearing
for my brother's case?
It hasn't been set yet.
But as soon as he's back,
we'll get it on the schedule.
I see.
Could you please
mention it to Judge Shen again?
Our family can't afford
to let this drag on any longer.
You have no idea
what these last ten years
have been like for us.
Ever since my brother was kidnapped,
my parents gave up everything
just to find him.
My parents
couldn't even rest in peace
because of what happened to him.
My grandmother practically
cried herself blind.
And now
our prayers have been answered.
We've finally found him.
My grandmother and I just want
my brother back.
Please,
help us get a ruling soon.
I just want to take Guo home.
There's something I have to tell you.
Your brother's feelings
are not quite what you think.
That's impossible.
Last time he was home,
we held each other and cried.
He told me he wanted to come back to us!
The Qians sent over a letter.
They say your brother wrote it himself.
Take a look.
(I'm staying with my foster parents,
Qian Zhengguo and Nie Baomei, and my sister)
No way.
This is a fake.
The original is right here.
(Case File, Qingcheng District
People's Court, Tianhai City)
I still don't believe it.
My brother would never
write something like this.
It has to be Qian Zhengguo
and Nie Baomei.
Those scoundrels must have forced him.
They're just like that kidnapper, Li Gaiying.
They're all the same!
I won't let them steal my brother away!
(Case File, Qingcheng District
People's Court, Tianhai City)
(Liyuan Community Service Center)
Hello.
I need your cooperation on something.
I'm Shen Xiezhi, a Family Court judge
of the Qingcheng District People's Court.
I need to have a word
with a child from your community.
May I borrow
your meeting room?
Let me check with my supervisor.
Great, thank you.
In here.
The judge wants to see you.
Thank you.
Hello, Judge Shen.
Mr. Qian, Ms. Nie. We meet again.
So...
Didn't we settle
everything in court last time?
Exactly.
The thing is,
it's really about Xiaosheng.
He just doesn't want to go back there.
He even wrote a statement himself.
So...
So why the second interview?
Here's the thing.
According to regulations,
we need to have
an interview with the child.
Another one?
Sure.
Xiaosheng,
it's okay.
Don't be scared.
Today, just tell Judge Shen
how you truly feel about this.
I'm sorry, but you two need to
step out for a moment.
We need to speak
with Xiaosheng in private.
Step out?
What do you mean by that?
Everything my son said is true.
Exactly.
Are you suggesting
that we're coercing the boy?
Yeah, what's going on here?
This is just standard
operating procedure.
Please cooperate. Thank you.
You can't leave him alone.
He'll be terrified.
Mom,
it's fine.
I'll just talk to the judge
for a few minutes.
It won't take long.
You guys head home first.
Alright, then.
Okay. It's fine.
Come on, let's go.
Alright.
Just tell him everything.
Tell the truth.
We're going.
Let's go.
Just stay calm, you'll be fine.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Just stay relaxed.
I wrote that letter myself.
I did it on my own.
My parents didn't force me
into anything.
Xiaosheng,
if it comes down to it,
would you testify in court?
Would you do that?
Is that really necessary?
Everything is in that letter.
I made myself perfectly clear.
Don't you think
that if you don't show up in person
to take a stand,
your grandmother and sister
will never believe
those words are truly yours?
I know
how difficult this is for you.
I know you're only doing this
because you're angry with your sister.
You blame her for going after
your foster parents,
and you want her
and your grandmother to give up
so they'll stop hurting your parents.
However,
if you don't show up,
do you really think
this is going to end that easily?
You were gone for ten years.
Your family gave up their entire lives.
They never stopped looking.
They never gave up.
I respect your feelings.
The parents you have now
have raised you for a decade.
And if it's true
that Li Gaiying told them
you were just an abandoned baby,
then they are victims too.
But whatever the truth may be,
your grandmother and sister
are without a doubt
victims in all of this.
In their search for you,
they already gave up everything.
If you can,
maybe you should meet them
and tell them yourself.
Tell them what you're really thinking.
Tell them that you want to stay,
but that you're also willing
to stay in regular contact with them.
It's better than just
hiding from them
and leaving them in despair.
Judge.
I'll do as you say.
I'll tell them in court.
Good.
(Serving the People is My Mission)
That kid has had it rough.
An adult would be reeling in his shoes.
Never mind that Li Gaiying insists
the child is dead.
The Qians also can prove that
they adopted the boy legally.
after ten years of raising the boy,
can you really just erase that?
There's no need to trade places.
That kid's life was doomed
to be a tragedy
from the moment that nanny took him.
If he'd ended up with monsters,
he wouldn't be so conflicted today.
But a childhood like that
leaves a lifelong shadow.
With foster parents
who love him like their own,
he's forced to spend his life
torn between love and hate.
Wait, are you saying
the Qians might have known
they were buying him?
Presumption of innocence.
Until we have certain evidence,
I'm not making that claim.
Judge Shen.
Let's not be so formal.
I'm telling you,
it just feels wrong.
We see too many complicated cases.
With emotion on one side,
and logic on the other, it's tormenting.
And the boy is so young.
It's too much to ask of him.
Alright, that's enough.
We should stop now.
If we keep going,
I won't be able to stay objective
about this case.
Welcome.
- Jing.
- Come in.
Should we change shoes?
Don't worry about it.
Really?
Come on in.
You brought so much stuff!
It's from my cousin.
She's on a huge decluttering kick
and sent over these things
her kids outgrew.
Since we aren't even expecting yet,
I figured Fei could play with them.
Where is Fei?
She's okay.
Look at all these books.
She's such a bookworm.
She'll come out to see them in a bit.
Fei?
Fei!
Last year, I missed the trip
because I was sick.
And the year before,
it was that interview, right?
No, that wasn't it.
I think that was three years ago.
What happened the year before last?
That year...
I was busy feeding strays.
It was because of the dogs, remember?
Your client claimed
there was an emergency,
but she just had three dogs
with no sitter.
And you said,
"This is my first big case."
You were so desperate that
you were even willing to dog-sit.
Okay, don't mention the dogs again.
That woman was
the Waterloo of my career.
I'm serious.
Bring up the dogs again
and I'll bite you.
Exactly my point.
Ms. Ding firing you now
must be a sign from above.
You've missed your grandma's
birthday every year.
Let's see
what excuse you find this time.
I'll give it some thought.
I have to go.
(Grandma:
Xiang, have you been busy lately?)
(Don't just focus on making money.)
(Eat well and take care of yourself.)
(I only have 600 yuan left.)
(That won't even
cover my expenses this month.)
(How am I supposed to go home?)
(I'm so sorry, Grandma.)
(I won't be able to make it back)
(for your birthday this year.)
(Work is going great.)
(I just landed a massive case.)
(Once I'm done with this, I'll...)
(Grandma: Don't worry about coming home.)
(Just get some rest when you can.)
(I've been feeling much better lately.)
(Don't you worry about me.)
(I love you, Grandma.)
(Thank you.)
(I hope you live to be a hundred.)
I've got your numbers down, ladies.
I'll give you a call
as soon as I'm back at the office.
Here,
take a sausage.
Free consultations come with a snack!
But to get a real sausage,
you have to bring me a valid lead.
Any potential case for me?
How about you, sir?
Are these even edible?
They look so cheap.
Here, boy!
Ugh, even the dog won't eat it. Toss it.
Just throw it away.
He's short on cash for a new car.
He wants me to lend him 50,000 yuan.
You haven't gotten yours?
Here,
take this.
Thanks.
Talk about a spending downgrade.
These sausages are high quality!
They're firm and full of nutrients.
Watch, I'll eat one.
See? Perfectly fine.
Here.
If you have a real lead,
just give me a call.
My number is right here.
(Plaintiff)
(Defendante)
Is Guo coming today?
Are they even bringing him here?
It's okay. Don't worry.
Look at them.
What a great performance.
We're clearly the victims here.
Calm down.
Try to stay calm.
There's no reason to be nervous.
Once we finish here today,
we're finally taking my brother home.
(Children's Room, In Use)
Your Honor, Court Clerk,
and to my dear family.
You are all gathered here today
because of me,
and because of
a mistake made ten years ago.
For the last decade,
my family has paid an unimaginable price
just to find me.
Moving forward,
I want to fulfill my duties as a son
and honor you.
The court will now come to order.
Over these past ten years,
my foster parents have
done everything possible
to provide me
with the best life and education.
They raised and taught me
with the deepest love.
Their love for me
is no different
than that of any other parent.
It is my wish
that I may continue to live
with my foster parents,
Qian Zhengguo and Nie Baomei.
I want to continue my life
in the environment I know.
But this doesn't mean
I am turning my back
on our blood bond.
I will still fulfill my responsibilities
and duties as a grandson.
I only hope that we can
let go of past hatred
and find a way
to live our lives together.
And find a way
to live our lives together...
Young man?
It's time to go in.
Don't be afraid.
Everyone in there is your family.
Just say exactly what's in your heart.
The Panel Judges are entering the court.
All rise.
Please be seated.
Court is now in session.
(Court in session)
Xiaosheng...
Guo...
Son...
It's okay.
Guo...
Don't be afraid.
Witness, please take a seat.
Witness Qian Xiaosheng,
you may begin your statement.
Judge,
may I say a few words to him first?
recently,
they haven't let us
see my brother at all.
They're probably brainwashing him.
This...
- How can you say that?
- That's uncalled for!
Just let my grandmother
say a few words to him.
Please?
Does the defendant
have any objections?
No objection. Let her speak.
- Go ahead.
- Why are we letting her speak?
Plaintiff,
proceed.
It's okay. Keep it brief.
Focus on the important part.
Don't be nervous.
Guo...
You must remember...
Your sister and I,
and your parents in heaven,
will always love you.
♪Happy birthday to you♪
Okay?
Xiaosheng,
Mom and Dad love you, too.
Qian Xiaosheng,
please continue.
Presiding Judge,
court clerk,
dear parents.
I am...
I...
I'm sorry, Judge.
Son!
Guo!
- Xiaosheng!
- Son!
- Guo!
Xiaosheng!
Son...
I've been trying to call,
but the Qians aren't picking up.
I called the police station
where they're registered.
Based on the ticket records
linked to their ID numbers,
they've returned to Qian Village.
All three of them went back together.
Here are the ticket records.
That was fast.
Heading home right after court?
Well, after all that ordeal,
maybe going home
holds a special meaning for them.
(Qian Zhengguo,No. 18 of Qian Village,
Baimao Town, Wuwei City, Huaiqing)
Baimao Town?
(Divorce Dispute:
Ding Yajing vs. Cheng Kuiyuan)
(Qin Rui, 20 Outang Village,
Baimao Town, Wuwei City, Huaiqing)
Five minutes left!
Free giveaway!
Legal consultations, free of charge!
Plus a free carton of milk.
Does anyone else need legal advice?
Come sign up right here.
I can't let you spend
your grandma's
medicine money on me.
Didn't you say the other day
that it's her birthday soon?
You convinced me even more
that I can't go back.
(Senior Lawyer,
Professional Consultation)
Thank you.
Judge Shen.
I'm actually here on business.
I'm not stalking you.
I was actually looking for you.
Me?
Do you have any plans to head home soon?
To your hometown?
I was going to,
but things have been so crazy lately.
I doubt
I'll have time.
Work's just too much.
Busy handing out flyers?
What's that supposed to mean?
My job is none of your concern.
It was actually a coincidence.
If you'd passed by at noon,
I would've...
If I'd passed by at noon,
you'd have seen me
at the court gates.
Forget it, you wouldn't understand.
You're just that kind of person.
I really need to speak with you.
Put those down first.
Can you send me your ID number?
My ID number?
What for?
I've given you plenty of case files.
It's all in there.
I need your consent first.
I'd like to buy you
one of those unlimited flight passes.
It's good for six months.
That way,
whenever you want to go home
to your hometown, you can.
Buying me a plane ticket?
What's this about?
You're a judge,
and I'm a lawyer. This isn't right.
There might be cameras around.
I don't want people
getting the wrong idea.
If you're going
to be that pedantic about it...
What about back at the fire,
when you helped me save Fei?
Trading a few tickets for a life?
Hardly crossing a line.
Don't be so dramatic.
Helping you back then
was just about survival.
It wasn't a big deal.
Besides, you've saved me before, too.
Does all this back-and-forth
really matter?
Is this important,
or is your grandmother's
birthday important?
Fine. It's settled.
I'm getting the pass.
Just don't let it go to waste.
(How did he even know?)
♪Lean on my tender shoulder♪
Judge Shen!
Thank you!
When I'm making the big bucks,
I'll definitely pay you back.
♪I'll be there for you
until the very end♪
(Standing for the Law,
Protecting Your Rights)
(Rui's Legal Lens is Live)
Is this a total loss of humanity,
or just a collapse of moral values?
Let's find out together on
Rui's Legal Lens.
To my regular fans,
you already know
that I usually handle
international legal disputes
that are very high-stakes.
I actually just hopped off a flight,
so I'm still battling
some serious jet lag.
Aren't you laying it on a bit thick?
The video is only a few minutes long,
and the intro was pure fiction.
Hey, that was all carefully staged.
I think it adds some flavor.
Let me give you some advice.
You should put
a polished headshot at the start.
"A beautiful lawyer leads you
into the legal world."
The views would be huge.
At that rate,
I might as well wear a bikini,
a sun hat, and some sunglasses too.
Polished photos?
Give me a break.
I let my talent do the talking.
My brand is all about professionalism.
Fine, fine.
Our respected Ms. Qin
doesn't take shortcuts.
Okay?
Snarky Lawyer?
Wait, is this the Snarky Lawyer
who was trending a while back?
What's up?
Is there some new scandal?
He followed you.
Followed me?
No way.
It's probably a fake account
with an underscore
or a space in the name.
The real guy would never follow me.
Even though I've followed him for ages.
It's real! Not an imposter.
See for yourself. Look!
(The Snarky Lawyer)
(Legal Outreach)
Oh my!
It really is him.
A million-follower influencer
just followed me!
I must be dreaming.
Am I going to get tons of new followers?
Maybe we can do
a joint livestream later.
Create some buzz.
I might actually go viral!
I could make a living off social media.
Think of the ad revenue!
I'd be rolling in money!
Exactly.
You'd be rich.
He really followed me.
I'm going to ride your coattails now.
It's really him.
I've been shown
a lot of kindness lately.
It looks like our luck
is finally turning around.
This is great.
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Come here and help us wrap dumplings.
What's the occasion? Why dumplings?
What's the filling?
Three-delicacies filling.
Dumplings for the road,
noodles for the welcome.
It's a procedure we can't skip.
I'm only gone for a few days.
There's no need to make such a fuss.
Exactly what I said.
A total waste of energy.
Waste of energy, maybe, but not money.
Besides,
staying busy helps prevent dementia.
I don't need to worry about that.
Between lesson plans and teaching,
my brain
is doing just fine, trust me.
Good to know.
So, who's going on this trip with you?
Is it Xianghui?
Should we invite him over for dumplings?
He's not going. I'm going alone.
The court is only sending you?
No one else?
No need.
Local colleagues will be assisting me.
Listen,
even as a Chief Physician
who's hit middle age,
you shouldn't let your standards slip.
When have I ever
let my standards slip?
What Dad means is,
stop meddling
and asking so many questions.
What's the deal with you two?
Dad, look at them.
They're ganging up on me!
This is a family feud.
Don't involve the innocent.
I'm a civilian.
I'm protected by the Geneva Convention!
(Home is meant to be our sanctuary,)
(our place of comfort.)
(But going home)
(can sometimes feel overwhelming)
(for those who are truly weary.)
(Once upon a time,)
(I couldn't really
grasp that complexity.)
(I had that academic arrogance,)
(even silently resenting my father)
(for being so hard on me.)
(It wasn't until
I joined the Family Court,)
(until I was)
(listening day after day)
(to stories soaked in tears,)
(that I finally understood his intent.)
(He wanted me to touch)
(the rawest, most authentic
marks of life.)
(The old me, who lived in a bubble,)
(finally touched the ground.)
(As judges,)
(perhaps all we can do)
(is strive to create moments)
(where both sides can open up)
(and talk sincerely.)
(To protect every)
(hard-won family reunion.)
(This realization)
(quietly melted the silence)
(between my father and me)
(that had lasted for so long.)
(When I finally sat down)
(and started listening to him)
(just as I listened to my clients,)
(I saw beneath his clumsy concern)
(the same core)
(as what I am doing now.)
(A stubborn, steadfast protection.)
(It turns out)
(that while helping others
find their way,)
(I also found my own way home.)
(After 11 years, Liu Hongying's son,
Yuan Guoguo, has finally been found.)
Judge Shen?
What a coincidence.
Are you going to Wuwei City too?
Yeah. Business trip.
I didn't expect you
to use your flight pass today.
There's only one flight a week.
I wanted to see Grandma early.
You're going to investigate
the Xiaosheng case, aren't you?
Don't try to hide it.
When Xiaosheng's
DNA results came out,
it went viral all over the internet.
Even my hometown chat groups
were buzzing about it.
Do you live in Qian Village too?
No.
I'm in Outang Village right next to it.
Very close.
Are you going alone?
Yes.
How about this? I'll be your guide.
♪All the little things
between you and me♪
♪Woven into our lives♪
♪The building blocks of life♪
♪Shape the sky above us♪
♪Are you doing alright?♪
♪What are you struggling for?♪
♪Some questions weigh like mountains♪
♪How do we piece life back together?♪
♪So hate can fade
and love feels new again♪
♪Reclaim the barren parts of life♪
♪Walking this road
together, still hoping♪
♪Let me be the wind at dawn♪
♪Blowing away all the pain♪
♪Let me be the balance
that holds the weight♪
♪Where fairness stands♪
♪Within every heart♪
♪So many voices calling♪
♪Struggling, lost,
waiting for an answer♪
♪Light up the lamps♪
♪To answer those voices♪
♪You deserve to be happy♪
♪Loud and clear♪
♪All the little things♪
♪Woven into our lives♪
♪The building blocks of life♪
♪Shape the sky above us♪
♪Are you doing alright?♪
♪What are you struggling for?♪
♪Some questions♪
♪Weigh like mountains♪
♪Let me be the wind at dawn♪
♪Blowing away all the pain♪
♪Let me be the balance
that holds the weight♪
♪Where fairness stands♪
♪Within the law♪
♪And within every heart♪