=Hold a Court Now=
=Episode 18=
Jing,
I think maybe
you should take
your husband to the hospital.
Well,
getting some medicine
to help regulate things would be good.
Forget it.
Look...
Fei is about to get out of class.
I will go pick her up.
I will go with you.
What are you going for?
Let Fei come home with me today.
When you get home tonight,
cook a few dishes for your husband.
Have a couple of drinks together.
Remember,
dim the lights.
Ideally,
light some scented candles too.
Once the atmosphere is there,
things will naturally follow.
You can't wait,
right?
You are overthinking it.
Look at how happy you are.
Ms. Lu.
Ms. Qin.
Let me, let me.
I will push you over.
This is fine, thank you.
How is your case going?
Has the hearing started?
Yes.
My brothers
forced them to do
an autopsy on my father.
Who is the judge?
I think
the last name is Shu.
Shu Jing.
Judge Shu Jing is very kind.
Do not worry.
She will not let your two brothers
take advantage of you.
You came all this way
in this condition.
It must be inconvenient to take the bus.
Let me call you a car.
It's okay.
I live very close to here.
Just past three intersections
and I am there.
I have been walking around here often lately,
so I am already very familiar with it.
Thank you.
Thank you, Ms. Qin.
Let me treat you to dinner.
It's alright.
Look, I already bought groceries.
Thank you.
It is very close. It just so happens
I have no one to eat with.
Come eat with me.
No, really...
You do not trust me
to treat you to a meal? Come on.
Then...
Let's go eat something good.
Your meal is served. Please enjoy.
Thank you.
Ms. Lu, you're welcome.
Are you used to the food here?
I am. It is delicious.
I did not think much of it just now,
but this happens
to be the restaurant
where I often met clients before.
Ms. Qin,
do you think
I can win this case?
Do not worry.
You will definitely
win this case.
Think about it.
All these years,
you were the one who took care
of your father the most.
And your own health
is not good to begin with.
Doing laundry, cooking,
even handling his toileting needs,
not to mention
taking him to the hospital,
carrying him up and down,
through wind and rain,
all of it depended on you alone.
That is not easy.
Your two brothers
are really inconsiderate.
And now they are even suing you.
Where is their humanity?
No matter what,
my father died
because I
took him out.
I just cannot get over this in my heart.
I really cannot.
The forensic examination
will help restore the truth.
May I know,
what is this examination process like?
I am a little scared.
I do not know the exact details,
but I have a friend
who specializes in this.
She works at Qingcheng District
Forensic Identification Center.
I will ask her for you.
The institution we are going to
is the one in Qingcheng District.
The one on Heping Road?
Yes.
That is great.
I will go with you.
I cannot afford a lawyer as good as you.
I will not charge you.
It is just a small favor.
I told you
my friend works there, right?
I will just treat it as getting
a free meal from her later.
I'll even get a full benefit out of it.
Eat the noodles while they are hot.
They will not taste good
once they get cold.
Welcome back, Le.
Dad, Mom.
Look who is here.
Fei is here.
Come, sit.
Fei.
I will get you some slippers.
Stretch your feet.
That is more comfortable. Here.
Take off your shoes.
Alright. Put your schoolbag down
and come with me.
I will pour some water for her.
Come with me.
Okay.
Come sit here.
Go take the things out.
Yes.
Xiao Bing, where are my slippers?
I will get them for you in a bit.
Coming.
Look.
Look at all my treasures.
Dad,
you even kept
my childhood stuff.
Of course.
We are saving them for our grandchild.
Fei, you must be thirsty.
Have some water first.
What do you like?
- Have a sip of water first.
- Go get the slippers.
Have some water.
Dad, Mom, Jing has something
to handle at home today,
so Fei will stay over
at our place tonight.
- That is great.
Fei, you can sleep with me tonight.
See?
- That is wonderful.
- Change your shoes.
Do you like this?
Look at this little car.
Look at this car.
She still has homework
to do later, Dad, Mom.
Homework is important, but we also
need a balance between work and rest.
Let her play first.
Le,
you come play too.
I heard
that playing with toys lifts the mood.
More importantly,
it helps with brain development.
I...
Just leave them be.
Fei does not come often.
Let them enjoy some family time.
As for us,
how long has it been
since we went on a date?
Before we got married,
we went on dates quite often, right?
After we got married...
After we got married,
it really has not been very many times.
The wedding
feels like it was many years ago.
I can barely remember it.
I remember the wedding clearly.
Halfway through the ceremony,
Liu Ren
was stirring things up on the spot.
I remember.
They asked me to dance back then.
I hate dancing the most.
I was so nervous.
You grabbed the microphone
and said you would protect me.
At that moment, I thought,
"This is someone I can marry,
he's really so good to me."
What are you talking about?
I was drunk at the time.
I have never danced on stage before.
I had no idea
what I was even doing.
Afterward, when I watched
the wedding video,
what dancing was that?
It was chaos.
Yes, I remember.
You danced like a monkey back then.
Do not think I did not notice.
You even practiced in secret afterward.
You knew about that too?
You have always been like this,
never telling me things,
always making me guess.
When I guess wrong,
you say I do not understand you.
I really did not
hide things from you on purpose.
Think about it,
you are already so busy at work,
with so many matters
at the court every day.
When you come home,
how can I trouble you
with those little things?
If I do not worry about you,
then why did we get married?
Did you forget?
Back when we got married,
did we not agree
to be honest with each other?
Have you forgotten all of that?
So all that
was just you brushing me off?
No.
I meant it.
I truly meant it.
Speaking of which,
did you ever learn the dance?
No.
But I did practice seriously.
Besides, I never
had a chance to show it.
No time like the present.
Right now.
You really want to see it?
Alright.
It has been a long time.
Look,
I will just do the first move.
Ready, go.
You still look like a monkey.
Come, I will teach you.
I cannot dance.
Come on.
I really cannot dance.
It is very simple.
I have no coordination.
Watch carefully. Here.
Again.
Turn around.
Spin, spin.
Shu Jing,
having you by my side is really nice.
(Ms. Wei)
Ignore it.
No, I should take this.
Hello.
Do not worry.
What is the client's request?
Okay.
I got it. Go ahead.
(Following He Xiuguang)
People who live here
can come down for a walk every day.
Quiet within the bustle,
a perfect place to settle down.
Yongxu, come take a look.
Distant mountains like ink,
nearby waters veiled in mist.
Autumn grass and withered lotus,
rippling under the sunlight.
This is a paradise on earth.
As we walked here just now,
those grand buildings
were hidden among the lush greenery.
The liveliness of daily life
blends perfectly
with this natural beauty.
Wonderful.
Xiuguang,
you chose this place very well.
It seems heaven
is looking out for us.
If we could build a home here,
it would truly be a joy in life.
Walking barefoot
on this kind of path
is very good
for the foot reflexology points.
Slow down.
This way.
The park next to our home
is quite lively.
Seeing these children
reminds me of when I
used to bring Xiezhi here.
Dad,
you really have a great memory.
I still remember when he was little,
he kept saying he wanted to be a doctor,
using a paper cup as a stethoscope,
going around listening
to the trees' heartbeats.
Grandpa,
you take a walk first.
I will come find you later.
Alright, go ahead.
This child.
Dad,
let us take a walk by the lake.
You are where I belong
for the rest of my life.
I wish I could become your belt,
wrapping around
your slender waist every day,
following you wherever you go.
I would be your sash,
embracing your graceful form.
You truly are my soulmate.
What are you doing?
Do not do this.
No, do not do this.
I am sorry.
No,
I am the one who should apologize.
Yongxu,
I am truly sorry.
My passion
was stirred by the fragrance
of these flowers and grass.
My soul
was cleansed by the gentle breeze here.
Everything between you
and me converges here.
In this perfect moment,
in this beautiful time,
right now,
I truly
cannot hold back my feelings.
But I cannot give you
a proper embrace,
nor can I share with you
a life of two people,
three meals, four seasons.
I am useless.
Xiuguang,
how much is this place per square meter?
Who is that?
Stop right there!
Give it back to me!
That is my phone.
You are awful, give it back to me!
I had a bad feeling early this morning,
kept thinking someone was tailing me.
I did not expect it to be you.
What did you capture?
I did not capture anything.
Give me back my phone.
Password.
Why should I tell you my password?
Besides, if you have done nothing wrong,
what are you afraid of?
Ma'am, listen,
he is actually a jerk.
You are hurting me!
You followed me and secretly filmed me.
That is a violation of my privacy,
do you understand?
Hurry up, the password.
If you keep this up,
I will call for help.
Go ahead.
Help! Someone!
- Help!
Are you crazy?
No one is around here.
It is secluded, so no one will come.
Tell me the password.
I will delete everything and let you go.
I am not telling you.
Not telling me, huh?
Fine, I will tell you.
Five eight one two.
Two.
What else?
Zero.
It is unlocked.
Wow,
you took quite a lot.
Select all.
Qian Guixiang!
Stop right there.
Stop.
Xiuguang!
Are you okay?
Help me.
Where did she go?
Did she run out?
Impossible.
Not that fast.
Look at you,
why could you not hold
your phone properly?
No, when the girl shouted,
well,
you did not turn around, so I...
Why did you turn around
as soon as she spoke?
Was I not also...
Just now,
she said something about Qian and Xiang.
Who is that?
Qian...
Stop.
You explain this to me.
Explain it clearly.
He Xiuguang, you stop right there.
Here.
I am sorry.
Why are you here?
I was taking a walk here with my family.
What happened?
I just secretly recorded
He Xiuguang fooling
around here with a woman.
He tried to snatch my phone
to delete the videos inside.
Luckily, you were here
and helped cover for me.
We worked together quite well.
You owe me a favor.
Is this not your case too?
The Sunshine Community
Elderly Care Service Center
has officially launched,
creating a one-stop new home
for happy senior living.
This morning,
the highly anticipated
Sunshine Community
Elderly Care Service Center
held a grand opening ceremony.
Zhang Min, Director
of the Civil Affairs Bureau,
Zhang Qiang, Director of the
Subdistrict Office, and other leaders
attended the ceremony
and cut the ribbon.
Representatives of nearby
residents and elderly citizens
witnessed this important
moment together.
(Sunshine Community)
Help me.
Xiezhi, have some Hami melon.
I think I should move back.
I have to get up early tomorrow.
What?
Why are you reading
those old, cheesy romance novels again?
You were the one
who recommended them to me.
Back then, you even said
they had progressive views on love.
And now you are calling them cheesy.
Do not push the blame onto me.
These days, you spend all day
either reciting sentimental poetry
or reading cheesy romance novels.
Go on,
what new plot twist have you got?
Really?
Just accept it?
Accept what?
We are bound to separate anyway.
Why even start?
There is no point.
Then you should tell him sooner
rather than later,
that you two should never
see each other again. Be decisive.
(Rather than breaking up indecisively,)
(staying entangled and unable to let go)
(it is better
to carry the relationship through,)
(at least there will be an end one day.)
Welcome back.
Why are you still awake, still busy?
I was waiting for you.
Fei is asleep?
Why are you back so late?
Do not even mention it.
A group came to the shop today
for team building,
a whole crowd of people, singing and dancing,
and they drank several cases of alcohol.
No matter how we tried,
they would not leave.
Just take it easy with the shop.
Your health matters most.
More customers
mean better business.
Is that not a good thing?
Come here.
What is it?
Take a look.
Are these two books professional enough?
(Selected Effective Defense Documents
and Practical Guide)
(Commentary on Real Estate
Dispute Cases)
They look quite professional.
What is it?
The other day, Yu Le said
she has a classmate
who works
as a legal director at a company.
It just so happens one of their subsidiaries
is short of a legal manager.
I think you are quite suitable.
You want me to be a legal manager?
Now that Fei is doing better,
it is time for you
to return to the legal field.
But going back to the court
is not very suitable,
and being a lawyer in Qingcheng
would conflict with me.
So being a legal manager
is the most suitable. What do you think?
Come on.
I have been away for so long.
I think things are pretty good now,
free and easy.
If anything happens with Fei,
I can always make time.
You do not understand.
Once a legal manager gets busy,
there is no way to guarantee your time.
Fei is not that clingy anymore.
Besides, since Yu Le brought it up,
you should just give it a try.
So you just want me to try it,
taking a shot in the dark?
Is that what you mean?
Your ability
is definitely not a problem.
The battle has not even started yet,
why are you already discouraged?
Let me add two more books for you.
No...
I have not even agreed yet.
Why are you still buying?
There are so many books
at home that I have not finished.
- No way.
- Do not buy them.
(Shen Xiezhi)
Hello.
Have the selection results come out?
Xiezhi,
each unit
has a different review timeline.
How would I know?
I am not the one in charge.
Do you not have any news at all?
Do you really think
you are a legal genius,
passing every exam you take?
If you still have not heard
anything by now,
there is a high chance you are out.
What?
Feeling down?
Let me tell you,
the candidates this time
are all exceptionally strong.
Some have received commendations,
and some have
over a decade more experience than you.
It does not look promising.
Just wait for the notice.
It is fine.
Life is long.
Take it slowly.
What do you mean?
Time for bed.
Good night.
(Life is long?)
(He was acting strange again
in the middle of the night.)
Come on, time to order.
I will go first. Coconut latte.
Same for me.
I will have a coconut latte too.
- Same for me.
- Then I will have the same.
Wait.
I will switch to
brown sugar stewed pear.
Hot.
Oh my god.
Le is drinking something hot too.
Exactly. Someone who never avoids cold drinks
even during that time of the month.
Le,
we always thought
you would need to sleep at night
on that cold jade bed
from an ancient tomb.
Pears are cold, right?
They are.
Then I will switch to
red date, longan, and lotus seed soup.
What are you doing, are you
trying to protect a pregnancy?
Come on.
If anyone were protecting a pregnancy,
it would not be her.
Exactly.
She has never missed a good cold drink.
Do you all agree?
- Yes.
- I think so too.
Only Judge Shen is left.
Judge Shen, what are you ordering?
Judge Shen.
Same for me.
Same of what?
Judge Shen,
your reaction is way too slow.
I will have the same as Le.
What, are you protecting
a pregnancy too?
What do you mean?
So everything we just said,
you did not hear any of it?
What were you daydreaming about?
Look at Le,
she is zoning out too.
Le.
What is going on
with you two today?
Good thing we all know each other well.
Otherwise, people might think you and Le
have something going on.
Alright, stop it.
Look, Judge Shen
is not even talking anymore.
I have something to do.
You all carry on.
You aren't going to report it, right?
(Office. Meeting Room. Changing Room)
Hello.
Have you finished your call?
When is the interview?
There is no interview.
Why?
HR already said
this job requires
frequent business trips.
I do not think it is suitable.
Then you should go talk
to them in person.
They made it very clear
on the phone.
That means
this is a serious issue.
Why did you not discuss it with me?
How do you know
I cannot accommodate you?
What is there to discuss
about something like this?
Forget it. You get back to work.
I will think about it.
(Lian Yongjiu Interview)
(Qin Rui)
(Courtroom 1 Hearing in progress)
This case is transferred
from summary procedure
to ordinary procedure.
(Hearing in progress)
It will now be heard by a collegial panel.
All rise.
Presiding Judge,
people's jurors, please enter.
(Qin Rui did not come?)
Please be seated.
Court is now in session.
(Hearing in progress)
Judge Shen,
sorry,
Ms. Qin could not make it.
With the consent of the party,
I have already
submitted the authorization letter
to the court clerk, Mr. Chen.
(Change of Attorney
Authorization Agreement)
(Qin Rui)
(What is going on?)
(Is she deliberately avoiding me?)
Few people can truly understand,
and I am afraid
others will say I am pretentious.
Xiuguang,
do not do this.
Do not do this.
I am sorry.
No.
I am the one who should apologize.
Ms. Xie Yongxu
comes from a scholarly family,
dignified in character,
kind at heart.
She became the third party passively.
She is willing
to appear in court
at any time for confrontation.
What else do you have to say?
You all...
Xiuguang, how...
how could you?
That is right.
It was me.
Guixiang,
I am tired.
I will not explain anymore.
Let us break up.
In this lifetime,
I am destined to wander.
My heart, like my footsteps,
will not stop for any woman.
No,
you are lying to me.
That is not what you used to say.
Why
are you so stubborn?
Do you still not understand even now?
From beginning to end,
I was only after your money.
Being with someone like you,
a woman 23 years older than me,
what else could I want?
No...
You are lying to me.
I do not believe it. I do not.
I came here today
to make a clean break with you.
I am done speaking.
Your Honor, may I be excused?
No,
you are not allowed to leave.
No one can take you away from me.
Are you trying to drive me to death?
I raised you all for nothing.
If he leaves,
I will not go on living.
Mom!
Xiuguang,
do not leave.
I know you are lying to me.
You have no choice.
You are putting on an act for them.
You do not want us
to turn against each other.
You do not want me
to be caught in the middle.
You have nothing to do with that woman,
right?
You are not allowed to leave.
I will not let you go.
My life
has already wasted sixty-one years.
I do not want to waste
a single day for the remaining 20 years.
Judge,
please issue the judgment
as soon as possible.
Return my property to me.
I want to start a new life
with Mr. He right away.
Now, immediately.
Xiuguang.
Guixiang.
Dear.
- Mom!
- Mom,
are you out of your mind?
Sit down.
This man is a fraud.
You should arrest him right now!
Sit down.
He Xiuguang, you shameless man,
come out here if you have the guts.
Come!
Sun Daming, what are you trying to do?
Do not be afraid.
Defendant,
control your emotions.
Wait for the judge's decision.
Whoever can stay calm now
will win the case.
Court is adjourned for deliberation.
I stand with the children.
This man is a complete fraud.
Exactly.
He specifically targets
elderly women lacking affection.
This house cannot be awarded
to Qian Guixiang.
If you award it to her,
He Xiuguang will cheat her out of it.
By then, she will lose both her money
and everything else.
If her children get angry
and stop caring for her,
how will she live?
I do not understand the law very well,
but is her revocation justified?
If we can avoid supporting it,
I do not agree to give it to her either.
From what we see now,
the children
are not completely unfilial.
If the property stays with them,
He Xiuguang will not gain anything
and will back off on his own.
Just now, I felt
that he was already
looking for a way out.
I just did not expect the elderly lady
to be so stubborn.
I think
he is not someone who gives up easily.
What he is doing
is playing hard to get.
Otherwise,
we could follow that lawyer's suggestion
and bring that woman in to testify.
The other party
has some social standing.
She may not be willing to testify.
And just now, He Xiuguang
has already blocked that path.
Even if she does testify,
the plaintiff
might still convince herself
that it is all staged,
that she was hired.
Then it seems
this is a dead end.
(Application for Property Preservation)
(Lefu Dog Farm)
Is the dog farm owned
by Sun Daming and his sister
near Qingshan Lake Wetland Park?
I remember there
is a retirement apartment nearby.
I think I saw news before
that the project was stalled.
Xinglang Real Estate took it over later.
Now the first phase is already occupied.
My mom went to see it with a friend.
They said the conditions are quite good.
Away from the hustle,
a place to rest and recuperate.
The cafeteria provides three meals a day,
and even late-night snacks.
They say the food is quite good too.
And the community hospital is open 24/7.
It sounds like a good retirement option.
It is just...
Just what?
Too quiet.
Absolutely quiet.
Aside from the retirement home
and nearby villagers, no one goes there.
Is that not exactly
what retirement needs, a quiet place?
Beautiful mountains,
good water, great scenery.
But if the body ages
while the heart does not,
then beautiful scenery
may just become boring.
(Qingcheng District People's Court)
After deliberation,
before issuing a formal judgment,
the collegial panel
would like to seek
both parties' opinions.
Are you willing to accept mediation?
How would we mediate?
The condition for the mother
to gift the property to them
was that they treat her well.
But now,
have they considered
her happiness at all?
Qian Guixiang, what do you think?
They cannot stand seeing me happy.
Mom,
if you insist on thinking that way,
I will not stop you.
I do not care what my brother thinks.
You can take back
the property under my name.
But let me be clear,
if you suffer losses in the future
and are left with nothing,
do not come crying to me.
Mom,
think this through.
Both sides, please calm down.
After several discussions in court,
I believe
there is no
irreconcilable conflict between you.
The mother
seeks freedom
in her later-life marriage,
while the children
are concerned
about her property security.
They are not trying
to take her rental income.
The core issue
lies in
your trust in the mother's partner.
Based on this,
the court hopes
to find a solution
acceptable to everyone
without harming your relationship.
I have a proposal.
See if you are willing to accept it.
Your mother's health
has not been very good.
And the children are busy with work,
unable to stay by her side.
Mr. He can stay with her,
providing emotional support
and taking care
of her daily needs.
I believe
you should accept him
as you would a family member.
Judge Shen, you see things clearly.
Defendants,
are you willing
to have the two plaintiffs
move into your dog farm?
No, no need for that trouble.
Guixiang and I
are fine living in the city.
We are free and easy.
We are not troubling anyone.
Besides, Guixiang's health
is not very good,
she needs to go to the hospital often.
No need to trouble.
The dog farm
and Qingshan Lake Wetland Park
are separated by just a river,
adjacent to
Taiyang City Retirement Apartments.
The facilities are complete,
and the medical conditions
are excellent,
especially in elderly care.
This arrangement is beneficial for us.
He says this is beneficial for us.
Of course,
if Mr. He is afraid of loneliness,
that is another matter.
No...
I think Judge Shen's suggestion is good.
You,
move to the dog farm
with my mom.
We have long thought
that since my mom is getting older,
we should live together.
It is just that the dog farm
is too remote,
no one to chat with her,
we worry she will feel lonely.
Now that you are there,
we can focus on our own work,
and you can stay with my mom,
take walks here and there.
Thirty mu of the dog farm
and two thousand mu of the wetland park
are all your private garden.
You two can enjoy
your later years there.
No, we...
We should discuss this further.
This old scoundrel
will not be able
to stay at the dog farm.
What is yours will remain yours.
Guixiang, let us discuss this.
About where to live...
We will go.
The children have finally accepted you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Judge Shen. Thank you.
(Office)
♪All the little things
between you and me♪
♪Woven into our lives♪
♪The building blocks of life♪
♪Shape the sky above us♪
♪Are you doing alright?♪
♪What are you struggling for?♪
♪Some questions weigh like mountains♪
♪How do we piece life back together?♪
♪So hate can fade
and love feels new again♪
♪Reclaim the barren parts of life♪
♪Walking this road
together, still hoping♪
♪Let me be the wind at dawn♪
♪Blowing away all the pain♪
♪Let me be the balance
that holds the weight♪
♪Where fairness stands♪
♪Within every heart♪
♪So many voices calling♪
♪Struggling, lost,
waiting for an answer♪
♪Light up the lamps♪
♪To answer those voices♪
♪You deserve to be happy♪
♪Loud and clear♪
♪All the little things♪
♪Woven into our lives♪
♪The building blocks of life♪
♪Shape the sky above us♪
♪Are you doing alright?♪
♪What are you struggling for?♪
♪Some questions♪
♪Weigh like mountains♪
♪Let me be the wind at dawn♪
♪Blowing away all the pain♪
♪Let me be the balance
that holds the weight♪
♪Where fairness stands♪
♪Within the law♪
♪And within every heart♪