=Hold a Court Now=
=Episode 19=
(Office)
(Did she leave Jindian?)
(Will I still see her in the future?)
You can't make
all the money in the world,
and there will
always be more work to do.
There are also
countless obstacles in real life.
However, life is short.
In this fleeting life,
love may be
but a momentary bloom.
It might even be
the only one in the vast ocean.
If you don't grasp the opportunity,
you will lose it forever.
(Qingcheng District People's Court,
Tianhai City)
Why didn't you attend court?
To avoid suspicions.
Let's be together.
Do you know?
I've thought about it
for a long time last night.
We listed out all our difficulties
and trapped ourselves inside.
But what will happen
in the future,
whether we are together or not,
I've thought about everything
that could happen in the future.
But no matter which possibility it is,
it will only happen in the future.
Besides,
they'll also make me regret.
I just want to cherish the present.
If we put an end to it right now,
every time we meet in the future,
we will have to suppress our feelings
with only regret left.
Instead of having that,
why not forget everything
and courageously be together?
Perhaps we'd be sick of each other
before the final day.
Then, we can just
break up happily.
I've thought about all you just said.
But in that case,
there will always be
a time bomb that can go off at any time
in our relationship.
It will end at any time.
This isn't fair for you.
Shen Xiezhi!
You were the one who said
you'd take care of me forever.
Let's be together.
From now on.
The agreement is in force immediately.
The relationship
will be executed immediately.
I smelled something nice at the door.
It's a feast, as expected.
My favorite hotpot.
I'm starving.
So many dishes.
What a feast.
Let me grab one.
What are you doing?
Wash your hands before you eat.
I washed my hands before I came back.
Go and wash your hands.
What kind of naughty child are you?
Fine, I'll wash.
I've washed my hands now.
Can I eat now?
You are back so soon.
I thought there was a burglary.
Which burglar would treat you so well
by cooking
and making hotpot for you?
Something's really off, then.
You came home early
and made dinner on your own.
Did you make a lot of money?
I know.
A huge bonus.
He Xiuguang's case is closed, right?
There's one more good thing.
What is it?
Fine. Just tell me. I can't guess it.
Shen Xiezhi and I are in a relationship.
Seriously?
Finally?
That deserves a celebration.
I wish you and Shen Xiezhi
could live in harmony
and give birth to a child soon.
What's that?
There's nothing wrong with that.
What did you say?
I am in a relationship.
Really?
With whom?
Is it related to that gift of yours?
The cat is finally out of the bag now.
Yes. It's her.
I knew it.
You can't hide anything from me.
Find one day
and bring her back to meet us.
It's still too early.
We just got into a relationship
and you're already
trying to question her.
How can you misunderstand me?
I am not a close-minded parent
who is picky about girls.
Also, I won't contact her in private
before you bring her home.
Yes.
You must approve of everything.
We just want
to find an opportunity
to have a meal together.
Sure.
I'll ask her later.
I'll try to get my client's opinion.
That's great.
Go inside.
I saw you
coming out of Mr. Guan's office
with a serious expression.
What happened?
Well...
I'm going to tell you, then.
Speak.
I told him
about your plan to usurp the throne.
Enough. Just tell me.
I'm just annoyed.
Mr. Guan is very unhappy.
Didn't our team just hire Lawyer Wang?
After he joined,
he ruined my case immediately.
He ruined
the sure-win case?
Look.
Well,
his results were good in school,
and he was a member
of the students' council.
However, he had no experience in society
and didn't know how to adapt.
The lawyer on the opposite
just used a few tricks
and tactics
and made Lawyer Wang fall into the trap.
Yes. This is
the most troublesome thing now.
Why don't we just
hire a few more people?
Do you think Ronghe Law Firm
can't hire anyone?
Yes.
We can hire people, indeed.
This is exactly what Mr. Guan
was discussing with me just now.
If we have an official recruitment,
our HR department
can get a group
of so-called ace students
from the best law schools.
But you know
that litigation
requires people with talent.
Right?
Can you think of
any suitable people?
Let me think about it.
Please think about it.
Someone came to my mind.
Wonderful.
Look.
Send her contact to me.
I'll meet her tomorrow morning
and treat you to lunch in the afternoon.
Pick any place you want.
I've been saving her for myself.
Here. Hold your cup.
I...
Come on.
I really need this person.
You are a talented person.
I only have talent, but I have no one.
You don't need me.
Your team doesn't need anyone.
Your talent alone is enough.
I need help.
It's hot.
Since both of you
have decided to be together,
you should stop overthinking.
Your main thing now is
to deal with your work problems.
Have you
already considered changing areas?
Right now, it seems like changing to
another area is easier for me.
However,
I don't know if I can find a job
so suddenly.
I'm sure you can.
You are now an influencer
followed by a major influencer.
You'll be fine.
I only
feel sorry for Lin.
He finally got me
to work for him here
so he can play sports.
If I resign suddenly,
what will he do?
The institution stays,
but people come and go.
Lin still understands that.
Don't worry about him for nothing.
Just take good care of yourself.
He has a car and a house, after all.
He even has an excellent wife.
Before his children graduated
from high school, he already bought his house.
What about you?
I don't know how to tell him.
Just tell him
your heart has been covered,
and you wanted to experience
being the female lead of a love drama.
I'd rather say
I've become a famous influencer
and have to leave.
Perhaps he will feel happy for me
and even send me off happily.
Nothing wrong with that.
This is amazing.
(Unknown Number)
Hello.
I am Ms. Lou Yue's assistant.
Are you Qin Rui?
Ms. Lou?
Yes.
A call from Ronghe Law Firm.
Go ahead.
Are you free tomorrow?
Our partner wants to speak to you.
Me? Yes.
I am free. I can do it.
Sure.
Do check your messages later.
We will send you
a text from the law firm.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Shen Xiezhi brings you good fortune.
Hold on.
Is this for real?
I didn't even
send Ronghe Law Firm my resume.
I'm sure you are too excellent
and have been appreciated by Lou Yue.
But the people at Ronghe Law Firm
are still working at this hour.
It's too competitive.
Life is stressful over there.
Why are you sighing?
This is good news. Eat.
(Are you asleep?)
(Not yet. What is it?)
(I'm going to an interview
at Ronghe Law Firm tomorrow.)
(Cheer me up.)
(That's wonderful.)
(That's one of the top-tier law firms.)
(But I don't feel confident.)
(Lawyer Qin gets nervous too?)
(What about
that fearless persona of yours)
(that is willing)
(to go through anything
for your client?)
(I was thinking)
(that if I joined Ronghe Law Firm,)
(what would happen if you
got promoted to the High Court.)
(Don't worry.)
(I won't get promoted
to the High Court so soon.)
(Just go to the interview
with peace of mind.)
(Besides,)
(Didn't we agree)
(to focus on the present
during the day?)
(We'll talk about what happens
in the future.)
(Are you swamped by love?)
(Do your best.)
(Rest well tonight)
(and calmly face
what's to come tomorrow.)
(All right. Got it.)
(Marriage Legal Counsel)
(I'm probably the one)
(who is swamped by love.)
♪Turn around for every part of life♪
♪Rushing between buildings♪
♪Caught in the grind of daily living♪
♪Facing the surging waves of life♪
Hello.
Is this Mingding Building?
This is it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
♪Ready to chase dreams
through sleepless nights♪
♪For the distant place we long to reach♪
Let's go over them again.
Here. Here, too.
(Ronghe Law Firm)
Get to work first.
Hello.
You must be Qin Rui.
Yes. I'm here for an interview.
This way.
Thank you.
♪Even if the road
beneath my feet is winding♪
♪I still look ahead with hope♪
♪I will run toward the future♪
♪Sweeping away the dust between us♪
(Lou Yue, Senior Partner)
(Ronghe Law Firm)
Mr. Lao.
Wansheng Group's diligence report
for this year is done.
A dozen of our people
worked on it for half a month.
Shouldn't you reward us?
Yamei Holding Group rewarded our team
with a Northern Lights Europe trip last year.
This year,
try to arrange something.
Come in.
Sure. I have an interview here.
Let's talk later.
Sure.
I'm hanging up.
Ms. Lou.
Come in.
Sit.
I didn't expect to meet you again.
Yes.
I didn't expect us
to be fated.
What do you think?
Are you a little surprised?
I personally asked for you.
Previously, in an internal meeting,
someone used Rui's Legal Lens
to explain his points.
A few senior lawyers and I
found it interesting
and followed your account.
Ms. Lou, thank you for your appreciation.
I remember you had a case
called "The Kind Teeth".
Yes.
This is a good title.
It helps instill legal awareness
with a clear line of thinking.
It also shows a solid grasp of the law.
In this era,
lawyers
can no longer
study laws and cases in a strict manner.
They still need to know
what the public is thinking.
So, I asked my assistant
to call you.
So,
what do you think?
It still feels like a dream to me.
All right.
I want you as my assistant lawyer.
You'll work under me from now on.
Oh.
The other lawyers
I told you just now
also have a strong foundation.
That's what you are lacking.
You need to catch up soon.
Don't worry, Ms. Lou.
I will surely work hard
and not disappoint you.
Do your best.
(Lian Yongjiu's Interview)
Ms. Jing.
What's wrong, Ms. Jing?
You don't look too happy today.
How did your husband's interview go?
Don't mention it.
He rejected the job on the phone.
HR required him to travel
on a business trip.
Don't you think he's stubborn?
If he goes on a business trip,
I can take care of the children.
Otherwise, we can still find a nanny.
But he just rejected the job.
Exactly.
Xiao Bing and I are also around.
Besides,
my in-laws
also have nothing to do at home.
Seriously.
Should I call Fan and ask him again?
Is that fine?
What about it? Let's ask him.
What if it's possible?
It's Fan.
Hello.
Fan.
What a coincidence.
I was just about to call you
and you called me first.
Is this
about Lian?
It is.
Really?
Fan,
I want
to explain this to you.
Mr. Lian was worried that no one
would take care of his children
when he was out on a business trip.
You should know
that his wife is our deputy chief judge.
She's also very busy.
He was afraid
that he would be wasting your time,
so he rejected the offer.
This is all negotiable.
He is the project manager
so he doesn't have to be
on the frontline all the time.
He can arrange
most of his business trips.
Does it mean he still has a chance?
Absolutely.
Give me his phone number.
Let me contact him directly.
Sure.
Let me share your WeChat contacts
to each other.
I'll also send you his number.
I still have a meeting to attend.
Talk to you later.
Sure. Talk to you later.
Thank you.
Done.
He is really lucky.
What do you mean by lucky?
He has a good reputation.
Everyone knows about it.
It's still thanks to you.
It has nothing to do with me.
Anyway, thank you.
Enough with the courtesy.
I won't accept it.
I'll take your pawn.
Let's see your next move.
This is bad.
Hello. Welcome.
She's looking for you.
What are you pulling?
Are you breaking my momentum?
Probably about
your retirement insurance.
Why are you here?
- Let us speak for a moment.
- Sure.
Come and sit here.
What is it?
Why have you come here to find me?
Director.
Director?
Why do I have a bad feeling about this?
Did something happen at the law firm?
Nothing can happen at the law firm.
Besides splitting the profit,
you don't need my help
with anything else.
Go ahead.
What is it?
My retirement insurance is up?
I can't renew it anymore?
Director,
I...
Is this a difficult thing to tell me?
Didn't we agree to it?
As long as you can find another job,
just tell me.
I will just
close up and leave.
Where is your next job?
What are the benefits?
Do you need me to find out more?
Do you have a better future?
Is the employer someone ruthless?
Don't leave a bad place
and end up at somewhere worse.
It's
Ronghe Law Firm.
I have nothing to say about that.
Have you eaten?
You must be hungry.
Later, let's go out
and have a farewell meal.
How about Fried Sauce Noodles?
Fried Sauce Noodles are best
for people breaking up.
You slurp the noodles until your mouth
is covered in black sauce.
Next, eat a few cloves of garlic.
That smell...
You won't even feel like staying.
Sure.
It's my treat.
Have you prepared the materials?
Wen Youyou's divorce case,
Ma Jinju's inheritance dispute case,
and Xie Changting's alimony case.
The details are all here.
- Where are you two going?
- External investigation at the bank.
A few of the parties' transactions
need to be investigated at the bank.
Will you be passing by Huaxing Road
at around four in the evening?
I have a commissioned autopsy
at Mingjing Forensic Center.
The family members want
to have a farewell with the deceased.
One of us needs to accompany them.
We need to go to three banks.
How should the route be arranged?
We'll depart now
and avoid the congestion
at Chengdong Road.
We'll head to ICBC first.
Next, we'll go to CCB.
Finally, we'll go to CMB.
CMB?
CMB is close
to Mingjing Forensic Center.
Let's go.
Sure.
Oh,
Fan said he was going to call you.
Did he call you?
He did.
On which day are you going to meet him?
Next Tuesday.
What time?
About two or three in the afternoon.
(Next Tuesday, two to three pm,
Talk to Fan about work.)
All right. I've marked it down.
(Judicial Appraisal Center)
Ms. Qin,
you are so busy
yet you're still here to accompany me.
(Reception)
I'm really sorry.
Don't worry.
I'm not busy at all today.
Thank you.
(Autopsy Room)
(For Examination Purposes)
This heart is quite heavy.
It's actually 270 grams.
It's my first time seeing
such a heavy female heart.
Her kidneys are quite heavy too.
Oh,
did you take a sample of the
lung lesion?
I did.
I took a huge sample.
It's enough for you.
I don't want to do it.
I don't want to do it anymore, Ms. Qin.
Calm down.
Return my father to me!
Madam Lu!
Get up.
What's going on?
I don't know.
Return my father to me!
Stand up.
Calm down.
Return my father to me!
What's wrong?
(Judicial Appraisal Center,
Evidence Room, Medical Records Room)
Ms. Qin,
stop persuading me.
Madam Lu,
if you refuse the autopsy,
the cause of your father's death
cannot be determined.
If the cause cannot be determined,
they will insist on your fault
and strip your right
to inherit your father's assets.
Let them do that.
Let them take his assets.
I'll give him everything.
I can't see my father being cut open
just to get a house.
Aren't you letting them
bully the weak, then?
You work so hard
but you still have to bear the crime.
Meanwhile, they did nothing
and made a lot of money.
You can't just spoil them.
No one will become
a filial child anymore.
I've caused my father's death.
How can I
still let him suffer after his death?
What am I doing? I'm not human.
I don't want to do the test.
I beg you.
I'm not doing this test anymore.
I'm really not doing it.
I don't care how the case is decided.
They can do whatever they want.
Judge Shen.
I beg you.
We should still
respect the party's intention.
No.
Madam Lu,
if you don't want to do the autopsy,
we won't do it.
However, we must not surrender.
I think there's still a chance
regarding this case.
Slowly.
Thank you.
Let me carry it.
All right.
Slowly.
Thank you.
Come on.
I've caused all of you trouble again.
Sorry.
It's fine. It's what we should do.
Go back and wait for an update.
Xiang Hui,
Send Madam Lu back.
Aren't you getting in?
I still have something to do.
I'll go back on my own later.
Sure.
Be safe, Madam Lu.
I've been busy and haven't had
a chance to introduce you two.
This is my roommate, buddy,
five-star chef,
godparent,
and angel investor, Liu Lian.
Hello.
I've heard a lot about you, Judge Shen.
Same here.
Are you
the fall guy
for the rearview mirror incident?
And also investor.
Lian and I were supposed
to have a meal together.
Why don't we eat together?
I suddenly remember
I have something to do at night.
Both of you should go first.
Stop finding excuses. Let's go together.
Let's go together. It's my treat.
There's also a dance performance later.
It's very lively.
Will this place be too noisy?
We must raise our voices later.
It's better than awkward silence.
Do you get it?
It smells nice.
They even have marbled beef.
Let's order this.
It looks nice.
Sorry.
Be careful.
You scared me.
Thankfully, you're safe.
What do you want to eat later?
We'll order it.
She hit me.
Table 16 in front.
First-come, first-served.
Both of you sit over there.
What are you doing?
I didn't say I wouldn't sit with you.
You prioritize your boyfriend over me.
What a narcissist.
I'll scan and order first.
Wait.
It's my treat today.
All of you know
I'm going to Ronghe Law Firm.
I thought
I would be unemployed for a while
to find a new job
after we got together.
Surprisingly,
Heaven treats me well
and gave me a new job so soon.
First of all, today is a good day.
We are also celebrating your new job.
However, before we came here,
I said I'd pay for this meal.
Both of you should stop fighting.
It's my treat.
Not bad, Qin Xiaorui.
You've grown up now.
I'll depend on you from now on.
I just got employed.
I'm probably just someone doing chores.
It's still a long way to go
to become a senior partner.
After all, you are still a lawyer
who works in a popular law firm.
Take it slow. There's no rush.
Excuse me.
Are you two a couple?
It's like this.
There's an event in our shop.
If it's your anniversary,
you will get a 20% discount
and a free fruit platter.
20% discount? Not bad.
Isn't it
your anniversary today?
Right?
Yes. We must take advantage of this.
It's free, right?
Sure. Sorry to trouble you.
- Thank you.
- All right. Let me get you the platter.
Thank you.
Judge Shen is really efficient.
You just posted it online
and he made it into his wallpaper today.
I finally understand what it means
to have love
is greater than everything.
But that doesn't work for me.
My love must be fed with carbohydrates.
Let's order. I'm starving.
You two may order.
You can order. What do you want to eat?
Tomato soup.
I want Mala soup.
Waitress,
he wants mushroom soup.
We want a pot with every soup.
We'll get everything.
Sure.
Great!
(Jiang Feng)
(You're awesome.)
(You fought your way out.)
(What's wrong?)
(The High Court's result is out.)
(You've been accepted.)
Not bad.
Let's take a selfie.
Come on.
It's my fault.
I'm the only one who enjoyed it.
She has never enjoyed such performances.
Yes. I don't like these performances.
I don't watch them.
What's wrong?
Are you really upset?
I...
I passed.
What is it?
The high court selection result is out.
I've been accepted.
I thought you went to Ronghe Law Firm
and I wouldn't affect you
by staying at the family court.
But if I go to the High Court...
Let me place your pot for you.
Thank you.
Let's drink soup.
Do you three need coriander?
Yes. Why not?
What about condiments?
We'll do it ourselves. Thank you.
Sure. The condiment bar is over there.
I'll go and make some dipping sauce.
Excuse me. Miss. Mister.
Do you have any desserts you fancy?
Sir, why don't you help her choose one?
I don't know how to make a choice.
These two
are our best sellers.
It's limited. Moreover, it's free.
Are you sure you don't want one?
Yes.
Since it's limited, why not?
I want this.
Enjoy.
I just made a simple sauce.
Why aren't you eating?
The meat is cooked.
Lian, have some meat.
Put it here first.
Come on.
You should eat, too.
Eat it while it's hot. Quickly.
Qin Rui,
sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
We agreed
that this relationship is a time bomb.
I said
we could give it a try.
I just didn't expect
the bomb
to go off so soon.
I know
everything I say now
is meaningless.
Shen Xiezhi.
Whenever I met you back then
and called you by your full name,
I was either angry
or addressing you
as Judge Shen politely.
I've never
called your name once.
It's a coincidence today.
This is a congratulations to me
for joining Ronghe Law Firm.
I also congratulate you
on going to the High Court.
After this meal,
I don't know
if we will have another chance
to meet again in the future.
I'm using tea in place of wine
to offer you a toast.
We must enjoy this meal.
♪Happy birthday to you♪
Happy birthday!
♪When a leaf can't find a place to fall♪
Eat. Don't space out.
Add more meat in.
♪Wandering without a destination♪
The vegetable is cooked.
Here. Eat more.
♪Until you appear and I see your eyes♪
♪I've decided♪
♪To stay by your side♪
♪Become your soaring wings♪
♪Let me be your safe haven♪
♪I want to be in your world♪
♪And cast away my disguise♪
♪Lean on my tender shoulder♪
(Grandfather)
Xiezhi,
when are you coming back?
My screen turned black
when I was halfway done
writing that thing.
Grandpa, don't touch the computer first.
I'll be there in half an hour.
Excuse me,
please turn around
and head to Yunshui Garden.
Sure.
♪Until you appear and I see your eyes♪
♪I've decided♪
♪To stay by your side♪
♪Become your soaring wings♪
What are you doing?
You can't drink.
♪I want to be in your world♪
♪And cast away my disguise♪
♪Lean on my tender shoulder♪
♪I want to be in your world♪
♪I'll be your shelter♪
♪I'll be there for you
until the very end♪
♪I want to be in your world♪
♪And forget the passage of time♪
♪You are the only one that I see♪
♪I want to be in your world♪
♪Everything is no longer faraway♪
♪I'll be there for you
until the very end♪
Xiezhi,
you're back.
Yes.
Grandpa's computer is broken.
I came back to fix his computer.
Let me ask you.
When we meet your girlfriend tomorrow,
should we give her a red envelope
or buy accessories for her?
Let me fix Grandpa's computer first.
Forget about the computer.
Where is your girlfriend from?
Let's go out and eat tomorrow.
What does she like to eat?
Forget about it.
Why not?
It's our first meeting.
We must give her a good impression.
We broke up.
What...
Oh.
I've been accepted by the High Court.
After a while,
I have to go and report for duty.
This is the WeChat chat history
(Chat History with Brother)
between the plaintiff and my defendant.
The deposit will be paid
with our father's retirement fund.
I heard
it was a fierce argument in the past.
I thought you were the one
who paid for it.
Turns out
the money is still your father's.
♪All the little things
between you and me♪
♪Woven into our lives♪
♪The building blocks of life♪
♪Shape the sky above us♪
♪Are you doing alright?♪
♪What are you struggling for?♪
♪Some questions weigh like mountains♪
♪How do we piece life back together?♪
♪So hate can fade
and love feels new again♪
♪Reclaim the barren parts of life♪
♪Walking this road
together, still hoping♪
♪Let me be the wind at dawn♪
♪Blowing away all the pain♪
♪Let me be the balance
that holds the weight♪
♪Where fairness stands♪
♪Within every heart♪
♪So many voices calling♪
♪Struggling, lost,
waiting for an answer♪
♪Light up the lamps♪
♪To answer those voices♪
♪You deserve to be happy♪
♪Loud and clear♪
♪All the little things♪
♪Woven into our lives♪
♪The building blocks of life♪
♪Shape the sky above us♪
♪Are you doing alright?♪
♪What are you struggling for?♪
♪Some questions♪
♪Weigh like mountains♪
♪Let me be the wind at dawn♪
♪Blowing away all the pain♪
♪Let me be the balance
that holds the weight♪
♪Where fairness stands♪
♪Within the law♪
♪And within every heart♪