How about we set work hours?
Can we really do that for making dramas?
-Let's just set the time first.
-Why?
We will just focus on work
during those hours.
Then I want to do something romantic
before and after work.
I think it'd be great
to have exact boundaries.
Does something sweet
have anything to do with me?
It has everything to do with you.
Now is the time
after getting off work, right?
Sure.
When he holds my hand,
I somehow feel comfortable.
I feel like I can hug him
and I won't regret anything.
I mean dating is all about
the process of breaking such trust.
Gosh, why would you say that again?
There's also a time
of restoring the broken trust.
That's dating, too.
You're thinking long-term, aren't you?
But the thing is,
I want to do only the sweet things now.
But something unexpected has happened.
I think it's good to go to work
in the morning.
Walking makes me feel good.
I'm walking too.
-I'm going to your office.
-Okay.
-Did you have breakfast?
-No.
I'm bringing some cherry tomatoes.
I see. I'll buy some bread
and milk on the way.
What kind of bread do you like?
Loaf bread.
Then I'll buy eggs too.
-I'll see you at the office.
-Okay.
I like loaf bread
I like milk too
I also like eggs
Delicious protein and calcium.
But if I keep eating, I'll keep farting.
How? Like this.
Then I should turn on the air purifier.
Why are you there?
I'm sorry. I was going to play a prank.
It was a bad idea.
And I didn't hear anything.
Don't lie to me.
Even a neighbor in the next door
would've heard it.
It's nothing. It's no big deal.
I once farted when you were around.
-It's okay.
-Don't come close.
I said it's no big deal.
It's just a sound.
It doesn't even smell.
I can't believe it.
It starts running all of a sudden?
I said don't come close.
We still have five minutes left
before we start.
I'll come back at nine.
And everything will be okay.
What? It feels a little too soon.
But it's something that lovers will
eventually have to compromise.
I don't think it's bad
to start it this way.
Gosh, I just don't like it.
Farting in around someone
you love is no good.
If it's something you can hide,
you better hide it.
I don't like it either.
But it just got laid bare.
Is it something to be serious about?
I'm serious. I really hate it.
So why did you fart
while putting eggs in the fridge?
Wait.
Are you sure it sounded like that?
Be honest.
Was it this cute sound?
Are you sure
it didn't sound a little dirty?
What sound was that?
It's a little hard to make
with my mouth.
Is it really something that serious?
She says it wasn't something
she can describe with her mouth.
That changes everything.
It's just a sound caused
by the vibration of a sphincter.
It doesn't matter how it sounds.
That's the sound. How did you know?
What? What did I do?
Gosh, that's not it.
Do it again.
I don't know. Why does it even matter?
It's a fart. That's what
we're talking about.
So what did Mr. Son say?
About the gas fairy you just let out.
It's inevitable
in the process of digestion.
And it has to be expelled.
-Stop it.
-If you hold it back,
the gas will be accumulated in your bowels
-and cause abdominal inflation.
-That's enough.
Some of the gas will be
resorbed to your blood
and released through your breath.
-So what?
-We need to be cool about it.
-I don't want to.
-Holding back your fart?
Doesn't it sound like an obvious lie?
Everyone knows we fart,
but we hide it and let it out in secret.
Sometimes you even get caught farting
and feels embarrassed.
Why would you do that?
Today was an accident.
Accidents are meant to be prevented!
Okay. Fine. Don't get upset.
The old saying "Farters blame the fart
on the bystanders" seem to fit this--
What did you just say?
I didn't say anything.
He's just a man.
He approaches the problem rationally.
But he can't say,
"Jin-joo, even your fart sounds lovely."
It's not that I want
an emotional approach.
It can be really annoying if it stinks.
Hey, why are you lost in thought again?
I mean it's good.
If you love someone, you just like
whatever the person does.
But there are things
that still bother you.
You should be careful
about the things that bother you.
There are times when you have a fight
and you don't even remember
what it was about after a while.
In most of the cases,
you weren't cautious enough
about the things that can be bothering.
Fine. Let's be rational then.
A human being farts
about eight times a day.
You should hide it four times
and open it the other four times, okay?
It might sound reasonable, but...
Farting is like a goalie.
Even if you block seven shots,
you might lose if you fail to block one.
So is there a conclusion to this?
Yes. I erased his memories
when we went for a walk
-after dinner.
-What?
Let's erase our memories
and start all over.
Do we have to do that?
I already heard and smelled it.
Gosh, don't say that.
Let's not be like this.
When we feel like fart,
why don't we hug each other
and let it out warmly?
Don't be ridiculous.
I don't want you to think that I'm farting
when I hug you out of affection.
I guess that's not good.
Okay.
Let's erase the memories and start over.
This is...
My gosh.
-What? It's gone.
-What?
-Your fart.
-It's not done yet.
It hurts.
-Your temple?
-Does it really help
erasing my memories?
The day we fought and got sick
You went to the bathroom
And made the sound
-Are you writing a song?
-Yes. I was bored.
-It's already titled "It Still Stinks"?
-I recently watched a short film,
which inspired me greatly.
It's the title of that movie.
What about it was so inspiring to you?
The husband fails in business.
And he has a fight with his wife
the day before they move.
He goes number two in the bathroom
and ends up making up with his wife
while smelling it.
What is this? B-grade comedy?
No. It's a beautiful love story.
What the... What's with the lyrics?
"The day we fought and got sick,
you went to the bathroom
and made the sound, boom, boom."
-What is this?
-Why? What's wrong?
It's so cute.
It reminds me of my ex-boyfriend.
We had a huge fight over a fart.
-Is the ex-boyfriend happen to be--
-Right.
It's him.
I see.
I guess he really hated it.
He hated it so much.
It doesn't matter anymore.
I want to send him a message
with this song.
That the smell will eventually go away.
Let me hear it once it's done.
Take it easy. You might get sick.
I get off work right on time. Don't worry.
And I don't eat a lot here.
Don't bring stuff to eat.
I'll just end up throwing them out.
Don't eat out.
All you need to do is cook rice.
And I'm dating Director Son. It's serious.
What?
What do you mean?
He's a director while I'm at work.
And he's my boyfriend after work.
How could you talk about
something so huge so casually?
It's not something huge.
It must've been
a difficult decision for him.
Why would he want to date you?
I think he's dating me
because of my looks.
-Is it even possible?
-Sure.
Bring him home.
I feel bad for him.
I should cook him a meal.
-You feel bad?
-Yes.
I don't fart.
So why? For your whole life?
I don't know why.
It just feels natural that way.
But I don't remember
why it feels natural.
You've never farted even once?
I just don't make a sound.
Then it means Dad has never heard
your fart his whole life.
That's right.
But Dad farts.
I know. But we're the older generation.
Try farting.
-What?
-Try farting around Dad.
Why?
You seem concerned.
I just can't hide my feelings, can I?
No. But you look just the same
whether you're concerned
about little things or big things.
What does that mean?
For example, you look the same
when you decide what to eat
and when you work on a budget
for billions of won.
-Do I really do that?
-Yes.
You're like a philanthropist who loves
all kinds of concerns equally.
I do hate discrimination.
But this sounds a little weird.
So what's your concern?
As your subordinate,
I'd like to help you find a solution
at least once.
It's about the casting matter.
Cheon I-seul is holding back for too long.
Whether she will work with us or not,
I just want her
to give us an answer quickly.
We just can't move onto the next stage.
You're right. She should give us
an answer quickly.
I wonder why something important like this
can't be absolute manners.
It's just too bad.
What are you doing?
I want to resolve it for you,
but there's nothing I can do.
So I'm just casting a spell.
Give us a call. Call us right now.
-Call and say that you'll do it.
-What?
It's from Cheon I-seul's agency.
Excuse me.
Hello, sir.
Yes.
Yes. Okay, then.
I'll call you back soon.
Bye.
Yes. All right. Okay.
Thank you. Bye.
This is so exciting
Ms. Lee. I got a call
from Cheon I-seul's agency.
Gosh, finally. What did they say?
She wants to meet
with the director and the writer.
It means we're almost there, right?
We should meet and convince her.
Call the director and arrange a meeting
as soon as possible.
Okay. And what do we do about Lee So-min?
The president of her agency
called us first.
Ask the director
and arrange a meeting if he likes her.
Okay.
Call me. Give me a call now.
HA-YUN
Okay. That's good.
Set it whatever time is good
for you and let me know.
Okay.
I guess we'll be casting Cheon I-seul.
I see.
But why do you look like
we didn't get her?
-I'm just nervous.
-About what?
How many difficulties do you think
we face while producing a single drama?
-Big ones or small ones?
-All together.
-3,600 times.
-Exactly.
But it feels like things are
going smoothly this time.
Why do we feel nervous
when things go smoothly?
A drama is like dating.
It's no fun when there's no crisis.
When it's not fun, it gets canceled early.
So I'm nervous. I'm afraid
that it will happen all at once.
It's okay. Just hang in there.
What's a director's job? It's hanging on.
Hold out and survive.
Just hang in there as you always do.
Whether it's a drama or dating.
Look at me. I'm hanging on so well.
You couldn't reach her yesterday again?
No.
She didn't pick up the phone after ten,
but she says she was asleep.
If she says she was, then she was.
Don't look at me like that. I'm fine.
I couldn't reach her for 16 hours.
So what?
It's no fun when there's no crisis.
I'm just holding out. That's all I can do.
Why did you lose so much weight?
I'm okay. I'm happy.
Beom-su, you should be happy too.
Why do you look so haggard?
Is he not here because he's busy
getting ready for the shoot?
I guess it's because of you.
He wouldn't want to see you.
He has to hold out.
If he does, everything will be all right.
All right.
Please tell us about So-min.
As a woman, person, and an actress.
She's honest.
Is it okay to talk casually like that?
I was just talking to myself.
Oh, okay.
Next question.
Is that all?
Is "she's honest" all you have to say?
Yes.
When did you first start
working with So-min?
Spring?
Was it spring?
What's with this jerk?
He either swears or is curt.
Is he doing this on purpose?
-He drinks cassia seed tea.
-Cassia seed?
-What about it?
-Do you know why?
I'm working now.
This isn't alcohol.
It's cassia seed tea.
Do you know
why I drink cassia seed tea?
I don't think I do. But maybe...
Because it's good for your eyes?
It's savory.
Because it's savory.
So what?
Isn't cassia seed tea bitter?
Is it savory? Let me take a look.
I can tell what people are like
just by looking at their eyes.
Let me see.
He's a successful commercial director.
Why is his office so shabby?
I don't know. I bet
he makes a lot of money.
He doesn't seem like
the humble type, though. Anyway.
I bet he loses money in gambling.
That's how he looks.
-How old is he?
-Thirty-four.
-He seems to have broad shoulders.
-He does.
-What about his height?
-Tall.
I can tell what type of guy he is.
-Your type?
-Yes.
He's so cute.
If he says it's savory, it's savory.
I don't mind gambling
as long as he doesn't lose my money.
Women like you are the reason
that bad guys don't stop being bad.
All right. Let's go to work.
She just arrives at the hair salon.
She just gets off the car.
-Hello.
She just says hello.
She just gets her hair done.
What?
I've thought about it.
Don't you think this documentary
will be so boring?
Why? Are you worried?
Everything is just so predictable.
What I think and how I work.
The only place I go to is a hair salon.
It's not even a beauty show.
It doesn't always have to be fun.
I know what you're saying,
but I'm a commercial actress.
I'm not trying to deny it.
So what? What do you want to do?
When we're together like this,
I should talk about Min-jun.
You could also shoot videos
of us being lovey-dovey.
-What?
-What do you think?
-What are you trying to do?
-Isn't it obvious?
We can add some of my love story.
People will like it
only when there's some romance.
Can we really do that?
No, we can't. But who knows?
I might get married to him
before the documentary is released.
I can do that.
My gosh.
I guess you like Min-jun a lot.
If I didn't, I wouldn't have dated him.
Then let me ask you my first
official question about Min-jun.
This is exciting. Go ahead and ask it.
Do you fart around each other?
What? Is it your first question?
Well...
That's one intense question.
But what's there to ask?
What?
Because I don't fart.
-You don't fart?
-No.
I didn't see this coming.
I'm serious.
I'm sorry. I went to the bathroom,
but I can't control what's happening
inside of my body.
We should be more careful
when we're in the car.
Okay. I'm sorry.
He intercepts your fart?
Was it part of his work or love?
Love.
That's one intense love.
As long as I'm with him,
I can live without farting.
Good for you.
So where are you going
after dressing yourself up like this?
I'm going to fight with the president.
You go to a hair salon
to fight against the president?
I need him to see with his own eyes
how amazing of a person I am.
You're amazing. I know that.
Of course I do.
But what? I'm only 32 now.
Why do you want me to play a mom?
I just can't help it.
It's not like I go around
asking people for mom roles.
It's not just a mom of a baby.
It's a mom with a teenage kid.
The drama is about school violence.
Do you want me to ask the writer
to change it into a story
about kindergarten violence?
Why should I be a mom of a teenager?
Do you want to be a teenager?
Why not?
I look young for my age.
Seon-mi.
You're a good actress.
You really are, but you don't look young.
Okay. Fine. I'll tell them no.
How could you say that as a president?
How could you say that to a president?
Hello, Seon-mi.
Hi. Carry on.
I told you to wait a few days.
I shouldn't accept
a supporting role right away.
What would they think of me?
There are a lot of rookie actresses
who want to play the role.
If you lose that role,
what would you think of me?
Why would I lose the role?
Am I worse than a rookie actress?
That's not what I mean. What if
they sign a contract with someone else?
-Then I should play the main role.
-Cheon I-seul is doing it.
Even if she wants to do it,
you should get me the role.
Am I the director here?
Do you think that's my drama we're making?
Can't you do that as a president?
So-min, you're a good actress.
But I can't buy you a drama.
Stop it. So you're not doing it, okay?
How could you say that as a president?
How could you say that to a president?
I'm glad that I decided not to do
a management agency.
I think he is
one of the pathetic ones out there.
It's better to yell and fight.
Some actors
pretend to be nice and obedient
in front of me,
but they suddenly move to another agency.
They say goodbye over a text message.
Are there people like that?
I've been in this industry for 20 years.
This is nothing.
I don't smoke, but I smolder inside.
But it's nothing. It's like...
Damn it.
I'm lonely.
Are you crying?
The shooting will begin soon.
You shouldn't be doing this.
You're the one who called me out.
You come out every time I call you.
Anyway,
Hwan-dong is doing a good job, right?
The problem is he's trying to be perfect.
He might melt down one day.
You should give him some advice.
Young people these days don't like advice.
They don't respect our generation.
But my assistant writers respect me.
That's a sad joke.
I'm lonely.
It gets lonely, indeed.
You have two dogs.
Oh, right. I should go feed my dogs.
I should get going.
-How much is it?
-Fifty-four thousand won.
-Did you include the soda?
-Yes.
We drank three bottles of soju, not two.
You took a bottle earlier.
That's right. It's 58 thousand won.
That's right. You should be careful. Bye.
That damn jerk.
Ms. Jung.
Mr. So.
Are you here alone?
Yes. My friend just left.
I came alone too. May I join you?
Sure.
By the way, why are you alone?
I have no one to hang out with me.
People should be good at playing alone.
It's not like I'm good at it.
I'm just alone anyway.
Thank you.
By the way, are you a cyborg?
Of course not. Why?
You never seem to get old.
You haven't changed a bit.
Gosh, stop it.
I have wrinkles on my face.
A bunny is still a bunny
even when she has wrinkles.
-"A bunny"?
-You do look like a bunny.
-What's going on?
-Mr. Sung.
So you're the one who just left.
I went to the restroom.
Gosh, it's been years.
-Why have you gotten so old?
-Like how?
In general. You should
be the president now.
By the way, you become more handsome
as you grow older.
You look like Antonio Banderas.
From The Legend Of Zorro.
"Zorro is everywhere."
And Ms. Bunny is only right
in front of me.
Is he crazy?
Are you crazy?
Hey, Zorro.
Come and catch me.
My beautiful villain, Montero Bunny.
Hop, hop, hop.
I have to hide.
Hop? You shouldn't be hopping.
You're too beautiful to hop.
No one has hopped like her ever before!
Is she an elk or a bunny?
I'm not an elk.
Is she a deer or a bunny?
I'm a bunny who wants Karaoke!
What do you think? Is it fun?
I'll try my best until the end.
I guess it's not fun.
I can't say it's not fun.
It feels like something's missing.
But I don't know what it is.
You're being too good,
so there's nothing missing.
Maybe that's why it feels like
something's missing.
No way.
It wouldn't feel like that
if it was perfect.
I sometimes felt that way
when I saw you work.
Everything will be fine
because you're good.
Am I
really doing a good job?
Why do you not believe me?
You used to believe me.
Where's Eun-jeong?
She's editing.
What about Jin-joo?
She went to her room with some beer.
What? Is she making
a video call or something?
Gosh, seriously?
I see. All right then.
I should do it too.
-In-guk, do you want to go to bed?
-Let's go to bed.
Okay.
Aren't you excited or something?
This is your first meeting
with an actress.
I'm not that excited.
I guess she's prettier than I am, right?
I think you're finished with that.
It's empty. What are you swallowing?
Gosh, it's refreshing.
Once Cheon I-seul is cast,
we will be busy.
She may be prettier than me, right?
I'm going to kill you.
-Did you have a good sleep?
-Yes. Did you?
-Hello.
-This way, please.
-Are they here yet?
-Yes.
-Hello.
He's the director, and she's the writer.
As you know, this is Cheon I-seul.
-Hello.
-Nice to meet you. Please have a seat.
We are not late, are we?
No. We came early.
I liked it because it's like a sitcom.
I mean, in a good way.
That's what we intended.
You're right about that.
The characters are fun,
and the lines are interesting.
But I'm a little worried though.
I'm the main character,
but she doesn't seem to have history.
It might look immature.
That's because the main character
has a clear goal.
She has an external goal as a writer
and an internal goal
she's trying to achieve through that.
She's the person who leads the story
and introduces the pains
of surrounding characters.
If she shows her growth that way,
I believe it will move people's hearts
in a simpler way later on.
-Oh, right. Mr. Son.
-Yes?
I look better from the left.
What? All of a sudden?
It just came to my mind all of a sudden.
So suddenly, yes.
You look better from the left.
Hello.
Oh, you're here.
This way.
-He's our director of photography.
-I see.
-He's the lighting director.
-Hello.
-It's hot, isn't it?
-Yes, it is.
Thank you for coming.
Let's go to the meeting room then.
They're just here to say hi.
Let's go to the meeting room,
I mean, the lounge.
-Okay. Fine.
-Shall we go?
This is our reference.
What we talked about earlier.
This one. This is it.
The camera should go under
and follow him.
-It's something like this.
-I see.
There you go again.
They specially made the equipment
to shoot this scene.
We can make one too.
This movie's budget was 200 billion won.
Why would you want something
from a Hollywood movie?
Why would you refer to an action movie
when you're shooting romantic comedy?
What's the budget
for this drama? How much?
What?
It's a little lower than this movie.
A little? Is it like
A little less than 200 billion won short?
It's a little lower than that.
There's no way we can do this.
Why not? What kind of people are we?
What kind of people?
We're people of delivery food.
That's right.
Damn it. I'm hungry.
Seriously.
Park Seo-joon, Jang Ki-yong,
Nam Joo-hyuk, Park Bo-gum,
Jung Hae-in, and Yang Se-jong.
Can we cast those actors?
No. We can't.
They are busy,
and the main characters
of our drama are women.
Then why are you naming them?
I'm just saying.
Why are you just saying that?
Jung Woo-sung, Gang Dong-won,
Ha Jung-woo, and Lee Byung-hun.
-Can we cast them?
-No.
Then why are you talking about them?
If we say names like this
before starting a project,
it brings us good energy.
What are you talking about?
-Gong Yoo?
-My gosh.
-All right, Gong Myung.
-I love him.
-I like him.
-My head hurts.
Stop. This is the concept
for Ju-yeon's house.
This is our reference.
Once you give us your opinion,
we will make revisions accordingly.
We don't need revisions.
I think we have to start over.
This is just a reference.
We should drop the whole idea.
Ju-yeon is a fickle character.
Do you think that matches her?
A characterful girl like Ju-yeon
would have sofa and furniture like this?
That's just what you can see
in any interior design magazine.
It's just a reference.
Stop saying that it's just a reference.
I mean, we will just refer to it.
I'm not saying I don't know the word.
What is this?
About the psychiatric treatments.
The data on psychological treatments.
-You should summarize it.
-I did.
I see.
Once I finish this, I'll make a doctor.
I guess you're more
likely to become a patient.
Thank you. You worked hard for this.
I'm so happy.
We will put these away first.
Move them.
Mr. Son, watch carefully. This is a scene
where Dong-u and Gyeong-jae fight.
We should show you a video of this,
but we wanted to get your confirmation
first. Just see how it goes.
Here we go.
I'm Gyeong-jae and he's Dong-u.
Okay. Wait.
You should do it while acting.
-You read the script.
-Okay.
All right. Do it again.
-You jerk.
-That's right.
He comes and Gyeong-jae flips him over.
So Gyeong-jae gets Dong-u on the floor
and gets him in an arm bar...
-Hey, move your arm a little.
-Okay.
I'll just pull on it.
Okay, arm bar.
So it's an arm bar, but Dong-u
manages to get out of it.
Gyeong-jae grabs him again
and triangle...
Damn it. Lower your head a little.
Okay.
Gyeong-jae takes him down like this.
The triangle choke is the point here.
-Sir.
-Yes?
-Director.
Gyeong-jae and Dong-u are
drama directors here.
Why would they suddenly do jujitsu?
A lot of people do jujitsu these days.
What's wrong with you?
How would they do the triangle choke?
I thought it would be
a little far-fetched.
-We did, right?
-Sure.
So we prepared something else.
-Bring it.
-Okay.
Watch.
Ready.
Head, head.
Head and straight to the stomach.
So this is what would've happened
if they learned kendo.
The quick moves are the point here.
Quick moves...
I'm glad it's not archery or gunning.
Watch it again. Hey, come here.
Let's do it again. All right.
-Are you okay?
-Did you not read the script?
Gosh, what's going on?
Am I dreaming or what?
Mr. Son.
I'm sorry to say this
when you have a headache.
But you need to decide the music director.
Okay.
I don't think Kim Tae-seong's
schedule will be available.
Then could you get me a list of directors?
Sure.
What do you think of Jeon Jo Mun-su?
He's been getting favorable reviews
with his recent works.
You mean Jeon Jo Mun-su from Plan D?
Yes.
Okay. I'll think about it.
Sure.
It's finally out.
We finally have the revised script
of episode seven.
It feels like editing
takes even more time.
Haruki is amazing.
What? Haruki?
-Haruki, all of a sudden?
-A regular life.
He listens to classical music
in the morning,
rock music in the afternoon while jogging,
and finishes a fixed amount
of his work every day.
He listens to jazz with some beer
feeling happy after work.
Before going to sleep, he chooses
the classical music for the next morning.
If you want to become
a master of your field,
you must have strict self-discipline.
You've been speaking for long,
but I don't get your point.
I do like music,
I do have the will to exercise,
and knows the happiness beer brings.
So I tried a regular life like Haruki did.
-Congratulations.
-But I gave up in two days.
I drank too much beer.
I got carried away
by the happiness from beer
and drank over and over again.
It's just too hard to lead a regular life.
So I made a decision.
If that's the case, I don't
have to become a master.
-I'll just be plain good.
-You need to make a decision for that?
This is what I did to be plain good.
Don't expect it to be the best.
I'm so excited.
This is a script that's just plain good.
I'll enjoy it.
You know what?
When the script is good,
the drama is fun however it's directed.
It will be fun however it's directed.
My headache is gone.
All right. Let's go to eat.
Where shall we go?
Let's eat something delicious.
It's six o'clock. I'm getting off work.
Can we leave now?
Sure.
-Thank you for your hard work.
-Good work.
See you.
Gosh, it's hot already.
-How may I help you?
-Turn on the AC.
The AC is on.
Thank you.
I think Ms. Lim and Mr. Son
are really cool.
They really are.
They both look a little clumsy,
but if you take a close look at them,
you can see
that both their work and love life
are very stable.
I know. It could be uncomfortable
to work together.
But once they finish their work,
they make honest decisions
about their feelings,
and take responsibility
for their decisions.
They don't even sway.
And that's why
they don't have to hide anything.
I think that's
how they respect each other.
That's amazing.
Do you know what's even more amazing?
They don't actually know
that they're so amazing.
That's why they don't seem condescending.
They are pure in a way.
But don't pure things
break easily?
Yes.
-Why don't you reconsider?
-Pardon?
He said
-he wants you to reconsider.
-I see.
Even though we're working together now,
I'll make sure our relationship
won't affect our work.
How do we look?
Like an assailant and a victim.
-Am I the assailant?
-Of course.
-Thank you.
-I'll be the assailant.
I'll try to become an assailant of love...
Stop it.
Thank you so much
for welcoming me like this.
I bet Jin-joo caused a lot of trouble
when she was younger.
But I don't think you scolded her a lot.
Her mom did. She beat her up a lot.
So she got beaten up,
but she didn't learn her lessons.
When she was nine, she packed her stuff
after she got scolded by her mom.
So I asked, "Are you
running away from home?"
She said yes.
She couldn't take it anymore.
So I told her, "It's cold outside.
Why don't you behave yourself
so you won't get beaten up and stay home?"
And she said "I'm not sure
if I could do that, Dad."
That's very simple.
So did she run away from home?
Yes. She came back in two hours
and got beaten up again.
I can imagine her face. That's funny.
I bet she was reckless and mischievous.
-Mom.
-Yes?
-Did you do that?
-What?
-That?
-Yes.
I did. I tried hard.
You don't have to try it so hard.
I mean, I farted around him.
But he didn't seem to care.
I know it's no big deal,
but it was a little disappointing.
Later on, I even tried harder to fart
out of spite.
Why would you try so hard?
If I farted that often,
he should've asked me
if I wasn't feeling good or upset.
Don't you think that's
what he's supposed to do?
You're being too serious about it.
That's right. It was really serious.
-I mean, your dad.
-What?
After a few days of farting...
-You're home.
-Hey.
He can't even hold his liquor,
but he came home drunk.
Hey.
What is this?
FULL MEDICAL EXAMINATION
I made an appointment.
We made a promise.
Once our kids get married,
we will go to the countryside
and live with nature.
But if we lose one of us,
we can't live with nature.
I'll be there all alone.
Without you,
it's all meaningless to me.
Your dad's friend recently lost his wife
from cancer.
She kept farting, and it smelled horrible.
But he just criticized her
without knowing about her cancer.
Damn it. All I did was fart a few times.
But we ended up talking about death.
That's just what people of our age do.
Hey. Just keep farting.
If you want to see him for a long time.
All right. Let me sing the song.
The day we fought and got sick
You went to the bathroom
And made the sound
Boom, boom, boom
I liked everything about you
But I hated it so much that day
Boom, boom, boom
It still stinks
It's not your fault
Gosh, I ate too much.
Can we walk a little more?
Sure.
What are you doing?
What?
That's enough.
I know what this is about.
I really do. I think this is enough.
The air is so nice.
It is nice.
Let's not just do it in a row.
That's just too much.
I feel like getting attacked.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Me too.
I'm safe now.
I spared your life.
Thank you so much.
You're the savior of my life.
It still stinks
It's not your fault
It's just smell
That eventually goes away
I'm sorry I hurt your feelings
It still stinks
It's only natural
Gosh, I'm not late.
-Hello.
Hello.
Hi.
Hello, Ms. Lim. Everyone's here.
Mr. Son isn't here though.
I'll bring some coffee.
What would you have?
Coffee, please.
Okay. This way, please.
It's been a long time.
Hello.
Or should I be more formal?
Let's just keep it casual.
Hello.
WHEN HE HOLDS MY HAND
I SOMEHOW FEEL COMFORTABLE
I FEEL LIKE I CAN COUNT ON HIM
I FEEL LIKE I CAN HUG HIM
AND I WON'T REGRET ANYTHING
I MEAN DATING IS ALL ABOUT
THE PROCESS OF BREAKING SUCH TRUST
I GUESS YOU LIKE MIN-JUN A LOT
IF I DIDN'T, I WOULDN'T HAVE DATED HIM
IT'S OKAY, JUST HANG IN THERE
JUST HANG IN THERE AS YOU ALWAYS DO
WHETHER IT'S A DRAMA OR DATING
LOOK AT ME, I'M HANGING ON SO WELL
I'LL BE THE ASSAILANT
I'LL TRY TO BECOME AN ASSAILANT OF LOVE
You're a writer. You shouldn't go out
drinking, especially not with men.
Mr. Sung, are you jealous?
I'm the CP of this drama.
I have to protect my writer.
What happened to your chin?
A shaving accident.
You should pluck up your courage
at a time like that.
Who bought you that?
You don't use electric shavers
because your beard is soft.
Let's do something fun.
-Let us be bold and go somewhere far.
-Yes!
Let's go somewhere farther away next time.
Let's think and feel a lot of things.
It's time to find something
we wanted to find during the trip.
But I've already found it.
I'll give you an important mission.
Is he doing some kind of
community service here
to make up for his crimes?
I saved her.
That was very righteous of me.
Are you worried it might seem
like you're trying to get over him
and it would disappoint him?
-Can I give you a hug?
-Why would you hug me?
Because you're sad.