In-guk, this is weird.
I know this can't be,
but strangely, my body feels light.
I bet. It's because we overslept.
I see.
-It's not the weekend, right?
-No.
-It's not a national holiday, either.
-Right.
In-guk, didn't you hear the alarm?
-Why didn't you wake up?
-Beats me.
Why didn't you wake me up?
You didn't on purpose
to be late for school, didn't you?
I'm not sure.
Come on.
Wake up. Please.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Good morning.
Hello, sir.
I'll clean up.
You need to get to work.
You didn't get much sleep, either.
Are you worried about me?
I'm sorry.
I'll clean it up. I made the mess.
-Hi, ma'am.
-Hello.
Hello.
-Hi.
-Hello.
Is Ms. Hwang here yet?
Well...
-Let's have a meeting this morning.
-Okay.
It's not even urgent.
Why did you stay all up night?
What?
Just because.
I have a lot of footages,
so I've been getting stressed.
And I had a slight headache.
You worked when you had a headache?
That means you're a workaholic.
It's better than being a gambler
or a drug addict.
Most people would do
something called resting.
I see. You're right.
You never go for a run.
Why did you suddenly want to run?
You didn't get much sleep, either.
You're right. Why won't you let me sleep?
People might get the wrong idea.
Aren't you tired?
Something didn't feel right
when I was with them.
Them?
They seemed younger than I expected.
Who? You?
No, them.
What's wrong with that? What?
They were prettier than I remembered.
What's your point? You're prettier.
Obviously.
Then, what's wrong? What is it?
I'm prettier,
but it wasn't overwhelming.
Goodness, damn it.
I'm an actress, so I take care of myself.
Even without that,
I was prettier than them.
So I should be overwhelmingly
prettier than them.
but for some reason,
my presence wasn't overwhelming.
So you're saying that you won,
but you own by decision?
You didn't knock them out.
You scored more points?
Is that why something doesn't feel right?
No, there shouldn't have been a match,
to begin with.
But I think you're setting up
the match on your own.
Let's go. Get up.
I won't go. Hey.
You'll age faster
if you run without getting enough sleep.
Stop running.
I won't do it.
I won't.
JU-YEON, SIN-AE, AND HO-PAL
LOOK AT HER AS IF THEY FIND HER PATHETIC
SHE AWKWARDLY WINS AT HO-PAL
-Jin-joo.
-Yes?
It's hard, isn't it?
No, I'm okay.
I just feel like I'm going to die soon.
You're okay. You didn't say
you were about to die right away.
I'm happy.
Rest for a bit.
Yes. I think I need to rest.
-How should I rest?
-While sitting up.
While writing your script.
Right. Rest up like that.
You give me a lot of moral support.
I'm glad to hear it.
She's working hard on her scripts.
How can I ask her to include
a massage chair in her scripts?
I'm happy to get sponsors, but still.
Whatever. Anyway,
until she finishes the script
for the eighth episode, don't call her.
Besides, why massage chairs?
I won't accept that.
Are we clear?
-Hey, why are you so upset this morning?
-Your face is more upsetting.
Are we running an inn here?
He's busy
because he'll start filming soon.
And I'm busy because I'm dating.
We're busy for different reasons.
Good for you.
-I guess things are going well.
-Yes.
Hey, Da-mi doesn't answer my calls
or texts when she goes out for drinks.
I was really upset, so I did
the same thing to her yesterday.
So that's going well.
Yes. I didn't check my phone last night
and went drinking and had fun.
-Do you know what happened to me, then?
-What happened?
I got tired.
Oh, right.
Something more important happened.
-What is it?
-Da-mi didn't text or call me at all.
She can see right through me.
Just go to sleep.
Go to sleep.
I should drink a cup of horse bean tea.
I sort of expected this would happen.
But my feelings for her were strong enough
to make me risk it.
If I were to disregard my feelings
because things may be awkward between us,
I thought that
it would be a silly thing to do.
If you need an explanation
to help you understand,
I will do so.
You don't need to explain this to me.
Don't worry.
Will you keep avoiding me?
-I didn't avoid you.
-Is that really true?
-I just turned away from you.
-They sound about the same.
Okay. I cannot force anything.
I understand.
Sir.
-Do you want to arm-wrestle with me?
-Arm-wrestle?
It's an unexpected turn of events.
I want to beat you at something.
With my strength.
Do you think you can beat me?
Well,
I don't think it will be hard.
What is this match for?
Money? Honor? Love?
All right. Whatever it may be,
don't be a sore loser.
Even if there's no return match,
you can't call the other a coward.
Even if your wrists break,
you'll cover medical bills on your own.
All right. Get ready. Go.
-Why are you staring at me like that?
-I'm working.
Sitting there is part of your job?
You're a writer.
You shouldn't go out drinking,
especially not with the president
of an agency,
especially not with men.
Which one is the problem?
His job or his gender?
He is the problem itself.
Mr. Sung, are you jealous?
I'm the CP of this drama.
I have to protect my writer.
I don't think a writer whose drama
is about to be filmed should drink.
I heard the writer, Park Hae-yeong,
doesn't even eat raw food
to avoid getting food poisoned.
That's the responsibility of a writer.
Just by looking at you, I feel exhausted.
That's a skill.
-Hello.
-Hi.
I made an appointment with Ms. Jung.
I see. Okay. You can go in.
-Did you cure your hangover?
-Welcome. Come in.
What? Why are you here?
I'm the CP of this drama.
Didn't you know that?
Why are you here?
What would you like to drink?
Anything cold will do.
I came by to give her the profiles
of the actors in my agency.
She said there were still
a few roles to fill.
Did the president have to come himself?
It sounds more like a manager's job to me.
No, I do things myself.
That way,
they'll get a chance to audition.
Give them to the director.
Why did you barge into her studio?
You're distracting her from her job.
She asked me to come, so I did.
Considering the effort you make,
the outcome doesn't seem so great.
That's why I work harder, sir.
I said that to piss you off.
-Why did you laugh?
-No, I'm pissed off.
That's how you look when you're pissed?
Yes. This is how I look when I'm pissed.
You're ugly.
Please allow me to tell you
that you are twice...
No. You are three
to four times uglier than me.
Thank you for the cool drink.
Here you go.
Here's the profile I promised you.
I'll have a talk with the director.
Put in a good word for me.
-Which one of us is uglier?
-What?
Which one of us is uglier?
What are you saying?
Mr. So is considered handsome.
That's shocking.
Then, are you telling me
that I'm considered ugly?
That's shocking.
Don't tell me that you didn't know
for the past 47 years.
What on earth is going on here?
I don't think
he really knew that about himself.
What happened to your chin?
A shaving accident.
Now that casting is done for the drama,
more PPL offers are coming in.
-That's great.
-Our director is the roadblock.
He's famous for turning down
product placement.
He is?
His reputation precedes him.
He said no to our marketing team.
I see. The massage chair.
The main character is a poor writer.
It's hard to place this in the drama.
I know that you're crazy busy these days,
but you have eight years of experience
in marketing. Please handle this.
There's too much money at stake
for me to side with the director.
Okay.
I'll do it.
-What?
-Ms. Hwang has a lot of work these days.
I can take care of something like this.
I'm not trying to marginalize you,
but you've been in marketing
for eight weeks.
This isn't just something
you can casually take over.
It's important from whom I learned
the trade for eight weeks.
I can do this.
It stinks
It's only natural
It's a nice song.
Yes. This song is from Plan D Studio.
The music director said
this might suit the drama well.
I was informed that if you want it,
you can use it as a soundtrack.
They are very eager to participate.
Should I set up a meeting?
-Yes, please do.
-Okay, I will.
But what happened to your wrist?
-Oh, this? I typed too much.
-I see.
-That must be hard.
-It's all right.
I'm sorry to bring this up now,
but this is the last of
product placement offers we received.
FRIED CHICKEN
MASSAGE CHAIRS
WE'LL SHOW YOU THE DIFFERENCE!
Gosh. I know that it's hard realistically
to produce a drama without advertisement.
I've done this before, haven't I?
For my last drama,
I actually persuaded the writer
to include product placement.
But a massage chair
doesn't fit in our drama.
We have a small set to begin with.
Where would we put this?
You can put it in for one episode
and take it out.
This isn't a hand massager. It makes
no sense to take out a chair this big
after using it for a day.
You can come up with an episode
that supports that.
The episode can be random.
You can just place it in one scene.
-It's easy.
-You think that's easy?
Of course, it is easy.
I can give you an example.
-Mom.
-In-guk.
Mom. I've been worried.
My gosh. Tell me about it, my son.
I am so bored.
That's why you've been worried.
In that case,
let's spend our time in a meaningful way
with something I prepared in advance.
Mom, what is this big thing?
You know what it is. Why ask?
Mom, I don't really mind,
but I'm just curious.
I told you I was bored,
but why are you on the massage chair?
There's no context in this scene, anyway.
Mom, I can't understand
what you just said.
And why do we have a massage chair
all of a sudden?
I think that's kind of random.
In this world,
various types of lifestyles exist.
And at times, our beliefs
could be compromised based on
reasons we cannot say no to.
It has to be placed in the drama
for 15 seconds. Please wait.
Okay. It's good now.
I'll come down since it's been 15 seconds.
Since you've started getting the massage,
you should finish it. I can wait.
Shall I?
-Like that?
-Yes, just like that.
-You're a genius.
-Thank you.
All right. Let's go talk this over
with my team.
Wait. Then, you'll include this
in your scene, right?
We just did.
We already did that.
-Thank you. Good work.
-Gosh.
It was nothing.
Since you worked hard,
you should have a sip of this.
Shall I?
We're amazing.
-It's all good now. Let's go.
-Okay.
Let's go.
What should we get?
-This place serves good kimchi stew.
-Right.
We'd like to order, please.
Excuse me. Weren't you on TV?
Yes.
I was on TV once. You recognized me.
I'm sorry, but could you please leave?
I don't mind,
but the owner asked you to leave.
Okay.
Let's go.
Are you upset?
Of course. We lost a restaurant
that serves good food.
Is their food good?
Yes.
That's a shame.
Do you want pho?
Sure.
Lately,
he's been showing up in my dreams a lot.
Usually, he doesn't say anything
or gets extremely mad at me.
That's him in my dreams.
Have you seen him behave similarly before?
Not at all.
He's not that kind of person.
He always smiled
and cheered me on.
He was really committed to the point
that it could be boring.
Are you worried
that he might be disappointed?
-Pardon?
-What I mean is,
are you worried it might seem
like you're trying to get over him
and it would disappoint him?
No.
I feel like I'm using him.
It's not that I'm disappointed.
I feel sorry.
I still
need him.
And I miss him.
So is that why
I'm mad at myself?
-I'm sorry.
-You can cry here.
It's odd though.
It's not your fault.
Why would you feel sorry?
Aren't you being too considerate?
That might offend him more.
If he does that again next time,
don't lose to him.
Get angrier and yell at him.
Have you two never fought?
We never fought.
You can take this opportunity, then.
Have a big fight. Okay?
He was the one who messed up.
Why is he making you the bad one?
That's how all men are.
Right.
I'll give you an important mission.
-A mission?
-Yes.
-You must complete it, okay?
-Okay.
Take a break from work.
Well, that's...
Don't people say that to you sometimes?
"Why don't you go on a trip?"
They all say that for a reason.
Even if you don't call it a trip,
spend some time
in a different environment.
In a different environment?
-You said that you made donations.
-Yes.
Have you been to the charity organization?
No.
I just made donations to the foundation.
That's easier, then.
Treat it as a break and pay a visit.
I'm sure it will be helpful.
They say that true rest is not at home.
What brings you here?
Glad to see you didn't cook this time.
I'm hungry.
You've never come here
because you were hungry.
Well, I was walking and thought about us.
When I did,
we looked like two pitiful siblings.
You're hungry because we're pitiful?
We need to have a lot of energy
to stay pitiful.
You do have a point.
I want to have a meal with my brother.
I'll accept it.
-Did something happen?
-Yes.
I had pho for lunch.
I see.
-Let's get Vietnamese spring rolls.
-Okay.
I'm tired. Give me a piggyback ride.
-Get on my back.
-Really?
Is there a baby carrier around here?
Really?
I'm tired.
What's happening?
This is sad.
Are you crying
as you're writing your own script?
Don't you laugh, cry, and say the lines
when you write scripts?
-I do.
-That's it.
Goodness.
Living my life is already hard enough.
But a screenwriter has to keep up
with the characters' emotions.
If so, shouldn't the screenwriter
work for half the time
other people work for?
That's a great line.
I should use that.
I know we work out of passion,
but people have to understand
when screenwriters throw a fit.
I like that. Thanks.
"You have to understand
when screenwriters throw a fit."
Thanks.
I'm tired.
SMART SHAVER
POMEGRANATE STICK WITH RED GINSENG
Ms. Hwang, you must be tired.
Make sure you take one.
I don't get it.
Is it because of my laugh lines?
DERMATOLOGY CLINIC FOR LAUGH LINES
Do you want to arm-wrestle?
I lost my wrist.
Let's play just one round. Just one round.
I'm serious.
Give me your arm. Give it to me.
Is this our first time having this dish?
Yes.
Can you give us one bowl of pho?
Who bought you that?
I bought it.
You don't use electric shavers
because your beard is soft.
YOU HAVE A NEW MESSAGE
This is Ha-yun, Jae-hun's girlfriend.
I can take care of my own boyfriend.
THIS IS HA-YUN, JAE-HUN'S GIRLFRIEND
I CAN TAKE CARE OF MY OWN BOYFRIEND
Damn it.
You'll die if you keep running!
I want to be happy even if I'm exhausted.
You must be tired.
At least, I sleep well.
Preparing to shoot must be exhausting.
I never took a break.
It's hard to hire the staff, isn't it?
The budget is the same, but the living
expenses and rates keep going up.
We have never had enough budget,
to begin with.
Isn't it tiring to be so handsome?
I was making a joke
because everyone seemed exhausted.
When I saw his face after making
that joke, I realized he's handsome,
so the joke's on me.
Drink this since you're tired.
A light drink.
That's enough.
Let's do something fun.
I can't work like this. Let's go somewhere
and have fun. We should stop working.
I'm torn in two
because my heart wants to say yes,
but my body knows I should say no.
Will you follow your heart or your body?
There's this saying.
"One finds what one wants to find
when one's back from the trip to find it."
We should go somewhere.
Let's not get stressed out thinking
we should've picked a farther destination.
Let us be bold and go somewhere far.
-Yes!
-Nice!
Awesome!
YEOSAN CITY HALL TO YEOSAN CATHEDRAL
JANGEUNG CHURCH
YEOSAN CITY HALL
YEOSAN CATHEDRAL
Hello.
Welcome.
As you requested,
I didn't tell them in advance.
When they hear a sponsor is visiting,
they usually all come out and say hello.
No, I don't want that.
That's what I thought.
You can take your time to look around.
You can talk to the kids later.
Since you're here,
if you're up for any volunteer work,
we have more than enough to give you.
You can get as much work as you want.
We must give back as much as we received.
Did that sound weird?
I was joking. I'm sorry.
-No, it was funny.
-Right?
Do you want to take a photo
with the kids later?
Is it not allowed?
No, it's not that.
Our kids are used to taking group photos.
It's just that we also look after
disabled kids here.
A while ago, an assemblywoman came here.
She insisted on giving a bath
to one of the kids. Damn her.
She took a photo of that
and posted it on her social media,
which made its way on the news, too.
Although we know it wasn't intentional,
we tend to stay away from taking photos.
I won't take any photos.
No, you can take photos.
Just be careful when you do.
-Okay.
-Okay. Shall we go in?
-Aren't they beautiful?
-Yes.
Goodness.
-Stop it.
-Did you guys eat?
-Yes.
-Okay. Don't go far.
-Okay.
-This is the cafeteria.
-Hey!
You're eating raccoons.
-Go away.
-Hey.
What's wrong? Are you leaving?
No. That guy in there...
-Do you know him?
-Is he doing some kind of
community service here
to make up his crimes?
Don't let him scare you.
He's not a criminal.
He's our angelic donor. He's Chairman Kim.
-Angelic?
-Yes.
We call him the Chairman.
Whenever he makes money,
he always makes a donation.
I wondered
how he was going to feed himself.
He comes here and eats.
When he's not on a project,
he practically lives here.
"Let's not get stressed out,
thinking we should've picked
a farther destination."
We were bold and came pretty far.
We're at Wolmido Island.
Wolmido is far enough.
There are over 20 subway stations
in between.
I like it. There's the ocean, too.
I like everything here.
The entertainment, food,
and the sights. I like it.
But we're here to work.
What do you mean?
Why did you choose a place in my script?
You came here to check out the location
for your shoot.
Location scouting.
Wolmido Island is an awesome place.
Look over there.
Look how much fun they're having.
Let's go somewhere farther away next time.
Let's walk a lot.
Let's think and feel a lot of things.
What's happening?
Why are you exaggeratingly
covering up your front
and looking at me like I'm a pervert,
but smiling at the same time?
A trip? Just the two of us?
Gosh, you're such a dog.
Excuse me. What are you thinking?
You want to go on a trip.
Just the two of us and somewhere far.
You want to experience a lot.
Hey. Why are you contaminating
such an innocent word like "trip"
with dirty thoughts?
Whatever.
What was that?
Why are you acting all flirty?
What's wrong with you, Ms. Lim?
Why are you acting like that?
Hello, Mr. Chairman.
Hey, mister.
Come on. I have a title, you know.
You keep calling me mister.
Let me introduce you to our guest.
Hey.
The cursing grandma.
I get the first part,
but why are you calling me a grandma?
-Do you know each other?
-I saved her.
That was very righteous of me.
Wasn't it more like cleaning up
what was in your way?
What do you mean?
She's a donor. Her name is Lee Eun-jeong.
Do you know her?
Donor?
Yes. We actually talked
about her not long ago.
The documentary filmmaker
who donated her entire assets.
I see. That... I see.
She's her.
I didn't know.
You should have told me sooner.
But
are you nuts?
How can you donate everything you have?
What? Nuts?
If that makes her nuts,
I'm looking at two
of the biggest nuts out there.
Two of the biggest nuts.
It's an honor. What an honor.
-Mr. Son. Ms. Lim.
-Mr. Son.
-Have one.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
This looks great.
When you're on a trip,
you should start it with a corn dog.
What do we do for fun
at a place like this?
Is this your first time here?
Yes, this is my first time here.
Don't people from the metropolitan area
usually visit Wolmido
before the age of 10?
I grew up in the South.
We have better oceans there.
You're having a good start
with the corn dog.
You can go on the amusement rides
if you want.
But there's something
we must think about in depth and plan.
Will we have grilled clams
and sashimi here?
Or will we not have a meal here
and go to Chinatown nearby
and have dumplings?
That's an important decision.
But isn't jjajangmyeon
famous at Chinatown?
Yes,
but I know a great dumpling restaurant.
Oven-baked dumplings.
That's a serious decision.
What should we do, Mr. Son?
That's what we need
to figure out together.
Jjajangmyeon? Dumplings?
Why do we need to think about this?
-We're supposed to eat all of them.
-Yes.
I'll eat all of it.
Of course.
We'll eat for an hour
and digest for an hour.
I didn't think about that. I love it.
Then, let's split into teams
and play games.
And the losing team will pay for the food.
-I'm in.
-Count me in.
-How should we do this?
-Okay.
Will we divide by gender?
Or will we divide by our roles?
We'll do hand-flips.
-Sure.
-Okay.
-Flip or don't flip
-Gosh. Nice.
-Yes!
-Let's go.
-Don't go easy on them.
-Take this seriously.
-Let's take this seriously.
-No joking around.
-No smiling now.
Don't joke around.
It looks like you hate washing dishes,
but you seem very experienced at it.
I don't want to do it.
Then, why are you doing it?
Because I have to.
You should try to look normal at least.
Why are you volunteering here
with the look that you hate this work?
It doesn't suit you.
What should I do
to suit this volunteer work?
It's your facial expression
and the way you talk.
Do exactly the opposite,
and it'll suit you.
That's lame.
What happened to the honorifics?
Who would speak with honorifics
when they talk to themselves?
I see. You've been talking
to yourself this whole time.
Balance.
-Pardon?
-If I only work, it gets boring.
If I only play, it gets boring,
so balance.
What's he talking about?
Let's see if I understood you correctly.
Are you doing this because you're bored?
To me,
this is having fun.
Having fun is important
for the sake of balance.
Do you know what happens
if there's no balance?
What happens?
You fall.
Do you know what happens if you fall?
It will hurt.
You got it right.
Come on.
You keep dropping your honorifics.
No one speaks with honorifics
when they talk to themselves.
Wait, no. Not the wall.
Try to hit the balloons.
Gosh. I don't think
I can zero in on the balloons.
We're throwing darts.
There's no zeroing in.
Let's take turns.
-Wait. What was that?
-Gosh.
-Stop.
-Goodness.
-Hold on.
-Wait, this... This is...
-We can't throw at the same time.
-Hey.
We're supposed to take turns to shoot.
-It's because we're rushing.
-Come on.
-Goodness.
-We can't throw at the same time.
-What is this?
-Gosh.
You can't hit my ball.
Gosh.
I said we can't throw at the same time.
That's it. Stop it. I'll pay for the food.
Nice try. Let's go.
Wait up for me.
It's ripped.
It looks good though.
I won! I won!
I'm proud of you.
Well done.
You should eat that. Dip it in the sauce.
-Well done.
-Yes.
-Great job.
-It came out completely.
Yes.
Look at you go.
You did well.
-Potato chips
What?
Do you have some kind of a story?
Something heartrending
and tragic, perhaps?
People always think I have a sad story
for spending my time here
when I'm perfectly fine.
I asked because
you don't seem perfectly fine.
I do have a story.
I was born into a middle-class family.
Our family wasn't filthy rich,
but we weren't poor.
And I had a happy childhood.
I studied hard and went to college.
And I became successful.
Is that it?
Yes.
You think that's heartrending and tragic?
Shall we listen to these kids' stories?
Do you know how heartrending and tragic
that this is the only story I have?
Seriously.
We ought to round up all those people
and make spaghetti sauce out of them.
Can I give you a hug?
What's your problem?
Why would you hug me?
-Because you're sad.
-Did I tell you that?
Even if that's true, why would you hug me?
A hug...
is cozy.
Damn it.
Why do you talk like that?
"When someone hugs you,
it's cozy." Say it at once.
Why do you pause
in the middle of the sentence?
Do I do that?
It's cozy.
Get off me now.
Get off of me.
Get off. Come on.
Hey, get off.
-Us, too.
-Darn it.
-Give us a lift, too.
-Get lost.
-Get off.
-We won't get lost.
-Come on, give us a lift, too.
-Don't touch me there.
Stop it.
Perhaps, we should've skipped the noodles.
-Wicked gluten.
-We should eat dumplings.
Is it true that in Incheon, they add
a fried egg on top of jajangmyeon?
Yes, it's true.
Deep-fried in oil.
-I can't eat that.
-Damn it. I agree.
But still, we came all the way here.
Shouldn't we drink soju
with grilled mackerel
at the Mackerel Street?
When you're full,
go for light food like grilled fish.
Yes. Since it's fish, it won't be heavy.
Okay. Let's do that.
You managed to pull out the conch.
I shall grant your wish.
Gosh, there's an abundance of food
in this city.
Did you drive here?
No.
Do you want a ride?
Well...
JANGEUNG CHURCH
When people take the bus,
they use the expression "take the bus
together," not "give someone a ride."
Is that so?
Do you not have a car?
Public transportation...
is fascinating.
Since transfers...
are free.
You can just stand there.
Are you trying to catch a cab?
One bus just passed by me last time.
For two, please.
Ma'am, one grilled mackerel,
gochujang stew,
one braised pot,
and rolled omelet, please.
This is different from what you said.
How many dishes did you order?
It's only one dish for each person.
-Let's finish all of it.
-That looks great.
Gosh, you deboned it nicely.
We can eat it with our spoon.
-All right.
-Thank you.
-Thank you. Let's dig in.
-Thank you for the food.
Dig in.
This calls for soju.
-Let's drink.
-Cheers.
-Cheers. I'll only clink my glass.
-This is so good.
-I'm so happy.
Jae-hun.
Have some rolled omelet, too.
I'm getting off at this stop.
Okay. Do you live in this neighborhood?
No. I need to transfer.
-Transfers are...
-Free.
The journey you took today is priceless.
Go home and get a present at home.
-A present?
-You'll find it at home.
To do that, what do you need to do?
Beep.
How do you keep his job as a director?
Can you lead a normal life like this?
-Bye.
-Take care.
I want to be happy even if I'm exhausted.
I'm exhausted, but I'm happy.
At least today was a complete success.
Isn't it more tiring to play?
Not really.
Right. It's just something people say.
Right. I prefer playing
to working. Always.
It's time for us to go back home.
It's time to find something
we wanted to find during the trip.
Well, it was a short trip.
Don't be disappointed
even if you don't find anything.
What?
But I've already found it.
-Really?
-Yes.
Here's the back I was looking for.
You definitely found it.
This is free, right?
-The back you're hugging?
-Yes.
It's not free.
I can actually pay you a premium for it.
Don't change.
I won't.
Promise me.
I found something, too.
I saw a different side of you.
Promise me.
I'll do it,
but I didn't know
you believed in these promises.
I want to believe it just for today.
Stop talking and promise me.
Stamp and seal.
Gosh, it's really okay.
It's late. Besides, you worked hard today.
Work hard?
I had so much fun today.
Is that so?
I'll drop you off at the main road.
Ha-yun might see me dropping you off.
I'm sorry
about the text message that night.
Gosh, don't even say that.
Actually,
I even thought about apologizing to you.
Gosh, don't even say that.
That's my point.
Something felt weird about that.
Never blame Ha-yun for it.
Women might feel insure about that.
She doesn't need
to feel insure now, anyway.
Ha-yun was sorry about
what she did to you.
She's not that...
I want to say she's not that rude,
but she had already been so rude to you.
So this is a bit...
You hate her, right?
Pardon?
I'm talking about Ha-yun.
You'll still be upset
even if she apologizes to you.
She behaved in a way
you couldn't understand.
And as you still don't understand
why she behaved that way,
how could you not be angry?
That's everyone.
You hate it.
Of course, that's only natural.
You should pluck up your courage
at a time like that.
The courage not to hate.
"The courage not to hate"?
It turns out you need nothing
but courage to achieve that.
Try it.
Love is more valuable than hatred.
Who were you with?
Never mind. I'm sorry.
What did you do today?
I waited for you.
I'm sorry.
I'm late.
You must be tired.
When you say yes.
I've been recording us very diligently.
I take photos and write things.
Look.
This is
an app where I can take photos
and leave short memos.
It's in private for now,
but I'll open it when we get married.
When you say "Yes, I will."
ONE-LINE JOURNAL
EUN-JEONG, HONG-DAE
This is the first photo we took together,
but you don't like this photo.
I'm sorry.
I'll put my head closer
to the camera next time.
As it's our first photo,
it gives me butterflies.
As time passes by
and reaches our exciting future,
let's look at these photos while smiling.
Well... Let's just say that I want
a taste of being cool, too.
They say no.
Let's go.
Get lost!
They're over there.
It was like that from the start.
"I want to stay with this girl a bit more.
I want to talk to her a bit more."
That's how I felt today as always.
I felt really crappy, but I held it in.
Gosh. I shouldn't have.
Don't you think
something is going to happen?
Like what?
I don't know.
Do you want to know?
We kissed for the first time.
I'll remember everything else.
You just remember this.
You kissed me first.
Today was the first time I saw you upset.
I thought about being upset at you, too
for a brief moment,
but I couldn't.
Because you were too beautiful.
What am I going to do?
I guess looks matter for me.
I went to the hospital.
I
miss you.
I WENT TO THE HOSPITAL
I... MISS YOU
The more I observe you,
the more reliable you are.
I have no doubt
that you will be brave even without me
because you are the love of my life.
I trust you. I do.
I really do, but...
Gosh, no. I don't.
Please
take care
of yourself
for me.
I will.
I'll do it.
I'll make sure I do.
I love you.
I told you not to come to my work.
Had you told me to come,
I wouldn't have come.
You still don't know me.
-Ms. Hwang!
-You want to take In-guk?
How about we live together?
To tell you the truth, I am...
I can't let you go.
-Delete them.
-What are you doing?
Say, "Please delete them."
-Come in.
-Just be nice to me.
I don't need you to be shy.
Why is he exchanging these photos
with you?
Those photos were no big deal.
They were cute.
Damn it.
Do you know
that being nice actually suits you?
-Thanks.
-For what?
I don't know. Just thank you.
Hey, it's not your fault.
What are you talking about?
I just want to switch the order
of Hwan-dong and your drama.
It's your fault.
You made her break her leg!
It's all your fault.
I want to see you.
But what can I do? It's our project.
Does he think I have nothing to do?
Damn it. That fool.
I was crazy busy.
That's an excuse.
Gosh, you know that both of us are busy.
Why do you let this upset you?
I'm going to be disappointed in you today.