MOON LOVERS:
SCARLET HEART RYEO
THIS SHOW IS A WORK OF FICTION
BASED ON HISTORIC EVENTS.
LAST EPISODE
Let me show you something
for your birthday present.
The Emperor has banned weddings.
But I prepared it secretly.
- Are you disappointed
- This is good enough.
Don't worry. I just wanted
to take you out of the palace.
We're still friends
even after the wedding.
I don't worry about it.
It's quiet here far from the main house.
You'll like here.
It's also close to my
favorite place, so come out anytime.
And this.
Thanks for saying that you want it.
Damn it!
You've mastered another skill.
I think you've practiced enough.
Let me see how sweet
you can be to your hubby.
Never mind.
Let's get in. I asked the loyal doctor
to stop by before he retires.
A doctor
I'm OK.
You've gone through a lot,
you should check.
Let's go.
There was no sign of fetus pulse
when you left the palace.
- But...
- It was very early stage.
Of course you wouldn't know.
Fetus Then...
As I have advised you before
your condition isn't good
from extreme stress.
but your pregnancy makes you weaker.
- If you insist on being pregnant...
- I'll be fine.
As long as...
- the baby is good, I'm OK.
- That's nonsense!
Please keep this confidential.
You should postpone your retirement.
- Stay in this house for awhile.
- Sure.
Please keep yourself warm always.
Also stay in bed as much as possible.
Baeka said their marriage
is just a mere formality!
But look at this.
It says the Fourteenth Prince's wife
was with him
while he practiced martial arts.
They were holding hands
and they care for each other!
Your Majesty.
You know her better.
They were close friends
since they were young.
And she's a lively person.
She also doesn't discriminate
men and women for her friends.
Su!
Why did you come out
You can't get cold with the baby.
Get up.
Don't worry about me
and go to your bed.
Why do you want to kick me out
on our first night together
Now that we see each other like this
we've gotten older.
The time has passed so fast.
Good days and bad days come around.
And they go around, too.
I've lived enough to know that.
Do you remember
when we met for the first time
I think it was
the Eighth Prince's library
Or when I saved you
When you were swinging
that big stick
I was so surprised.
I've never seen that
brave woman like you in my life.
And when you were in
fight with Eun.
Every time I think of it
I'd smile.
Your hair was messy,
Eun had this huge bruise on his face.
- You'd still show a bold front.
- Right.
How come you don't keep the promise
that you'll sing for my birthday
I've been waiting every year.
Fine, I'll sing this year for sure.
Do you remember that
You sneaked into Princes' bath.
What were you even thinking
Now that I see,
you were perverted somewhat.
That's not so true.
I was so shocked that
I couldn't see much.
Don't lie.
You saw it all, right
What about my body
From now on...
do not report about them.
Make sure I don't hear about them.
Finally we're alone together.
It's you and me
and me and you.
Without any worries...
I can love you as much as I can now.
ABOUT SIX MONTHS LATER
How's Su
How come the baby came out this early
But the girl is healthy.
She's very beautiful.
This girl was born...
dead.
Do you understand
Bring her to her nanny.
Do not tell anyone.
She's used up all her energy.
Don't worry about the baby.
The baby is lucky.
Very pretty and healthy.
The best nanny is hired.
That's good to hear.
So don't worry about the baby.
Think of yourself first.
Please get well soon.
Please.
Do you want to show
the Emperor the baby
I want to...
see the baby.
Sure.
Please give this to the Emperor.
Please make sure he reads
as soon as possible.
Wait.
It'd look strange if my wife writes
the same style as the Emperor.
Your Majesty.
This is from the Fourteenth Prince.
He won't get tired about it
Why won't you read it
It'd be full of complaints.
I don't want to feel bad reading it.
He said there's something
you must know.
He even sent a messenger.
Do you think I have to time for that
I'm sorry.
He has not come yet, right
I've sent many letters.
He must hate me so much.
Please send a messenger.
If the messenger conveys my message,
he'll come.
I did, but...
Right, I forgot.
I'll send a messenger.
Let's get out.
Let's get some air and get healthy soon.
I've called the best band in Songak.
I've also prepared peony blossom.
Don't you want to see them
Peony blossom
Do you have any particular song
you'd like to listen to
Please play your best song.
This song is popular with the story
that a court lady became
the Emperor's favorite after playing it.
The Emperor
I'd like to hear it.
Do you remember your promise...
that you'd regard my life...
as your own
My baby...
please...
take care of her for me.
Do not send her to the palace.
Why do you say that
He won't come.
Su.
In your next life...
will you remember me
I will forget about you.
I'll forget about everything.
Not even in my dream...
I won't remember...
Su wouldn't...
hate me this much.
They said she has been
sending you letters.
Did you read them
Life is like a dream.
Right or wrong,
love and hatred...
they all pass by with the time
and are buried.
Are you still upset for our love
The opposite of love is...
not hatred.
It's neglecting.
Because I left you
with hatred, not love
I'm always worried that
I may have made you
restless.
I still love you.
When you stood by me in the rain
giving up everything you had...
when you threw yourself for me
from the arrow...
that's when you've become
unforgettable for me.
I miss you.
And I miss you more.
But I can't get close to you.
I'm getting tired of coldness
from the sweetest person.
I hope we encounter again
on the curvy bridge.
I'm waiting for you...
every day.
Su!
Where's Su Where is she
Su.
Stop playing!
Su! Where are you
Where are you
Su! Su!
Why are you looking for her now
Don't pretend you're sad now.
You made me act this way.
It was your name on the envelope.
I didn't know it was from Su!
That's because her handwriting
is just like yours...
But you'd know that
she was dying at least.
I know you've put spies here!
Because you've shared the same room
and showed affection with her.
He didn't get any report about Su.
Su.
Don't go.
Please don't leave.
No, you can't.
She's my wife!
Get out of my way.
Su is dead but...
she's still mine.
Please!
You know it better!
Who Su would like to stay with.
If you really care about Su,
please stop fighting with the Emperor.
Haesu's life was...
stuck in our lives.
She couldn't do anything.
Would you...
still make her sadder
You...
Su...
What a stupid.
I'm OK since I'm not alone.
I have you.
Why am I alone
I won't leave you.
Let me go!
I was almost the Emperor!
If you'll kill me,
kill me in front of the Emperor!
So I should kill myself
What
Did the Emperor tell you
to check on me
making sure I'm dead
I have something for you.
It's Haesu's favor.
- She died a long time ago.
- She left...
her will to give you the letter.
I'm sorry that
I can't be more help.
I know my end has come.
Can I go to you...
for this chance
Since I don't know
when I can get out of the palace.
I am just...
a silly girl
who can only love one person.
Silly girl.
How can you not hate me
It's the son's birthday.
How can you not see us not even once
Your care for him
would be good enough.
He's afraid of his father.
Because you treat him
like your competitor.
You've cleared up all other nephews.
You should trust your son at least.
Excuse me, Empress.
I know well about people
who hide their real face behind.
You and the boy...
I know you'd strike me anytime.
So you'll only remember her
Haesu was the only one who said
that all people are equal.
You're banning slavery
because you can't forget about her.
Did you think I wouldn't know that
Let's say you're right.
But what difference would that make
Now that I see it...
I think I know
why she left you.
Be careful!
You bumped into me first.
Who are you
Father!
I greet you, Your Majesty.
You're not supposed to leave
Choongju, why are you here
It's Su's anniversary...
I'm so sorry.
I was out of my mind.
It won't happen again.
Is she your daughter
Yes, Your Majesty.
I remember approving your re-marriage
as your family requested.
But...
she's pretty older.
- How old is she
- You must be busy with work.
You don't need to worry
about my children.
Let's go.
Stop.
Leave her here.
I can't do that
unless you kill me.
Is that so
She said...
her daughter can't live in the palace.
Because it's so scary and lonely...
she didn't want to send her there.
Haesu was...
worried about that
until her last moment.
For the Fourteenth Prince,
Wang Jung...
the order that bans from the palace
will be removed.
You can come to the palace
from time to time.
I don't understand why you'd
like to bring children to the palace.
This is hard-earned chance
from the Emperor
to bring them as friends
of the Prince for his birthday.
So pack for them.
You should convince your wife too.
I don't...
want to send them to the palace.
After I die...
- he'd remove the ban from my children.
- No.
Your children must
get used to the palace.
I will make your son Chi next Emperor.
- What
- You've turned down my dream
and Yeonhwa betrayed my dream.
But I haven't given up yet.
You'll get caught by Father.
You must be the daughter of Uk.
I'm your uncle.
- Thirteenth uncle.
- You're lying.
You look like a wanderer
with an instrument.
I'm not lying.
- What's your name
- My name
It's Boksoon.
What's your name
- It's Boksoon.
- Woohee! We need to go now.
OK.
Boksoon
Is that yours
- Where did you get it
- I don't know.
I always had it.
It's my favorite.
I wish
I wasn't Baekjae's people.
I want to be...
wholly yours.
I heard that you're still going out
and not thinking about getting married.
The life would be boring
without any romance.
The Emperor spent time
reading books at first
and now he's putting it into work.
He investigates slaves
and open fair tests.
It's all to weaken
nobles' power.
You're still interested
in the affairs.
I'm just watching it.
Because I wonder what kind
of Emperor would So be.
Maybe...
Goryeo has the greatest
Emperor in history.
He has given up that much too.
Recently...
I think of many faces.
Do you still...
miss Haesu
Well...
I've always...
made mistakes
when giving my heart
to someone.
I've learned that too late.
You want to leave that much
Yes.
I think of him a lot.
It's not what you promised.
You said you only belong
to the Emperor.
Right.
But there's only one Emperor for me.
He was like my brother,
my friend and my master.
Maybe Haesu isn't from this world.
There have been many instances
to prove it.
So please forget about her.
If you miss someone you can't reach,
you'll become like me.
Then should I call you, my girl
You're my only Empress.
Why again
Who is it to make me feel this way
THE CULTURE OF GORYEO'S MAKE-UP
Due to the influence of Buddhism,
Goryeo's been advanced in
the culture of face wash, bath
bathing items and make-up skills.
The envoy of Son dynasty writes that...
I've been dreaming the same dream
for one year now.
It's a guy with this big scar
on his face.
He covers it with his mask.
The clothes are from old days.
Because you woke up from death.
You've been unconscious for a year
after you were almost drowned.
I'm healthy now.
But why every time I dream
about him...
I cry that much
The tea culture was also advanced.
They also had today's face masks.
From trading...
they brought roses
from today's Bulgaria.
And they made cosmetic products.
Hello.
- Your last name is "Ko"
- What
Right, my name is Hajin Ko.
Did you know today's "Ko"
was Goryeo's "Hae"
Oh, yes
Our company advertises Goryeo's
cosmetic culture too.
It's a funny coincidence.
There's no coincidence.
Everything will come back
to its place.
I smell rose fragrances here.
Yes, we've put rose oil
in our products.
Especially in this serum.
We've added
- Bulgarian rose oil...
- Bulgarian rose oil.
Did you put that in
Are you OK
Nothing.
It's good for your skin
if you put on this serum every day.
Did you know even Goryeo had
something like BB cream
- Even men use this these days...
- Brace yourself.
I won't never lose you.
I think you should rest.
What's wrong with me
I think you should go. Don't worry
about here, I'll take care of it.
I'm sorry.
Gwangjong
It wasn't a dream.
It's not a dream.
Thank you for your mercy,
Your Majesty.
Don't worry.
I'll protect you no matter what.
How can you enjoy this party
all by yourself, brother
You're mine.
I said that girl is mine.
Brace yourself.
I won't never lose you.
Even when you put
your hand on my face
I won't ever lose you.
HIS NAME IS 'SO'.
HE ESTABLISHED
SLAVE INVESTITURE ACT...
THE GREATEST KING OF ALL...
DOUBTING HIS OWN RELATIVES...
THE EMPEROR OF BLOOD...
You won't be remembered
as a bloody emperor in history.
I will help you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I left you alone.
The Eighth brother has...
left us now.
I don't have anyone else to see.
I'm leaving again.
I wish you a comfortable life.
Transient life.
Father's last words
were "transient life".
The life is vain and empty.
He said that's the life.
But I think he's wrong.
It can't be vain
when we're together like this.
That look on your face
makes me nervous.
It seems like
you'll leave me far away.
What are you afraid of
What are you hiding
Just...
living here every day is nervous.
Every step...
I feel like I'm walking
on a thin ice sheet.
Sometimes it suffocates me.
Even if you're with me
I sometimes wish
if we met in a different time
at different places.
It must be great.
If that happens...
I won't be afraid of anything.
And I can...
love you...
as much as I want.
If your world and mine
are different...
I'll go find you.
My Su.
Like here...
Here, come up.
- Please get up.
- It's OK.
- Now we're off to go.
- Sure.
Let's go.