MOON LOVERS:
SCARLET HEART RYEO
THIS SHOW IS A WORK OF FICTION
BASED ON HISTORIC EVENTS.
Don't push me away.
Don't tell me to leave.
Don't say your unhappy because of me.
Don't call me a monster.
You especially can't do that.
You...
are mine.
I'm not yours.
You're mine.
I said you belong to me!
Without my permission...
you can't leave me
nor can you die.
You are completely mine.
Su?
No way.
You've seen it wrong.
She can't leave the palace.
No way.
EPISODE 10
It's her, I'm sure.
You can check the door keeper.
No court lady can leave the palace!
Do you think So would care?
He must just dragged her out.
Only Su will get punished.
Let's go find her.
Give me a horse and men...
- Go back to the palace.
- What?
It's not good for you either
that they find you sneaking out.
Just go back.
I will find her.
I appreciate your thoughtfulness,
but I can't just go like this.
If they find out about Su...
you really don't know
what will happen to her.
Let's find her together.
OK.
I treated you like a child.
I'm sorry.
I trust you.
You listen to me carefully.
Even though we're married...
I can't admit that you're my wife.
So we'll leave the way
we've been before.
Don't ever try to nag me, OK?
Please answer my question!
It makes me infuriated.
I'm already married to you.
I'll follow you because our marriage is
based on friendship, it will prosper.
What...
language is that?
How would I like you when you seldom
talk and only do in hard languages?
I like to use a big part of the bed.
You told me to hold it
until first snow comes.
Haesu.
You're such a terrible liar.
You and I are not safe anymore.
Then should we just run away?
If you want, I can do that.
Whenever I have to leave Songak,
I wanted to show you here before.
I was always pushed away.
I still don't know why I had to leave.
I didn't make anyone unhappy.
I didn't harm any animal.
I didn't use swords easily on people.
But I still have to leave?
I hope you can live with no pressure.
I hope you can live without
having to see blood or unfairness...
outside of the palace.
If you go with me.
I'm a court lady.
I have to live in the palace.
Then I won't leave either.
And I...
have someone special in my heart.
Is it Baeka?
No, it's not him.
Then it's fine.
As long as it's not Baeka.
If it's others, I can kill him.
What?
I said you were mine
when you were beaten by Yeonhwa.
Since then, you're mine.
You looked at me as myself.
You didn't need any explanation.
You said you're scared of me.
I don't trust that.
Because you're my only friend.
So I'm not sorry for anything.
Even kissing...
or dragging you out here, and...
threatening you not to
love any other guy.
Here.
I wanted to give you something
like this.
I just wanted to help you.
I didn't ask for your love.
Try to run away from me, then.
You can throw it away
if you don't want it.
Su!
How did you find us here?
The palace already knows about me?
Thankfully it's just me and Uk,
but they'll find out soon.
Let's go.
Come on.
What are you doing?
I'll take her back,
since I took her out.
People will gossip if they see you
together. That's an even bigger problem.
Su.
The Emperor has given her
to me already.
It's right that I take care of her.
He gave her to me.
I'll go with the Fourth Prince.
Don't worry, please go back.
He'll take care of me.
I think we can do that.
You'll go with the Fourth?
Yes.
You'll keep your word.
Don't ever let her get hurt.
I wouldn't want that either.
You can't just let them go.
What if he's not going to the palace?
Then I won't just sit and watch.
What?
This is the only time
I'm letting them go together.
Court Lady Oh. I...
I just took her out.
Don't blame her.
You went out of the palace?
The Emperor ordered her to
take care of me. We had to go out.
Still, taking a court lady out will
be seen as a challenge to the Emperor.
So are you going to punish her?
- Do you have to?
- Please go back, Prince.
She'll have to make more excuses
if you're spotted here.
I trust you.
I'm sure your thoughtless kindness
has shaken the Fourth Prince's heart.
This is why you don't fit in here.
You can't be kind to anyone here.
You need to be careful
each and every step.
That's the only way you survive.
I...
What should I do now?
You have to wait until
his feelings go away.
Bull's-eye!
What a surprise.
Seeing you miss the target.
These days make me practice more.
I think of someone when I see the target.
The one who became a hero
instead of me.
If I see his face there, I aim
as if my arrow goes through his heart.
I never miss it.
Bull's-eye!
What about you?
Who's your target?
I've never...
imagined someone when I shoot.
Someone like you with lack of purpose
is easily swayed.
I'm leaving Songak soon. Father
is sending me far away. I'll survive.
You'll be fine.
Of course.
I'll come back with great condition.
So you think it through while I'm gone.
Who'd be fun to be your target?
You and I are getting along
pretty well surprisingly.
I'll be back soon.
You better calculate well until then.
I'll wait for your comeback.
Let's go.
Who's there?
Hello.
What are doing here?
Who ordered you to follow me?
Who are you?
I'm just here to play the music
for the dance, not following you.
Really?
And you followed me first.
Did you forget already?
I didn't know you play the music
for the gisaeng school.
I have nothing I can't do well,
but there are more I'm great at.
I didn't know you're here to be gisaeng.
Your talk sounded like a loyal lady.
Whatever you are, just do your job.
Don't ever judge people like that.
It's a bad habit.
Let's tell names as it's our
third time meeting.
What is your name?
Boksoon.
Woohee, let's go back to our rooms.
OK.
Boksoon?
What a trick.
Woohee. Your name is Woohee.
Are you not upset?
I just saw the sunrise
with the Fourth Prince. That's it.
I said I'll go with him
so you're not affected.
I'm not upset.
I'm just sad.
I've always had you in Damiwon
as I'm only calculating and thinking.
But So just took you out at once.
I'll ask the Emperor for
permission to marry you.
Marry?
When I heard you've disappeared,
it reminded me when you
entered the palace.
I was so afraid that
I might lose you again.
I won't repeat that mistake again.
As Lady Hae said,
my nights were never restful.
Because of the pressure of
the expectation and future
I felt guilty to sleep well.
But then it was you who showed me
smiles and light jokes,
and poems.
It was you.
I want to go back home with you
and live happily.
I want to repay Lady Hae by giving
all my love to you. Su...
Would you be my half?
He's not going to change or hurt me.
I can be happy with him.
If Gwangjong kills him...
Do you not like me anymore?
No, it's not that.
Then, you can't trust my promise?
No...
Then will you answer me?
Will you marry me?
What are you doing?
It was you who sneaked in
when the Princes were bathing.
I'm so sorry.
I'll explain everything.
Who would be killed first
if this secret meeting is revealed?
I'll close down this place.
Anyone having an affair with
a court lady will be punished.
Let's go.
- You, leave the palace with me.
- What?
Doctor Tae ordered me to go out
to take care of my health.
Come with me to my hometown.
I've been watching you and Prince Uk.
The only answer is to avoid it.
The Eighth Prince asked me...
to marry him.
And I'm going to.
Think of the Fourth Prince!
You can't survive between them.
If anyone changes his mind
you'll die in your early age.
The Eighth Prince is different.
He won't ever change.
No, the palace can make
anyone break their promises.
The person I loved...
Yes, as you assumed, it's the Emperor.
He wanted to marry me once
but to keep his position...
he had to forget about the poor girl.
But I still wanted to be with him.
And I decided to live as
a court lady, not a woman.
I boiled tea for him,
washed his hair and changed his cloths.
I call my lover as Your Majesty,
and cleaned ladies' bodies for him.
Su, think ahead. If you don't escape now,
you'll be miserable, too.
The Prince said...
we'll leave the palace to live in Hwangju.
We can be happy as long as we stay low.
I trust him.
How is it going keeping the Emperor
and the Fourth Prince apart?
We have to let the Emperor think Fourth
Prince is the enemy or the Crown Prince.
If you pretend you're
giving the Fourth Prince power,
I'll take care of the rest.
I gave the Crown Prince's uncle's
debt document to the Fourth Prince.
The Crown Prince will be
suspicious of him if he finds that paper.
You will meet up with Wang Sikryum.
Everything is perfect.
I'll get ready too.
I'm just here to see
if you're OK.
I'll tell Court Lady Oh
so you can rest today.
Prince.
Please come to the make-up room.
I'll help you.
Anyone will cherish the person
who's next to him and cheering
when he's suffering.
It's easy to think that person is
the only one on the same side.
You call that person as a "friend".
Friendship and relationships can be
confusing.
But they're different.
I'm worried that you're confused
about those differences.
I'm worried about you.
And I don't make friends that easily.
Friendship or relationship,
they're all same to me.
I only have one.
I know you're trying to push me away
but it's not working for me.
I told you to brace yourself.
Don't worry.
I won't do it again
without your permission.
What did you just say?
At the festival, I'll ask the Emperor
to allow Haesu and me to get married.
If Su leaves the palace
we'll leave in Hwangju together.
I know what you expect of me, but
I'm not interested becoming an Emperor.
I'm just sick of politics.
I just want to live freely.
You'll give up the Emperor's seat,
abandon Mother and me...
to just live as a husband?
Then who'll protect our family?
There are many way to protect us
without becoming the Emperor.
Trust me.
Have I ever stopped your wish?
If you know what you want
do it as you wish.
But you'll have to brace yourself
as it won't be an easy way.
Su will appreciate you, too.
You should stop him.
You should say no!
I sometimes get sick of politics, too.
I'm sure he was as well.
Your brother's burden is
a lot heavier than you think.
Let him do what he wants.
You were framed that
you caused the
Emperor's favorite
court lady's miscarriage
and kicked out of palace
only ten years ago.
No one was on our side
even though we knew it was the Empress.
Shinju Kang, Myunchun Park
Uisung Hong, Gwangju Wang.
These families will attack us
any time if we're not the Emperor.
The Emperor and the Crown Prince are
different and the country has changed.
Don't look at this too extremely.
I think it's my time
to leave your wings.
Yeonhwa.
I'll change my goal from now on.
I won't be a daughter or a sister
of Emperor, I'll be the King of Emperor.
You don't have to forgive me.
Your Highness,
Princess Yeonhwa is here.
Princess Yeonhwa?
You asked me to come
if I have any fun stories.
I'd like you to hear this today.
Is that so?
I must listen if you insist this much.
I can't wait.
Su!
One, two, three.
You're getting good at this.
With all those finger flicks
any dummy could learn.
One, two, three!
I got you.
You can hit hard.
I'll can get arrested
for hitting a prince.
You surprised me more
when you're kidnapped by Fourth Prince.
Where the heck did you take you?
He just rode with me.
It was so much fun.
He's out of control these days.
I don't like it.
Please try to understand him.
You're well-loved by the Empress.
But he wasn't.
He has no close family.
You have to work hard to be loved.
Since he came up, Mother and Brother Yo
have changed a lot.
Don't tell me you're
blaming him for that.
It's not only because of him, but...
if it wasn't him, I wouldn't have known
Mother and Brother Yo's intention.
Su.
I miss our old days,
when we were all good together.
You looked prettiest
when you smiled at Uk's house.
I think of that, too.
I want to go back.
Why are you going to
the Crown Prince's family house?
I have some business to do.
Don't tell the Crown Prince.
OK, by the way...
is it true that you
took Su out of the palace?
Su is a court lady. If you treat her like
any girl, you and she will be in danger.
Don't make it complicated.
I didn't mean that.
I have no intention
of making it more complicated.
I am just...clumsy at this.
I don't know how to treat people well.
Do I have to be criticized for that?
I didn't know you
like Su that much.
Only you and Hasu are
my people in this world.
Prince! Prince!
We have a big issue.
Numerous complaints are
coming in that
the Crown Prince has
collected double taxes.
All of the heads of each village are
asking the Emperor to
relinquish his crown.
Did you know about
your family's embezzlement?
We have reports that you were there
when your family collected the taxes.
I found out later.
It was a mistake.
It's not like we planned to
rob our people, as you say.
Do not even try to frame us.
We found out later.
You still hold accountability
for not catching it earlier.
Your Majesty, all members agree that
we cannot let the immoral family
rule our country in the future.
Please reconsider.
Then...
who do you want for his seat?
Your Majesty.
Will you dethrone the Crown Prince?
We need to have a plan
in order to decide that.
So I'm asking you who'd be
the best fit for Goryeo's future.
Your Majesty, we think
Fourth Prince will be a good fit.
Fourth Prince?
Wang So?
Since Wang So was adopted to another
family,
he won't have a family
that will attack.
And through the ritual he is now trusted
among people including foreigners.
I see he's the best fit.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know it'd be this complicated.
What are you talking about?
I just told So because
I worried about you.
I trusted him that he'll support you.
I just showed your uncle's document
to him.
Did Fourth know about my family's issue?
I told him myself, so I'm sure.
But I didn't know
he'd threaten your seat from this.
Please forgive me.
It's time for you to go back
to Shinju.
Leave after the Ninth.
Do I have to?
People suggested you as the Crown
Prince. Your mother and Choonju family.
They're planning to get my seat
through you.
I have no connection with them.
Why do I have to leave?
A man's heart is cunning.
Even if you don't mean it now,
if you have more followers for you,
you'll lose the faithfulness you have now.
You're only the shield
for the Crown Prince.
You don't even know
that your father used you.
So my faithfulness doesn't matter to you.
I want to have you by my side
for a long time, but what can we do?
Any challenges should be rooted out
before they grow.
That's how it's going in the palace.
Please make sure
that girl is handling this.
Yes, Lady.
I've ordered as you told me.
The Empress should not know
that I ordered you.
Yes, Princess...
I understand.
Are you still not
satisfied after all that?
When will you leave me alone?
Didn't you say you wanted
to be the Emperor?
A mother should
make her son's wish come true.
Don't worry, if everything goes well,
you'll be the Emperor.
Don't say it's for me.
I don't know what you're planning behind,
but it won't work as you wish.
The Crown Prince...
he'll die on September Eighth.
I've sent the poison cup already.
He loves teas, so he'll drink it.
Did you think I won't do anything?
How will you tell them how you
knew about the poison? From Mother?
If I have to, I will.
Sure.
Then I'll just say
I was trying to make you an Emperor.
I'll just say, to make you the Emperor,
Choongju and Hojuck family worked
to reveal the Crown Prince's
corruption and send poison.
We already made a compact that
we'll make you the Emperor.
In this palace, we're eating
each other to survive.
If you can stop the Crown Prince's
poisoned tea, try it.
Then it'll be your neck
that will have a rope tied to it.
It won't go as you wish.
You still don't know
after the Emperor kicked you out?
If we just have one court lady killed
who delivered that tea,
the Crown Prince will be gone.
Then you'll be the Crown Prince.
How could I...
trust you, Mother?
You said it yourself.
You won't kill your brothers
even if you become the Emperor.
I trust you.
That's why I'm supporting you.
Why is the Crown Prince's star so weak?
If we meet in any form later,
I won't ever forget my debt to you.
I'll keep our promise from now on.
I'll cherish Haesu.
Please look out for us.
SEPTEMBER 9TH
Drinking together with arms hooked.
Who would Baeka choose this
punishment?
The Emperor wasn't picked yet.
Can he be safe again this time?
The one who'll be drinking with me...
will be you.
I'd like to drink with you.
No.
I'm a grown man, I won't do it.
From here, "no"...
is not a word.
Here.
Shall we start again?
First, a wide circle flow
is hung up high...
to show its color.
Second, the pure yellow color
is the color of soil.
Third, blooming later is the bless
of the King.
Fourth, a flow blooming out of frost
is strong spirit.
Fifth...
Fifth is...
Fifth.
Flower flowing on drink
is the food of gods.
It's written by Jongye,
poem "Chrysanthemum."
Good job. Jung, martial arts are good,
but focus on study, too.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The Crown Prince seems to
have no appetite today.
I'm sorry, but it's hard to drink today.
We'll then bring out some chrysanthemum
tea. It's for all our good health.
- Lady Oh, please bring out the tea.
- Yes, Princess.
We need to bring out
chrysanthemum tea.
OK, hold on.
Can you go for me?
I'm getting a cold.
I'm sorry, but Lady Oh told me
not to serve the Princes for awhile.
Fine, then.
Are you OK?
Hurry up! We'll be in trouble
because you took so long to get ready.
What's that face?
Do you think it's because I woke up late?
Look at that bold face.
I greet you, Your Highness.
I said hurry up.
You need to accept her greeting.
What?
If you don't accept,
she has to stay like that.
Lift up your head.
I don't want to see you
so turn around now.
Yes, Prince.
From now on, always turn around
whenever you see me.
I don't feel like going anymore.
You can come or stay.
If you're that sad, you should've
become his second wife like I told you.
I can see you like him that much to
offer me that chance.
Please take care of him.
Make sure he's not involved in any issue
or hangout with anyone
because he's easily swayed.
I'm his wife now.
That shouldn't be your concern anymore.
We'll test the tea first for poison.
Your Majesty, I have something
to tell the Crown Prince.
You can say now.
Actually...
If we just have one court lady killed
who delivered that tea, he'll be gone.
- I've prepared the tea.
- Thank you.
So what were you going to say?
Yes.
As I have made you uncomfortable
these days,
I'd like to get your three drinks
to renew our brotherhood.
Sure.
But I only have tea, not alcohol.
I feel like I'll be drunk
only with the tea on a day like today.
Please send this to him.
I'm so sorry.
It's my fault. I had some
oil on my hands from food.
Bring the new cup.
First shot is for your longevity.
Second shot is for
your hard work for this country...
and to celebrate it.
It wasn't the cup, but the tea.
I'm drinking...
poison from you.
Lastly,
even if anyone tries to part
you and me...
I wish our brotherhood
would never change.
Thanks for your faithfulness.
Your Majesty, you've seen him.
How can I live apart from him?
Please reconsider your order
to send him back to Shinju.
I'll bring more tea, Your Highness.
I will be right back, Your Majesty.
We found poison and valuable things
in the court lady Haesu's room.
Arrest Haesu for attempting
to poison the Prince.
Why do you lock up the innocent one?
I think he knew who did it.
Who did he try to protect with his life?
I won't just let her go like this.
I will find the evidence.
Hang Haesu for poisoning the Prince.
Haesu!