SCARLET HEART
THIS SHOW IS A WORK OF FICTION
BASED ON HISTORIC EVENTS
Is the tea room ready?
Miss!
I mean... Lady!
When did you come back?
All went well, thanks to you.
Thank you.
I was super nervous.
14th Prince left a message
before he took off.
Really?
He found a way out of the palace.
Let him know if you're interested.
You know Narye is coming up.
- I need everything to be perfect.
- Yes, Lady.
Prince Wang So is conspiring
with Songak nobles
in order to stall
the palace construction.
He mixed in rocks
so the walls can break.
And he laid off men.
Are you sure?
Minister Wang Sikryeom has fallen sick.
The supervision is not going too well.
Why, why, why!
What's his objective?
Not just to rebel against me...
The throne.
He's targeting the throne.
Right?
I have a question before I answer.
Why did you break your promise?
Promise?
People who can't pay taxes
are forced to do labor.
Our poor Hubaekje refugees
are dying on the site.
If it goes on like this,
I have no reason to continue being...
your eyes and ears.
So... are you going to stop?
If there's nothing to gain.
Princess Uhui.
Has it been a while
since someone called you this?
You know, Baeka...
He loves everything that's pure.
Typical for people
who are fascinated with beauty.
If he finds out you were my dog...
...I'm sure he'll love it.
Please take me out...
Yo...
Please take me out, Yo...
Fire... flint...
Why...
Brother!
Please let me go!
Is anyone around?
Anyone?
Think of our brotherhood.
Brother!
Please let us go!
Spare us!
Yo.
Your Highness?
No...
- Don't come...
- Yo.
Don't come!
Go away!
We need to go.
Your Highness!
Your Highness...
Call the royal doctor!
Now!
This is my chance.
I can be the next Emperor.
Get the horses ready.
We are heading to Seogyeong
to see Wang Sikryeom.
Why?
Don't you want me to be Emperor?
No.
But I don't want to break up.
Thank you.
You will be Emperor.
I know.
But still...
...never lay hands on your brothers.
Lady.
Lady?
What are you so absorbed in?
Chaeryeong.
Let everyone know
to not leave Damiwon today.
No need to tend the gardens either.
It might get loud outside.
But reassure them
it'll be okay in here.
Okay.
Lady, the Emperor
asks for medicinal tea.
Right now?
What are you hiding from me?
Did you poison the tea?
No, your highness.
Eunuch tested it.
Now I'm in this state...
It all started with you.
Excuse me?
Brother Mu and Eun...
Eun's wife...
Even my father...
The reason they are haunting me...
It's all because of you.
The reason I wanted to be Emperor,
even if I had to kill my brothers, was...
because you...
you cleaned up So's scar
and let him take my place.
He took my place...
Your Highness!
Yo!
It's So.
So is coming here!
Wang So started a revolt!
Yo, here...
Grab this.
Write down Jeong as your successor.
What?
We can't let them steal the throne.
Hurry.
Put down Jeong as the next Emperor.
Then we can get through this.
Hurry.
Then...
...what about me?
Am I even your son?
What am I to you?
Just someone to fill your vanity?
If I am no longer Emperor,
do you not need me any longer?
Yo.
Don't do this.
We'll lose everything.
Hand it over to Jeong.
Please.
Now I know...
...how So felt.
Drag the Empress Dowager out!
Yo...
Yo, don't do this.
Yo!
Let me go!
Let go of me!
Yo!
Let go!
- It's Prince Wang So!
- The rebels are coming!
Lock the gates!
I still can't get a hold of brother.
Park Sugyeong is with them.
The guards don't stand a chance...
Mother?
I will make up my mind
depending on your decision.
After seeing your brother change,
I realized what I didn't teach you.
If you want to own the palace...
you need to give something up.
- Mother...
- Make a decision now.
Seize the world
and lose your sane mind.
Or keep that sane mind,
but live in a small world.
I want... the world.
Okay.
I give up Uk.
I've come to siege the palace
I used to protect.
I knew he would take everything away.
What...
What did I do so wrong?
I was scared of being abandoned.
Just like So.
An afterthought...
Mother told me.
That I was perfect.
Flawless.
But...
It's because of you.
You messed it all up!
You choose.
Who should I give the throne to?
Jeong?
Uk?
Baeka?
Or So?
If you're so smart, choose one!
- Find the Emperor, now!
- Yes, sir!
I just...
...wanted to survive.
Did you read it?
Move away!
Get out of my way!
Yo...
Greetings to the new Emperor.
Hurray.
Emperor?
The Emperor left me the throne
before he passed.
He appointed me.
What?
Greetings to the Emperor!
Hurray! Hurray!
Hurray!
I will help you enter without bloodshed.
I will remember your loyalty.
Emperor!
Hurray! Hurray!
Hurray!
Emperor!
Hurray! Hurray!
Hurray!
Gwangjong.
Goryeo's 4th Emperor.
You won't be remembered
as the "Blood Emperor" now.
I will help you.
Did you really open the gate for him?
Yes, I did.
I told her to.
- You told her to?
- We had no other choice.
From now on,
we Hwangju Hwangbos
will try our best to make an Empress,
not an Emperor.
You finally dropped
your expectations of me.
The situation has changed.
I am your mother, Uk.
But I'm Yeonhwa's mother too.
Above all...
I felt bad you changed so much.
The more you wander off
the more you'll be in pain.
Might be better for you
to distance yourself from the palace.
Why didn't you come to the coronation?
What if they misapprehend it?
When I arrived at Seogyeong...
...Wang Sikryeom was already dead.
I was immediately detained by
So's men, and when I got out...
...the throne had a new owner.
A traitor who dethrones another traitor
becomes a hero.
Wang So took the position I craved.
To make me witness that...
...would be too harsh.
Help me.
Once I become Empress,
I will compensate all your losses.
I will share your burden
and responsibilities.
I need your support.
Please.
Denied.
I just want to go back home in peace.
I need your help the most right now.
Why do you want to leave?
To be honest...
I am sick and tired of this place.
Whenever I walk around...
my daughter...
My child...
I see her, I hear her.
No matter how hard I try,
the image of you...
thrusting that sword...
I keep recalling that moment.
It pains me.
Don't go.
- Don't go.
- Your highness.
For the country and the people...
...be a merciful ruler.
I urge you.
Your Highness.
That way, when I see...
our founding father when I die...
I can stand up straight.
I, Park Sugyeong.
Your Highness.
Bid farewell.
Park Sugyeong left.
He said he's sick and tired.
And scared...
...of me.
Aren't you curious whose name
was on the Emperor's will?
If I stole this spot or not?
I'm not curious.
I'm probably the least curious person.
It was empty.
There was no name.
So...
That's why I tore it up.
Worried it might cause more trouble.
We had occupied the palace anyway.
You have me.
I won't leave you.
Did So really become Emperor?
Yes.
Appointed?
When I recommended you as successor,
Yo didn't bat an eye.
He couldn't have appointed So.
Pull yourself together first.
You could get sick.
Jeong, look into it again.
There must be something they missed.
Oh, yes. Haesu.
I heard she's already
admitted to Cheondeokjeon.
They must be up to something.
Look into it.
Okay?
Jeong.
Announce that the transfer of the capital
has come to unconditional halt.
- Refugees mobilized for construction...
- The deceased during labor?
Comply with the family's requests.
Su.
Greetings.
Here, have this.
I'm in your debt, Your Highness.
Su!
I think and think about it
Every day,
I can't sleep because I think of you
Every day, only you
Do you hear my heart pounding?
I love you, I love you,
I love you
I'm not joking.
I'd rather be serving as a court lady.
They don't let me do anything.
I feel like a doll waiting for its master.
Be careful with what you say.
The Emperor has a first wife,
but she's not around.
The Empress spot is essentially empty.
You're now a target.
You have to be careful.
I wanted him to be Emperor
because I was tired of waiting.
But now I feel like
I have to wait even more.
Lady!
- Lady!
- Chaeryeong, I warned you.
Lady Hae.
Empress Dowager wants to see you.
Greetings to Empress Dowager.
I had a question.
Jeong.
I found this in the former Emperor's room.
It looks like his will.
It looks like it's about his successor.
It means there could be another name on it
other than So's.
Tell me.
Did Yo really appoint So as his successor?
If you're afraid to talk
we can protect you.
Please be honest.
Did the former Emperor
really appoint So as his successor?
Yes.
Liar.
That's a lie!
I know Yo.
I know him better than anyone else.
He never would have appointed So!
Tell me.
Tell the truth!
- Mother.
- Tell me! Now!
Stop it!
That's enough.
If you had a question,
you should have asked me.
Really?
Then tell me the truth.
Why did you tear up the will?
Who says I did?
I don't know why brother tore up his will.
But he verbally appointed me.
He has a son.
Why would he appoint you?
If you're that curious,
maybe you can go ask him in hell?
It's fortunate he appointed me.
What if I had forcefully taken it?
By now, the palace would be
full of the blood of...
my brothers like Jeong
and my nephews.
Empress Dowager, focus more on
remembering our former Emperors.
I'll try to visit you more.
Don't call me Empress Dowager.
Even if you sit on the throne,
I don't want to be called that.
I'm still your son.
If a son is Emperor,
you are the Empress Dowager.
You're just a thief
who stole my son's throne.
Let our Chungju family know
I'm coming for a visit.
If she calls you again,
you don't have to go.
Okay.
Whoever it is, they need my permission
to see you, got it?
Yes, Your Highness.
And...
Your Highness.
We're receiving complaints from all over.
About what?
They want the former Emperor's son
to be the lawful successor.
Minister Park Yeonggyu is
spreading rumors
that you fabricated the will.
Kill them.
Excuse me?
Execute the malcontents for treason.
Also kill all servants and soldiers
who were in Cheondeokjeon when Yo passed.
Anyone who doubts or makes excuses,
I want them all killed.
Kill them...
...all.
The Emperor is after me.
You were spreading malicious rumors.
Did you think you would remain unharmed?
Is that so?
Maybe I should reveal that
you were spying on 4th Prince and Baeka.
I won't go down alone.
You fool.
Boo!
Hey...
I remember this guy.
It's dirty.
You should change threads.
I don't want to lose it...
Was it from your parents?
I have to apologize
to your parents for something.
- What is it?
- Before we marry...
I need you to be adopted
into a noble family.
I guess my Hubaekje background
is a problem?
My mother and her family
have bad blood with your people.
They had family members slain
in front of their eyes.
If possible,
they want nothing to do with Hubaekje.
It was all before we were even born.
I know you're not directly involved.
I just don't want to make a fuss.
I'll visit your parent's grave
to apologize.
Wow.
So this is how Cheondeokjeon looks.
I...
I have a favor to ask.
I know there are court lady pardons
to celebrate the new Emperor.
I was pardoned too.
I have to leave Damiwon.
Guess we won't see each other much.
Where are you headed?
Can't you help me stay here?
Can't you ask the Emperor?
What happened?
She said she'll ask the Emperor.
Good.
I need you to stay at Damiwon.
Can't I just...
...be with you?
I don't know when
my next pardon will be.
Chaeryeong.
I still need your help here.
When the time comes,
I will come get you.
Leave it in my room.
Yes, lady.
You ended up...
...with him.
You told me...
...it's greedy to ask for both.
But you went to him.
I don't understand.
He was honest with me.
He said he didn't want
to lose me or the throne.
He confessed his desires.
I had no choice but to understand.
I was always curious why you...
Why you never thought
I could become Emperor.
In your eyes...
...was I not worthy?
- It's not like that.
- Then what?
Prince Wang So was
born with an Emperor's star.
Founding father knew that as well.
It's not your fault.
It's fate.
It's destiny.
Emperor's star?
Because of a star?
Fate?
Destiny?
My heart is towards you
It hurts to love you
Will you promise me?
That you'll never take it off.
Please do not forget
My love never stops
If it's destiny,
it's okay if we have to wait
We will meet again
It's not your fault.
It's fate.
It's destiny.
A sad dream,
I turn around and cry
With all my heart, I hope one day
You will...
become Empress.
Are you going to help me?
He can't...
...have it all.
It's not fair.
Okay. Finished.
Why do you want this many?
I have my reasons.
Wasn't the food instead of paying rent?
I didn't know I had to pay it back.
You ate the whole thing, didn't you?
I was going to share it with
Baeka and astrologer.
Don't think of others.
Just me.
It's all mine.
Did something happen?
No.
Why do you ask?
It's just that...
you're laughing much more than usual.
Don't meddle in
every single thing I do.
We're not even married yet.
Don't make me think otherwise.
I have nothing to do
but wait for you all day long.
Can't I work in Damiwon during the day?
I don't need to serve.
There's a lot of other work to do.
And...
about Chaeryeong.
I heard you are pardoning her.
Can't we let her stay?
She has nowhere to go
outside of the palace.
Chaeryeong?
Well...
I'll be lonely without her.
Please?
Okay. All right.
But...
You won't be lonely in a while.
When you raise our kids.
Kids?
Royal doctor will stop by.
If we want babies,
we need you healthy.
We're not even married yet.
It's too early to talk about babies.
Marriage?
All right.
When shall we do it?
You pick the date.
No.
I don't want to marry.
No?
I need a formal proposal.
Do you remember at the rock piles?
You had something to say.
I'm not stupid.
Weren't you about to propose?
Rock piles are out of reach now.
It's hard to leave the palace
with all this security.
Oh, well.
To marry you...
do I need to think of
a satisfying proposal?
You are harder to deal with
than our state affairs.
Whatever it is,
I want you to be honest.
I will choose what to tell
the Emperor myself.
Your knees are in bad shape.
After you were tortured...
you hadn't treated it properly.
It became a chronic problem.
You might not be able to
walk one day.
Okay.
I will be careful.
But the real problem is...
...your heart.
My heart?
When you are tired or in shock,
have you ever had a hard time breathing
or felt like you're about to faint?
Yeah, well...
You have suppressed anger.
Your mental stress
has eaten into your physical health.
At this rate...
I can't say for sure
that you'll live long.
What do you mean?
Am I dying soon?
It's okay.
Tell me how long I have left.
I will look after my health.
I'm still in my twenties.
Ten years is too short.
Let me live longer.
With him...
I want to be with him longer.
What are you praying so hard for?
Are you praying for brother So
to hold a long reign?
I want the manly 14th Prince
to be my friend again.
That's what I'm praying for.
You said you'd never take sides.
But you took 4th brother's side.
I feel betrayed.
Don't misdirect your anger.
It was the former Emperor who
murdered brother Mu and Eun.
The reason why brother So is Emperor...
It's fate.
Yeah, you might be right.
But I still think all this misfortune
started when brother So first got here.
Fighting over the throne
is nothing new.
But once So got involved,
it became complicated and bloody.
I mean, he did steal the throne.
I'm worried you might get hurt.
Do you think
you can become an Empress?
Empress?
I don't know.
Never really thought about it.
An Empress...
with the help of her family and nobles
needs to support the Emperor.
That's why my father
married that many times.
If it goes on like this,
you will only become one of many wives.
Is that what you wanted?
Didn't you want to ride a camel
and explore the far oceans?
Didn't you mean it?
Remember what I said?
My message through Chaeryeong.
That you know a way out of the palace?
Let me know
when you get tired of this place.
If you want to leave...
I do know a way.
I will keep in mind.
8th Prince is here to see you.
Welcome.
I came to speak
as representative of your lieges.
- Representative?
- First...
As for the commanding officer
of the 300 thousand reserves,
let us lieges vote to decide.
Second...
Let local nobles manage 'po's.
PO
HARBORS STORING TAXED CROPS
For the rest,
once they pay their taxes
let them manage
their lands independently.
Then, you will soon have loyal lieges
fill up this place.
Let go of control over
arms and funds?
Want me to clip off my wings?
If you thought lobbying would work...
you're mistaken.
If not your wings...
...what about your heart?
Hwangju Hwangbo family
requests a marriage.
What a nice room.
Good taste.
Say what you need and leave.
I won't listen after today.
I didn't come to fight.
I just wanted to clear up
what we each want.
I didn't know we had
anything left to clear up.
Princess.
I don't need anything from you.
I will let you stay here...
if you want.
I mean, I'll accept you
as the Emperor's lover.
You can't be an Empress anyway...
I won't interrupt
you serving him from close by.
I don't understand...
what you're saying.
I only want honor and recognition.
And my son to be the next Emperor.
I am about to marry the Emperor.
I will be his wife.
I...
will be Empress.
Once you marry Yeonhwa,
the nobles will come under your wing.
Hwangju Hwangbo family has your back.
Don't try to manipulate me.
Although I'm Emperor...
I still have a dog wolf's temper.
The throne...
Hard to obtain,
but harder to protect.
Now that you're up there,
you probably see clearly
that the nobles are
like a double-edged sword.
If you want to lengthen your stay,
you need the nobles on your side.
I already have another marriage in mind.
You mean Haesu?
She...
...can never be Empress.
If I say so...
...she can.
Did you forget?
Haesu, in order to avoid
marrying our founding father...
she slit her wrist.
A women with a scar...
cannot marry the Emperor.
SCARLET HEART
You can protect your throne.
I want our son to be
the next Emperor.
Dare manipulate me
by using the throne as leverage?
You can't leave.
You are my only Empress.
Give up the marriage.
Let go first.
What should I do?
How could you do that?
Su.
You beat her to death.
I became a monster to her.
I will make them pay.