DOCTOR ON THE EDGE
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
SOME SCENES WERE GENERATED USING AI
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED SAFELY
Can I ask you something?
Mm-hmm.
Why did you go to Madeokdo…
with Dr. Hyeon Chiyeon?
We were supposed to go together.
Ah…
How could I have gone there with you?
It's not within walking distance.
It's over an hour away by boat.
Ah…
So you were looking out for me.
I didn't even realize that.
But I kind of regret it.
Maybe I shouldn't have looked out for you…
and just gone there with you.
Next time…
do you want to go with me?
Hmm?
Oh…
Rain…
What are you doing? Run!
Wow, it's really pouring.
Watch your step.
-  Are you okay?
-  Yes.
Which way? Left or right?
-  Right. No, left!
-  Left?
Stop. Let's take a quick breather.
Okay.
Shall we get going?
Right now?
- Should I go first?
- How about on three?
One, two…
EPISODE 4 - A NOTORIOUS WOMAN,
A PATHETIC MAN
:cue
Dr. Do.
- Hi.
- You're soaking wet.
Ah…
Yes.
This is nice.
Yeah.
Dr. Do.
Yes?
- Oh, it's nothing.
- Okay.
DID YOU GET HOME SAFELY?
PHOTOS
I took a photo of you.
It came out nice.
BATHROOM
MS. YUK HARI
WOW, THE FIREFLIES REALLY…
Are you okay?
Yes.
Did you catch a cold because of the rain?
The rain makes the humidity go up.
It's just allergies.
It's only in the morning.
Oh… Ah!
About the photos
I took yesterday…
Here's another good one.
Did you do all this?
I shaved your jawline and gave you
a nose job. Doesn't it look great?
It does.
I got the fireflies and a flattering shot
of your face too.
What the…
This is driving me crazy. I'm so sorry.
How can a doctor be so bad
at holding in a sneeze?
How are we supposed to hold in a sneeze?
Doctors are human too.
Huh?
Didn't they teach you how in med school?
There's no such thing.
Oh… I guess they don't teach you.
All nurses learn how to do it.
We can't sneeze while we're looking
for a vein or we're in the OR.
You're just pulling my leg.
I mean it. Have you ever seen
a nurse sneeze in a hospital before?
Want me to tell you how?
Mm-hmm.
Okay. Follow my lead.
First, press your tongue
against the roof of your mouth.
No, further back in.
Next, close your mouth.
That's it.
Now, it's crucial
that you really flare your nostrils.
For proper circulation.
No. Flare it more.
Just a little more…
What kind of doctor
falls for such nonsense?
I didn't fall for it.
As if anyone would.
Hello?
Okay, I'll head over right away.
Okay.
- Did something happen?
- Oh…
Someone requested a home visit.
Someone called your personal phone
to request a home visit?
Uh, yes. They're rather indisposed.
I'll be right back.
:cue
Ma'am.
- Are you okay?
- Oh, gosh.
I'm sorry to call you
out of the blue like that.
That's all right.
Let me take a look at your wound.
I came out of my room to take my meds
but I suddenly got dizzy
and just collapsed.
Fortunately, it doesn't look deep.
Let me take a look.
- Would you take a seat here for me?
- Okay.
Nice and easy.
- It hurts, doesn't it?
- Yes.
CHAVOXIFEN
Goodness.
Silly me.
I left this out in the open.
I'm guessing those meds are for you.
What?
Yes.
I'm a little unwell.
Hmm…
Taking painkillers day and night
makes my stomach turn.
So I stopped taking them,
you see.
And look where that's gotten me.
Human bodies can be so miserable.
Don't you think so?
Please be sure to take them.
Painkillers are a necessary prescription
for a patient.
Okay.
They may not cure your disease,
but they'll let you forget for a moment.
Right.
You should probably
adjust your prescription with your doctor.
I'll check at the center
for any meds that might help.
Oh, no. Don't do that.
I don't want people to find out.
If people were to find out,
they'd all treat me like a sick patient.
I want to live as Hari's grandma, Oh Mija,
not a patient.
The reason I told you to come here
without letting Hari know
was because she makes such a fuss
if I say I'm sick or hurting anywhere.
Don't worry about that.
Doctors have an obligation
to respect their patients' secrets.
But did you know this?
Patients also have an obligation to be
entirely forthcoming to their doctors.
That's why you can tell me everything.
:cue
Yes.
I understand, Doctor.
Right.
Ms. Yuk.
My grandma was the urgent patient?
Is my grandma okay? I'm going in.
Wait.
I don't think you should go in just yet.
I guess my grandma finds
the doctor she met once
to be more reliable
than her own granddaughter.
Then again, if I were her,
I wouldn't have told me either.
Because I'd cry more than my sick grandma.
And I keep trying to forget
that she is sick.
Thinking about it is too scary.
I'm a coward, aren't I?
No.
To be honest, when I first met you…
I saw it in your suitcase.
The anti-cancer drug…
Chavoxifen.
Mmm…
At first, I thought you
were the one who was sick.
But I couldn't bring myself
to ask you about it.
Even if I knew how much you were hurting…
it's not like
I could have done anything about it.
And…
it was scary.
I'm sure it's not even close…
…but I'm saying…
I kind of get how you feel.
You're not a coward.
Anyone would feel that way.
Ah…
I think we've been away for too long.
Shall we go?
Uh, sure.
:cue
Mom,
why did you send so many side dishes?
I can't finish all this on my own.
I packed enough to share with everyone.
You said the people there like you so much
that the place couldn't run without you.
Okay. Bye.
Goodness.
What's gotten into him now?
Sorry for stepping away.
It's fine.
We didn't get that many patients.
Dr. Do.
We need to talk.
- What for?
- Hurry…
What…
What is it?
This just isn't right.
What's this about?
You haven't seen the PH doc group chat?
They talk so much, so…
Is something wrong?
I'm not comfortable saying it myself,
so just check it out now.
Come on!
Okay.
JEONNAM PH DOC GROUP CHAT
Stop everything. Major PSA.
Has a nurse recently joined
any of your health centers?
Apparently, she's notorious
for being a doctor hunter.
I heard she only goes after
doctors. Could she be doing it here too?
It looks like they're talking
about Ms. Yuk Hari, doesn't it?
Not at all.
Who else but Ms. Yuk
could have transferred from Asong Hospital
to an island as a contract nurse?
And I got all my friends at Asong Hospital
to do some digging for me.
Guess how many doctors Ms. Yuk got to.
Three.
T-Three?
Be honest with me.
You've also felt it, haven't you?
How Ms. Yuk has gotten her hooks in.
Whoa, I'm not…
She hasn't gotten her hooks in
or anything like that.
I'm telling you,
she's definitely gotten her hooks in!
Into Dr. Hyeon Chiyeon!
What?
Everyone knew
those two were going out except us!
So you're saying Dr. Hyeon Chiyeon is
going out with Ms. Yuk Hari, huh?
I saw it myself.
They were riding around
on an ATV together.
If they shared an ATV ride,
they're practically an item, no?
Practically an item indeed.
Oh, my.
Gosh.
To be so young and in love again.
You know what the chief of Madeokdo said?
He said sparks were flying
between those two.
And I heard there was only
one available room that night.
No wonder you could see hearts
in their eyes.
Hearts in their eyes?
Looks like we might be having
a wedding on Pyeondongdo!
The ATV was because
Dr. Hyeon came to pick us up.
And Madeokdo was because
they missed the boat.
So let's not talk
behind our coworkers' backs, okay?
- Wow.
- So not cool.
It's time to head over
to the health education session, right?
Yes.
If you use too much
technical jargon to explain,
no one will understand,
so when explaining…
Look at me running my mouth.
I'm sure you'll nail it
without any instructions.
We'll be going now.
I'll see you later.
- I'll see you later.
-  Good luck.
I'm good.
- Let me carry it for you.
-  No.
I'm telling you,
she's definitely gotten her hooks in!
Into Dr. Hyeon Chiyeon!
Ms. Hwang.
Any plans for the evening?
I just figured
we might have dinner together.
What for? Any special occasion?
:cue
My mom sent me a buttload of side dishes,
so I thought we could…
Then just bring it over here tomorrow
so we can have it together.
Ah…
- There's a solution.
- Right.
Why didn't I think of that?
They were supposed to
take that to the session!
They left it behind.
How careless. I'll take it to them.
I…
I will go.
Was he listening in on us?
- Village Hall, right?
- Right.
Mmm…
PYEONDONGDO VILLAGE HALL
That's right.
Once you've called emergency services,
you need to check for a response.
Watch me. Take your palms, and say…
"Sir, are you okay?"
He's not responding, right?
In that case,
you have to check if they're breathing.
Place your hand on their chest,
listen for breaths with your ear,
and check to see
whether their chest is rising and falling.
Have you washed your hair?
You have to press down really hard.
So hard that it feels like
the rib cage might collapse!
Oh, man. She brought him back to life!
- He really came back to life.
- Wow, he came back!
Are you okay?
You two make a fantastic couple.
I can see you as a married couple.
- I know.
-  And don't you try to deny it.
Even the pebbles have eyes
here in Pyeondongdo.
Come on. It's not like that.
It's not.
What do you mean, no?
I heard young people nowadays start off
by taking it slow with a situationship
before they make it official.
That's what it is, right?
It's not…
That's enough.
Now, now. Stop teasing us.
We'll move on to hygiene training.
Let's get ready.
-  What? Hygiene training?
-  Oh?
When are you gonna tell us
about the ventilator?
Huh? The ventilator!
We came here to check this out.
Remember? The ventilator!
What about this?
I'm done! No more!
Oh…
People here come up with
totally baseless rumors.
Why didn't you say anything?
That's like adding fuel to the fire.
I just didn't think
they were totally baseless.
What?
Does it bother you that much?
Rumors can be really powerful.
Once people get swept up by a rumor,
they don't even care about the truth.
That's why I don't like rumors.
I understand.
I'll be careful.
Bokdol. Boksun.
What do you guys think?
Should I tell him?
Or should I not?
Should I?
Dr. Yong.
The herbs we ordered didn't arrive,
so I'm going to order them again.
Okay.
Did you hear what I said?
About ordering them again?
I did.
What are you doing right now
during consultation hours?
All the elderly have gone to the session,
so we have no patients.
What was that for?
I'm feeding them. Look at them eat.
These guys aren't meant
to be raised like that!
You don't have any friends, do you?
- You have no one to hang out with, right?
- What?
You pick on me all the time
because you're bored
and have no friends, right?
I'm the one picking on you?
I'm wrestling with
a serious dilemma right now, okay?
The prince is in a dilemma, huh?
You're probably just torn between
two luxury choices!
Wrestle away, your highness!
The fate of our center
hangs in the balance!
You have no idea, damn it.
Why'd she have to dump
all that expensive food in there?
I can't even get it out now.
:cue
Dr. Do.
Hi.
Are you here for beer?
That's great. I've been wanting
to grab a beer with you.
Take your pick. Drinks are on me tonight
since I owe you and all.
I don't actually feel
like drinking beer today.
Really?
I didn't know that was possible.
Oh, right.
You came to the village hall today, right?
Yes. You had left something behind.
Why did you just leave?
You could have stayed and helped.
You didn't have many patients today
because of the session.
Well, you seemed to be doing fine
with Dr. Chiyeon.
So I wasn't sure I should butt in.
Dr. Do.
Did I upset you in some way?
No, not at all.
Really?
Guess I'm just imagining it.
Then let's have a beer out by the beach.
The breeze is nice,
and we've got plenty of snacks.
No, I don't want people to get
the wrong idea about us.
What do you mean, the wrong idea?
I had no idea
that you and Dr. Chiyeon were, well…
Wait, you also believe those rumors?
Come on, that's just the village elders
gossiping among themselves.
It didn't seem to be just a rumor.
The two of you…
seemed really close.
I don't know why I should have to
defend myself about this.
But if being seen as close
starts those rumors,
shouldn't there be more rumors about us?
We spent the night together,
drank together,
and even got caught in the rain.
Doing things like that
with just anyone is why
they're spreading rumors about you being
a doctor hunter and a gold digger.
I mean…
I see.
I thought you were acting
a little strange today…
So you were scared
that I'd get my hooks in?
No, that's not what I mean--
Don't be scared.
I have no intention
of getting my hooks into you.
Ms. Yuk, I didn't mean it like…
You stupid idiot…
Setting timer for one minute.
Dr. Hyeon.
I need to tell you something.
But don't turn around.
I don't think I can tell you
if I looked you in the eye.
I've given it a lot of thought,
:cue
and it feels like
this is the right thing to do.
Listen closely to what I'm about to say.
Ms. Yuk Hari…
She's not going out with you
because she actually likes you.
Ms. Yuk Hari is…
a doctor hunter!
Holy crap.
Are you in shock?
Dr. Hyeon?
Yes?
What is it?
Why would you wear those in the quarters?
Did you not hear anything I said just now?
The heck?
Hello?
This is Eom Jeongseon.
I'm in the middle of something important,
so call me again later.
I doubt it's more important than this.
Your phone is with me.
That's nonsense.
I'm literally on the phone right now.
"Ninnyhammer"?
Who the heck is this Ninnyhammer?
- Hello?
- You took my phone, and I took yours!
How did that happen?
How the heck should I know?
Bring it over to me right now!
Me? Why should I?
Oh, my. I guess you don't want
to go on leave anymore.
- What?
- Right now.
Damn it!
Dr. Hyeon, do you know
what "ninnyhammer" means?
Stupid…
- Idiot?
- What?
Damn it.
Who does she think she is,
telling me to come over?
Here.
Be more careful from now on.
Look who's talking.
You're the one who took mine.
What the…
What's with the feast?
Throwing a party or something?
What's it to you?
Seaweed soup and ribs.
Is it your birthday or something?
It's your birthday?
Who eats by themselves on their birthday?
It's because I have no friends!
Just go!
:cue
What?
I'll be your friend.
What…
What are you doing?
Oh…
It looks so good.
Grab yourself a bowl of rice and sit.
I asked you what you're doing!
Ah…
Isn't it obvious?
I'm throwing you a birthday party.
Who eats by themselves on their birthday?
And just so you know,
there are three essentials for a birthday.
A birthday feast, friends,
and birthday drinks.
Do you have any alcohol?
Okay.
One, two, three, four.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, de… ♪
♪ Ms. Jeongseon ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Blow them out.
You're taking a lot of credit
for a feast you didn't even prepare.
Happy birthday.
Oh, hold on,
I prepared something for you.
Ta-da!
Shall we toast?
I'm sorry.
Cheers.
I wasn't expecting
a prince like you to care so much
- about someone else's birthday.
- Hmm.
I've always thought that birthdays
should be lively, joyous occasions.
Of course you did.
Not that I ever got to enjoy that.
Ah.
The truth is that I kind of got picked on.
The son of a Korean Medicine clinic
director in Seoul got picked on?
I know, right?
Isn't that really weird?
I don't get why someone
would hate on a kid from a rich family
who's as adorable and nice as me.
That's why I'm not a huge fan of
people spending birthdays alone.
So you won't be
spending it by yourself today.
You'll be spending it with me.
Cheers!
:cue
MS. YUK HARI
Hello?
Dr. Do,
please come to the center right now.
- Hurry.
- Huh?
Okay. Let's apologize to her in person.
Hmm?
Dr. Do.
What is it?
Hold on…
That's a fishhook. How did this happen?
During a meal, apparently.
I guess the fish still had a hook in it.
- The lidocaine, please.
- Okay.
- You've gotten your tetanus shot, right?
- Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
I'll remove it in no time.
This is going to sting.
What happened?
He got a hook stuck in his tongue.
Hold on.
Fishhooks aren't like regular needles.
They have a barb at the tip,
so just pulling it
could tear the tissue apart.
That'll cause way more damage.
Then what should we do?
I've done it before, so I'll do it.
- Have you administered lidocaine?
-  Yes.
Can you feel this?
Okay, we're done.
Thank you so much. Ow.
I'll prescribe some antibiotics,
so be sure to take them.
I'll help you with
the rest outside. Watch your step.
You can head on up now.
I'm on call,
so I'll write the prescription.
Okay.
Man, my head is killing me.
What the…
What the heck?
No way.
:cue
Why don't you get up now?
I know you're awake, so get up!
I can see you in the mirror!
I'm sorry.
- What?
- I'm…
I'm not sure how this happened,
but I'm really sorry.
Well, whether you remember it or not,
or whether you're pretending
not to remember,
I couldn't care less,
so just do what you will.
What really matters to me right now is
that no one sees you leaving my house.
If someone saw you sneaking out of here,
can you imagine
the scandal that would cause?
That's right.
Which is why I'm going to leave right now,
and you should wait 20 minutes
before you leave.
That's when the grannies gather
at the village hall to play Go-Stop.
Mmm.
Let the center know you'll be late, okay?
Y-Yes. I-I'll call them. Okay.
And about last night…
Last night…
Let's just forget it ever happened.
Stick to the plan. Twenty minutes!
Right. Twenty minutes.
I'm so screwed.
Damn it.
Oh, Dr. Yong!
- I just cleaned that area!
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Why did you enter through that door?
Sorry?
Well, I…
I was out on a walk.
Oh, you're late to work
because you were exercising?
How admirable.
Thank you.
Mmm. Give it to me.
Hello? This is the Public Health Center.
Huh? What?
But why would
someone like that come here…
Mmm.
Yes, I understand.
- Hang up. Hang up.
- Ms. Hwang, are you okay?
Goodness me, what a disaster.
What is it? What happened?
Choi Hyangmi, the Director of
Public Health Care Services,
is coming to our center right now
to give us an official warning.
Choi Hyangmi is coming in person
to our center?
What's an official warning?
An official warning is
a penalty that applies to civil servants,
and it can accumulate.
If a PH doc gets too many warnings,
they can dock your pay,
restrict your leave,
and in the worst-case scenario,
even extend your mandatory service.
Horrifying, if you ask me.
Yes, governor.
It's a little windy,
but the ferry has departed.
I'll report to you once I return.
Okay.
:cue
Who was it?
Did any of you slip up
while I wasn't looking?
Huh?
Uh…
By any chance…
ca-ca-can one's private life or…
…rumors…
- be the cause of--
- Why would you bring that up now? Sheesh.
Calm down! Everyone, wear your gowns!
Get changed, pronto!
Wear your civil servant IDs.
- Ms. Hwang. Ms. Hwang.
- What is it?
I'm sorry, but I haven't received
my civil servant ID yet.
- I have applied for one, though.
-  What?
Why are you
telling me this now?
I actually kept telling you about it--
It's too late for that now, isn't it?
Mr. Kim Dupal!
Yes, Mr. Kim Dupal, Mr. Kim Dupal.
Mr. Kim Dupal. He-Here it is.
- Oh, thank you. Oh, thank you so much.
- Whoa.
- But this is a bit…
-  This should do.
Just flip it over! No one will notice.
Okay. What are you doing?
Put your gowns on!
- Let's all stay calm now.
-  Uh, Kim Du… Kim Dupal…
How can she be so calm and composed?
Am I the only one losing my mind here?
What is her deal?
Dr. Yong.
I'll leave the mugwort
and the cups in the therapy room.
Okay.
I'm so scared.
She's here, she's here!
Welcome, ma'am!
Hello.
- Is something going on?
-  Hello.
Oh, um, no. What brings you here?
Our baby's been sniffling for a few days,
and her throat is raw.
Can the doctor of Korean medicine
take a look?
Western medicine isn't helping at all.
-  Can you say "Ah" for me?
- Ah.
Hmm.
Oh.
Her throat's a bit swollen.
Were there any other symptoms?
Like breaking out in a cold sweat.
I don't think so.
Medicine works well for colds,
but acupuncture can also help.
- Oh, I see.
- Let's get you better with it.
No, I don't want it!
- It won't hurt at all.
-  He said it's not gonna hurt.
- This is cool to the touch.
-  Hang in there, okay?
It feels nice and refreshing
when you put it on.
That's refreshing, right?
See? Nice and cool, right?
Oh, hold on.
I think there's something here.
It's an ant. Hold still.
Got it.
Ta-da. That didn't hurt at all, did it?
:cue
- Grandma.
-  It's okay.
Does it hurt?
- Oh, dear.
- It's okay.
Why are you crying?
I know it doesn't hurt one bit.
- It does hurt!
- Oh, dear.
Stop lying! If it really hurt,
you would've cried earlier!
Oh, dear.
- Deokhwa, it's okay.
- It hurts!
Come on, why are you crying?
You liar.
I'm barely holding back my tears myself.
Why are you crying?
Dr. Yong.
Come outside. The director is here.
Oh, okay.
Just a second, Deokhwa.
Welcome, ma'am.
I came here today
to issue an official warning.
Does anyone know what you did wrong?
Which one of you is Dr. Do Jiui?
Th-That would be me.
How would you define
a civil servant, Dr. Do?
Excuse me?
How can a civil servant
managing provincial affairs
not even know the name of the person
leading the organization?
That is a dereliction of your duty
and a direct challenge to authority.
Those were the words…
of Governor Ko Changmok.
Personally, I don't agree with him.
How should a doctor know
what the governor's name is?
I've delivered the governor's words.
And you've received them, so that's that.
Right.
Then, since you came all this way,
how would you like to take a look around?
-  Sure.
-  Okay.
Deokhwa, don't run!
Deokhwa!
-  Ow.
-  Deokhwa!
- Deokhwa!
-  Are you okay?
-  Oh, dear.
-  Come here.
Come here, Deokhwa.
-  Are you all right?
- Let me take a look. Excuse me.
Are you okay? I'm sorry.
Oh, my gosh.
The location and depth of the wound
don't suggest any nerve or muscle damage.
But since you fell,
there may be a wrist fracture
or some foreign debris inside,
:cue
so I think it's best to get an X-ray.
Should I just dress the wound,
or suture it?
That's for
the attending physician to decide.
Why are you asking me?
I'll suture it.
Let's have you wear this.
POLYAMIDE SUTURE
Plastic surgeon?
Yes.
Then I'm in luck.
Attention, all residents.
Due to a sudden high seas
and gale warning,
all passenger ferries and ship operations
have been suspended.
Due to a sudden hazardous seas
and gale warning,
all passenger ferries and ship operations
have been suspended.
We can't have the ferries suspended.
That means the director is stuck with us.
Since the ferry's been suspended,
let's go out for a team dinner.
What do you say?
Uh, wow.
I know you're on-call, Dr. Do,
but everyone else is good to drink, right?
-  That's right.
- Right.
- Director, I don't think you should…
- Just one glass.
Okay everyone,
let's all drink plenty but responsibly.
Here's to the Public Health Center!
Cheers!
My, here's the good stuff.
Here's your wild flounder.
- Here you go.
-  The flounder's here.
Does the center have any issues?
So many,
like you wouldn't believe.
They shut down two clinics last year,
so it's absolute chaos
every time the seasons change.
Ms. Yuk, you've had a decent number
of relationships on the mainland, right?
A decent number, I guess.
So I'm curious.
Is it true that folks on the mainland
don't get clingy and stuff
even after a one-night stand?
Huh?
Well, some people are like that,
and others aren't.
It depends on the person.
But aren't most people like that?
That's how it was on TV shows.
Uh, Ms. Eom…
Yes?
It's nothing.
I'm going to step outside for some air.
-  Oh, goodness.
-  Would you like another glass?
Yes, please.
Goodness, that burns.
Yes, yes.
:cue
CLIFFSIDE RAW FISH RESTAURANT
Can we talk?
I made a mistake--
You don't need to apologize.
Those rumors weren't false anyway.
If only dating doctors makes someone
a doctor-hunter gold digger…
then I am a doctor-hunter gold digger
as people say.
What are you…
I practically lived at the hospital,
so the only guys around were doctors.
Naturally, I dated a few.
That's right.
So I am a doctor-hunter gold digger.
But I told you not to worry, didn't I?
I won't get my hooks into you.
Why not?
Huh?
Why wouldn't you?
I'm a doctor too.
Help!
Somebody, help!
-  Huh?
Wait, hold on. Let me take her.
Huh?
Oh, goodness. What happened?
Let's sit here.
Deokhwa, can you tell me where it hurts?
Just a moment.
Your throat?
Her hoarse, muffled voice
while seated in a tripod position.
Chin lifted and mouth open
to breathe better.
All classic signs of acute epiglottitis.
INFLAMMATION OF EPIGLOTTIS
Children have narrow airways,
so severe respiratory distress
can become fatal
if they aren't rushed
to a hospital immediately.
It's an emergency.
Call a medical boat.
Get ready for an intubation
and come to the port.
Okay.
INSERTION OF TUBE
INTO BODY PASSAGE
I'll go with him.
-  Someone help me.
- Yes, ma'am.
PUBLIC HEALTH CENTER
DISPENSARY
ADULT - PEDIATRIC
:cue
All set.
Why won't they pick up?
Hurry, hurry!
- Stethoscope.
Turn her for me.
Oh! The chief's boat is coming in.
This way!
Over here, over here!
- You get ready too, Dr. Do.
- Me? No, I can't.
I'm not a pediatrician,
and I've never done this in a real case.
Get a hold of yourself, Dr. Do.
I have a hand injury,
and you're the only doctor
who didn't drink.
PYEONDONGDO FISHING
I heard from the Coast Guard!
Don't worry,
I'm certified for local emergencies!
I'm taking you out to meet their cutter,
so hurry up and jump in!
Grab my hand.
- Hurry and climb on board.
-  My goodness.
-  It's a race against the clock!
- Come on, let's go.
Careful.
It's going to be okay.
It's okay, Deokhwa.
- I'll get a blanket.
-  Dr. Jiui!
Dr. Jiui.
We agreed to go together, remember?
Put on your life jackets
so we can go.
Okay.
:cue
Dr. Do, Deokhwa…
Deokhwa…
Dr. Do, get ready to intubate her.
- Deokhwa, wake up.
- Hurry!
-  Oh, Deokhwa…
- Kill the engine!
You have to do it, Dr. Do.
Captain, he's going to die!
Please go faster!
Seonu!
No, no, I can't do this.
She's already showing signs of cyanosis,
which means we will lose her soon.
Legally, you have a justifiable reason
to refuse treatment,
and I can't force your hand
if you absolutely won't do it.
But please save this child.
Dr. Do, I'll help you. Okay?
- Please.
-  Doctor, please save her.
Let's switch places.
- Okay.
-  Deokhwa…
Deokhwa, hang in there a little longer.
It's a cold intubation
on a moving boat, so it won't be easy.
Get a clear view of the airway first.
Intubation isn't something you do by feel.
You have to have visual confirmation
before you proceed.
I can see the epiglottis.
Can you see the vocal cords?
Uh…
If you drop it there,
you'll hit the esophagus.
Use the laryngoscope blade
to directly lift the epiglottis
so the larynx opens up.
Seonu!
Wh-Whoa. You can't just lift it like that.
If you lever it against the teeth,
the blade will snap them right off.
Lift upward and forward.
Laryngeal edema is obstructing
the view of the trachea.
I can't insert the tube.
How about now?
- It's open. Give me the tube.
- Yes, Doctor.
:cue
- The tube's in. Remove the stylet.
- Yes, Doctor.
- Connect the Ambu bag right away.
MANUAL RESUSCITATOR
Stethoscope.
Her cyanosis is gone.
That means
her lungs are getting airflow.
Thank you, Doctor.
Dr. Do, are you okay?
Seonu!
Dr. Do!
- Dr. Do!
- Dr. Do Jiui!
What the…
Dr. Do!
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT
DOCTORS HAVE AN OBLIGATION
TO RESPECT
THEIR PATIENTS' SECRETS
CHECKING THE PLAYBACK
IS ABSOLUTELY ESSENTIAL!
DOCTOR ON THE EDGE
Ms. Hari.
What are you hesitating for?
Are you going?
He's way too conscious of her.
So it was you, Ms. Yuk Hari.
I guess the rumors are true.
That Ms. Yuk Hari is a doctor hunter.
That woman…
She's not really into you.
But you said
we should give this a go.
Hari.
I told you I'm not breaking up with you!
Why? Is it because of
that PH doc you came here with?
Dr. Do!
Translated by Yoon Hyuk Park