♪Full moon in Wuxia♪
♪The lanterns are shining♪
♪So many guests in Tianxiang Restaurant♪
♪When I use the knife♪
♪I cut perfect slices♪
♪I cook with the world in the palm of my hand♪
♪With sauce and vinegar♪
♪And cooking skills♪
♪Let's have a battle♪
♪With my cooking♪
♪And my fighting spirit♪
♪I can't help but accept everything with laughter♪
♪Joys and sorrows♪
♪I've tasted everything in life♪
♪I can still smell the flavor
of the delicacies in the past♪
♪Delicious food is necessary for love♪
♪My great partner♪
♪Let's march on together♪
♪Afflictions in life♪
♪Let me feel them all♪
♪As long as I'm happy♪
♪Then every day♪
♪Is a perfect day with love♪
[The Legend of TAOTIE]
[Episode 2]
It smells so good. So good.
Why does it smell so good?
I'm hungry now.
Do you want to sell it?
How much should I pay?
How dare you!
This is the Prince of Langya, the new Mayor of Wuxia.
Behave yourself!
Girl,
why did you say that just now?
Do I smell of something special?
Because you're a beast.
And a very fragrant one.
You're asking for it!
Easy.
I've always heard
Miss Zhu is best at cooking beasts.
You deserve your reputation.
But I didn't expect you
to be so interesting.
Come here.
This girl is the best chef in the world?
This is
fried with sea salt.
Have a taste.
How's it?
It's really extraordinary.
However, Miss Zhu,
it's still inferior to what I brought.
The Black Turtle from Beidi.
Chisel its tortoise shell to get its meat
and pickle it with gold foil
to preserve the flavor forever.
It is the best of the best in the world.
No wonder you smell like a beast.
It's its smell.
Mingyan.
Your Highness.
Don't you understand?
Put your sword back.
You want me to cook it?
Exactly.
No.
How dare you!
Miss Zhu.
I also have temper.
Exactly.
You're a prince.
You!
Your Highness.
What Miss Zhu means…
The beast is spiritual.
The fresher, the better.
Sashimi is the best.
Braising and scalding take second place.
Steaming and boiling take last place.
You have kept this meat for so long.
It has long lost its spirituality.
Even if the flavor does not change,
what's the difference with a piece of ham?
I take your point.
Miss Zhu.
If we don't do business today,
I'll go up and hang the white cloth
to avoid misunderstanding.
Why did you hang it earlier?
He's so handsome!
He is also a prince.
I have never seen
such a handsome man in my life.
How long do you live in this life?
However, Miss Zhu,
even if the cloth hung out,
what if I want to eat it?
Can you do me a favor?
This meat should not be cooked by me.
Take it back to your royal chef,
Zhao Heng.
You know me?
Yes, of course.
Zhao Heng, the Prince of Langya.
Everyone knows you.
But you didn't come to Wuxia
just to let me cook this meat, did you?
I am good for nothing.
I was not able to stay in the capital.
So I was sent here
in charge of the Inspection Department.
Inspection Department?
So from today on,
thank you, Miss Zhu.
I can't take your gratitude.
But if the Inspection Department
catches any rare beast in the future,
you must think of me.
Absolutely.
Rare animals
must be shared with Miss Zhu.
It sounds like I am so greedy.
But I tell you what,
if there's any beast secretly hidden
in Miss Zhu's Tianxiang Restaurant
and you don't tell me,
I won't allow it happen.
I heard that someone carried a jar
into the Tianxiang Restaurant yesterday.
Was that the merman?
The merman eats people.
If it's hidden here,
that'll be very dangerous.
Let's go.
I ate the perch yesterday
raw with mustard.
Your Highness is late.
Where's others?
Just the two of us.
No one else.
Look.
My taste
is really light recently.
I really want to eat a special dish.
Since Miss Zhu cooks beasts
so well, then…
I don't have any beasts here.
Look at my Tianxiang Restaurant.
It's been closed for a long time.
Get out of the way.
Mingyan.
Let's get back.
Official Xu.
[Inspection Department]
I am Xu Shuying, an official of Imperial Academy.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Official Xu, please.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I have long heard
that Official Xu
has written the book
“Records of Beasts in the Continent”
In the book, you described
all the rare animals in the world.
This time, I am ordered by my father
to be in charge of the Inspection Department.
About the Lotus Tower,
I need to consult with you.
Your Highness, please.
I heard that
500 years ago, Monk Lotus's kindness
secretly influenced the beast Taotie
who broke into the world.
This led the Portal open
and a large number of beasts
have broken into the human world.
Some of them were ambitious.
Led by the Black Qilin King,
they intended to massacre human
and occupy two worlds.
Monk Lotus fought with him in Wuxia,
which is the closest place
between the two worlds.
Although he did not win a complete victory,
he suppressed him
by turning his body into the Lotus Tower.
Is this true?
Your Highness,
that's right.
That is the origin of the Lotus Tower.
From this point of view,
the Lotus Tower is down and the Black Qilin King is out.
It's true.
Is the damage to the Lotus Tower recently
related to the Black Qilin King?
About this matter,
I'm not sure.
Please forgive me.
Your Highness, you went to
Tianxiang Restaurant today.
What information have you got?
Why did you say so?
Miss Zhu's origin is a mystery.
She cares about Lotus Tower very much.
It has long been rumored
that she was
the incarnation of that Taotie.
Jiao.
Hard work for you, Jiao.
Not at all.
Are you okay?
Miss Zhu.
What's the matter with you?
You're a lady.
In broad daylight,
it's not decent.
How can you fall asleep
while chatting in front of a strange man?
If you hadn't stopped me last night,
I would have gone to bed early if I was full.
Why did I talk so much nonsense?
You still want to eat Jiao?
Actually, before going out,
I have eaten Jiao.
You're lying.
No.
Then I'd be blind.
I have been here for so long.
What little trick
can you hide from me?
Besides,
As long as you lie,
your eyes
will turn around.
If I knew it,
I would starve you to death at the door
of Tianxiang Restaurant.
Tell me the truth.
What are you up to?
Do you really want to give Jiao
to Prince of Langya?
Yeah.
If you do this,
you're hurting Jiao.
The Inspection Department's job
is to catch beasts.
I'm just making use of an opportunity.
Oh, I see.
Do you want to take a chance
to have a finger in the pie?
There's no way.
I'm hungry.
You!
Why do you have such big temper?
Qing!
Jiao.
Stop. Stop.
I want to see Jiao.
- I want to see Jiao.
- Stop.
- Jiao.
- Jiao!
You cannot enter.
So here you come.
Mister Chang Qing.
I want to get Jiao back.
I can't make the decision.
Mister Chang Qing.
Who is it?
Who dares to shout in my Tianxiang Restaurant?
Miss Zhu.
Cuiyan.
Mister Gao Cong.
I'm afraid you don't know
the rules of my Tianxiang Restaurant.
Miss Zhu.
I regret it.
Didn't you let me go back
and think about it?
I thought it over.
I shouldn't have sold Jiao.
After all, she is my beloved woman.
There are many fortunes in the world,
but Jiao is always my only treasure.
Please let me get my love back.
You called her monster when selling her.
But now you call her your lover.
Ridiculous.
I thought of Jiao's kindness to me in the past.
I really regret it.
It's all my obsession
that I did such an indecent thing.
Please give her back to me.
I will treat her well!
Mister Gao Cong.
How can you
easily regret it
when doing business?
If this goes out,
how can Tianxiang Restaurant
do business?
Miss Zhu, please show mercy.
I was just in a moment of madness
to do such a shameful thing.
Miss Zhu.
Please give Jiao back to me.
I would be very grateful.
Even if I agree,
Jiao may not want to go back with you.
Since she is your wife,
you have to follow her wishes.
Here's the thing.
If she wants to go back with you today,
I will help you two.
Thank you, Miss Zhu.
You really want him to get Jiao back?
Jiao.
I'm inhuman!
It's all my fault!
We should live together
and die together.
This is the vow that can be made
between the closest relatives and loved ones.
We took vows before.
But I sold you out
because I wanted to be rich for a while.
I spent more than ten years studying in vain,
but lived as a wife seller
and ungrateful bastard.
Now,
I regret it.
If I treat you bad again from now on,
I will be doomed
eternally.
My dear.
Would you forgive me?
My Tianxiang Restaurant is not your home.
If you want to cuddle, go back to your home.
My dear.
Let's go home.
Sure.
Not going?
Stop hanging around in front of my eyes.
Thank you, Miss Zhu.
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go.
Is what you said
a little too mean?
[Jia Residence]
What are you doing?
What are we doing?
You ate so many of our brothers.
You're plump now.
It's time for us to have a good meal.
No!
Mr. Jia.
Your nightmares
come more and more frequent.
The plan has been implemented.
I will surely give the merman to you.
After you eat the merman,
it will cure the nightmare.
How much is this?
This water spinach costs a penny for a catty.
Is it fresh?
Yes.
I just pulled it out of the ground this morning.
The Inspection Department is handling cases.
What about this?
The merman once appeared here.
No trace can be left behind.
Yes!
What's the matter?
Have you heard of it?
Someone
saw the merman nearby.
Don't frighten me.
How could I frighten you?
They really landed?
Is it true or not?
Lady.
Why are you leaving?
Do you want this?
We have been wearing the same dress
for two months.
When can Mister
draw a new one for us?
Indeed.
I saw a pair of cherry red earrings
on the street the other day.
They are perfect for me.
If I wear it,
I must be so beautiful
that the Prince of Langya can't even
open his eyes.
Can't open his eyes because of your beauty?
I think you will be so ugly
that even the Prince of Langya
dares not look at you.
Cuiyan, what are you talking about?
I'm teaching you a lesson!
Cuiyan, stop!
Cuiyan!
Stop!
In the daytime,
it won't be a ghost, right?
What kind of ghost dares to come
to Tianxiang Restaurant?
Don't frighten yourself.
Yes.
Go.
Okay. Go.
This is the third time this month.
A ghost in the daytime?
Are you really afraid?
Mister.
Since Miss Zhu plays so hard,
of course we should cooperate.
Miss Zhu.
What are you up to this time?
I'm hungry.
My illness is getting serious.
Look, my hands can't even move.
Qing.
I'm so sick.
Don't you care about me?
Of course I do.
Cuiyan, Yingtao.
Go and fetch Miss Zhu's Taotie Cauldron.
Mister.
Draw me new clothes.
Draw me new earrings.
You two go get the thing first.
Mister.
Why does Miss Zhu get whatever she wants?
We get nothing we want.
Exactly.
Although you look good,
you're very biased.
All right.
You two maidservants have gone bad.
Let me redraw two
to replace you.
I don't want Taotie Cauldron.
Qing!
You know what I want!
I know your bodies are stiff
and you love sleeping.
But what's wrong with you now
is not about that.
The problem lies in your appetite.
Since I met you two years ago,
I knew you have the problem of eating beasts.
You can be cured by smelling before.
Why not now?
It changed, okay?
You just try to eat the beast.
Yes!
Here comes Prince of Langya.
It seems that
I come at the wrong time.
At the right time!
Wait a second.
Don't go.
Why does he come again?
Where's the turtle?
Miss Zhu, what's the matter with your hands?
Your Highness.
Mingyan.
I am here to deliver meat.
Cuiyan, Yingtao.
Bring my incense.
You.
Follow me.
What are you going to do?
You don't let me eat any beast.
I'll show you.
Gluttonous girl.
You know this bacon
has long lost its spirituality.
It's the same as ordinary ham.
Why are you so obsessed?
I just want to tell you today that
as long as I am willing to do,
dead things can also become alive.
Didn't you say it was bacon?
Just watch.
It's alive!
Marvelous.
You do it.
Enjoy it.
This meat
melts at the mouth.
The gravy is filling.
Even the taste is the same as ordinary fresh meat.
No.
It should be better.
Miss Zhu's cooking skill
is worthy of being the best in the world.
This is called reincarnation of beast.
This is called never change.
Leave him alone.
Miss Zhu.
He's gone.
Don't pretend.
What do you mean by that?
The meat of the beast,
I have tasted it before.
Even if Miss Zhu is a good cook,
you can't control life and death.
The so-called theory of reincarnation
is just physical change
instead of qualitative change.
Even if the meat is delicious,
there is no spirit of beast.
You can tell it.
If cooking
can solve all the problems,
I don't have to fight with that stinky Qing.
Qing?
This nickname is quite interesting.
Interesting?
Let me tell you.
I'm really good at nicknames.
Look at them.
The green is called Chunjiu.
The red is called Xiefen.
Are they good?
Chunjiu, Xiefen.
Let me give you one, too.
You're Heng.
You!
You
are Choudoufu.
Miss Zhu.
My surname is Zhao and my given name is Heng.
Just call me by my name.
Heng, you come to me again today.
Is there no delicious food at home?
Recently, there have been traces
of merman in the market.
The mermen are cruel
and dangerous.
I came to remind Miss Zhu.
But I also heard that
the meat of merman is delicious.
Don't you want to taste it?
Sure enough.
You can still see me through.
What is that?
Monsters! There are monsters!
Monsters!
There are monsters!
Let's go.
Go.
Husband!
Father.
Daughter.
Go back with me.
Father, I can't leave him.
Father.
Husband!
Jiao!
Run fast!
They're mermen!
Husband!
Chase!
Hurry up.
How are you?
I'm the one who dragged you down.
If you and I never met,
you would not be expelled from the Gao
and you would not end up with a broken leg.
I have dragged you down from beginning to end.
Now my father and brother have come.
It's time for me to leave.
No.
Jiao.
Don't leave me.
No.
Jiao. Jiao.
Husband.
Husband, you…
Jiao.
No, don't leave me.
Now even you don't stay with me,
in the big world,
where is my shelter?
How can I protect you?
Husband.
You must take it with you.
Don't lose it.
I heard that the emperor doesn't like you
and put you in exile in disguise.
If I say yes,
what do you think?
Then you must not be his own son.
I am!
It's so late.
You're not sleeping yet.
Didn't you just come back?
It's getting late.
I'm leaving.
That's good.
Goodbye.
Heng!
Bye-bye!
You drank so much.
What were you talking about?
We talked about how to eat the mermaid.
You still want to eat Jiao?
It's all her fault.
Does falling in love with a foreign race
mean taking the blame?
What's wrong with her?
Do you care
if I starve to death or be sick to death?
Even Gao Cong could come around.
Why are you still obsessed?
All living beings are equal.
Do you have to hurt the innocent
to satisfy your appetite?
The meat of beast is meat.
Isn't the meat of chicken, duck and fish meat?
You say that all living beings are equal.
Should the whole world be vegetarian?
Are vegetables and fruits lifeless?
You!
Where are you going?
Go fishing at sea.
Monk.
The Lotus Tower has cracks.
Is there anything big to happen?
I am Taotie.
All things in the world
should be my food.
But you just told me
that the human world is a world with temperature
and emotion.
But is it really a good thing
to have emotion?
It's all your fault.
If it wasn't for my promise to you,
I wouldn't be constrained
in this small city.
What kind of promise makes
Miss Zhu so attentive?
Don't you know that
no one is allowed to enter the Lotus Tower?
But there is no sign at the door.
This is the rule
that everyone in Wuxia knows.
I am a newcomer.
Those who don't know are innocent.
But I don't know who set the rule.
I set it.
You're quite able to find excuses for yourself.
Your Highness.
Please go back.
Miss Zhu, rest assured.
I am not interested in your secret.
It's just that it's getting late.
Why don't I take you back?
Miss Zhu.
Your Highness.
Please go back.
Don't hold up if you feel unwell.
Have more.
Eat more.
I want to eat that.
Hot pot.
It's low-class.
Only like-minded people
can get together to eat hot pot.
Obviously,
she's not with us.
I heard
someone was brought back yesterday.
You dare to say?
It's you who won't let me eat the beast!
It makes my legs weak.
I'm Taotie!
I can swallow the whole Tianxiang Restaurant
in one bite.
Neither this
nor that can I eat.
How about
I draw a mermaid for you?
Good.
Where is your pen?
Draw now!
Come on. Come on.
Where is your pen? Where is your pen?
I…
When you have stomach-ache,
you will cry on the table again.
Miss Zhu hasn't eaten for several days.
If you can draw one,
let her try.
Yeah.
You completely forget who drew you two out.
You help her now.
Is eating so easy?
Do you think she's just eating the meat?
What's wrong with them two helping me?
Who is the Miss now?
Do you know how to trick me now?
What you have eaten before are ordinary beasts.
But Jiao
has human feelings now.
What's wrong with human feelings?
She's so miserable.
What's wrong with me helping her out of her pain?
The relief she said
is to eat Jiao.
It's killing!
What's more,
whenever she devours a painful beast,
the beast will be free,
but she has to live with pain.
That is to say,
if Miss Zhu eats Jiao,
Miss Zhu will bear the pain of Jiao
and go on living.
You're right.
That's something big.
Then we have to find some
happy beasts for Miss Zhu.
Or we can help Jiao
to be happy,
then Miss Zhu can eat it.
Exactly.
What's wrong with you?
You're absolutely wrong!
What's wrong?
I think they understand it quite well.
With your reason,
if neither of them can understand,
who else can understand?
I think you two are right.
Yes.
Let's make Jiao very happy first
and then let Miss Zhu eat her.
Miss Zhu will be happy then.
Yeah, I think so.
I think Cuiyan is quite right.
She will not be unhappy anymore!
Miss Zhu, do you think so?
Cuiyan is right.
If Jiao became happy,
I could be happy after eating her.
Right?
Very good.
That's right.
Cuiyan.
In the future, we will catch more beasts.
I am like living among a group of old hens.
How did Cuiyan become so smart?
You're quite right.
If Jiao became happy,
I could be happier after eating her.
I just want to eat happy beasts!
They had a fight again?
Every day is like this.
Let's go.
Why are you looking at me?
How do you know I'm looking at you
if you don't look at me?
What did Gao Cong come to see you today?
He gave me a gift on the Mid-Autumn Festival.
Giving you gift without reason
must be asking for something.
What did you promise him again?
Can't he just give me gifts?
He is not such a person.
If he had something valuable,
he'd already sell it.
He thanked me.
I let him and Jiao
live a happy life again.
Right?
Yes.
As long as you give up the idea
of eating the mermaid,
you will benefit everyone.
By the way,
well,
how do we celebrate the Mid-Autumn Festival?
I beg your pardon?
How do we celebrate the Mid-Autumn Festival?
None of your business.
I'm just asking.
I don't care about you.
Here comes Prince of Langya.
Miss Zhu.
Nice to meet you again.
Why doesn't Your Highness stay at home
with your family tonight?
Why do you come to Tianxiang Restaurant again?
Of course, I specially invite Miss Zhu
to go to the Mid-Autumn Festival Feast.
This is the first time that I spent the Mid-Autumn Festival
in Wuxia.
Without the delicious food of Miss Zhu,
isn't it a pity?
Miss Zhu is not going anywhere today.
We will be reunited at home.
How?
There is nothing to eat at home.
Heng.
I'm going.
Your Highness, please wait for a second.
I'll change into a beautiful dress.
Wait.
Let her go!
Qing.
Watch your manners.
Miss Zhu.
Don't be so harsh.
He's just a
little accountant.
Mingyan.
It's so beautiful!
Get back.
I don't know if this golden silk dress
can meet the wishes of Miss Zhu.
Very good.
Extremely good.
You two.
Help your Miss to get dressed.
Sure.
Let's go.
Who are you with?
♪Here's a flower for you♪
♪I don't know what to say
when we look at each other♪
♪Time goes by so quickly♪
♪My obsession leads to my fate♪
♪Destiny is confusing over the years♪
♪It feels bleak even with the light on♪
♪I see the shadow when I almost forget you♪
♪A ray of light on my journey♪
♪It's like you're here to pour out your heart♪
♪Although the memories of our love♪
♪Bring us pain♪
♪All I ask for is to hold your hand♪
♪Until the end of time♪
♪Selflessly♪
♪We taste the sorrows and joys♪
♪I'll never let you go till death do us part♪