♪Full moon in Wuxia♪
♪The lanterns are shining♪
♪So many guests in Tianxiang Restaurant♪
♪When I use the knife♪
♪I cut perfect slices♪
♪I cook with the world
in the palm of my hand♪
♪With sauce and vinegar♪
♪And cooking skills♪
♪Let's have a battle♪
♪With my cooking♪
♪And my fighting spirit♪
♪I can't help but
accept everything with laughter♪
♪Joys and sorrows♪
♪I've tasted everything in life♪
♪I can still smell the flavor
of the delicacies in the past♪
♪Delicious food is necessary for love♪
♪My great partner♪
♪Let's march on together♪
♪Afflictions in life♪
♪Let me feel them all♪
[The Legend of TAOTIE]
[Episode 16]
Young Master.
You all leave me first.
I'll take care of Miss Zhu.
Qing,
wipe my room clean.
Be gentle.
Don't tear apart my room.
Here.
Wipe the floor for me.
Qing.
Here.
And wipe my table clean.
The teacups too.
And the bed.
Qing.
And the crane.
And the qilin.
The weather is great,
remove the curtains.
Is this really good weather?
Qing, Qing.
Miss Zhu.
I've finished cleaning.
Good.
Then go clean
outside Tianxiang Restaurant.
Why can't I hear?
Miss Zhu.
I'm deaf now.
What should I do?
- Qing.
- I can't hear.
I can't hear. I can't hear.
Qing.
I...
Miss Zhu.
If I don't clean the whole building
to perfection,
you won't let me off, will you?
Qing.
This is the new dish I developed.
Try it.
Miss Zhu,
you'll get better for sure.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Have you found out who did it?
Your Highness,
there's no need to investigate.
What do you mean?
Your Highness, forgive me.
It was I who did it.
You?
I acknowledge my crime.
What are you doing with this umbrella?
I learned that
to find the recipe
of Heaven and Earth in Spring,
Mei Sheng died far from home.
He spat blood on this umbrella,
which formed a plum blossom shape.
Then, his soul
gathered in this Red Plum Umbrella.
I don't want to hear you
talk about Mei Sheng.
Tell me.
Why did you attack Miss Zhu?
I consulted ancient texts
and found this umbrella
is an extraordinary
magical artifact from ancient times.
That's why it could gather
Mei Sheng's soul.
Miss Zhu's illness
is because of the war 500 years ago.
That caused her soul to scatter.
So tonight,
I went to Tianxiang Restaurant
to use this Red Plum Umbrella
to gather Miss Zhu's soul
so that she can recover.
Is this true?
Absolutely true.
Why didn't you report to me
and act on your own?
Because I wasn't sure
how effective this Red Plum Umbrella is.
I dared not report to Your Highness
and could only try it out.
But Miss Zhu had already prepared for it
and was waiting for me to show up.
To protect myself,
I had no choice but to resist.
What about the Dragon Scale Arrow?
Trading the Dragon Scale Arrow
for Xunfang Manual.
Not a bad deal, right?
[Xunfang Manual]
I haven't found it yet.
If anything happens to Miss Zhu,
I will hold you accountable.
I accept any punishment.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Young Master, what are you doing?
Young Master.
Why are you packing?
I need to go out for a while.
Cuiyan, Yingtao,
take good care of Miss Zhu these days.
She is still very weak.
Be sure to close the doors
and windows at night
so she won't catch a chill again.
Be careful
with her diet too.
Buy some marinated quail she likes,
phoenix pastry, duck soaked in dew,
and that...
Young Master, didn't you just return?
Why are you leaving again?
I'll be looking for herbs for Miss Zhu.
Don't worry.
I don't know
when I'll find all the herbs.
Miss Zhu is so weak now.
I wonder if Cuiyan and Yingtao
can take good care of her.
♪Time goes by so quickly♪
♪My obsession leads to my fate♪
One last look at her
brings only more sorrow.
Forget it.
♪It feels bleak even with the light on♪
Miss Zhu,
you must hold on until I return.
Don't worry.
No matter what,
I will definitely gather all the herbs
and return to save you.
♪It's like you're here
to pour out your heart♪
♪Destiny is confusing over the years♪
♪In the cycle of reincarnation♪
♪It's a dream in the making♪
♪Tasting life, a gentle fragrance♪
♪A long road, paying for karma♪
♪Waiting for a lifetime♪
♪A heart that never changes♪
♪Although the memories of our love
bring us pain♪
♪All I ask for is to hold your hand
until the end of time♪
♪Selflessly♪
♪We taste the sorrows and joys♪
♪I'll never let you go
till death do us part♪
Go.
Are you
feeling unwell?
That's good.
Miss Zhu has woken up.
You've just woken up.
Don't overexert yourself.
I've already had my subordinate
retrieve the Red Plum Umbrella.
With this umbrella,
your senses will recover soon.
Don't worry.
Stone
has almost fully recovered.
He's making green dumplings
in the kitchen.
When the green dumplings are ready,
eat them and you'll recover faster.
You just need to rest and recuperate.
Let Miss Zhu rest first.
Let's go.
Alright.
We still can't find it.
I'm exhausted.
Where is Qing?
I've been awake for so long.
Why haven't I seen him?
Well...
Young Master.
Young Master has...
Young Master has gone home.
Yes, yes, yes.
He said his sister Li is sick.
He went home to check on her.
Yes.
Li again.
Why do you have to mention Li?
Your Highness.
Wan'er.
You're back.
Why are you here?
Why aren't you resting at Yunlong?
I'm worried about you,
so I came here.
You don't blame me, right?
I left Yunlong in a hurry
and didn't tell you.
I thought you'd be angry with me.
You traveled day and night
back to Wuxia.
There must be more important matters
than me.
How could I be angry?
Recently, the areas around Wuxia
has been severely affected by disaster.
I'm really worried.
But you
didn't have to travel like this.
You need to rest and recover properly.
A few days ago,
His Majesty went to see me
and asked about the imperial edict
brought back from Wuxia.
I'm not sure
when do you plan
to hold the grand ceremony.
I didn't know how to answer,
so I requested from His Majesty
to come to Wuxia
to discuss this matter with you.
Right now, inside the city,
the disaster is serious
and the people are suffering.
It's inappropriate to talk about
my marriage at this time.
I understand.
I don't know if Miss Zhu
can help you
resolve the drought issue.
As for the disaster,
I will make the decision.
Maid.
Your Highness.
Take good care of Her Grace
and make sure she rests well.
Yes.
Your Highness.
Her Grace has arrived.
Go.
Your Highness.
Didn't I tell you
to rest well at the residence?
Why are you here?
I'm fine now.
I thought it was time for lunch,
so I made some food and brought it.
You must be hungry too.
It's all your favorite food.
Smells so good.
What's that, smells so good?
Miss Zhu.
Did you make all this?
You...
Are you the Princess
Mingyan often mentions?
Miss Zhu,
just call me Wan'er.
Wan'er.
You're truly beautiful
and your name is also lovely.
Miss Zhu.
How about
you join us for the meal?
No.
I want to do it myself.
Your sense haven't fully recovered.
You still need time to recuperate.
Rest well.
Heng.
Why are you
acting more like Qing now?
So naggy.
I'm doing it myself today.
No one can stop me.
Fine.
I won't stop you.
Can I at least help you?
No.
If you help me in the wrong way,
I won't be able to eat.
Miss Zhu.
If you don't mind,
why not let me help you?
Sure.
Stone.
Miss.
How come you're down here?
I just finished
making the green dumplings.
I was going to bring them to you.
I'm much better.
How about you?
How's your health?
I'm all good now.
Miss,
I'd like to discuss something with you.
I want to go back to live in my own shop.
Is there something wrong
with my Tianxiang Restaurant?
No, no, no.
Everything here is great.
But my master's memorial tablet
is still in the shop.
I miss my master.
Alright.
Go back if you want to.
But remember,
you need to make green dumplings
for me every day.
No slacking off.
Thank you, Miss.
Then
I'll go back now.
Wan'er, right?
I've heard His Highness mention
your cooking is outstanding.
Everything you make is delicious.
His Highness especially likes it.
So this time,
I want to ask you
to teach me a few tricks.
Since you sincerely want to learn,
I'll teach you a few tricks.
[Residence of the Prince of Langya]
It smells so good.
The fresh flavor
of the pigeon is coming through.
It really smells good.
Her Grace's cooking skills
are really good.
Yes.
It's definitely good.
The taste is not bad.
Lian, Lian.
Come try it quickly.
It really tastes good.
Hope His Highness likes it too
[Residence of the Prince of Langya]
Your Highness.
You're back so late.
You must be tired.
Why haven't you rested yet?
You've been waiting until now?
It's fine.
Your Highness,
it's so late.
Are you hungry?
Today I specially made you
bird's nest and pigeon soup.
Try it.
Lian.
Not bad.
Thank you, Your Grace.
I'm glad you like it.
Maybe my cooking
is not as good as Miss Zhu's.
I'm tired.
You've been busy all day too.
It's better to rest early.
Okay.
I'll take my leave.
You should rest early too.
I told you to rest properly
and don't cook by yourself.
Why didn't you listen?
How many days have I rested?
It's time to move my muscles a bit.
Alright.
Miss Zhu worked hard to cook.
I'll enjoy the food.
Wan'er.
Wan'er, you're here.
Yingtao,
add another pair of chopsticks.
Yes.
Your Grace.
You came just in time.
We can eat together.
These past few days,
I don't know what's wrong with them.
They just don't like my cooking.
I thought my cooking skills
were the problem.
You try it.
Thank you, Miss Zhu.
Try it and see how's the taste.
Okay.
The taste of this dish
tastes so strange.
How is it?
Miss Zhu,
this dish tastes great.
Look.
I told you my cooking skills are fine.
If it's delicious, eat more.
Heng, eat more.
Okay.
Heng.
Look,
I've been eating
the green dumplings made by Stone.
My health has improved a lot.
Can I
stop using that?
Of course not.
Your priority now
is to take care of your health.
But I'm already feeling much better.
Hurry up and eat more.
Your Grace.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you crying?
Why are you sitting on the floor?
Lian.
Tell me.
What should I do?
What should I really do?
Lian.
What should I do?
I really want to leave here.
Your Grace.
No matter where you go,
I will be with you.
But
after leaving here,
can you really let go of His Highness?
Now my time is almost up.
But don't worry.
About this tower
and this city,
I will keep my promise to you
and protect them well.
The dragon's blood you entrusted to me
will also dissipate
with my soul.
This Portal
will never be opened by anyone again.
But why didn't you fulfill
all the promises you made me?
We've agreed
to travel and enjoy the world together.
Now
I've trapped in this Lotus Tower alone
for 500 years.
Lotus,
do you want to see me again?
You've been lying to me.
I clearly got the prescription,
why can't I still make
Heaven and Earth in Spring?
Miss Ji,
what's wrong with you?
Disciple,
it's not about the prescription.
It's about the person.
I've said it before
only your junior brother
can make Heaven and Earth in Spring.
The hands.
It must be those hands.
It must be the hands.
I will chop off those hands.
He can't have what I don't have.
Miss Ji, calm down.
I've been in the martial world
for many years.
Maybe
I might help you fulfill your wish.
[Tablet of Master Min]
Stone.
If you lose your hands,
I'll see how you can surpass me.
[Pastry]
This should be the place.
Look.
Young boy,
His Highness asked us
to take the green dumplings.
Young boy.
[Residence of the Prince of Langya]
How are you, Stone?
Without my hands,
I can't make
Heaven and Earth in Spring anymore.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of everything.
I'll find a way
to make you get better.
Really?
Rest well
and relax.
I don't care what method you use,
you must get it done for me.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
Otherwise, I'll hold you accountable.
Everyone,
I have something to ask.
You can speak beast language?
You are Mr. Chang Qing?
It's me.
Mr. Chang Qing,
did you perhaps
find the way back home for us?
I...
I haven't found it yet.
I came
to ask for your help.
I wonder if you're willing.
Please speak, Mr. Chang.
I have a friend whose life is in danger.
Only...
Only by making your horn into medicine
can she survive.
Do you know
if I lose a horn, I will die?
My friend is in imminent danger.
If I don't save her,
I won't be able to get the Portal.
Take it, Mr. Chang.
Please keep your promise.
I lied.
Even if I save her,
I may still not be able to do it.
I'm sorry.
Father, Mother.
Help!
Brother!
Child.
Mother.
- Brother!
- Son!
Mother!
Bai Ze.
I promise you
I will take them home.
Take them home.
Go to Tianxiang Restaurant
to find Taotie
and open the Portal.
Eat.
Is it delicious?
Miss Zhu.
Mr. Chang,
please keep your promise.
Even if there's a glimmer of hope,
I'm willing to try.
I'm sorry.
♪Here's a flower for you♪
♪I don't know what to say
when we look at each other♪
♪Time goes by so quickly♪
♪My obsession leads to my fate♪
♪Destiny is confusing over the years♪
♪It feels bleak even with the light on♪
♪I see the shadow
when I almost forget you♪
♪A ray of light on my journey♪
♪It's like you're here
to pour out your heart♪
♪Although the memories of our love
bring us pain♪
♪All I ask for is to hold your hand
until the end of time♪
♪Selflessly♪
♪We taste the sorrows and joys♪
♪I'll never let you go
till death do us part♪