♪The autumn wind slips in,
never asking when I'll return♪
♪Before the mirror,
I comb my hair, lips parted just so♪
♪An old melody plays faintly,
perhaps the answer to this life♪
♪If fate leaves any trace at all♪
♪Wild geese disappear in the woods,
flowers wither at dusk♪
♪How cruel the moonlight flooding
the empty tower, wine growing cold♪
♪Long dreams and night rain
tearing through the heart of Luoyang♪
♪Who still rides forth
to keep a vow long left behind?♪
♪Paint the love and the hate♪
♪With gentle strokes of ink,
like a lone wild goose flying far away♪
♪Frost and snow to sketch memories,
drawn taut like a bow♪
♪One arrow dyed in deepest red♪
♪The bitter chill within my heart♪
♪The sorrow falling between your brows♪
♪Scalding memories lodged in my throat♪
♪Burning away the warmth we once shared♪
♪I would fade away
with the candle's shadow♪
♪Sever the ties and stay behind alone♪
♪Let you go♪
♪Your sorrow lingers as you glance back♪
♪This longing has already worn me thin♪
♪We once vowed to grow old together♪
♪But if fate bears no guilt, then why♪
♪Does it play this song of tears
for me alone?♪
=Destiny of Love=
(Adapted from Lin Nan's novel, Destiny of Love.)
=Episode 13=
(Little Ears?)
(Two little kids?)
(Why does that sound so familiar?)
Little Cloud, look.
Don't these look like
a pair of little ears?
They do! It's adorable!
This is my one-of-a-kind
bandaging technique.
(How does he know about my childhood?)
(Could it be...)
(If he really is that boy,)
(then he must know I'm not...)
Prince Yunnuo.
You came up with an interesting story.
Unfortunately, I'm too dull
to understand what it's trying to say.
It means
the little boy is me.
And the little girl...
I know.
She must be that sweet girl
you mentioned.
That's right.
That little girl
was you.
Me?
Prince Yunnuo, you must be joking.
I grew up in Xilin and never left.
How could I possibly be that girl?
I don't know exactly
where you grew up.
But I am certain
that the only person who knew
that special bandaging method
was the girl I met
when I escaped the palace as a child.
You don't have to worry.
I didn't expose you before,
and I won't in the future.
Prince Yunnuo.
Why are you doing this?
I know you're that girl
from back then.
So please, trust me.
Prince Yunnuo.
Honestly, I never meant
to take Princess Aliya's place
and marry Prince Jin.
It was all just
one big misunderstanding.
A single misstep led to a whole mess.
Thankfully,
I kept meeting people who helped me.
I had no choice but to go along with it.
I knew it.
You never wanted
to be Princess Consort Jin.
Don't worry.
You won't have
to keep going down this path.
I'll find a way to get you out of here.
Get out of here?
All right.
Prince Yunnuo.
Since we're on the same side,
I'd like to show you something.
Why don't you head back first?
I will see you later.
Very well.
Prince Yunnuo.
This is the Golden Box.
It's very important to me.
I have to open it.
Do you have any idea how to unlock
the cloud pattern on it?
The pattern looks
quite complicated.
I will help you figure it out.
Thank you.
(Benevolent and Kind)
Princess Consort Jin?
Princess Aliya of Xilin, right?
You're exactly who we're looking for.
Kill her.
Don't worry.
Leave this to me.
You healed Brother's legs.
Probably someone
wants to get rid of you.
From now on,
the danger will be hard to avoid.
I...
Believe me.
Today's attack
is just the beginning.
More people could get dragged into this.
You'd be better off leaving Brother.
Your Highness.
His Highness is asking to see you.
I am a bit tired.
Maybe tomorrow.
He said it's very important.
He needs to see you no matter what.
(There has been progress
with the cloud pattern.)
(It's time for me to leave.)
All right.
Tell him I'll be right there.
Understood.
Your Highness.
I'm sorry for being late.
It's fine.
Sit.
- There's something I need to...
- I have something to say...
Let me speak first.
I need to tell you the truth.
If you talk first,
it might be too late.
My leg injury
has been fake all along.
I never meant to lie to you.
I have faked it for over ten years
because the palace is too dangerous.
This was the only way
I could protect myself.
I'm sorry.
I hope you won't be angry.
You hid your strength
to escape from the world.
But you stood up for me.
How could I be angry?
Thank you.
Thank you
for everything.
Actually, I...
I have something to ask you.
Do you still mean
what you said before?
I always keep my word.
Then, please keep the promise
you made on our wedding day.
Let me go.
Neither of us wants this marriage.
But we have no choice
but to go through with it.
When the time is right,
I promise I'll find a way to let you go.
Let you go?
What do you mean by that?
You can repudiate me or divorce me.
Either is fine.
As long as you set me free.
All right.
You say you want to leave.
Then tell me, where will you go?
The world is wide.
Anywhere can be home.
But this is your home.
His Majesty ordered me
to cure your legs.
Now that you're healed,
I will go see His Majesty
and come up with a reason to leave.
No.
Your Highness...
I won't allow it.
I've already made up my mind.
You want to leave? Fine.
Father's birthday is coming soon.
It is highly inappropriate for you
to leave at a time like this.
I have thought of a compromise.
Stay until
the birthday celebration is over.
Once that is done,
I will speak to Father
about this matter.
Your Highness...
It is decided.
Good night.
(Benevolent and Kind)
What?
She plans to speak to my father.
Looks like she is set on leaving.
That can't be right.
From what I have seen between you two,
Her Highness doesn't seem like
she wants to leave at all.
This came way too suddenly.
Maybe I misunderstood.
Maybe she really doesn't like me.
No way.
You clearly like him.
So why were your words so harsh?
That's exactly why I said what I said.
I don't understand.
We agreed you'd
be honest with His Highness.
But instead,
you not only hid the truth,
you asked for a separation.
Your mind certainly works
in unusual ways.
Yuetao.
You know what?
It actually makes perfect sense.
I knew pretending to be
someone else was risky,
but I refused to believe it.
If I don't leave now,
I might end up
hurting both myself and others.
When you love someone,
you want what's best for them.
You don't knowingly let them
walk into danger.
What if he wants
to face that danger with you?
But I don't want him to.
He's Prince Jin of Luzhao.
He has a noble status
and great responsibilities.
He can't have a walking disaster like me
by his side.
But...
Why two people
who love each other can't be together?
Your Highness.
I have a perhaps naive guess.
Go on.
Could it be that Her Highness
thinks her identity
might bring trouble to you
by staying in the residence?
So what if it brings trouble?
I've already stood up for her.
I'll protect her no matter what.
Or does she think
I'm not capable of protecting her?
In that case, I'll prove her wrong.
How?
Based on what he said tonight,
I think I'll be leaving soon.
You mean...
- The birthday banquet.
(Hanyuan Hall)
What kind of gift
should I prepare
for His Majesty's birthday?
The birthday celebration?
Your Highness.
You don't have to put
so much effort into the gift.
His Majesty has never liked
any of your gifts
all these years anyway.
Mind your words!
Ridiculous!
I apologize.
How can someone as intelligent as me
end up with someone
as dumb as you serving me?
I've no idea how you've survived
all this time in the palace.
Your Highness.
Should we consult Prince Yunnuo?
I'd love to.
If only I could actually see him.
Who knows what he is busy with
all day?
I heard
ever since Prince Jin recovered,
Prince Yunnuo has been turned away
every time
he visited Prince Jin's Residence.
After a few failed attempts,
he just stopped coming out altogether.
It must be
because of Princess Consort Jin again.
But I heard
it was Prince Yunnuo
who kept going to see her.
That's only because
that temptress seduced my Yunnuo.
She cured Prince Jin's legs,
and she's even
taken over my role in organizing
His Majesty's birthday celebration!
Deliver a message
to Prince Yunnuo.
Tell him to focus on planning
the celebration for His Majesty.
No unwarranted outings.
I'll take care of everything else.
Yes, Your Highness.
(Liuyun Mansion)
Your Highness.
What is it?
Noble Consort has issued a decree.
You, Prince Jin,
and Princess Consort Jin
are to handle His Majesty's
birthday celebration with utmost care.
Got it.
Guihu.
Have you prepared
everything I asked for?
Your Highness.
The gifts for His Majesty have been...
I'm not talking about that.
I meant the cloud pattern mechanism.
I found a few leads.
Based on your description,
it sounds like
a Xilin cloud-pattern lock.
How do we unlock it?
I haven't found the method yet.
It was created decades ago,
exclusively for the royal family.
The craftsmanship
is incredibly intricate.
It has been lost for over a decade now.
There are very few clues remaining.
Keep looking into it.
Yes, Your Highness.
(Prince Jin's Residence)
At least eat something.
You have important business today.
You've to discuss the birthday banquet
with Prince Yunnuo.
It's fine.
Prince Yunnuo is on our side.
What about Prince Jin?
He'll be present too.
Please eat something.
Yuetao.
I'm full. Let's go.
Aliya.
Today's meeting will be
mentally draining.
You really should eat more.
Thank you for your concern.
I really am full.
I'll excuse myself.
Greetings,
Princess Consort Jin, and Brother.
I just finished breakfast
and was waiting for you.
You came at the right time.
Let's begin our discussion
about the birthday celebration.
Sure.
Come, Aliya.
Prince Yunnuo.
Follow me.
Let's move the banquet to start
at the hour of Wei.
One hour for greeting guests
is definitely not enough.
What do you think, Your Highness?
Agreed.
- One hour is short...
- Princess Consort Jin.
How about this change?
Let me see.
Here.
You removed the steamed duck slices?
We already have
the roasted stove-hung duck.
It might be too repetitive,
so I removed it.
What do you think?
Well, One's a side dish,
and the other is sliced on a platter.
They taste different.
Then we'll keep both.
Is there anything else
you need help with?
Well, what is this
"Eight Immortals with Mu Shu Pork"?
I'm not familiar with it.
It is a traditional folk dish.
Made with black fungus, eggs,
and cucumber.
Do you think Father
would like a dish like that?
I think so. He cares for his people.
I'm sure he'd enjoy
a humble commoner's dish.
Let's include it then.
All right.
We still need one more soup.
Soup...
How about abalone and sea cucumber soup?
(Abalone and Sea Cucumber Soup)
We already have that.
How about
the Refreshing Three-Ingredient
Shredded Soup?
Refreshing Three-Ingredient
That's a great idea!
(Refreshing Three-Ingredient
Shredded Soup)
Your handwriting
may be a little messy,
but it's kind of endearing.
- This...
- I think we should stop here.
You must be tired, Aliya.
Let's retire to our room.
I wasn't done writing!
Come on.
Let me go!
Let me go! What's your problem?
What's my problem?
What were you doing just now?
What did I do?
Do you seriously not understand
what you did?
The way you acted was completely
unbefitting of a princess consort.
Have I not always been like this?
That just proves
I haven't been strict enough with you,
which is why you acted
so disgracefully just now!
So now I embarrass you, is that it?
No matter.
You only have to endure a little longer.
Once Father's birthday is over,
I won't embarrass you any further.
I didn't mean it that way...
Your Highness.
Well?
Yuetao told me
Her Highness had already eaten.
She's currently working on preparations
for the birthday banquet.
Is she still upset?
I couldn't get a clear answer.
Then what took you so long?
Your Highness.
I think there was no need to even ask.
Her Highness is definitely upset.
You went too far
with your words.
But
was I
wrong?
Your Highness.
In my experience,
when it comes to feelings,
there's no such thing as right or wrong.
Moreover,
Her Highness and Prince Yunnuo
have always interacted like that.
Why were you so worked up today?
They've always interacted like that?
That close?
I should've guarded her
more closely from the start!
But
it was you who pushed her
toward Prince Yunnuo back then.
I didn't need that reminder.
You think I don't know what I did?
I regret it too, all right?
I just didn't have the courage
to tell her how I felt.
Your Highness.
I think you can't keep stalling.
You need to explain everything
to Her Highness
before the birthday celebration ends.
If you delay any longer,
you'll lose her for good.
Explain to her?
Will that really
make her stay?
You've got to try either way.
Let me think.
We're seeing Noble Consort tomorrow.
She always tries
to make things hard for her.
Then tomorrow,
I'll stay close
and protect her at all times.
What do you think?
Your Highness.
Are you asking me for my opinion?
Your
personal
guard?
Forget it.
Pretend I didn't say anything.
One really does make a mess of things
when one cares deeply.
(Benevolent and Kind)
Your Highness.
What brings you here?
I admit
I went too far yesterday.
It's fine.
You were already quite gentle about it.
I haven't behaved
like a proper princess consort.
I've already apologized to you.
Please don't be upset.
I am not upset.
We have to go see
Noble Consort soon.
It won't look good if we're late.
We should leave now.
Is she not
bothered by this at all?
Does that mean she doesn't care
about our argument at all?
Her Highness
is magnanimous indeed.
But she didn't used to be like this.
(Hanyuan Hall)
You're early, Yunnuo,
as always.
And you're right on time,
You're all here.
- Your Highness.
- Mother.
If His Majesty's
birthday celebration goes well,
then I will be well.
Your Highness is right.
Your Highness, here is the detailed list
I put together overnight
(Guest List for the Birthday Banquet)
for the preparations.
Please take a look.
Princess Consort Jin.
His Majesty's birthday may be
a celebration with his subjects,
but your guest list is far too long.
What if His Majesty is exhausted
after all those formal greetings?
That...
And what is this?
3,000 in spending?
His Majesty has always valued frugality.
This is far
too extravagant.
Your Highness, I...
Let me take another look.
Silk drapery decorations.
Too much.
Blessing dance.
Gaudy.
Various opera performances.
Too noisy.
From where I stand,
none of this is appropriate.
Your Highness.
I think it is excellent.
What did you say, Prince Jin?
I said I think it is excellent.
First of all,
she referenced your guest lists
from past years.
And this year's guest count is less.
Secondly,
my father values simplicity,
but this is not a family banquet.
I believe 3,000 is just
the right amount to spend.
As for the silk drapes,
the opera performances, and the dance...
If you knew my father
as well as Aliya does,
you'd know that these touches
suit my father's preferences quite well.
You...
There's no need to defend Her Highness.
She has her own ideas.
Your Highness.
This is my first time organizing
my father's birthday celebration.
Oversights are inevitable.
I appreciate your guidance
and will keep it in mind.
Once I return,
I'll review everything
and revise the plan
based on your past arrangements.
Based on my past arrangements?
That will not do.
His Majesty entrusted
this year's celebration to you all
for a reason.
He wants a surprise.
If it ends up the same
as every other year, he'd be displeased.
Mother.
Actually, I helped with the entire list
you just reviewed.
Truly?
Then I must say,
some of the arrangements
are quite fitting.
The silk drapery adds
a lovely splash of color.
The blessing dance
is festive and auspicious.
And the opera performances are...
Very lively.
Yes! With several performances going
at once, it'll be quite the spectacle.
Well done, Yunnuo.
Mother.
The truth is, it was
all Princess Consort Jin's idea.
That matters little.
What matters is
that this birthday celebration
must outshine everyone before it.
Princess Consort Jin.
I'm giving you seven more days.
At the end of that time,
I want a real surprise.
Your Highness.
Seven days is far too short a time.
You think so too?
Your Highness.
I will do my best.
Excellent.
It's settled, then.
I'll see you in seven days.
If you need anything,
just come to me.
Thank you.
Guanguan?
Guanguan!
You can't eat that!
You'll get poisoned if you eat that.
Don't eat it again.
Aliya.
Aliya!
Do you hate me that much?
You see me and immediately turn around.
It's not that I hate you.
I just have
no intention of arguing with you.
No intention of arguing?
Then why does everything you do
feel like you're starting a fight?
♪The clouds stretch endlessly
across the sky♪
This is all my fault.
I'll be going now.
♪Looking down at eyes
that gaze into the distance♪
You're overstepping, Your Highness.
That is nothing for a married couple.
But we won't be husband and wife
for much longer.
Soon,
we'll be nothing more than strangers.
♪It's more than
just the courage to yearn♪
♪It's destined that we cannot be close♪
♪Loving you is a secret♪
♪Afraid of disturbing you
and then you'd distance yourself♪
♪Endlessly♪
♪How I wish I could dive into the sea♪
♪And gently rest♪
♪Don't forget the love
they could never have♪
Your Highness.
Did you find out
what you wanted to know?
Do you know
cats can't eat luoying grass?
Of course.
Cats get poisoned if they eat it.
But I saw it eating just now,
and I didn't stop it.
Why?
It likes it,
so I let it eat.
If it gets poisoned,
I'll do everything I can to cure it.
It's its favorite, after all.
Your Highness.
This is about you and Her Highness,
isn't it?
Do you love her that much?
Then there's an easy solution.
We've got two Resurrection Pills now.
Just tell her
you've already known who she really is.
Then the two of you
take the pills together.
Problem solved!
But luoying grass doesn't move.
If it could,
it would run far away from the cat
that keeps nibbling at it.
She just wants to stay away from me.
I think you went too far today.
Even I can tell
His Highness genuinely likes you.
You're aware of that too.
You like him.
He likes you.
Just tell him
who you really are.
What's on your mind?
Say something.
What do you really want?
I want him to stay away from me.
That way, no matter what happens to me,
he won't be dragged into it.
But you really like him.
That's exactly
why I have to stay away from him.
(Benevolent and Kind)
(Liuyun Mansion)
Prince Yunnuo.
You asked me to come alone.
Do you have a lead on the mechanism?
Not yet.
I wanted to ask
if you've thought more
about what I said last time.
I've already brought up
the separation with Prince Jin.
Good.
That's good.
When do you plan to leave?
I promised Prince Jin
I'd leave after Father's
birthday celebration.
All right.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of everything
after you leave his residence.
That's all right.
I can take care of myself.
You don't have to be so polite
to me.
Prince Yunnuo.
You kept my identity a secret,
helped me out of tight spots,
and even looked
into the cloud pattern for me.
I have no way to repay you.
Then,
does our promise still stand?
That was just childish talk.
What if
I was serious?
Let's go see taller mountains,
and visit farther places, together.
Then I'll take it as a joke
you meant sincerely.
I still have things to do.
Please excuse me.
Your Highness.
Everything you ordered
for His Majesty's birthday celebration
is ready.
This time,
we will take Prince Jin down for good.
I didn't ask you to act on your own.
What?
Your Highness.
We must not act out of sentimentality.
If we let this chance slip,
the consequences could be unfathomable.
She'll leave his residence
after the celebration.
I will have no more need
for this kind of opportunity.
I don't want anything that will put her
in harm's way.
Your Highness...
Understood.
Your Highness.
I went to see Prince Yunnuo
about some personal matters today.
I...
See whoever you want.
We won't be tied together
much longer anyway.
Your Highness?
Your Highness!
That wasn't the plan!
Weren't you going
to explain everything tonight?
Forget it.
No matter how hard I try,
I can't make her stay.
If she no longer wishes to be here,
I'll let her go.
(Aliya,)
(you went all out for just one coin.)
(It's still money.)
(I never take advantage of others,
however small.)
This is yours.
♪The clouds stretch endlessly
across the sky♪
♪Looking down at eyes
that gaze into the distance♪
♪Time keeps moving on♪
♪Whose footprints are left behind?♪
♪It's more than
just the courage to yearn♪
♪It's destined that we cannot be close♪
♪Loving you is a secret♪
♪Afraid of disturbing you
and then you'd distance yourself♪
♪Endlessly♪
♪How I wish I could dive into the sea♪
♪And gently rest♪
♪It's to soothe the reason
for your heart's pain♪
♪If everything could overcome
all barriers and fall in love♪
♪Even the cloud and sea
could be together♪
♪Forget how far from shore
and how dangerous it is♪
♪We can't see♪
♪If distance can't tear us apart
and it's not hard to endure♪
♪Our tears will stay together♪
♪Don’t forget the love♪
♪They could never have♪