Why did my sister die?
You were right by her side!
Although our reasons were different,
I would have joined Madoka in pressing that death button long ago.
Even successful people have plenty of fucked up stuff going on.
Seriously, life isn't worth shit.
The world's ending?
That just means I finally get my happily ever after.
What's happier?
Dying while believing in a miracle,
or while not believing in it?
You can't sleep?
No.
Ritsu...
I'm sorry.
It's your time to shine.
[The End Of The World With You]
I've always been exceptional at anything I tried my hand.
[Episode 7: Entwining Gaze, Tangled Heat]
I heard I was both quick to walk and talk.
- I'm home.
- Welcome back, Ritsu.
Here, this is from your grandmother.
Remember the essay competition you won?
Well, she had nothing but praise to say about you!
Isn't that wonderful?
Now let's get you a snack.
I'll be right back.
Whenever I was praised,
my ostracized mother smiled a lot.
So?
What did you need, Father?
Ritsu...
Could you give up going to Tokyo University?
[T/N : The most prestigious university in Japan]
Why? I was already accepted.
See, Akio... your stepbrother, that is, applied last year, and failed.
My wife begged me. She said she didn't want to upset him.
I'll back you financially.
Leave your tuition and living expenses to me.
Deal?
Yes, sir.
Alright.
- Sorry about that.
- Everyone of them was egoist.
Hell, even I was the result of forbidden love.
Your longest relationship lasted for half a year?
Yes.
And this relationship was with a man?
The fact you've saved his pictures must mean you're still smitten.
I'm right, aren't I?
Well... I guess so.
Still, he's not what I expected.
He's sort of... plain?
I mean, you've charmed idols and reporters alike.
But he's the one?
Is that so unexpected?
See, if you look closely,
he's pretty cute, you know?
Why did you two break up anyway?
Why?
Because I cheated on him.
Seriously?
You're the worst.
I'd have to agree.
I know! You should try contacting him.
What ?
Hey, why not?
It sounds fun.
No, thanks.
Besides, I think he hates me.
You never know.
You're right, but he changed his number.
How about social media?
Is he active online?
"Masumi Nishina"...
Right. Who would use their real name?
[Hashimoto Yosuke]
[START TELEGRAM: One new message]
Of course not.
[Could you tell me Nishina's number?]
Do you even know what he was like after your breakup?
He completely broke down, both physically and mentally.
Ultimately, he repeated a year, and couldn't find a job.
When he finally did, the working conditions broke him again.
It was hard seeing him like that, man.
I'm sure you're the last guy he wants to remember.
Please, just leave him alone.
Who would have thought...
you'd still be in that apartment.
I should have visited sooner.
Sorry, I'm going on ahead.
Spit that out.
Spit that out!
Do you hear me?
You damn fool!
Masumi...
What do you mean, you're "going ahead"?
Answer me!
Take responsibility, damn it!
Listen to me.
Die.
Just go die!
Die!
Calm down, okay?
Shut up!
Act like you care all you want.
I'm sure you don't give a damn about me!
Answer me!
You never considered what would happen to me...
if you disappeared, did you?
Shit!
Damn it...!
I'm sorry.
I really am.
No need to worry about gas anymore!
Don't go too fast.
I know!
Be careful, OK?
Hey, tell me if you get tired.
No, I'll be fine.
Masumi, yesterday... Well...
I'll turn a blind eye to it.
For now, let's focus on getting to Matsumoto.
OK.
I made the wrong move yesterday.
My head wasn't in a good space.
Meguru, are you okay?
I'm fine.
And you, Ritsu?
I'm alright.
We only have three days left.
- Too bad, but they're useless now.
- Yes.
Let's go.
I should have just persevered.
After all, I'm the one responsible for dragging him out here.
Oh god...
It's way too hot today.
Make sure you hydrate, Masumi.
You too.
No, I'll manage.
Like hell you will. You're sweating a lot.
Drink up, alright?
Thanks.
Hey, do you two have any water left?
No, both our bottles are empty.
If we can't find water, we're screwed.
Yes.
Hey!
What's that?
Excuse me sir, is this water safe to drink?
Of course.
It comes from a hidden spring only locals know about.
We're really grateful for it, since there's no more running water.
This is the stuff.
- It's so cold and delicious.
- Right?
There's also a river up ahead. Perfect for a quick dip.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- Let's stop by!
- Sure, sounds like a good idea.
Be careful.
But it feels great!
Come join me, Meguru!
Will you manage?
Yes.
It's pretty swollen.
Nothing we can do about that.
I'll be fine, really.
Can you stand?
Yes.
The water is cold for sure.
Masumi, watch where you step.
If only this were a hot spring.
Agreed.
You'll be fine! I promise.
This place is tingling with negative ions.
I haven't heard anyone say "negative ion" in a while.
Really?
I mean, it's all pseudoscience, right?
Hey, no need to be a hard-ass.
I'm just trying to say this place feels refreshing.
My bad.
This is all so weird.
Weird how?
Just look at me. I'm sitting in a river, in my boxers.
It would have been absurd to me ten days ago.
For one, I never even wanted to partake in outdoor activities.
You have a point there.
Every day, I had a routine of going to and from work.
My days off were spent drinking at home,
watching stupid videos,
and playing mobile games.
Who knew the great outdoors could be so beautiful?
And it wasn't even that far from home.
I should have ventured out a bit more.
Masumi.
That's exactly why...
I'm grateful for what you did.
Yuma and Meguru...
are both people I would never have met if I hadn't accompanied you.
After all, I never expanded my social circle after graduating.
So...
I sort of feel like I've wasted my life.
If I had had the courage,
I could have seen so much more, you know?
Not like there's any use having regrets now.
Ritsu, could you help me up?
What a sight to see before dying.
This might not be the end.
I...
still want to explore the world with you.
I still have plenty things I want to see...
and do.
So I have a request.
Would you please...
fall in love with me again?
Damn, you look terrible.
Didn't you say...
you could easily tell who's in love with you?
Wasn't that refreshing?
Sure was.
Isn't that...
Oh... I guess they're like "that"?
For real?
Let's just pretend we didn't see that, okay?
Y-Yes.
♫ Our shadows come close, as if reminiscing ♫
♫ I stopped, unable to touch your cheek ♫
♫ I'll no longer regret ♫
♫  those days long past ♫
[September 22nd, 2023 / 1:00PM] [Kagami]
♫ For I'll always remember them ♫
Coming.
♫ Do not disappear, do not waver ♫
M-Madoka?
- Mother-
- Dear!
- Madoka is...
- Mother!
- Hold on!
I can't blame their reaction.
Neither can I.
Thank you for bringing Meguru home.
Of course.
Our apologies it took us this long.
[Posthumous Buddhist name]
We were suddenly faced with the reality of death.
♫ Do not disappear, do not waver ♫
♫ Let’s burn as we might, heartrending as it may be ♫
♫ Yet being with you  ♫
♫ This very moment is my everything ♫