(The characters, groups, background, events, etc. of this play
This is purely fictitious, please be informed)
No. 5802, Unique City
It is the only connection between the three victims.
The last owner of this house was Lee Mi-young
The previous owner was Jiang Zhimu
The first owner of this house was Do Run-su
When Du Runxiu first started selling the unique city
Purchased 13 houses
No. 5802 is one of the 13 households.
Currently, the remaining 12 households are under the name of his family.
Why did he give this house to Jiang Zhimu?
Where exactly does this story begin?
Blood Puzzle
Jiang Zhimu and Li Meiying are in a relationship of marriage
It is normal to transfer the house
But Du Runxiu transferred the house to Jiang Zhimu
There must be a reason.
Is it because of vested interests?
No. 5802, Unique City
No lawsuits or accidents involved
The strange thing is that they all completed the transfer in a short period of time
After Du Runxiu bought the house
Transfer to Jiang Zhimu within two months
The house was transferred to Lee Mi-young within a month.
As if it was agreed
What kind of agreement would allow them to transfer the house?
Yoon Dong-hoon, Lee Mi-young, Kang Ji-mok
You said that the three of them might be the criminals.
Rather than the victim
If Do Run-su is included
The four of them committed a crime together
The reward for crime is to make three other people
How about getting the unique city number 5802?
But why only my uncle?
Not getting paid?
Why didn't this matter have anything to do with him?
He was the victim in the first case.
There must be a reason.
The intersection should be Han River Police Station
The only city is within the jurisdiction of the Han River Police Station
Chief Police Officer Yoon Dong-hoon
Served as the Chief of Han River Police Station for one year
Is it Chief Police Officer Yoon Dong-hoon?
Covering up the case related to the One City?
He covered up a crime.
If it's to help cover up a crime
He should be paid more generously.
What was my uncle paid for?
A case involving four people.
Do Yoon-soo's Jigsaw Puzzle
There is a clown
Trampling the sand castles built by the children
Jiang Zhimu's is someone dancing with armbands
Lee Mi-young's is someone whispering to someone
Chief Police Officer Yoon Dong-hoon's Jigsaw Puzzle
Someone shot at the doll.
These pictures on the puzzle
Can it correspond to any criminal behavior?
I think...
My head hurts
I need a cup of coffee, do you want some?
I want hot latte
Switch to oat milk and add two parts condensed
I said my head hurts, what do you mean?
I'll order takeout.
No thanks, there's a nice cafe up ahead
Let's go out for a walk.
I want to take a walk
- Welcome
- Hello
I want a cup of hand-brewed coffee
And a latte, hot latte, and...
Switch to oat milk
And add two parts of concentrated
good
A cup of hot hand-brewed coffee
A hot latte for oat milk
Two portions of concentrate, right?
Sorry for bothering you
Why did you turn off the light?
Because you snore loudly
I don't snore.
You should help me put on some clothes at a time like this
There's a reason you've been single for ten years.
You don't understand women
I even ran errands to buy you coffee.
You actually said this
The room temperature is 27 degrees Celsius now.
Some people sweat.
The coffee here is delicious
So sleepy
Shall we go out for a walk?
Very sweet
You came here early in the morning.
It's definitely not to buy me coffee.
What do you want?
Chief Police Officer Yun Dong-hoon
What kind of policeman is he?
Dongxun? Why are you asking about him?
I know he's someone you admire.
There are many things I am curious about.
Including his murder
But what you said
That sounds weird.
You sound like
It seems that Dongxun died because he made a mistake.
(Yin Yiluo, calling)
After all, human hearts are unpredictable.
The human heart is unpredictable?
Jin Hanquan, your true nature is revealed again
Just like when you asked me
Do I have that?
Isn't there? Brat
What kind of person is Brother Dongxun?
He's a different kind of policeman.
After all, he is the youngest director.
The superior must like him very much.
Of course I like it
He is very good at handling cases and has the demeanor of a police officer.
So why did he resign?
Rather than saying he resigned
It's better to say that he was kicked out in order to calm public opinion.
The area was in chaos at the time.
Hey, you know it too
Central Japan Serial Murder Case
Every Monday when it rains, someone gets killed
Stockings on the face
That case happened within the jurisdiction of the Han River Police Station.
Until three female students died
We found out it was the same criminal.
Five people died in the end
At that time, things were in turmoil
Dongxun will be kicked out
His ending was terrible.
Are we going to talk about the place that can make you fall asleep today?
Do you still want to keep it a secret?
It's not really a big secret.
But there's nothing to say
I had already said it.
I have thought about
The reason you can sleep in such a dirty place
Well, there is a behavior called hoarding disorder
Once you own something, you can't throw it away
That is also considered a mental illness
What kind of person is he?
Let’s talk about my uncle today.
I used to think
Maybe my uncle
Not the kind of person I know.
After all, we can't satisfy everyone.
How could you think that?
Last time you asked me
Trying to follow my uncle's choice
I'm going to do what you said now.
actually
I chose to turn a blind eye
Because I don't know what to see
Something pops up
Because I'm scared
sometimes
People feel tired just by keeping their eyes open.
You are like me
Are there things you want to ignore?
Of course, I am human too.
What's the matter?
My privacy is also a secret
(Second Consultation Room)
Hello
My friend
Work Here
This is the only police-designated hospital nearby.
yes
Did you see Lee Mi-young's car on the day of the incident?
right
The reason I remember...
Because of the Porsche Panamera
It's my dream car.
So I will pay attention to it when I meet it on the road
But she stepped on the accelerator at a red light
She knew the police were watching
It was nearly 10pm and there were no cars on the road.
So I didn't follow.
If I had stopped that car...
If I did that
Maybe that wouldn't happen.
This has always bothered me.
Why do you think she was under the police's nose?
What if you violate the rules by running a red light and stepping on the accelerator to the floor?
What?
That's right
She ran the red light on purpose.
Lee Mi-young saw the patrol car
I tried my best to send out a distress signal.
Do you remember anything else?
Or did you see anything?
Especially the back seat of the car
No
Because the window film is very black
Anyway, thank you
Even if you stopped the car
The result will not change
It may take you a long time to overcome
But don't feel too guilty.
（Document Library）
I'm behind you
Why don't you answer the phone every time?
You're so embarrassed to say that to me
Then why didn't you answer the phone before?
I can't win you at all
I just went to see Senior Tai Dongshu
you
How well do you know your uncle?
I thought he stopped being a cop because of me.
My uncle, a respected policeman
What case was covered up?
After all, human hearts are unpredictable.
The crimes he covered up and the cases he shielded
Maybe not a few
But can you do it?
Can you face those cases?
Can you serve as Yin Yiluo's regular guard?
Analyzing cases as a criminal profiler?
I have to do that.
No, I'm asking if you can do it.
Um
Then find it
Find those who have been shot, deceived by whispers
Trampled by the power of the armband
And the people whose sand castles were destroyed
Right?
What's the matter?
How is Han River Police Station?
Why are you asking this out of nowhere?
A junior guy
How dare you be so rude to your seniors?
Hanquan came to see me
(Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency)
He asked me about Dongxun
It’s not the first day that guy has been like this, what’s wrong?
What's bothering you?
You showed me before
Criminal profile report written by Yi Luo
Say
Why do you think Dongxun died?
This is it
(The Mingcheng Daily defamation lawsuit)
The victim's family members reported to Mingcheng Daily
and the journalist responsible filed a defamation lawsuit
The case was closed after three months with no suspicion
The plaintiff is the Central Region serial murder case
The brother of the last victim
This case happened to be the case of Chief Police Officer Yoon Dong-hoon
Reasons for quitting the police job
So this defamation case
This must be the last case he covered up.
Let's investigate this defamation case first.
If our reasoning is correct
That should be it.
Because Chief Detective Yoon Dong-hoon covered up the case
The victim whose life was ruined is killing people
The other party is the victim
He is also the culprit in the Jigsaw murder case.
- Let's go
- etc
I have something to tell you
handkerchief?
It was just an ordinary, old handkerchief
The kind that old men would use
Cui Suanyou, who arrived at the scene first, saw
Then it disappeared
Scene photos and evidence list
There's no handkerchief either.
Only I, Cui Suan and Team Leader Liang know about this
maybe
The perpetrators or accomplices are among us
But why are you saying it now?
Please, that's because you...
Do you believe them?
- What?
- Do you believe in Cui Suan?
Of course I believe
Where is Liang Zhenghu?
Anyone in the Han River Police Station could be the criminal
You can even doubt me
But the criminal is definitely not Zheng Huge
Can you do it?
What can be done?
Can you look them in the face?
Can you serve as a normal Jin Hanquan guard?
Investigating as a criminal police officer?
You need to change your career.
Don't you understand me yet?
What? Are you going to take off your hat and get mad again?
I say again, don't take your hat off in front of me
Don't learn from me
That's my sister.
Ahn Mi Sun
She is the suspect in the serial murder case in central Seoul.
The last victim
It's been 20 years
Why are the police coming to me now?
We fully understand your feelings
You must feel aggrieved and angry.
Is that why you filed a lawsuit?
Of course
If they had
Catch that lunatic in time, I...
My sister
I wouldn't have died at the age of 25.
And that bastard from Mingcheng Daily
Spreading rumors that my sister is a KTV hostess
She is not a KTV hostess
That day was her birthday
She went to KTV with her friends
She was going home
I'm really angry
How could he not confirm the facts?
Just write a report about the victim?
That's why I filed a defamation lawsuit.
Those guys at Hangang Police Department are covering up the case.
Makes me angry
That person died.
You mean Director Yoon Dong-hoon?
Is Director Yoon Dong-hoon dead too?
Otherwise, who else died?
The reporter from Mingcheng Daily
The reporter died?
Yes, he committed suicide.
Lee Gang Hyun
I haven't even forgotten the name of that unscrupulous reporter
By Lee Gang-hyun, reporter
Was it really suicide?
Let's confirm it.
He said Li Gangxuan lives in Mudong, wait for me
(Dialing, Senior Sun Renhuan)
Hello?
- Senior, how are you doing? I am Hanquan
- Oh, Hanquan
- Are you still at Yangxi Police Station?
- Of course
(Lee Gang-hyun murder case)
What else interests you?
This was a case ten years ago.
I can't say I showed it to you.
Okay, thank you, senior.
You can enjoy this with your team members.
It's really rare
You go
OK, I'm leaving.
(Lee Gang-hyun murder case)
Give me
(Wu Zhejin)
Wu Zhejin?
- Yin Yiluo
- Um?
This is Chief Police Officer Yoon Dong-hoon
Eight months before the murder
My uncle's death is not the first case
Lee Gang Hyun's murder case is the first case
How come I never thought of that?
I found it weird at first.
Even the murderer who killed as many as 21 people
On first offense
Also because of leaving a folding knife at the scene
And run back to get
It is impossible for people to start from
A perfect murder
It is inevitable that criminals will make low-level mistakes
Or leave clues at the scene
But for the first murder
The scene where my uncle died was too perfect
There was no one left at the scene
Fingerprints or DNA, why?
Because this is not the first time the criminal has committed a crime
Lee Gang Hyun's murder case is the first case
This means that we may
Can we find evidence in the murder case of Li Gangxuan?
I will meet with the detective in charge tomorrow.
Find the puzzle first.
I will ask the Yangxi Police Department for assistance.
No. 5802, Unique City
Jurisdiction of Hangang Police Station
And Lee Gang Hyun
(Reporter Li Gangxuan)
(Illegal demonstrations that obstruct innocent citizens)
(Hanjiang District urban renewal project finally started)
(Seoul Han River Police Station)
(Annual leave application form)
Why do you suddenly want to take annual leave?
The suspect in Do Yoon-soo's murder case has not been found yet.
Do you still remember Guard Yin Yiluo?
A criminal profile report?
I'm working with her on the Jigsaw murder case.
(Serious Case Team 2)
(Lee Mi-young murder report)
(Analysis of the correlation between Yin Dongxun's murder case)
Not only Yoon Dong-hoon and Lee Mi-young
There are also Jiang Zhimu and Du Runxiu
All deaths are related.
But the criminal who killed Jiang Zhimu has been arrested.
But the puzzle was sent to me later.
He seemed to be the criminal's target.
Who else knows about this?
I'm just telling you first
There are still puzzles that have not been confirmed
As soon as I find it, I'll make it public.
This case is too serious.
but
I don't know yet
Who among us took the handkerchief?
Would it be too hasty to make the case public like this?
And most importantly
Yin Yiluo Guard
I once asked you if she could be trusted.
Do you know everything about Yin Yiluo?
How many things do you know?
What does that mean?
You're asking like this, I guess you don't know
Go ask Yin Yiluo yourself.
Also, I will not accept your annual leave application
After all, you are investigating the murder case of Du Runxiu.
You don't need to come to work for the time being, just continue your investigation
But if you find anything, report it to me immediately.
(Director Xuan Haojin, calling)
Sit down
I'll stand and listen.
good
You don't even have the right to sit down.
You can't even catch the murderer of Du Runxiu.
Still busy investigating ten years ago
The case of Yangxi Police Station?
Are you free?
What are you thinking about?
Explain clearly so I can understand
I can't tell you yet
What?
Should I report this to my superiors?
Why is it you who decides?
Say it
I think the murder of Do Yoon Soo
It's related to the murder of Li Gangxuan ten years ago
And also with Lee Mi-young, Jiang Zhimu
It's related to the murder of Chief Police Officer Yoon Dong-hoon
I also think that the center of all this may be
Our Han River Police Station
What is the clue?
What made you think that?
I'll find it out
Hey, stinky guy
Then you should find it first and then tell me this.
I will go find it
Those boxes contain evidence from early 2010.
I'm not sure if there is one. Please look for it.
good
- Lee Gang Hyun murder case?
- right
yes
The case ended in suicide.
But I actually feel something is wrong
He died in a plastic bag
I think it's a bit strange
People who want to commit suicide don't usually do it that way.
Why wasn't a facial autopsy conducted at that time?
It’s not that we don’t test, but that we can’t test.
His family members strongly opposed
Lee Gang Hyun
After divorcing his wife
He lived with his son for a long time.
He suffers from severe depression
So I can't live without alcohol and sleeping pills
The day before the incident
He told his best friend that raising a child alone is tiring
He also said he wanted to die
Suicide motives are very strong
Senior, do you still remember
Was that the puzzle piece that was at the crime scene?
puzzle?
Found it
I remember
Strangely enough, there is a puzzle piece
Neatly placed next to the corpse
Like someone put it there on purpose
Although I was investigating the case
Often find a variety of things
But Lee Gang Hyun's son said that it was not his property
I was wondering why there was a puzzle
How to say it?
The picture above
Makes people feel very uncomfortable
What happened to that picture?
It shows a man holding a camera.
His eyes are funny.
It was sewn together with something like thread.
That picture is weird.
Looks like a child's drawing
It looks like an adult's painting.
Do you remember anyone at the time of the incident?
Or do you feel something is strange?
Let me think
The person who knows the case best?
Aren't you affiliated with the Han River Police Station?
- right
- Then you should know Liang Zhenghu
Yes, we are in the same group.
He's so close to you.
Zheng Hu should be the person who knows this case best.
What? What does that mean?
Liang Zhenghu was originally in charge of this case.
But he was suddenly transferred to the investigation headquarters of the headquarters
That's why the case was handed over to me.
In fact, the cases are all investigated by the Zhenghu
I just followed my superior's instructions to close the case.
Oh, but it was much better then.
Don't quit your job as a police officer.
This society is more difficult than imagined
Are you really talking about the Han River Police Station?
Is this Chief Inspector Liang Zhenghu, the leader of the Serious Crime Unit 2?
right
Did you find anything?
In the surveillance camera near the scene where Do Yoon-soo died
I finally got the back door of Kaineng Building
Beer house surveillance camera images
Didn't they say that was broken?
The store owner was unwilling to cooperate because it was too much trouble, so he lied.
I threatened to shut down the store.
They told the truth
Did you capture anything?
I didn't capture any special footage.
As you can see, the quality is terrible.
I heard you told Jin Hanquan
The disappearance of the handkerchief at the crime scene
In addition to the handkerchief
Do you remember anything else?
For example, someone who was behaving strangely at the time
Because the scene was a mess.
That's all I told Guard Kim.
So what should I do now?
How could the handkerchief disappear?
(Jin Hanquan: Team leader, I have something to report)
How can you drink in broad daylight?
It's working time now
You are here
What do you want to report?
elder brother
Do you know when I think you are the most handsome?
You go to the orphanage every month.
Being a volunteer is really cool.
But you grew up there.
So it's normal to do this.
What are you talking about? Report first.
before
When you first became the team leader
You said you had to go to the victim's funeral
I also asked why you went there
Do You Recall?
This is how you answered me
You said you were going to apologize
You said the criminal police's duty is to protect the people
But you couldn't do it
And you have to promise that you will catch the criminal.
I felt
You are the most handsome
I think solving cases is fun.
Because I like mystery novels and detective movies
That's why I became a policeman.
But your starting point is different
I've never seen a police officer with such a strong sense of mission as you.
I thought
"People like you should be police officers"
Because you are a very warm person
Because Liang Zhenghu is justice in the world
I really thought so.
That's why I call you Batman.
What exactly do you want to say?
But why didn't you tell me?
You are the detective in charge of the Lee Gang Hyun murder case
A puzzle piece appeared in that case
That was the first Jigsaw murder.
You obviously know everything, why didn't you tell me?
Did you take the handkerchief?
Hanquan
Is that you?
Why would I do that?
Otherwise I can't explain why you didn't tell me
Why do you think I didn't tell you?
I have no idea
I asked you before
Do you know Yin Yiluo well?
How much do you know?
Mokdong Apartment 212
That is the resident number where Lee Gang Hyun died.
That day
Do you know who is at No. 314, the floor above his house?
Lee Gang Hyun's son, Lee Sun Wook
And his son's friends
Jo Seul-gi, Oh Young-hoon
And Yin Yiluo
It was winter vacation.
They are at the home of a friend of Li Gangxuan's son
Group Math Tutoring
Classes are from 9pm to midnight
Monitor screen display
At 12:05 a.m. they all went home.
But there is no sign of Yin Yiluo
Why?
She claimed she was unwell
I went home early at 11pm
But Yin Yiluo did not leave the apartment at that time.
The time she was caught on camera
It was one hour later at 12:23 am
Lee Gang Hyun's death date
It is estimated to be between 10 pm and midnight.
On the day of the incident, only Yin Yiluo
The alibi is unclear
But I can't see her
Because Chief Inspector Yoon Dong-hoon stopped me
According to Chief Police Officer Yun Dong-hoon
That day, Yin Yiluo was in a bad mood and went to the top floor.
Then stay there until the tutoring is over.
Do you think this makes sense?
I also want to continue investigating the murder of Lee Gang Hyun
But I was suddenly transferred to the Investigation Headquarters of the General Office.
Then eight months later
Chief Police Officer Yoon Dong-hoon was murdered
Same
Yin Yi-ra's alibi is not clear
Can you still trust Yin Yiluo in this case?
That's why I can't tell you
As long as we find the accomplices hidden among us
The truth will come out then.
Lee Gang Hyun's residence is No. 212
Ten years ago that day
The place where I have a tutor is No. 314
Hey, damn, aren’t we all chaebols?
I don't have much money.
They can't do this to me, can they? Damn it.
Hello
Damn, I can reveal more explosive news
Damn, even if they say I'm a has-been reporter
But you know me damn well, right?
I'm Lee Gang Hyun, damn it
As long as I make up my fucking mind and turn over a new leaf
If they start writing news again, they will all be doomed
Damn it, I'm not going to die on my own, get it?
Stop laughing, go to hell
Hello
I'll show no mercy, damn it
Did you hear that?
8:55pm, five minutes before the tutoring session starts
Nothing unusual happened that day.
Zhejin, I always talk to you about money
I really feel sorry
But please say a few good words for me.
What?
If I knew it would turn out like this
Of course I won't sell it, damn it.
Just help me once.
Hey, just once!
Hey, when we had our glory days together
But it can be a relationship of life and death
We are like comrades on the battlefield, hey...
Hello?
"Glory Days"
What I saw at that time
This is the last sight of Lee Gang Hyun
We have learned that the variance is npq, and q is equal to 1 minus p
Okay, take the positive square root of
The standard deviation is obtained
Then let’s look at the topic
What is the mean and standard deviation of 2x minus 5?
How do you write the average of 2x minus 5?
To write 2x minus 5
But it can be rewritten as twice 2e times x minus 5
So what is the result?
If we move 5 over...
Because I was feeling depressed during the tutoring class
So I went to the top floor
If my memory serves me right, by then
Nothing special happened
It was very cold that day
What music am I listening to?
That was the music I often listened to when I was in high school.
Then I saw someone
Enter the apartment from the main entrance
Who is it?
That was the first time the criminal killed someone.
The killing method is almost perfect
The first time you commit a crime, you should be nervous.
But the criminal did not make a stupid mistake.
Or leave clues at the scene
The only thing that can fail for a prisoner is
The puzzle didn't get attention.
If you clear out the shochu bottles and sleeping pills
The case would not be covered up as suicide.
Looks like a perfect crime.
That was the criminal's mistake.
I?
Liang Zhenghu asked you if the prisoner was me?
Why would he doubt me?
Wood Cave Apartment 314
What were you doing when Lee Gang Hyun died?
That day
I'm on the top floor
I really don't want to read
If I go home, my uncle will definitely complain about me.
So I just spent my time on the top floor
Don't you believe me 100%?
When you are in the document library
Why didn’t you say you knew Lee Gang Hyun?
You must know your friend's father.
How could I not know?
You didn't tell me about the handkerchief.
- What nonsense? I told you about the handkerchief.
- You said it later.
That's because you never answer the phone.
Anyway, I told you
Then why didn't you tell me later?
Do you know Lee Gang Hyun?
Everyone has things that they are embarrassed to say.
I don't even know about the illegal tutoring classes I took in high school
Do I have to tell you everything?
If it's related to the case, of course you have to tell me.
What about Liang Zhenghu?
Why did he know about Lee Gang Hyun's murder?
But you said nothing?
Why did I mention the puzzle?
He ignored what I said?
Because he doesn't trust you, he thinks you're a criminal.
Just forget it if you don't tell me
Why didn't he even tell you?
He should have enough time to tell you.
Think carefully about who you should trust.
(Call record details)
(Wu Zhejin)
Wu Zhejin
Yi Luo, you are at home
Aunt
Do you know Wu Zhejin?
Who? Wu Zhejin?
I've heard of this name
But I don't know what he looks like.
(Yin Yiluo: Decide who you want to believe quickly)
(If you have made a decision
You have to believe me anyway.)
Look here
1.2
(Jeju International Airport)
You will send gifts to my uncle, right?
Every festival, and my birthday
No wonder I think your name is familiar
Because I heard Director Yin
She loves her niece very much.
Also, those aren't gifts.
It's the phone bill
Many problems can be solved with just one phone call
That was a very long time ago.
Is that the reason you came all the way here?
How is that possible?
There is a person named Li Gangxuan
Are you familiar with it?
How do you know Gang Hyun?
Are you really Director Yoon’s niece?
(I don’t think this should be sent.)
(Let’s talk about it when we meet)
(What are you doing?)
(Dialing, Yin Yiluo)
Hello?
This is Miss Yin Yiluo's cell phone.
this…
Isn’t this Yin Yiluo’s cell phone?
Yes, that's right.
This is the Jeju Police Station
What is your relationship with Miss Yin Yiluo?
I am a colleague of Yin Yiluo's guard.
What happened?
This is hard to explain.
Guard Yin Yiluo was
We are staying at the Jeju Police Station.
What happened? Was she sent for backup?
It's not like that
She is a murder suspect.
What?
Miss
Miss!
What are you doing there?
Hello
I asked you what you were doing there.
Subtitle translation: Zhang Xinru