last episode
presidency
Open the door!
You're dead if you do this to your friends!
Settling search
1. Can Kang Tting-ok escape by using a special skill
2. If so, can Kang Tting-ok easily escape?
Kang Tting-ok hasn't come home since yesterday
so please cut his production from now on
He could avoid the road
Let's request for location tracking and check the route.
Yes.
Let's move to the last place where Kang Chimok's phone is turned off.
Let's find Kang Chimok's car first.
I'll look over there first.
Yes, this is Yang Jong-ho from Han River Police Station.
Yes, we request cooperation from the singer team.
Violence, impulsiveness, addiction, precision, planning, emotional dissection, high self-control.
Lee Mi-young and Yoon Dong-hoon are on the opposite sides of the suspect profiling of the murder.
It's the second car, right?
Yes.
Can you turn it around quickly?
There's no scene where it comes out again.
Do you want me to show you more?
What's behind the rest stop?
There's a mountain behind it.
There's nothing.
There's no black box, navigation, or SD card.
I think it's not a suicide.
It's not a suicide.
And it's direction is to Seoul.
It's the way back from somewhere.
This is the first time I've ever planned.
That's why I erased all the records.
Wait a minute.
Caught selling shares a long time ago.
Are you ok?
Gaenam whistle
I found it below the bridge
and I saw it on the CCTV in front of my house.
Anyway, I fell off the highway at 23 o'clock last night.
It's the direction of Yeongpyeong Lake,
and I got on the highway again from the direction of the lake.
It's 0229 a.m.
And finally, I entered the rest area where you are now.
I stayed in the direction of the lake for over 3 hours.
It's a problem if it's not fishing.
Let's go to Yeongpyeong Lake first.
Choi San, you join us here.
There's no fishing spot here.
Yes, we have the information about using a credit card.
The last place I wrote was Yeongpyeong Y Hotel.
Huh?
This is the Holy Land of Unwanted People.
I'm late on the weekly shift, so I don't know much about last night's guests.
Then, can you confirm that there was a name Kang Chimok among the guests who came yesterday?
Wait a minute.
Oh, yes, here it is.
Really?
You reserved for a night.
But you already checked out last night.
What number is that?
What are you doing?
Excuse me.
I'm a police officer.
Can I take a look around for a second?
Are you already cleaning up?
No, I just came in.
I'll take a look around.
What's going on?
Who else did you kill besides Lee Mae-young?
I think the bastard is out, but where did you hide the body?
After checking, the body was in the cure circle at 9 o'clock last night, and the CGTV was already abandoned because the removal was the principle.
It's not even a week, but it's been a week.
I'm sorry.
Is privacy that important these days?
If you checked in at 9 o'clock, it means that someone else checked in in advance.
Did you talk to the night shift worker yesterday?
I was going to tell you, but last night, there was a lot of noise from the music on the fifth floor, so there was a lot of noise.
Music?
So I'm thinking about going up, but at 2 a.m., a man in red pants went out in a hotel lobby in a carrier.
Carrier?
Red carrier.
Red carrier and red pants?
Kang Chimok also wore red pants yesterday.
The man who was in the car was also in the car.
Ikso!
Kang Chimok must have come because his emotions were extreme.
He must have been in a fight.
There are no traces of physical fight, either on the wall or on the floor.
Kang Chimok suppressed the opponent at once.
How did he suppress the victim?
Violence, impulsiveness, and addiction.
Kang Chimok is not the type to prepare this in advance.
I don't have a head or hands.
It won't be easy to find the identity.
Let's look around the hotel and the basement.
Did you hide the rest of the parts here?
I'll see if it's here.
It's getting blurry.
Yes.
Let's move the mountain from this side.
I thought it was the scenery, but it didn't move.
I'm sorry.
There's no scene where it doesn't come out.
The criminal and I have similar tastes.
I bought it because it was pretty.
Red carrier.
Are you playing a player in case I ask?
You know it's another brand, right?
Anyway, it's not Kang Chimok.
It means that it wasn't Kang Chimok who killed Lee Mi-young.
It means that it wasn't Kang Chimok who killed the man in the carrier.
Both.
Kang Chimok, who is the enemy of your team, how is it?
Defeat due to violence, multiple changes, and even non-conformity ofè·.
He's a low self-control person.
The culprit of the Lee Mi-young case this time was very systematic and planned so that there was no evidence left at the scene.
Besides, he's a high self-control person who controls his emotions.
The temperature is very low.
But Kang Chimok?
Isn't the temperature too high?
You're talking about the temperature.
In the clear motive, Lee Mi-young's car even had fingerprints.
Do you remember the last image of Lee Mi-young on CCTV?
The shoulders that were so full of excessive movement, the two hands tight on the handle, and the unstable eyes.
It was like feeling extreme fear.
Like a beginner driver who just got his driver's license.
Like a beginner driver.
Lee Mi-young is a tough person enough to run a bar alone at a young age.
It's impulsive, but Kang Chimok, who looks like he's going to kill himself, is not responding to the situation.
It was a situation where someone unfamiliar who had never seen before in his life would not know what to do to himself.
Like he's scared because he doesn't know what's in that deep water.
So it's not Kang Chimok who killed Lee Mi-young.
You said you weren't both.
Then who's the dead body in the carrier?
Isn't that Kang Chimok?
What are you talking about?
That stupid dead body.
I think that's Kang Chimok.
You said Kang Chimok was wearing gloves at the rest stop on CCTV.
Why did he drive his car with gloves on?
Is that Kang Chimok?
Are you sure?
What's the evidence that the person in the CCTV isn't Kang Chimok?
Gloves?
That's all?
I'll know if I compare Kang Chimok's DNA and that dead body.
Good job.
I'll go first.
Yes, yes, I see.
I'll call you back.
The dead body without a head in the reservoir is similar to Kang Chimok's DNA.
Wow, this is a real accident.
Then he killed Lee Mi-young and was killed by a slaughterhouse.
Does this make sense?
I was attracted by the story, but I'm embarrassed.
Is it true that Kang Chimok killed Lee Mi-young?
Young-ha, what's wrong with you?
The evidence is out.
Why are you shaking the foundation?
I can't be 100% sure of that.
What's going on?
I'm so pissed off.
Come on.
Let's check again to see if the man on the CCTV at the rest stop is Kang Chimok.
Yes, sir.
The best way to find out is to meet the staff at the store.
If you just leave it after eating, I'll erase it tomorrow.
Ma'am.
Huh?
Have you ever heard of Lee Mi-young and Kang Chimok?
No, I've never heard of them.
What about them?
What kind of person was my uncle?
I think he was different from what I know.
I don't know.
What about when your uncle suddenly changed?
What do you mean suddenly?
No, then it's okay.
When I was left alone,
right after my parents died in a car accident,
I changed.
Like someone else.
And then I stopped being a cop.
I'm going.
The sofa is still soft.
I thought I'd buy one of these.
I thought I wouldn't have to sit there anymore.
What's going on?
It started again.
That dream.
I remembered everything.
I knew it wasn't me.
Why did I dream again?
Because I couldn't find the answer that night.
Is that why you can't sleep?
I couldn't sleep, so my eyes were too swollen.
Or maybe it's because I ate ramen yesterday.
It's not an ultimate answer that In-ha is not the culprit.
It's not.
Why did that happen that night?
Who killed my uncle?
I think we should try to find the answer first.
I asked you something obvious.
I'm going to find the answer.
Oh, but the dream is a dream.
When can I sleep?
When you feel safe even when you sleep.
Can you prescribe some sleeping pills?
Then I can't sleep.
I have to meditate.
Oh, you know the sushi restaurant at six tomorrow, right?
Should Mr. Hwang come with me?
I'll ask him.
I'm sorry.
Is it really my husband?
Is it really your husband?
It matches the DNA from Kang Chimok's razor.
I just said I'd be late.
That can't be true.
I'm sorry.
This man.
Please look at it again.
You really don't know who it is?
I don't know.
I thought it was my husband.
It's the same as the husband's clothes I wore that morning.
I don't know.
I don't know the staff at the store.
The price of the CCTV is so bad.
But he must know Kang Chimok.
Of course he knows.
Hey, there's no way he got a call and went all the way there.
Look.
If you look at the contents of the cell phone,
Kang Chimok got a call at 21 40.
The call time is only 47 seconds.
He got a call from near the house and moved.
But what did he say to get there?
I think he booked the hotel in the name of Kang Chimok.
Or he must have gone straight to the hotel at the store, not home.
And the check-in time is not right.
This is also part of the rest area CCTV.
He had to disguise himself as Kang Chimok and escape.
First of all, I see a good relationship in the form of a damage to the body.
I'll meet the people around me.
The movie and I are in a relationship of money.
It's all about money. Money.
What should I do?
You check all the CCTVs around the rest area.
There are a lot of things.
If you go in, there's a place where it comes out.
Analyze it carefully.
Okay.
If anything happens, report it right away.
Yes.
CCTV, CCTV.
You're a CCTV.
Good morning.
Have a cup of coffee.
Oh, my God.
Every time.
Thank you.
Why?
Tell me. What is it?
You know.
The puzzle didn't come.
It's not Kang Chimok.
What's in Kang Chimok?
Can't you sign?
But why?
You said you didn't know.
Why do you have to know that?
Do you feel like a competitor to me?
I do.
Do you know Lee Mi-young?
It's the first name I've heard.
I think it's a pretty common name.
There's nothing to worry about.
Who is it?
Oh, my God.
Who are you?
Oh, hello.
I'm Yoon In-ha, the criminal analysis team at Seo Il-jung.
I have a few questions to ask.
Can I go in?
It's a little awkward, isn't it?
I'm not sure if I can get rid of it because I'm not used to it.
When did you hear about Lee Mi-young from your husband for the first time?
You know, Lee Mi-young.
Oh, I'm not trying to die.
I just have some questions.
I didn't think my husband would have no woman because he was old.
That didn't even matter.
Do you know how much the apartment I gave to Mi-young was?
That's exactly what I asked.
I was sad all the time when I was selling my newlyweds.
That's when I first heard the name Lee Mi-young.
What about other stories?
Have you ever heard of anything like that?
It's different?
I don't think so.
But why do you keep asking about the dead woman?
Did you hear from your husband?
Lee Mi-young's dead?
No.
I heard it from the police yesterday.
Yeah.
But how did you know I was that woman?
I lied because I was afraid you'd be bothered.
It's best to know that.
Because you're a profiler.
Really?
I wanted to do that, too.
Would you like a cup of coffee?
You've been at the store all the way from work.
You left before lunchtime.
It must have been around 1130.
When did you come back to the store?
It's past 7.
With three members who played golf together.
Golf members?
Yeah.
Did anything happen?
Or the atmosphere?
Oh, it's piled up.
The golf members went and the owner was a little excited.
He threw it on the wall of the bottle and it was a mess.
Why?
I don't know.
I'm a person like a fire.
It's a secret.
Because you're one personality.
Did you meet any golf members or people you met after coming to the store?
No, I didn't.
He called a taxi right at 9 o'clock and left.
Oh, he called a taxi?
Yeah.
How about coffee?
I learned it for free.
It's not bad.
It's like the first barista breathing in six months.
Oh, my God.
It's been six months since I learned it.
Oh, it's similar to me and tomorrow.
Oh, really.
I'm sorry.
What else do you see?
You liked being alone.
You used the same room with your husband, right?
Yeah.
I can't sleep if someone's next to me.
I really hate it when someone is breathing next to me when I sleep.
If the distance is too short, there's always a problem.
Right?
So I used the room separately from the beginning of my honeymoon.
My husband didn't understand.
He liked doing everything together.
When did Profiler get his own room?
Since I was born.
I lived well at home.
Both my parents were doctors.
I envy you.
What?
I've been in the room since I was born.
I became a profiler.
I'm sorry.
What happened?
I've lost someone before.
You can see that?
I was under police investigation and I wasn't nervous at all.
I think I'm used to the situation of death.
That's amazing.
I shouldn't lie to Profiler.
I was 13 years old when the house was on fire.
My grandmother and sister died then.
Do you know that the next day was the day I moved?
There were two rooms in the new house, but my room was not there.
But I think you've lost someone before.
That's right.
My parents died in a car accident when I was in elementary school.
But why did you think that?
Just.
I had those eyes.
Just like me.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Are you leaving already?
I had so much fun today.
I hope we meet again.
Hi, everyone. How have you been?
Manager Yoon.
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
If you missed me, you should have seen it.
It doesn't smell like anything I've never smelled before.
Didn't you go home yesterday?
Oh, this is a cake I haven't seen.
Where is it from?
It's a strawberry cake.
I was just looking at the data.
The case was fun.
It's fun, but it's terrible.
Don't be like In-ha.
What's wrong with me?
Let's get started.
I'm the culprit of this case.
Let's ask.
Do you know the victim?
Yeah.
That's why you lost your body.
Because you're suspected right away.
But you caught it in a day.
You must have been hurt.
No, not yet.
The police are looking for that man who was on CCTV, not me.
Then what's the relationship with that guy?
Did you refuse?
It's not a request.
I just thought that guy wouldn't betray me.
Who asked you to kill him?
I did.
Why? Because of money?
Money doesn't matter.
I just wanted to clear it up in front of my eyes.
Why did you want to clear it up?
That's how I lived.
This isn't the first time.
That's right.
So I know how the police will come out.
I've been to that hotel before.
Is there a name for the government?
No way.
Then how did you call the hotel?
I stimulated him.
He's with me.
So he couldn't stand the anger.
He's talking.
He's just shaking.
He can't stand anyone touching his own.
You're a woman.
How did you kill him?
He knocked on the door.
He opened the door.
I went behind him and fell down.
Then I turned over 20 plastic bags and dragged them to the bathroom.
I ordered everything.
How did you feel when you killed him?
I couldn't breathe in front of me anymore.
I was really, really happy.
Wait a minute.
It's different from the typical characteristics of a female killer.
Most of them use poison or drugs to kill because of physical conditions.
The law and motivation have changed.
I'm more bold and active in identifying evidence.
I used sleeping pills and weapons together when I saw my ex-husband's murder at a pension in Gapyeong.
I couldn't find any traces of the dead body.
How can I catch me?
Kang Chimok's wife said that day that Kang Chimok didn't come home.
I said I was late, and I didn't come home that day.
I know that I shouldn't do that.
But I was so angry that day that I didn't go into the parking lot and just put it in front of the house.
If you catch me, I'll just report it right away.
That's why I just took it just in case.
I don't feel like the
No way.
1025...
Wow!
It's open!
Oh, you're a fan of Agatha Christie.
You're not my type.
It's a little weird to talk about the real story.
I'm going to meet you again tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
Hi, Karen.
Are you here?
What are you doing here?
I didn't answer the phone.
What?
I bought pizza.
Don't you have honey at home?
I'll eat it with dough.
I'm sorry.
Why did you use the password 1025?
Isn't the profiling over yet?
I'm done.
It's your turn now.
How did you know the password?
You know this is a death-strike, right?
I thought we would have the same mind.
It's our house 1025 shop.
The day my uncle died.
It's your first and only secret case.
There are more things we're similar than you think.
Was the father of the deceased a police officer?
There's no such thing as a person.
I'm sorry, but this time, I got it wrong.
My father is not a police officer.
Really?
But why are you wearing a police uniform?
Did you watch the movie Red Earth?
No.
When you were filming that, you played a strong detective.
My father learned it.
It wasn't famous.
No wonder you said you were handsome.
Your mother must have liked it.
Why do women usually kill their husbands?
Money, domestic violence, and depression are one of the three.
It's generally true.
I met with Kang Chimok's wife.
Why are you?
I was curious if you had heard about Lee Mi-young from Kang Chimok.
But it was a little weird.
When my grandmother and sister talked about their death, they didn't look sad at all.
When I said I didn't have a room, I even saw a sad expression and an angry expression.
Your room?
Why are you talking about the room all of a sudden?
And I didn't ask about my husband's death.
I think I can't stand being curious.
I didn't ask if there was anything in the investigation or anything.
Why?
Because I know the answer.
That's why I don't get a regular reaction as a child.
I don't think you know that.
Did you react normally as a child?
That's why we bought a similar carrier.
I'll ask Seoyoung to come to the interview tomorrow.
Why is the conclusion so obvious?
I haven't even been confessed yet, what kind of interview are you going to do?
She doesn't confess.
Oh, like you?
I'm not confessing, I'm confessing.
I'm going to ask for a job tomorrow.
Let's see what you say.
And I told you not to talk informally.
Oh, I ordered coffee.
Start.
Who is this man?
I don't know.
You have to find that.
You don't tell me you don't know anymore.
You said your husband didn't come home on the day of the incident, right?
Yes.
Then how can I explain this?
I guess I fell asleep early that day and didn't know.
I die once I fall asleep.
After the call from your husband, Seoyoung's cell phone was off all day.
Until the next morning.
Where were you?
I was at home.
I kept sleeping.
But am I the suspect?
Why do you think so?
I've seen this kind of scene a lot in movies.
When my husband died, my wife was the first to be suspected.
Is there a reason to be suspected?
Of course.
Isn't that why you called me?
Have you ever met another man besides your husband?
Yes.
All three or four.
Wow.
That's amazing.
You had a special person among them.
What about the sportsman?
He broke up with me a month ago.
So I can't be his colleague.
That's not normal. You even gave me information first.
Is it that man's doing?
Did I have a heart of gold because I wanted to break up?
What's the reason for saying that?
I just thought so.
I've asked if you can take that position without your husband.
Would you like to meet him if you're okay?
Yes, that's right.
I broke up with him a month ago.
But the woman wasn't that much.
Anyway, she's a married woman.
It's a little too serious.
It's just a lot of fun.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do it.
It's just a lot of fun, right?
You must have hurt your hand.
Can I see it now?
Oh, yes.
I often get hurt because I fall down when I play tennis.
But ask Yang-hee about this.
I once said that.
I was really upset that I couldn't get a job without my husband.
Yes.
It's time for the next lesson.
I'll go now.
How did you hurt your hand?
They're accomplices.
Seoyang and Noh Jae-ho were in the same class in high school.
I don't think there was any exchange all the time.
I think Seoyang and Noh Jae-ho met again while he was in the tennis club a year ago.
There was a rumor in the club.
I've been on the phone with two people.
All contacts were cut off a month ago.
I can call you a couple of times, but there's nothing.
It's a little unnatural like a anesthetic.
But I was trying to give you a life insurance, but there wasn't a common life insurance.
What are you talking about?
If the life insurance is dead, it will all be inherited from Seoyang.
If you calculate it, you'll have a few hundred million left, except for the debt.
And the profit from the store is said to be two or three thousand won a month.
If the life insurance is gone, both of them are in a win-win situation.
But there must be a reason.
If Kang Chi-mook recently found out about their relationship.
It's going to be a mess.
I heard you're not a joke.
I think you said you were going to kill them both.
Yes, I think so, too.
If the two people who were so pressured decided to kill Kang Chi-mook.
Kang Chi-mook, who was angry at Noh Jae-wook's phone call, can run right away.
There's enough motivation and resistance, but there's no definite water.
We need to be confessed.
It's like a strategy to push each other.
We need to be balanced.
It was on CCTV on purpose. It's an idea of Seoyang.
It's also a body in a red carrier that stands out.
The personality of the criminal is reflected in the evidence, the person and the manipulation.
Seoyang is very familiar with disguise.
Then who will be more vulnerable?
Who will confess first?
How much do you know about Seoyang?
I know a lot because I'm in high school.
And I met him as a reason.
Until a month ago.
Did Seoyang ever talk about his family?
Yes.
My parents died when I was young.
My grandmother and sister lived together.
Didn't you say that both grandmother and sister died after that?
I did.
But why is this?
How did you say you died?
I said there was a fire at home.
He wasn't home.
You were just saying that you weren't home?
It was a defense.
I didn't catch the criminal.
At that time, Seoyang was 13 years old, so no one doubted it.
Elementary school students lost both grandmother and sister at the same time.
You must have felt sorry for them.
There was someone who was doubted at that time.
Like Noh Jae-wook.
A 15-year-old middle school student who lived next door.
Do you know what happened to that middle school student?
Do I have to know?
He's missing.
I haven't found him yet.
You should know this, too.
It could happen to you.
You know that Seoyang is in the next room, right?
Seoyang is claiming that Noh Jae-wook killed her husband.
It's so funny.
How can this be?
Really?
You've been suspecting a profiler for 10 years as a murderer?
Yes, I told you.
I'm sick of it.
There's no evidence that I killed him.
There's no evidence that you didn't kill him, either.
Yes.
But do you know that?
You know the carrier that was picked up from the reservoir?
It was similar to my carrier.
What kind of carrier?
And this carrier found in the reservoir.
It was found to be the same product as the carrier that Seoyang bought three months ago.
It even has a card.
That carrier.
Where is it now?
I think I've done everything I can.
Then can I go home now?
Noh Jae-wook.
Don't you think it's safer to just stay here?
Seoyang was next to me when I ran away.
I think I've seen a person alive among those who are related to Seoyang.
No one has been alive among those who are related to Seoyang.
Your parents, grandmother, and sister.
What will happen to Noh Jae-wook?
Actually, I was supposed to meet you after today.
Yang-hee.
I found the bag.
The victim of the murder of the soil in Yeongpyeong was arrested after several years of discovery.
Surprisingly, the wife who cried over her husband's death at the time of the incident was a murderer.
The police are investigating the exact motive for the murder of Ahn Hye-seo.
This is what reporter Park Ji-hoon said.
The police arrested Ahn Hye-seo and Nae-yeon Nam Noh for the crime of murder and death.
At 6 p.m. yesterday, the local newspaper was told that Ahn Hye-seo and the criminal Noh were the victims.
It's only been a few days since the body was found.
They were also accused of killing the body and killing the victim.
The police are investigating the crime of murder and the new release.
Another shocking fact is that the murder of the victim and the murder of the woman in the whiskey bar are related.
The police are investigating the crime of murder and the murder of the woman in the whiskey bar.
What is this?
Bone.
Oh, this is a good one. The neck is different.
I'll use it well.
I bought it in the style of a famous detective, but it looks really big.
It's weird.
I'll try it on.
How is it? Did you go to the detective?
It's an accident.
Oh, I just changed my mind.
I gave it to you as a gift.
I'm a man, so I just saw it.
We can give it to you as a gift. Do you have anything you want?
I don't have anything I want, but I have something I want to say.
Do it. The case is closed and I got a gift.
The case is not over yet.
It's not Seoyang or Kang Jin-mok who killed Lee Mi-young.
What are you talking about?
Then think about it.
Why?
Oh, you don't like the hat?
So who do you think you are?
What do you mean?
You said that it wasn't even Kang Jin-mok who killed Lee Mi-young. Who do you think you are?
I don't know that yet.
I think everyone around me except you is a suspect.
You know that, so you're not talking about it, are you?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I used a stopwatch because I had a similar taste.
My parents died of an accident when I was young.
I thought I was used to the disguise like that girl in the West.
That's not it. In my eyes, In-ha is too transparent.
When I held Seoyang's hand, I remembered a movie I watched when I was young.
In the movie, the main character talks like this about the killer he was investigating.
He grew up in one house, he went out the back door, and I came out the front door.
It's important that In-ha came out the front door.
Seoyang didn't kill her husband because she wanted to live with her lover because of money.
Seoyang wanted a bigger house and a bigger space.
So she got married, but she was invaded by her husband.
Seoyang was just being invaded by her husband, so she just removed the hindrance.
As if she killed her grandmother and sister when she was 13.
It's too hard. I'll find the answer.
What kind of sleep is this?
I'm done with work today. I'm drinking beer today.
I'm going to work.
Thank you.