Goblin
Timing and Subtitles by The Immortal Team @viki.com
A new face. The one I mentioned before who's got a lot of info and has been living in the nether world for a long time.
Ah...
20 years ago,
he even ran away from a grim reaper.
Has it been about 20 years? I made eye contact with some deceased person.
But that deceased had no information about him.
Really? I also had a similar experience when I was nine years...
It seems like he had been wandering in this life for so long. He seemed to have no fear.
It was my first time seeing a deceased person that was not afraid of a grim reaper. It was fascinating.
Nice to meet you.
So you are that Goblin's Bride.
Yes. Same to you.
Now, if you gather in someone else's business place
there won't be any customers. Now we have to do business so you should all leave.
- Cold-hearted girl.
- Starting with you, Unni. Hurry, hurry.
That unfriendly brat!
The feeling is a bit...
In my horrorific life of 20 years, it's my first time seeing that.
Let's forget it. Forget it. I'm so busy so I have no time to think about a ghost.
If I move it all to the middle of the week...
I should push my part-time hours...
A love letter? What nonsense.
I am too busy living, and what? A love letter?
I am...
a grim reaper.
I want to meet him.
I don't want to meet him.
♫  I love you, love you, love you ♫
How could I run out of it after 7 glasses?
Even after knowing I would finish it in 7 glasses,
I started with I wanted to meet him.
I want to meet him. I don't want to meet him.
I want to meet him.
You... have you ever been hit by a peach blossom?
I have. I went to see a shaman and I got beat up. The effect lasts a long time, you know.
The earlier one was better.
Right? The one before was better.
But then... have you ever thought of wanting to find your memories?
No.
What are forgotten memories? Isn't it the same as no memories?
It wasn't there from the beginning, so why...
♫ I love you, love you, love you ♫
♫ I could feel that we were fated to be ♫
I... miss that.
Don't. We are all sinners.
How do you know what's behind that longing?
I know.
Even though I know...
Every step I take because of this longing,
even though I am afraid where it would reach,
I...
keep longing for that.
♫ Don’t leave my side ♫
You seem to be drinking too much today.
I got caught... That I'm a grim reaper by Sunny.
Nice going. Good job.
In the middle of winter, where could she have found a peach blossom branch?
- I know, right?
- What do I do now?
- She must be so confused.
- About what?
Since it came to this, hold her hand once more. See if I am in there or not.
- I got caught, I said.
- Since you're caught, hold her hand.
See if my face is there or not.
You have no idea. Do you know how hard it is to see a past life?
It's like someone pushing forcibly in. In an instant!
The face that I only saw in a painting, to see it vividly in person, was so beautiful that it made me lose my...
It's my sister.
...mind.
I just saw one young and foolish looking face. That young king's.
She must have thought of that dummy, my ugly.
She doesn't care about her Orabeoni.
I am here. Why?
No, next time.
Give it to me! Why are you going through someone else's notebook?
Why is my writing in someone else's notebook then?
What is this? Did you forge a document without me knowing?
Feigning ignorance. It's a love letter. The one that you wrote.
You wrote a love letter?
He did. To his first love. What kind of grand love story is it?
I was curious about the ending, so I was going to ask for your help.
What do you mean? This is not a love letter.
As if! It was very well written.
"One day after living hundreds of years,
on a day that was just right..." Huh?
- It's not the contents though.
- Yes, they are.
- Oppa Deok Hwa read it all to me.
- After living like that for hundreds of years on a day,
on a day that's just right...
That can't be. There's no way Deok Hwa can read this even if he came from the dead.
Those are words that I kept to myself that is not recorded anywhere.
After living like that for hundreds of years on a day,
on a day that was just right on a day,
I wish I could confess that it was first love...
That's right. It's not what it says.
That's not right. Deok Hwa Oppa translated it for me.
It's a love letter.
Last time,
when you wrecked a lot of cars, did you perhaps tell Deok Hwa
that I could help with erasing memories?
- No.
- Uncle down the hall, you have to go somewhere with me.
But how did he know to ask for me to help?
Now that I think about it, Oppa  Deok Hwa also found my maple leaf.
Something that I completely lost.
This maple leaf, try to guess where this is from.
What is this?
Wow. That's pretty cool.
Why did I not know?
He even dared to rent out the Goblin's house.
If it was the king, God or me.
This character is to hear, "cheong."
I found that girl. She's at a ski resort.
That is because your boss is the younger sister of my uncle in his past life.
Should we grab a drink?
Finally, the Goblin and the Goblin's Bride meet.
It's fate.
Why involve Wang Yeo?
How could you make the person who got stabbed meet the person who stabbed him?
- What brings you to my house?
- You live here?
That is also fate.
- He was also coincidentally looking for a house.
- You should bring it down a notch.
What on earth are you thinking?
I love him particularly.
Kim Shin has been punished for 900 years already. Is that still not enough?
Such is the weight of a person's life.
You should have just created a perfect world without sins from the first place, then.
Then they won't seek God.
They are children I've blessed with love. Stop bothering them.
Stop covering that child's eyes, too. Leave them alone to recognize each other,
whatever decision they make.
That's too bad. I liked his good looks.
They're finally here.
Deok Hwa, you...
Who are you? Let's introduce ourselves.
God of stars! God of heavens!
Do not pray to anyone. SinceGod is not listening.
"God is still not listening."
You were complaining.
"God must have a reason to erase my memories."
f you remember, you do. If you don't, you don't. if we don't, then we don't. It should all be God's intention.
You were guessing my intentions.
I was always listening. Since you were pleading for death, I gave you a chance.
But then, why are you still alive?
I have never erased your memory. You chose to have it erased. Even then,
does it seem like God's plan or a mistake?
God just questions. Fate is the question I throw, the answer...
you can find it.
My goodbye to this child,
you can, too... Then,
I'll get going.
Uncles, why are you here? When did you come?
Why am I on the ground?
Awesome! Did I just black out?
With just one drink?
Whoever you are, let me hit you once.
Why are you doing that to the child? He's innocent.
That person?
- I am sorry for always saying, "Let's go somewhere."
- What?
What's wrong with him, Uncle?
How can you say... Are you really Deok Hwa?
Hey! The butterfly! Butterfly man!
- Uncle, you're drunk!
- Come here! Aren't you coming?
Time. I'll talk. Let go of me. Let go.
So hot. Hot.
But it's really delicious.
The man turns out to be a grim reaper.
- How did you know?
I witnessed a very strange moment.
I somehow had a connection with him since I was young.
I'm sorry for not telling you. But then, Mr. Kim Woo Bin as a grim reaper
is really kind and gentle.
Are there any obsessive girl ghosts that follow him?
That was the first thought I had.
He doesn't match with my conditions. I'm out of his league. It's this life and the afterlife.
How could you think of those?
I thought of this, if that person is a grim reaper,
then the person who claims to be my Orabeoni must have really lived close to a thousand years.
Is that right? So are you the wife?
- Goblin's wife?
- Technically speaking,
I'm the "husband," since I'm the breadwinner.
This is crazy.
But you know, Boss, even if you hang around our house
the probability of meeting Mr. Kim Woo Bin is slim.
It's an occupation that requires a lot of overtime. Just call him.
How could I call after hearing him say that we broke up? If he calls
then I'd force myself to answer it. Just cooperate.
Yes.
But then, Boss, I'm so sorry.
- Sure, do that.
- I  haven't said anything yet.
Weren't you going to ask to have your hours adjusted
since you're a college student, now?
Wow, awesome!
Boss, you are a human, right?
Welcome.
That startled me. It's been a long time since I was startled by a human.
Me, too. But why a chicken place all of a sudden?
That person just now, she lives a floor below me.
She knows me. It would be good to help her out.
That's good. Let's hurry and eat so that we can go.
There are so many incidents and accidents in the beginning of the year. I'm dying.
Please enjoy.
We didn't order that.
It's on the house. A new menu is out and you have a tough job.
Aigoo. Thank you for acknowledging.
Woah! The taste is killer!
What's wrong?
Eat. Dip in, too.
What's with you? How dare a soul appear before a grim reaper?
It's been a long time.
You were living as a grim reaper all this while?
What do you mean? Do you know me?
- I sure do know.
- Don't make things up.
Aren't you curious who am I?
How I'm so fearless in front of you?
But more than that,
aren't you curious as to who you are?
Go and hold that woman's hand.
The owner of the store you just came from.
People who have committed a huge sin in the past life become grim reapers, they say.
In her past should be your sin.
And...
inside that sin, I will be there.
I did not erase your memories. You just chose to have them erased. Despite that
it seems like it's God's plan
or a mistake?
What are you thinking so hard about?
A thought that I shouldn't do it.
Why do it when you know you shouldn't be doing it?
I think I might do it tomorrow if I don't do it today.
Don't do that. The atmosphere now is not good.
The department of grim reapers has issued a code of conduct after the incident with Kim Cha Sa from Janghang-dong.
- What is it?
- You all are sinners.
Don't forget that.
I feel so unsettled because of it. This is this month's rosters.
Did he give an answer
or give a question?
I gave you the register.
[Yoo Sin Woo. 81 years old. February 22, 2017 17:10. Myocardial infarction]
I'm home.
It's in 3 hours. The cause would be myocardial infarction.
You should go say goodbye.
I already said everything I wanted as he lived.
Even till the end,
I don't want to see him be sorry to me.
For sending off... you can do it in my stead.
Don't worry.
Tell him that he should be born again
and that in the next life
live freely and not be tied to anyone.
And that I was thankful.
That I am very grateful.
What's going on?
Prepare some black clothes. You will get news about Chairman Yoo's death, soon.
Please keep an eye on him.
♬ You don't know my heart. You're too much, too much.
This is too much. Aigoo, my back.
Just wait until I become CEO. I'll come here all the time, have company dinner all the time,
and send you off in a deluxe cab, for sure. (He'll have her very drunk.)
I'm going to suggest really tacky clothes and make you always wear that.
Mr. Deok Hwa.
What?
Did Grandfather ask you to keep an eye on me so obviously?
You need to come with me. Now.
There's still a long time till I can get off work.
I prepared clothes, so you may change in the car.
What clothes?
A person who was good-hearted every moment in this lifetime
rests here.  Yoo Shin Woo
[A person who was good-hearted every moment in this lifetime rests here. Yoo Shin Woo]
I guess this is what it's like, being immortal.
Chairman Yoo will keep turning back,
saying, "He makes me worry."
So, the people left behind must live more diligently.
We might cry from time to time, but we should laugh more.
Again, with confidence.
♬  We were here in old days  ♬
That... is the courtesy for the love you have received.
♬  With you, with me  ♬
Would you like something warm?
♬ All my fears have gone  ♬
♬ When you whisper to me ♬
Deok Hwa...
I'll pick him up and eat with him.
♬  No matter how♬
♬ Near or far apart, apart♬
What should I do?
I wasn't good to him. I feel so bad.
What should I do if he just leaves like this, Uncle?
♬  I'll be here   ♬
I'm so sorry towards Grandfather. What do I do, Uncle?
♬ To shelter you   ♬
♬   When you feel   ♬
What do I do now?
♬ So lonely ♬
Now what do I do alone?
♬  I'll be here   ♬
What do you mean alone?
♬   Here for you   ♬
Uncle...
Yeah. You have your Uncle. Stay with me, and don't worry.
♬  If I could fly above the clouds   ♬
♬ Like all the birds ♬
♬  And I could hold you for a while  ♬
Get up and eat something.
♬   Let you feel my pulse ♬
Even if the apple is shaped as a rabbit?
♬  Still here   ♬
Should I make gold appear?
♬ all alone  ♬
Give you a ride through the wall?
Oppa, have my camera. You liked it a lot.
It's fine. Grandfather got it himself to give it to you.
Sorry I didn't tell you in advance.
I regret not giving you time to prepare your heart.
But there's something called order of things in the world.
I know. Our household has been the Goblin's caretaker for many generations.
♬   And I'm here   ♬
Thanks, everyone. I have something to do, so...
♬   With you  ♬
I thought Grandfather would worry over it.
You know our Grandfather's personality.
I do.
Secretary Kim filled in as CEO. Grandfather had it all prepared before he left.
It worked out well. I wasn't ready yet anyway.,
Right.
I'll learn my work from the bottom, because that's what Grandfather would've wanted.
That's right.
Baduk, also, ...
I'll learn that, too. So, I can become a good older brother,
father, and then grandfather to you, Uncle.
Like my grandfather.
Right.
[Yoo Deok Hwa]
[Kim Do Yeong]
One day, if a person who has a surname Kim and name Shin that means trustworthy, comes
and says that he's here for his things, give them to him.
Everything I have left belongs to him.
He will come walking  in the rain and go in a blue flame.
Then, know that he is Kim Shin.
He left.
Who are you? Do you know me?
I do. You're a child who is nothing but nice,
so you brighten the world.
Your luck comes from your good heart. Don't forget.
Yes, well. I'm not really a child.
Would you like to have a drink with me?
Drink with a beautiful person.
You're beautiful.
I said drink with a person. Bye.
What the hell? Jeez.
Why are there so many?
Deok Hwa's coming.
Pass me the pepper.
I'm jealous of Deok Hwa. He has an Uncle.
Don't mind me. These days, I keep getting jealous and longing for something.
Just say it. You are jealous of an uncle. A really super handsome uncle.
What?
When did you say you became a Grim Reaper?
It's been a little over 300 years. Why?
Do I have something on my face?
Just... for a moment,
I saw a different face on you than usual.
Who? What face?
A face that shouldn't be in my sight.
Uncle! Sit, help out, or go to your room! Why are you loitering around?
I am in the middle of being proud of how useful you are.
Jeez.
It's a  given for a third-generation heir to take work outside the hourly paid time.
Uncle, what's wrong?
[Resume : Kim Woo Sik]
Today is the first day of school. There will be a freshman party. Thus the short dress.
No.
I'll be back.
Deok Hwa will drop you off. I have an appointment, but if something happens--
I know. Perfect, right?
One's missing.
Ah. I know what it is.
I don't know why you're closing your eyes.
It's perfect now.
This... is from that maple country. Oh, I'm touched.
What does it say?
It means a fate set by heaven in French. An absolute fate that is far beyond the realm of humans.
It's a word I like, fate.
How did you know?
No meeting, no blind dates, no romance, and no Oppa Tae Hee.
No man in a 30 cm radius from this necklace. This is the kind of fate I'm thinking of.
Ah, really. I applied to college so I could do those things.
There's no way. The heavens made it that way. You'll be late. Goodbye.
I'll be back.
♬ I want to keep you close ♬
♬ She blew me away ♬
♬ Heaven is in your eyes ♬
♬ Heaven is in your sound ♬
♬   It's everything in the world you show me  ♬
♬ Heaven is in your kiss ♬
♬  Even though tears fall down  ♬
♬ You are the only one under this heaven ♬
[Message from Eun Tak]
I arrived at the school safely and brilliantly, and I'm sending you this in case you are having to go back and forth to hell because of me.
Fighting on your appointment.
She's wearing her necklace, and she made sure there's no man behind her. She's pretty.
[Cheon Woo Group Experienced Employee Recruitment Interview]
I will obey my commander's order.
Please forgive me.
I will soon follow suit.
We must have missed each other,
because I am alive like this.
You must have been lonely.
Please forgive me.
Mr. Kim Woo Shik, Mr. Choi Sang Min,
Mr. Lee Jae Ha. Please come in.
I was accepted? Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Honey! I got in!
- Dad!
- My baby!
Should we eat jajjangmyun? (black bean noodles)
It's the apartment that the company provides.
- To me?
- Yes, because you did well on the interview.
It's the car that the company provides.
To me?
Yes, because you did really well on the interview.
This is the name of the son that will be born on May 1st.
He will become a person who lights this world generation after generation.
- My child?
- Yes.
By the way... I've been wondering who you are?
Ah, my introduction is a bit late.
I am the president of Cheon Woo Group, Kim Do Yeong.
The President? I'm sorry I didn't recognize you.
But ... why are you giving me more than I deserve?
Because you saved a nation in your past life.
- I did?
- Yes.
- Hello?
- Where are you now?
Do you know what time it is? Why are you not back from this dangerous world?
It is 5 in the afternoon now,
and the sun is still  high up.
You should tone down on the nagging.
Tone down? Where are you? I've been asking!
Me?
You will be totally surprised at where I am at.
I'm here. In this confined and small place.
Hey, look at you!
Oh! Over there!
- 1, 2, 3.
- Act pretty.
Wow! They came out well!
Ohh! Amidst that chaos, look at you smile.
- When are we getting out of here?
- I'm not sure.
- After five minutes.
- Why after five minutes?
In that moment, there might be a happening that would cause my heart to drop
in a such a tight space.
There won't be such a thing.
There should be.
Like this. I rounded up the 8 won to 5210 won ($5.21).
See, your heart dropped, right?
How could you pay back the money in such a cramped, tight space?
With that money,
hurry and pay my boss back for the sweet potato.
Is she asking me to pay her right away?
You want to see your sister, but my boss is living in the present.
Going to the store is a bit awkward... but you want to see her, right?
So, as you pay for the sweet potatoes,
I'm making you an excuse to see her face.
I'm going to my part-time work. Do you want to come along?
I do miss her but your boss is scary. I will go next time.
Awesome! Real siblings.
- Let's get out.
- Already?
Why?
It's so cold outside. How's school?
Is it bearable?
- You know... Oppa Tae Hee ...
- That son of...
Did I ask about his well being? I asked about school.
No... Oppa Tae Hee is going to America to play in the Major Leagues.
I heard goblins can recognize potential
so I was going to say how cool it was.
This might sound like I'm bragging about myself.
But I've been able to recognize people who would be a big person since a long time ago.
Hwang Hui, that buddy, is the prime example. (Politician in both the Goryeo and early Joseon dynasties)
- That friend Maeng Sa Seong, too.
- Alright about that. (Deputy premier under King Sejong)
An adult is talking...
I am busy.
I am late for work. In such a tight cramped space,
where did talk of Hwang Hui come from?
I will be going.
Oh... if something happens call me.
In this small and tiny place, very awkward.
Small and tiny mean the same.
I want to come every day.
Wind burst!
Come here. Come to Noona.
It's late. Go straight home, your Grandma is waiting.
We see each other again.
Last time, I thought I wasn't able to properly introduce myself.
I am... Park Joong Hun.
You look like
you already know me.
- I don't.
- Kim Shin...
Didn't he tell you?
The one who killed me is him.
The punishment that Kim Shin is receiving
increases with the weight of life.
Inside that is also the price for my life.
- What is it that you want?
- There is nothing.
It's just that I want to tell a funny story.
Since you know me, you probably know Wang Yeo as well.
The sword that is in Kim Shin's chest...
It was given to him by Wang Yeo.
The start and end of this tragic story is...
Wang Yeo.
Do you know who Wang Yeo is living with?
How would I know that?
Wang Yeo is now...
living with Kim Shin.
What kind of nonsense...
That's right. The nameless grim reaper...
he is Wang Yeo.
If those two recognize each other...
what do you think will happen?
Now, for Kim Shin to kill me or save me
is in your hands, it seems.
Just like how Kim Shin's death is in your hands.
Now that I look at it,
so you are a child that is in control of death.
You are wrong.
The Grim Reaper that we know
has a name,
Kim Woo Bin.
Did you ask what I want?
I...
want their destruction.
What are you doing not moving aside? Let them take one alone
I don't want to! I sat here first.
Wang Yeo is now...
living with Kim Shin.
I'm going crazy.
Miscellaneous Omitted Person.
Thanks for the drink.
I'm sorry for startling you.
Is there something wrong? Did you come on purpose?
I was frustrated.
I have no one else to talk to but you.
What is it? About my boss?
More or less.
In the past life, if someone commits a huge sin
they become a grim reaper.
What sin?
I don't know. But somehow,
inside the history of Kim Shin and his sister
it seems like I am there.
Inside that history, there are three people who committed huge sins.
Kim Shin who killed a lot of enemies,
Then alongr with Kim Shin,
the one who commanded to kill the Queen,
Wang Yeo.
And the one who controlled Wang Yeo,
the one who led to the death of Kim Shin and Kim Seon,
Park Joong Hun.
Kim Shin is still alive.
Kim Seon is reincarnated as Sunny.
Then if that is so, I am ... Wang Yeo
or maybe Park Joong Hun.
That's my thought.
The nameless grim reaper...
is Wang Yeo.
But then...
Among those two, whoever it is... I
am probably Kim Shin's enemy.
and Sunny
probably can't date.
Oh! You startled me!
I almost hit you.
I am sorry, you must be startled.
Well... yes, a bit.
What should I do? We're already closed.
I see. So see you next time.
Yes. Come next time.
You must never.
bring any tonics to the queen's quarters.
King above the people./i>
God (Shin) above the King.
They say that "god" (shin in Korean) refers to Kim Shin..
Hello?
Let us... meet.
You said we should break up.
I am in front of your house.
Wait right there. I'm going crazy.
How could you come so suddenly like this?
I was barefaced at home.
I came out to get the ring back.
We still have that excuse left.
What's wrong with your expression?
Didn't you come because you missed me?
- You're right.
- But?
But... I don't know who I'll turn out to be...
with a frightful heart... I'm stepping back.
What are you doing now?
Everything about me is a wrong answer...
I sincerely hope this is the right answer.
- Don't do this.
- I, who am not alive, do not have a name.
Thank you for asking
about my well being.
I said, don't do it.
A grim reaper's kiss... will make you remember your  past life.
In your past life, I am scared as to who I was.
However, I hope you remember only the good memories.
Inside... I wish you also have memories of your brother.
And also, I hope that person is Kim Shin.
Your brother is returning in triumph again.
Between the two of us, whom do you wish would stay alive?
- Your Majesty.
- Answer me.
No, have you already made up your mind?
Well... whether I live or your brother lives, you have nothing to lose.
You are a fool.
Do you wish to die! Why are you dressed like that?
In your heart, you are already mourning.
Bring the Queen's jewelry box!
Why don't you wear them?
Do you think I granted you these for you to keep them here?
I don't know anymore, whether those barbarians at the borders are the enemy or your brother is the enemy!
Park Joong Hun is the enemy.
Your brother who the enemies could not kill. I will kill him today.
Your Majesty!
Your brother's sin is treason!
So you should wear this and greet your traitor brother like a queen.
Whose side are you on? Even once, was there a time when you were on my side?
Even just once, did you have me in your heart?
Even for just a moment, did you ever love...
me?
Do not stand by his side.
That is... the only way you can live.
You'll have to decide.
To  live as my woman or die
as a traitor's sister.
The woman who loves the king
is a traitor's sister.
What is this?
Those that I saw... what are they?
It is... your past life.
Perhaps... inside the memories of your past life, is Kim Shin there?
Perhaps... inside your past life...
am I also there?
For a little bit... can you please look into my eyes?
May all those shining moments of happiness remain
and all the hard... and sad moments, forget them.
Be it in the past life or the present. And also...
forget me, too.
♬   I’ll certainly find you.   ♬
♬   I’ll recognize you   ♬
♬   Wherever you are. Whatever you look like   ♬
You, at least...
♬   I’ll certainly recognize you   ♬
will hopefully have a happy ending like this.
♬  I’ll look at you   ♬
♬   Even at a place without you, even if many years pass by  ♬s
♬   I will not forget.
I'll retain the way you speak to the way you look  ♬
♬   I’ll certainly find you.   ♬
♬    I’ll recognize you   ♬
♬   Even at a place without you, even if many years pass by   ♬
♬   I will not forget.
I'll retain the way you speak to the way you look  ♬
[Closed]
[Open]
Orabeoni, over there.
Why are you staring into my store again?
What is it today again?
Ornament? Cookies? Socks?
It's not that today, but for the payment for the sweet potatoes.
Let's just say that was my treat.
But Orabeoni,
did the King really say I was ugly?
Even though you were a brother in combat ... how could you not send a single reply?
Are you...
Are you really...
I'm sorry for belatedly recognizing you, Orabeoni.
And the promise that I would be happy... I was not able to keep it.
I am sorry, Orabeoni.
Persimmon, traditional shoes, and silk... thank you.
Now, you should come and see this ugly sister of yours more often.
[Ji Eun Tak, age 20]
Uncle down the hall, if you're not busy come and see me.
Something wrong?
Just... there's something that's bothering me.
Did you fight with Uncle again?
No.
Even before that... since that day. Once in a while.
When?
What's wrong? Are you sick?
[Wang Yeo]
If it's that day, it's not because of my uncle. We were in the temple that day.
- Temple?
- Yes.
Uncle lit a lantern. He does that once a year...
I was told they were people whom he was indebted in his heart that's why he does that.
The names were two characters. It was  Kim Seon and...
Wang something... It was in Chinese characters.
What do you call this?
A horse surrounded.
Hey!
Look at her. She's pretending not to see me again.
You bad wench!
It's not that she's pretending not to see me but she really doesn't see me.
Me, too.
Huh?
I am also excited to be picking you up from school.
I'm so excited that you came to pick me up from school.
Forget it.
I have some stuff to think about.
Did something good happen? You seem to be since earlier.
You took so long to ask.
My sister... My Seon has remembered me.
Really? Really?
That's great. But how?
I didn't ask about that. That's right,
how did she remember her past life?
Why do you look like that?
So... first, can you stop the car?
What I'm about to say, don't get mad and just listen.
I have been pondering about it all along.
What is it?
Ahjusshi is someone bigger than I think. I really believe that.
I... met some soul...
and I think it's Park Joong Hun.
How... do you know Park Joong Hun?
I'm sorry. But I overheard when you were talking with Mr. Reaper.
At first, I thought it was just a bad soul...
but I'm not sure what his goal is.
I think that all the strange things happening are related to him.
Boss remembering her past life might be because of him, too.
You did good by telling me. Thank you.
First, I will take you home. Just stay there.
The Goblin's house is the safest.
Yes.
I was avoiding you for 900 years and meeting you like this...
How futile.
Don't worry. I'll get rid of you right away.
But... you avoided me for 900 years, and you shall answer why you appeared before me now.
Being a lowly warrior,
even after living for 900 years, you still have no insight.
You are laughable for not being able to recognize your enemy right beside you.
I am here to let you know personally.
Indeed your tongue is still senile even after 900 years.
I will take your tongue out first.
After that I will rip your body apart.
I will do those now.
You or me... a life of 900 years,s
you can't kill me with a mere sword.
Working as a guardian...
did you think that you became the Almighty?
Don't worry, I'll kill  you somehow for sure.
Because you are so foolish, you lose your life so trivially.
For 20 years while you were rotting away,
he had grown so much that you would not be able to recognize... Yeo.
If you say Yeo's name once more...
Do you know who that grim reaper  beside you is? The one who gave you the sword
and the one who stabbed you with the sword is precisely him.
He is precisely... Wang Yeo.
Insane words...
Your foolish sister fell for him in this lifetime, again.
So pitifully...
You can't even seek revenge.
He said you cried. Why would you cry when even I don't cry?
But who is it? The girl in the painting?
I don't have memories, only feelings exist.
It was just really sad.  My heart ached.
A really super good looking uncle.
Perhaps, have you seen a ring like this?
[Wang Yeo]
[Kim Seon]
In your past life, is the grim reaper in there?
Have you seen the grim reaper?
Look here, Orabeoni. What are you doing in someone else's business place?
Just because I remembered my past life, you must think that I'm really your sister.
He... Is he really Wang Yeo?
I need to go home...
I asked if he really is Wang Yeo?
You... in this lifetime again...
are protecting that dummy.
Is that so? Was I Wang Yeo?
The feeling without memories... was so I didn't forget I was Wang Yeo.
Was it the punishment I gave to myself?
As expected, I seem to be the worst memory..
To you...  to Kim Shin, to him also.
You hear my voice, right?
I also can hear your voice. Very clearly.
General Kim Shin
is here to see Your Majesty.
Timing and Subtitles by The Immortal Team @viki.com
♬  One day or two,  a week    ♬
♬   time passes  but I only see the sky   ♬
♬  Like a clueless man   ♬
[Preview]
These royal garments...
have no owner.
Or perhaps...
this is what you are looking for?
♬   I keep thinking of  you    ♬
♬  Do you feel  ♬
Then...
♬  the same as me?  ♬
...take them.
♬ Whether I want to love you   ♬
♬  as much as I wish or a hopeless desire  ♬
♬ I'll keep doing it. ♬
It's an order.