Goblin
Timing and Subtitles by The Immortal Team @viki.com
- Episode 13 -
As expected, I seem to be the worst memory.
- To you too ... Kim Shin, to him also. You hear my voice, right?
I also can hear your voice. Very clearly.
General Kim Shin...
is here to see Your Majesty.
After 900 years
I am seeing you, Your Majesty.
Whether my eyes were covered by the 900 years of time
or by God's dislike for me, I could not recognize you even though you were next to me.
I see you...
are Wang Yeo.
In the end...
am I him?
Am I...
Wang Yeo?
The young and foolish face...
in the end...
is it me?
The battlefield was always hell, and we came back from that place.
Even the enemies were not able to kill us.
But those men... my young sister...
and my relatives who had no sins...
they were stabbed with swords and shot with arrows in front of my own eyes.
By an order,
with one word from the young and foolish king.
Am I...
him?
So I really am... Wang Yeo?
I still remember every single minute and second of that living hell every day.
But since you have no memory,
it must be comfortable for you.
Even after 900 years has passed...
When did the heavens side with you?
The heavens, as always, are on your side.
What on earth... did I do?
What memory did I erase?
What choice did I make?
Exactly...
how much of a coward was I?
How did it go? Did you meet Park Joong Hun?
I met him. Park Joong Hun and Wang Yeo, too.
Pack your things lightly and come down. Let's go.
- Where to?
- We are going to Chairman Yoo's main house.
Yes. Just give me 10 minutes.
Ji Eun Tak,
why aren't you asking anything? Did you know...
that he was Wang Yeo?
It was something that the deceased told me. I wasn't sure about his intentions,
so I thought it shouldn't be relayed to you carelessly. However,
whether I told you or not, I thought that a fate that's meant to be avoided will be avoided
and if it's a destined meeting, then you would meet it.
I'm sorry.
Pack your things and come out.
We're going to stay here for now. Let the helpers have a break for the time being.
Okay.  But, Uncle, why are you staying here?
We will use a guest room each on the second floor. You don't have to worry.
I... will go to Boss' place.
I'm worried. I'm sure she must be full of questions.
Okay, then I'll ask that of you.
- If something happens...
- I know.
Rest a bit. Opa Deok Hwa  will take me there.
I will?
What is it? Why did you pack your things and leave? Did he fight with Uncle down the hall?
I mean, even if they fought... he should chase Uncle down the hall out. Why leave?
Won't it be consideration? Since Mr. Reaper has no place to go.
Ah... If you put it like that, it's sad.
The phone is turned off. You will be connected to voicemail.
Charges will be made after the beep.
You... in this lifetime,  are protecting that dummy again.
What about Orabeoni? Where is he?
He came out of the house with me.
Then what about that person?
I think... he's at the house.
That means he's at least alive.
I don't think he's someone who was alive to begin with...
Right.
But then, about you getting the memories from your past life...
how did you remember them?
In an erotic way.
What?
It means, let's drink. Soju or beer?
Part-timer, if a person really has four lives...
I have thought about it, and I think I am living the fourth one.
- Why?
- I know at least two lifetimes.
And since I met my Orabeoni
and my lover in this lifetime...
What about you?
Me... I wish the present would be my first life.
Why? In the second life, third life,
and fourth life, you want to meet my Orabeoni, too?
You should have seen his horrible stubbornness during the Goryeo Dynasty.
He knew he would die, so why did he have to return?
He should have just lived by himself.
I mean, it's unfair for us to have to split the utility bill according to the number of people in the household.
Ever since that woman downstairs came, it went up 4000 won more.
She said she got her apartment's deposit and moved here. She's pitiful.
Then what about me?
I just barely got the deposit together to live on my own for the first time in my life.
Well... be it the first or fourth, it's still important.
Isn't that so?
What are you talking about?
And also, the pipes are frozen so water does not come out.
So why do I have to pay equally per person?
Exactly...
It's sad... fate is.
In the end, will they end up paying so dearly?
I really should not be like this...
What is your name?
Give me cash, the card is not accepted.
Send a message that you died a heroic death and I will send a message that I lament it.
I don't want you to die.
Those two  didn't come for your graduation, they came thinking they will meet someone here..
About Reaper Kim from Jangam-dong,
it is just a rumor
but because of some soul's whispers
he held a dying person's...
hand.
Could that spirit be the one that you lost?
That Miscellaneous Omitted Person?
Are you listening?
Senior!
Huh? What did you say?
What's wrong with you these days?
With a Miscellaneous Omitted Person...
what happened?
Here you are.
Seeing your face,
in the end, you held
that hand.
So what did you see?
What sins were in there?
I wasn't in there.
It was only that woman.
That woman, in the past, in some era
was a queen.
In there, was I there?
Perhaps...
is there a hand that brought tonics beside me?
Just like yours, slender and white.
Do you know what was in that tonic?
My sin is your sin.
No. No, there's no way.
The owner of the hands that brought that tonic was you.
How pitiful is this?
Since you have no memories
you don't even recognize yourself.
No...
There's no way.
Don't worry.
I will keep your secret.
More than that, if it gets known that you used your abilities as a reaper
then you will be in trouble.
So both your sins
and my sins...
let's keep them a secret.
As expected, you are Kim Seon.
Even in this life, you will have to die in my hands.
Miscellaneous Omitted Person,
we have met before.
I felt it 20 years ago, too.
You are an evil soul,
a human's dark heart.
You take their evil energy and live off it.
I just change their black greed
to action.
If I covered their eyes...
Is that why you pushed me on that rooftop?
....or if they covered their eyes.
Stop all that nonsense.
What is your name?
Don't waste your time.
Even if you know my name, you won't be able to do anything to me.
Wouldn't that be the reason I am still here after 900 years?
Stop that nonsense...
and say your name.
Do you even know your name that you're asking for mine?
Should I tell you?
You still hold a lowly thing in your hands.
Seeing how you're holding onto her thinking she is precious,
even in this life, too,
she will die without fail.
Does he... know me?
- I thought you'd laugh.
I shouldn't laugh.
Ah! I shouldn't laugh though.
Hello?
Deok Hwa, it's me.
It looks like this.
So the king... gave him this sword....
Seeing how you're not asking anything,
you must be on the Goblin's side.
I'm sorry, but just once...
couldn't you be on my side?
What is it?
This... can you please give it to Sunny?
I thought there shouldn't even be such an excuse...
for me...
I will.
She will... probably not remember me.
The ring... make up an excuse for me.
I'm going.
But... I think she remembers...
Are you still waiting... for the king?
I can't wait now.
Why? Because you remember your past life?
Because the woman who loved the king...
is a traitor's sister.
That's why she died in that person's hands.
I keep getting confused.
The pain that is felt in the chest from the arrow
if it is me...
or if it was me from the past life.
I wonder if he was sad, too.
I only saw him turning his back.
He told me to cherish only happy moments...
but I must have liked all of it.
Seeing how I remember everything.
What about that person?
Did you meet him?
It's all in the past. It's far away in the past since it's a lifetime ago.
For you, it's your past life,
but, for me, it's still my present life,
because I am living that life.
I have nowhere to retreat to,
so I can only go forward.
And he killed you.
He didn't kill me but he killed Kim Seon. Is is not me.
I am Sunny. My life...
is this lifetime.
But if you insist on going forward...
then as always, even crossing lifetimes,
my answer will be the same as then.
Go, Orabeoni.
This time, if I go forward,
what I intend to do to Yeo,
will not be forgiveness.
Don't worry about me.
In this lifetime,
I will really be happy, Orabeoni.
With this sword in his chest...
he lived 900 years.
That person...
We're the Grim Reaper Auditors Team.
Have a seat.
While you were on duty,
we have confirmed that you used your abilities for personal reasons.
Aside from erasing a human's memory,
revealing a name card,
not reporting that your identity was revealed,
giving the memories of a past life back to a human being,
et cetera...
You two had a fight. You didn't see anything.
"I will be going first," say it.
I will be going first.
I will go first.
Can you please look at my eyes?
I'm sorry,
but can you please look at my eyes?
Miscellaneous Omitted Person's name card arrived.
A name card arrived.
Miscellaneous Omitted Person.
There's something I didn't tell you. That I saw Sunny's past life.
-You said it was a secret..
- Sunny seems to be a reincarnation of your younger sister.
I am a grim reaper.
Do you acknowledge everything?
- I do.
- Now that you've acknowledged it,
we will impose a severe disciplinary action.
So face the severity of this matter.
I will accept the punishment.
It won't be so easy to accept.
Grim reapers are those who have
committed great sins in their past lives,
and while living through 200 years of hell,
they are those who chose to erase their memories.
Thus, you should face your sins again.
That is the punishment for all that you have violated.
Since you destroyed the band of traitors and showed them how robust you are,
the people are finally able to sleep well through the night,
so their praise of you has spread throughout the nation.
In case your mouth feels prickly, I ordered wine for you before the meal.
The scent is beautiful and with sweet and bitter flavors
mixed together, it will give you an appetite.
People are worried that your mind and body are not well.
Starting tomorrow, decrease the King's food and present him with a tonic.
Please take it even if it's bitter and make your body and mind
more clear so you can show your robust...
Is this... robust enough?
If ever one day you would be looking for this...
These silk clothes...
who should I put them on?
This beautiful jade ring, whose hand do I put it on?
This fine silk dress ...
who should I put them on? This beautiful jade ring...
whose hand should I put it on?
That beautiful jade ring...
give it to me.
That beautiful jade ring, give it to me.
I have a use for it.
Do you want to have it?
Fine.
Then I should give it to you. Have it.
The fine silk dress has no owner, it seems.
Perhaps...
are you looking for it?
Then...
take it.
Your Majesty, your tonic.
My people, my subjects,
my woman, too...
and even I myself... no one...
loved me. Till the end, from anyone,
I was not able to receive love.
Get more tonic.
I know what is in there.
Pardon?
Let's end it all at once.
The tonic... Bring me more.
It's an order.
Your sins from this world,
and within all your sins, the greatest sin, which is taking your own life,
and 600 years of hell,
you have received all of them back.
Thus, as your duties as a reaper are suspended,
be on standby until your next order is given.
I see I...
was Wang Yeo.
I...
killed them all.
I killed myself...
Kim Seon. Wang Yeo.
What are all your thoughts?
What should I do?
What should I do with him?
Don't touch this again. You have no right to look at this and cry.
I...
gave the sword... to you.
I killed...
I killed everyone. My memory returned.
I...
I was Wang Yeo.
That's right. It was you. You did it. You killed everyone!
You killed and killed and then you...
even killed yourself.
You...  Your woman, your loyal subjects, your Goryeo
and even yourself, you weren't able to protect any of them.
Seon... my young sister protected you with her life.
You should have lived! You should have remained alive to the end and died by my sword!
So that crime of treason that you put on me,
you should have given it proof with your death!
Yes.
My sister probably knew that when my name came out of Park Joong Hun's mouth,
the next would be her name. That it would make a myriad of excuses for you.
So that fool... rather than become your weakness,
on that spot, she died as the sister of a traitor,
to save you.
The ring...
That ring... I...
put it on her in such a cruel way.
In her hand... that ring...
came and went in this lifetime, too... I ask of you...
please...
kill me, please...
As expected,
you want to abandon yourself this time, too.
The sins you have committed... seem to be enough of a punishment for killing yourself...
I thought about it a lot, if it was right that I should give this to you.
So I had it for a couple of days. I'm sorry.
Why would you be? I'm the one who's sorry.
Aren't you going to ask more?
What about? I know it all.
Though... I didn't know I would be receiving it like this.
Someone's regret, guilt, and longing were all mine?
That shaman was quite skilled.
But then... what sin did you commit?
Huh?
You said you are my Goblin Orabeoni's bride. That person and I were lovers in the past...
But why are you entangled with my Orabeoni?
It's just fate.
Do you also do something strange? Do you perhaps fly? Like a bird?
I don't do those things.
An extinction tool to end the Goblin's immortality,
that is the Goblin bride's fate.
The moment you pull the sword out, he will scatter
like dust in the wind. In this world ...
or to another world somewhere, forever.
Part-timer?
I... just can make it rain less,
so it isn't inconvenient for people. I can also make the first snow come sooner
to excite the world's people.
You do the most important work.
But, why did my brother become a goblin?
Because the world needs miracles
- that are weird and beautiful.
-Says who?
Me.
Okay. Then what about the Grim Reaper?
Because people all die in the end?
Since life is splendid because there is death.
Look how good you are with words. As expected of a university student.
Long time no see.
The lowly warrior's sister, a queen from a lowly military family...
Why? Is something there?
You stay out of it. It's not your turn yet. Yours is after that wench's.
Don't come close. Boss, get me the lighter from my coat, quickly!
Lighter? Why a lighter?
Yeo was like my son.
That wench ruined everything.
I will kill her.
- Boss, quickly!
- Alright.
This wench!
Part-timer! What's wrong? What? What is it?
Come to your senses! Part-timer!
Are you okay? Can you walk?
Yes, I'm fine. You must have been startled.
Of course, I was startled. Who were you talking to earlier?
That blue thing, that thing like light, what was that? You said you were human.
Perhaps, are you a human that isn't a human that is similar to a human?
(referring to the song, "Some")
That was a first for me, too. Boss, you go inside first.
I'll come in after seeing your Orabeoni.
He's coming?
If I call him, he has no choice.
How are you?
I missed you.
Me, too.
Have you been well?
I'm sorry. I'll soon come to get you.
The mark on your neck...
Why?
It's almost invisible.
Is that so?
- I wonder why?
- The fact that it's this faded
means that I've put you in that much danger.
And that I might not be able to sense you from now on.
Don't worry. I will be more cautions and careful.
Perhaps, did you see him again, Park Joong Hun?
I did but...
I wasn't his target.
My boss was his target.
That isn't something for you to worry about, either. Just worry about yourself
since someone else will protect my sister.
Just two more days.
Fate is the question I throw. The answer...
you can find it.
We received a question,
and the Grim Reaper and I have to find the answer.
[Park Joong Hun]
[Park Joong Hun, died in the 14th year of the sexagenary cycle, April.]
[He did not respond to the call by the Grim Reaper and fled.]
[I met the man again in 1997
but he fled again and I was not able to capture him.]
What is it about?
The papers for the Miscellaneous Omitted Person I told you about...
The one that got away 20 years ago?
But since I am on standby, I can't process it.
So you have to do it. Listen to me carefully.
- I'm listening.
- He's a soul that's been wandering around for 900 years
and feeding off of the dark emotions of humans. He has managed to stay alive until now.
Even if we come across him, it will be hard with just our own strength.
But if we put his name on the list, I think we can at least control him for now.
Please take care of it quickly. It is an urgent matter.
- By noon tomorrow--
- Today by midnight.
- Thank you.
- I have something to say as well.
I thought you should know. I saw this when I was assigned to your area.
The name on the list, Ji Eun Tak,
this person, isn't she the Goblin's bride from before?
I saw the date, and--
Don't say it. Take your hand off the name card.
I looked at it. You don't know anything.
[Ji Eun Tak]
It's in a week...
It's not your turn yet. Yours is after that wench's.
In the end...
is he saying that he's after me?
[Yoo Shin Woo]
Eun Tak's name card came.
- It must be...
- Related to Park Joong Hun, right?
- In the 14th year--
- That date has no meaning anymore.
- You know that.
- But still...
I thought it would be good if you knew.
Park Joong Hun...
is lingering around my sister.
Protect her.
At least once protect my sister, like how my sister protected you.
That day...
the path to the king was too far...
and in the end I couldn't reach him.
Even though I knew I could not reach him ... even after knowing that... I could only go forward.
That day, for what did you keep on going forward?
When that place....
you knew all too well that it was going to be your grave.
To tell you what I wasn't able to before.
After I received the sword,
I asked to see you countless times, but the king who was also my brother-in-law
only ordered for me to travel west-by-southwest.
Only when you were sure that I would die, you showed your face.
So...
by going that far.... what did you want to say?
- The former king--
- By not taking care of him
I took care of him, tell him that.
He took care of you by not caring for you.
From the late king who was your half-brother,
from your lover who was my sister, from me who protected your Goryeo,
that you received love.
And to tell you just one thing, "Since I will lay down this sword filled with rage and apprehension,
so behead Park Joong Hun."
Just that one thing...
But that sword...
I didn't know would be in my chest, instead.
How could it...?
It's been 900 years for you and I both.
You can't kill me with a mere sword.
I came this far....
but I end up holding this sword again.
What's wrong?
Is the sword hurting again?
The purpose of this sword, in the end...
was that.
To take out Park Joong Hun.
Are you an engineer?
The final point to a phone number... are the lips.
♫ When I look at you  ♫
♫ I don't know why My tears keep falling ♫
I'm going crazy, seriously.
You need to look pretty. Stop crying.
♫ Were you coming back to me? ♫
♫  This love which can't be avoided♫
♫  I love you, love you, love you ♫
♫ I could feel that we are fated to be ♫
♫ And I miss you, miss you ♫
♫   You are my fated person ♫
♫  Why do you look at me with those sad eyes? ♫
♫Don’t cry  ♫
♫ Didn't you recognize me at first glance? ♫
- Why do you keep following me?
♫ Why didn't you come to me til now? ♫
It's been a few days already. Are you a stalker?
♫ I love you, love you, love you > ♫
It's nothing like that.
I think our paths just cross by chance...
Thanks to you, it felt like I was having a date
with Mr. Kim Woo Bin.
♫ And I miss you, miss you ♫
Exactly why?
How could you remember?
Because you put the wrong spell on me.
The hard and sad moments... forget them.
Be it the past life or the present life.
And also... forget me, too.
♫ Don't leave my side. ♫
And in this way... I hope that at least you will have a happy ending.
♫ Don’t leave my side ♫
Asking me to forget you after telling me to forget everything
except for happy moments... It doesn't make sense.
All the moments that you were in... even the sad and hard moments, everything...
Even those moments, I liked them all.
So... protecting you with my death... did it become a happy ending for you?
Looking at how young you look now, it seems like you weren't able to live long.
Every day... with bitter regret...
I longed for you.
Then why, if you were going to do that?
Because I was foolish.
I wish you had realized it sooner.
But how did I...
even in this lifetime, too, fall for you?
Maybe because your royal face is so bright?
Here.
Let's really break up.
I won't fall for you in this lifetime...
The punishment that I can give you... is only this.
Goodbye, Your Majesty.
Give it to me!
You don't even have money, so how did you get snacks? Did you steal?
No! My grandmother bought it for me!
Did she get it by begging?
Don't put my grandmother down! Gust of wind!
He's doing this again. Seriously...
Hey! That's not how you do gust of wind. You do it like this.
Gust of wind!
Hey, you rascals, again!
What? It was real?
Are you okay?
Noona, how did you know?
You said to me last time that I would be able to shoot a real gust of wind.
I really shot it! Gust of wind!
When I was your age, I also thought how I should become a Goblin's bride
and I really became one.
But it's a secret. Gusty winds and such are very dangerous so you can't just shoot it anywhere.
Understand?
I will tell just my grandmother.
That's pretty cool.
If it's cool then let's go on a trip.
- Wow!
- Why?
My heart just dropped.
That's good. You said you liked that.
You seem to be in a good mood.
Let's do that. Let's go on a trip.
♫ Through the endless daydream  ♫
♫ I saw you on the way back ♫
♫ There I walk with you in my arms ♫
♫ Through the blurry ♫
- Mister.
♫ Darkness ♫
♫ Who's veiling on the twilight ♫
♫ We've been far away from my fears ♫
♫ Somewhere else I'll see you ♫
♬  Our days be like a blossom   ♬
♬   Blooming all around you, so bright ♬
♬   All around me is your light. With you everything so shines    ♬
- It's nice.
♬  How come we’ll leave all behind?   ♬Cause your love is falling on my heart
♬   And I’m falling for you... Falling with broken wings again   ♬
♬  Hush now, my angel.  I will always be with you   ♬
♬  In your pretty smile, in a glow of tears    ♬
- I have a gift.
♬ Out across the frosty night, I’ll be there with you ♬
This is enough. This is already perfect enough.
♬   Maybe you‘ll always breath in me    ♬
I bet not.
Oh! This.
Now that you are an adult, remember. Usually each person gets one.
So that's why I forged it,
but then I got caught.
But which one is the original?
So it's that one?
- Give me that.
- I don't want to.
I want to have that!
B grants A's wish every year on the first snow,
because A would be waiting.
Awesome!
It's snowing.
It's the first snow, Mister!
Do you think I should be sad for a thousand years?
Do you think I'm in pain every day?
I'm just an energetic goblin who humbly accepts his fate and lives cheerfully..
Now I am a strong Goblin's bride who's living her life bravely while accepting her fate.
Where would you find sadness that goes on for thousands of years?
Where would you find a love that goes on for thousands of years?
I give one vote that there is one.
Which side are you going to put it on? On sadness or love?
A permission that's like an excuse ...
I wish I had it.
With that excuse... I wish I could continue to live
with you.
Sad love.
Mr. Yoo Deok Hwa!
Card! My card!
Did you sleep well? This is not your house but a workplace.
Let's please set your mind on the job!
I'm sorry.
Welcome, customers.
You must be here to look for a bed.
You have good taste. To tell you about this bed...
If you lie down, you would fall asleep right away.
Mr. Yoo Deok Hwa...get up immediately!
I'm sorry.
I will miss you a lot.
♫ Please touch my heart just once ♫
Here's your order.
♫ It’s cold all day long ♫
Welcome. Have a seat there.
Since you look peaceful, you look healthy...
then that is enough.
Live well as you in this lifetime.
♫ Please call quietly just once ♫
♫ My name you used to call countlessly ♫
♫ Going back to etenity, just one day, no ♫
♫ If I could see just one minute ♫
♫ If you can, I’ll endure it ♫
♫ At the end of the waiting, I hope you’ll be standing there ♫
♫ My memories of you are like a painting ♫
♫ A day like a gift, I’ve waited for so long ♫
- Now, even if I just think of you you're right in front of me.
♫ I'll go a long time ♫
- I just thought of you.
♫ to re you ♫
- What brings you here?
♫ You are the first snow in my heart ♫
I missed you...
and I have a favor, too.
Go ahead.
It concerns Park Joong Hun.
I had already been thinking about that, and I was curious.
Why did he have to appear now? He was wandering for 900 years, so why would he appear now?
That...
Yeah, because of that...
You have to be brave for just a moment. Can you do it?
I am the Goblin's bride.
Listen well. I will be calling in a few moments.
Summon me right away at that moment.
That's a piece of gum. (easy)
♫ How can I get over you ♫
♫ Why do we have to be apart ♫
I will be back.
♫ We go where... apart... ♫
Didn't I tell you already...
you can't take me out with a mere sword made from water.
I know that.
So should we go to our last battle?
How do you know where I will be going?
But buckwheat flowers... what do they mean?
Lovers.
As expected, you can't see me anymore.
[Ji Eun Tak: 20 years old,  March 11, 2017,  18:47. Heart attack.]
It was because of me.
He was waiting for my mark to disappear...
Impressive.
However, it's too late.
By using me...
he plans to take the sword out.
It's now. Summon me.
Don't be resentful.
This is your fate.
Are you alright?
Ji Eun Tak!
I found out. I found out the reason why he appeared now.
Strike me. Hurry.
It will be the end if he goes into my body. He's trying to use my hands to take the sword out!
If not for you... I was fated to die anyway...
Hurry up and strike me!
What this child said was right. You should have killed her.
Now it's either you die or I die.
But because you keep looking back...
I guess you will die by my hands.
Park Joong Hun,
a deceased should answer the call of the Grim Reaper.
- Insolent!
- Park Joong Hun!
Park Joong Hun!
So I go like this.
However, it is not for naught since I killed you again.
Look.
In the end... it is destruction.
Please forgive me.
I am able only now able to notify you
of my dying a heroic death.
You can't!
No! No!
♬   And I'm here just like I used to be   ♬
♬   You are here always   ♬
♬   with me   ♬
♬   All my fears   ♬
Because I met you, this life...
was a reward.
No, I don't want this...
Please...
♬   No matter   ♬
You promised you wouldn't let go of my hand.
You promised.
I will come as rain...
♬   When you feel so lonely  ♬
I will come as the first snow.
So that I could at least do that...
♬   I'll be here   ♬
I will beg God.
Don't!
Don't go like that!
I love you...
I love you. I love you.
I do, too.
♬   If I could fly above the clouds   ♬
I love you.
♬   I can hold you for a while  ♬
Even that...
♬   To let you feel my pulse   ♬
I already did that.
♬   Still here all alone   ♬
♬   My whole life and all my heart   ♬
♬   You're my whole life and all my heart   ♬
♬   And I'm here, home, home with you.   ♬
♫ I did not know before I held you in my arms  ♫
♫  That the world I remained in ♫
No!
♫  is so glorious ♫
♫ Reached by a person with a small breath ♫
♫ The love that called me without fear♫
♫ I loved so very much.   ♫
♫ Watching over you and being excited.   ♫
♫  Being ridiculously jealous. ♫
♫  All the ordinary moments ♫
♫  A dark eternity ♫
♫  In that long wait ♫
♫ You fell like the sunshine ♫
Goblin
Timing and Subtitles by The Immortal Team @viki.com
♫  I did not know before I let you go ♫
♫  The world I remained in  is so desolate.♫
♫  This place where beautiful flowers are about to bloom♫
♫  and the season that you will never be again ♫
♫  I became greedy to live with you and grow old ♫
In end I...
♫ Holding the wrinkled hands ♫
...made that decision.
♫ Only once blessed.  That brief encounter has passed ♫
Now, I understand.
♫ You cried like rain ♫
♫ I will not forget ♫