Never let your guard down on COUPLE PALACE.
- It's huge these days. - It's huge.
- A lot of people are so into this. - Right.
One person who's like that is Cha Tae Hyun.
- He always messages me. - Really?
He's like, "Why are they doing that?"
(He can't help but ask.)
Any couple you were curious about?
Jae Keun and Jin Ju.
(Three women are tangled up with Jae Keun.)
And Hye Won.
Jae Keun is really popular.
I can't wait to find out...
how it will be resolved.
I'm curious about Sin Da and Jung Won.
I don't know what happened to them.
They suddenly moved to the couple zone.
(Sin Da and Jung Won suddenly moved to the couple zone.)
And Ji Woong just happened to...
sit next to her.
I wonder if she'll be swayed or become firmer.
That will be something to watch.
I'm curious about...
how they decided to get up to the couple zone.
(Day-2, couple zone)
- What's this? - What?
(The couples are surprised by something.)
Why are you surprised?
Marriage exam?
(There's a marriage exam in the couple zone)
- What exam? - Marriage exam.
That marriage exam is important...
because they can check each other's values through this.
- That's right. - It's the best.
Marriage exam.
It's cute.
(The couples start taking their marriage exam!)
This is hard.
(Would you let your spouse go out to meet their friend at 2am?)
Of course not.
At 2am in the morning?
Not even your mom would let you go out at 2am.
(A. I won't let them go. B. I'll go out with them.)
One, two, three.
- A. - A.
- We matched. - But I don't like...
any of these answers.
I'd just let him go.
- You'd let him go? - Yes.
Wouldn't you feel offended if I stopped you from going out?
- Letting you go out... - Can I ask you an extreme question?
Don't do it.
- At 2am, - A woman? A female friend?
what if your spouse wants to go out to see Sin Da?
What's wrong with him?
- Why would he bring her up? - Why all of a sudden?
That's such a strange example.
What if your spouse wants to go out to see Sin Da?
- That's... - Would you go with him?
- That's a bit... - A, you'd let him go out.
B, you'd go with him.
I'd feel uncomfortable, but I trust him.
That's why I'd let him go alone.
Okay, it means that I have one chance.
I got it.
- I'm kidding. - She got serious.
Yes, that's understandable.
I haven't said that I'd marry you yet.
- What? - No, she hasn't.
That was a good comeback.
Good job.
(I'd let my spouse know if I won the lottery.)
"I'd let my spouse know if I won the lottery. Yes or no."
- One, two, three. - Two, three.
- Yes. - Yes.
"The parents of your spouse will buy a house for you...
but only if you give them the passcode to the door."
- One, two, three. No. - One, two, three. No.
(They both say no.)
- I wouldn't accept the house. - Me neither.
"The parents of your spouse will buy a house for you...
but only if you give them the passcode to the door."
I'd be very grateful.
- I'd be okay with that. - I'd thank them.
Isn't that a given?
They bought the house for us, so I should let them know.
There's nothing to worry about Yeong Seok and Soo Min.
They're so therapeutic.
That's right.
- Let him know my phone passcode? - I don't think so.
Me neither.
- They both agree on everything. - Right.
Among all the people on COUPLE PALACE,
I think you're the most compatible for me.
- Regardless of gender. - Yes.
I was looking for...
the male version of me to marry.
That's exactly who he is.
You're cute.
- Am I cute? - Yes.
I like holding hands.
I like it too.
I'm so jealous.
You're the most beautiful.
(Yeong Seok expresses himself to Soo Min without hindrance.)
- Gosh. - "You're the most beautiful?"
My goodness. I want to hear that every day.
He took care of me a lot.
Everyone told me how he looked at me in adoration.
There's adoration in Yeong Seok's eyes.
- It's so therapeutic to watch them. - Right.
- There's no conflict at all. - It's nice.
It's very nice.
(Day-2, single zone)
Ye Rin.
Many people are rooting for Ye Rin.
What do you think of the model from Canada?
I like him. He's nice.
(During Round 3, speed date)
You have a beautiful voice.
(Kyung Seok and Ye Rin went on a date.)
(After making a connection, they came to Palace Week together.)
Go and talk to him.
I'm bad at expressing myself in the beginning stages.
It was still hard for me at Palace Week.
In the single zone... I mean, in the couple zone,
people hold hands.
- I want to hold hands too. - Really?
- Try this. - It's the first time.
"Can we compare our hand sizes?"
Then put your hands together.
As soon as you do, hold his hand.
Why are you getting excited when it's just me?
- This is annoying. - This is very...
You should learn.
Can I really do that?
Of course. What's the problem? It isn't illegal.
That's cute.
They look like high school students on a school trip.
Right. They're very shy when they talk.
Give me some more helpful advice.
First of all, you act like you're always at work.
You talk like you're explaining something to a client.
- I do? - Yes.
- Really? - Yes.
Don't just sit there but try crossing your legs.
- Twist your body like this. - This is so interesting.
Twist?
Try to touch him with your foot.
- Goodness. - Or your shoulder.
(100 percent focused)
- Twist. - Twist.
Cross your legs. Get close to him.
I'll try it all tomorrow.
I've never flirted with anyone before.
I want to be more proactive this time.
Ye Rin is only thinking about how to flirt.
Cross your legs. Twist.
(Kyung Seok and Ye Rin came upstairs for a private chat.)
- Oh, wow. - I don't want to go home.
When I go home...
Ye Rin keeps waiting for the right time to flirt.
Ye Rin, it's right now.
It could be tiring,
so let's drink some caffeine.
I appreciate it. Thank you so much.
Do you have inner-fold double eyelids?
- Yes. - I like inner-fold double eyelids.
- Really? - When you look at someone,
- you often look at their eyes. - Right.
She's getting closer to him.
- We don't look at their hands. - Right.
There are some people with murky eyes.
Around 11 o'clock, my eyes will become murky.
Really?
That's okay.
You'll feel hazy.
I don't know if I did a good job.
She's cute.
Whom have you talked a lot with?
Only you.
Haven't you talked with someone else 1-on-1?
Honestly, I hardly talked with men.
I don't really know who is who.
Ye Rin is only talking about Kyung Seok,
and she's only curious about him.
I think...
I'm not sure, but it's best to act how you feel.
Without feeling much pressure.
I'm timid.
- Really? - Gosh.
It's okay.
I need to use the restroom.
Let's go.
(Their conversation ended short contrary to Ye Rin's wishes.)
The chat is over.
He doesn't notice Ye Rin's feelings at all.
It's not that he doesn't notice.
Her enthusiasm seems to make him push her away.
That's how I see it.
But Ye Rin is so pretty.
(After her conversation with Kyung Seok,)
(Ye Rin has a lot on her mind.)
I had to think a lot about it.
Last year, I was eliminated quite fast,
so it was disappointing.
Ye Rin is trying to talk to Kyung Seok again.
She seems to be looking for him.
I want to meet a good person this time.
That's why I wanted to talk to him again.
Where is he?
(While she was looking for Kyung Seok)
I think so.
- Goodness. - What?
(He was chatting with Soo Jin.)
Oh, no.
He's talking with Soo Jin.
She slipped out quickly as if she didn't see them.
She turned away like she didn't see them.
To avoid making him feel uncomfortable, right?
(Kyung Seok and Ye Rin's conversation a few hours ago)
I saw you on a date with someone.
Is she Number 25?
- Is it her? - The one who came as the catfish.
Why Number 25?
Men's speed trains went first, right?
- Right. - She chose me that time.
That's when we went on a date together.
When I mustered up the courage to talk to him,
reality hit me.
Oh, no.
What do I do?
She couldn't try...
any of the flirting techniques that she had prepared.
- I know. - She only talked about his eyelids.
(At that moment, the alarm goes off in the single zone.)
Now, a secret favorability vote will start.
What's this again?
Please choose two people you want to see the most right now.
Two people?
The result will be applied to your next date.
(Sighing)
Two people? It's so easy for me.
The voting result will not be revealed.
It won't be revealed?
I guess it really is a secret.
It's a chance to get to know the person of their choice...
one more time without pressure.
(The secret favorability vote ends.)
They will be going on dates outdoors.
- Yes. - They could compare...
the person that likes them...
with the person that they like.
They could find out with whom they get along better.
To whom they lean towards will be more clear.
They must be excited about their date outdoors.
(Which couple will go on a date outdoors?)
- First... - Who is it?
- It's Sang Gyeong. - Sang Gyeong.
Who is he going on a date with?
(Sang Gyeong's date is?)
Hello.
This is amazing.
- Gosh, hello. - Soo Jin?
Hello. Are we going on an outdoor date?
I think so.
(How did she end up going on an outdoor date with Sang Gyeong?)
(In Round 3, Soo Jin rejected Kun Hee.)
I voted for Number 24.
(She had Sang Gyeong in mind.)
Soo Jin had Sang Gyeong in mind,
so she refused Kun Hee during Round Three.
(Soo Jin came to Palace Week as an additional resident.)
Hello.
May I sit here?
(The first person to catch her attention...)
(Number 24, Lee Sang Gyeong)
Soo Jin has always been aware of Sang Gyeong.
The person I'm most interested in from the single zone is Sang Gyeong.
The one who's proactive will gain love.
Have you been on an outdoor date?
- No. - Am I your first date?
Yes.
- She's smiling with her eyes. - She's smiling with her eyes.
She must be so happy.
Oh, wow.
(The door opens again?)
- I'll sit in the back. - No, stay there.
(There's another girl who's joining Sang Gyeong and Soo Jin.)
Someone else is here. I guess it's not a 1-on-1 date.
Are the three of us going on a date?
The three of us on a date?
What's going on?
- This is crazy. - What a bummer.
I was happy thinking it would be just the two of us.
- It's Jin Ju. - I see.
Sang Gyeong is really popular.
Right.
I'm very shocked right now.
- Are you happy? - How do you feel?
You're happy. Aren't you happy?
You're going on a date with two women.
I wasn't sure what was going on.
I didn't even know what to say.
I was having a mental breakdown.
(How will their date turn out?)
I was his first wife, though.
Usually, the concubines have more power.
(Usually, the concubines have more power.)
But still. Our tie can't be broken that easily.
A newcomer can drive out the old-timer.
Am I too mean?
They entered Palace Week because they matched.
But I'm the third wheel.
I need to mess things up.
I'm in trouble now, aren't I?
I think Soo Jin is determined to get her way.
Here's the thing. Sang Gyeong and Jin Ju...
spent more time together.
- Right. - For Soo Jin to insert herself...
between them,
- she will have to work hard. - Make sense.
(The three of them arrive at the date spot.)
Nonetheless, let's pick some delicious dishes.
This looks tasty.
Should we order both?
- Yes. - Let's order both.
Should we order both and share them?
We're turning quite greedy.
You say that now, but you won't eat a lot, right?
Her portion is small.
I noticed that you didn't finish your breakfast.
I'm not sure if it was because the food wasn't good.
I went for seconds.
I bet I ate the most among the women.
My gosh. Look at that.
I filled up my rice bowl,
- Okay. - but I wasn't full.
I see.
What kind of food do you not like?
I'm good with anything.
There isn't anything I can't eat. Seriously.
- I can literally eat everything. - Really?
That's impressive.
I like big eaters.
- Is that so? - Yes.
- You guys are very different. - Yes.
- Is there anything you can't eat? - Me?
First of all, I don't like gukbap.
- Oh, no. - Really?
Oh, no.
A lot of men like gukbap.
- Gukbap. - I love gukbap.
My gosh.
My favorite dish is seolleongtang.
It makes me sound like an old man.
(Feeling a strange sense of despair)
Gukbap is like the national anthem for men.
- Gukbap is the national anthem? - Yes. That's how important it is.
Some people might think I'm making a fuss.
But when I have gukbap, I don't mix rice in the soup.
Same here. I only scoop up the broth like this.
Because there's too much salt in the broth.
- Same here. - I always leave some broth.
(The gukbap talk continues between Jin Ju and Sang Gyeong.)
(Soo Jin can't get a word in.)
A sense of alienation? Jealousy?
It was uncomfortable.
(The food is served to alleviate her discomfort.)
- Thank you. - Seriously.
- Enjoy. - Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
Sang Gyeong, do you want some of this?
Should I give you some of my pasta?
(Jin Ju's already serving Sang Gyeong.)
- She's already... - She's quick.
- She's already serving him. - Have that first.
I'll eat this first. I'll get more later.
- Then I'll just go ahead and eat. - Yes.
Dig in. Go ahead.
I was cutting the pizza.
Soo Jin asked him if he wanted the pasta.
He ate my pizza first.
I loved that.
(The mood is very different for these two women.)
Oh, no. Poor Soo Jin.
Of course, she's thirsty.
- This just crossed my mind. - Yes.
Jin Ju, what about me do you find attractive?
(His question catches her by surprise.)
All of a sudden, he asked me what I liked about him.
He asked me that.
There were three of us at the table,
but to me, it felt like he chose me.
Jin Ju, what about me do you find attractive?
(Right now?)
Do I have to answer in public like this?
No, you don't have to answer it. But that just crossed my mind.
- Yeah? I'll tell you later. - Yes.
Okay. Thank you.
(Things are getting romantic between Sang Gyeong and Jin Ju.)
Gosh, it looks like it's only the two of them at the restaurant.
They click so well.
- Right. - Soo Jin has nothing to say.
I'll stop talking.
Why not? Come on, talk.
It's...
I don't know.
It didn't feel like he was expressing any interest in me.
So I don't know what to do.
(Feeling dazed)
When the 3 of them are on a date, but the 2 of them click so well,
- it feels so awkward. - Right. You have nothing to say.
(Another outdoor date is taking place here.)
There's another one.
It's Young Taek.
- Joo Hee. - My gosh. No.
This is crazy.
- Joo Hee. Can we talk for a bit? - Yes?
(He approached Joo Hee and pulled her away for a chat.)
(He carefully expressed his interest in Joo Hee.)
I was shaking like crazy. I was a baby bird.
I was shaking.
You are
A lot of musicians bring their dates to their studios where they work...
- Right. - when they want to impress them.
- That's right. - Yes.
He's indeed working in it.
I've been there and done that.
(She's been there.)
Right. I mentioned you in my interview.
The guy who sang "Sudden Shower."
You are a present to me
But the song suits you...
because you resemble Byeon Woo Seok.
- I resemble Byeon Woo Seok? - Yes.
I mean, you have a similar vibe.
He's the one whom we'd call a sweet big dog.
He's the perfect example of it.
Why? Sweet? Big?
No, medium-sized?
- A Samoyed! - So...
- A Samoyed? - You're a Samoyed.
Yes, that's it. So cute.
Joo Hee is great at complimenting people.
- Right. - She has...
this talent of making anything uncomfortable disappear.
That's her charm.
Well, things seem to be going so well for them.
But all I see is Jae Yeon sitting in the empty middle seat.
Right!
It feels as if his spirit is sitting there.
- Poor Jae Yeon. - Yes.
What's Jae Yeon doing right now?
(Meanwhile, what's Jae Yeon up to?)
(The single zone)
(Jae Yeon and Na Kyung are talking.)
Seriously. You're a rare find.
This is the vibe I'm getting.
- She seems... - Okay?
a bit uncomfortable because I'm too forward with my feelings.
- You think so? - I'm not sure...
- if it's just in my head. - Okay.
I noticed that she began to take an interest...
- That's possible. - in other people.
But I could be getting in her way.
- If she is... - I see.
- serious about it... - Gosh, that's going too far now.
I could be burdening her emotionally.
She could be interested in me.
But if she can't let go of me because she feels guilty...
No way. Come on.
If that's the case, I should...
(If that's how she feels, I should step back.)
This isn't easy.
- Right. - It's heartbreaking.
If he feels that he's burdening her...
- with his feelings... - Right.
- If he's burdening her... - Right.
- Gosh. - Then that's frustrating.
What if he keeps thinking like this and leaves her?
That's a possibility.
(Jin Ju and Sang Gyeong came back from the outdoor date.)
I want to go out.
- I'm getting a slight cabin fever. - Right?
Do you want to step out?
- I want to step on the snow. - Same here.
Just that, nothing else.
- It's so cool out. Fresh. - My gosh, it's...
The snow's so soft, right?
It feels great.
I love it here.
(The men and women in the single zone...)
(go back to their childhood and have fun with the snow fight.)
So funny!
(They're having more fun because they're together.)
We were having a snow fight.
I still have the innocence of childhood at heart.
I like someone who can enjoy these activities with me.
Can we make a snowman?
- Do you want to make one? - Let's make one.
There's Hye Won.
- Gosh, you're so good! - She saw them.
- It's so easy to clump the snow. - Gosh, she saw them.
- Oh, no. - My gosh.
Jae Keun and Jin Ju were getting along so well.
I kept observing them.
Gosh, Sang Gyeong saw them too.
He should go out.
We'll make a snowman for the show.
(Sang Gyeong comes out to look for Jin Ju.)
- Help me. - Okay.
The body and the face.
(No need to fret, Sang Gyeong is rolling the snow.)
- Could you put it on here? - Oh?
Put it there, please.
(You want me to lift it?)
He can't lift heavy things. I have to lift it for him.
(Hands empty)
- But it's lopsided. - My gosh.
- That's the body. - Gosh, that's crazy.
(There's another one.)
- Let's make a three-layered Olaf. - That's...
(This one is even bigger than the other one.)
- He can't lift heavy things. - He can't lift that.
We need to carry this.
- I'll do it. - Hold on.
- Okay. - Okay.
- My gosh. - You're so cool. Okay.
- This is scary. - Okay.
(Sang Gyeong just cheers them on.)
- That's crazy. - One more.
- That's cool. - You're so strong.
- I had fun thanks to you. - Seriously.
I didn't know this many people would be good at building snowmen.
(Just like the piled-up snow, they begin to bond more deeply.)
- Did you talk to a lot of people? - Yes, sort of.
Sang Gyeong is a cautious type too.
- Right. - Yes.
- You have different charms. - Me...
- A retriever I'd like to adopt. - I do have other charms.
- You want to adopt me? - Yes.
- Let's go home. - My gosh. Really?
Adopt me then.
My goodness.
- I do want to adopt you. - You...
You just have to feed me regularly. I'll be fine.
- Really? That's great. - I'll go out and make money.
That's great.
Gosh, I'm not sure about these two.
I can't predict how things will go...
- in the single zone. - Totally.
I started to get to know you...
since yesterday. Right?
Yes. That's right.
To me, you came out of nowhere like a comet.
I see.
- By the way, - So the truth is...
- I feel the same way about you. - Yes.
To me, you showed up out of the blue like a comet.
I came here with a light heart.
But when we were on the marriage-focused date,
you and I clicked so well.
- You were exactly what I imagined. - Yes.
- So... - This is hard.
- My gosh. - Isn't that Hye Won?
Hye Won lowered her head. Oh, no.
So...
(The two of them continue their conversation.)
To be honest, I'm attracted to you.
- We're so compatible. - Right.
- We just met. - Right.
- But we're so compatible. - Yes.
After getting that feeling...
Let's be honest. You and Sang Gyeong...
- have been going on dates... - Right.
consistently from the beginning.
I see.
(Sang Gyeong walks past them this time.)
- Gosh, it's Sang Gyeong. - It's Sang Gyeong.
You look cute.
Yes.
It's clear that Sang Gyeong...
keeps checking what she's up to.
He keeps glancing at her.
(Meanwhile, in the women's lounge...)
What was he like? The professor.
He's such a great guy.
(Sang Joon has a cheerful charm.)
But I don't find him handsome.
- That's so important. - Yes.
Right. It's like...
- You have to be attracted to him. - Right.
I don't find him attractive.
- That's the most important. - Yes.
How can you date him then?
If you can't kiss him, you can't date him.
- My gosh. - I...
- What is it? - I thought of "The Frog Prince."
(The Frog Prince has come to life from the fairy tale.)
A lot of people check the possibility of dating...
by considering whether they can be physically intimate with someone.
- A lot of people use that... - Right.
- as their standard. - Yes.
I decided to muster up my courage today.
I'll do my best today.
- Anyway, I'll give it a try. - I'll try it.
(When Jae Keun walked in as the additional resident,)
(she noticed that she was happy.)
- I see. She's interested in him? - Really?
(Seo Hee was frustrated when he had breakfast with another woman.)
Seo Hee declared that she'd go after him.
- Could you give me a moment? - Sure.
Since I made up my mind,
I had to give it a try.
I should do whatever I can.
(The two of them went to talk in private.)
There's something I want to give you.
What is it?
It's nothing much.
What's that?
I made it myself.
- You made it? - Yes.
She made it herself. That's so cute.
This is so cute.
- What is this? A puppy? - Yes.
(Jae Keun's keyword was a sweet, large dog.)
Well, when I realized that you were eliminated from the show,
this...
crossed my mind.
"I'll end up meeting him no matter what."
- But I was eliminated by then. - Right.
She had no idea he'd come,
- but she still made the doll. - Right.
That's so cute.
I wanted to give it to you someday.
I brought it with me just in case.
I'm happy that I can give it to you.
- Thank you so much. - Sure.
She made a doll for me.
I thought that she couldn't be faking it.
I could feel how sincere she was about me. Seriously.
Well, this is...
To be honest, when I first met you,
I was so surprised.
And that someone like you...
chose me for your date.
In the beginning, it felt surreal.
That's how I felt.
So I was thrilled.
But to be honest,
I'm quite indecisive.
I'm sure you felt it too.
Actually, putting aside the fact that I'm your fan,
I thought the right thing to do here was to make up my mind.
To be honest with you, right now,
I'm interested in getting to know Jin Ju more.
I see.
I wanted to get to know her more,
so I decided to have breakfast with her.
And Female Number 19...
She came as a catfish.
Out of the blue, she gave me her vote.
So I was like, "What's going on?"
I was flustered when it happened.
Then did you just turn me down?
- Turn you down? So... - No?
Seriously. I...
No? Not yet, right?
There's hope for me, right?
No?
So...
for now...
Well, this is...
(Do you not even have an ounce of interest in me?)
No. So my conclusion is...
that...
I'll go with the person I feel more drawn to.
(It will be either Jin Ju or Hye Won.)
That will be my decision.
At first, I wasn't sure if I was interested...
or if I was just being a fan.
I didn't know what I was feeling then.
I didn't think it'd be fair...
if I kept stringing her along.
I thought it was fair to tell her how I felt.
I understand.
(Seo Hee goes back disappointed.)
(The connection between Jae Keun and Seo Hee began from Round 1.)
The person I want to get to know more...
I wrote down some topics.
The one I want to have more conversations with is Jae Keun.
I was happy to see Male Number Three the most.
I was happy.
I don't think I gave my 100 percent.
I didn't know I'd be this foolish.
It's disappointing.
Seo Hee mustered up her courage and expressed her interest.
But Jae Keun turned her down.
- Yes. He told her how he felt. - Yes.
But...
- this could be better for her. - Yes. I agree.
(Seo Hee comes back to the women's lounge...)
(after sorting out her feelings.)
He turned me down.
Jae Keun turned you down?
Just like that?
There's nothing I can do if we don't click.
- You expressed yourself boldly. - Yes.
Jae Keun will go after Jin Ju.
(Seo Hee says that he will only focus on Jin Ju.)
Why would she say that? That's not true.
- No! He's also interested... - What? That's not true!
- in Hye Won. - That's...
- It will cause a misunderstanding. - He named Jin Ju and Hye Won.
Her mind was all over the place.
She couldn't hear the last part.
Oh, my goodness.
(Meanwhile, Jae Keun is looking for someone.)
I don't know how Female Number 19 feels.
I wanted to talk to her more. I was curious about her.
(Wherever he goes, Hye Won is nowhere to be seen.)
Male Number Three, Jae Keun...
He will go after Jin Ju.
- What is this? - I don't know.
What's going on?
I was trying to find her, but I guess I wasn't any good.
(The two of them miss each other with a misunderstanding brewing.)
This misunderstanding can be cleared up...
- if they just talk to each other. - Right.
But if this keeps going, it won't be good.
- I'm worried. - Hye Won is very careful.
- Right. - She rarely talks.
- Right. - Yes.
(The night of Day Two rolls in.)
They're not back.
Who still hasn't returned?
- Male Number 13. - And Joo Hee.
- Joo Hee left too? - The two of them?
- They're still not back? - Still?
- Right. - That's why Jae Yeon...
- Over there. - Right. Jae Yeon was like...
Joo Hee hates smokers. So Jae Yeon...
even quit smoking for her.
- It's been a week. - That's true love.
- He smokes a lot. - It's been a week.
But he didn't smoke here.
Wow, that's amazing.
But they just met.
I didn't know his feelings could get serious this quickly.
I mean, it's bothering Jae Yeon. But Sang Gyeong...
- is quite bothered by that too. - Yes. Right.
Jae Yeon is back.
(Jae Yeon enters.)
- My gosh. - She's back.
- My gosh. - Look who's here.
You're back from your date.
- Look who's here. - Where have you been?
How did you know?
Was it Male Number 13?
I was just making a guess.
You were making a guess,
- but you got it right. - Right.
I'm worried because this might be hard on Jae Yeon.
I've been feeling down today.
- But can't you just have fun? - What?
You need to check out other people too.
I didn't know I'd be like this either.
You're a total catch.
Why won't you hang out with other women?
I just...
want to stick to what I've been doing so far.
Someone who can appreciate that might be the one.
- Right. - That's what destiny is.
Right.
I think it's a difference of personalities.
- That's Jae Yeon. That's who he is. - Yes.
- He's loyal. - Yes.
- Yes, it looks like it. - Just goes for one person.
Did you go outside?
- To his workplace. - Oh, his workplace!
And Young Taek even sang for her.
That's incredible.
Was it an existing song or your own song?
- My own song. - That's so cool.
(They're talking about Young Taek and Joo Hee's date.)
That's awesome.
I should invite her and show her how I pull out teeth.
Pull them out properly.
Yes, show her your specialty.
- Pull them out properly. - Yes, show her.
(Another announcement begins in the single zone.)
What's that?
The potential proposal vote will begin now.
- What's that about? - Already?
In the potential proposal vote, you will vote for the person...
you want to propose to on the last day of the program.
It's too soon!
You can pick...
up to two people in the potential proposal vote.
I'm so...
(They have a lot to process before the vote.)
If you're certain about one person as a future spouse,
you may vote for one person only.
If a man and a woman vote only for each other,
the two will become a couple and move to the couple zone.
But if you have no one you want to propose to,
you may choose not to vote.
It's a moment to confirm each other's feelings.
I bet they're nervous.
Will they go for one person only...
or show interest in both people?
If we vote for two, we'll never go to the couple zone.
That's true.
Write the number and name of the potential proposal...
on your profile card.
- Are you still torn? - Yes.
Are you actually looking for a potential spouse?
Yes.
- Okay. - That's why I'm torn.
It feels like the calm before the storm.
(It's the calm before the storm in the single zone.)
How are you feeling?
I was torn between Number 7 and Number 24,
- and the date happened. - Number 13 is also on your list?
You said it was fun.
It was fun. But I'm considering marriage.
We're most curious about Joo Hee's choice.
What's the point of deliberating?
(Jae Yeon looks rather composed.)
- He looks calm. - He does.
It's not so difficult to pick two candidates.
Choosing one between the two is the tough part.
Exactly.
Jin Ju must be torn between Sang Gyeong...
- and Jae Keun, right? - Right.
(Jin Ju can't decide between these two.)
I should have made up my mind...
to write this.
Poor Joo Hee.
Joo Hee must be the one...
who wants to make up her mind.
How did they go to the couple zone?
What were they so sure about?
That's a similar question that unmarried people have...
- about married people. - Right.
"What were they so sure about to get married?"
Yes, I am curious about that.
It's the moment of truth.
(The given time ends.)
Now, we will reveal the outcome...
of the potential proposal vote.
- What? - What?
You're revealing them already?
When your name is called, go to the opposite sex's lounge...
and deliver your profile card...
- to your choice directly. - Seriously?
We need to deliver it ourselves.
If you decided not to vote...
or weren't chosen,
you must leave COUPLE PALACE.
- No way. - Are you serious?
We have to leave.
You must leave COUPLE PALACE.
I knew it.
- Oh, no! - Oh, my gosh.
- That's intense. - Some of them will leave tonight?
(Who will leave for the first time from the single zone?)
- I might be going home. - Same.
It's so suffocating.
Number Seven, Choi Jae Yeon, please deliver your card.
- Jae Yeon. - Jae Yeon.
- Good luck. - Good luck.
- You've got this. - Good luck.
(Jae Yeon departs with an anxious heart.)
I assume he'll go straight to Joo Hee.
I don't like how vague this situation is.
(Jae Yeon only had eyes for one person,)
(and Sang Gyeong felt bad for him.)
We can't be sure yet. He might give up.
He does seem a bit exhausted.
- Hello. - Hello.
I'm so nervous.
Don't tell me you gave up.
Good luck.
- Oh, my! - Thank you.
I knew it. He's straightforward.
After voting for her...
(What's his decision that shocked everyone?)
Oh, my gosh!
- What? - Where is he going?
Hang on.
He must have another person.
(Does Jae Yeon have another interest?)
I gave her the other card with a madeleine cake.
I decided to go only for her,
so I only chose Joo Hee.
He's so sweet.
- What? - Come on!
Just give her all of them right away.
I was so touched and thankful.
He's so sweet.
Jae Yeon is the best.
Number 13, Kwon Young Taek, please deliver your card.
- Young Taek! - Let's go!
Here goes Young Taek.
I can't wait to find out who he chooses.
No, he took two cards.
He went on a date with Joo Hee today.
Right.
(Young Taek nervously came to the women's lounge.)
- You can do it. - You've got this.
Let's find out.
(Who is his potential proposal?)
I chose Number 18.
(He chose Joo Hee.)
I loved our little chat.
I think he fell harder for her after the date.
Number 18, Bae Joo Hee, please deliver your card.
- Here goes Joo Hee. - She's next?
Bae Joo Hee, please deliver your card.
Okay.
(The men's lounge is buzzing with the news...)
(that Joo Hee's coming.)
Let's see.
This is so nerve-racking.
(Young Taek is also nervous.)
I don't know why I'm so nervous.
I know, right?
Walk over with a smile.
- Yes. - Good luck!
Here she goes.
She's on her way.
I kept contemplating.
It's making me so confused.
Number 24,
Number 13,
and Number Seven.
I don't think I can give the card with a light heart.
Hello.
She was chosen by Jae Yeon and Young Taek.
Who will she choose?
(Who will Joo Hee choose?)
I did see it coming.
It didn't look like she'd choose me.
I was hoping she'd pick me.
I wished she'd pick me.
(What is her choice?)
(It was Jae Yeon.)
Jae Yeon, good for you!
The straightforward guy succeeded.
We still have to see if she's done.
- Didn't she give them all? - She might choose one more.
- Wait for it! - Oh, you're right.
Seriously?
(She has another card in her hand.)
- See? She's got one more. - She has one more card?
(Is she going all-in for Jae Yeon, or will she choose one more man?)
I was hoping she'd give it to me.
Who? Young Taek? Sang Gyeong?
(Who is her second pick?)
(She chose Sang Gyeong.)
- What? Seriously? - This means...
Did something happen between them?
(Sang Gyeong and Joo Hee went on a marriage-focused date...)
(on the first day of the Palace Week.)
(He found a little place in Joo Hee's heart that day.)
Both of them are...
(She chose Jae Yeon and Sang Gyeong.)
Jae Yeon must be so shocked.
Sang Gyeong is also surprised.
I honestly didn't expect her to choose me this time.
Number 24, Lee Sang Gyeong, please deliver your card.
- Good luck. - Thanks.
Here he goes.
(Who will he pick?)
Number 24, Lee Sang Gyeong, please deliver your card.
I had a feeling he'd only pick me.
We had fun during today's date,
and I hoped he'd choose me.
I had some expectations after our chat yesterday.
(Who will he choose?)
Goodness.
Hello.
(He goes straight to her as soon as he enters.)
He doesn't hesitate.
- He chose her right away. - No way!
(He chose Jin Ju without hesitation.)
I was so glad.
(But he has another card left.)
It wasn't over yet, so I waited.
Thank you.
- What? - No way!
What?
(He only chose Jin Ju.)
That's cool.
I was confused, thinking, "Why am I swaying?"
I thought it was wise to pick one person only,
so I voted for Jin Ju.
I wanted to go to the couple zone.
He wanted to go to the couple zone with Jin Ju.
Right.
- Did you only write one name? - Yes.
- He's made up his mind, then. - He has.
- That's cool. - You're so cool.
What a man.
- Number Three, Hwang Jae Keun, - Go on.
please deliver your card.
(Number 3, Hwang Jae Keun)
I'll be back.
(Female residents waiting for Jae Keun's decision)
Oh, my gosh.
I wonder who he'll pick.
I believe marriage is a long-term game.
Marriage with Jin Ju seems stable.
Marriage with Hye Won seems passionate.
I thought really hard about this.
- Welcome. - Hi.
I believe in destiny.
I believe he'll pick me again.
(What's his choice...)
- Jae Keun. - Let's find out.
(between stability and passion?)
- Who is it? - Who?
What?
(Jae Keun chose Jin Ju.)
- It was Jin Ju. - Jin Ju.
He has one more card. Is it for Hye Won?
(He still has one more card left.)
- What? - Is he leaving?
What's going on?
(His only choice was Jin Ju.)
- What? - Nothing.
I thought he'd pick two, but he only gave one to her.
What happens next?
He constantly said that he liked me at first.
I had never experienced this before.
I thought, "This must be what it feels like to get dumped."
I never imagined he'd only pick Jin Ju.
- I thought... - Are you sure, Jae Keun?
Has he decided on going all in...
for Jin Ju?
(What was on his mind?)
I talked so much with Jin Ju.
I see.
I had a feeling that she was...
into me at the moment.
- People have preferences. - Right.
You're my preference.
Was I too honest?
- That was straightforward. - Yes.
- So... - I like it.
If I'm being honest, I wish I could date you...
for one more month.
Right.
- Doing simple things, you know. - Having coffee...
Yes, like having coffee.
And eat dinner together.
- With a few light drinks. - But...
I can picture it.
(I can picture it.)
How come I can picture it?
I just can.
(Jin Ju proactively expressed her interest.)
That gave me conviction,
so I went all in for her.
- I see. - I did.
I'm so curious about Number 19,
and it's true that I'm drawn to her.
- She's attractive. - She's so attractive.
She really is.
But I wasn't sure...
if she was ready to consider marriage.
- I see. - It all came down to that.
I think I was more compatible with Jin Ju in that perspective.
I see.
She seemed ready to get married.
I decided to go all in for Jin Ju.
I can totally relate to him.
There are men who go straight for one woman from the get-go,
but there are also men...
who go all in once you give them certainty.
This isn't just dating, you know.
They're looking to get married.
Number 23, Seo Jin Ju.
(Jin Ju's name is finally called.)
I was swayed hard.
Two men picked me exclusively,
and I thought, "What am I going to do?"
Seo Jin Ju, please deliver your card.
I'll be back.
- Good luck. - This is a lot of pressure.
I think Jin Ju is into Sang Gyeong.
Go to the couple zone.
Sang Gyeong and Jae Keun went all in for Jin Ju.
Her choice will determine it.
(Where is her heart headed?)
There might be a surprise, though.
No, this may be bigger than we think.
Jin Ju's decision is crucial.
It is.
I don't want to regret my decision.
(Two men await her decision.)
I'm sorry.
She's sorry?
(Who is she apologizing to?)
(She hands over the card to Sang Gyeong.)
She gave it to Sang Gyeong.
I thought that I expressed my interest enough.
(She gives Jae Keun her second card.)
I was so flustered.
I thought, "Maybe I didn't give her enough trust."
Of course, I'm offended.
I'm running away.
The men went all in for her, and...
Pouring 100 percent of your feelings only to get 50 percent back...
- would upset you so much. - Definitely.
- Naturally. - They chose her only.
- Right. - Yes.
The two had such different charms,
so it was tough to pick only one person.
I thought, "Am I the only one...
who's taking it too seriously as if the wedding is tomorrow?"
That's what I thought.
What should I do?
Number Eight, Lee Yoon Seo, please deliver your card.
Me?
- Goodness. - Thank you.
- He gave one to Hye Won. - Good for her.
Oh, my.
Number Eight gave me a card, so I was grateful.
She won't have to leave now.
But I wonder who she will pick.
Number 26, Lee Jung Won, please deliver your card.
Jung Won is also interested in two women at the moment.
(Has he made up his mind?)
(The conversation between Jung Won and Sin Da on Day 2)
(He honestly told her about his worries.)
I'm not sure about how I feel.
(The woman who made him so uncertain)
(Seung Yeon came in between Sin Da and Jung Won.)
Will it be Sin Da or Seung Yeon?
I get that he's not certain about marriage.
But if he's not even certain about who his favorite is,
I no longer want to waste my time in this situation.
Who will get Jung Won's card?
(He gave Sin Da his card.)
- Oh, my! - Look at Sin Da.
- She's so cute. - She's so happy.
(He turns away and leaves right after.)
He's going all in for Sin Da.
(He only chose Sin Da.)
He came to me with a cute look...
and shyly gave me two cards.
I was exhilarated.
You look so happy!
So cute.
Is it done?
She has to give her card to him as well.
Oh, right.
If she only chooses Jung Won,
- they're going to the couple zone. - Yes.
(Number 9, Oh Sin Da, is here to deliver her card.)
I've been sulky all day.
Part of me was angry,
I had severe mood swings,
and I was stressed out.
I was pretty exhausted.
But it was all worth it. I forgot all about it.
I only have good memories now,
so...
I ran up to him.
- Go on. - Here she comes.
I gave them like this.
I gave him both my cards.
(Sin Da is also going all in for Jung Won.)
Both her cards.
(They're going to the couple zone!)
Jung Won and Sin Da are going to the couple zone!
They've been matched now.
He made me feel certain.
She looks so down all of a sudden.
- Who? - Sin Da.
Really?
Sin Da looked sad,
and it made me worried.
(He lingered around her because he was worried.)
I tried to make her feel better.
- Are you going to eat? - I'm not sure.
- I don't have an appetite. - I know.
(He subtly looked after her.)
Don't you have a jacket?
I do,
but this dress looks better without it.
(He always smiled when he heard her whimsical remarks.)
It doesn't sound so bad to stick with someone...
that you're into.
I like having you next to me.
- Having me? - Yes.
She's very straightforward with her expressions,
so I decided...
to choose her.
I feel certain now.
What? What's going on between them?
That was pretty sweet.
You look so happy in situations like this.
- Earlier... - I'm so transparent.
Lee Jung Won and Oh Sin Da only chose each other,
so they will go to the couple zone.
Congratulations!
(Everyone's congratulating them.)
(But there's one person who can't.)
- You make such a cute couple. - Congrats.
Thank you.
I guess there really is a match for everyone.
Number 21, Oh Seung Yeon, please deliver your card.
It's Seung Yeon's turn.
Oh, no. She has to choose.
Let's go.
She and Jung Won gave off...
pretty good vibes until the afternoon.
Right.
(Who will she choose?)
No way.
(She gave it to Jung Won.)
Seung Yeon chose Jung Won.
(She chose Jung Won, who's going to the couple zone with Sin Da.)
How is Jung Won going to react? He just became a couple.
- What's wrong? - It's nothing.
What's happening to your mouth?
Seung Yeon had written my name.
It was a shocker.
These are the male and female moving to the couple zone.
- Lee Jung Won and Oh Sin Da. - Bye.
(Lee Jung Won and Oh Sin Da)
Min Dong Sung and Kim Ja Hyun.
(Min Dong Sung and Kim Ja Hyun)
My Ja Hyun is here. Ja Hyun.
(They gave one vote for each other and entered the couple zone.)
Shall we go?
(A lovely couple with similar looks is born.)
The two look great together.
My gosh.
I stuck my name in the center like you.
I see.
(The two happily head to the couple zone.)
I'm freezing.
(Jung Won takes his jacket off right away.)
Thank you.
What a lovely sight.
(The two couples arrive at the couple zone.)
(The couple zone has a slightly different vibe.)
- What? - My gosh.
- We also got whisky. - You're right.
- We're finally... - Finally.
The couple zone is having a party.
Great work.
- "Great work?" - What's with that?
Cheers.
He said great work.
(A peaceful and loving air continues.)
Right?
(Hyun Joong and Si Yeon are sitting side by side.)
Isn't it really dry here?
- The heater is blasting in here. - Do you want some?
Can I?
(Hyun Joong and Si Yeon are in their own little world.)
It's literally a couple zone with real romance.
(The couples share stories,)
(and the mood is warming up.)
(Nobody wants to be apart.)
Ji Woong and Ha Yeon are too close to each other.
(At that moment, the door opens and somebody comes in.)
- What? - My gosh.
- Goodness. - What?
(Sin Da and Jung Won have come to the couple zone.)
Hi.
(As well as Dong Sung and Ja Hyun.)
Everyone. Get up and clap for us!
(Everyone seems happy for the new couples...)
For real?
Gosh. They're here?
(Ji Woong is interested in Sin Da and she's finally here.)
I was quite surprised.
Sin Da kept...
expressing her feelings to me.
Little did I expect her to become a couple...
and join us so quickly.
He looks quite shocked...
at Sin Da's appearance.
(Jung Won, Sin Da, Ji Woong, and Ha Yeon...)
(are sitting side by side.)
Hi.
- My roommate. - We're roommates.
I've heard.
Ha Yeon knows that Ji Woong...
- has feelings for Sin Da. - Exactly.
(Jung Won leaves for a while.)
(Even Ji Woong leaves.)
- Our schedule was too tight. - What happened?
In the morning, we had breakfast...
with my older brother.
Going outside was really nice.
We took a car and went on a little drive.
Her face is like, "So what?"
(Ji Woong returns...)
(and sits next to Sin Da.)
You shouldn't do that. That's not your seat, Ji Woong.
How can you sit there?
Why are you sitting there?
Go sit next to her now.
She's scary.
(Ji Woong finally returns to his seat.)
I'm sure Ha Yeon isn't happy about it at all.
What was it like at the single zone yesterday?
He liked it.
- How honest of him. - Who called you over?
- The one from the interview. - The tall Miss Korea...
took him, saying he was hers,
and talked with him.
She took him to the room with the bed.
(Ji Woong was invited to the single zone party.)
Yes, to the room with the bed.
I also wanted to talk to him,
- so I went to the room. - We talked a lot more.
- That's not true. - No, we did.
No way.
I gave you two enough time to talk.
The Miss Korea...
I'm hearing a lot for the first time.
When Ji Woong left, he said, "I'll be right back."
The interview went on for a while.
Interview?
Looks like you had plenty to say.
(There's a weird vibe between the two.)
We're here for that very purpose.
- You're in the couple zone. - Not in the couple zone.
Thinking the situation could change at any time...
made me a little worried.
Gosh, this is bad.
(Meanwhile, in the single zone)
- Did you receive two votes? - Yes.
- Who? - Numbers 7 and 13.
(Joo Hee received votes from Choi Jae Yeon and Kwon Young Taek.)
And I voted for Numbers 7 and 24.
(Joo Hee voted for Choi Jae Yeon and Lee Sang Gyeong.)
What a surprise.
Great choice.
I think it's a good idea to get to know everyone.
- I couldn't. - It's not everyone.
That...
It's not everyone.
I was only interested in Numbers 7 and 24.
So you also voted for Number 24.
- I kept voting for Number 24. - You did?
- I had no idea. - It was only these two for me.
As we expected,
the single zone is experiencing difficulties.
- What now? - It's tangled up...
and a total mess.
Jae Yeon is all about Joo Hee.
Meanwhile, Joo Hee has voted for Jae Yeon and Sang Gyeong.
Sang Gyeong and Jae Keun are all about Jin Ju.
And Jin Ju has voted for both Sang Gyeong...
and Jae Keun.
Jin Ju is practically the winner here.
Whichever decision I make,
it's going to be a mess.
If I choose Number 23, then I'm competing against Jae Keun.
If I choose 18, then I'm competing against Jae Yeon.
- I'm losing it. - How interesting.
(The females are also in a complicated situation.)
What now, Joo Hee? You're debating, aren't you?
Me? I'm going nuts.
Same here. What do I do?
Are you deciding between two males?
- Yes, two. - Who and who?
- Number 24 and... - Numbers 24 and 3.
Number Three is the type...
I had fun with when I dated someone like him.
- He's like that. - Okay.
Honestly, Number 24...
isn't a type I have dated before.
- He isn't? - No.
- But he feels like a husband. - Really?
I'm the complete opposite.
- For real? - Number Seven is like a husband.
- And Number 24... - Right.
- is like the other guy. - I get it.
- This is so interesting. - We're alike...
- but in opposite situations. - Exactly.
We have the opposite opinion of the same person.
Maybe I'm being hated.
- Why? - Like, "Why hasn't she chosen yet?"
I had the same thought. What if they call me a fox?
"She's sly as a fox."
- And playing the field. - "She's playing the field."
What if they think like that?
Everyone does.
But we understand.
- It's only day two. - Yes, we understand.
We totally understand.
We understand why you're worried.
To be honest, when that crossed my mind,
I also thought,
"How can you choose someone...
when it's only been a few days?"
- "Is this for real?" - My plan...
was to become a couple, get married,
and leave smoothly.
Really? Same here.
I wanted to get married right after the show.
I had such determination...
before coming here.
I want to get married right now.
Those two are sincere.
That makes it more difficult.
(COUPLE PALACE is in chaos.)
(The single zone's party has started.)
Something surely happens when there's a party.
The alcohol tastes bitter today.
You had a hard day.
Thank you.
In the midst of it all, he's worried about Joo Hee.
- There's no water. - Should I get some?
I'll bring a bucket full of it.
- Do we have water? - No.
How about downstairs?
Joo Hee goes after Jae Yeon.
Could I have some water?
- Can we take it all? - Yes.
It's water.
- I've got water. - Give me some water.
(At that moment, Joo Hee turns around and walks out.)
Where is she going? And out of the blue.
(Jae Yeon follows Joo Hee outside.)
What's going on? It's like she's looking for someone.
- Zo In Sung. - Zo In Sung.
- Zo In Sung? - Yes.
(Joo Hee approaches Sang Gyeong.)
- No, we're... - Do you want to talk?
(Do you want to talk?)
Okay.
(Sang Gyeong and Joo Hee leave together.)
I'm extremely quick-witted.
- What? - What?
What is it?
- Did you stop by? - It was uncomfortable over there.
It was uncomfortable.
- I see. - They're going to talk.
It bothered me.
(He's bothered by the two.)
- We got busted. - For what?
- We got busted. - We got busted?
- Yes, by Jae Yeon. - But this is no secret.
Sang Gyeong can't help but consider Jae Yeon.
Why does this feel like cheating?
That's a very provocative word.
Right.
- This is so embarrassing. - What?
Yes.
- Actually, - Yes?
- you left a big impression... - Yes?
during the speed train.
(During Round 3's speed date)
Are you always this funny?
(The two had a fun conversation over the most trivial things.)
- My ideal type is someone funny. - Is that so?
The first impression must be important.
Whether you have the same sense of humor is important.
Yes, it's important.
- I thought... - Yes?
you were on this show for fun.
- Me? - Yes.
- For real? - Yes.
It seems like everyone thinks like that.
- About me? - Yes.
- I wouldn't go for Number 18. - What?
I wouldn't go for Number 18.
She's quite flippant.
(He heard about Joo Hee from others.)
I think she wants to talk...
with many people but on a light level.
It seems like everyone thinks like that.
- About me? - Yes.
Is that so?
And here's what I also thought.
Compared to the others,
- you're quite young. - Yes, I'm young.
I thought you might not be into marriage.
- Really? - Yes.
But I'm so serious about it.
Marriage to me is... Others might think like that.
- But I've always wanted... - Yes?
to get married before graduating from university.
Even during university, I wanted to get married.
I believe I'm quite late to the party.
It's to the point that I want to get married...
as soon as I meet the one.
(He realizes her true feelings for the first time.)
But nobody knew because I never talked about it.
Exactly.
Her enthusiasm...
- to get married... - Right.
caused such misunderstanding.
That's totally possible. Yes.
Honestly, I had a great dilemma...
between you and Jae Yeon.
For so long.
- Really? I had no idea. - Yes.
Wasn't it obvious?
No. You were always smiling brightly,
so I thought you were just happy.
I'm a bright person, but I did vote for you.
You did, but I thought it was for fun.
"For fun?"
- I see. Because it's fun? - That was...
Yes. I thought I had become...
- a fun friend to you. - Really?
Our conversations were always on fun topics.
That was why I couldn't notice it.
But it was too funny for us...
to have a serious conversation.
What was I supposed to do when everything you said was funny?
So, when you voted for me again,
it put me in a dilemma.
- You seemed serious about me. - Really?
I get everything now that we're talking.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(The misunderstanding has been cleared up.)
It's so important to talk.
You're right. Talking is important.
- Yes. - He finally understood that...
she thought about him with sincerity.
I...
want to talk more.
I mean us.
(Knowing how Joo Hee feels, Sang Gyeong pushes ahead.)
- Really? - Yes.
I simply...
Will this bring a change or something?
He also had the wrong idea about me.
But I'm as serious as anyone about this show.
I appeared on this show to get married no matter what.
But the misunderstanding has been cleared up.
We decided to clear up...
the misunderstandings we each had.
That was quite interesting.
(Meanwhile, in another part of the single zone,)
(Jae Keun is sorting out his thoughts alone.)
Hi.
I want to talk to you.
- Talk? - Yes.
- I feel bad about something. - About what?
For not clearly choosing someone.
But that's to be expected. It's not the final decision.
I consider it as your right.
I'm not mad or anything.
I was just not entirely happy.
I thought you'd feel that way.
There are things that keep me wondering.
There's a huge time difference.
The time I've spent with him...
since our first decision...
Although we had...
- a simple meal together, - Right.
our conversation was very invaluable.
It didn't even last for an hour,
but I felt your sincerity.
I pictured our future for the very first time.
(Jae Keun opens his heart to Jin Ju.)
"I'm not happy. I'm quite upset."
I hated the idea that she might catch on to my lousy feelings.
(Joo Hee is done talking to Sang Gyeong.)
(She immediately runs into Jin Ju.)
- Why did you drink so much? - Who did you talk with?
- Number 24. - Number 24?
Is he one of the people you're thinking about?
It's either Numbers 7 or 24 for me.
- Is it the two? - Yes.
- I see. - Things were tough...
because of the two.
Really?
She didn't know about it.
- He's popular. - He's a popular guy.
Joo Hee wasn't in the picture. She came out of nowhere.
- Jin Ju had no idea. - No, she didn't.
I'm guessing they didn't know what was going on.
(They get ready to go back to their rooms.)
Where were you?
I talked with Number 24.
- Until now? - Yes.
I'm losing my mind.
The atmosphere is turning cold.
(The atmosphere is suddenly awkward.)
What are you troubled about?
Is it the opposite of mine?
My plan was to cut things off.
- He picked you as the first choice. - Right.
I thought he had no feelings for me.
- I was going to make... - Let's go.
a clean-cut.
Did that change after talking to him?
Why does Joo Hee have to explain herself?
Exactly.
We should talk, too.
How are you feeling now? Is your dilemma back?
Or what?
I'll most likely choose Number 24.
- Really? - Yes.
I see. And Joo Hee has said it.
I'm not sure, either.
They both have a lot to think about now.
My mind was set on Number 24 from now on.
- Really? - It's because...
he gave me assurance.
I thought you were thinking between...
Numbers 13 and 7.
I didn't know it was Number 24.
I kept telling you it was Number 24.
I thought it was Numbers 7 and 13.
Really?
(Joo Hee was honest to Jin Ju.)
(She even talked about Sang Gyeong.)
(But the conversation led to a misunderstanding.)
Everyone thought her dilemma...
was between Numbers 13 and 7.
But suddenly, she said, "Number 24 has been looking handsome..."
"since last night." That took us by surprise.
From what I heard, Joo Hee called Number 24 over...
and sort of persuaded him to date her.
It's tough.
(Jin Ju directly came over to Sang Gyeong.)
I want to talk to you today.
We can talk tomorrow.
I want to talk today.
Talk here.
I'll give you privacy.
Jin Ju is bothered...
- by Joo Hee's words. - It seems like it.
Thinking one thing after the other has made...
her more anxious.
Are you upset I didn't vote for you twice?
Well, I was quite disappointed.
But I didn't know.
I didn't know it was our ticket to the couple zone.
I don't blame you.
Earlier, I felt really...
Don't worry too much.
But I felt terrible for some reason.
Jin Ju and I...
cleared up what you could say was a misunderstanding.
It's thrown me into confusion. I wonder what this is all about.
I didn't know Joo Hee was thinking about Number 24.
I was really taken aback.
In the car, she made a fuss about...
- how handsome he was. - Joo Hee did?
- Yes. - From what I see,
Joo Hee likes Number 24 a lot.
(Jin Ju asked Joo Hee about her true feelings.)
(I'll most likely choose Number 24.)
He's so annoying!
What? What are you talking about?
He's just that handsome.
Oh, come on.
Joo Hee told you how she felt about Number 24.
- Yes. - She wanted you...
- to hear it. - Out of the blue,
- Really? - she sat next to me in the car.
- I didn't know. - We didn't ask her.
- I didn't see it. - "I was going to cut off Number 24,
but my feelings grew back."
That was the end of the conversation.
- But she talked to herself about... - My eyes were closed.
how handsome he was when nobody asked.
Number 24 only voted for Jin Ju.
It felt like she deliberately said it...
for Jin Ju to hear.
When someone suddenly provokes you...
when you're in a dilemma,
- Right. - don't you get upset?
- But... - I bet she irritated you.
How does it irritate you?
I get irritated.
I assumed you got irritated.
I did. I was like, "What?"
From what I see, you're the one holding all the cards.
It'll depend on your decision.
What do I do?
(Jin Ju's dilemma gets worse.)
(Everyone has left aside from Jung Won and Ha Yeon.)
Did your interview go well?
Me? It wasn't that fun.
- Is that so? - You did your interview, right?
Can I share it?
Will Jung Won find out?
Tell him.
- Tell him. - Tell him.
Can I share it?
He kept asking me about Sin Da.
She's my roommate.
- Really? - Yes.
Nice.
The arrows pointing to Ji Woong...
I had no idea.
But...
the two must have a thing. I don't know.
Really? We never talked about him.
Is that so? Was it not brought up during the interview?
I'm talking about Sin Da, not the interview.
But now that you two have become a couple,
Sin Da will focus on you.
- It's just... - That might not be the case.
We can never know what's on her mind.
I suddenly...
(During the speed date in Round 3,)
(the first person Sin Da visited.)
(Ji Woong was confident about...)
(preparing a house that's worth over 2 million dollars.)
We get along.
Come here.
(Someone invited Ji Woong to the single zone party.)
- Is this... - Come here.
- Yes. - Sit down.
Who...
(During the single zone party,)
(Jung Won asked about where Sin Da was.)
(Sin Da didn't say anything.)
Are you pretty serious with the person you're matched with?
(Sin Da and Ji Woong's date...)
(looked like it was going to be kept a secret.)
I'm...
swayed once again.
(To be continued)
(A silent night when everyone's asleep.)
(Sin Da is up alone.)
(She carefully comes out...)
(and heads somewhere.)
- Where's she going? - What's she doing?
- She's putting it in. - The mailbox.
The secret mailbox.
(Sin Da asked someone out secretly.)
That gave me the chills.
- What was that? - That gave me the chills.
- I'm getting goosebumps. - Me too.
- When she just arrived? - Look at me.
- I'm getting goosebumps for real. - Yes.
- Yes. - I'm getting goosebumps.
That's crazy.
- COUPLE PALACE... - He wasn't the one?
It's more fun than a TV show.
- Right. - That's unbelievable.
(Everyone's curious about Hye Won's vote.)
(I...)
(What?)
(That's a twist.)
(Hye Won's being proactive?)
(Joo Hee's eyeing Sang Gyeong.)
(The time has come.)
(Joo Hee makes Jin Ju nervous.)
(I made it pretty clear.)
(Jin Ju makes a crazy announcement.)
(I can't stand to watch them working it out.)
(Did you hear anything?)
(Is it okay to say this?)
(Whatever.)
(The single men and women's hearts fluctuate.)
(Meanwhile, a strange air in the couple zone)
(Do you want to be swayed?)
(You can never expect where it might go.)
(Don't you want to visit the single zone?)
(How can I secure Ji Woong?)
(I have something to say.)
(Male Number...)
(is moving to the single zone from the couple zone.)
(What will become of their entangled relationships?)