♫  I've walked around in a big circle  ♫
♫  To finally meet you  ♫
♫  How can my love be restrained?  ♫
♫  My love for you is too obvious  ♫
♫  I guess you must have already discovered it  ♫
♫  On that clear evening  ♫
♫  It was romantic meeting you  ♫
♫  An unforgettable memory  ♫
♫  I heard that passionate love  ♫
♫  Can dissolve glaciers  ♫
♫  I say good night to you every night  ♫
♫  If you get used to it as well  ♫
♫  I like your eyes  ♫
♫  The years become gentle   ♫
♫   As the wind gently blows behind you   ♫
♫  I walk slowly with you, hand in hand  ♫
♫  If I can travel across the entire universe  ♫
♫  And roam around the Milky Way with you to pick a planet   ♫
♫  I'm willing to wait for you  ♫
♫  We cross time and space to grow old together  ♫
♫  Your gentleness  ♫
♫  It's like being among a magnificent galaxy of stars  ♫
♫  If I can rest on any planet I want  ♫
♫  I will run into you in this universe  ♫
🎈
At the time, I hadn't composed any new songs in a long time
and wasn't in my best state.
I seemed to have lost my inspiration for music all of a sudden.
I didn't like any of the songs I wrote either.
Well, let's rewrite this song.
I believe you already found back your inspiration for music again.
But we don't have enough time.
I'm not sure I can do it.
Do you want to hear my story for this half-finished song?
The day I was diagnosed with ALS,
I felt like my entire world collapsed.
No one could understand how I felt back then.
I'm sorry.
Hello, Dad.
Daughter, you said you've been feeling weak lately.
What did the doctor say?
The doctor said I need to exercise more.
Okay, okay.
Then if anything comes up, you can tell me.
If it's nothing, you should come home soon.
I'm waiting for you to come back to eat.
I accidentally picked up a music score.
I didn't think the song I picked up would be filled with an uplifting energy
where it refused to give in to life.
So I used its etude and taught it to my students.
I didn't know my song could be used to teach others.
Should I ask you for some music royalty?
Am I not enough?
You are.
Do you remember I told you that if I'm lucky enough
to meet the owner of this music score,
I will tell him personally...
Not everyone in this world
has the chance to pursue their dreams.
If he has the chance,
he shouldn't give up easily.
I will officially give you these words now.
♫  Remember the first time we met  ♫
♫  Both of us were caught unprepared  ♫
♫  No time to hesitate. We're already running out of time  ♫
♫  Leave a hint in your smile as we go on  ♫
Reduce two decibels here. Let me hear it.
Is the chorus too loud here?
- Reduce another three decibels of the chorus here.
- All right.
♫  You and I will both try hard to be reasonable  ♫
♫  All we can do is   ♫
♫  give each other our tacit understanding  ♫
♫  We'll put away our words  ♫
♫  And end it with a smile  ♫
♫  Oh, at this moment  ♫
♫  The past ends with one final note  ♫
♫  The skill to forget  ♫
♪ But I can never perfect  ♪
♪ I wish you would hold my hands ♪
♪ But you're stuck in the memories of the past ♪
♪ Ten thousand kilometers ♪
♪ is the distance between the dawn and midnight ♪
♪ Oh, at this moment ♪
♪ It's clearly not how it used to be ♪
♪ But it feels so real ♪
♪ I cannot turn my eyes away ♪
♪ My heart's in the most painful story ♪
♪ The late winter when I long for you ♪
♪ Love gradually fades away ♪
♪ In an ending without you ♪
You're drinking this early?
Jiang Nan is about to go on Cool Singer-Songwriters.
Cool Singer-Songwriters is such a popular show.
Aren't you afraid Jiang Nan will become more popular than before?
By then, no matter how hard you try,
Gu Jia Yi won't spare even a single glance at you.
I have no choice.
I'm telling you, Alex is so stubborn.
He has set his mind on Jiang Nan. What else can I do?
So, Alex chose Jiang Nan instead of you?
That makes sense.
Sometimes money can't do everything.
No, no, I don't think so.
Who would go against money?
I still made an investment.
Here's what I think.
I must first set out the fish hook,
so it would be convenient when I want to go fishing.
You still have other ideas?
So that's why I came to discuss them with you.
What are you planning to do?
The higher he climbs, the harder he falls.
The way I really like it is...
How do I put it? It's like...
It's the pleasant sensation you get
when someone gradually climbs to the top
and falls all the way back down.
Here's what I think.
I want to put a person of mine into Cool Singer-Songwriters
and bind him with Jiang Nan to create news.
What do you think?
I have a perfect candidate.
No one is better than him.
That's why I say us two brothers
should hang out more often when we have time.
Cheers.
- Brother Rui.
- Lord Bao.
- Xiao Du is here too?
- Brother Nan.
Can you two stop casting dog food all the time?
(T/N: Internet slang. Couples who act lovey-dovey in public are giving "dog food" to those who are single)
Can you consider my feelings?
Lord Bao, are you jealous?
When will you get a girlfriend?
We're waiting to eat your dog food.
Lao Jiang, I'm telling you that Cheng Cheng has been led astray by you.
She's already starting to rub in my weaknesses, you know?
Let me tell you, the happiest person in here is this guy.
He's going back to his hometown today to get married.
Xiao Du, this is a small gift from Cheng Cheng and me.
Bring your wife with you when you come back from getting married.
I don't want to see you two live separately.
Thank you, Brother Nan and Sister-in-law.
I...
Lord Bao, where's your red envelope?
(T/N: Given to celebrate couples getting married)
Hurry, take it out now.
No, why are you looking at me like that?
Am I such a frugal person?
But to be serious, I'll be sending Xiao Du to the train station later.
Tonight, on the stage, you can...
No problem.
I think I asked about my own loneliness.
Yes, no one needs me anymore.
You're right.
But Lao Jiang, you haven't been on stage for a while.
Today is the day to see if you will win this battle.
I understand. Why are you still nagging me?
- Let's go.
- Bye-bye.
- Xiao Du, congratulations on your marriage!
- Congratulations on your marriage!
What do you think? Do I look all right?
Is my hair messy?
No.
You can do it!
I'm not afraid of anything with you by my side.
Brother, everything is ready.
Jiang Nan will be the last to go on stage.
Just wait and see what happens when he starts singing.
President Liang's people really did a good job.
Brother, why don't we go watch what happens live?
You're right. There's nothing to see.
He just going to sing.
What is he even saying about pursuing his aspiration for music?
Brother, I'll get going then.
What's wrong?
Are you nervous?
I'm nervous when you're here.
I'll go check up with your accompaniment. I'll be back soon.
Jiang Nan, I feel like we came to be your supporting role in this show.
Everyone can tell Alex thinks very highly of you.
I never heard what everyone is singing and no one knows what I am going to sing.
So, before the show begins,
no one knows who will be the final winner.
If you ask me, it doesn't matter who wins.
Jiang Nan, do you know Jian Xing?
Yes, I do. Why do you ask?
He suddenly joined the show right before it began.
They say he's a challenger.
What do you think Alex means by that?
Are you crazy?
Jiang Nan, please, respond!
Jiang Nan, please, respond to Jian Xing's accusation.
Jiang Nan, are you really terminating your contract with Sheng Yu Entertainment?
Jiang Nan, please, respond.
Please, give us a direct response!
Give us an explanation.
Due to Jiang Nan's drunken act of violence towards Jian Xing,
and the disbanding of 2BeOne, Sheng Yu Entertainment will be terminating its contract with Jiang Nan.
Jiang Nan will have to pay a high penalty fee for his contract termination.
At this moment, he has waved his music career goodbye.
I made some adjustments to the accompaniment, so I want to replace the track.
All right. Please, listen to see which version it is.
This sounds exactly like Jiang Nan's new song.
Yes, that's the one.
Okay, I have your confirmation then.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Mr. Sound Engineer, hello.
Do you have the latest performance order list?
You are...
I'm Jiang Nan's personnel.
Thank you.
- Let's have a drink tonight.
- Sure.
Jiang Nan, long time no see.
Come on.
You haven't changed from the last time we saw each other.
Who do you think will be the winner of this competition?
Come out for a moment.
What's wrong?
I just went to confirm the accompaniment
and I discovered Jian Xing's song is almost the same as yours.
Are you sure?
There are too many similarities.
He's a challenger contestant.
No one notified us of his appearance.
He is also going before you.
I think something is wrong.
What should we do?
We'll change to another song.
There are only a few more hours before the show starts.
Do we have enough time?
If Jian Xing is targeting me,
changing the song is our only choice.
You don't believe me.
I do believe you.
I'll go confirm with the accompanist that we are changing songs.
Hello, Alex. There has been an accident that has come up last minute.
I might need to change to another song.
Just to let everyone know that Jiang Nan is changing songs last minute, so...
Changing songs last minute?
Can he do that?
He has the talent to do so.
No, he's just wasting everyone's time.
You can't do that. I have another show I have to go to afterwards.
Changing songs last minute?
What should I do?
I think I was a bit nervous, so my breath was unsteady just now,
but the encouragement the judges gave me warmed my heart.
Da Lin, how many performances have we seen already?
Why isn't it Jiang Nan's turn yet?
Jiang Nan is the last performer.
You have to wait.
Seems like the show doesn't think highly of him.
What do you know?
He's the grand finale.
Only big shots do the finale.
Use your brain.
All you care about is eating.
If you keep this up, you'll have to leave!
How can you work for me if it takes you so long to get some equipment?
If we came any later, we wouldn't get any evidence of Jiang Nan's plagiarism.
President Liang, we have a situation.
I was planning to use Jiang Nan's song,
but I didn't expect that good-for-nothing changed songs last minute.
I am not sure what happened.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing here?
Why did you plagiarize Jiang Nan's song?
Are you crazy?
Don't leave!
I heard everything when you were changing your music track.
Your song is exactly like Jiang Nan's song.
Are you crazy? Didn't Jiang Nan change songs?
I've never heard of it.
Jiang Nan only changed his song because you plagiarized him!
We have records of the original score and revisions of Jiang Nan's song.
We can confront each other and see who plagiarized the song!
I am too lazy to talk nonsense with you.
Jian Xing!
Although there are grievances between you and Jiang Nan,
he already paid his price.
Why are you playing these shenanigans on this show?
If you don't explain yourself, I'll expose you to the media!
You also know the stupid things Jiang Nan did in the past?
Oh, I remember now.
You're his girlfriend, right?
Go expose it to the media.
Since I dare use this song today, why would I be unprepared?
If you want to make it public, do it anytime!
So, you admit you plagiarized the song?
Let me tell you, watch your mouth!
Jiang Nan will be done for sooner or later.
Don't overestimate yourself!
Jiang Nan, calm down!
Jiang Nan!
Jiang Nan, let go!
- Let go of me!
- Calm down, Jiang Nan!
Let go.
How can they say that?
That's not what happened.
This is really good.
I used to think drinking herbal soups was like a woman in post-parturition
(T/N: In Chinese culture, after childbirth, women follow special diets and drinking herbal soups.)
but now your skills are getting better.
Your father's true skills have been passed down to you.
What time it is now?
How can you be in the mood to say that?
Also, why does Jian Xing have your music score?
Why did you beat up Jian Xing back then?
It's all in the past.
As for why he would have my music score,
we will have to talk with Lord Bao tomorrow about it.
Cheng Cheng, I'm sorry.
I made you worry today.
You have to promise me something then.
From now on, no matter what happens,
you cannot hit anyone again.
I promise you.
This article is way out of line!
Every word is hinting that there is something wrong with Jiang Nan's character.
They are using such an old topic to create a buzz by taunting him up front.
I even played badminton with her a few days ago!
I'm so pissed!
All right, don't be so angry.
Lord Bao, someone is calling.
It must be from a reporter. I'm not answering it.
Why is that Jian Xing so disgusting?
If it weren't for Orange, Jiang Nan would have been accused of plagiarism.
Where did he get the music score?
Actually, not a lot of people know about this song.
Besides us, there's also...
Xiao Du?
Finding who leaked the music score is not the most pressing matter.
What's important is how Jian Xing will act next.
He had such a large scheme planned, but he failed and was beaten up by Jiang Nan.
He definitely won't leave the matter at that.
It's Alex.
Put him on speaker.
Jiang Nan, you really disappointed me.
You've created such a scene!
Alex, I'm sorry. I was too impulsive.
I'm sorry, Teacher Alex. I'm Bao Rui.
It's like this. I wanted to ask if Jian Xing told you why Jiang Nan hit him?
He said Jiang Nan was jealous of him for coming on the show at the very last minute!
Without saying anything else, the two of them started fighting.
How can he say...
I don't care what reason you have.
Jiang Nan hit him first, so he is at fault.
Jiang Nan, you must handle this properly
or I will never give you another chance!
Alex, I'm very sorry if this incident affected the show in any way,
but what I want to tell you is, I have my reasons for hitting Jian Xing.
I wasn't acting on impulse.
Even if I lose my chance to be on Cool Singer-Songwriters, I won't have any regrets.
Young man, don't be so sure of yourself.
Judging by how big things have got,
why don't we have Jiang Nan and Jian Xing withdraw from the competition?
I don't care about Jian Xing.
As for Jiang Nan, he really does have the skills.
Also, I didn't think we would get so much trending news from him.
Let's wait and see.
Anyway, the show has generated a large amount of buzz.
It would be even better if Jiang Nan is problem-free.
He can continue to be on the show and generate more news.
Lao Jiang, why didn't you let me speak?
He won't believe anything we say now.
It's because this show is really important for you.
In my opinion, Alex won't easily give up on me at this moment.
This show has been generating quite a large amount of buzz.
Got it. How about this?
I'll contact a few reporters I know to ease the public for now.
Is that okay?
There's no rush.
As you said, Jian Xing must've come prepared.
Besides waiting, there's nothing else we can do.
In that case, I'll take Cheng Cheng to eat at the Happy Family Restaurant.
I haven't visited my father-in-law in such a long time.
We're leaving.
You have worked hard, Lord Bao.
I...
Editor-in-Chief Qin, do you need to see me?
Did you write the article about Jiang Nan?
Why did you publish it without my permission?
There are two editors-in-chief in True Image now.
President Liang says I have the power to publish articles independently now.
If you have any problems with it, you can go ask him.
First of all, both chief editors should supervise each other.
As you didn't hold a publishing meeting, you went against protocol.
Secondly, your article is highly subjective and instigating.
That's not the style of True Image.
Even those clickbait writers on the internet won't write something like that.
Qi Qi, at the very least, I was the one who trained you.
Is this the level of journalism you have?
That's all in the past, yet you still clearly remember it.
You have your style and I have mine.
What I want is high viewership.
Stop!
I know you have an opinion on Jiang Nan,
but there was no need to do that at all.
What do you mean?
Are you saying I have a selfish motive?
You and I both know about it.
What do I know?
You're just upset that I've become an editor-in-chief like you, right?
All right, I'll let everyone know who's the real boss here.
Everyone, put down your work.
I'll make it clear to you all today.
President Liang belives the reason why True Image wasn't doing well financially before
is because our previous style was too old-fashioned and inflexible.
I'm just following his instructions. I hope everyone will cooperate.
From now on, we will publish a trending article every week,
and it will affect your performance rating.
From now on, all work will be reported directly to me.
Do you understand?
Qi Qi, listen up!
Since the establishment of True Image,
it has never belonged to me,
and it certainly won't belong to you.
Is that important?
Your job is more important, right?
We used to always call Sister Shan the Female Devil.
Now, we know that Sister Shan is the Female Guardian Deity,
while Qi Qi is the Monster in human skin.
Jiang Nan, don't just sit there. Have some meat.
Jiang Nan, I stared at the TV for a long time.
I didn't see you come out on stage. What happened?
You're such a bumpkin.
Popular shows these days are split into two parts.
- Am I right, Jiang Nan?
- Is that true?
Uncle, Auntie, it's like this.
Someone was stirring up trouble backstage while we were recording the show,
so the show might be suspended for a while.
Stirring up trouble?
What happened then?
You got physical?
- This child.
- You...
You're an adult, why did you hit someone?
I have to scold you.
You should think before you act. You have Cheng Cheng now.
- You have to keep a clear head when you encounter problems.
- No, Dad, you can't...
That...
That person pushed me.
Jiang Nan only beat him up to protect me.
He pushed you?
- Uncle!
- Dad!
- What are you doing?
- Let go!
- Uncle!
- Sit down!
- Uncle, please, take a seat!
- You...
- He pushed our daughter!
- Think about it. I...
- Uncle!
- What are you doing?
- Uncle, you must stay calm and clear-headed.
Calm down!
Are you hurt?
No.
Uncle and Auntie,
there might be a lot of news about this matter for the next few days because I hit someone,
but please, don't worry about me.
Because what they're saying isn't true.
That's right. Mom, Dad, those people just want to use the opportunity to promote and gain views on their articles.
Don't worry, Jiang Nan.
No matter what they say on the news, we'll only believe you.
That's right. Your Auntie is right.
We believe you wholeheartedly. We all support you.
- Let's eat.
Bring me along next time.
Cheng Cheng, thank you for staying with me.
Jiang Nan, you're acting a bit strange today.
How so?
You aren't worried at all, even when something this big  happened.
That's nothing.
I've been through worse things.
Back when we were at the peak of our popularity,
a lot of people asked to work with me every day,
as if their ads and shows were tailor-made for me
and they couldn't do it without me.
I was the center of attention wherever I went.
But after 2BeOne was disbanded,
all the people around me disappeared all at once.
It was as if everyone forgot my existence,
but after being with you, I am more certain of what I should cherish.
It's like everything else isn't important anymore.
Why did you disband back then?
Xu Duo Cheng, I'm telling you all my true feelings.
Can you play along and act touched?
You're my boyfriend.
I want to know your past and your future.
Do you really want to know?
Five years ago, Sister Yun, the boss of Sheng Yu Entertainment,
was also our band's manager.
She brought Zhan Zhi Lin and me to attend a dinner party.
Don't worry. Just leave it to me.
President Yang, I'll count on you for helping A'Nan.
A'Nan, his clothes.
Send him out.
President Yang, take it easy.
He's drunk.
President Yang!
President Yang, take care!
Lin Zi.
Lin Zi, are you drunk?
Does he have an ambiguous relationship with Sister Yun?
What did you say?
I said Jiang Nan is just a pretty boy.
He's trash who lives off a woman by sleeping and drinking with her.
Come on.
Lin Zi, let's have a drink.
You are saying Zhan Zhi Lin was the one who hit him?
At the time, Uncle Zhan didn't support Zhan Zhi Lin's music career.
If Jian Xing exposed him, he might have never had a chance to ever sing again.
Also, Liang Zhe kept targeting me because of Gu Jia Yi,
but I think Liang Zhe was the one who told Jian Xing to hang out with Zhan Zhi Lin.
Jian Xing doesn't have the guts to do so himself.
Did you tell Zhan Zhi Lin?
Why didn't you tell him?
You should let him know.
He has been targeting you just because of that matter.
But he didn't continue to sing later on.
All right, that's all the time I have for stories today.
We'll continue some other time.
Come to think of it, the bar we used to often perform at before debuting is near here.
Do you want to go see?
Before your debut?
- I do.
- Let's go.
Jiang Nan?
It's very rare to see you nowadays!
Long time no see.
Yes, it's been about two or three years already.
What do you want to drink?
We won't be drinking tonight.
I'm keeping her company. We'll just have some alcohol-free beverages.
He is...?
Brother Cheng is the owner of this place. He's a very loyal friend.
Hello.
At the time, we would always perform till 2 or 3 a.m.
We were hungry and tired.
Brother Cheng would prepare midnight snacks for us
and let us drink his prized collection.
I really want to go back in time and watch 2BeOne's concert.
You are playing the guitar and Zhan Zhi Lin plays the bass.
You worked really well together back then, right?
I really envy your audience at the time.
Here comes my prized collection.
- Wahaha?
- Here.
(T/N: Yogurt Beverage)
- Cheers!
Jian Xing will be live-streaming tomorrow.
I invited some media.
That way, the incident of Jiang Nan hitting him will get even bigger.
Jian Xing is a scumbag.
It's been so many years and he is still playing the same old trick of complaining to the media.
Jian Xing is just a pawn.
Please, don't take him seriously, President Zhan.
But what I don't understand is,
you, Jian Xing, and Jiang Nan were all from the same agency
and you were very close friends.
Why did you all turn out like this?
I'm leaving if you're looking for small talk.
We won't talk about it.
I won't ask, all right?
Today is a day worth celebrating.
Let's drink.
♫  I walked past many side roads before you met me  ♫
♫  Destiny's plan makes me very flustered  ♫
♫  Your eyes are like another kind of starlight in the darkness  ♫
♫  You shine a light to all my loneliness  ♫
♫  I only dare to secretly practice my love confession  ♫
♫  I only dare to imagine hugging you from behind  ♫
♫  I only dare to tell my thoughts to the Wishing Tree  ♫
♫  One, two, three, you opened the door to my heart  ♫
♫  I suddenly became very foolish  ♫
♫  I was just like a wooden person  ♫
♫  My longing still asks me at night  ♫
♫  "How much do I mean to him in his heart?"  ♫
♫  Why have I become so strange?  ♫
♫  It has become difficult to guess your every word  ♫
♫  The best arrangement is to cross over the sea of people  ♫
♫  I don't want to wait any longer  ♫
♫  One, two, three, from now on I hold your hand  ♫
♫  Day and night, I won't let you escape again  ♫
♫  I raise my head to gaze into your eyes  ♫
♫  I share all my joy and sorrow with you  ♫
♫  Don't be shy, I'll give you all my gentleness  ♫
♫  In this universe, I will hold nothing back  ♫
♫  As we walk side by side, I reach out my hand  ♫
♫  Our two planets will finally never drift apart again  ♫
♫  I only dare to secretly practice my love confession  ♫
♫  I only dare to imagine hugging you from behind  ♫
♫  I only dare to tell my thoughts to the Wishing Tree  ♫
♫  One, two, three, from now on I hold your hand  ♫
♫  Day and night, I won't let you escape again  ♫
♫  I raise my head to gaze into your eyes  ♫
♫  I share all my joy and sorrow with you  ♫
♫  Don't be shy, I'll give you all my gentleness  ♫
♫  In this universe, I will hold nothing back  ♫
♫  As we walk side by side, I reach out my hand  ♫
♫  Our two planets will finally never drift apart again  ♫