⟨The one who saved the embezzled Risa from Kuwabara was →
It was my husband Takaku⟩
⟨Risa tells Ryo that she has no more money to give⟩
(Lisa) Did your wife leave a will?
(Ryo) It's true that I looked for it, but it wasn't there.
⟨Finally, the true nature of the magical man Ryo is revealed⟩
(Takaku) [It's said that he hid his deceased wife's will →
It didn't make any sense]
[Wouldn't it have been better if he had followed the will?]
♪～
(Ryo) Even if you follow this, the money will end up...
(Nagiko) Because it's a love letter.
You've written well, haven't you?
(Nagiko) Show it to everyone.
(Ryo) Nagi-chan, please forgive me and I will apologize.
>> Will you give me your back again?
(Ryo) Hit me until you feel relieved.
Then set me free.
(Lisa) Are you crazy?
(Lisa) That's a goldfish.
It's not Nagi-chan.
(Lisa) A will?
It was there after all.
Why can't you show it?
Is there something written? Besides heritage.
(Ryo) It's just a will that wasn't written. (Risa) Then why do you still have it?
It would have been better to dispose of it quickly.
(Ryo) That's why I'm about to burn it now... (Risa) Were there words of love written on it?
on second thoughts.
That's why I cherished it.
(Ryo) No! Let's burn this thing already.
(Sound of hitting the shelf)
(Lisa) Why, why is it that person?
I've been hurt like this for so long!
(Lisa) I thought you chose me.
He says he seriously wants to leave his wife.
That's why I believed you!
I lost everything for you!
(Ryo) I understand... I understand, so stop it already.
(Lisa) Got it? What do you understand? You don't understand anything!
(sound of tapping)
Look.
Isn't it beautiful? My bruise.
(Lisa) Say it again, ``You're beautiful.''
Are you mine?
Say it's mine.
Hey, tell me!
It's mine!
(Ryo) I...
It's Lisa's.
(Lisa) Hahahaha A-ha!
Liar! Liar!
Liar! (Sound of stomping)
Liar! Liar! (Sound of stomping)
(Kanako) Hey, what happened? Stay strong!
(Lisa) Let go! >> Hey, take a look in the mirror over there.
You're really ugly right now.
I'm already freaking out, so please stop. This sudden change in character.
Are you okay? Ryo-kun.
(Ryo) Kill me.
I want to die like this and go to Nagi-chan.
(Kanako) Hey, what are you talking about?
(Ryo) I couldn't get anything.
>>I also want to go to my baby.
I'm sorry Ryo-kun.
They have children without permission and involve themselves without permission.
I was really selfish.
Having a child without permission →
This is also violence against women.
(Lisa) What does this mean?
(Lisa) What? This is called ``drug replacement.''
(Kanako) What is it? That letter.
(Lisa) Will Wife's will.
“My husband Ryo Jouchi →
Infidelity with Risa Yajima →
Unless drug substitution is allowed→
The inheritance shall be as follows.
Ryo Jouchi takes my psychotropic drugs→
Replace it with the allergy medicine the person takes on a daily basis →
It has led to a significant deterioration in my health."
(Cool) Nagi-chan→
He'll do anything to push me.
>>The shapes are very similar, aren't they?
(Ryo) Shut up.
(Lisa) Huh?
>> By the way, Ryo-kun→
You came to the hospital to get allergy medicine.
(Lisa) Allergy to grapes.
(Kanako) No, but Ryo-kun, you wouldn't do something like that, would you?
Don't answer, Ryo.
(Lisa) Do you still have it? This is the medicine that my wife gave me that night.
(Kanako) I have it though.
(Lisa) If you look into it, you'll find out, right?
Is it an allergy medicine?
>> Hey, I don't know.→
Does that mean I will die if I change my medicine?
(Ryo) I won't die. (Risa) But I died.
(Ryo) He committed suicide. (Risa) Didn't you set him up to do that?
It is written here that ``If you approve, you will be allowed to inherit.''
(Ryo) It's too late now.
(Lisa) What happened that night?
What did you do to that person?
>>I'll do anything.
(Nagiko) If it's to push me into a corner.
[coughing]
[Haa haa…]
〔where? Where did you hide it? ]
(Ryo) [Painful? ]
>> [Ryou please...]
[Haa haa…]
(Ryo) [Get comfortable now, Nagi-chan]
>> [Haa ha…]
(Ryo) [disappeared]
(Lisa) Hey, what did you do?
Ryo-kun, please answer.
(Ryo) I haven't done anything.
Nagi-chan just left the house.
>>And jumped off.
(Ryo) It's not my fault!
Before I knew it, it suddenly came out...
>>We still share the pain.
(Ryo) It's because Risa showed up!
(Lisa) Yeah.
(Ryo) If only Risa-san didn't show up...
(Lisa) [It must have been painful, but you endured it.]
(Ryo's voice) I was able to avoid noticing my own pain.
I never thought I wanted to be free.
It's Risa's fault that Nagi-chan died.
>> Hey, Ryo-kun. (Ryo) I haven't done anything.
This will is a lie.I cannot be bound by something like this.
I... I didn't do anything!
(Lisa) I understand.
I'm not doing anything.
(Lisa) But Ryo-kun.
So can you really be free?
♪～
(Nagiko's voice) ``However, someday in the future→
If Ryo changes his mind →
The right of inheritance arises again.
At least cool →
One moment, he loved me."
(Nagiko's voice) ``That's how I was able to live.''
Why do I →
I guess I couldn't love Ryo properly?
Why is it cool →
I guess I couldn't be loved properly?
I’m sorry, Ryo.”
(Lisa) I'm home.
(Sound of turning on the light)
(Lisa) I'm not in a position to say that.
(Oshima's voice) Is only one senior going to move?
(Lisa) Yeah, I'm looking for a good place.
(Oshima) You won't get any severance pay if you are fired for disciplinary action, right?
(Lisa) Unemployment insurance won't come out for a while.
It may be difficult to find work again.
>>Do you hold a grudge?
I reported everything to the company.
(Lisa) Thank you.
For dragging me back to this world.
I couldn't go back on my own.
Thank you.
>> I'll eat it.
I hated my senior.
(Lisa) Huh?
>> Well, I might be a little jealous right now.
My senior went crazy in love.
I wonder what will happen so indiscriminately →
I wonder if there is a future in my life.
(Lisa) But there's nothing left.
(Lisa) All that's left is to put people's money into the ATM →
The feeling of being sucked in.
>> Is that really the only thing left?
(Lisa) 《There's one more feeling that won't go away》
>> I was told not to say that →
Mr. Takahisa came to my company after that.
``My wife caused you trouble,'' he said, bowing his head.
What are you going to do now? senior.
Will you go back to your old self?
Or myself as a woman I don't know →
Are you going to survive?
(Lisa) 《I committed a crime》
(Lisa) 《I'm always dissatisfied with my life in some way →
Because I wanted to be different.
(Sound of placing a bag)
(Lisa) 《Devouring the food that comes in front of you with desire →
I lost everything》
(sound of door closing)
(Takaku) Ah...｡
(Takaku) It's been a while.
(Lisa) Yes.
(Takaku) Sorry, I completely forgot to press the stamp on the divorce notification.
If you push it, I'll go home. I'm busy with work.
Ah... I'll take care of the delivery.
(Lisa) Yes.
(Takaku) The registered seal... Where is the registered seal...｡
There was, there was, vermilion, vermilion, vermilion.
(Lisa) Thank you for the money.
(Takaku) Huh?
(Risa) I heard from Oshima-chan that she was trying to make a change.
(Takaku) Ah, I'm just a little curious.
(Lisa) Yes.
(Takaku) Here.
(Takaku) You know...
(Takaku) All the rice balls were the ones I liked.
(Lisa) Oh, a present?
Sorry for leaving it there.
(Takaku) When I think that Risa slept with another man →
I'm still in pain and my heart feels like it's going to burst.
I was the one who had the affair first →
I know that's what caused it.
But... But that's what I think.
(Lisa) I still feel bad about it too.
I remember the day I realized that Takahisa was having an affair.
But I'm more ashamed of what I did.
Takaku is in a place I don't know →
I think I was embarrassed a lot.
sorry.
(Lisa) I'm really sorry.
(Takaku) I'm sorry too.
I thought I was pretty smart →
When I realized that I was thinking about everything with ease →
I mistakenly thought that it meant efficiency and wisdom.
It's true that it's about Risa and the child...
I'm really sorry.
(Takaku) Isn't there a choice not to break up? Us.
(Lisa) Huh?
(Takaku) Maybe things like that between us like now →
If only I could say what I'm holding back →
I wonder if this didn't happen.
(Takaku) So, is it a bad idea to try that?
(Lisa) It's impossible.
(Takaku) No, it's not impossible.
(Lisa) Now is now.
There's no guarantee that you'll be able to say the same thing again.
(Takaku) I will try my best.
(Lisa) I...
I don't know if I can do it.
(Takaku) I will never have an affair again.
(Lisa) That's also me...｡
I don't know.
(Lisa) Even though I know it's hell from there→
You might want to go again on your own.
(Takaku) Well...
(Takaku) Well then, rock, paper, scissors.
(Lisa) Huh?
(Takahisa) If Risa wins in rock-paper-scissors, it's a divorce.
If I win, I'll continue.
That's the worst choice of words →
I have been →
All I was thinking about was continuing with Risa.
Please.
♪～
(Takaku) Well, let's go.
Rock, paper, scissors pon.
(Takaku) Rock, paper, scissors Pon.
Let's talk about Aiko.
(Takaku) Aikode Sho.
♪～
(Lisa) 《Another feeling that still remains inside me》
《The pain in my foot when I stepped on him →
That numbing sense of immorality》
(Lisa) It's been a while.
It won't change.
Is it obvious?
>> Have you decided on a job?
(Lisa) Not yet.
Video editing for attending vocational training.
>> Ah~ Edit It's so detailed.
(Risa) Hehehe...｡
(Kanako) Super? (Shoya) Yes.
Now's the time to put the discount stickers on.
I bought some grapes and made some Shine Muscat.
I understand.
Woohoo.
From now on, the two of us can spend money freely →
I go to various places.
Overseas or somewhere I've never been before.
(Lisa) Looks fun.
>> What about your ex-husband?
(Lisa) Yeah... I think I'm doing well. I'm only connected to Instagram.
>> Well, that's what it is.
Have you finally become free?
(Lisa) 《I still dream about him》
♪～
(Lisa) 《When he feels pain→
I remember feeling special only at that moment.
♪～
(Risa) Come on, rain!
(Lisa) 《That guilt→
If I could taste it again...