♪I miss you like the wind
rises among the branches♪
♪It sweeps through my heart,
causing ripples♪
♪Reminiscing about the past in tears,
I dare not expect♪
♪You will detect this secret♪
♪I miss you like the wind
rises among the branches♪
♪It fills half of my life
with lonely gusts♪
♪The sight of you took my breath away♪
♪How can I forget easily♪
=Sacrifice for Love=
=Episode 6=
(I Won't Blame You Even If You Kill Me)
Yichuan.
Yichuan!
Yichuan, wake up!
Lu Yichuan, stay with me!
Don't scare me.
I...
This, this is
my elder sister's pocket watch.
(The pocket watch blocked the knife.)
(Could there be something
behind my sister's death?)
(Lu Yichuan might not be the murderer.)
Go investigate
and find out who did it.
Yes, sir.
Yichuan acted impulsively.
But today thanks to him,
you were not hurt seriously.
However, his merits
can't cancel out his demerits.
The wrong thing he did can't be undone.
Between my beloved
and my son,
only one can live.
It's up to you.
I let you make the choice
because
I hope you will be the one
who can stay alive.
Why?
You might not know.
Because if a person
betrays you once,
he will betray you again.
When he got off the ship,
he should expect
this would be the consequence.
Don't worry.
After he drinks the potion,
his appearance
will become unrecognizable gradually.
Nobody will know Lu Yichuan is dead.
(Back then, my sister died)
(as Lu Ding described.)
(Could Lu Ding have killed my sister?)
(No.)
(Lu Yichuan can't die now.)
I got it.
Lu Yichuan saved my life today.
It is fair and sensible
that I should drink the poison for him.
You must think it through.
You made great efforts
to join the Lu family.
Lu Yichuan saved my life.
If I return evil for good,
I am sure I'll be perturbed
from now on.
I don't want you to drink it.
Will you
disobey me as well?
If you think I am wrong,
you can do whatever you want to me.
Darling,
I have learned a new dance lately.
I will teach it to you.
OK.
(God has taken Gu Manxi away.)
(Luckily, I met Su Kenian.)
(I can't lose her.)
Master.
(Mr. Zhou, butler of the Lu family)
How is the kidnap investigation going?
The investigation is thorough.
It's not an outsider's job.
Has Zhang Rong come back?
Stop beating me!
Darling, I beg you to stop it!
Stop beating me, darling!
I beg you to stop it!
Keep beating her if she doesn't confess.
Darling,
I do hate Su Kenian.
But I only dare to attack her orally.
How dare I pay someone to kidnap her?
How dare I have her killed?
Darling,
I beg you to stop beating me!
I am not the culprit.
Darling!
Darling, stop beating me!
I know
after all these years,
I didn't bear you
any, any children.
However, I have been your wife
for many years,
I should be given credit
for hard work, if not for merit, right?
I tended the attic for you
and did my part
for the Chamber of Commerce.
Why do I deserve
such, such treatment?
Master, I beg you to stop!
If,
if you continue,
my mistress will die.
Master!
Brother,
she doesn't seem to be
the culprit.
Why do you have the cheek to say that?
I asked you to watch Lu Yichuan
go aboard the ship.
However, you failed.
If I had stopped Yichuan,
Su Kenian would have died.
Mistress.
Su Kenian!
Since I was born,
I have never suffered like this.
You won't heard
the end of this.
Mistress,
let me help you go back
to apply some ointment.
Don't touch me!
♪Fallen flowers figured autumn out♪
You are scared it's gonna hurt?
No, I'm not.
♪After we parted,
our love turned to dust♪
My wound has healed.
It need not to be treated.
No, it must be treated.
♪I try to forget
with the change of seasons♪
♪But I can't erase you from my mind♪
♪I miss you like the wind
rises among the branches♪
♪It sweeps through my heart,
causing ripples♪
♪Reminiscing about the past in tears,
I dare not expect♪
You shouldn't have chosen to drink
the poison.
I don't want you to take the risk.
Don't worry.
Your father wouldn't let me drink it.
What if?
If he didn't stop you,
you may have died.
Then answer my question honestly.
Why do you have
my elder sister's pocket watch?
Look into my eyes and answer me.
Did you kill my elder sister Manxi
two years ago?
I didn't cause Manxi to die.
If you don't believe me,
I won't blame you even if you kill me.
♪How should I
embellish my life without you?♪
♪When I think of you,
I probe for the news about you♪
♪In front of the mirror,
stand half of me and half of you♪
♪In a trance,
it feels like we merged into one♪
♪The replay of the past scenes
goes on and on♪
♪Where else can I escape?♪
♪The satirical longing passes by♪
♪I struggle to break free from its grip♪
♪You even take away my happiness♪
♪Where else can I escape?♪
♪Memories occupy
the very last corner of my mind♪
♪Don't make me remember♪
♪Until this day♪
♪I was deeply loved by you♪