♪I miss you like the wind
rises among the branches♪
♪It sweeps through my heart,
causing ripples♪
♪Reminiscing about the past in tears,
I dare not expect♪
♪You will detect this secret♪
♪I miss you like the wind
rises among the branches♪
♪It fills half of my life
with lonely gusts♪
♪The sight of you took my breath away♪
♪How can I forget easily?♪
=Sacrifice for Love=
=Episode 19=
(She's Pregnant with Lu Ding's Baby)
Zhang Kai,
go check Fu out.
Yes, young master.
I didn't lie!
I was set up!
It wasn't me!
It doesn't matter
whether you lied or not.
I-I lied.
I'll tell you everything.
Please don't kill me!
Please!
You are lucky today.
The bullet was stuck in the barrel.
You know what to do tomorrow.
Move!
Quick!
Young master,
bind me looser next time.
Thank you.
Zhang Kai,
I want to join the organization.
Welcome!
Comrade Lu Yichuan.
I've been wondering
why we don't kill them all.
We have weapons, and we have people.
Yichuan,
our members are not like them.
We rely on evidence
to make decisions.
This is our ethic
in this dark age.
(In Memory of Our Father Lu Ding)
As long as you die,
Yichuan will love me.
Bury her.
Stop!
(In Memory of Our Father Lu Ding)
Fu has something to tell you.
Fu, what are you doing here?
I-I-I was
bribed to say
what I said yesterday.
Tell everyone
whether you see clearly
Concubine Su poisoning.
It is...
Fu,
think twice before you say something.
Did anyone bribe you?
Bribe?
Lu Xiaoqian, what did you do?
Now he's a dead man.
Su Kenian is the murderer.
Bury her now!
Stop!
You can't bury her.
Grandma, why are you here?
She's pregnant with Lu Ding's baby.
You can't bury her.
The baby will inherit
the Lu family's property.
She's pregnant?
Get her out of the pit.
Now I can
legitimately inherit
the Chamber of Commerce.
Then we can
restart the business at the dock.
Yes.
Why are you
so calm today?
Aren't you happy that
I'll inherit the Chamber of Commerce?
Yes.
Why are you like this?
I'm worried about you.
Why didn't you tell me you're pregnant?
Why did you confront Lu Xiaoqian alone?
If Grandma hadn't shown up in time,
you'd be dead.
You care about me,
but you pull a long face,
acting like you're teaching me a lesson.
So scary.
It will be a big deal
if I don't pull a long face.
I didn't want you to worry about me.
All the uncles were present.
If there was solid evidence,
they could have saved me
with good reason.
I didn't expect Lu Xiaoqian
to be so crazy
to kill the witness.
Fortunately,
I asked Chun to invite Grandma over
in advance.
Besides,
I just found out about it.
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
Fine.
You always have your reasons.
Come on. Don't be angry anymore.
I won't do it again.
Smile.
Promise me,
it will never happen again.
I don't want anything bad
to happen to you.
Let's go on a date.
OK.
♪We exchanged desires
on the brink of darkness♪
♪Your image appears kind of hazy♪
♪Concealed in the fog
when the wind blows♪
♪We exchanged desires
on the brink of darkness♪
♪Your image appears kind of hazy♪
♪Concealed in the fog
when the wind blows♪