♪I miss you like the wind
rises among the branches♪
♪It sweeps through my heart,
causing ripples♪
♪Reminiscing about the past in tears,
I dare not expect♪
♪You will detect this secret♪
♪I miss you like the wind
rises among the branches♪
♪It fills half of my life
with lonely gusts♪
♪The sight of you took my breath away♪
♪How can I forget easily?♪
=Sacrifice for Love=
=Episode 24=
(Talk to Me for a While)
Yichuan!
You don't have much time left.
Say anything if you want.
I'm sorry.
I should've given the ring to you
two years ago.
Now,
you are finally my wife.
Promise me
to live your life well.
Don't do anything stupid.
Yichuan.
Lu Ding,
I hope you can keep your word.
Of course, I will.
Did I promise you
not to kill her?
How could I possibly spare you?
I want to watch you suffer
and struggle
to let out my anger!
Don't worry.
Gu Manqing will reunite with you later
in hell.
They're almost here.
Who?
Master!
A lot of people are coming!
What?
- Stop them!
- Yes!
So you've been stalling all this time!
Kill them, now!
Freeze!
Master!
Move.
Hurry!
Yichuan,
what is going on?
We decided
to arrest Lu Ding
after we get evidence
of his crime.
This is hard evidence
that Lu Ding trafficked our compatriots
and killed Gu Manxi.
Lu Yichuan!
Do you know what you are doing?
You...
I know clearly.
I'm avenging
the death of Gu Manqing's sister,
exposing the murderer of my father,
consoling my uncle in heaven,
and getting justice
for the compatriots
you've harmed!
What about you?
Are you aware
of the consequences you have to bear?
Yichuan!
Lu Ding, I'm killing you!
Manqing, don't kill me!
Manqing!
I was wrong.
I shouldn't have killed your sister.
It was my fault!
Please forgive me!
Don't kill me!
Don't get your hands dirty.
Hand him over to the organization.
Yes.
Go to hell!
I'll get the doctor!
Yichuan,
are you all right?
Yichuan!
Yichuan, let's go to the hospital.
I'm OK. Talk to me for a while.
OK.
I don't
like to see you cry.
I like it better
when you chase me with a knife.
Manqing,
I'm in a lot of pain.
Can you agree to my last wish?
Of course.
♪I try to forget
with the change of seasons♪
♪But I can't erase you from my mind♪
♪I miss you like the wind
rises among the branches♪
Yichuan!
Yichuan, what are you doing?
♪You will detect this secret♪
No, Yichuan!
What are you doing?
Can you help me
like I helped your sister?
Mister. Miss.
Do you want maltose?
Sure. One bag, please.
What are you doing?
Give me the money.
Here you are, Miss.
Thanks.
All right.
Do you like maltose, too?
Want some?
When my father passed away,
I met a little girl by the river.
She liked maltose, too.
What's wrong?
My dad is gone.
I'll give you my favorite candy.
Don't cry anymore.
Thank you.
♪It fills half of my life
with lonely gusts♪
♪The sight of you took my breath away♪
When I was little,
I once gave maltose to a little boy.
He was crying sadly back then.
♪It sweeps through my heart,
causing ripples♪
♪Reminiscing about the past in tears,
I dare not expect♪
♪You will detect this secret♪
♪I miss you like the wind
rises among the branches♪
♪It fills half of my life
with lonely gusts♪
♪The sight of you took my breath away♪
♪How can I forget easily?♪
It's all over.
Here's a message from Lu Yichuan.
He hopes you can leave Nancheng
and have a good life
in the future.
This is not the end.
This is the beginning of a new era.
Where is he?
You've joined the Communist Party,
so you should've known the rules.
He could be in Beiping
or Chongqing.
You will meet
when he's cured.
I'm not leaving.
I'm going to
fulfill Lu Yichuan's unfinished mission.
I will stay in Nancheng
and witness the dawn of a new era
with him.
♪Listen with you♪
♪The wind lifts the skirt corners of time♪
♪To the beautiful melody
from yesterday♪
♪The stars in the night sky are quiet♪
♪I am captivated♪
♪The solemn pledge of love♪
♪Is nothing
compared to our encounter♪
♪How can I comprehend my heart?♪
♪Trail the sail's deep blue shadow♪
♪Flash across the vast azure sky♪
♪I am sure the love is true♪
♪It awakens after death♪
♪The clouds seem to be within reach♪
♪There is the dreamlike distance
between us♪
♪I choose to fly
in the opposite direction of the sea♪
♪Lost control of my heart
after falling in love with you♪
♪We exchanged desires
on the brink of darkness♪
♪Your image appears kind of hazy♪
♪The coast line kisses
and caresses silence♪
♪Concealed in the fog
when the wind blows♪
♪My love is unveiled
when the fog disperses♪
♪We exchanged desires
on the brink of darkness♪
♪Your image appears kind of hazy♪
♪The coast line kisses
and caresses silence♪
♪Concealed in the fog
when the wind blows♪
♪My love is unveiled
when the fog disperses♪