♪I miss you like the wind
rises among the branches♪
♪It sweeps through my heart,
causing ripples♪
♪Reminiscing about the past in tears,
I dare not expect♪
♪You will detect this secret♪
♪I miss you like the wind
rises among the branches♪
♪It fills half of my life
with lonely gusts♪
♪The sight of you took my breath away♪
♪How can I forget easily?♪
=Sacrifice for Love=
=Episode 21=
(Oh No, Manqing Is in Danger)
Who called the police?
I did.
My maid found some unknown medicine
in Miss Lu's room.
I hope you can check it, officer.
So you knew about my plan.
But it doesn't matter
even if you expose it.
You can't do anything to me.
This is
the poison in
the Chamber of Commerce murder case.
What?
What I bought was abortion medicine.
How could it be poison?
Su Kenian!
Are you taking revenge on me?
How dare you change the medicine
and frame me?
You!
Lu Xiaoqian, don't be stubborn
and make mistakes repeatedly!
Yichuan.
I didn't do it!
Please trust me!
Say that
in the police station.
Lu Yichuan!
Why did you do this to me?
I've loved you
for so many years.
Don't you know that?
Miss Lu,
please go to the police station with us.
I can walk.
Miss Lu, what else do you need?
I can get them for you.
That woman thought
she could control the Lu family.
In her wildest dream.
Please give your orders.
Closer.
I want to report
the Chamber of Commerce's business.
I wonder if she can
still be the chairwoman
when the Chamber is in trouble.
Miss Lu, please think twice.
Uh...
Although the police station never asked
about Mr. Lu's business,
it is connected
with the interests of half of Nancheng.
If there's something that I can't get,
I'd rather destroy it
than watch her get it.
What's more,
Su Kenian
is the perfect scapegoat for this.
By the way,
tell Lu Yichuan to bail me out.
I can't stay
in this nasty place any longer.
Yes.
Yichuan!
Why did you bring her here?
Want to meet Lu Yichuan?
He won't come to see you
after you caused him
so much trouble.
Nonsense!
Yichuan wouldn't be so heartless to me!
Why not?
Lu Xiaoqian,
have you forgotten what you've done?
You! It was you!
You ruined my family!
You made Yichuan hate me!
It's all your fault!
Lu Xiaoqian,
you are so hypocritical.
I never hurt you.
You kidnapped me.
You wanted to kill me.
You threatened Lu Yichuan
with my life
to marry you.
I want to make a deal with you,
using her life.
What is it?
I want you to marry me.
Otherwise,
you know what will happen.
Lu Xiaoqian,
you are cruel and selfish.
You disregard human life
and confuse right and wrong.
You and Lu Yichuan are destined
to be on different paths.
Don't you understand?
You pushed him
further and further away.
Even without me,
Lu Yichuan wouldn't be with you.
It wasn't me.
I didn't do it!
I didn't!
It wasn't me!
It's you!
Su Kenian!
It's all your fault!
(Xue Fuming Law Firm)
Now, I think
I should be qualified
to cooperate with Mr. Smith.
Mrs. Lu, you are such a speed demon.
The Lu family never
neglects Mr. Smith's business.
Mrs. Lu is more capable than I thought.
When will the goods be available?
Anytime.
In fact, I invited you over today
because I want
to talk about a bigger deal.
Apart from human trafficking,
the Lu family is willing
to cooperate with Mr. Smith
on any business that can make money,
be it opium or arms.
You don't have to worry about any risk,
because we will deliver the goods first
and you pay the bill later.
You will definitely be successful.
Fine. Let me sign it.
(Gu Manqing)
Zhang Kai.
Freeze!
What's this for?
Nothing.
Mr. Smith, if you can hand over
the list of your accomplices,
you might get the chance
to go home in your lifetime.
- You...
- Take him away.
- Move.
(In Memory of Our Father Chen Ren)
- Dad.
- Manxi.
We've avenged your deaths.
Wait.
What's wrong?
Your sister's posture seemed strange.
Where's the pocket watch?
In my room.
I'll go get it now.
The shady business at the dock
is still going on.
It should have been stopped.
Who is running it?
Zhang Kai.
Do you know
who else in the Lu family smokes?
I think no one smokes
except Lu Ding.
Why do you ask?
In my memory,
my father didn't smoke either.
He didn't smoke.
So what?
That means
no lighter should have been found
on my father's body.
But Lu Ding said
it was my father's.
Wasn't it found on your father's body?
The things found on my father's body
may not belong to my father.
They may belong to the murderer.
It was Lu Ding who poisoned my father.
He couldn't have poisoned himself.
Oh no, Manqing is in danger!
♪How should I
embellish my life without you?♪
♪When I think of you,
I probe for the news about you♪
♪In front of the mirror,
stand half of me and half of you♪
♪In a trance,
it feels like we merged into one♪
♪The replay of the past scenes
goes on and on♪
♪Where else can I escape?♪
♪The satirical longing passes by♪
♪I struggle to break free from its grip♪
♪You even take away my happiness♪
♪Where else can I escape?♪
♪Memories occupy
the very last corner of my mind♪
♪Don't make me remember♪
♪Until this day♪
♪I was deeply loved by you♪