♪I miss you like the wind
suddenly rises among the branches♪
♪It sweeps through my heart,
causing ripples♪
♪Reminiscing about the past,
dare not expect♪
♪You will detect this secret♪
♪I miss you like the wind
suddenly rises among the branches♪
♪It fills half of my life
with lonely gusts♪
♪The sight of you took my breath away♪
♪How can I forget easily?♪
=Sacrifice for Love=
=Episode 8=
(Let Me Tell Her Myself)
Darling, I want to take a break.
I'm afraid it's too late.
Don't do it for nothing.
I'm just tired
because I don't dance often.
Fine. Take some rest.
Steady your hands.
Fire.
♪Fallen flowers figured autumn out♪
♪They bid farewell in the moonlight♪
♪It's like our fate♪
♪After we parted,
our love turned to dust♪
♪Away faded our indelible feelings♪
♪Going through
the unavoidable ups and downs♪
♪I try to forget
along with the change of seasons♪
♪But I can't erase you from my mind♪
I'm glad you're okay, Yichuan.
♪It sweeps through my heart,
causing ripples♪
♪Reminiscing about the past,
dare not expect♪
♪You will detect this secret♪
♪I miss you like the wind
suddenly rises among the branches♪
♪It fills half of my life
with lonely gusts♪
♪The sight of you took my breath away♪
♪How can I forget easily?♪
♪Away faded our indelible feelings♪
♪Going through
the unavoidable ups and downs♪
♪I try to forget
along with the change of seasons♪
♪But I can't erase you from my mind♪
You are alive.
I was so desperate
when I thought I would lose you.
I was thinking about it on my way here.
I thought you were really…
What should I do?
I couldn't think of anything.
If you really…
Thank God you are alive.
You've always wanted to kill me.
As long as you are alive,
as long as you can wake up,
you can kill me anytime you like,
because I love you.
Yichuan!
Manqing.
It's okay, it's okay.
Yichuan, please don't leave!
I'm here!
It's okay, Manqing. It's okay.
I'm going to prepare some medicine.
I'll be right back.
Useless!
Now I have to do it myself.
Yichuan, you are finally back.
Lu Xiaoqian, I've warned you
not to hurt her.
This is the first time
you pointed a gun at me.
Are you going to kill me?
I will.
Then she dies, too.
You can't kill two people
with one shot after all.
Put the gun down and let's talk.
I won't.
You won't listen to me if I put it down.
What do you want?
You know clearly what I want.
I love you.
I give all my love to you.
I treat you so well.
But you still don't want to marry me.
Why?
You can hate me.
I don't hate you.
I can't hate you.
So I hate her.
She is the reason for everything.
Lu Yichuan,
I finally found your weakness.
So don't worry.
I won't kill her now.
I want to make a deal with you,
using her life.
What is it?
Even if I can't win your heart,
I want you.
I want you to marry me.
Otherwise, you know what will happen.
Xiaoqian! Stop!
Put the gun down!
I won't!
You…
Dad, you hired a killer to kill Yichuan.
Why must I go soft on Su Kenian?
Don't move.
You both think she's precious,
but she's nothing in my eyes.
Lu Yichuan, I am not a patient person
and you know it.
I'll count down to three.
If you don't agree,
I'll kill her.
Three.
Two.
Yichuan!
I agree!
Really?
On one condition.
What?
I'll tell her about
the engagement myself.
♪How should I
embellish my life without you?♪
♪The thoughts of you
bring only the news about you♪
♪In front of the mirror,
stand half of me and half of you♪
♪In a trance,
it feels like we merged into one♪
♪The replay of the past scenes
goes on and on♪
♪Where else can I escape?♪
♪The satirical longing passes by♪
♪I struggle to break free from its grip♪
♪You even take away my happiness♪
♪Where else can I escape?♪
♪Memories occupy
the very last corner of my mind♪
♪Don't make me remember♪
♪Until this day♪
♪I was deeply loved by you♪