I think we should drop this whole "dating" act.
What if we weren't acting?
Yukino-san, what if I said I like you?
Would you go out with me for real?
Oh, come on, Aoshima-kun.
Is this another one of your jokes?
I wasn't—
I have some work to finish back at my place.
I'll need to get it done.
Sorry. It's late so I'll see you home.
No, it's fine.
- But—
- Really, I'll manage.
See you.
[Aoshima-kun Is a Bully!]
What? Aoshima-kun confessed to you?
Quiet!
So? Tell me everything.
I think it was just another of his jokes.
Don't say you fled without even giving him an answer.
Joke or not,
a confession from a guy, nine years your junior, is a rarity.
Not to mention that junior is Aoshima-kun.
It's a rarity, but nothing more.
And why confess to me, of all people?
Who cares? How do you feel?
Were you offended by his confession or something?
Not exactly...
- See?
- But—
- But what?
- I've been tormented by romance.
I just want a calm life, with no drama. That's all.
Besides, we're nine years apart. It would never work out.
Would you have dated him if he were our age?
Well...
As your reflex, you're just trying to prevent a crisis.
You're running from the issue,
because you fear you'll end up hurt.
Your feelings for Aoshima-kun are true, and you know it.
What are you so desperate to protect at the cost of lying to yourself?
How come Takako is so harsh?
She's too logical.
Time to drink my worries away!
[Banraitei Bar]
Are you eating pig's feet again?
It's my food, my choice.
I'm glad to see you today, Yukino-san.
I might run into Aoshima-kun here.
[Reiko Snack Bar]
Good evening!
Oh my, are you here for relationship advice again?
"Advice"? No way.
You both just love to make it a conversation topic.
All in good fun. Right, Reiko-chan?
Of course, anything for our adorable son.
Today's update: he made this girl worry for nothing,
then she took his confession as a joke.
What an absolute fool you are.
A fool indeed.
Your suave good looks won't let you get away with everything, Dear.
I do regret alarming her like that,
but my confession was serious.
Maybe it's because I'm younger.
So she's older, by how much?
- Nine years, she's 35.
- I see, so she's 35...
Wait, 35 years old?
Now I see why she's unattainable.
No wonder she dodged all of your advances.
She's 35 years old.
I don't think age matters.
That's what love-sruck boys say. We ladies get perplexed though.
Say, isn't your new husband 10 years your junior?
He is. This story takes place right after my divorce.
I got absolutely fed up with Mizuki's father and our marriage.
I don't blame you. That man is not husband material whatsoever.
I thought romance was not in the cards for me anymore,
but my husband now is both passionate and kind.
He never relented in courting me.
Like a warrior, forging through a castle with only his blade before him.
Was the war a tough one?
Not for him, I was powerless in the face of his passion.
How thrilling! What happened next?
- What do you think happened?
- Tell me!
Tune in next week to find out.
What is this?
I never knew there was so much drama.
Right?
"A guy 9 years younger confessed to me."
"What should I do?"
And the answers say:
"This is the opportunity of a lifetime."
"If you don't date him,"
"you will be a crying idiot."
People say all they want when it's not their problem, right?
I thought I was beyond romance.
What am I trying to protect, by pursuing an easy, simple life?
I don't know.
­ [July 24, 14:27]
Oh my gosh, this is awkward.
Good afternoon.
This is bad.
What if he pulls that move again?
He's not making any moves.
The doors will be closing.
This is even more awkward.
I need to say something.
So...
I'm so sorry for the other day.
It's fine. I'm not bothered by it.
On that note, I want to tell you something, Yukino-san.
What is it?
We can drop the dating act.
What?
Feel free to tell everyone we broke up.
That's all.
The doors will be closing.
I almost forgot.
Just so you know, my confession was not a joke.
The doors will be closing.
Why do we have to work on a weekend?
And all the way in Yugawara.
[Yugawara Hot Spring Resort]
Besides, it's an outdoor event to promote sales, not general affairs.
Why are we forced to help out?
It can't be helped due to another event.
They are short-staffed
- Here.
- Thank you.
Now get folding.
I don't mind helping out from time to time though.
Kimura-san, you look happy though you're losing a whole day off.
That's because my boyfriend will come pick me up
for a hot spring date afterward.
- Really?
- He even booked us for a famous inn.
No wonder you're in high spirits.
It'll get me through the day. I need the motivation.
Fair point, I totally understand.
Then what about you, Katsuragi-san?
What? Me?
You could invite Aoshima.
I doubt he will be available even if I do.
He said work has been slowing down for him.
I'm sure he's still busy.
Besides, Aoshima-kun prefers to work on his days off.
He might be called in to fix our systems again.
I bet Aoshima would drop everything if you invited him, though.
He is madly in love with you, after all!
- Tomorrow?
- Yes.
I don't have any particular plans.
Great. Come visit us then.
We go to Yugawara to help at the promotional event.
Why should I?
Because your beloved Katsuragi-san will also be there?
Yukino-san will be there?
I told her to invite you, but she didn't think you would come.
I bet she's being considerate, since you're usually busy.
As expected, Katsuragi-san truly is a wonderful girlfriend.
A hot spring date after work?
No, I am not jealous or anything.
Just so you know, my confession was not a joke.
He was just teasing; that's all.
Right then.
[Miyakaze Park Main Stage]
Our team is expected to give out all of these samples today.
This much? Won't we have leftovers?
It's getting hot. We could give them all out soon.
Let's liven this event together!
- Yes, Ma'am!
- Great.
Ready to go.
Good morning.
Aoshima! Thanks for coming.
Aoshima-kun? Why?
I invited him since he said he was free,
and you felt bad inviting him yourself, Katsuragi-san.
He came today to see you? You two are so lovey-dovey!
I'm jealous.
Kimura-san, your boyfriend is coming after your shift, too, isn't he?
- I suppose.
- Lucky you.
Right, but...­
Cute accessory.
Should I help?
- No...
- Relax, Dude.
It's your day off.
Go and chill in the shade over there.
Wait!
Here, one for you.
- Thanks.
- Your essential "Blue Punch."
Refreshing cider!
Congratulations to our winner!
Please try a bottle of our newest product, Blue Punch.
Give it a try.
Would you like a Blue Punch?
Please try a bottle of our newest product, Blue Punch.
These bottles don't dwindle one bit.
Tanizaki-kun.
Make sure you stay hydrated.
Right.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
Kimura-san, don't push yourself. Take breaks if you need to, okay?
I will.
Please try our Blue Punch!
We have Blue Punch right here!
Would you like some Blue Punch?
We're not doing so well.
We still have many boxes left.
I suppose the sales team gives out samples in the main area.
Compared to their area, less people are here.
Let's not give up yet.
We can do only our best, right?
I'll help.
Aoshima.
We can do this. Let's get through our whole stock.
No, but...
Would you all like some Blue Punch?
How about some Blue Punch?
Please try our Blue Punch.
Who's that?
Blue Punch, anyone?
- I'd like one.
- Thank you.
- Here you go.
For you.
We can do this. This is our chance!
Blue Punch, anyone?
Here you go!
Please, take one!
For you.
We still have plenty more.
Please try our Blue Punch.
Here you go.
­Thank you for your hard work.
- Great work, you all.
- You, too.
Man, I'm glad we could deplete our whole stock!
We have everyone's hard work to thank for that.
Aoshima-kun, too. Thanks for helping.
You're welcome.
Oh, my boyfriend is calling.
I'll get going then.
- See you.
- Enjoy.
Where are you?
- I'll be heading out as well.
- Sure.
Thanks for coming and helping today, Aoshima.
Since I can read the room, you two enjoy yourselves, yes?
Goodbye, you both.
- Don't forget this.
- Thank you.
I'll put it here.
See you two at the office!
Looks like it's just us two now.
Shall we get going as well?
I'm not actually heading straight home today.
What?
I booked a night at a nearby hot spring resort for myself.
So we will part ways—
Excuse me, are you people with Cats Beverage Inc.?
We are, yes.
How could they forget so many things?
We will have to take it back ourselves.
Should I call Tanizaki back here?
It's fine; I'll carry it all back.
All this by yourself, again?
What did I tell you about relying on me?
Sorry to have you help with everything.
It's fine with me.
Aoshima-kun, you can head home now. I'll carry the rest in.
Maybe I'll stay a night with you.
What?
I'm already here. I might as well dip in the hot springs.
Right, I understand.
But staying the night, together?
I never said we'd be in the same room.
I'll ask for an available room.
I was able to book a room.
I don't usually visit hot springs so this is nice.
I see.
That's good to hear.
Then I guess I'll head to my room.
Right. Thanks for helping me carry all this.
Of course.
Yes?
Tomorrow, let's meet to leave together.
I'll help you carry all of this.
Oh, right. Sounds good.
I'll see you then.
We can do this.
Let's get through our whole stock.
What did I tell you about relying on me?
I got his help with many things all day.
Maybe I should have thanked him somehow.
Oh, shoot!
[Are you free to meet later?]
[Shall we share a couple of drinks together?]
She's probably exhausted.
Aoshima-kun? You took a dip as well?
I did.
Aren't the hot springs nice?
They fulfill their reputation.
They sure do.
All right, then good night.
Thanks for your help today.
Good night. See you tomorrow.
By the way...
I'd like to thank you for today.
How about we share some drinks?
Cheers.
[Blue Heron]
Well, I invited him over.
Is more expected to come out of this?
No. We're just drinking in my room.
Right, I invited him to my room. Does he think I'm seducing him?
What do I do?
These vitamins are great for hangovers.
Give them a try for tomorrow.
Thank you.
I bet your legs are sore, too.
This massager helps with that.
Here, give it a try.
Thanks for this.
Also, here.
Ta-da.
Wear these to sleep, and you won't feel bloated in the morning.
It should fit.
Then thank you.
Oh my. I've run out of things to say.
If it comes to this...
Let's drink ourselves silly. We have tomorrow morning off anyway.
Not that.
Yukino-san.
Yes?
♫ A feeling of love that begins unexpectedly ♫
♫ It was like an unbelievable episode ♫
♫ Today would have been just another day ♫
♫ But you changed it all ♫
We're already here.
I won't let you use alcohol as an excuse tonight.
♫ But I can be myself with you ♫
♫ You must be special. I believe ♫
♫ I've never felt like this before ♫
♫ Once I recognize it, it's unstoppable ♫
♫ I was looking for you ♫
♫ You are my destiny. Oh, my lady ♫
♫ Sweet love story. I'm in love ♫
♫ My heart is pounding more than I expected ♫
♫ You are shining so bright that I feel I'm dreaming ♫
♫ Nobody can replace you ♫
♫ I've been in love since the day we met ♫
♫ My feelings for you are about to overflow ♫
♫ Always be with me. You are mine ♫