=Sword Rose=
=Episode 12=
Calm down.
The police brought our child back.
Oh, my Jing!
Why were you there?
You disappeared so suddenly.
Don't run off again. Do you hear me?
Ma'am.
I'm a police officer.
We brought your daughter back to you.
Look at her.
She is all grown up now.
Mom,
it's me, Jing.
I'm home.
Jing?
You...
Look at me.
It's me, Jing.
I'm home.
Please stop this.
I'll never leave you again.
Please be all right.
Please?
It's me, Mom. I'm Jing.
Mom...
Please be okay...
That poor family.
Their daughter is back,
but the mother has lost her mind.
Human traffickers have no conscience.
How could he bring himself to do it?
People like that
will do anything for money.
Nothing is beneath them.
A child is the heart of a family.
Once a child is taken,
the whole family falls apart.
Some wounds
can only be healed by time.
But the good thing is,
the daughter is home now.
I'm sure her mother
will get better with time.
So,
as long as we never give up,
there will always be a day
the families reunite again, right?
Yes.
There will be a day
when families reunite.
That'll be 76.
Did you pack the duck eggs?
Yes.
Thank you.
(Wanted: Wang Guangqing)
We received a tip from a local
that a suspicious man
resembling Wang Guangqing
was seen in the outskirts
of Hongxi City, in an urban village.
I want the Anti-Abduction Office
and the Criminal Police Unit
to act together.
We can't let Wang Guangqing
get away again.
Understood.
Deng,
this operation is critical.
Leave Chang Rui out of it.
Let him rest.
That's Chief Xiao's instruction too.
(Linshan City Police Bureau)
Director Deng told you to take a break,
didn't she?
What are you doing here?
Where's the rest of the unit?
They're out on a mission.
I don't know the details.
I just know they contacted
the Hongxi City Criminal Police Unit.
If you really want to go,
give Director Deng a call.
They just left not long ago.
(Linshan City Police Bureau)
Captain Wang.
Hello.
This is the captain
of Hongxi City's Criminal Police Unit.
Hello.
This is our new Director Deng.
Nice to meet you.
Please tell us the situation.
We got the call
and came over immediately.
We're certain
that Wang Guangqing is hiding inside.
We just can't confirm which unit yet.
We've been waiting for you
to decide how to proceed.
If we can catch Cripple
through Skinner,
that would really help the case.
Yes.
We can't act yet.
He might still be in contact
with Cripple.
Keep watching.
Director Deng,
you haven't eaten all day.
Eat something.
The phone.
Yes, Captain Wang.
Director Deng, I have an update.
While checking surveillance,
Captain Wang found
that Skinner once used a public phone
to call a number.
He checked it out
and found the number
was disconnected a few days ago.
The person registered to that number
died two years ago.
Got it.
Director Deng,
if the number is disconnected,
does that mean Cripple
has already cut ties with Skinner?
No.
Mr. Yin said
Cripple is ruthless.
He kills every trafficker
who's seen him.
But Skinner has worked with him
on many cases
and is still alive.
Why would Cripple let him live?
I bet
they're still in contact.
Director Deng,
it's another call from Rui.
Are we really not going to tell him?
I can't keep this up.
Not yet.
Director Deng, Skinner is on the move.
He's heading toward the riverbank.
Everyone, follow him.
Copy that.
Move out!
(July 29, 2009,
River Cargo Dock, Linshan City)
Skinner's likely trying
to escape by water.
All units, stay alert.
Copy that.
Attention, all units.
Suspicious boat spotted.
Director Deng,
we can't move freely on the water.
Should we make a move now?
Not yet.
We want him
to lead us to Cripple
and whoever he answers to.
Let's see who else is on that boat.
Wang Guangqing!
Chang Rui?
Move in!
Call the water police! Stop that boat!
Copy.
It's the police! Run!
Hurry!
Pull Chang Rui out!
Let go of me!
Rui!
Let me go!
Let go of me!
Rui!
Chang Rui! Chang Rui!
Chang Rui! Calm yourself!
Hurry!
Take him away.
Quickly!
Get him secured and take him away.
Regroup.
Chang Rui,
you were completely out of line!
You acted without orders
the moment you got emotional.
You ruined the whole plan!
Because of your impulsiveness,
we might have lost the lead on Cripple.
Can you take responsibility for that?
What were you thinking?
I wanted to beat him to death.
Chang Rui, watch your language!
Han, look at him.
Does this look like
the descendant of a fallen hero?
You're reckless.
I'm telling you right now,
you're done questioning suspects.
Do you hear me?
How am I supposed to stay calm?
My father saved that man's life.
Now he's turned into a criminal.
That means my dad died for nothing.
I want to kill him
to make up for it.
Fine.
Inspection Unit, tell your captain
to send two officers to my office.
Keep your mouth shut!
No need.
I'll go myself.
All right, you've got guts. Go ahead.
Chang Rui!
(Chief's Office)
Chang Rui?
Chief Xiao. Captain Han.
Chief Xiao, please calm down.
As his superior,
I should take responsibility
for what Chang Rui did.
Forget about the brig.
Let him reflect for a few days...
Both of you, get out.
Now you want to play the good guys?
Where were you during the operation?
Where? Huh?
Why are you still here?
Chief Xiao,
please calm down.
I know you're saying this
out of anger.
Chang Rui is grieving his father.
Anyone would be upset.
I won't calm down!
Deng Yan, listen up.
I understand this situation
better than anyone.
Chang Rui's father, Chang Yongjun,
was my comrade-in-arms.
The partner I trusted most.
Trusted.
Do you understand?
Now he's gone,
it's my responsibility
to discipline his son!
I understand.
(Brig)
Director Deng, Rui is being held
in disciplinary detention?
Can't we help him?
It's not fair to him.
We'll question Wang Guangqing first.
(For The People)
(Interrogation Room)
Wang Guangqing,
talk.
Talk about what?
I don't even know why I'm here.
You don't know?
Why do you think we brought you in?
Honestly,
I'm just as confused as you are.
Why was I arrested?
You cops always say
you can't let a bad guy go,
but you also can't pin something
on someone innocent.
So, how could you arrest
a good guy like me?
How old are you,
Miss?
Listen.
I'll play
the good guy today.
Here's a tip.
Bring in someone older
and more experienced
to question me.
All right?
Wang Guangqing.
Cut it out.
Okay, okay.
Sorry.
Come on.
Let's get started.
Let's begin.
Do you know Bai Wentao?
No.
What about Zhao Dafeng?
Don't know him either.
Mangshan Villa,
and the station by Mangjiang?
That place?
I don't really remember.
So you don't know anything.
But you do know Zheng Weiwei, right?
Looking at the photo,
I don't really recognize her,
but the name sounds familiar.
Zheng Weiwei...
I remember now.
Zheng Weiwei was in the class
next to mine back in elementary school.
She was cute,
just a little chubby.
It's been over a decade
since we last saw each other.
I have no idea what she looks like now.
What do they say again?
Time flies.
Youth doesn't come back.
Now,
I'm just old.
Wang Guangqing!
Enough with the nonsense.
We're talking
about the Zheng Weiwei you kidnapped.
Officer,
you scared me.
I thought you were going to hit me.
This is a law-abiding society.
We don't go around hitting people.
Sorry,
I was out of line.
I'll cooperate.
I will.
Let's start over.
Ready? Go.
(Wang Guangqing)
After every successful abduction,
Wang Guangqing picks a group of girls
and forces them into prostitution.
The rest are sold off
to remote mountain villages as brides.
Even if we can't get a lead on Cripple
through Wang Guangqing,
we might still uncover clues
about Huang Chuan.
But no matter how hard
we interrogate him,
he won't say a word.
He's completely unfazed.
Should we try Director Deng's tactic
and show him
the miserable lives of the girls
he trafficked?
Wang Guangqing is a shameless,
contemptible lowlife.
If anything could break him,
he wouldn't still be committing crimes.
Well, we can't just sit idly.
Mr. Yin,
should we let Chang Rui have a shot?
All right.
Chief Xiao, Skinner isn't talking.
He's a repeat offender.
The usual interrogation tactics
won't work on him.
I'm thinking an emotional approach
might be worth a try.
But if we go that route,
we might need to bring Chang Rui in.
Can we get him released early?
That's your solution?
You want to release Chang Rui early?
Let me be clear.
Three days means three full days.
Not a minute less.
Chief Xiao...
He broke the rules
and must face the consequences.
As a police officer
and the child of a hero,
he should hold himself
to an even higher standard.
I don't buy that you don't have
any other investigative options.
Deng Yan,
do you know why I transferred you
to the Anti-abduction Office?
Think about it.
(Han, look at him.)
(Does this look like
the descendant of a fallen hero?)
(October 19)
(is a heartbreaking day.)
(To save a drowning boy
named Wang Guangqing,)
(Chief Chang Yongjun
of Nanyangdian Police Station)
(tragically drowned.)
(He died at the age of 43.)
(Linshan City Police Bureau)
(Deng Yan,)
(do you know why I transferred you
to the Anti-abduction Office?)
(Think about it.)
Mrs. Zheng.
All right.
I'll be right there.
Please come in.
Director Deng, I'm so glad you're here.
After Weiwei was discharged
from the hospital,
she locked herself in her room
and wouldn't come out.
I'm worried
she might do something reckless.
I understand. Where is she?
She's in this room.
Please check on her.
Weiwei,
your mom called me.
She said you haven't
been sleeping well recently
and asked me
to spend some time with you.
The weather's nice today.
Looking out at the kids playing outside
reminded me of a girl
I met recently.
Let me tell you her story.
She's incredibly
kind,
brave,
smart,
and talented.
She plays the guzheng.
At just 13,
she became the last disciple
of the most famous
traditional music master
in Linshan City.
She's also
a gifted writer.
Her work has even
been published in magazines.
I brought a copy of one of her pieces.
I'll share it with you.
"A sailboat drifts across the ocean,
like a kite floating in the sky.
Without wind,
the boat cannot move forward,
and the kite cannot soar.
But sometimes, often even,
the wind doesn't blow in your favor.
The boat must face calm seas
or strong currents.
The kite must fight
against howling winds.
Maybe
that's just like life itself..."
Stop.
Just stop.
That piece won a gold award
just a few days ago.
See?
When I read it, I wondered,
if I were that girl,
facing a tsunami ready
to swallow everything,
could I be
as brave?
Could I stay calm, think fast,
and ultimately pilot the plane
that leads everyone to safety?
In the story, all the villains'
evil deeds were uncovered,
and every person who hurt you
was held accountable.
They sold me to a nightclub.
Someone called Mr. Li
would come by all the time.
If I didn't behave,
they'd yell at me and even hit me.
One time, I scratched Mr. Li's hand,
and they pulled out my nails.
I've been busy lately.
I must've forgotten to trim your nails.
Skinner, get in here!
What is it, Mr. Li?
This girl's nails
are getting a little long.
Take care of it.
Sorry, Mr. Li.
We'll handle it right away.
Come here!
No!
Hold still!
Oh, you're really going to do it.
I see him in my dreams
every night.
I'm so scared.
You don't have to be scared anymore.
You have us now.
You have your mom and dad.
We'll protect you.
And back then,
you weren't afraid.
You chose to be brave.
Do you remember Pingjiao?
She survived too.
She even helped us
catch those criminals.
How is she?
Don't worry about her.
She's back with her parents now,
just like you.
To me,
you're both just like
the girl from the story.
Brave enough to stand firm
in the face of a tsunami.
Please sit down.
She's already asleep.
She refuses to go back to school.
Her father and I are very worried.
But with both of our family situations
being what they are,
you know how tough it's been.
We didn't want to upset Weiwei,
so we rented a place close
to the school.
Still, ever since she left the hospital,
she's been locked up in her room,
and nothing I say seems to reach her.
In the end, I thought of you.
This is all my fault.
If I hadn't gotten divorced,
maybe none of this would have happened.
Mrs. Zheng,
please don't blame yourself so much.
Right now,
try not to bring up family
or school issues around Weiwei.
After all she's been through,
what she really needs is your care
and quiet support.
Weiwei is sensitive
and proud.
She probably isn't ready to face family
or school just yet.
Please talk to her father too.
You two need
to be there for her, to understand
and support her.
We can't rush things.
We have to take it slow.
Healing
takes time.
All right,
Director Deng.
I'll take good care of her.
Director Deng,
you have to catch those scumbags.
I want every last one of them taken down.
Rest assured. We'll find them,
arrest them,
and bring them to justice.
Thank you.
(Linshan City Police Bureau)
(I went to visit Zheng Weiwei.)
She mentioned two key figures.
Mr. Li and the man with sunglasses.
Since Skinner isn't talking,
we'll start with those two.
Jiajia, pull up the surveillance footage
from the Play House raid.
That should be
the first time Zheng Weiwei saw Mr. Li.
(Play House Security Corridor)
Do you recognize this girl?
Do you?
No.
No?
She recognizes you,
and you were the one
who handed her over to Mr. Li.
Who's Mr. Li?
I don't know him.
All right, then.
We'll come back another time.
By the way,
we got a call a few days ago.
Your mom had a bad fall.
She's in the hospital now.
That can't be true.
My mom's perfectly healthy.
Chen A'mo,
do you think we'd joke
about something like that?
She fell and had to be admitted.
The doctor said it's serious.
What happened?
When did this happen?
Right when you got arrested.
She panicked and fell.
Is she okay now?
What...
What did the doctor say?
Does she have money for treatment?
I see you do have some conscience left.
You told your mom
you wanted
to start a small business in Linshan
and take care of her.
You planning
to take care of her from prison?
I just wanted
to give her a better life. I...
Is someone looking after her?
We've already arranged
for someone to help her out.
Chen A'mo,
you know your options.
Think hard about what you want to do.
Based on Zheng Weiwei's testimony
and what the two girls we rescued
during the Play House raid said,
I've identified 17 adult men
who were at the club during that time.
Print out all their photos for me.
Yes.
That's him.
That's Mr. Li.
Are you sure?
Skinner and I have seen him a few times.
I know it's him.
Honey.
Food's ready.
Honey!
Come here!
Let's eat.
You were in the kitchen for so long,
and this is all you made?
I just wanted to make the meal perfect.
What's this?
I completely forgot...
I... Honey...
Honey.
Honey, I really...
I really forgot.
I'm sorry.
What do you ever remember?
How many times have I told you
that I hate that smell?
I know.
Things at the company
have been so hectic lately.
I promise I'll remember next time.
The company?
And who gave you the company, huh?
Without my family,
would you even have that company?
Yes, well...
Forget about the soup.
I made fish
and shrimp too.
Let's have some fish.
Eat it yourself. I've lost my appetite.
Where are you going?
Whatever.
The nerve of that woman...
Who is it?
Who are you?
(Yan Lei, Police)
We're from Linshan City Police Bureau.
You must be Lu Sheng.
We'll need you to come with us.
(Summons)
(Interrogation Room)
Why did you bring me here?
You even had a mandatory police summons.
What's the meaning of this?
What did I even do?
Do you know this girl?
No.
What's she got to do with me?
You must know this guy at least.
Officer,
I see so many people every day.
How could I possibly remember
all of them?
Take a good look at him.
No idea who he is.
Zheng Weiwei not being able to come
is definitely a problem.
Yes, for now,
we'll have to rely on Chen A'mo's ID
to figure out our next move.
Look at the lineup.
Do you recognize anyone?
Him.
I know him.
That's Mr. Li.
Rape? I raped her?
I don't even know her.
Why would I rape someone I don't know?
You'll probably say
you don't know this guy too, right?
Of course...
Do you know him or not?
I don't know him.
But he knows you.
He saw all the filthy deeds
you committed.
Chen A'mo has already identified you
as the one who raped the victim.
How do you explain that?
Explain what?
This is a setup! A false accusation!
I didn't do anything.
I'm telling you, I've never
even seen those people.
They're just trying
to scam me for money!
They're extorting me!
Officer, you've got to believe me!
They're lying.
Believe me!
I'm a law-abiding citizen.
Where's my lawyer?
Call my lawyer.
I'm not saying another word
until my lawyer's here.
I think you're on their side.
You're the police,
you know that?
That scumbag's a real piece of work.
What's going on?
Lu Sheng denies
everything.
He keeps insisting he's innocent.
Director Deng,
Lu Sheng's wife just arrived.
She wants to see you.
Arresting someone without evidence
is a legal risk.
Surely the police understand that?
Ms. Cai,
we don't arrest people without cause.
We'd like to know what crime
Mr. Lu is suspected of.
Can you at least tell us
what evidence you have?
The case is still under investigation.
We can't share
too many details right now.
♪What kind of person do you want to be?♪
♪A beacon in the night,
lighting the way for others♪
♪A brave soul♪
♪No matter the role I play♪
♪My heart stays true♪
♪Through it all, I became who I am♪
♪I walked my youth
with nothing to regret♪
♪Bearing love's pain,
I fight for the impossible♪
♪Never letting down
those unwavering eyes♪
♪Go on river, just keep flowing♪
♪With steady eyes, I raise my hand♪
♪The gentle strength of navy blue,
one moment etched in eternity♪
♪Once I choose this path,
I won't turn back♪
♪Let time come and go as it will♪
♪There's always someone
behind the spotlight♪
♪What we cherish in time
stays forever new♪
♪Just like my heart♪
♪It will never rust♪
♪This heart in navy blue♪
♪Will never rust♪