Production: Takeshobo Co., Ltd.
Shintoho Company, Ltd.
Xmv-nﬂm: (WO-IZVU DOJO
Pricks. Move!
You son of a bitch!
And who are you?
I'm Shining Muroto.
I've come to challenge your dojo!
Bring out your master!
I am Rin Saejima.
I am the master of this Shin-Kage Itto-ryu dojo.
Huh. Well, well. A WOMAN, huh?
I shall be your opponent.
If I win, this dojo is mine.
And you'll be my woman.
I'll fuckin' kill you!
Dammit...
The Sultry
Assassin
The Sultry Assassin
Aphrodisiac Killer
Man, that's nice!
Is someone there?
W-wait!
She's burning up!
Wh-what are you...?!
You had a terrible fever,
so at the risk of being forward...
I see. Thank you.
There's no need for thanks.
You seem to be of a military family.
Why were you dressed so?
I cannot say. Do you
also practice the sword ans?
I'm still just a student.
What is your name?
L-| am Yasaburo.
I came here to Edo from a small village
in Shimofusa to study the sword ans.
I am Rin Saejima. I am master
of the Shin-Kage Itto-ryu dojo.
Come visit my dojo.
You shouldn't be moving yet.
Ah! I-I'm sorry.
I wish to thank you.
Th-there's no need for thanks.
A dream?
An illusion? No.
This is definitely real. My hand is still warm.
In any case, I'm glad that you're safe.
I'm very sorry. I'd hoped the plan would go well,
but THIS was the result.
Still, for my infiltration
to have been so easily noticed...
I can only think they must
have been told beforehand.
I know full well how careful you are.
I will look into this matter.
If there is a betrayer,
he won't escape investigation.
Still, I'm glad it was just anesthetic.
If it had been the aphrodisiac, then right now...
I received word earlier.
It seems a third victim has surfaced.
No matter what, we must find
the source of that drug.
I have an idea. Will you leave this matter to me?
Welcome!
It's no good!
That woman's naked body distracts me.
When I try to rid it from my thoughts,
I put too much strength into my technique.
It's you!
I am the master of the
Shin-Kage Itto-ryu dojo, Rin Saejima.
I ask that we cross swords.
This isn't a dream.
Why is she here?
WHY?
No! I have to concentrate.
Still, her stance has no opening...
It's no good! At this rate, I'll get nowhere!
I've lost.
I wish to again give thanks for the other day.
Thank you.
Why are you here?
I have something to ask of you.
Are you free now?
You know of Edo's inner palace, yes?
Yes.
A forbidden aphrodisiac
is being passed around there.
Aphrodisiac?
It's said that if you rub it on a woman's
private areas, she'll crave sex till death.
Climax after climax, she will seek men
until finally it kills her.
It's claimed three victims in the palace.
We are still searching for the source of the drug.
Why is someone from a military family,
a master like you, involved?
I am a secret Guard of the Inner Garden.
"Guard of the Inner Garden"? I've heard of that.
They look into incidents in Edo
that can't be made public.
Exactly. This matter cannot be made public.
The matter fell to me, but...
my infiltration was a failure.
The day that I met you?
The previous night, dressed as a courtesan,
I'd infiltrated a meeting about which
we'd heard strange information.
Perhaps because my identity was known,
anesthetic was slipped into my saké.
Sensing danger, I attempted to flee,
and after a fight with my pursuers
I somehow escaped into the forest alive.
So that's what happened?
I've gauged your skill, and would ask a favor.
Will you perform this search in my stead?
M-me?!
Given that this concerns aphrodisiac,
a woman was chosen to head the search.
But I think a man would be better suited.
Is something the matter?
It's nothing. First, seek out the girl Onami
at the Uega-ya drapery shop.
She was recently allowed leave from the
inner palace yet refuses all talks of marriage.
Onami may be distributing
the aphrodisiac at the palace.
Very well.
I'll do it.
You agree to this?
Yes. I'll do my best.
I'm counting on you.
Okay-
Good morning.
I quickly began following Onami,
the girl at the drapery shop.
And a few days later...
M-may I help you?
Huh? Uh, I am Yasaburo,
a servant of the authorities!
We've received word of a forbidden aphrodisiac!
Could THAT... not be it?
Why do you run?
I cannot stand being seen, having been
caught in such embarrassment!
Yeah, I bet... Rather, what
you were doing isn't important!
So, this is the aphrodisiac?
I've heard of the rumors. But this is...
But what?!
This is... It's taro root paste,
made to cheer me up.
In that case...
Do it.
YOU do it, please. With your hand.
Such thick fingers!
P-please! Put your member inside of me.
Is this REALLY taro root paste?
It's not aphrodisiac?
If it were aphrodisiac, I would already have cum.
Onami. You know something
about the aphrodisiac, don't you?
P-please enter me! Then I'll...
Quickly!
Onami.
And from behind as well, please.
Onami! Tell me what you know!
M-Miss Miyuki, the lady-in-waiting...
They say she knows Master Genemon,
head of the Fujinoya shipping agency,
and that she frequently comes and goes.
I-it could be...
Miss Miyuki is... bringing the forbidden
aphrodisiac to the court...
Miss Miyuki the lady-in-waiting...
That's some good information!
I raced to deliver the news.
I long to see Mistress Rin's smiling face!
Xmv-nﬂm: (WO-IZVU DOJO
Are you all right?
Can I beat you not even once, Mistress Rin?
I am truly worthless.
That's not true.
Why can I not win against this slender body?
Perhaps you are holding back your strength.
Not at all. Were I to do that,
your father would have rebuked me.
You have truly become strong.
I'm sure your father would be proud.
Yasaburo'?
That is an unfamiliar fellow.
Yes. He is Yasaburo, and he's
assisting me with the search.
He's from Shimofusa and is
studying the sword ans.
And? Is he good?
He is skilled in his own right.
He looks like a man to be trusted.
Now then, if you'll excuse me.
What are you doing out here?
Who was that man just now?
That was Kageyama, my father's
trusted friend. I owe him much.
Owe him, huh?
Are you jealous?
Why would I be jealous?!
In any case, you've found
something out, haven't you?
Join me in a drink. I'll hear your story.
I'll go get ready.
SAKE
Miyuki the lady-in-waiting?
Yes.
I've heard of her. She is a strict woman.
Her age is not known, and there are
many strange rumors about her in the court.
She's that remarkable?
I've only heard rumors,
and have never seen her in person.
Also, about the Fujinoya shipping agency...
It was Fujinoya that held the meeting I infiltrated.
Then that means...
This is big news indeed.
You've done well, Yasaburo!
No, it's hard to take praise
from you, Mistress Rin.
Kageyama is a secret Guard of the Inner
Garden, the senior who gives me my orders.
Is that so?
My father worked as a secret guard as well.
He died one year ago.
My father set out to investigate this aphrodisiac.
At the time, there weren't yet any victims.
But a woman appeared in the court
who'd lost her wits, was acting violent.
My father, being a secret guard, acted covertly...
And one day, he was struck
from behind and killed.
That's terrible. Who did it?!
The crime was done at night,
and there were no witnesses.
The matter is unsolved, with no criminal caught.
By this investigation, I intend to find
who killed my father.
Your father found the source of the aphrodisiac,
and was killed to keep him quiet.
Is that your thinking, Mistress Rin?
Well done, Yasaburo. You're quite clever.
No.
If I locate the aphrodisiac's source,
I believe I'll find my father's killer.
This is an extremely personal matter, but...
I wanted you to know, Yasaburo.
If one such as I will do, please tell me anything
at all! I think it would do your heart well.
Thank you.
Kageyama knows of this as well.
He was, after all, my father's man.
Since my father's death, he has looked after me
like a member of his family.
He is important to me.
I did not know he was such a man. I'm
ashamed at having had such strange thoughts!
Enough of that. I was happy
to know your feelings, Yasaburo.
Yasaburo. The moon is beautiful.
Yasaburo... The pain continues
till it's unbearable.
Even without drugs, that's how
a woman's body becomes.
I'm counting on you, Yasaburo.
Fill!
Has Onami been dealt with?
Yes, earlier.
So you were enough of a man to silence her?
A mere peasant. More importantly,
are you all right with this?
Doing it yourself, Mistress Miyuki.
I'd like to have a little fun, too.
It's been two days since then.
Miyuki hasn't taken a single step
outside the castle.
Has something happened?
A dead girl, wrapped up in a bamboo mat.
It's a terrible thing.
Did you... know Onami?
Recently. Not for long.
I left the imperial court with her.
I never dreamed this would happen.
I should have been more watchful!
I am investigating a forbidden aphrodisiac
that has been circulating the palace.
That is how I encountered Onami.
You know something, don't you?
My apologies. But why try to flee?
Let us go somewhere private.
I... cared for Onami as a younger sister.
But when she took that drug, she lost her mind.
I'm grateful it was a small dose. Somehow,
she was able to rid her body of it...
It was around then that she and I
became estranged.
That drug has no place in this world! If you know
something about the aphrodisiac, please tell me.
I know nothing about the aphrodisiac.
Furthermore, I've not been to
Fujinoya even once.
Then why kill Onami?
Perhaps out of spite toward me.
Onami and I were once a couple.
But you're both women!
It happens often at the court.
Two women, fulfilling each other.
"Fulfilling"? You mean you had relations?
Onami had relations with YOU as well.
She no doubt resented the fact
I no longer cared for her.
I wanted to meet you.
That's why I went to see Onami, so...
Who would do something so terrible?!
I will find the culprit, for sure.
This small vessel... Onami and I
used this when we had relations.
I continue to use it to comfort myself.
Won't you please comfort
this lonely body of mine?
No... No! I'm not worthy...
H-hey!
No, no...
Hey!
Such a splendid member.
I'm jealous of Onami.
Hey!
Do I repulse you?
N-no. But, our statuses...
Never mind status!
No.
A man and a woman have no need of status.
Mistress Miyuki...
We may be back to square one.
That was incredible.
I have to get back to the castle.
I don't know if this will be of any use,
but hearing of Fujinoya from Onami,
I grew suspicious and did some investigating.
Anything will help! Please tell me!
At six tomorrow morning... A package from
Nagasaki will arrive at Fujinoya.
Once he's sorted it, he'll deliver
something to the castle.
What's inside?!
That I do not know. But deliveries always
come to the castle at the start of the month.
It is unusual for him to deliver it himself.
Six in the morning...
If you could strike Onami's killer...
It was with this in mind that I told you.
I'll do some investigating.
I WILL get Onami's killer.
A duel for real, huh?
I'll have to prepare myself.
What is it?
Uh, nothing really.
Do you have more good news?
Nothing in particular.
I see.
You should beware of Miyuki.
I've heard from another source that
her connection to Genemon is a close one.
Mistress Rin, have you ever
dueled with live swords?
Why do you ask?
Uh, no reason.
Yes, I have. But all ended in a strike
with the back of my blade.
YOU sure are strong...
Striking someone down requires anger.
Being strong or weak isn't enough to kill.
When I find my father's killer,
I'm sure I can strike him down.
Anger?
I'll get back to the investigation.
I'm sorry for the intrusion.
Yasaburo!
There's really nothing going on?
That's right.
Well. You're quite good.
Bitch!
Don't worry. It's just an anesthetic.
C-coward!
Cowardice ain't got nothin' to do with it.
Everything for the sake of that
pretentious woman, eh?
What I'm after is... HER.
I want you to take this.
Sir.
Hello, sir.
Okay, get on it.
Sir.
Let's go.
FUJXNOVA
The world's economy is dire,
yet business is booming.
We must eat too, yes?
If the people want something,
though they know it to be illegal, then...!
We MUST trade in it, no matter what it be, yes?
People are dying because of it!
That is no concern of mine! Such is the choice
of he who desires till death, yes?
Business is business.
Individual taste is individual taste.
Someone near and dear to you
shall be coming here shortly.
What will you do to Mistress Rin?!
That is one FETCHING woman!
Fetching women have a poison of their own.
She desires the drug.
Liar! There's no way that's true!
It's a lie.
That person has caught the fancy
of SO many others.
One of those has stated that he wishes
to try the drug upon her.
Onami's body?
Yes. I just received word.
Any clues as to the culprit?
Not at this time.
What about Fujinoya?
I was thinking of investigating it shortly,
but what was the name of that man from before?
Yasaburo. He should be staking out Fujinoya.
He got word that the courtesan
Miyuki was suspicious.
Then I'll send word to my men.
Shall we storm them at once?
I'll go to Fujinoya alone first.
If something were to happen to Yasaburo...
Are you in love with him?
What? No, not in the slightest.
It's just, he's only a peasant samurai.
But I've put him in danger, so I worry for him.
I worry for YOU.
Kageyama...
Don't get the wrong idea. I am concerned
for your safety, nothing more.
I will soon instruct my men to go to Fujinoya.
You just stay safe till then.
Sir.
I'm responsible for involving Yasaburo in this.
If something were to happen to him...!
Do you know...
what this means?
Where is Yasaburo?! Is he safe?
He's waitin' for you.
FUJXNOVA
Sir.
Take her sword.
Before we go inside...
why don't we have some fun?
Mistress Rin!
Yasaburo!
Kill this man!
No!
Once the fun is over, I'm gonna finish you off.
It would seem, Miss Rin, you haven't grasped
the situation in which you've been placed.
What are you doing?!
Stop it! Don't lay a hand on him!
Such beautiful breasts!
You have a truly beautiful body.
This is for what you've been searching, yes?
Shall we try some?
Kageyama!
You're rather late, Kageyama.
A lovely sight. Seeing you like this
has been my dream.
Have you applied the drug?
Yes. Plenty.
Why? Why would you...?
Secret orders mean nothing
in the face of our ruler's personal desires.
When I learned that, I thought this job
nothing but foolishness.
So I decided I would act
according to MY desires.
Your father was about to learn of my actions...
He was a nuisance.
Sol killed him.
He called your name till the very end.
I knew you were a splendid daughter,
but I never thought you'd be this beautiful.
Has the drug taken effect?
Your eyes are saying they want me.
How's THAT?
Hey. Don't go untyin' him.
Oh, shut up. You can't order me.
Say it!
Say that you want it!
If you say you want it, I'll give it to ya!
Yasaburo... It might be easier to accept it.
I want it! I want your member,
Kageyama! I want it!
Is that so?! Then I'll give it to ya!
I'll give it to ya till you die!
Miss Miyuki... I can't hold back anymore!
You pest.
Let's go...
You're not getting away!
Bastard.
Rin.
Can you strike me down?
Mistress Rin!
Yasaburo.
Mistress Rin.
After that, Rin slept for three days and nights.
When she awoke, circumstances
began forcing me from Edo.
And then the day came.
You're determined to go?
When I get back to my village,
I'd like to open a sword-fighting dojo...
While helping my father in the rice fields, that is.
If I hadn't asked you to help with the search...
That's not it. My father's hip pains
have gotten worse.
I wanted to stay with you, Mistress Rin,
for much longer.
Will you come again?
Of course! Please call for me
should you need anything.
What you taught me,
about killing someone in anger...
It would be nice if we didn't live in
that son of world, wouldn't it?
The sword ans don't exist to kill people.
My father taught me that.
Well, then.
Yes. See you again.