No Poongsik had been conducting illegal experiments on animals every night.
Since he is the director of an animal hospital,
no one would have suspected him.
Then, Kim Mooyoung knew all about No Poongsik's illegal experiments.
Yes.
Since he watched everything, including the disposal procedure.
But that night, at that place,
no one could have imagined that a person was buried there.
As that drug seeped into your body,
you came back to life from death, it seems.
I think so.
Hello.
Is this HBS?  I would like to report something.
But why the heck did No Poongsik conduct these experiments?
You said that No Poongsik's daughter went missing, didn't you?
Yes.
She is thought to be the first victim
of a missing person's case that occurred in Gangrim City five years ago.
I think President Lee Sungrok might know something about the cases related to No Poongsik.
I am telling you...
This World King Agency that's been in business for 20 years...
To fall because of Kim Mooyoung...
Would I have to put up for sale even this building?
How long are you going to be like this?
You need to get a grip in order for us to accept clients.  Aren't you going to work?
It's because you haven't seen that Kim Mooyoung.
That punk was not a human.
Don't come.  Don't come!!!
Not a human...
If not a human, then are you saying he is a ghost, goblin, or the grim reaper or something?
- What?  Say more.
- Eh?
Ghost, goblin, grim reaper.  Aren't there anymore?  Other than human...
Mermaid princess.
No, it wasn't any sort of fish.
- Nine-tailed fox.
- No, it didn't have any tail.
- Apparition?
- No, it didn't have that feel.
- Hong Kong Granny?
- It wasn't a granny.
Genie.
It wasn't blue.
Centaur?
No, they weren't a horse's legs.
- Zombie?
- Zombie—
Zombie?  Zombie.
Oh, damn!  That surprised me!
Do-Don't open it.
- Yes, coming.
- Don't open it!
- Acting so childish.
- I told you not to open it!
That punk! He really doesn't listen!
No!
President Lee.
About last time...
Anyway, since this is my first visit, I didn't want to come empty-handed...
Anyway, wh-what brings you here, sir?
Gosh, you surprised me!
We want to know about a missing person's case that occurred in Gangrim City five years ago.
Missing?
A missing person's case...
Are you talking about the "shadow" case maybe?
"Shadow" case?
There was a missing person's case in Gangrim City a while back.
Our agency was also asked to work on the case.
Of course, no one, including myself, was able to solve it.
What was that case?
The time was five years prior.
Woman, man, child, or elderly, it didn't matter.  All disappeared, regardless.
Gangrim City's mysterious missing person's case...
But no one saw the face of the culprit.
Only the shadow was seen.
I heard that the first victim of the "shadow" case
was the daughter of the director of the Gangrim animal hospital.
Yeah, she was Hyungnim Poongsik's daughter.
You are close to No Poongsik, aren't you?
No Poongsik?
Yeah, I've heard of his name, as a fellow citizen of Gangrim City.
But I haven't even met him.
Didn't you talk on the phone with Hyungnim Poongsik even yesterday?
- You mean Hyungnim Choongsik?
- Poongsik—
- Choongsik.  Ah, it's possible you could've heard it like that—
- Poong—
Ah, that's why you heard it like that.  Did you get poong in your ear?  Poong...
(T/N: "stroke" or "wind" in Korean.)
I will send you to see an Ear-Nose-Throat specialist.
Anyway, I have nothing more to say, so hurry up and go.
But are you feeling all right?
No Poongsik... It will be best for you to be careful around him.
Have a good day.
He has no idea what kind of jerk No Poongsik is.
Unless you see it for yourself, it would be hard to believe.  Even when you do see it for yourself, it's hard to believe.
Kim Mooyoung!  Are you gone?
You are gone, right?
Gosh, I was scared to death.
Wait a minute. Why is Kim Mooyoung asking about Hyungnim Poongsik?
Does he know something?
Kim Mooyoung came by, is that right?
Yes.  He asked about the Gangrim City missing person's case.
He seems to already know about your daughter as well.
I am not sure why Kim Mooyoung is digging up that case.
It didn't seem like he was asked to by a client.
What he wants to know—
Anyway, he came by with that intern.
I will be right back.
Please attend to business and come back, Hyungnim.
Doesn't it seem like Hyungnim is not in a good mood?
He just looks that way.  He is a good person.
- What was that?  What was that sound?
- What are you talking about?
Just now, this sound.  Is it a dog?
I didn't hear anything.
Uh, don't you hear this sound?
I hear your nonsense.
I think it's coming from here.
Boss, come back!
What if he gets mad?
Boss!  Should we take a quick look?
I don't think we're allowed to go in.
This place seems weird.
You scared me!
That surprised me.
Be careful.
That sound...
Don't open it.
Why is he locked up?
Boss, what is that?
Boss?
Damn it.
Did you want to prove you were a detective?
He sure has many suspicions.
If we don't have proof that No Poongshik killed Kim Mooyoung,
No Poongshik will have to confess on his own.
And this veterinary hospital has been closed for days now.
Where is he hiding?
What was that? What was that sound just now?
I couldn't eat breakfast this morning. I'll go get something from the convenience store.
If there isn't any raw chicken left in the refrigerator, I can get some more.
No, let me just come with you.
No, no. I don't want to hit you on the head in public.
Then, at least get it through a BOGO.
(T/N: BOGO - "buy one get one free")
Obviously.
I'll be back.
Oh right!
Give me your phone.
What do you want with my phone?
I suffered so much trying to find you in the alley last time.
What is that?
A location tracking app.
If I do this, we can know each other's location.
Location tracker?
I'll be back.
What is this? Isn't this for couples?
This is cool.
What's this now?
"'My Girl' is on the move..."
That— Why did she download this on mine?
♫   Even Heaven is on your side   ♫
- Thank you.
Come again.
- I hope you sell a lot!
- Thank you.
♫ Martini blue ♫
♫ I'm swimming in your waves baby you're mine ♫
♫ Oh, oh, oh, martini blue ♫
♫ I can't come out of your ocean ♫
Is your head in the clouds? Why didn't you respond when I called you?
You called me? I didn't hear you.
Gosh. What are those chickens for?
I thought you were supposed to be at work.
I don't think you plan on eating that at the office.
I'm going volunteering at an abandoned dog shelter with my boss.
Volunteering? If you have time to volunteer there, volunteer where I work.
"My Man" has...
- My Man?
- sent you a message.
What is this? What was that?
Did you get a boyfriend?
No. I downloaded an app, but why is it making weird sounds?
Is it... your boss?
- My boss? Don't be ridiculous.
- Give it.
Kim Mooyoung has sent you a heart.
- I love you!
-   I love you? I love you?
- Sis!
- He loves you?
What's wrong with you?
- Wait!
- Hand it over!
Go deliver your stuff!
What is this? What are all these hearts?
Cancel! What—
Who is it?
Come in.
No Poongshik?
Wang Wei.
Yes?
Wang Wei...
I'm Detective Cha from the Violent Crimes Unit at Gangrim Police Station.
We came after your call.
Are you sure it was this person who came by?
Yes, it was him.
He stayed for three days right by the memorial.
He didn't sleep a wink or go to the bathroom once.
I thought he was her biological son.
Thanks.
Kim Mooyoung attended the missing Kang Minho's mother's funeral service.
But they don't know each other at all.
Do you think Writer Gong might know something? She came to the funeral—
She probably came because their agency investigated Oh Hyungchul.
She didn't have any other family, either.
You know she has a big heart.
Do you think she really came solely because she was the victim of a case she was investigating?
About Writer Gong,
do you think she knows something about Kim Mooyoung and is hiding it?
It's not like that.
A detective only believes what they see.
Only what we see.
Boss!
Boss, I brought chicken that's bigger than your head...
So where the hell did he go in that short time?
What the— Why is it so clean?
Gangrim Veterinary Hospital?
No Poongshik?
♫ The night only gets lonelier ♫
♫ The words we exchanged through tears ♫
♫ I feel it inside ♫
♫ So many nights pass ♫
♫ But my heart only knows you ♫
♫ Though my tears fall sadly ♫
♫ You are the face I miss ♫
Is this possible?
I can't believe I succeeded.
What is this place?
What the hell are you doing?
Why did you kill Kim Mooyoung?
Did you kill Kim Mooyoung so you could continue this crazy shit?
Is that what you want to know?
What's important is that a zombie like you exists.
You can walk, talk, and think like a person.
You're a zombie with senses.
You crazy bastard.
Let me go. I said, let me go!
This is definitely the right place.
Location tracker?
I'll be back.
Crap, if I'm not here when you're back or something happens,
don't you dare poke your nose around uselessly.
That will be best for me, understood?
Writer Gong!
PD!
You didn't have to buy this, you could've just come.
It wasn't that expensive, anyway.
So, you're curious about the Shadow case, right?
I reported that case.
It was really something. There was no evidence and no body.
The body was never discovered?
Yeah, here.
- These are all the victims of this case?
- Yeah.
The missing people generally had no family.
They were foreign labor workers or senior citizens and women who lived alone.
Then, adding the number of people who were never reported to be missing, there must be an overwhelming amount.
Right.
- This is the last known location of these missing people?
- Yeah.
They're all around the veterinary hospital.
In a way, that hospital is also a victim of this case.
- PD, can I take a picture of this?
- Sure.
Writer Gong, have you ever considered coming back to the broadcast station?
We're a bit short on staff for 70-Minute Chase.
I mean, you already caught the Santa culprit.
If I'm being honest, you're an extremely nosy person.
How many cases have you solved because of that?
PD, for me, rather than wrapping up a case officially,
I think I'm better suited to actually solving cases behind the scenes.
I won't have to hurt innocent people needlessly.
PD, I have to go.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- I'll call you.
- Okay.
Let me know if you change your mind! And take care of yourself!
Detective Kim, are you really a zombie?
But how— No... is this even possible?
There's a zombie in Korea?
Let's get out of here for now.
No.
Don't do this.
This sound. No way.
Hey!
It's another zombie.
There are other zombies besides me?
What is that?
He... went after...
the human who turned him into a zombie...
and struggled to move his mouth to speak...
Could it be?
This is too hard. I'm stuck.
"It was you." Or not.
"You said it was you." No, he's already turned.
I need inspiration.
Inspiration!
Dad!
Son!
- Hello!
- Hi.
Yeon Woo and Tae Yoon came here, too?
- You're hungry, right?
- Yeah!
- Should I make you guys spicy rice cake?
Auntie, hello!
What are you doing here at this time? You can have lunch with us.
No, I have to go right out.
Have fun, kids.
- You should at least eat.
- Eat with us!
No, I'm okay. It's your favorite spicy rice cake!
No, thank you.
How could she turn down spicy rice cake?
Of course, we need fish cake.
I'll be back.
You're really not going to eat? It's your favorite
- spicy rice cake.
- I'm not.
I'm not eating.
Can we put ramen in it, too?
By the way, doesn't your dad go to work?
Nope, my dad works at home all day.
I want to be a movie director when I grow up, too.
That way I won't have to go to an office.
Guys, you don't know how amazing he is, do you?
Don't be like that, Sister-in-Law.
Did you guys see Busan Express?
The Gangshi's Back Hug?
Will You Marry Me?
Why did the Hong Kong Grandma Go to Hong Kong—
Sister-in-Law, please stop. They said they haven't watched them.
Brother-in-Law, stand straighter. What are you ashamed of?
To me, you're like Park Chanwook or Bong Joonho.
(T/N: famous movie directors in Korea.)
You really are the only person who knows how I feel.
Thank you.
Stop the crying.
Why the hell did you make a zombie?
Do you know?
That a wolf only loves one female wolf all his life.
Honey, I will save you for sure.
You have to live
so that I may live.
You can do it.
Honey?
Honey, can you hear me?
You are alive.  Alive.
What?  What do you want?
Water?  Okay, wait just a bit.
Honey, water!
Honey.
Honey?
Honey...
I thought it then.
If only I could save my wife,
I could do any damn thing.
But still, you made a dead person a zombie?
Honey, we can go back to how it was.
You saw that there is hope, didn't you?
That crazy bastard.
He's in there for sure.
If he ran away, the hospital would be in chaos by now.
Ah, what should I do?
Why are you hesitating?
Ah, Noonim.  Hello.
Because you hesitate like that, you can't catch her.
What are you going to do now?
I am asking what are you going to do about Kong Sunji?
What are you talking about?  Did something happen to Sunji?
Ah, to be honest,
I think she is dating her boss.
Dating?!
Kim Mooyoung?
I heard with my own two ears
the two of them sending each other hearts as couples.
Ah, I am so upset!  I can't really do one-shot (bottoms up) with yogurt or anything...
Aigoo.
Yes, this is Gangrim Police Violent Crimes Unit.
Where?
Yes, we will be right there.
Senior, an unidentified body has been found at Chowol Mountain.
Oh, what in the world!
Ah, I will give you a call after work, Noonim.
Okay, do that.  Hurry up and go.
Let's go.
Ah, you keep working like that all the time.  When are you going to date?
But I wonder what's going on in Gangrim City.  I am so curious.
To live as a zombie...
do you know how painful it is?
To have an appetite when looking at a human,
how miserable, disgusting
and abominable it is?
That fact alone makes you want to die.
But you can't even die.
To a person you love so much,
do you want to make her feel that pain?
Being alive is what's important.
Alive, by my side.
At least, being alive
is better than being dead.
Even if it feels like hell.
Detective Cha!
Ah, really!
Are you all right
Did the meeting between your family and the future in-laws go well?
We exchanged greetings and the meeting was over in exactly 3 minutes.
What does it matter if I get a special promotion, when I am a zero-point dad to my daughter?
What was the cause of death?
It seems that the bleeding due to a skull fracture is the direct cause of death.
But we will need to do an autopsy in order to find out whether it was an accidental death or a murder.
You said the body was buried at a hillside.
It's a murder case, of course.
Senior, we just got the result of the fingerprints analysis.
Yeah?
But it's a little strange.
What do you mean "strange"?  What is?
The victim's identity came back as Kim Mooyoung of the detective office.
- Kim Mooyoung?
- Yes.
Look at this.  The meter wouldn't be running at an empty building.
Should I go in?
(Let's work together)
(Do that! Pull it up!)
(No, I won't do it.)
(That...  go there.)
(Pull it up.)
I knew it.
Boss.
Boss!
What is this?  How did you come here?
What is that?!
I will explain later so untie the World King people first.
(Go! Go! Go!)
(Come on, go!)
Bend a little.
(I can't because of my back.)
Don't get afraid and listen carefully.
Your boss is... a zombie.
I said he's a zombie!
I know.  You are hurting me.
Gosh, when I am so busy...
You know?  I can pull shoes out, dummy.
Hurry with Wang Wei! Untie Wang Wei.
She knew but worked with him?
What is this?
- Boss, are you all right?
- Yeah, I am okay.
Untie me.
Listen carefully.
If you are a detective, you cannot ever be shaken at any situation.
I understand.
We will report first.
Boss, why aren't you coming?
Kkotsoonee.
Kkotsoonee?  Then, he really experimented on animals?
No Poongsik!
My Kkotsoonee...
Boss, calm down.
A detective is not shaken in any situation—
Boss!
Why is he like that?
Hyungnim... you, how dare you do that to my Kkotsoonee—
What?
When I am trying to revive a dead person, is a mutt's life that important?
After I begged so much...
Sungrok, hunting is never done by the hunter himself.
It is done by the hunting dog.
You were a good hunting dog to me.
But what do you think happens when the hunting dog can't do its job?
Then, the hunting dog
is eaten as well!
That's right, you bastard.  Kill me as well, you bastard.
Me, too.  Kill me like you killed Kkotsoonee, you bastard.
No!  Wang Wei!
Go back!  Because of this bastard, you...
Go back, Wei!  You have to live!
Hurry, run away!  At least you should run away!
That dum—
What the heck is No Poongsik up to?
He was much crazier than we thought.
He did this crazy experiment because of his wife who became a zombie.
Are you going to pull that off tomorrow?
It's not working.  Why is this so hard?!
Wait just a bit.
It will soon be done.
Please, quickly.
Wait just a bit.
Don't look.  Stay still.
You understand me, don't you?  Let's calm down.
Boss.  Boss, this...
These look like they belong to the missing persons.
- You are saying that all these people are the victims in that case, right?
- Yes.
No Poongsik had been illegally experimenting not only on animals but also on humans as well.
And...
in the end, the wife took care of the clean up.
A monster was making a monster.
It looks like another food has crawled in here.
Then, shall we have a meal time in earnest?
Well, the zombie was on the wall for too long.
I told you to take it down already.
Gosh, you surprised me!
I told you I really don't like it.
Who?  Zombie?  Detective Kim?
Give me a glass of beer.
By chance, did you talk to Sunji today?
She's been busy lately, you know.
She's been looking into No Poongsik.
Thank you.
No Poongsik?
You are referring to that vet at the animal clinic?
If you're so worried, you should go.
What good is switching jobs from 70-Minute Chase to a detective agency?
She is still nutty as ever.
I bet she went to the animal clinic again today.
With her boss for sure.
What dreamy teamwork between the two.
You saw the way that kid was looking at me, right?
Why on earth are zombies flipping out whenever they see me?
A zombie's weakness is the back of their head.
Honey, eat up.
Wait a minute!
Let's not do that.
You can live sufficiently without having to eat humans.
Of course, it might be hard at first, but I was able to do without after much trying.
So, let's not live like this, please.
Oh, how unfortunate. (She) has tasted many humans already.
Get to your senses! She's not your wife but a zombie!
Not a human but a zombie that feasts on humans!
All (she) needs to do is be within my sight whether she's a human or zombie!
Sunji!
Kong Sunji!
Boss!
I... killed a zombie.
It's over.
Boss! Wake up, boss!
Boss... Boss!
I am also... I may also...
become a zombie then?
That's not true, Director Lee. Please come to your senses.
Director Ki—
One moment, please.
Wang Wei, thank you for the time (you spent with me).
Also, I'm sorry.
All you did was face hardship in Korea, thanks to me.
Boss!
When I pass,
you keep the World King detective agency.
Boss....
Guardian?
Would you like to accompany him?
No...
I will follow you in a taxi.
And perhaps if my boss has a seizure
or tries to bite you, cut his life short on the spot.
For your information, a zombie's weakness is the back of their head.
Don't worry. Nothing much will come of it. Won't you go on ahead to the office, Boss?
I will contact you if anything happens.
Kong Sunji!
♫  Another day passes...  ♫
- Hey Cha Dohyun.
- Are you okay?
- You aren't hurt or anything?
- I'm fine.
What's so fine? Why do you always insist that you're fine when you're not?
Why do you get mad over it?
Let's go to the hospital first.
Ah, I'm fine seriously.
Excuse me! Hurry, please!
♫  Even this deep darkness as time passes...  ♫
- Are you all right?
- Ah, yes. I'm not hurt anywhere.
I'm really fine.
Come on! Stay still.
♫  ...tells me that it'll be okay  ♫
Never mind. Don't insist. I'm really fine.
♫  Heartbreaking through countless nights  ♫
- Hang on a second.
- No, I'm okay.
♫  Heartbreaking through countless nights  ♫
Excuse me, senior.
There's something you should verify.
I will take care of it. Take off.
Roger that.
Let's go quietly, huh?
Everything is befuddled.
What should I do now?
What is this?
Kang Minho,
you are under arrest for the murder and kidnapping of Kim Mooyoung.
♫  A world without you   ♫
♫  Is nothing  ♫
♫  To me  ♫
If someone were to come looking for me and ask about me, deny any knowledge.
You and I were of no connection, understand?
That was the boss then...
The body at the time of discovery did not have the head or organs,
so the police are investigating under the assumption that the probability of illegal human organ sales involvement is high
The head (brains) is missing. Zombie has appeared.
It appears (you) haven't been able to eliminate the hope of returning to being a human being.
Don't worry. You will never be able to return to being a human being.
The zombie had no business coming down to where humans lived in the first place.
I came back alive... to hell.  Zombie Detective.
♫  When I quietly listen closely  ♫
♫  You come back...  ♫