Cinderella and Four Knights
Jung Il Woo
Ahn Jae Hyeon
Park So Dam
Lee Jung Shin
Choi Min
Son Na Eun
Cinderella and Four Knights
Do you need money that badly?
Hey, Han Ji Woon.
Don't you dare mistreat my girl.
"My girl?"
Stop it, both of you!
Wait.
I know that you people can easily throw around this kind of money
but there are plenty of people in the world who can't.
Wait.
- Who are you?
- What are you doing?
I have no interest in what you have to say, so get lost.
In other words, stay away from Kang Hyeon Min
if you don't want to see things get really nasty.
Your name is Kang Ji Woon, right?
Stop ranting about things you know nothing about.
This is my last warning to you.
If you ever touch me again, that'll be the day you die.
Wait.
Are you upset?
Do I look like I'm so easy to push around?
No, it's not that--
♫ While I keep looking only at you ♫
♫ It's the first time I've felt  ♫
♫ a trembling feeling like a lie ♫
♫  pointing only at you♫
♫ Why did you show up now? ♫
♫ It's the fate I was looking forward to ♫
♫ I've bet my everything on you ♫
♫ You are so precious ♫
♫ I feel your heart heart heart. ♫
♫ From the first to the last, I wonder about everything. ♫
♫ Even If I secretly  ♫
♫ must close my eyes, I open them ♫
♫ Make you feel ♫
♫ my love, love, love ♫
♫ Now you're not alone anymore. ♫
♫ My love is growing bigger every day. ♫
♫ Truly you're the only one I know. ♫
♫ You're the only one for me. ♫
♫ Look only at me yet. ♫
♫ Even if the world is ending, I will run ♫
The magic has worn off.
♫ I'm the only one for you ♫
♫ I like it when you smile ♫
♫ I will only dream as brightly as you ♫
♫ I will love you with everything I've got ♫
♫ A jealous and petty spat ♫
♫ That's not a problem ♫
♫ Even though every start is clumsy and awkward ♫
♫ To the contrary I will be strong ♫
♫ Love is always a paradox ♫
♫ whether it's serious or not
♫  It is a restraint as much as I hate that ♫
♫This is a marathon I need to control.♫
♫ If I keep professing my love  ♫
♫the soul's thirst will naturally be quenched.♫
♫ You gotta trust me now ♫
♫ Bye bye bye Sad Goodbye ♫
♫ I cherish our meeting ♫
♫ As though you are mine ♫
♫ How will this beautiful  ♫
♫  feeling exist? ♫
♫  Even if it were possible to  ♫
♫ cite the star in the sky over there ♫
♫ It's no comparison to you.  ♫
♫  Because you're flying there must be hidden wings  ♫
♫ I feel your heart, heart, heart  ♫
♫ At the sight of your back, my heart pounds. ♫
You have to go inside now, okay?
Oh, we're already here?
♫ Make you feel ♫
♫ my love, love, love  ♫
Why are you spacing out so much?
♫ Doing anything for you excites me. ♫
♫ I'm not letting you go easily ♫
Do you like Kang Hyeon Min that much?
♫  You're the only one for me.  ♫
Even though he won't even look twice at you?
I'm going to make him look at me. Don't you worry.
♫  So that I can protect you ♫
♫ I'm the only one for you♫
Kang Hyeon Min. Just what are you trying to pull?
Well, I just took a shower.
Do you know what you did at the wedding today?
Oh. What? Was it bad of me to have gotten Grandfather a present?
To reciprocate, he's also prepared a present for you.
Who's that?
Your real fiancee. She's the grand-daughter of K Group's Chairman.
What the hell? Are you telling me now to have an arranged marriage?
You'll be meeting with her tomorrow.
It's the first meeting, so make sure you're good to her.
Aw, come on, Hyung! Why are you doing this to me?
You really thought you'd get away with pulling that stunt?
Oh, whatever. Whatever.
You'd better go if you want to keep your place as heir to Haneul Group.
Damn it.
Oh, whatever!
I've gotten married five times, but yesterday was the best wedding I've had.
I got to see quite an amusing spectacle.
Wait.
I know that you people can easily throw around this kind of money
but there are plenty of people in the world who can't.
That girl is no ordinary girl.
Look into that young lady who came to the wedding.
Yes, sir.
Oh, good morning!
Hey, I have to eat breakfast!
How are you ever going to get anywhere in life when you move so slowly?
I'm sorry. I woke up a bit late today. I'll whip something up quick!
Damn it, I'm going to starve because of you!
So annoying!
What do you want?
Um, I have a favor to ask you.
No, don't bother.
Um...
Can't you hear me out, just this once?
What, huh?
Could you lend me some money to pay my tuition for the first semester of college?
I'll be sure to work really hard at my part-time jobs and pay you back!
Tuition? What are you talking about?
Are you talking about my Yoo Na's tuition?
What, did you pray for Yoo Na to not get into any colleges, so you could go?
No... No, that's not what I meant.
You were acting all high and mighty before, saying you had tons of money!
But, what? You want me to give you my Yoo Na's tuition?
Are you crazy? Are you out of your damn mind?
Why are you being so loud?
Let me sleep, damn it! Let me sleep!
Hey. Go.
Just leave.
I'll head out, then.
She's become the "Nation's Jackpot Girl."
She's the fiancee of Kang Hyeon Min, first in line to inherit Haneul Group.
But, who really is this girl?
Who is she really? Did she save the country in her past life?
There's finally a pic of her online! I'm a guy and even I'm jealous!
Did you hear about that girl? I feel like she must be pretty!
The biggest news story from yesterday: Kang Hyeon Min, the heir to Haneul Group
brought his fiancee to the wedding of his grandfather, Chairman Kang!
And there's something we've prepared for everyone, in light of that news, right?
Here you are. This photo of the Nation's< Jackpot Girl is all over the web now.
Doesn't that girl kind of look like Eun Ha Won?
Eun Ha Won? As if! No way!
Her face ...
- No, they do look kind of similar.
- Mom!
I'm really sensitive right now, okay? Stop bothering me!
Yes, Honey? Of course, we're all doing well!
Ha Won and Yoo Na left for school together.
The two of them are practically inseparable!
Oh, I see.
Oh, you're coming tomorrow?
The government needs to do its job! Geez, this is really pissing me off!
- Boss.
- What?
- Today is payday.
- So?
Could you pay me in advance for next month?
I promise I'll work really hard!
Stop being ridiculous. You're pissing me off.
Hey, you have to work to get paid!
Does it make sense to be paid before you work?
Jesus, I'd kill you if you were serious.
You have to put in the work to get paid!
What kind of ridiculous request is that? Huh?
She started working part-time at a convenience store
and then she began working at a cafe, restaurant, movie theater,
as a dog-walker, and at an amusement park.
She currently has ten part-time jobs.
Is she the only one who can support the family?
Not exactly, but it is true that she has to fend for herself.
Her biological mother passed away when she was young
and her father remarried.
She's currently living with her stepmother
and her stepmother's daughter, who is the same age as she is.
Her father is a truck driver, but he often works in the countryside
so he only comes home every couple of months.
Her family isn't exactly well-off
so it seems they only have money to send< one of their daughters to college.
Therefore, it seems that Ms. Ha Won is >doing her best to earn her own tuition.
No wonder she seems so mature for her age.
It may be better to get someone like her, who's close to them in age
rather than someone who will try to cater to all of the boys' requests.
Haneul Columbarium - 3,995,000 won
Remaining balance: 800 won
Deadline for tuition deposit!
Important for my dream!]
Yeah. I can just go to college next year.
I'm sure I'll earn 4 million won in no time if I work hard for a year!
No. I'll have to earn more than that.
That way, Mom can rest in peace.
Objective: 4 million won for tuition!
Let's start again!
Why isn't Dad responding?
Huh? What the heck? This isn't mine!
Oh no. Did it get switched at the hotel?
There's someone who'd like to meet you, Ms. Eun Ha Won.
What?
Hello.
Oh. You have something on your clothes.
What?
What a nice bow. It sure is nice to be greeted with a bow twice!
You have a great sense of humor.
That's a compliment, right?
I'm sorry about what happened that day.
I was really worried that I ruined your wedding.
There's no need to worry about that.
But, um, why did you ask to see me?
I'm sorry, but I did a bit of a background check on you. "The Art of War by Sun Tzu"
It's the first time I've met someone of your age
with similar tastes in books as me.
My mother told me that adhering to Sun Tzu's teachings
would get me through life without hardship.
How amusing. Would you be willing to lend me some of that wisdom, then?
Excuse me?
Let me explain everything to you first.
Haneul House's architectural design is based on nature.
In terms of modern architecture, it's in the top 100 in the entire world.
It's incredibly secure, and no outsiders can enter.
Wow. So who lives there?
Chairman Kang's grandsons live there.
The Chairman's eldest grandson, Kang Hyeon Min, is a person...
who seeks to spread the incredible amount of love he's received to many people—
In other words, a total player.
The Chairman's second eldest grandson, Kang Ji Woon
is a person who challenges boundaries, and cannot be tamed by anyone—
In other words, a total thug.
The Chairman's youngest grandson, Kang Seo Woo
has all the qualities of a singer-songwriting star, and is unrivaled in—
In other words, a good-for-nothing.
These three cousins began residing in Haneul House last year.
And it's because of these punks that I'd like to make a proposition to you.
Make my grandsons into decent human beings.
What do you mean by that?
Do you want me to give them etiquette lessons, or something?
It could end up being something like that, yes.
Whoa. I thought that third-generation chaebol sons weren't taught etiquette on purpose,
for fear they might be too nice and give away all the money.
So I thought they were raised to be people with terrible personalities who only focus on money.
Really? Then, will you reform them, for me?
I've come up with a program to reform them.
All you have to do is carry out the missions I give you, for three months.
How could I possibly do that?
You can definitely do it.
If you'll do that for me, I'll pay for your college tuition
and even send you to study abroad. I'll give you anything you ask.
College?
What I'm saying is that I can change your life, Ms. Ha Won.
Okay?
You really had me excited for a second,
but I am not qualified to reform someone.
I'm sorry.
Thirty-Six Stratagems, Chapter 1, Section 5! Loot a burning house!
In other words, make sure you take ample advantage of every opportunity.
Don't you think that this may be that kind of opportunity?
Chapter 3, Section 14: Borrowing a corpse to resurrect the soul!
One should avoid opportunities that look hopeless.
And honestly, this does seem kind of hopeless.
Chapter 3, Section 18: Defeat the enemy by capturing their chief!
You don't know the outcome of a battle until it's over.
You'll have to see for yourself if this is
a hopeless venture or the opportunity of a lifetime, won't you?
Chapter 6, Section 36: If all fails, retreat!
I think that's the best teaching that suits my current situation.
Is there a need to go to such lengths for her?
For me, changing a person's life takes almost no effort whatsoever.
You're even prettier in person.
I don't really like such blatant flattery.
I really like this style of clothing.
You must really like women.
Everyone's talking about the rumor that you brought someone to the Chairman's wedding.
It's not a rumor. I guess you didn't do your research on me before coming.
Of course I did.
But I didn't realize I'd get a glimpse of your infamous personality at a meeting like this.
Or is this a cleverly-crafted maneuver of yours?
Why would I bother to strategize when I'm just meeting a woman?
Why don't we just have a fun time today? Just the two of us.
I was told that I would be meeting with a business partner today.
I guess you're not that person.
Let's negotiate the terms of our agreement first.
You're here?
Hyeon Min.
I'd heard the rumors, but wow. You're really something else.
Looks like our negotiations fell through. I won't be seeing you again, I hope.
Sorry.
Kang Hyeon Min!
- What are you doing now?
- What are you talking about?
Don't use people for your own purposes.
And that's why I apologized.
Just what am I to you?
Someone I used to be friends with when I was young?
That's all I am to you?
What else would you be, then?
Are you going to bring up the past again?
I know that you changed after that day, but—
Of course, someone would change after ten years.
That's true. I've changed too, after all.
But you know, this is the most repulsive I've seen you since you've changed.
I still believe that some part of you from ten years ago
is buried in there, somewhere.
Sir, you left this behind yesterday.
I don't think this is...
No wait, it is.
Thank you.
Only for a moment, please.
I think my phone got switched, and I left something else behind.
Not just anyone can check into one of our suites.
I went up yesterday, so why can't I go up today?
You came here with another guest yesterday, right?
I guess you don't have anyone to pay for your room today.
What?
We may have made an exception since you were with a guest yesterday
but I cannot let you into the suite today.
- Please leave.
- Wait, Mister, just this once!
It really will only take a second! Please? Please!
Hey, Sweats!
What are you doing here? Let's go.
Is there anyone who accidentally got their phone swapped?
What about a school uniform? Or a white bouquet of flowers?
I didn't see anything like that.
You didn't throw it out because it was a bit old and shabby did you?
Um, I'm not really sure.
Thanks. I'll definitely repay this debt to you.
Ask Kang Hyeon Min to buy you a new one. Isn't that why you're seeing him?
So he can buy you everything and anything you want?
Are you done?
The strategy that girls like you use is to act all proud
and then take all the handouts, isn't it?
I let you go that day because you're a girl.
But seriously, don't ever show yourself to me again
- Are you serious right now?
- Ow! Hey!
What? And what about guys like you, huh?
You act like you're so hot and just go around disregarding girls like nothing.
But you're a real jerk you know.
Why, that little!
You're the Nation's Jackpot Girl?
Why won't the owner of this phone pick up?
I SEOWOO U ❤︎
Only You ❤︎ Seo Woo
Wow, are you serious? That's awesome!
Are you living at Haneul House now, then?
No. I decided not to go.
Are you crazy? Do you know what kind of place that is?
That's where the Kang Cousins of Haneul Group live!
The one-percenters! The Royal Family of Korea!
You had a chance to live somewhere like that
but you rejected it to make coffee at a place like this?
To me, this sound is the same sound as money stacking up in my bank account!
I have to work hard at my part-time jobs!
Are you out of your mind? This is a chance for you to reset your sad life
so why wouldn't you go there?
That's why I didn't go. I may not be from a distinguished family
but I have some pride, you know. I'll protect my own life.
Today's concert was awesome, Kang Seo Woo!
- Can I have my phone, please?
- Okay.
Thank you.
What the heck? This isn't mine!
- What?
- Let me borrow your phone.
Sure.
Twelve... 09, 09. Put that in.
The customer you have called ...
- Damn it, he's not answering.
- He's not answering?
Damn it, I have so many of my lyrics and demos in there!
Huh? Oh no! Your phone died!
I didn't bring my charger today! They didn't call from your phone?
This phone is dead, too!
Damn it, what if I never find my phone?
Thank you for tuning into the beauty show, "Love is Now!"
I'm your host, Kkongyang Yoo Na!
Ta-da!
I even got myself on a TV show!
I guess it won't be long now until I become a celebrity!
All right, I'll start my beauty show now!
All right, everyone.
You all know that salmon is one of the 14 superfoods, right?
Now, we have a salmon product that you put on your skin!
Wow! It'll make your skin smooth, and
get rid of all your wrinkles! Try it!
I'm home.
Okay, now I'll teach you how you can make a mask at home...
You're the Nation's Jackpot Girl, right?
Um, who are you?
Wait, this isn't the girl you want! What are you doing?
Why are you filming her?
She's Kang Hyeon Min's fiancée!
So, how does it feel, now that you're the Nation's Jackpot Girl?
Um, it's not like that.
- Um...
- But...
- Get out! Right now!
- Wait, but...
I thought you came to film Yoo Na! What's all this, all of a sudden?
You're... the Nation's Jackpot Girl?
How the hell could you be Kang Hyeon Min's fiancee?
How did you even go to the wedding?
Something happened.
What happened, exactly?
I can't tell you, but I didn't go because I wanted to.
I'm being honest, Unni!
Stop acting so high and mighty, Eun Ha Won.
Isn't this what you wanted
to escape your shitty life by seducing some rich boy?
So why the hell do you keep going on about some damn "situation"?
There's nothing between us, really!
And I don't want to use someone in order to change my life.
I'm not going to freeload off someone else's life.
Get out. Get out! Get the hell out!
Unni!
I thought you said that you weren't going to freeload off other people!
And yet, you keep leeching off our family!
But we are family.
I've never once considered you family.
Please, get the hell out of my life!
You know, Dad said he's coming back tomorrow.
You're really going to kick her out?
I don't know! Whatever!
Darn it. I don't even have other clothes to wear.
I bet this will leave a stain.
Damn it, what am I supposed to do with this?
I still believe that some part of you from ten years ago
is buried in there, somewhere.
You've already been checked out.
- Then give me another room, please.
- Yes, sir.
This card is no longer valid.
Mr. Kang Ji Woon. The Chairman wants you to return to Haneul House.
I'm not going.
Then, you won't be able to take< advantage of any of the benefits
that come with being affiliated with Haneul Group, either.
I can get by without that kind of stuff.
It seems that Mr. Ji Woon's wounds run quite deep.
And it seems like he can't get accustomed to Haneul House.
This may be impudent for me to say, sir,
but I believe that it will be difficult to get Mr. Ji Woon back to Haneul House.
That's why we have to get him back there as soon as possible.
I've already thought of a way.
Right this way.
- You're done here, right?
- Yeah.
There isn't a single customer in theater three. Let's go see a movie!
A movie and popcorn? Sounds awesome!
- I'll be right there!
- Okay!
Damn it, I have to go. I have to leave now. Have fun!
How come?
Why should I run away, though? I didn't do anything wrong.
Oh my gosh, you surprised me!
Do you have any money?
Are you really a rich chaebol? If you are how could you not even have 10,000 won?
I think that's enough prying out of you.
So do you have money, or not? Just answer the question.
I do. Or I would if you'd actually paid your debt at the convenience store.
Wow! I have 5,000 won!
What an enormous amount of money you've got there.
Whatever, Sweats. Forget about it! Gosh!
Wow, your words and actions don't match, do they?
Was this all because you were hungry?
Just wait a bit. I'll get changed and come right out.
I can take care of everything with just this!
My debt to you for helping me out
at the hotel is repaid now, okay?
Don't even think about saying that I still owe you later, okay?
My help to you was only worth 1,500 won?
What about the cost of the cheese? With that, it's 2,500 won!
I'm the one who taught you that it tastes better with cheese in it!
I already knew about that, okay? I just forgot for a second!
What, so you're going to disregard that extra 1,000 won I paid?
Hey, give me back the cheese. Hurry up and give it back!
Give it back! Don't you dare eat it!
You know how gross it tastes without cheese? Give it back!
Hey, I'm sorry. I won't bother you while you're eating anymore. Eat up.
You said you were hungry, right? Hurry and eat up!
So he ate and ran, huh?
I lose my phone and get kicked out of my house.
What's with today? Seriously.
Can I charge this just for a bit?
If the boss finds out, we'll be in huge trouble! You know how he is.
Can you lend me your phone, then?
I'm sure you realize that it'll be of no use to cut me off financially.
I can do much worse if it will get you to come back home.
There'll be no reason to go back to that house.
- Come back, already.
- I said no.
All I want is for things to go back to the way they were.
You do realize what that means, right?
Everything you think is yours can disappear in an instant.
That's the kind of power I wield. And it'll soon be yours, too.
I don't need that kind of power.
Stop clinging onto me. I'm going to live as Han Ji Woon now.
Let's go.
Will it be all right to leave him alone like that?
It'll be fine. He'll come back on his own soon.
- Um, who is this?
- I'm the owner of that phone.
Why didn't you pick up my calls?
I was waiting for your call for a really long time, too!
At any rate, I couldn't read any of my messages because of you today!
- Oh, you keep getting texts.
- Really?
That might be from someone at home! Can you unlock my phone?
- What?
- First, I'll tell you the pattern.
Start where 5 would be on the keypad, and then 7-2-9-4-3-8-6-1.
Wait, so how do I unlock your phone?
Just move your finger toward where those numbers would be on the keypad.
Why is it so complicated? Are you a celebrity, or something?
Come on, try doing it slowly! Five7-2-9-4-3-8-6-1!
Oh, it worked! I did it!
Really? Who texted me?
Just a moment. Um... it's from "Unni Yoo Na..."
What did she say?
Hurry up and tell me!
Oh, she says that... um... you'll be eating dinner together tomorrow.
And that your father's coming home tomorrow.
Really? She really said that Dad's coming home?
She asked me to have dinner with them?
You bitch! Just eat dinner and leave
- Yes.
- Wow, thank you!
But, um, where are you right now?
Um, excuse me.
I came here to get my phone back.
What, is he a celebrity or something?
Kang Hyeon Min's fiancee?
Delete these messages?
Huh? Where did my texts go? I thought you said that I got texts.
Oh, that? I accidentally deleted them.
What?
Anyway, they were telling you to have dinner with them tomorrow.
Did they really tell me to come home?
And she really said that Dad's coming?
Yeah!
Thanks for finding my phone for me. I'd better get going.
Bye.
Gosh, why do I feel so uneasy about this?
I heard that you're coming home tomorrow...
Why didn't you contact me at all?
See you tomorrow.
Does she really work here? How many hours have we been waiting for already?
It's the Nation's Lottery Girl!
- Ms. Eun Ha Won!
- Is it really you?
Are you really Ms. Eun Ha Won?
Is it true you're engaged to Mr. Kang Hyeon Min of Haneul Group?
How did you two meet?
Um, I don't have any relationship with that man!
I'm sorry! Please leave! I'm sorry!
- Please, just one comment!
- How did you two meet?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Let's go.
- How did you two meet?
- Since when have you been dating?
- Please, just one comment!
- How did you meet?
- Where are you going?
- Ms. Eun Ha Won?
Hey, I'm totally awesome, right?
You got the nickname, "Nation's Jackpot Girl" after you met me.
And you even got yourself a man who'd save you under such circumstances.
Do you not realize the gravity of the situation here?
Gravity of the situation? You mean how I saved you?
Just look how serious things have gotten because of your stupid lie!
Go and tell the reporters that we're not in a relationship.
- Is that what you want?
- Yeah.
Fine. All right. Just give me five minutes, then.
I'll make your name disappear from the internet.
What, are you some kind of a genius hacker or a magician or something?
How could you possibly do that?
Why can't you trust me?
Hey, is this Joon Myeong? It's me, Kang Hyeon Min.
Isn't this a bit beneath you guys, as the number one portal site in Korea?
The news about my fiancee is plastered everywhere.
This is clearly defamation and libel
and it could really harm one's freedom and dignity!
For the sake of social justice, you shouldn't be doing this.
Do you want me to spell it out in a way you'll understand?
I'll pull all our ads off your site!
Take down everything that pertains to "Kang Hyeon Min's fiancee" immediately.
You totally fell for me just now, right? You did, right?
You wouldn't be human if you didn't fall for me after that!
Wow. Even I'm stunned by how cool I just was.
- How could this happen?
- Of course, it couldn't, for most people.
Honestly, even I think I was really amazing this time.
What is this? Are these goosebumps? Look, look! Do you see my goosebumps?
I heard you could control portal sites if you had enough money
but that was actually true?
I trusted my online sources so much! I can't believe this... seriously?
Seriously, I can't believe this.
How could you be thinking about something like that at a time like this?
What?
I just thought of one thing that money can't buy.
- What?
- Your smile.
That's none of your business! Anyway, thanks for getting the photos taken down.
Hello?
What? My father took my mother's urn?
- Hey, what are you doing?
- I'm here!
What? Did something happen?
Get out of here.
- Clean this up, you guys.
- Yes, sir.
Hyung, what's going on?
Don't ask any questions, and just leave.
I'll come back next time.
Ji Woon.
This is the money that the boss saved up.
I'm really sorry, but please don't come back.
What?
We promised your grandfather that we'd never see you again
and that we'd act as if we never knew you.
He gave us enough money for us to make that kind of promise!
That Haneul Group sure is powerful.
I guess changing someone's life is child's play for them.
That's good, then.
What?
Of course, you should've gotten that much money when you sold me out.
It's fine.
I'm sorry!
Is this the power that Grandfather was talking about?
The power to buy people?
He could erase everything that you hold dear if he wanted to.
Wow, he truly is an amazing person.
There's no such person as Han Ji Woon in this world.
There's only Kang Ji Woon now.
I told you, I'm Han Ji Woon.
You'll no longer be able live as you please, either.
Hey, the heiress to K Group is going around
and trying to make sure you can't do business with other people anymore!
Whatever.
You sure are carefree.
Arranged marriages are pretty much a given for people like us.
It won't be much help to you if you can't get a suitable wife.
What if you end up jeopardizing your position as the heir by doing this?
- What?
- Well, yeah.
Kang Seo Woo lives at Haneul House now,
and Kang Ji Woon came out of nowhere, too, and is apparently related to you.
You're competing against a lot of people!
One month's worth, please.
Citizen ID Card: Kang Ji Woon
Then, she's not really Hyeon Min's fiancee?
I think she only acted like she was for money.
What an impudent child.
I told her to go and live at Haneul House with my grandsons.
What is it about that girl that you like so much?
Even though I'm rich, I often wonder who's really in charge: me, or the money.
And yet, she didn't lose her resolve at the sight of money.
I think she's more than worthy to keep around the boys.
Yeah?
Yes, so how did it go?
I've solved the issue regarding Ji Woon.
And what about the girl?
I've assigned someone to watch over her.
But I don't think she'll change her mind.
I don't think she has any intention of agreeing to your deal.
As to be expected. But I definitely can't lose her.
Oh my, our Ha Won is here!
Little Sis! Come and have dinner.
Where's Mom?
Your mom's right here, Sweetie.
I heard that you took my mom's urn!
Your mother's right here, so who the hell are you looking for?
Oh, I'm okay, Honey.
How could you do this?
I heard that you never paid the columbarium fees!
They said that we owed them five million won, so I paid four million won!
If you had just paid the rest, I could have let Mom rest in peace!
Why should I have to use so much money on a dead person?
She was your wife.
It's not like those ashes are a big deal!
In the olden days, we'd just scatter them in a river or the ocean!
Stop making a big deal over nothing.
Mom lost her final resting place and she was just cast aside like this
so how can I just stay still and do nothing?
How dare you do this
in front of your stepmother, who raised you with so much care?
Way to go, clutching your dead mom like that. Great job.
Honey, I told you, I'm fine. I'll also try to get some money for that.
I have some money I saved to send Yoo Na and Ha Won to college.
You told me that you could only send one of us to college.
Ha Won. I know you're angry, but you shouldn't lie like that!
Also, where are my belongings that were on the balcony?
You just shoved all my stuff wherever last time, too, because Dad was coming.
I had to look for a really long time because the photos of my mom disappeared!
What are you talking about?
Your belongings are in your room, of course!
The room that you share with Yoo Na!
No, my room is that balcony.
Are you trying to make me look like the bad guy on purpose?
No! I'm just stating the facts!
Stop it! How dare you speak that way to your mother!
You don't even appreciate her kindness for raising you all these years!
And now you're trying to make her seem like a liar?
You don't believe me at all, do you?
I never should have gone and raised someone else's child.
What are you talking about?
Your mom had you with another man!
So, I'm not really your daughter?
I wanted to believe that you were my real daughter.
Wait, Honey. What do you mean by that?
What, you're not related to Dad at all?
So I guess we weren't really family after all.
Where are you going? Your father only said that because he was upset.
That's right. Everything will be fine once you're gone.
- All right, let's go!
- Let's go!
Be careful!
All right, almost there! Yay, we're here!
♫  How much more painful will it be? ♫
- Let's go!
♫  If I could hold you in my arms ♫
Are you mad, our little princess, because you couldn't get a black belt?
Eun Ha Won. What did I say?
Thirty-Six Stratagems, Chapter 1, Section 4.
"Wait at leisure while the enemy labors." Wait until the proper time comes.
That's right! You can do better from now on, right Ha Won?
Of course! Hyah! Hyah!
Why, you!
♫  Without you ♫
♫  I will wait for you forever. ♫
♫  Even the reason that I breathe ♫
♫  is you is something you don't know. ♫
♫  Saying I love you is not enough. ♫
♫  My love only for you. ♫
Ja Yeong
♫  How much more painful will it be? ♫
- Hello?
- Ms. Ha Won.
Have you thought about my offer?
♫  If I could hold you in my arms ♫
Chairman?
My offer still stands. What's your decision?
Is your answer the same as last time?
♫  You're the only reason to live. ♫
Haneul House is open to you.
♫  Without you ♫
♫  I'm not letting you go. ♫
Everything will change at Haneul House. Come and see for yourself.
- Let me see.
- Wait, let me see one more time. Where?
Everything will change at Haneul House. Come and see for yourself.
- I'm off.
- What? Where are you going?
Ah, I'm cold.
Sorry. All right, all we have left now is one radio appearance.
Okay.
Let's get some rest after we're done today, Woo Seok.
All right, shall we go?
Everything will change at Haneul House Come and see for yourself.
- Hey!
- What?
- Turn the car around!
- Why?
- It's Grandfather!
- Woo Seok, turn the car around!
Yes, sir!
Everything will change at Haneul House. Come and see for yourself.
Mom, is it really okay if I live here?
Let's go inside.
Oh, and there's one condition you< must adhere to while living here.
Dating is strictly forbidden in Haneul House.
♫  While I keep looking only at you ♫
♫  It's the first time I've felt  ♫
♫  a trembling feeling like a lie pointing only at you ♫
♫  Why did you show up now? ♫
♫  It's the fate I was looking forward to ♫
♫  I've bet my everything on you ♫
♫  You are so precious. ♫
♫  I feel your heart heart heart. ♫