[English subtitles are available]
[Fall in Love with a Fox]
[EP11]
It's him again!
Stop!
Young Master
Give out my order,
block the whole valley.
Yes, sir!
What!
Shu got hurt!
Don't worry,
Young Master is fine.
What about Lord Qu?
I'm not quite clear about that
Lord Qu
No,
I'll go to see him.
Shu
Qiuer
I know
what happened at the warehouse yesterday.
Are you okay?
Let me see.
Young Master
has recovered.
But if he knew Miss Jin
is so worried about him,
he would be more than willing
to stay unrecovered for a few more days
so you may look after him.
Jueming
I'll leave you alone.
How are you?
I was so worried about you.
If something happened to you,
I...
Who are those evildoers?
They dared strike out at you
at Taoyuan Valley.
It's still under investigation,
and it's weird.
Thanks to Lord Qu's rescue.
I was too mean
to him before.
I didn't expect that
Lord Qu
is such a
gentleman.
Fortunately, he was not hurt.
I'm glad you didn't get hurt.
Qiuer
You haven't
officially married me yet,
but you care about me so much.
It's all my fault.
Shu
Don't say so.
It's all about the evildoers.
By the way,
will they attack
Taoyuan Valley again?
It's not over.
You're still young,
but you need to
face it with me.
I feel so guilty.
Shu
You don't have to.
I will be your wife.
Whatever happened,
we'll stand and
face it together.
Besides,
My dad and Jin's Escort Agency are with us.
Don't worry.
Qiuer
It's my great honor
to have you be my wife.
Is this your medicine?
Let me help you.
Well...
Taoyuan Valley was blocked last night,
and no one broke out.
The two people should still be there.
There are many experts in Taoyuan Valley,
of course they dare not do that.
Then why didn't we
just catch them?
The man I fought with last night
wasn't him.
If we caught
those nonentities,
they must sacrifice them.
Then we'll lose
the clue.
What are you going to do next?
The scent-following finch!
-Qu...  -Lord Qu
Who is this girl?
Lord Qu, I'm Xiaocui.
You've saved my life before,
do you remember?
Xiaocui
I heard you were attacked last night,
and you beat them away
for Young Master.
I brought these pastries
to visit you.
Baiwan
I'm quite relieved
to see that you're fine.
Baiwan
I have important things to do right now,
I got to go.
Lord Qu
I brought you these pastries.
Excuse me,
you can give it to me,
and I will give it to my husband.
I...
Thank you so much.
Where is the stuff?
Fortunately, guards of Taoyuan Valley
only searched the room,
not to the woods.
There's no time to lose.
It must be sent back immediately.
Then we'll
bring the saussurea back to the palace.
They're from the Nonuple Palace.
You bring the saussurea back.
I still have a thing
to do.
Lord Xueyue
Is it because of her?
I won't be at ease
if she is alive.
Young Host
Why are you here?
You're supposed to be asked.
Is it Host
who asked you to steal saussurea?
Young Host
I thought
what he usually makes you do
is to wear masks
to kill a few people.
It's him.
He turned out to be
Young Host of Nonuple Palace.
I didn't expect that
you even
stole things now.
We're Host's most trusted
Heisha.
Young Host, watch your words please.
Heisha
You're just executioners
to solve troubles for him.
There are lots of people in Taoyuan Valley.
Do you dare to stand in front of them
and tell who you are?
Young Master
It's not appropriate to argue here.
Then tell me,
why did he send you to steal saussurea?
Tell me,
otherwise I'll destroy it.
No.
The Host is waiting for saussurea to save him.
What's wrong with my father?
Come to me when you figure it out.
It's really him.
I can't believe
you can restrain my palm strength.
Nonuple Palace always
has a good reputation in the world.
The manipulator
was him.
Whoever it is,
it is not a surprise.
No wonder that not only Envoy Xueyue
came to Taoyuan Valley,
but the Young Host of Palace
hid in the kitchen.
The Heisha they were talking about
are the group of elusive people
wearing masks.
It seems that
his power
not just cover
the Nonuple Palace these years.
Those Heisha
are assassins he secretly trained.
Zheng
Are we get closer
to the truth?
It's been five years.
All the sins he committed
against the Xu family
must be paid back.
You're on time.
Qingyun
Give saussurea back to me.
Neither you nor I
can afford to delay.
I can give you back,
but I have something to ask you.
Did you recognize
Chu long ago?
What did you say?
Still wanna lie to me.
Was it you
that day?
What happened five years ago?
Why did everyone tell me
Chu is dead
when I woke up?
It's been five years.
Haven't you forgotten her yet?
Jin Baiwan is Chu, isn't she?
So what?
She is the wife
of Lord of Tingqin Garden now.
What can you do?
Sure enough.
So you wanna kill her
at the womenfolk gathering!
You did this to me for her.
Well, then I guess my decision before
was right.
You can't kill me.
Otherwise
the Host is not gonna let you off the hook.
Who do you think you are?
You're just a tool.
I'm telling you for the last time.
If you try to kill Chu again,
I will never let you go.
I can't believe you don't even
care about my life because of her.
How can I
let her live?
Saving her life?
Who allowed you to save so many people?
Baiwan
Why are you here?
I haven't eaten
the pastries you prepared today.
Of course I'm here to ask for that.
I've thrown
the pastries from the girl away.
Well done,
I like it.
I like
what you said too.
What about the pastries you made for me?
They were also thrown away.
Because I'm angry today.
Are you
jealous?
Maybe, probably,
yes.
I'm so happy.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Great.
Zheng
Zheng, wake up!
Zheng, what's wrong with you?
Zheng
Zheng, how do you feel now?
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
Don't scare me.
I haven't heard
you say like me yet.
How can I be willing to die?
Lord
Lord Qu
How is he?
The poison did harm to the heart.
I'll have acupuncture on him
to protect the heart,
and force the poison out.
You,
fetch a basin of hot water.
Zheng
How are you feeling now?
Much better.
Don't worry.
I'll send some medicine later.
Remember to
let him take on time.
Thanks, Miss Su.
Keep in mind,
never channel the "qi"
before you recover.
Otherwise,
you'll be in danger.
Thank you, Miss Su.
Knock it off,
take good care of him.
Zheng
I'll be right outside,
call me if you need.
Miss Su
What's up?
I can't be more grateful
for your help.
You can say that again.
I always know
you are capable.
OK.
Consider it
Lord Qu and you
owe me one this time.
In the future,
I'll take it back.
That's easy.
But,
I have told Lord Yu of Valley
and Head Escort in private
about the poisoning.
Beyond that,
keep it a secret,
especially to the new couple.
Don't affect
their dinner party tomorrow night.
I see.
Take good care of him.
You,
I'll take good care of you too.
Do you want me to prick you?
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Zheng
Ever since you met me,
I've been a burden on you.
I was like a big trouble.
There is nothing I can do.
You
just be my wife.
I'll do the rest.
Why do you like me?
Why would you
do so many things for me?
Because you are what you are.
Whatever your name is,
no matter you are a cook or someone.
As long as it's you,
I'll do anything
for you.
But there's nothing I can do.
There's only
one thing
I want you to do.
Don't leave me again.
When did I ever do?
Then promise me,
don't leave me ever.
Of course.
That's what you used to say.
Used to?
Zheng
Are you confused because of the illness?
I didn't say words
like that before.
Never mind.
I'm confused.
Baiwan
What did you bring
this morning?
Sesame dumplings in rice wine soup.
But you ignored me,
so I was mad and ate it.
It was you made
for me,
why did you eat it all?
What,
you wanna eat?
Well, then lie down,
I'll make it for you.
OK.
It's done.
Eat it while it's hot.
Zheng
I promise,
I'll never leave you.
But you have to promise me too.
Stop scaring me,
okay?
They were prepared for it.
You don't have to do anything here.
Take saussurea back,
the Host is more important.
OK.
Then should we
tell everything here to Host?
Truthfully report to him.
Yes, madam.
Young Master
There's something wrong!
I...
Why are you
in such a hurry?
The warehouse was stolen,
Lord of Valley gave an order
that check all the property
of the valley.
Get to the point.
What a surprise!
In Miss Jin's room.
There were plenty of suspicious objects.
Horrendous, exactly.
What on earth are those?
I'm, I'm too embarrassed to say it.
Jueming
Those are something about
hugging,
cuddling,
kissing and so on.
What!
No,
it's wedding night.
I can't even fit into my wedding dress.
I can't eat any more.
But Mrs. Yu always
doesn't let me have enough food.
I have to eat when I'm hungry.
Eat it!
Miss Muqiu
It's you.
You scared me.
In order to prevent
thief stealing,
Young Master checked
your dowry chest.
All your novels
were found out.
What!
Miss Muqiu
Jueming
Give my order,
what have been found
in Miss Muqiu's room
must not be told to anyone,
especially Mr and Mrs. Yu.
Yes.
Young Master
There are two more cases next door.
Wha...
You,
what are you doing?
Jueming
Leave us alone.
OK.
Qiuer
Are these books
really yours?
If I say no,
will you believe me?
Then explain it to me,
why is there your handwriting
on these novels?
Why do you ask
if you know it?
How silly you are, Qiuer!
You are from a noble family.
How can you write,
write these
dirty novels?
What's wrong with my novels?
They're all
my hard work,
how can you degrade them?
Why can't you realize your fault?
Never mind.
I'll cover
what happened today for you.
But these things
can't be kept in the valley,
and known by anyone!
What are you going to do?
These are mine,
you can't take them away!
In this situation,
what do you want?
It makes people think
Young Mrs of Taoyuan Valley
is a person
who write disgusting and dirty books!
What will they think of us!
So many people like my novels,
why are they dirty
only
in Taoyuan Valley!
Well, what if I tell you,
you have to give up
those dirty things
if you want to marry me?
What do you mean?
Taoyuan Valley has strict rules,
these stuff can't be accepted.
If you want to calm things down today,
you must promise me.
From now on,
Never touch
and write these novels.
All that nonsense you did before
can not be
told to anyone!
You threaten me, don't you?
I didn't,
I just want you to think it through.
Young Mrs of Taoyuan Valley
is definitely not someone
who's amoral and unreasonable.
I won't back down
over the issue.
I can't believe you said that to me.
What I said is fact.
Do you think I want to get married to you
at Taoyuan Valley?
It's not possible for me
to give up the novels.
I won't marry you! Who cares!
You!
Nonsense!
The wedding day
is coming.
You are not going to marry him.
It's his fault!
You...
Sweetie,
What is going on?
Tell me,
I'm so worried about you.
Fenger
You go first.
Father, please,
please forgive me,
it's inconvenient to tell you.
You,
such a j*rk!
Mr Yu
What are you doing?
The warehouse was just stolen,
and there are many casualties.
Obviously,
there is someone targeting at us.
At this point in time,
you're so childish.
What is it?
It's my fault!
Don't worry,
the wedding will be on time.
And I will apologize to Miss Muqiu.
But I beg you,
allow us to settle this privately.
OK.
Mr Yu
Listen to him,
let them settle this.
Remember,
don't humiliate
Taoyuan Valley!
Calm down.
Mr Yu
Wait.
Are, are you all right?
Miss Muqiu
The engagement is of great importance.
What done is done.
Even if you don't want to marry me,
you have no choice.
It was you threatened me not to marry you.
I just want you
know your place.
Stop writing
those novels.
So you and I can
put all these behind us.
Let me stop writing
unless you kill me.
Kill you?
Under this situation,
do you want
the whole world knows it,
and both families are humiliated?
As long as you promise me
to get married.
I'll promise you,
I'll pretend I don't see
what you write,
even if you do something
out of line.
What do you mean?
As long as no one laugh at us,
I'll let you do whatever you want in private.
However,
the prestige of the Yu family
can not be ruined.
Wait,
in your opinion,
is the prestige of Taoyuan Valley
more important than anything else?
Including the marriage,
you marry me for
the prestige of Taoyuan Valley!
That's right.
This engagement
is about the prestige.
In my mind,
there's nothing more important
than that.
In your opinion,
is the prestige of Taoyuan Valley
more important than anything else?
Including the marriage,
you marry me for
the prestige of Taoyuan Valley!
That's right.
This engagement
is about the prestige.
In my mind,
there's nothing more important
than that.
Young Host
Gather all the disciples of Nonuple Palace
near Taoyuan Town.
Be there before the wedding tonight.
Yes.
But what happened in the valley?
I rarely see Young Host of Palace
be in such a hurry.
She'll be back soon.
Baiwan, what are you gonna do?
I have no idea
why I am on your bed.
But I definitely didn't mean to.
Baiwan
Today is Miss Muqiu's wedding day.
I almost forgot.
Right,
we can't miss
the big event.
You're right.
Now we should...
You should
get up now.
Otherwise
you wouldn't be able to get out the door.
What's wrong?
My heart pains.
I need a dose of medicine
to move on.
What kind of medicine?
Will you
give me?
I'm just kidding.