The Best Chicken
Park Sun Ho
Kim So Hye
Joo Woo Jae
Yes. Yes. Here we are. Please make yourself at home and enjoy looking around.
This is in a great location.
It has a wonderful view as well. And from outside, your signage for your office
will be showing well.
This kind of place
is not on the market often.
You don't need to look around more.
I like it, but
- it's a little expensive.
- What?
What do you think?
I really like it.
Let's get this. We don't need to look for more.
You told me you liked the previous place and we didn't need to look for any other places.
Well, I liked that place, too, but—
You told me you liked the one before that as well. And the one before that one as well and so on.
Forget it.
No, it really is nice here though.
Do you have anything cheaper?
What?
It will be nice if we can find someplace as big as this.
There is one, right behind this street.
It's cheaper and spacious and you can use the whole building.
It's a pearl-in-mud (hidden gem) kind of place, but no.
No, no, no. Because it's located on the deep inside of the street.
Don't even think of that place.
But you mentioned that it's so called "a pearl in mud."
What?
Show it to us. Let us decide after looking around.
I can already predict
what you will decide.
Pardon?
Then, let's go. I will show it to you
but you need to know one thing before you look at the place.
Don't be tempted.
- Be tempted?
- Yes.
In that place, everything is not as it seems.
Don't believe your eyes. Believe me, okay!
Excuse me?
To be honest, that location is not totally bad.
Why those rascals there—
Those bad guys!
Don't ever be deceived, okay?
Okay? Okay? Okay.
Episode 1: The Pearl in the Mud
Sunhwa Tang Monthly Income and Expenditure Record
Pay Here
Monthly (Fixed Budget)
zero
five
hundred thousand
negative three thousand
Grandfather
Again this month, there were not enough customers, so we are short on rent.
I will send it to you next month
if there are more customers.
four hundred ninety-seven thousand
Realtor
Emergency! Grandfather is back on the street.
Chatting: Mina, Gyoo Man, Young Ho
There are no customers coming.  It's just a false alarm.
Friends,
consider this as your jobs
and work diligently today.
Daeduk Butcher Shop
Take it! Take it!  Take it!
What?
Agh!
Under construction
What are you doing?  Spread it quickly!
Spread out more!  More! More!
Hey!  It's all clumped together. Geez!
Practice smiling 100 times.
From the main street, you just turn once to get to this street.
That way leads to the 4-way intersection.
And this is a stationery store. There is a grain shop there too.
Ugh! Aigoo.  There is a boutique. Okay.
This used to be very clean, but...
Look at this darn trash.  Aigoo!  Hey.  Hey.
This street gets lots of foot traffic.
This street feels cozy.
You even like this one? I shouldn't ask your opinion.
I mean this feels different from the crowded and cold-hearted Seoul.
What are you doing?
Since this is bothering me.  Go ahead.
Hey, don't do that. Don't.
Wow. Even a drunken person has manners in this neighborhood.
Wow, how could he vomit in a bag when he's so drunk?
No wonder.
These guys. This place is like that.
Liquidation?
Liquidation with huge discount
Available for lease?
Inquire for lease: No premium
Don't ever fall for these things, okay?
Yeah, those stores have been in business for
30, 40 years. Now the second generations are running the businesses.
- Really?
- Yes.
The stores also get along great!
Is this what you call a business?
Sir, I'm sorry.
How dare you try running a business without paying me a fee for your spot, Mr. Supermarket?
How could I?
Business is SO bad, so—
Accept this.
My boss is not a child! This is pocket money, not enough for a fee for a spot.
Is this enough for it?
A fee for a spot? (Gangs force shop owners to pay for it. Totally illegal.)
How could that exist in this era?
What do you mean, a fee for a spot? Are you a Gumajeok (famous gangster)?
I've got it! I've got it. Hey! Kim Gyoo Man! Hey!
How could you do this? I'm so frustrated.
Aigoo! Aigoo!
- Who is Kim Gyoo Man?
- This rascal!
If only my boss didn't tell us to respect old men.
Aigoo, this rascal! You should watch out what to say.
I'm the type of guy who doesn't just take a beating.
I shouldn't bother speaking! Aigoo.
Let's go, go.
That grandpa must have mistaken you for the neighborhood fool!
If you're talking about this guy, he's not Kim Gyoo Man, but a total gangster!
The neighborhood fool?
Are you going to do it or not? Hurry up!
Surely you're not doing this because you don't want to pay the fee?
If someone saw us they might mistake us for gangsters! If we weren't here, this neighborhood would have so much junk!
I told you to kick this one.
We have to sell that, bastard!
I got confused between this and that, I'm sorry!
How could you get confused between a red basket and a blue basket?!
Why did you do that to me?
What, why?
Over There.
Excuse me. Goomajeok.
- Yes?
- Be grateful for that 'boss'.
Because at least he taught you to respect your elders.
If it weren't for that, I would have just—
What are you doing?
Go.
- Did we get caught?
- I don't know.
Seonhwa Bathhouse
Here!, Here!
Public Bathhouse available
Places like these still exist today.
You can use this entire building,
but the lease conditions are very shocking! The monthly rent is very low.
After the contract, the landlord will pay for the demolition
so that the exterior of the bathhouse will remain after demolition.
That's unfortunate.
What? What's going on? Why is it like this?
We just have to change the lights!
Since this area will be demolished.
You just have a look when the light is on.
You're the first guests in a long time.
You scared me.
I'll say it again, don't be deluded by this!
I'll go with the one we saw earlier. That one on the main street, although it's expensive.
No, we can't make a decision that rashly.
It'll be considerate to her if we look at this place properly in bright lighting.
No, I'm perfectly fine.
- Do you have a ladder?
- In the storage—
No, I don't have one.
Hyung, get down.
What?
You have to take a look too. The light is off for longer than it is on.
I'm really okay. I already made up my mind.
I'm also fine with it.
The flickering is like a club. It's nice, right?
You're right.
It's exciting?
Is that it?
We should at least catch the rats.
I will go with the one that was expensive on the main street.
Let's see. These...
you can put your stamps on after looking at the contracts separately.
That bathhouse is such a pain in the neck.
The building owner complains over the phone,
but I can't find a tenant for that bathhouse. What a hell of a job.
Where did he just go?
It was nice there though.
What? That bathhouse building?
Yes.
Yeah, it's just because it's on the back of a road. But it's near the subway, and the foot traffic isn't bad.
But more than anything, it comes with great lease terms.
By any chance, are you not thinking of the place?
He's an office worker. Myeongseong Group.
Oh, what a great place to work! Your parents must be so proud.
The hyung is a doctor, the younger works for a conglomerate.
Mr.Park, what is this?
It's a resignation.
Why? Is it hard being at the company?
It's not that.
I wasn't supposed to say this, but you're the candidate for the next promotion for Asst. Manager.
Even if it's hard, endure a bit more. The higher ups are all supporting you.
I'm thankful, but I have something that I want to do
What is that?
-Running a shop.
- Running a shop?!
What? Running a shop? Not a business? What are you going to sell?
Thanks.
You must be happy? Yes, have a nice day.
Let's go.
I said let's go, you waited for a while
Let's go eat.
This time, you wait.
For what?
I'll go with that place.
The pearl in the mud. I want that place.
What?
The pearl in the mud?
Seonhwa Bathhouse
Cashier
Is it going to take long?
No, it won't be long.
I'm hungry. I worked too diligently today.
Let's go!
Cheers.
Its good.
You guys went through a lot because of me.
There was nothing difficult,
but today we almost got caught, right?
Right? Most people turn around before even entering the bathhouse.
However, I think your grandpa figured it out.
I don't think your grandpa wants to take this bathhouse off of the lease listings.
Bo Ah, how about you start drawing webtoons again?
Draw webtoons? Forget it.
Why? Your comics were the most entertaining.
Bo Ah, aren't you still drawing right now?
- Hey!
- You guys didn't see when you came up?
There's a tablet on the counter.
You probably didn't want anyone to see you draw.
You're still drawing, right?
- You, just eat meat!
I'm not drawing.
I told you I wasn't going to draw again.
It's nice now.
My job is comfortable, money is coming in nicely, and I have you guys.
I finally feel comfortable. But what's up with my grandpa disturbing me?
He should've just left me alone.
Right, drink.
Let's drink.
You worked hard.
You've worked hard.
What's with you?
This is for business, not for apartment leasing.
Hyung, I'll explain it to you slowly.
Whether it's an explanation or whatever, why would a company employee lease here?
First off, I'm not an employee at the company.
What are you doing?
- Did you quit the company?
- Yes
Are you crazy? Do you want to see your mom faint?
Exactly, so keep it a secret from her. I have a plan.
Once my business does well, I'll tell her.
You can't suddenly come here and tell me you'll sign a contract. Who's plan was this?
Hey, you can't impulsively make a decision like that.
First, go home—
I think it's that elder. I'll talk to you at home.
Hey!
Lease Contract
You have to wait a little.
Yes, take your time.
I heard you quit your job at a normal company.
You don't seem to have much determination.
Hey, don't start with that nonsense.
Don't get offended.
He's normally rash.
I'm okay.
If you're trying to run a shop to avoid working at a company, give up now.
I'm not running away. I quit the company a short while ago, however, I've been preparing this for a really long time.
What? When did you?
Getting my heart ready.
Geez, take it easy on him.
It was really hard to find a renter.
I've verified everything. Do I just stamp here?
Oh, yes, go ahead.
Wait.
If you are okay with it, I want to add a condition.
A condition?
It probably won't be bad for you either.
It's nice.
Aspirations or whatnot.
Having a sweet dream at night is enough for me.
That's right. As long as you like it, it's fine.
Hey, there's no right answer in life.
That's right.
We will help you no matter what.
If you keep doing it for a year, two years, your grandpa will change his mind.
Landlord
Hey, speak of the devil.
Hey!
Hello?
Our beautiful granddaughter.
Grandpa, did something happen? Are you okay, did you get hurt?
You hurt your head, didn't you!
No, I'm healthy.
All my worries went away.
What?
The bathhouse has been leased. Even the deposit was made, that's why.
Aren't you mistaken?
Oriental medicine works—
Get out of my building right now!
Grandpa? Hello? Grandpa?
Grandpa? Hello? Grandpa!
What is this?
How is it?
It's not entertaining?
Well, I think I have seen this plot somewhere.
Perhaps, is it because of Writer Lee Jin Sang?
Yes, I'll be honest with you.
Our platform has no intention of working with you, Writer Seo Bo Ah.
What on Earth is this!
Why are you so noisy!
I said why are you so noisy!
What is that sound?
What are you doing right now?
Oh, hello.
Here are the stairs to the second floor.
Get out! Get out!
- No, no, wait a minute.
- Get out now!
Excuse me. Ouch.
Excuse me! Oh!
W-Wait!
Excuse me. I think you didn't hear me, but I'm the new tenant.
Excuse me!
Oh, Min Ah! What happened? You told me I still had time left.
How can he barge in as soon as he signed the contract? What kind of situation is this?
The thing is...
I just heard of it right now. It's been settled like this.
The new tenant said that he wanted to start as soon as possible, that's why your...
Does that make any sense? What am I suppose to do?
Should I get kicked out when I'm not even ready?
Try dragging out some time. I'll...
I get it, Min Ah. Please be quick.
What is this?
We are getting paid today no matter what. There are no pay cuts.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Landlord, what happened—
Wait, don't make a fuss over something this minor.
Landlord.
What is this? Are you crazy?
This is still our bathhouse!
I'm going to call the police on you!
Hello? This is 112 (police station), right?
There's a strange person breaking down our door right now.
I don't know! I don't know the person!
Please come quickly.
Grandpa!
Grandpa, let's discuss first.
I have money. I didn't waste my rent money.
Come in. I'll get a new door, so don't worry.
Yes.
Seriously! Why are you doing this to me?
Landlord, please calm down.
You need to finish what you started.
You signed for the whole building, so you'll also use the second floor and the rooftop.
It is true, but your granddaughter seems shocked and you can slowly empty the second floor—
Stay out of this.
Open the door while I'm still using words.
This is my house! Why are you doing this?
How is this your house when you don't even pay rent!
Grandpa, you're trying to get money out of me? You normally don't seek rent for the second floor.
I'm going to start seeking it now. The second floor will be used by this male boss.
While I'm being nice, open the door.
I won't open it! Then, where will I live? Are you telling me to sleep on the streets?
Grandpa, did you pick me up from the streets (am I not your family)?
Either go back to live with your parents or go find your own place!
I won't do it! I said I won't! Just let me live like this.
Grandpa, why are you doing this to me? What has suddenly gotten into you?
Do you want to see me die?
You should start living like a human!
Until when are you going to linger in the bathhouse like a corpse and keep killing time?
Grandpa, what do you know to be saying this?
I... I also worked hard! What more do you want from me?
Move back. You'll get hurt.
Wait!
What's wrong with you?
I, well, I rented this whole building, right?
That's right.
So, you can't break down doors without my permission.
I told you that I was going to get you new doors. Step aside.
I like this door. It matches totally with my restaurant's concept.
What?
And you should remember our contract's special clause.
I'll try talking with your granddaughter.
If she understands with words, would I be making this fuss?
You'll regret it if you meddle in this. Just move away.
Elder, this is my place now.
Stop blabbering and empty out the second floor. I'll give you exactly one week.
You. Don't be late on rent.
Of course, I won't be late at all, Elder.
Excuse me, you dropped your cellphone.
Excuse me!
You're inside, right? I heard some noises just now.
Ah, what?
Come out. Grandpa left, so let's talk between us.
Come out? Come out where?
I'm going to starve to death here. So, whether you want to destroy the bathhouse or seal it here by pouring cement,
do whatever you want.
I'm sorry. I didn't know things would turn out like this.
I just really like this place.
What's the point of apologizing now? I don't have anything left.
I'm going to get kicked out with nothing left.
You must think I'm pathetic, right?
Why am I making such a fuss over this bathhouse?
You don't understand, right?
This bathhouse that you took from me, it's the only thing that's left for me.
Everything I wanted to do, everything I wanted to be,
I gave up all of those and I am left with this as my everything.
Can't I just live like this?
Why are people so cruel?
A special clause?
That's right. My granddaughter is hiding in the bathhouse that's even older than she is.
She's not doing anything.
She was a child who had lots of dreams and lots of ambitions.
But after she started drawing manhwa or whatnot and got rejected...
Yes, you must've been really worried.
Rather than her close friends,
once she starts to encounter other people, she may feel like living as a person again.
Yes.
So, since you're going to open a store and will need employees,
if you use my granddaughter as a part-timer,
I'll cut 500,000 won off your rent.
And I'll let you add another condition.
My condition?
Yes, what do you want?
Landlord, I want to do business here for a really long time.
Your grandpa gave you one week to empty out.
Do you have anywhere to go after a week?
Are you teasing me?
No, I need to find a place to live in too.
I'm living at my brother's house while walking on eggshells and troubling him.
That's your problem.
Now that you've destroyed someone else's business,
you want to take my place too?
If you need a job, I can give you one.
What?
Once my restaurant opens, I'll need part-timers.
Since you've lived in this neighbourhood a long time,
you seem like the perfect fit.
Perhaps, you don't want to work with me here?
What is he saying?
Forget it.
Excuse me! Wait a second!
I have your cellphone.
Please open up.
I said forget it!
I'm going to starve to death anyway. What's the use of a cellphone?
I said that your grandpa is not here.
I'll leave the cellphone in front of the door, so come and get it after five minutes.
I'm going to go home now.
To be honest, I can't open the door.
Pardon?
I said that I can't open the door.
I was afraid Grandpa was going to break it down, so I stacked some stuff up.
You need to reach it from the bottom.
You're reaching it.
Stretch a little more.
A-Almost.
Wait a second.
Your arms are too short.
Throw it.
What?
I said to throw it.
You're telling me to throw the cellphone?
Yes, throw it.
What happens if it falls?
It's okay. Throw it.
I'm really going to throw it.
Yes.
Catch it well.
One, two, three.
What? You can't even throw it properly.
It's not that I can't throw properly, but rather I'm afraid the cellphone will fall.
It's fine if it falls.
Hurry up and throw it.
- I'm really going to throw it hard this time.
- Yes.
One, two, three.
Wait.
Tie it at your end.
Yes.
- Wait.
- What?
Wait a bit, I'll be back.
A little more.
Hello.
Cooking oil.
Welcome.
Give me one chicken.
How much is it?
It's 5,000 won.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Mr. Journalist!
Please stop it now, you must be tired from today's shoot.
What is this?
I'll talk to you later. I'm busy.
If you give me a few names, I'll sent you their information first thing tomorrow morning.
Please erase what you just recorded right now. Okay?
Park Choi Go
♫  I like chicken, I like chicken  ♫
♫  I really like chicken  ♫
♫  A little more fry coating, a little more seasoning  ♫
♫  And more of soy-sauce flavor chicken  ♫
♫  Crispy chicken fills my mouth  ♫
♫  It makes me smile broadly  ♫
♫  A chubby leg, a  meaty breast  ♫
♫  They are the best and tastiest gift  ♫
♫  Chicken, chicken, chicken, chicken  ♫
♫  I like it, I like it, I like chicken  ♫
♫  The best chicken with gold color  ♫
♫  I like it, I like it, I like chicken (Yeah)  ♫
♫  Our ever-lasting friend  ♫
You're seriously amazing.
Okay, give it to me.
Let's see what kind of amazing chicken you came up with to sell.
Where are you going? You didn't fry it for me?
No.
Then, why did you fry it in my kitchen at this time?
I'm going to hire a part-timer.
What?
Pull it up.
I said to pull it up.
Oh, yes.
What is this?
This is the first chicken I've fried for somebody else.
I'm going to open a chicken restaurant on the first floor.
Try it.
Once you eat it, you'll want to work with me.
Its not too bad.
What is this?
If Park Choi Go hires Seo Bo Ah as a part-time worker,
he will get ₩500,000 off his monthly rent?
When I open we'll need a part-time worker.
Would you by any chance want to work here?
No wonder why he yapped such nonsense.
What? Are you toying with a person right now?
Wonil Real Estate Office
She doesn't pick up my calls and he hasn't contacted me all day.
Is she really alright?
Bo Ah
Why couldn't we reach you? Do you know how worried we were?
It's Bo Ah.
I had a situation, that's why.
But what was that? If I become a part-time worker, ₩500,000?
Is that important right now?
What?
Didn't you read the whole message I sent?
Did you not check the length of the lease on the contract?
Wait a minute.
Lease for 30 years
The lease term is 30 years?
Yeah! I thought about ways that you could get the bathhouse back.
There's no other method.
Unless his business fails and he leaves on his own two feet,
we won't be able to push him out. That's how the contract was made. The landlord can't kick him out arbitrarily.
Hello? Hey.
Seo Bo Ah, hey.
Are you listening, Seo Bo Ah?
Hello?
So what it means is this is the only way, right?
No. There's no way at all.
You just said it right now.
He just has to fail and he needs to leave on his own two feet.
That's what I'm saying. So it's not too late to get some purified water and pray.
Hope that his chicken tastes bad and that his business fails!
Well, his chicken is okay.
What are you saying? How would you know that?
It's not a problem that will be solved if I just get some pure water and pray.
Barun Chicken
Refreshing Bath/ Barun Chicken
Let's wash up.
What?
- Hey, I'll—
- Oh?
What?
It's changed a lot.
It seems totally new
I think it did change.
Welcome. It's just you too, right
Yes, but
Come this way.
Go, go.
Isn't this a bathhouse?
Would you like to order?
Order?
♫    Will you be my one and only universe?   ♫
♫    So a pretty flower that resembles you
can bloom the cracks of my heart   ♫
♫   You probably don’t know but you’ve  ♫
♫   become the world to someone  ♫
The Best Chicken
Ten thousand won an hour, with no probation period.
Good. Can't you do it one more time?
Boss, Boss, Boss.
Just by looking at it, the feeling came!
How is this chicken?
You still don't have the basic understanding of the ingredients.
What were you doing so excitedly?
One, two, three!
No, how could that be?!
Running a business must be interesting to you.
Let's go!
This won't do.
We need something special.
Fail it. Fail it.
Seo Bo Ah, what is this?
♫   Has a hidden happiness  ♫
♫   come into my arms?  ♫
♫   I’m dreaming of my eyes getting blinded by looking at a gem  ♫
♫   I’ll hang you  ♫
♫   like a star on the sky of my heart  ♫
♫   Sweet days and nights, I only want to look at the heavenly you  ♫
♫  Baby I have a crush on you  ♫
♫   Will you be  ♫
♫   my one and only universe?  ♫
♫   So a pretty flower that resembles you can bloom the cracks of my heart  ♫
♫   You probably don’t know but you’ve become  ♫
♫   the world to someone  ♫
♫   Even my smallest wish  ♫
♫   has become you  ♫
♫   Baby I need your love  ♫
♫   Will you follow the clock hands  ♫
♫   and come here?  ♫
♫   Into this picturesque scene where your breath touches, into our own time  ♫