-Shall we make rice now?
-Let's cook.
Shouldn't we mop the floor?
You can make rice here.
And we can grill the meat here.
Let's flip the lid.
Shall we start a fire here?
That would be too strong.
-Then, here?
-Yeah.
Let's fire it up here and grill.
STARTLED
Watch out.
I think I just saw something amazing.
TERRIFYING FIREPOWER
-Kian, use this.
-What?
We had this?
-I got it.
-You got it.
There you go.
Wow, it's so strong.
LIGHTS THE FIREPLACE
WITH AN EMPTY CAULDRON
TO MAKE RICE
AND TO GET RID OF INSECTS
PUTS IN A LOT OF WOOD
Why didn't he make
a chimney for the fireplace?
WITHOUT A CHIMNEY,
SMOKE GOES OUT THE WINDOWS
My eyes are burning.
Geez, mine hurt too!
-I mean…
-It's too strong.
Who builds a fireplace without a chimney?
I DO
We have to clean this right now!
It's heating up.
WASHING AFTER HEATING
Put it over here.
My eyes are burning.
Why is it so heavy?
I'll do it.
Wait a minute.
We have too much smoke in here.
We're sleeping like this?
USING THE FAN TO VENTILATE
I can't even open my eyes.
Even when we made rockets in high school,
I don't think there was this much smoke.
Gosh, I can't open my eyes!
You idiot!
Damn it!
OVERFLOWING WITH DOPAMINE
Your true colors are showing now, Ye-eun.
ME TOO
Go outside. I'll do it.
Like this? Okay.
THE CAULDRON IS SET
It smells like the countryside though.
It's nice.
It would be better
if you stayed over there.
Don't mind us.
Make yourselves at home.
It's peaceful.
What on earth is this?
I can breathe now.
Still, it was only our first day there.
We thought we should be like,
"This is fun!"
But I think Kian should stay away
from designing houses.
I should make the rice.
HOW WILL KIAN'S RICE TASTE?
A POT INSIDE THE CAULDRON?
What idiot designed this house?
I DID
My eyes!
-Meal trays.
PREPARING THE MEAL TRAYS
IN THE MIDST OF CHAOS
-Gosh, the smell.
-Man, I'm…
I can't stay in there.
ESCAPING AFTER RICE STARTS COOKING
Geez, I'm crying!
Wait, so the rice is cooking.
We can grill the pork belly now.
Let's cook it when the guests arrive.
Should we do that?
Gosh, look at the sky!
-Wow, it's a rainbow!
-Wow.
-That's amazing.
It looks like it's from a cartoon.
Want me to take your photo?
Stand over there.
Kian, you're very sentimental.
I don't usually do this, but…
Say "rainbow."
-One, two.
-Rainbow.
That rainbow is amazing.
Should we go and unpack our stuff too?
We have to go unpack too.
-Sure.
-Okay.
-We haven't been to our rooms yet.
-I see.
Let's go unpack and come back.
Opening the B&B from the first day
is a lot of work.
I'm mad at you, Boss.
I'm sorry. This is my first time too.
UNPACKING IN THE STAFF'S QUARTERS
WHILE THE RICE COOKS
A TOAD?
A SMALL STATUE OF THE BUDDHA?
A BELL?
6:30 P.M.
AT THE MONORAIL
-You can put your suitcase in the back.
-Okay.
So this is where we get on?
I think so.
My goodness.
QUICKLY TAKES OFF
This is so scary!
What is this?
THE ONLY WAY TO GET TO KIAN'S B&B
Watch out!
My face is all wet from the rain.
Wow, it's so pretty!
But this is too…
It's so pretty though.
But how far are we going?
There's a rainbow.
-Where?
-Over there.
That's amazing.
Are we the first guests?
I think they're here.
But none of the staff are here.
What do we do?
This is crazy.
HESITANT
-Hello.
Hello.
It's really smoky inside.
TWO GUESTS CHECK IN
AT A KIAN-LESS KIAN'S B&B
The staff left for a moment to unpack.
What did they do inside?
-What did they do?
-They're making rice.
-Rice?
-Yes.
-But…
-I think it's burning.
Can we go in?
You can if you're okay with it.
My eyes are burning.
I was so shocked.
The smoke coming from the cauldron
was beyond imagination.
It was the first time in my life
I was unable to open my eyes like that.
I'm crying.
-Goodness.
-I'm crying.
I think something's gone wrong.
PLEASE HELP KIAN'S B&B SUCCEED
What's that?
When you rub its back,
it'll bring good luck.
Good luck's coming in.
I can hear the luck coming in.
CROAK
Let's go.
I think the guests are here.
The staff's coming now.
-Hello.
THE STAFF RETURNS
I think your B&B will go out of business.
-Did you put out the fire?
-What?
Hold on. Gosh.
ACTIVATING THE VENTILATION SYSTEM
That's a great idea.
The fire's really strong.
PUTS OUT THE FIRE IN THE FIREPLACE
Well done.
Good job.
My gosh.
We're suffering so much with a dumb boss.
I know.
What did you say?
-I was expecting Hyori's Bed & Breakfast.
-Really?
Over there, it was definitely…
-Me too.
-It's…
I came expecting
Hyori's Bed & Breakfast too.
They said it was the same director.
When we received the guests,
I wanted to talk and mingle with them.
But things were already hectic for us.
I was in a total state of panic then.
DID THE RICE COOK WELL?
IT'S JUST WATER AND RICE
It did cook a little bit.
What on earth do you mean?
It should be fully cooked.
What do you mean "a little bit"?
It's half-cooked,
like a rare steak.
Rice cooked rare.
It's just rice soaked in water.
This isn't going to work.
Let's just use the portable stove.
It'd be nice if we had another one.
With just one…
THINKING
You're hungry, aren't you?
-In that case, sir…
-Yeah?
-Let's cook here with the portable stove.
-Okay.
And relight the fireplace.
-Relight it?
-The cauldron…
Let's clean it.
-Let's just grill the pork belly on it.
-All right.
I'll give it my best.
Should I just go and buy some mulhoe?
Mulhoe?
That would be faster.
Just for tonight since we have no choice.
Just for tonight…
No, Ye-eun.
Don't compromise!
Hold on.
-Just for tonight. Yeah.
-Just for tonight?
-Ye-eun!
-What I mean is…
-People make mistakes.
-Ye-eun!
-But we…
-People can make mistakes.
What are you doing, Ye-eun?
We can just light the firewood
and grill the meat.
In that case,
that'll take an hour and a half.
I think buying mulhoe would be faster.
COOKING FOOD THEMSELVES
VERSUS BUYING MULHOE
WHAT WILL THE OWNER CHOOSE?
No, we shouldn't.
We…
We have to serve our guests.
KIAN'S PHILOSOPHY
WE MAKE MEALS FOR GUESTS
That's right.
I'll wash the cauldron then.
Gosh, that's cold!
RELIT
SILENCE
So, are you liking your stay?
They just got here.
ARE WE LIKING OUR STAY?
How many days are you staying here?
-I'll be here for three days.
-Me too.
Both of you?
Did you two first meet here?
Yes, we just met.
-We just met on the monorail.
-Right.
Well, in any case,
you're here now, so just relax.
8:00 P.M.
THE RICE IS COOKED
-Everyone, scoop your rice.
-Come eat.
The rice is cooked so well.
I know I made it, but…
-The rice is…
-Look at it steam.
Go and scoop your rice.
Everyone…
-There's no breakfast tomorrow.
-Okay.
-So you have to eat a lot tonight.
Even if you're hungry tomorrow…
-How come?
-The only B&B with no breakfast.
We usually serve it,
but just not for tomorrow.
They usually serve it
and not dinner. It switched.
We're treating this
as tomorrow's breakfast.
FINISHES OILING THE CAULDRON
Gosh, it's hot.
This might not work.
Let me ask for help.
-Hey.
-Hi, sir!
-Are you having fun?
-I'm shooting a show right now.
Who's that?
You know cauldrons, right?
-What kind of cauldron?
-Those cast-iron cauldrons.
-Is that Paik Jong-won?
-It's Mr. Paik. They're close.
-Yeah, I hear his voice.
-But…
Isn't calling Mr. Paik
about a burned cauldron a bit much?
I've been wiping it for a while,
but I get black residue. What do I do?
With cast iron, you have to use it first.
Whether you fry or boil something,
you have to use it first.
That way, it becomes naturally seasoned.
But I keep getting black residue
from the cast iron.
You can just eat it.
You won't die, kid.
You won't get residue once it gets hot.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Okay, I got it. Thank you.
-Enjoy your meal. Bye.
-Sir.
-Yeah?
I just asked Mr. Paik.
What did he say?
He said it's okay to eat.
PROBLEM SOLVED
All right, it's settled.
It's all set.
If being clean is important, use this.
If you're adventurous, use that.
He said if we use high heat,
we'll get less residue.
Okay. I'm looking forward to it.
Good luck.
GLARES
What?
What's wrong?
Want me to help?
-That would be great.
-You need my help?
All right, I'm coming.
You should've said so then!
It's lonely if you cook by yourself.
It is?
Of course!
Hey, we shouldn't leave the food out here.
We're staying here for a while.
MUNCH
-Why are you eating raw green onions?
-Want some?
-No.
-It's tasty.
It's all set. Pass me the meat.
Sir, the fire has weakened.
Let's stoke it again.
We should use the butane torch.
Is it working?
Mr. Paik was right. It's not black.
THE FRYING PAN TEAM
Let me cook it for you first.
I'll do it for you.
You can just sit and relax.
This works so well. We're cooking faster.
Their meat won't cook.
Let's hurry up and eat.
You must be starving.
The meat's cooking.
We're the winners.
It's a complete mess in there.
Look at the smoke.
It's like when they cooked the rice.
VENTILATION SYSTEM IS ON
Are you good at grilling meat?
-Not too bad, I'd say.
-Okay.
Let's also grill some kimchi
in the middle.
Should we do it or not?
-Let's try this much first.
-This much?
Put it in.
Green onions.
Why are you putting green onions in?
They're delicious when grilled.
Let's grill this one too.
That's hot!
-Cook this.
-Why are you grilling these?
Try it. It's delicious.
What are you talking about?
-Try it.
-Come on!
-They eat this in Italy.
-It's all burnt!
Put it in.
It's all burnt!
Put it in. Give it to me.
Hey, this is…
Let's use the frying pan. Geez.
It looks good though.
-Those green onions are raw.
-We should grill them some more.
Gosh, it's so hot.
Hold on a second.
Take this first.
-And the kimchi.
-One more piece of kimchi.
We're already eating.
Ye-eun was right.
See? I was right.
The frying pan's much better.
-It was easy and enjoyable for us.
-Exactly.
-Eat up.
-Hurry and eat.
Is it good?
It's so good.
-It's delicious.
-I know!
-It's splattering again.
-Is it good?
It's delicious.
-I know!
-It's so good.
VERY PLEASED WITH THEIR FIRST MEAL
-Let me…
-The kimchi is so good.
Sir, is this what you wanted
to do for the show?
What I wanted to do?
Yeah, I like it.
-Then, it's fine.
-Right.
-B&Bs are all about taking some rest.
So then…
you just lie down in your room and relax.
But we don't have walls here anyway.
TOGETHER AS ONE AT KIAN'S B&B
Well, during your stay,
let me know if anything is uncomfortable.
This is uncomfortable.
-Sir, the smoke…
-Right.
That's a lot of smoke. Seriously.
-My nose is running.
-It's uncomfortable.
-Right.
-It's so uncomfortable.
You want us to sleep there?
I can't believe what I said either.
After making this mess,
I'm asking you what's uncomfortable.
Seriously, this whole situation
is uncomfortable.
Since you're here,
let's all share a drink.
Do we even have any cups?
We don't have cups.
Or with the meal trays…
Should we drink from the meal trays?
-I don't mind.
-Me neither.
Yeah, let's use the meal trays.
I'll serve everyone a drink
since you're all here.
Okay, I'll pour your drink.
Goodness.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy your stay, everyone.
MAKGEOLLI BOWLS FOR GUESTS
Make yourself at home.
For me…
MEAL TRAYS FOR STAFF
That's hilarious.
Shouldn't we take a photo?
This will be a fond memory.
Gen Z takes photos of this.
One, two, three.
-Nice to meet you all.
-Cheers.
That's nice.
-You look like an athlete. Right?
-Is that so?
-Are you an athlete?
-I'm retired now.
-You're retired?
-Really?
You must be in your twenties…
-I'm 23.
-You're 23, but…
-Why are you retired at 23?
-I think I know your sport.
You were a dancer, right?
-No.
-I know!
-Swimmer.
-Gymnast.
Swimmer. Gymnast?
I did artistic swimming.
Synchronized swimming.
-I was close!
-Synchronized swimming.
I was born in 2005. I'm 20.
Wow, you're 20?
-What's your dream?
What do you want to do the most?
I want to become a flight attendant.
-A flight attendant. It would suit you.
-Right?
Thank you.
-Our guests need to go to bed soon.
-Right.
-Everyone.
-Yes?
Those who want to sleep can go to bed.
-It's 10:00 p.m.
-Those who want to drink can drink.
It's all up to you.
There should be a curtain
to divide the men and women,
but I don't see it.
We'll have to tape it on.
Yeah.
-It won't fall.
-Right.
-It'll be fine.
-It's sturdy.
BEFORE
Good night, everyone.
-I'll see you tomorrow.
-Okay.
AFTER
I'll head to bed first!
Wait for us!
10:30 P.M.
THE STAFF CLOCKS OUT
They might not be able to get up tomorrow.
-Good job today.
-Good job, everyone.
-Hey, Boss!
-Yes?
These are…
pajamas that I made.
-Wow!
-Really?
-Yeah.
-That's amazing.
-These are called "devil pajamas."
-Okay.
Devil pajamas?
Yes, you wear them
when you think your day
didn't go too well.
These ones are called "angel pajamas."
You wear these when your day went well.
When your day went well?
I did have a good day.
These are like heirlooms.
I had five sets at home.
I gave one to Coldplay.
-They're pretty rare.
-I gave one to Mr. Paik.
I brought the remaining two here.
I'm honored.
This is awesome.
It's cute.
KIAN BEGINS WASHING UP
THREE MINUTES LATER
-Are you taking a shower, Kian?
-Give me a second. I'm almost done.
-You're done already?
-Of course.
You're already done showering?
That makes no sense.
-I don't like long showers.
-It's not about liking it or not.
What are you talking about?
Nice.
It does look nice.
But do we have any shampoo?
Shampoo? There's soap.
-But no shampoo?
-All different types.
You mean all different types of soap?
There's body wash,
shampoo, and conditioner in bar form.
THE ALPHA MALE OF ULLEUNGDO ISLAND
HAPPY WITH HOW HE LOOKS
There's a bug.
-Sir.
-Yeah?
This…
-What is it?
-Could you kill this for me?
-Is there a bug?
-Yes.
This one too! This moth too!
-This one too!
-Where?
-It just flew by.
-It's fine.
This bug is more scared of you.
Here! Here it is!
The bug! Hurry!
Gosh, don't look.
It's scared of you too.
It's going there to rest.
No, please! Don't!
-I killed it for you.
-Please help!
-Don't! Help.
-Seriously? It's that bad?
-Please!
-It's here.
It went off to sleep.
No, it'll start flying around again.
-What?
-It'll start to fly around.
Should I turn off the light?
Moths don't suck your blood. It's fine.
-I'll tell you if I see it again.
-Okay.
SHOO, SHOO
WAVING THEM AWAY
KICKS
CASUALLY UNFOLDS JIN'S MAT TOO
WARMHEARTED INTENTIONS
HALF-HEARTED ACTIONS
I'm going to bed.
Good job today.
JIN THE ANGEL GETS READY TO SLEEP TOO
My goodness.
I'm so exhausted.
Hurry and go to sleep. You must be tired.
THE GUESTS GO TO BED AS WELL
THE SECOND DAY
7:00 A.M.
KIAN'S B&B ANNEX, STAFF'S QUARTERS
BLANKET TURNED INSIDE OUT
Hello?
-Hello.
-I'm the one coming in today.
-Have you arrived?
-We have one more person in our group.
-Okay.
But he missed the train this morning.
I see.
He'll arrive on Ulleungdo
at about 7:00 a.m. tomorrow.
I understand, sir.
You have to get here by monorail.
Is that so?
So we…
What was it?
-So we…
-Yes?
I'll text you the address.
So you can take a taxi to that location.
-Right.
-From there…
Then, you'll…
-The monorail.
-You'll see the monorail.
You can take that and ride that down here.
ON HIS WAY TO WORK IN HIS PAJAMAS
SPACING OUT IN THE MORNING
STAGGERS AS HE GOES TO WASH UP
KIAN'S B&B
ONE BY ONE, THEY GET UP
Gosh, look at the ocean outside.
It feels different
when you see it in the morning.
We're deeper in the forest than I thought.
THE OWNER ARRIVES AT WORK
Good morning.
-Did you sleep well?
-Yes.
A bird…
A bird pooped on Jin's seat.
SLEEPY
I wonder if he's almost here.
AMAZED
Hello.
-Hello.
Why did you oversleep yesterday
and miss the train?
A bird pooped on the middle seat.
-So sit in the front.
-Okay.
I can tell you're friends
with the guys who came yesterday.
What's your name?
My name is Kim Ki-hong.
Jim Ji-hyeon?
What? No. It's Kim Ki-hong.
Kim Ji-hyeon?
No.
-Your name's Kim Ji-hyeon?
-No.
Kim.
-Okay.
-Kim Ki…
Ki-hyeon?
Yes, that's right.
I see. Ki-hyeon.
Yes.
GIVES UP ON TALKING TO KIAN
Is someone coming?
I think it's our friend.
-Your friend?
-Yeah.
Hi.
-Do you also study at KAIST?
-Yes?
That's right.
There's no breakfast today.
Really?
So, we had dinner last night
in place of breakfast today.
-We'll resume serving it tomorrow.
-They'll have it tomorrow.
Everyone, even nice hotels…
don't offer three square meals.
-They only serve breakfast.
-I see.
-So…
-But I haven't had breakfast.
That's why you should've come yesterday.
-You're right.
-But we have instant noodles.
-Help yourself if you'd like.
-Okay.
So…
Let me know if you have any problems.
-Okay.
-All right.
I need another hour of sleep.
I'm Kim Ki-hong.
Ki-hong? Nice to meet you.
It looks like Jin's up.
-Did you get some sleep?
-Yes.
-Good morning.
-Yeah.
You were snoring last night.
It woke me right up.
Goodness…
THE EMPLOYEE WORKED HARDER THAN THE OWNER
Why is he the one snoring?
We didn't do the dishes, did we?
I'll go and wash the dishes.
-Now?
-Yeah.
Let's go together then.
No, I'll do it alone.
It's not big enough for two anyway.
-What's not big enough?
-The area for washing dishes.
Boss, I'm heading out first.
-Thank you for the food.
-Sure.
DIY RAMYEON BREAKFAST
-It's slowly getting hot.
-Right.
The weather is perfect for snorkeling.
Good morning.
-Good morning.
Guess who he is.
Why do you keep putting me on the spot?
I guess all you did was study in school.
BY THE WAY, WHO ARE YOU?
-Would you like some?
-He woke up puffy today.
-He woke up very puffy.
-Who are you?
THEY BOTH DON'T KNOW EACH OTHER
HE DIDN'T TELL ANYONE ABOUT THE NEW GUEST
CHECKS THE DISHES TO WASH
STARTS WASHING THE DISHES
You were washing dishes?
Gosh, you're working so hard.
It's no problem. You can leave it here.
Thank you so much.
-No problem.
-You're working so early.
You can put it in here.
MORE DISHES TO WASH
Thank you.
ALL DISHES RECEIVED
THE FAUCET IS A BIT TOO HIGH
GETS UP
AND SITS DOWN AGAIN TO WASH THE DISHES
My arms are aching.
What was Kian thinking when he built this?
Hey, Ye-eun.
We got one more guest.
-He's a friend of the KAIST guys.
-Right, he was late yesterday.
The new guy didn't have breakfast.
-Should I make some soy milk?
-That's a good idea.
SOMETHING SHE BROUGHT FOR THE GUESTS
I'll go make some.
OFF TO MAKE HOMEMADE SOY MILK
TIME FOR KIAN TO WASH UP
KIAN'S WAY OF WASHING UP
KIAN'S WAY OF BRUSHING HIS TONGUE
CLEANLY FLOSSES AS WELL
WASHES HIS FACE AND RINSES HIS MOUTH
AT THE SAME TIME
SHAVES WITH LEFTOVER WATER ON HIS FACE
RINSING THE FACE AFTER SHAVING IS A WASTE
DONE
Sunscreen.
SMOTHERED IN SUNSCREEN
-Hello.
YE-EUN ARRIVES AT WORK
-Are you the new guest?
-Yes, I should've come yesterday.
I heard you were hungry.
I brought a soy milk maker.
HOMEMADE SOY MILK FOR THE LATE GUEST
BLACK BEANS
It's really good for your health.
TIMER
KIAN RETURNS TO WORK
We need sponges.
LET'S CLEAN
COLLECTS THE "ITALIAN" GREEN ONIONS
Cups.
-I think it's done.
-It's done!
It's very thick.
-You first, Ki-hong.
-Give it a try.
It looks delicious.
-It's nice.
-Yeah.
It's good. It's very rich.
YE-EUN'S HOMEMADE SOY MILK
WRITING ON SLIPPERS?
-Hey, Boss.
-Yeah?
Toss me those slippers.
"S1?"
Those are yours.
Why did you write "S"?
-Staff 1.
-I see.
THE OWNER'S SLIPPERS, S1
Hold on.
His slippers are dirty.
We can wash them again.
You have athlete's foot, don't you?
Me?
Hey, we can get athlete's foot together
and grow close that way.
Do you really have athlete's foot?
Athlete's foot? No.
Be honest.
It comes and goes.
-You don't have it?
-He's so honest.
Of course not!
You usually get it while in the army.
Sir!
Aren't you supposed to get it
by working hard for the ARMY?
That's some insane logic.
Our fans won't like it
if we have athlete's foot.
They're not true fans if they hate that.
-Ridiculous! Who likes athlete's foot?
-It's beautiful.
Ye-eun, do you like athlete's foot?
I love it so much! I wish I had it.
-The appeal of athlete's foot…
-Wear those then.
I should secretly pass my virus onto her.
On the day we leave,
she starts scratching her feet like crazy.
We have to get there today.
The weather was nice.
So all I could think about
was the main B&B here.
THE MAIN KIAN'S B&B ON THE SEA
THEY DECIDE TO MOVE TO THE MAIN B&B
Everyone,
we might move,
so you should pack your stuff.
You should have most things packed.
-Okay.
-All right.
-We might move because the weather's nice.
-Okay.
We'll get going now.
They're going out.
-See you later.
-Have fun.
-See you tonight.
Take care.
Where are you going to hike?
We're going snorkeling today.
We'll go rent scooters.
Scooters?
Let's drop off the guests.
Then, let's visit the barge.
DROP OFF GUESTS
AND MOVE TO THE BARGE
Goodness.
My gosh.
THE STAFF ARE ON THEIR WAY
It's so picturesque here.
It's beautiful.
Brace yourselves for the bump!
Please send it right down.
Our guests are waiting for it.
WHILE THE STAFF PREPARES THE VEHICLES
TEAM KAIST IS ON THEIR WAY
I thought you were patting my head.
-You're going to rent scooters?
-Yes.
Where is the place?
-It's near Ulleung County Office.
-It's here.
KIAN'S B&B
TOWN CENTER
I'll take a person on my motorbike.
Rock, paper, scissors.
MODES OF TRANSPORTATION
FOR KIAN'S B&B
CAR
TO BE REVEALED
MOTORCYCLE
WITH A SIDECAR
KIAN AND SEONG-EUN ON THE MOTORCYCLE
JIN, YE-EUN, SUNG-HO,
AND KI-HONG IN THE CAR
JIN'S RIDE, KIAN'S RIDE
-This is fun.
-It is.
HAHAHA
EXCITED
The sidecar is so cute.
Let's ride in that next time.
-Sure.
-It looks so fun.
-All right, take care.
-See you later.
-Bye.
-Bye. See you later.
THE STAFF HEAD TO THE MAIN B&B
Maybe riding in the car would be better.
Are you scared?
-It should be fine, right?
-Tell me…
-Tell me if you feel scared to death.
-Okay.
Wow, this is fun.
This road is so nice.
Look how clear the sky is.
It's so nice!
It's beautiful.
Look at the color! it's so pretty!
This is absolutely beautiful.
What do you call that?
The reflection on the sea?
-Heat haze?
-Sun glitter.
Right, sun glitter.
Isn't it pretty?
Yeah, it is.
SUN GLITTER, NOT HEAT HAZE
This has been the best part
since coming to Ulleungdo.
I'm so happy.
SAME TIME, DIFFERENT FEEL
Is this the right road?
Being alone is so boring.
I'm so lonely.
Gosh, it's so pretty.
That's not it, right?
What?
THAT?
CAN'T SEE ANYTHING
That's the B&B, right?
THIS
That's the B&B.
Unbelievable.
Yeah, you're right.
B&B SPOTTED ON THE SEA
That's incredible.
It's really floating on the sea? My gosh.
FEELING PROUD
KIAN'S DREAMS COME TRUE
Finally, it's your time to shine.
My gosh! I'm going to lose my mind.
-It's a bit worrying.
-Wait, hold on.
You're driving…
It's my first time on the ocean.
But you won't die.
A BOAT ALL OF A SUDDEN?
Are you sure about this? Can you drive it?
I'll have to try and see.
SPECIAL MISSION FROM THE PRODUCTION TEAM
GET A BOATING LICENSE
JUMPING INTO PRACTICE
WITHOUT EVEN KNOWING WHY
This is so embarrassing,
but I got it on my fourth attempt.
I did study really hard.
CAPTAIN JI'S MISSION FROM NOW ON
PICK UP THE GUESTS
FROM THE PORT
AND GO 800M
TO KIAN'S B&B
IN PARTICULAR, THE TURN
THROUGH THE BREAKWATER
IS THE TOUGHEST PART
STARTING POINT
DESTINATION
TODAY IS HER FIRST TRY
AT DRIVING ON THE SEA
WILL CAPTAIN JI BE ABLE TO DO WELL?
-Are you nervous?
-Of course, I am!
-Why are you nervous?
-I don't know.
I'm so nervous.
Show us what you've got.
This is crazy.
We'll depart now.
Wow, Ye-eun!
This is crazy!
-Ye-eun, you're doing great!
-Nice.
This is great.
Go, Ye-eun!
-You're doing great!
-Go faster, Ye-eun!
To the left.
-This is insane, Ye-eun.
-I know.
-Wait.
-Hey, Ye-eun!
-That's the breakwater!
-We'll crash!
Hey, Ye-eun!
-That's the breakwater!
-We'll crash!
-Hey!
-Wait. Hey!
-Are you trying to kill us?
-Hey!
The breakwater!
Keep quiet!
-Shut your mouth!
-Okay, I'll be quiet.
Geez!
-I mean…
-You have to trust me.
-I can do this.
-All right.
THEY GET PAST THE DANGER
BEYOND THE BREAKWATER
AROUND THE BREAKWATER
INNER PORT, OUTER PORT
THE INNER PORT HAS CALMER WAVES
THE OUTER PORT HAS STRONGER WAVES
Where is it?
I can see it over there!
My fellow warriors,
I see our destination ahead!
You're doing well.
Let's go!
Let's go! Destroy them all!
The boat is flying!
This is…
We're going to fly off
into the clouds at this rate!
COLLAPSES
STUMBLES
UTTER CHAOS
Get up!
We're going to fly off into the sky!
My goodness!
-You call yourself a captain?
-What the…
Ye-eun, what are you doing?
Look, I haven't…
What are you doing?
I haven't driven
on such strong waves before.
What are you doing?
-I can't believe we made it.
-We're finally here.
We're really here.
This is amazing!
AFLOAT IN THE WATERS OF ULLEUNGDO
IS THE MAIN B&B
KIAN'S B&B
WHERE KIAN'S IMAGINATION HAS COME TO LIFE
WITH THE ELEPHANT ROCK IN THE BACKGROUND
-Just a moment.
-It looks scary up there.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
THEY FINALLY STEP ABOARD THE BARGE
We're finally here.
This is so moving.
OVERFLOWING WITH DOPAMINE
This is amazing!
It's better than I thought.
REALLY?
OVERFLOWING WITH DOPAMINE AGAIN
They built this so well.
How about we go inside?
That'll be the problem.
HA HA…
How do we sleep here?
I mean, the beds are…
-They're small.
-They're not long enough.
It's going to really hurt if you fall.
Still, we won't die though.
I made an outdoor sleeping area.
Rock climbers sleep on cliffs like this.
-Right.
-So we'll sleep here.
THREE-STORY BEDS
We'll put two slides here,
so we can go in and out.
ACCESS THE FIRST FLOOR
WITH THE PINK SLIDE
You get on the slide to get down…
-Right to the sea.
-My goodness.
You slip right into the sea.
THE YELLOW SLIDE LEADS YOU
STRAIGHT INTO THE SEA
IT'S YOUR CHOICE
How can we sleep up there?
Seriously, we're going to wake up
when the sun rises.
You're supposed to wake up
TAKEN ABACK
Go to sleep when the sun sets.
Are those the buckets?
Yes, that's where you'll shower.
You can splash water on yourself
or take a shower.
We're at the end of summer.
SPEECHLESS
-I'm just speechless.
-Seriously, me too.
I mean, this…
How do we go up?
THE CLIMBING ZONE
The climbing area entrance
is on the second floor.
You have to put it at the far end.
That way, we have to climb
as high as possible to go in.
I've never done this before.
FIRST TRY AT CLIMBING
I'm sure you can climb it.
You're light, so I think you can do it.
He's going to make it!
I mean…
TREMBLING
HAVING SO MUCH FUN
I mean…
-Hold on.
-How is it?
It's scary, isn't it?
Hold on a second.
That part's hard, right?
-No!
-It gets hard from there.
No!
Hey!
-Come on, Boss.
-The thing is…
I didn't want people to get in easily.
We can't enter the B&B!
The owner's lost his mind.
-We can't get in at all.
-I mean…
What do you mean "get in easily"?
I didn't want…
I didn't want to see people
enter the B&B so easily.
I wanted to make it hard for them.
Wait. Let me try again.
I'll try again.
I can use different colored holds, right?
I don't think I can get up otherwise.
We'll have to use
a variety of holds to go up.
Hold on.
MEANWHILE, YE-EUN…
Can you go up the slides?
You'll have to keep this in mind.
Things that aren't entrances…
The slides.
-If people try to go up the slides…
-Okay.
-you have to stop them.
-That's a rule.
-Okay.
SHE'S GOOD AT ANSWERING,
NOT LISTENING
GIGGLING
I got up.
I'm here!
How did you get up?
Hey, you can't use the slides.
-I'm here.
-Yeah, you can't use the slides.
That's…
-That's cheating.
-That's…
disrespecting those…
those who climbed up…
This is amazing!
Hold on.
-Boss!
-Yeah?
Are you crazy?
I'm going to lose it.
Just because you can't climb this?
LET ME SHOW YOU
A DEEP SIGH
THE TOUGH PART WHERE JIN KEPT FALLING
I got it.
I got it!
HE DID IT?
Did you make it, Kian?
He's here.
So this is it.
ENTERS ON ALL FOURS
-How funny.
-This is it.
I'm going to lose my mind. This is…
Hey, come up. It's so nice here.
Can you help me from up there?
TRUSTS KIAN WILL HELP
AND CLIMBS UP AGAIN
-Now.
-Do I grab your hand now?
Grab my hand.
Even if things are difficult,
I want people to bond.
Struggles leave a lasting impression.
If it's easy, it isn't memorable.
Slowly.
You got it.
I got it.
-My goodness!
-Did he make it?
Geez!
Come on!
ENTERED SUCCESSFULLY BY BONDING
This is impossible to climb!
He's right. Seriously.
THANK YOU FOR CLIMBING UP
LET US INTRODUCE THE SECOND FLOOR
ENTRANCE TO THE BEDS
WHEN YOU OPEN THE DOOR
YOU'LL FIND BEDS
WITH AN AMAZING VIEW
-Where do we put the guests' luggage?
-Their luggage…
We need a room for clothes.
There is an area for luggage.
-Where?
-If you look here…
Geez, it's hot!
It's so hot!
It's too hot to sleep there.
-It's literally impossible.
-Look.
-Like this.
-Where?
It's actually pretty high up here.
This is a cabinet.
-Okay.
-Right here.
There's an outlet too.
You can charge your phone.
This is ridiculous.
Let's say you want to take a nap here.
-Just like this.
-Who'd sleep there? It's too hot!
-I mean…
-Who would…
This is so scary.
No one's going to sleep here!
-It's too scary to sleep there.
-Let's say you roll off while sleeping.
-There are more mats down there.
-But if you fall from here…
People are going to be
too afraid to sleep here.
It's really scary up here.
-Up there? That is pretty high.
-Yeah.
This is where we can tell who's selfless.
Because those who'll sleep
on the top bunks
will get wet if it rains.
We can witness
beautiful acts of sacrifice.
KIAN'S PHILOSOPHY
THE SELFLESS SHALL SLEEP ON THE TOP BUNKS
I'll use that bed over there.
-Where?
-There.
-There?
-Yeah, that one.
Then, I'll use a top bunk.
I should set the example.
THE SIGHT OF A RESPONSIBLE MAN
FROM THE BACK
PEEKS OVER
Damn. It's so high up here.
Let me check how high it looks from below.
How do I get down from here?
-Kian.
-Hey, Jin-seok.
-It's Seok-jin.
-It's too hot.
My real name's Seok-jin.
-Okay, Jin.
-How do I get down?
I'm even confusing your name.
-With this?
-Go down that way.
THIS WAY
And…
If you don't fall asleep quickly,
you have to wake that person up.
"Excuse me."
"I have to get down."
NUISANCE TO THE BOTTOM BUNK
Come on!
Hold on.
How do we get down?
Let me see.
I can't see how I can get down from here!
Is there a ladder here too?
-It's too scary.
-I mean… Hold on.
Seriously, it's too scary!
OVERFLOWING WITH DOPAMINE A THIRD TIME
How do I get down? Hold on.
Kian84, you…
-Geez, Kian84.
-Wait.
He's going to die from laughing…
Wait. Geez.
My hands can't reach the rung, you fool!
What do you mean?
What is it? Be careful.
-Be careful when you go down.
-The ladder…
-My hands can't reach!
-Right, so be careful.
Wait. I'm getting a cramp.
You can get down if you go carefully.
Hold on. I'm going to get down.
SHAKING
-How are we supposed to get down?
-What?
-Hold on.
-How do we get down?
Like this? Geez.
Hey, Ye-eun.
How do we…
I don't think we can sleep here.
REALISTIC WAY OF THINKING
That spot has no window…
We don't need windows.
We're outside anyway.
KIAN'S WAY OF THINKING
Where do I unpack my stuff?
On the first floor?
Your stuff…
I said you have to put it
in these cabinets after unpacking.
No, it's too hot here!
I can't put my stuff in them.
My facial cleanser will melt.
It's not just your stuff that'll melt.
You'll melt too, so it's fine.
KIAN'S PHILOSOPHY
THERE SHALL BE NO PROBLEM
IF YOU AND YOUR BELONGINGS ARE BOTH HOT
-Geez.
-Damn it.
Seriously. This is unbelievable.
What on earth?
There's water dripping here.
Water?
Since it's hot, wash your face.
DUMBFOUNDED
I like this spot though. I'll take it.
I'll sleep like this.
We're able to talk pretty well here.
We can talk with the guests.
They built this well.
THE ARCHITECT IS VERY HAPPY
BLOCKS OUT
-Hey, Boss.
-Yes?
Any thoughts on changing the entrance?
No, we can't do that.
-Please maintain our rule.
-Then…
Let's block the entrance
in front of the slide.
Then, we really won't be able to go up.
We'll need to set penalties
for using the slides.
You'll be penalized if you use them.
I really can't climb up.
THE SLIDE USER IS DISAPPOINTED
What am I going to do?
This is the area for having tea?
Where?
Okay, let's take a look.
Let's see. What?
-What is this?
-This is…
TEATIME ZONE
THEY MUST STICK THEIR FACES OUT
AND LOOK AT EACH OTHER
-What is this?
-This is…
How do you drink tea?
-Like this?
-That's right.
If you sit like this…
Usually,
we share coffee
while looking at our phones.
-This is uncomfortable.
-How can you drink like this?
But if we sit like this,
we can see each other's faces.
You can focus on looking
at each other more.
KIAN'S PHILOSOPHY
BEAR SOME DISCOMFORT TO SEE EACH OTHER
What if we spill our tea
because of these shaky tables?
-What?
-What if we spill our coffee?
The coffee?
If you spill your coffee,
we can chat while cleaning it up together.
Okay, let's check out the dining room.
-The dining room.
-That's a bit of an issue.
The dining room is… Okay.
Open it up.
Hold on, this is kind of scary.
This is too scary!
Even I can't get up on this.
It's too high! What do we do?
This is how we'll get down.
You ride the pole down.
RIDE THE POLE FROM THE SECOND FLOOR
DOWN TO THE FIRST FLOOR TO FIND
THE DINING ROOM
RECOGNIZED AS THE TOUGHEST OBSTACLE
IN THIS HOUSE
THE POLE
Hold on, I'm scared too.
But if you become hungry,
you'll have to withstand
either your hunger or fear.
There will be a time
when you'll have to make a choice.
Wait, this is too scary.
Can we even go up?
-Move.
-Come back up.
-What?
Yeah, climb back up.
This is hard for even a guy to do!
STRUGGLING WITH ALL HIS MIGHT
Are you kidding me?
Can you even climb up?
I can't go down on this.
It works if you use your knees.
It's like you're pole dancing.
Want me to grab your hand?
-Want me to grab your hand?
-No. Wait.
-Even that won't work.
-I'm so tired.
See? He can't come up!
Try coming down. I'll catch you.
No, you come up first.
What? I don't think I can.
You come down first.
-I can't go down.
-If we go down…
We can't come back up!
If we carry each other on our shoulders,
one of us can get back up.
-Seriously, I'd just fall.
-You can't look down.
Then, the two of us
will catch you down here.
-You can't look down.
-You can't catch me.
Well, that's…
You're doing well, Jin!
Goodness.
Hey, how do we get back up now?
2.2 METERS LONG
I can't do this!
Ye-eun, you have to get used to it.
We can only eat in here.
I have my socks on.
OKAY, LET'S DO IT
NO, I CAN'T DO IT
-Am I going to make it?
-Want us to catch you?
Just grab the pole tight.
You'll come down naturally.
Hold on tight.
-Here I come!
-Okay.
I'm going for real.
NO, I CAN'T GO
Don't slip and fall. Come on.
Help me!
Okay, it's time to eat.
Just come down first.
Seriously, I can't do this!
I can't do it!
How am I supposed to do this?
Are you insane?
How can you design it like this?
Seriously!
-Wait.
-I mean…
I didn't like having people
go to the dining room so easily…
-This is too much!
-I didn't want them get there so easily.
Seriously, you've gone too far!
-I didn't like having them go so easily.
-This is so…
No matter how much you dislike it, still…
How could he even think of that?
It's like he's from a different world.
What on earth was he thinking?
But that pole…
I really wanted to go down.
I wasn't pretending to be weak.
I really was scared.
Hey, just come down first.
I said I can't!
Hold onto the pole tight.
I'll carry you on my shoulders.
I'm too heavy.
IDEA 1
CARRY ON SHOULDERS
I have a great idea.
-I'll carry you on my shoulders.
-Okay.
And then, she can sit on yours.
I'm about 80kg. Is that okay?
Yes, I'll be fine if I hold the pole.
We'll be too heavy.
-Let's try.
-It'll be really heavy.
I'm quite heavy.
I weigh 80kg.
Let's go to this side.
ASSEMBLE
-Stand up. Okay. A bit to this side.
-Okay. To this side?
I'll be too heavy.
-Get on.
-Just hurry!
-Hurry and get on!
-I did.
-Get on him!
-I did!
-Get on!
-Now, go slow.
Wait. Go back up!
-Why?
-Keep going up! Hold on. Just go up.
-Okay, she's on!
-Go down?
-Go down!
-You should move! Step away.
-Should I move?
You said to get out!
Move out of the way.
IT'S TOO SCARY
IT'S TOO HEAVY
Move out of the way.
-Hold on!
-We got it.
We got it. My goodness.
-Move out of the way.
-Hold on!
We got it.
We got it. My goodness.
Geez, we barely got her down.
Hey, Kian!
How do you expect me to move
if you squeeze like this?
Move out of the way.
SQUEEZING TIGHT
Should I move?
You said to get out!
We almost all died.
Still, you made it down.
I made it down!
Yeah, you did.
IN ANY CASE,
THEY DID IT
I wonder how the guests will react.
Our show's become
another version of Physical: 100.
AFTEREFFECTS OF PARTICIPATING
IN PHYSICAL: 84
THE GUESTS WHO AREN'T EXPECTING
PHYSICAL: 84
JUN-HEE, SEONG-EUN, SUNG-HO,
KI-HONG, GA-HYUN
-We're going to an island called Jukdo.
-Okay.
It's about 30 minutes to Jukdo from here.
There's a lot of fish near Jukdo.
-And the waters are so clear.
-I love it.
A SMALL ISLAND NEAR ULLEUNGDO
WITH COOL, CLEAR WATERS
Enjoy! Have fun!
ARRIVES AT JUKDO
We're going to dive here,
so you can get ready.
Have fun!
GETTING READY TO GO INTO DEEPER WATERS
MEANWHILE, THE KAIST GUYS
HAKPO PORT, A POPULAR SPOT FOR SNORKELING
JEODONG PORT
GA-HYUN IS FISHING ON ULLEUNGDO
Come on and bite.
I'm going to catch one no matter what.
SHE CATCHES A ROCK BREAM
Nice! I'm going to show it off to my dad.
I've thought about it,
and I'm sure
everyone will be here in the evening.
So instead of breakfast,
let's serve them dinner every night.
-That would be better.
-Right?
-Instead of breakfast.
-What about breakfast?
We'll tell them
to take care of that on their own.
What do we do now?
Let's go out and bring in our stuff.
Let's try lifting each other to go out.
But I can't keep being the only one
who sits on your shoulders.
We'll boost you up by your feet.
We'll hold your feet like this.
-And you'll grab the pole.
-Okay.
Then, we'll lift you up.
That will never work.
It will. You just have to stand
and hold onto the pole.
But I'm afraid she'll let go.
If she does, then…
I'm sure she'll hold on.
She's not a fool.
The thought crossed my mind
that she could be.
Honestly, I am a fool.
Should I just try to go out that way?
I don't think I can though.
OF COURSE NOT
A TINY WINDOW THAT'S 30CM TALL
REALIZES THE REALITY
Geez, Kian84!
You can go out that way.
And then, you can help us out.
YOUR PAIN IS MY JOY
I don't think I can go up.
You have to put your feet together.
-Like this.
-It won't work because of her socks.
-Take off your socks.
-Take them off?
-Throw them up there.
-I don't think this will help.
-It don't think it'll help.
-Just toss them up there.
-You don't have muscle strength.
-I don't.
Put your feet together.
-One, two.
-I can't put them together.
-Step on me.
-I'm really going to do it.
-Go ahead.
-Don't let go of the pole!
-Grab it.
-Stand up.
-Don't let go.
-I won't.
-Stand up. There you go.
I can't let go. I can't go up.
-You can't?
-I can't.
You can't? Sit back down.
-Sit down. Wait.
-Wait, don't let go.
Not you. Hold on.
SUCCESSFULLY PUTS HER FEET TOGETHER
It's okay. Let go. It's not that high.
-There you go. Coming down's easy, right?
-Ye-eun.
You stay here. We'll go out and come back.
All right.
No, she has to drive the boat.
-She has to go.
-You're right.
You have to drive the boat!
KIAN'S B&B ON THE SEA
ISOLATED WITHOUT A BOAT
SPECIAL MISSION
LIFT UP CAPTAIN JI
I don't have any strength in my hands.
-Don't give up. Focus.
-Yeah, you can do it.
Ye-eun, focus.
Ye-eun, you can do it.
-Repeat after me. "I can."
-"I can."
"I can do it."
-"I can do it."
-Focus.
-Use your strength to grab it.
-That's it.
-On rhythm, okay?
-Yes.
-Believe.
-That's right.
-Don't give up.
-I'm going insane.
-Okay. I can do this.
-One foot at a time.
Lift one foot at a time.
-There you go.
-My goodness!
-There you go. Don't bend your legs!
-That's it.
Don't bend your legs.
Hey! Don't bend your legs.
Keep them straight!
-Keep them straight. Not like that!
-Your legs.
-Grab it and go up.
-Hey, go up!
-Go up. Okay.
-Go up. There you go!
-Good job!
-Yes!
-Go up!
-Now, your feet…
-Get up there!
-Pull your legs back.
-You can do it.
-Ye-eun, focus.
FOCUS
Grab it.
GRAB IT WITH ALL YOUR STRENGTH
Believe.
BELIEVE IN US
-Go up!
-Now, your feet…
-Get up there!
-Pull your legs back.
Don't give up.
Put your legs on that!
-Get up there!
-Pull your legs back.
-Put your legs on that!
-Hey!
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B
Subtitle translation by: Da Young Lee