We have to hurry and go get the luggage.
The guests will be coming back soon.
We'll lift you up slowly,
so you just do this.
I don't have any strength on my hands.
-Don't give up. Focus.
-Yeah, you can do it.
Ye-eun, focus.
Ye-eun, you can do it.
-Repeat after me. "I can."
-"I can."
"I can do it."
-"I can do it."
-Focus.
Focus.
Use your strength to grab it.
-That's it. Yes.
-On rhythm, okay?
-Believe.
-That's right.
-Don't give up.
-I'm going insane.
-Okay.
I can do this.
One foot at a time.
Lift one foot at a time.
-There you go.
-My goodness!
-There you go. Don't bend your legs!
-That's it.
Don't bend your legs.
Hey! Don't bend your legs.
Keep them straight!
STRETCHES OUT
Not like that!
-Grab it and go up.
-Hey, go up!
-Go up. Okay.
-Go up. There you go!
-Good job!
-Yes!
-Go up!
-Now, your feet…
-Get up there!
-Pull your legs back.
-Put your legs on that!
-Up. Hey!
-Let go.
-There.
-She got it.
-You are strong.
Yeah, you're doing well.
She got it.
See? You can do it.
Incredible.
Can you get up there already?
Wait, hold on.
I can't go up. Hold on.
-Use your legs.
-Push the pole with your legs.
-Yeah.
-Push it with your legs.
-That's it.
-Use your legs.
-There you go.
-There we go. Jesus Christ.
Jesus Christ.
Seriously!
Do we have to do it like this?
THE OWNER'S TURN NOW
Good job.
WHILE THEY STRUGGLE WITH THE POLE
A NEW GUEST ARRIVES ON ULLEUNGDO ISLAND
Look at the color of the ocean.
That's insane.
Hello?
-Hello?
-Yes?
I'm Lee Ah-jin. I'm checking in today.
Right, hello.
How many are with you?
-It's just me.
-Just you?
You need to come to Hyeonpo Port.
Could you check your GPS
and tell me how long it will take?
Okay.
ANOTHER GROUP OF NEW GUESTS
RENTAL CAR AREA
It must be that car.
HANDS FULL OF LUGGAGE
Will mine fit in there?
Can we put it in like this?
-Hello?
Hello.
We're supposed to be checking in today.
How many of you are coming?
Three people.
Three?
NINE PEOPLE?
WE'RE IN TROUBLE
Okay. Are you coming now to check in?
No, we might explore a bit first.
Then, we'll text you the address.
Okay. We'll see you soon.
Okay, thank you.
Bye.
More guests are arriving in two hours!
In two hours?
In two hours!
Jin says guests are coming in two hours!
Come down!
Then, how many are there in total today?
We originally had five.
-It's nine.
-Then, four more.
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven.
We're one bed short.
-We're short?
-Yeah.
I think Ye-eun might be better off
sleeping in a tent.
-On the ground?
-Yeah.
So we're…
-We're one bed short.
-Okay.
Want to sleep in a tent?
-We'll set one up down here.
-Okay.
It'd be in the corner there.
I would love that.
Thank you. I'll work hard.
WHAT LUCK
Let's go!
We need to go fetch everyone's luggage.
EARLIER THIS MORNING
WAVES ARE CALMER TODAY THAN YESTERDAY
We might move because the weather's nice.
NOTIFIED GUESTS OF MOVE
We might move,
so you should pack your stuff.
MOVE THE LUGGAGE FROM THE ANNEX
Let's go.
Go slowly this time, Ye-eun.
Yes, I know.
Here we go.
THEY RIDE THE BOAT DRIVEN BY CAPTAIN JI
BACK TO THE PORT
THEY UNLOAD THE GUESTS' LUGGAGE
LOAD IT ONTO THE BOAT
AND GET IN THE BOAT AGAIN
Ye-eun, the water's so salty!
It can't be helped!
-Thank you.
THEY ARRIVE AT THE MAIN B&B
Moving all of this inside
is going to be the issue.
-So…
-Yeah?
Pass me all the groceries
through that window.
-The groceries?
-We'll do that.
-Take out just the food and send them in.
-Okay.
JIN WILL ORGANIZE THE KITCHEN
Be careful.
Is this right?
HE WHO LAUGHS LASTS
1. CLIMB THE WALL
2. SLIDE DOWN THE POLE
HUP, HUP, HUP
Man, it's cool in here.
A SHORT BREAK
The groceries.
ALCOHOL FIRST
-Please line them up here.
-Okay.
The suitcases…
We have to move the suitcases.
A BUNCH OF SUITCASES
TURNS HIS HEAD
GAZES
-How do we take the luggage up?
-You have to carry it on your back.
It's a suitcase.
Strap the suitcase onto your back.
You have to climb up.
GRITS HIS TEETH
STILL TOO MANY
TURNS HIS HEAD
STILL TOO HIGH
I keep wanting to make compromises too.
It's human nature to compromise.
I like… the slides.
All right.
Let's try it.
SLIPS
Dammit, this is hard too.
Just take one.
YE-EUN TRIES TOO
Gosh, this is heavy.
THE ARCHITECT CAN'T STOP LAUGHING
ALMOST THERE
I made it.
Hey, I'm slipping.
Grab the slide.
-Go up quick.
-I'm sliding down.
I'm sliding down.
Go up.
I think we should prioritize bringing in
and organizing the stuff first.
I don't have the energy to go up now.
My arms are going to fall off.
What are you doing up there?
We're moving in the luggage.
I SHOULD HELP, BUT…
I don't have the strength to go up.
BUT I STILL NEED TO GO
ROLLS UP HIS PANTS
AND TRIES AGAIN
WOBBLES
How did you move them up?
LIKE THIS
Just a bit farther.
How many are left, Boss?
-Should I take over?
-What?
You want to try?
-To be honest, I was so worn out.
-Yeah.
So it wasn't easy to get up the pole.
Seriously.
This place is unbelievable.
Ye-eun.
He said you can't come up that way.
We can. I got permission to earlier.
-From who?
-From Kian84!
FROM KIAN84
Boss.
Yeah?
Can we use the slides to come up?
What I'm thinking is…
HOPEFUL
CURIOUS
Don't make too many
unnecessary trips up and down.
If you do that…
UPSET
Is there a bathroom down here?
-No.
SPEECHLESS
So after we take a shower,
we're supposed to climb up
and be covered in sweat?
-Once you get sweaty again…
-Right.
Then…
You'll end up deciding
to shower only once a day.
But we can't be smelly
while greeting the guests.
The guests will soon become smelly too.
The guests too…
If the guests smell too, then it's fair.
That's true. He's not wrong.
Lately, you've been saying things
that are right.
I think you're losing it too
because of me.
No, I think they're all right.
If only one person's clean
while everyone smells,
-something's wrong with them.
-Right.
THE KIAN EFFECT
Right.
-Let's make the clean feel self-conscious.
-Yeah.
-We should.
Lying down here is refreshing.
But the view…
This view from the ocean is beautiful.
And our location
keeps changing little by little.
That was the thing
I really wanted to see while doing this.
That thing on the sea…
Moon jitter?
WHAT?
-Moon glitter?
-Moon glitter.
"Moon jitter"!
Gosh, that's hilarious.
The moon glitters
on rippling waves at night.
I thought…
BACK TO BEING SENTIMENTAL
That would be amazing to see.
SWAYED BY THE WAVES
A GRADUALLY CHANGING VIEW CAN BE SEEN
A PLACE FULL OF DREAMS
COLORED BY KIAN
MEANWHILE
-We got a text.
-What does it say?
"Hello, this is Kian's B&B."
"Please come to Hyeonpo Port by 7:00 p.m."
"If you're late, your luggage is mine."
HYEONPO PORT?
-Let's go.
OFF TO HYEONPO PORT
Hyeonpo Port by 7:00 p.m.?
I have to go pick up the guests.
I'll be back.
Okay, be careful.
FINALLY, THE FIRST TIME PICKING UP GUESTS
This place looks cool at night.
Yeah, it's nice.
When are they coming?
I think they're on their way.
Hey, then the…
That's insane. It really does look great.
This place is incredible at night.
It looks like a theme park ride.
Yeah, it's like a theme park.
A theme park from hell.
"A theme park from hell"!
I…
I can't feel my arms and back right now!
A THEME PARK THAT NUMBS YOU ALL OVER
Damn, it's hot.
A SUDDEN BATH
What is he doing?
WASHES THE ARMPITS
He really is an unpredictable person.
This is so refreshing.
Is this what Kian's B&B is all about?
Wow, that's refreshing.
FINISHES CLEANING HIMSELF
BEFORE THE GUESTS ARRIVE
There's Ye-eun.
TEAM KAIST ARRIVES AT 6:50 P.M.
Where are the guests?
That's Ye-eun on the boat, right?
We're taking a boat.
A BOAT?
We're taking a boat. I was right.
-Guests of Kian's B&B!
-Yes?
Come this way!
Hello.
GA-HYUN AND JUN-HEE ARRIVE
Pick up? We're not going by car?
MEANWHILE, THE NEW GUESTS
Wait, Hyeonpo Port is a port.
Hold on.
-What's that?
-What?
Up ahead?
A ship?
That's the B&B?
Isn't that just a cargo ship
that people work on?
I have a bad feeling about this.
THAT BAD FEELING
BECOMES A REALITY
Hello, are you here to stay at Kian's B&B?
Please put on flotation belts.
THREE MALE GUESTS ARRIVE
I guess you wear it around your waist.
A NEW FEMALE GUEST ARRIVES
NINE TOTAL GUESTS
FIVE EXISTING GUESTS, FOUR NEW GUESTS
Hello.
Hi, are you the new female guest?
Yes, I am.
-But I have more luggage.
-Yes, your luggage.
Could you help me with it?
Thank you.
We have to move the lumber.
What? For what?
Are you a carpenter?
I am.
NEW GUEST
LEE AH-JIN, CARPENTER
There you go.
-I stepped on your foot.
-Thank you.
-I'm sorry.
-No, it's fine.
-Do you have your flotation belts on?
-Yes.
-I'm driving.
-What?
I want to get off!
-No way.
-I want to get off!
NO WAY
Have faith in me. Everyone, hold tight.
Those in the back need to sit.
It could be dangerous.
-My eye is twitching.
-I really want to live.
I got my license.
This is how
disaster movies typically start.
YE-EUN'S BOAT SETS OFF
WOW
WHOA
I'm going to speed up.
This is so cool.
It's going fast.
Wow, what's that?
What is that shining island?
That's amazing.
-What is it?
-I can see lights.
Oh my!
That's so cool!
It was like the animated movies.
The colors and lights
were far beyond imagination.
It's flashy.
It's a bit unusual.
It felt like a bizarre theme park.
With its spires and bright yellow color,
it really catches your eye.
Shock. Horror. Fear?
Some kind of fishing boat
slowly got closer.
It turned out to be our B&B.
THE FISHING BOAT IS OUR B&B?
Look, there's a climbing wall on the side!
So that's how we have to go up.
You're right.
-That's crazy.
-Wait. I mean…
Wait, why does that lead into the sea?
Hey, the slide really leads into the sea!
They made this?
GUESTS FLUSTERED BY THE BIZARRE B&B
I'm so amazed.
-He's excited.
-He is.
It has a climbing wall there.
THE BIZARRE OWNER IS HERE TOO
It's in the middle of the sea.
We'll need motion-sickness meds.
We'll probably need those.
Grab my wrist.
-Hello.
Hello.
-Did you have a good time?
-Yes.
What gave you the idea to put a B&B here?
Here?
I didn't expect this
to actually happen either.
Hello!
Hello.
ALL GUESTS CHECK IN AT THE MAIN B&B
I'm Kian, the owner of the B&B.
Your beds…
have been set up outside.
OUTSIDE?
So that's the sleeping area.
I didn't think they were actual beds.
I thought they were decorations.
The entrance is on the second floor.
You can't go in through the first floor.
You need to enter
through the second floor.
And when you come down…
The slides.
-Don't get confused!
-Okay.
You have to take the pink one.
So that's why there's two!
The yellow one will take you into the sea.
Anyone who's scared
can put this on to go up.
TIME TO ENTER KIAN'S B&B
Also, if you think
the beginner's course is too easy,
it gets harder the further right you go.
I'll show you how to go up.
Yes, please show us.
JIN THE DEMONSTRATOR
Show us how.
Oh no, my nails…
-Today was my first time doing this too.
-Show us.
You go up like that.
He's good at it now.
-You're so good, Jin.
-He's improved.
-Look at him go.
-Yes, he's gotten better.
That's how you go up.
But if you come down,
you always have to climb up like this.
Put down a ladder for us.
Please make us some stairs.
This is ridiculous.
Everyone, I was thinking…
Since we all enter our homes so easily,
I wanted to see what it'd be like
to make it harder to enter.
I SEE
I've never done climbing before.
Anyone think they can do it?
-Should I go first?
-Sure, go ahead.
I think he might be good at this.
Is it okay to use a different route?
So cool!
Wow, a different route.
The way he chalked his hands
was different.
Wow, he's good!
He must be a pro.
He's just comfortably
hanging from the wall.
Wow, he's good!
He's so good at it.
I feel embarrassed.
I'll go up the blue route.
-Wait, who are these guys?
-How are they so good?
-Look at him go.
-Who are these guys?
-How are they so good?
Oh, my gosh!
-Oh, my gosh.
-Hold on. Wow.
He's flying up.
Seriously, who are you guys?
INTIMIDATED
My goodness!
He's so good.
He has the forearms of an athlete.
What on earth?
These people have abnormal muscles.
KANG MIN-JUN
KIM TAE-IN
SHIM MIN-SEOB
-Let's go, KAIST.
-Give it a try, Team KAIST.
-Okay.
-Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
-Yes!
-Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
Give it a try.
Want to wear the harness?
-If you fall, you'll be safe.
-Okay.
We should go help them put on the harness.
-You can take the slide down.
-Got it.
Yippee.
-We're professional climbers.
-What?
-I knew it.
-Really?
-They chalked their hands like pros.
-We're also instructors.
Then, you can teach people
who can't climb how to go up?
-We can help them go up.
-Then…
For our other guests…
-Really?
-You could teach them.
WE'LL SEND YOU UP
Fasten this higher.
I can't believe I'm learning this here.
That's it. One.
Lift your right foot up.
I thought if I can't climb this wall,
I won't be able to do anything here.
AT KIAN'S B&B, CLIMBING IS SURVIVING
SUNG-HO
If I can't climb up,
I can't enter the B&B.
We have no choice but to do it.
Watch your feet.
This isn't easy.
-It'll be easier if you grab this.
-Okay.
CLIMBING IS A CHALLENGE
SEONG-EUN
They're all managing to go up.
It's comforting to have them here.
The entrance is on the second floor,
and we have to climb to get there.
That was really hard.
I'll push you up a bit.
Look up. There you go.
Lift your foot up more.
-With your big toe.
-That's it.
Then, grab this yellow one.
That's it.
Okay, come inside.
TEAM KAIST MAKES IT IN
They did well.
-It's reassuring to have experts here.
-Exactly.
Try climbing up.
AH-JIN'S TRY
Where do I go from here?
-Can you reach the yellow hold?
-Yes.
Okay. Now, lift your foot up.
Yes, that's it.
-Then, this handle.
-Grab this.
Wow, this is so…
Come in this way.
NEXT UP IS JUN-HEE
It had a lot of elements
related to sports, so I liked it.
I really like things like that.
Hey, it's not that bad.
You think you can give it a try?
I think I can if I wear that harness.
And we have instructors here.
You have to step into it.
PUTS ON THE HARNESS
GA-HYUN'S TRY
The yellow ones are good.
To reach the second floor,
we had to climb a wall to get there.
It was beyond anything
I could have imagined,
so that was the hardest thing for me.
-Thank you.
-Sure, come inside.
ALL GUESTS SUCCESSFULLY CLIMB UP
-They did well.
-They did.
We need to haul those suitcases up.
IT'S TIME FOR THE LUGGAGE NOW
Then, the luggage…
-Take them up now?
-Yeah.
DELIVERING THE LUGGAGE WITH THE SLIDE
You don't need a hand with them?
No, it's fine.
Nice.
It's nice having the instructors here.
Look at them lift these in.
I guess this is another way.
The instructors!
They're so smart.
WE DID IT THE HARD WAY
I guess this is another way.
We've lost our jobs now.
Do we get paid for this?
We'll make you a nice dinner.
Well, that should be plenty.
I hope these guys don't go home.
Yeah, I hope they never go.
Our climbing guys,
how many nights are you staying?
We'll be here until Saturday morning.
-Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday.
-Yes.
-Three nights? That's quite long.
Please take a seat.
Where should I start?
The dining room is below.
But with the dining room,
rather than just walking there…
That's why the pole is…
I really like High Kick!
Lee Soon-jae used to climb
a pole on the show.
We made this with that in mind.
How about we head down and make dinner?
-Shall we open this lid?
-Okay.
This is…
-the first floor.
-It's a long way down.
The first floor.
I don't think I could climb up.
I'll go down first.
-Just like this.
-It looks fun.
THE OWNER DESCENDS FIRST
That looks painful.
Just like Lee Soon-jae.
Just as we thought.
That military experience!
That was cool.
-That was cool.
-I'm an expert.
You can come down one by one.
Anyone who thinks they can go?
We have to eat.
-We have to eat.
-I'll catch you.
-Geez.
-It's okay.
-I got it.
-You did well.
Gosh, this guy.
THIS GUY
KI-HONG DESCENDS
-They're good!
-You did well.
-The pros are…
-The pros…
The pros are on a different level.
STEADY
It was really unique.
This is scary.
It was the most Kian-esque feature.
Why are you so good at this?
Rather than a house,
it was like a playground for adults.
It felt like I was starting
a new adventure.
They were all using the features
I'd imagined for them.
That was when…
I felt really happy.
Sir, then where is the bathroom?
For the bathroom, go up the pole
and down the slide.
Okay.
And go around to the back.
Up, down, and to the back.
The bathroom is next to the gym.
I don't think I can do it.
So with this…
For people who can't go up,
we found a way.
-Could you help me?
-Sure.
Each person will grab hold of a foot.
You put your foot here.
Oh, my God.
You'll need to hold on tight to the pole.
-Just place your feet here.
-Oh my.
Grab it tight and lift your feet.
I'm sorry!
HUMAN ELEVATOR
My goodness.
I thought she came up by herself.
Could you explain
where the bathroom is again?
-The bathroom?
-Yes.
Go outside and go around to the right.
Okay, I got it.
Can we go check out the gym?
Of course.
OFF TO THE BATHROOM
OFF TO THE GYM
It has a pull-up bar and other stuff too.
This is nice.
-It's the bathroom
-That's the bathroom.
GYM, BATHROOM, SHOWER
That's the shower room.
THE OWNER COMES BACK DOWN
Come on down.
-I can't do this!
-Really? I thought you'd be good at this.
-Be careful.
-I can't do this!
It's okay if it's too scary.
You don't have to.
Will you be okay?
WORRIED
He's coming back up.
I think he's coming back up.
Oh my.
Dammit, this is exhausting.
I can't believe I designed this.
I'm going to lose my mind.
Are you okay?
What do we do with the guests
who can't go down?
Would this be too hard for them?
We're going to reinforce the bottom here.
I really want to go down.
Man, I really can't do this.
Your feet.
Gosh, I'm sorry!
Wait, hold on.
Careful.
What are we going to do with this?
This won't work. Should we close it?
Yeah, this won't do.
Do we decide to close the first floor?
THE OWNER FACES A DILEMMA
-At least for tonight…
-Yeah?
Let's eat outside.
They can't come down.
Why not?
They can't use the pole.
I don't want to force them to use it.
-So you know our carpenter guest?
-Yeah.
Let's make a ladder here.
That strays a lot
from your original intent.
-I'm sorry.
-Then, go upstairs.
And move the ingredients.
-Take this first.
-Okay.
We can cook the stew and rice here first.
Sure.
Let's cook them here and move them.
THE OWNER LEAVES
TO SET UP THE AREA OUTSIDE
JIN PREPARES DINNER IN THE KITCHEN
TODAY'S MENU
JIN'S BEEF BRISKET AND SOYBEAN PASTE STEW
There's no garlic or green onions.
THE CONSEQUENCE OF THE MOVE
The cutting board…
is also missing.
ANOTHER CONSEQUENCE OF THE MOVE
IF THERE'S NO CUTTING BOARD?
STIR-FRYING THE BEEF BRISKET
ADDS THE VEGETABLES
AND PLENTY OF SOYBEAN PASTE
JIN'S BEEF BRISKET AND SOYBEAN PASTE STEW
IS COMING ALONG NICELY
OFF TO SET UP THE AREA OUTSIDE
We can eat here.
-Goodness!
-We can eat here, Kian.
Hey… What was I going to say?
You can't make it downstairs, right?
I can't.
Even if you want to cook.
We'll need a ladder tomorrow.
You know what's gradually
becoming the problem?
What?
I don't want to go inside.
Why would he make the B&B like this?
What was he thinking?
Why on earth is he so…
We have a carpenter here.
So you know what I was thinking?
What?
"Should we make a first floor door?"
Seriously, can't you make us one?
Kian, people inherently do
what's comfortable for them.
But I saw this coming.
I thought I'd eventually want
to make a door.
-I expected to after two or three days.
-Right.
-But it happened too soon?
-It happened in only half a day.
With the guests actually here, I softened.
Yeah, I softened.
I worried people might get hurt.
I think it might be good to make a door.
Boss!
So…
How about we make…
a door on the first floor?
I mean, we have a carpenter here.
It's because we have a carpenter.
So I think it's a good idea.
And with this climbing wall,
we can also…
You know…
I think…
I think we shouldn't make a door.
It's fun going up and down.
Earlier, we lifted the carpenter
up like this.
But… Right.
Whoever comes down,
we can lift them back up.
That's true.
I don't think we need it.
Right, but I'm…
There's no compromising with him.
It's about dreams.
It's nothing without them.
I guess this is why being an owner's hard.
People have differing opinions.
PRINCIPLE VS COMPROMISE
But I think…
THE TWO PHILOSOPHIES CLASH
You shouldn't compromise.
I shouldn't?
Then, you wouldn't be the owner.
True.
-You'd just be a boatswain.
-A boatswain.
Please make us a door.
I'm so grateful to have you tell me that.
Ye-eun doesn't look very happy.
No…
I mean, this is exactly
what you had in mind.
It's no wonder he's a global star.
He clearly understands
the intent of my design.
I waver because of Ye-eun
and refocus because of Jin.
Ye-eun is a Seoul girl.
SEOUL GIRL
Jin is
my world-class anchor.
You can't compromise.
Let's set up a place to eat.
Wait, we don't have a table.
I think we should empty out
one of those basins.
How about flipping
the biggest one over to use as a table?
Flip that basin?
Flip it.
-We don't have anything else to use.
-Right.
FOLLOW THE WORLD CLASS ANCHOR
Should we move it there?
-Next to that basin?
-Is it full of water?
One, two, three.
Goodness.
-It's a little small.
-Yeah, it is.
Flip another one?
It's not bad as a table.
-It's not bad.
-One for sitting and one for standing?
Let's pour out this one.
One, two, three.
Wait, hold on.
Three. Wait.
-One, two…
-Wait.
-One…
-Let me get ready.
Let me take some deep breaths.
-We can do this.
-Of course, we can.
-One, two, three.
NOT MOVING
STRAINING
STRAINING TOO
-We need Ye-eun's help.
-Good idea.
A SWIFT SURRENDER
One of the climbers is there.
-Let's ask for a little help.
-Excuse me?
Could you lend us a hand, sir?
Sure.
You've worked out a lot before though.
-Yeah, but…
-So it's this basin.
-We'll lift it.
-Okay.
Could you hold up the bottom
-to pour the water out?
-Yes, sure.
-One, two.
-One, two, three!
Okay.
-Thank you.
Kian, we were such idiots.
Instead of asking for help,
we could've just scooped the water out.
-Like this? Nice.
-Like a standing table.
I have to climb up the wall again.
I have to climb again.
Boss, we really shouldn't compromise.
Okay.
Climbing is the only way up.
But where are you going?
I have to get all the food.
This is the most inefficient house
in the whole world.
You can't compromise.
CAN'T COMPROMISE
Everyone, please use the wall
when going up.
KIAN'S B&B RULES
CLIMB THE WALL TO ENTER THE B&B
HERE COMES THE SLIDE POLICE
Guys, you were on your way down, right?
Yes, we were coming down.
Right? They were coming down.
-Is that so?
-Climbing is too hard.
We're going down, Ki-hong.
What are you doing?
THE OWNER IS MOVING THE INGREDIENTS
ONLY THE INGREDIENTS ARE ALLOWED
TO PASS THROUGH THE WINDOW
UP THE POLE AGAIN
Oh my, that startled me!
You're actually climbing this
as it rattles away.
-Ye-eun.
-Yes?
-Let's move these.
-Okay.
Do you need this tofu?
Yeah, it goes in the stew.
I have to slice the tofu.
-Climbing pros.
-Yes?
I'm sorry, but…
Could you toss me
a spoon from the kitchen?
-The kitchen?
-Yes.
Go down the pole.
I'll go.
Don't we need a lot of spoons?
I need at least one for the stew.
But he's already inside.
-So ask for more.
-Right.
Since you're there, a lot of spoons.
-A lot?
-A lot of spoons.
-Ask for everything needed.
-Chopsticks!
Quickly tell us everything you need.
Spoons, chopsticks, and cups.
A lot of spoons and chopsticks.
Spoons and chopsticks?
We have them here.
-Where are the spoons?
-He said they're here.
Is there any MSG in there?
I'll get you some MSG.
There's a bag
with all the seasonings in it.
This.
-What?
-Oh, this?
There's soy sauce, MSG, and sugar here.
Thank you.
Excuse me. I'm sorry, but…
Could you fill these with water?
Fill them both about halfway.
-Halfway? Okay.
-Yes.
HERE ARE YOUR POTS OF WATER
Could you rinse these
for us by any chance?
Sure.
GARLIC WASHED AND READY
Here's the rice!
Please take the rice.
Thank you.
This is…
Anything else?
-Is that really it?
-Yes.
They said that's it.
Got it.
COMPLETES ALL MISSIONS
WHILE IN THE KITCHEN
9:00 P.M.
YE-EUN GRILLS THE PORK BELLY AGAIN TODAY
JIN IS ALMOST DONE WITH THE STEW
SCOOPING THE TOFU WITH A SPOON
I've never scooped tofu like this before.
Oh, this.
Don't we need ssamjang
as a dip for the meat?
-We need it for the meat.
-Right?
And less for the stew, right?
Do you normally put ssamjang
in soybean paste stew?
All barbecue restaurants use it in stews.
-Really?
-Really.
Is that so?
Then, just a spoonful?
Just a spoonful.
THE KICK IN JIN'S STEW COMES FROM
SSAMJANG
THE BEEF BRISKET AND SOYBEAN PASTE STEW
IS COMPLETE
YE-EUN'S GRILLED PORK BELLY IS READY TOO
Wow, this looks amazing.
THE OWNER PREPARES THE KIMCHI
-Kimchi?
-Yeah.
Let's tell them
to fill their trays by themselves.
Everyone, take a tray…
KIAN'S B&B RULES
SERVE YOURSELF
And help yourselves.
Wow, this looks great.
Anyone need a spoon?
Everyone has one?
Can I get a spoon?
This was used to just stir the stew.
That's okay.
-Enjoy.
-You don't have a spoon.
I'm fine with just chopsticks.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Ye-eun.
-Yes?
Well done.
Thank you.
Thanks, Jin.
The stew looks great.
-It's not bad.
-Yeah.
-It came out really well.
-Really? It looks delicious.
Enjoy your meal!
9.30 P.M.
DINNER
Thank you for the meal.
By the way, everyone,
things will go a lot smoother tomorrow.
We apologize. Tomorrow, we'll buy
all the stuff we're short on.
We're short on cups,
so please share if you're with friends.
Okay.
We're out of cups,
so we'll pour the drinks.
Okay.
For those drinking from the bottle,
if your neighbor is out,
pour them a drink as you drink too.
Want some?
The stew's really good.
It's really good.
Yeah, it is good.
Really good.
Ye-eun, try this.
Gosh, thank you.
The stew's really good.
Really?
THE OWNER IS PROUD
-A stew made by BTS.
-BTS soybean paste stew.
This BTS soybean paste stew.
This is seriously good.
-Really?
-Yeah.
You don't have any chopsticks.
I don't have a spoon.
And our boss has neither.
That piece of kimchi was huge.
THE OWNER HAS HIS HANDS
WIPES HANDS ON HIS LEGS
Use this to wipe your hands!
This reminds me of my time in India.
WIPING HANDS ON HIS CLOTHES
Use this.
My friends from India come to mind.
The stew's seriously good.
-It's good.
-It's the best.
I'm glad.
How can you be good at cooking too?
Right?
What can't you do?
Seriously!
Before you go to bed,
I'll go downstairs and pass them up.
The blankets.
Yeah.
If it's too cold
or scary to sleep outside,
you can sleep downstairs.
Yeah.
Why have you gone soft, Boss?
No, I just…
I need to think things over tonight.
You seem to be having
a hard time with running a B&B.
I am.
You learn through trial and error.
Maybe I designed it this way
to purposely go through trial and error.
-But we'll never be able to forget this.
-Never.
We'll never forget this.
It's like I'm on a college retreat,
so it's nice.
I think I'll remember this for a while.
Who's leaving tomorrow?
Just you?
-Both of them.
-Both of you?
You're leaving tomorrow?
But why tomorrow?
My trip was for three days.
What a shame.
It feels like
they've been here for a while.
Because they were our first guests.
Our first guests.
I feel sad.
We still…
don't know anything about you two.
Exactly.
Should I stay another day?
Do you have any beds left?
Are there guests tomorrow?
I don't know how many are coming.
You're hair's blowing
like a comic book character's.
-I know. He's handsome.
-In a dreamy way.
Your look makes me want to draw you
as a web comic character.
Your hair's blowing
like a male protagonist's.
-It is.
-How annoying.
He's handsome.
The three of us are a team.
-Really?
-We're a climbing team.
How old are you guys?
I was born in 1998.
-I'm 27.
-Gosh.
I was born in 1990.
In 1990? He's older than me.
The only guest who's older.
The only older guest.
How old are you?
I was born in 1992.
Hey, we're the same age. My friend!
We're the same age.
-Nice to meet you, my friend.
-What are the chances?
Paris Saint-Germain.
-You haven't graduated yet?
-I'm still in school.
I am a carpenter,
but I'm currently studying architecture.
I started working on sites
when I was 18 years old.
And this year,
I felt I needed to learn more,
so I enrolled in college.
That's so cool.
-Are you studying abroad?
-Yes, in Australia.
You do, don't you?
-How did you know?
-She had…
-This foreign carpenter vibe.
-Yes.
-It's how she talks.
-Right.
-You can tell.
-Right?
You're right.
If she was a carpenter in Korea,
we'd say, "We're out of gigs today."
What?
-Right?
-Right.
I used to work on construction sites
when I was young.
I see.
I was born in 1992.
As a hobby, I perform as a singer.
-"Hobby."
-"Hobby"?
My day job is…
at the B&B…
Yeah.
I'm the manager here.
As for my work experience,
there isn't much,
but I've won Billboard Music Awards.
My goodness!
-My goodness!
-That's fire!
That's crazy.
-He's won Billboard Music Awards.
-That's incredible.
I've also won a few grand prizes
at Korean music awards.
He won those
even though it's only a hobby for him.
We were also nominated for the Grammys
but sadly didn't win anything.
I plan to work harder so we can try again.
I'm so jealous.
Our next global star.
Let's have Ye-eun introduce herself.
You can drive boats.
-Boats…
-Right, boats.
-The best driver.
-She's a captain.
Captain Ji.
I'm Ye-eun94.
Not Kian84. Ye-eun94.
I'm 41 years old.
And I'm the owner of your B&B.
I'm sorry for serving your dinner so late.
I'm sorry for making
the B&B so strange too.
It's so nice to meet you all.
Yes, that's all.
I'm slowly starting to slur my words.
I think it'd be fun
to play Mafia with everyone.
I like that idea.
-I'm good at it.
-Sounds fun.
It'd be fun with this many.
Then, I'll be the moderator.
Shall we play a round of Mafia?
It's been a while. I want to play.
I'll use my mind-reading ability.
Okay, everyone! Put your heads down.
Start pounding the ground.
If you don't pound properly,
I won't continue with the game.
If you don't pound properly
with your palms…
ENTHUSIASTIC MODERATOR,
PALMS ON FIRE
I won't continue with the game.
Ki-hong, hit the ground harder!
Okay, I will now select the mafia.
I don't know who it will be yet.
THE MODERATOR HAS CHOSEN
YE-EUN AS THE MAFIA
Hello, I'm Ye-eun, and I'm a civilian.
YE-EUN IS THE MAFIA
My mind reading ability has spoken to me.
It's you.
It's not time to choose yet.
HE CHOSE A CIVILIAN
HIS MIND READING HELPS YE-EUN
That is hilarious.
My mind reading ability
has been activated.
-What does it say?
-He's the mafia.
ME?
She's the mafia.
NOPE
They're the mafia!
Just an utter…
This is driving me nuts!
I finally know now.
My mind reading ability…
has revealed that you are clean.
You're spot on with that.
With my ability,
I can read everyone's mind!
NOPE
Okay!
My goodness!
But!
THE EVER-ENTHUSIASTIC MODERATOR,
STARTLED
But?
At this point…
-Thumbs up for guilty.
-I swear.
Down for innocent. Cast your votes.
-One, two, three!
-This is so frustrating.
YE-EUN IS INNOCENT
I'm telling you I'm not.
It's not me.
YE-EUN IS GUILTY
Unfortunately, the mafia…
has been killed.
We were right.
You were the mafia?
-Yes.
-Okay…
I swear my mind reading was right.
Darn.
-Everyone, did you enjoy the game?
-Yes.
-You were good.
-It was great acting.
MAFIA AT KIAN'S B&B IS OVER
Mafia, seriously…
Shall I climb up?
No, I'll go inside.
-Impressive.
-Damn it.
CLIMBING ONCE AGAIN
I'll go inside and take them in.
Then, let's go in together.
I'll take them in.
By the way,
is it illegal to climb after drinking?
I doubt it would be well-received.
-Right?
-Yes.
In that case…
SENSING BACKLASH
Since I drank, I should go the other way.
LET'S BE MINDFUL
This should go in the fridge.
THE ENTIRE TRAY GOES
INTO THE FRIDGE
-Tomorrow, we will…
-Boss!
-Yes?
-Use the colander there.
Put it over the sink.
-And pour the food waste into it.
-Okay.
FOLLOWING ORDERS
FROM HIS WORLD-CLASS ANCHOR
CHECKS THE MIRROR
BEFORE WASHING THE DISHES
EVEN WASHES HIS FACE
DRIPPING WITH WATER
STARTS WASHING DISHES WITH A WET FACE
Boss!
-Yeah?
-I'll go shower first.
-Go ahead.
-Okay.
JIN GOES TO SHOWER
AFTER WORKING HARD TO COOK
-In that case…
-Yes?
Could you take these blankets…
Hey, friend!
-Yes?
-Sir?
We're going to lift up bedding.
-Could you take them?
-Sure.
EXPRESS DELIVERY
That looks fun.
Would you like to try?
I don't think I can.
SCARED
What about the blankets?
Why are there so many?
There's so much.
All done.
THE OWNER IS DONE
WASHING DISHES TOO
KIAN'S B&B MOVES BEHIND THE BREAKWATER
If you look at the beds,
this spot…
-This one is mine.
-Okay.
-And…
-And this one.
-Here.
-Okay.
The bottom bunk.
The bottom bunk is Jin's bed.
-Only two beds are taken?
-Yes, just two.
There are 12 people and 11 beds.
One of our employees
will be sleeping downstairs in a tent.
How should we pick our beds?
The bottom bunks can only be reached
by going down the ladders.
Yes, so they said
if the person above sleeps first,
you have to climb over them.
You can just climb up from below.
Wait, is that possible for me?
JUN-HEE TRIES TO ENTER
That's it! Get up!
-Hold on.
-Just lift yourself up.
That's it.
Okay, you can go straight to sleep now.
Okay. It's decided.
I can't do it!
She decided by herself.
KI-HONG FROM TEAM KAIST
TAKES A TOP BUNK
SEONG-EUN FROM TEAM KAIST
IS HOPING FOR A BOTTOM BUNK
DANGLING
SIGHS
SUCCESSFULLY ENTERS
MIN-JUN FROM THE CLIMBING TEAM
TAKES A MIDDLE BUNK
Good night.
You don't need a pillow?
A pillow? One would be nice.
-Would you like one?
-Is there a spare?
Yes, here.
Wow, thank you.
I have a blanket too.
You can cover your stomach
if it gets cold at the night.
-Thank you so much.
-They're right next to me.
Thank you.
Are you going to sleep now?
I'm just going to lie down here. Yeah.
THE OWNER FASTENS KI-HONG'S BELT
Wear your belts before you sleep.
Yeah. Put these belts on.
-Okay.
-It's so you don't fall.
Thank you.
-Everyone, sleep with your belts on.
-Okay.
If you don't,
that won't do.
Hello there.
I have my belt on.
This reminds me of the train in India.
Sleep with your belt on. Make sure.
We can't have you get hurt.
When I was drawing this,
it was really idyllic and romantic.
But now that it's built,
why does it feel like that goes
hand in hand with danger?
I only thought of how idyllic it would be,
but after really being here,
there are so many things to worry about.
Are you worried about tomorrow?
I am.
I was thinking too much
in terms of comics.
It was fun to imagine things,
but the problem was
whether they would feel
the same way about it.
That was my biggest worry.
The experience could end up being
anything but idyllic and romantic.
Boss, you're not going to shower?
I'm fine.
I WASHED UP EARLIER
TOSSES THE BLANKET AND PILLOW DOWN FIRST
Boss, are you sure this is right?
Where should I put my head?
Sleep away from the cabinet.
-You might end up hitting your head.
-You're right.
What on earth?
Good night.
YE-EUN TAKES A CORNER
ON THE SECOND FLOOR INSTEAD OF A TENT
MEANWHILE, THE GUESTS
WHO CAN'T FALL ASLEEP
That's so cool! You see that?
The Seven Sisters.
Messier 45, the Pleiades star cluster.
That's crazy.
There seems to be a lot.
Want to go down for a look?
-Is that Cassiopeia? It's not, right?
-It is.
-Really?
-Yeah, it is.
It's that big?
And then, look over there.
One, two, three, four, five,
six…
seven.
You can see all seven stars
in the Pleiades.
I haven't felt like this in a while.
It's practically a first for me.
Why did you like constellations?
It started from dreams.
We're overdosing on dreams right now.
I know.
It'd be nice if Kian could come
and see this with us.
They all arrived today.
Time really flies.
It disappears instantly.
-Right.
-We didn't do much.
It's a shame.
I can't believe
our ferry ride wasn't canceled.
I wish it was.
I want to see bit more of Ulleungdo.
Want to see the sunrise?
Let me see what time it will be.
Look up the sunrise time.
-Yeah, I'll look it up.
-Okay.
4:00 A.M.
It's raining.
The rain.
It's cold!
We're not going in?
Hold on.
Gosh, it's raining so much.
Boss.
Boss!
Are you okay?
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B
Subtitle translation by: Hyesoo Lee