-It feels heavy.
-What's going on?
I feel something!
-What is it?
-It's a big one!
-Hey, there's something in it.
-I see something.
What is it?
-We're having a party tonight!
-Party tonight!
Get ready to eat until you burst tonight!
-This is huge for sure.
-What is it?
Hey, feel this.
-Feel the weight.
-What is it?
I see something white.
-This is really…
-What is it?
This has got to be…
What is it?
What the heck?
WHAT IS THIS?
-It's raw squid platter!
-Is that real?
What the heck?
What is it?
What did you guys catch?
IS THAT A RAW FISH PLATTER
INSIDE THE FISH TRAP?
7 HOURS AGO
JIN'S IDEA
Let's buy a flounder,
put it in a fish trap,
and have the Job-Seeker Team take it out.
They'll be so surprised.
-That sounds fun.
-That's brilliant.
Since they're looking for jobs,
catching a big fish
will make them feel lucky this year.
JOB LUCK
Why don't we go
with fish that's already been prepared?
You still have to clean it.
DIZZY
What if water gets inside?
They originally come from the ocean.
BAFFLED
Ma'am, can you make sure
water doesn't get inside
even if it's submerged in the ocean?
I can vacuum pack it.
-Really?
-Yes.
-But why are you doing that?
-It's for a surprise.
IT WILL BE A SURPRISE
10 MINUTES AGO
It's time to put this in the ocean.
SUCCESSFULLY PUTS IT IN THE FISH TRAP
INGREDIENTS FOR SPICY FISH STEW
Take it out.
NOT KNOWING HOW TO REACT
-You caught an assorted fish platter?
-A platter?
Hey!
HERE GOES NOTHING
JUST ENJOYING IT
I can't believe
you caught a raw fish platter.
This is crazy.
-I'm so freaking lucky.
-Yeah, you really are.
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE?
-What is this?
-Did you also catch spicy fish stew?
Spicy fish stew!
Spicy fish stew and squid platter?
In the middle of the ocean?
And it's already been prepared!
How is this possible?
You're really lucky, my friend.
YOU'RE REALLY LUCKY
Let's have spicy fish stew and raw fish
for dinner tonight.
I'm dizzy all of a sudden.
You are all too energetic.
Let's go help them cook now.
JIN HEADS TO THE KITCHEN TO COOK
Are you going to work out?
THE JOB-SEEKER TEAM HEADS TO THE GYM
Slip and counter.
KIAN AND CHUNG-IL ARE WORKING OUT
One more.
Two more.
That's right.
Just like that.
-He looks so cool.
-Look at his abs.
One, two.
Great job.
CHANGE POSITIONS
One, two.
Right.
One, two, hook, right.
Hook, right.
STUMBLES
So good.
You go hard on the last one.
Again.
I can't take this.
-Let's stop here.
-Sounds good.
-Thank you.
-This hurts too much.
I thought I'd never come back to this.
I don't know why,
but I always go back to boxing.
-Do you still get excited every time?
-Well, I…
Yes, that's the case for me.
I sometimes fight
in stand-up matches on the side.
-So you have two jobs.
-Basically.
Thank you.
SUDDENLY PRACTICES HIS KICKS
You're kicking
like the original stand-up fighters.
Can we try this too?
YEO-JIN AND YOO-JIN JOIN
-What is it good for?
-This?
-I want my shoulders to get bigger.
-For your shoulders…
YOU MEAN LIKE MY SHOULDERS?
Wow, you have a great body.
EMBARRASSED
SNEAKS BY
-I'll put this away. You can teach them.
-Okay.
I'm just a newbie.
THE OWNER LEAVES
I'm so thirsty.
-They're having a good time at the gym.
-Really?
It's like people are flirting.
-Flirting?
-It's kind of like…
-That's exciting.
-We're by the sea.
There's a gym
where men can show off their muscles,
and the ladies are asking them
to teach them.
-One!
-Now, two!
-Two!
-Three!
-Four!
CHUNG-IL'S HARDCORE TRAINING
My nose is getting runny!
I'm so happy that people are flirting
and having fun.
It's like we're at an amusement park
I built, and the…
What should I call them? Not hamsters but…
-The young folks.
-Right.
I seriously need to change.
I'm sick of wearing this.
How long have I been wearing this?
DAY 2
DAY 3
DAY 4
DAY 5
AND TODAY
My energy is limited.
Since I didn't spend much energy
on appearance,
I could focus on other things.
I flattened my hair with water.
That's about it.
FIRST TIME CHANGING IN 5 DAYS
BUT HE STILL KEEPS THE SAME SHORTS
-Thank you.
-For what?
Thanks for offering to work out with me.
-But I wasn't much help.
-No, you were.
It's been too long for me,
so I had trouble landing a hit.
-Would you like a gummy?
-I'd love one.
GUMMY TIME AFTER WORKING OUT
-Don't you miss it?
-Not the people, but I miss my hometown.
-I bet you do.
-I miss my friends.
I'd like to visit the school I went to.
Sometimes, I would zoom in on Google Maps
to see my hometown.
-Does it show up?
-It doesn't. It's blurry.
I see.
I used to hate my mother.
-Why?
-She left me when I was too young.
-Because she came here first?
-Yes.
My father passed away
when I was 11 years old.
He got shot on his way…
-To where?
-To here.
My mom knew it'd be difficult
to take care of the two of us.
She figured she'd come here first
and then come get us later.
But that's not as easy as it sounds.
So you and your sister
lived all by yourselves?
-Yes.
-How did you feed yourselves?
She left exactly 28 kg of maize rice
when she left.
It was enough for an 11-year-old
and a 12-year-old to last for a month.
Even now, it's hard for kids that age
to live on their own.
Your mother must've felt
horrible at the time.
Yes, she did.
Now I'm thankful for her.
It's all thanks to her
that we're able to enjoy this lifestyle.
You know, I seriously think
I'll remember this experience
for the rest of my life.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Thank you.
-When I came here…
I realized that
you're a lot kinder than I expected.
-Me?
-Yes, I was really surprised.
-Thanks.
-I mean it.
-I still have a long way to go.
-You're a lot more gentle than I thought.
-You're gentle too.
-Right.
MEANWHILE IN THE KITCHEN
TODAY'S CHEF
WASHES HER HANDS
Oh my.
Oh, it's working.
I should use it all up.
WHAT IS YE-EUN COOKING?
Hello, everyone.
This is Ji Ye-eun's cooking class.
Today, I'll be making
buckwheat noodles with perilla oil.
First, I'm going to boil the noodles.
It's the most important step.
JI YE-EUN'S COOKING CLASS
You have to keep stirring
because there's not much water.
YE-EUN'S TIP
DO NOT RUSH WHEN COOKING NOODLES
There's no need to rush in life either.
Take it slowly
and you'll get there someday.
Wherever that is.
SLOWLY COOKS THE NOODLES
RINSES IN COLD WATER
ADDS PERILLA OIL
SEASONS WITH SOY SAUCE
ADDS POWDERED PERILLA SEEDS
AND SOME CRUSHED DRIED SEAWEED
It's good.
YE-EUN'S BUCKWHEAT NOODLES
WITH PERILLA OIL IS DONE
-I'll go down and get the pork ready.
-Sure.
I'll make the spicy fish stew.
-Are you going to cook pork?
-Yes.
TONIGHT'S DINNER
NOODLES BY YE-EUN
SPICY FISH STEW BY JIN
BOILED PORK BY EUN-SIK
CHOPS THE GREEN ONIONS
AND THE ONIONS INTO LARGE PIECES
THE INGREDIENTS FROM THE FISH TRAP
THE SECRET TO SPICY FISH STEW
IS RAMYEON SEASONING
COMPLETED WITH RAMYEON NOODLES
EUN-SIK FINISHES THE BOILED PORK TOO
-What time is it?
-I think it's around 8:10 p.m.
Let's eat dinner now.
Come down, everyone.
-I can do it.
-You're good at that.
-You're strong.
-I am.
It's soft here.
I wasn't sure how much to make.
DISTRIBUTING THE BUCKWHEAT NOODLES
WITH PERILLA OIL
Let's sit in a circle.
It feels like we're getting offerings
at a Buddhist temple.
IT'S LIKE STAYING AT A TEMPLE
Let's eat.
-Okay.
-Yes.
I haven't washed my hands.
-Okay.
-Yes.
-I haven't washed my hands.
-Let's do that.
-We're eating with our hands?
-Well, we want…
We want the new guests to experience this.
Oh, I'm okay with that.
I LIKE THAT IDEA
THE NEW GUESTS EAT WITH THEIR HANDS
I'm wearing gloves.
THE OTHERS WEAR PLASTIC GLOVES
Are we the only ones?
THE OWNER IS WITH YOU
-Please enjoy your meal.
-Thanks for the meal.
I ate like this when I was little.
Hey, Ye-eun!
It's so good.
Thanks for the meal.
Hey, Ye-eun!
Isn't it good?
This is delicious.
-Great job, Ye-eun.
-Right?
-It's good.
-It's amazing.
The seasoning is perfect.
-This is delicious.
-Yeah.
It's really good.
-Ye-eun's a good cook.
-Honestly.
You're good at cooking.
-It's so delicious, right?
-Yes.
What's wrong?
I can't eat this.
Because there's no more left.
-What the heck was that?
-I want more.
-There's no more left.
-Then I really can't eat this.
I wish I could make more.
NEXT DISH COMING UP WITHOUT A BREAK
2ND COURSE
BOILED PORK AND SPICY FISH STEW
SPOONS ARE GIVEN OUT FOR HOT DISHES
So this is…
This is so good.
WIPES ON HIS THIGH
ADDICTED TO EATING WITH HER HANDS
It's good.
You eat so naturally with your hands.
This is great.
How did you adapt so fast?
It's like you've been here for days.
THEY EAT THE FISH PLATTER
THEY CAUGHT IN THE FISH TRAP
SATISFIED WITH HIS FISH TRAP PLAN
-Since we're almost done…
-Okay.
Jin and I booked a squid boat.
Squid boat?
THE ICON OF THE ULLEUNGDO ISLAND
IN THE EAST SEA
SQUID FISHING BOAT
THE SQUID CAUGHT OVERNIGHT
ARE SOLD AT THE AUCTION DURING DAWN
We'll catch squid
and enjoy them with some drinks.
THE SQUID BOAT APPROACHES
Be careful.
The boat's shaking a lot.
THEY'RE OFF TO CATCH SOME SQUID AS A SNACK
I can't believe I'm on a squid boat.
I don't know if we'll catch any.
We have an hour, so maybe we will.
It's so bright.
So that's the squid boat. I'm excited.
THEY ARRIVE AT THE SQUID FISHING SPOT
-This must be the squid fishing spot.
-Right.
KIAN'S B&B
KIAN, JIN
He's lowering the machine.
MANUAL JIGGER FOR SQUID
What do we do, sir?
-You lower the line.
-Yes.
-When the squid bites, you'll feel it.
-I see.
Then you pull it back up.
-We should try not to tangle the line.
-Oh, I see.
THE LINE CAN'T BE TANGLED
-Do you think we'll catch some in an hour?
-Yes.
-I also…
-It's here.
ALREADY?
Here it comes.
-We caught one.
-That was fast.
CAUGHT ONE IN 5 MINUTES
Give it a try.
Poor squid. Why do I feel so bad?
-It's really big.
-Yeah.
It's still breathing.
Why do I feel bad? I want to let it go.
Watch out. It'll squirt ink.
-Don't octopus squirt ink?
-Squid can do it too.
Really?
We've got this now, sir.
I'm sorry.
I didn't understand what he was thinking.
LOOKS AWAY
He's an odd duck.
I hope you're reborn
as a son of a rich family.
-Do you feel it?
-I don't know.
CAUGHT ONE
Jeez, I got one!
CAUGHT ANOTHER ONE
Nice.
CAUGHT TWO IN A ROW
I caught two!
Every time I caught one,
I screamed because it was so exciting.
It was fun.
STARES
When I met eyes with the squid,
I saw it still breathing.
It even made a sad sound.
I felt bad for it, but it was also cute.
I pitied it.
-Do you want to try?
-Okay.
THE OWNER'S TURN
Let's catch two more.
NOT SO EXCITED
I just felt bad when I saw its eyes.
I have this weird pity for them.
Poor squid.
Keep turning it.
Let's get just enough.
-Let's go back after this.
-Okay.
Nice one!
You got it.
We caught four.
That's plenty. Let's go now.
We caught plenty.
I can't even look at them.
It keeps staring at me.
-That was fun.
-Was it?
-It wasn't bad.
-Really?
CAUGHT 4 ULLEUNGDO ISLAND SQUID
Which way are you going up?
Shouldn't we show them what we caught?
PASSES 3 SQUID THROUGH THE WINDOW
THE REMAINING ONE
CAREFULLY FOLDS IT
GOES IN HIS POCKET
You're putting it in your pocket?
-They're back.
-Welcome back.
Did you catch any squid?
The squid provides us with mulhoe.
TAKES IT OUT
That's amazing!
Why did it come out of your pocket?
-It's looking at him.
-We caught four.
Really?
-I'll prepare it and serve it to you.
-That's so great.
It's easy to prepare these.
WASHES THEM CAREFULLY
They're so excited.
Hey, guests.
Is this real?
THE OWNER'S SPECIAL
ULLEUNGDO ISLAND SQUID SASHIMI
I'm kind of proud.
I'm glad we didn't come empty-handed.
I need to pee so bad.
I have to pee.
Oh gosh.
I can't hold it in.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy.
-Go ahead.
-Thank you.
I have to go pee.
Go ahead and eat.
-Dig in, everyone.
-Thank you.
It's really tender.
-This is delicious.
-Yeah.
Because it's straight out of the sea.
-It's delicious.
-It's the best.
PROUD
Let's go to bed now.
-Where's your bed, Yoo-jin?
-Over here.
Wow, this is so fun.
What do you want for dinner tomorrow?
-Stewed pork and kimchi.
-That sounds amazing.
Stewed pork and kimchi?
Everyone needs to wear
both the top and bottom straps.
This is so much fun. I can't fall asleep.
DAY 7
EMPTY
WHERE IS EVERYONE?
THE OWNER IS STILL ASLEEP
EVERYONE IS AWAKE EXCEPT HIM
ZONES OUT
GLANCES
HERE COMES THE SLIDE POLICE
-I thought you weren't watching.
-Sir.
We're operating under strict rules here.
-You can't do that.
-Okay, got it.
EMBARRASSED
STICKS TO THE RULES
It's nice and cool.
TELLING ON HIM
What are you doing, dear guest?
-Chang-jun…
-Dang it.
GOES BACK DOWN
THE OWNER'S PHONE RINGS
Kian.
Your phone's ringing, Boss.
YE-EUN IS CHANGING TRASH BAGS
YEO-JIN DELIVERS THE PHONE
-Hello?
-Yes?
MORE GUESTS?
-Where are you?
-I'm at a port.
Are you at Hyeonpo Port?
Our staff will be right there, so hold on.
-You're picking me up?
-Yes.
-Okay.
-See you.
-Ye-eun.
-Yes?
-You have to go pick someone up.
-Who?
Well, he…
He's going to take my place for a day.
I have to shoot I Live Alone.
7 DAYS AGO
Where are you going?
The shoot is only for a night.
OWNER'S 24-HOUR BUSINESS TRIP
You're leaving everything
up to the two of us?
-I called someone over.
-Who?
A REPLACEMENT WILL COME
I feel terrible
about bringing a world star here
and going off to do my own thing.
I couldn't cancel it because it had
already been scheduled a while back.
WHO IS THE PART-TIME WORKER?
I'm worried, to be honest.
PART-TIME WORKER
KWAK JOON-BIN
Kian said he'll be away for one night.
I hope I can fill his shoes.
It's my third time
on Ulleungdo Island this year.
It's only been two weeks since I was here.
ULLEUNGDO ISLAND EXPERT
I know all about this place.
I know the restaurants and tourist spots,
so the guests will like that.
There's no way…
What is that?
That can't be it.
Joon-bin!
-Who's calling me?
-Joon-bin!
Hey, Joon-bin!
I'm on another show with Joon-bin,
so I've known him for a while.
I was so happy to see him.
Joon-bin!
Are you driving right now?
You can drive a boat?
I got a license.
-Really?
-Yes, really.
-Wait.
-Ride this.
-Ride what?
-The banana boat.
No, I'm too scared to ride that.
-I really can't.
-We have all the equipment.
-I still can't.
-You have no choice.
-Please go easy on me.
-Okay.
I know you're a scaredy-cat.
-Just get on.
-But I…
Oh gosh. I forgot to tell my mom.
A 32-YEAR-OLD WHO NEEDS MOM'S PERMISSION
Just hurry up and get on.
It's too early to be riding a banana boat.
I'm scared, so you'd better chill out.
Here we go.
Where's the B&B?
IT'S ON THE OCEAN
I'm seriously scared, Ye-eun.
-I'm going to take revenge on you.
-Sure.
Jeez…
Why a banana boat?
Just trust me, Joon-bin.
We can only depend on each other.
PAST THE BREAKWATER AND INTO THE OCEAN
There's nothing in the ocean.
It's tilting!
THE BOAT IS CLEARLY TILTING
THE BOAT IS FLOODED
What is that? Is that it?
-We're here.
-That's a B&B?
Damn.
Dang, it's huge.
Is this really it?
Oh, they're back.
-Who's on the boat?
-Who is it?
I'm so curious.
-Someone's on the banana boat.
-Hello.
-It's Kwak Joon-bin.
-Hello!
-Hello.
This place is amazing.
THE PART-TIME WORKER ARRIVES
-Do you like it?
-Yes.
It's like a castle.
HEY, JOON-BIN
-Long time no see.
-Yeah, hurry on up here.
We filmed a YouTube video together.
I was happy to see him here.
He's really smart and quick-witted.
I thought it was a great idea
to bring him here.
Hello.
-Is this funny, Joon-bin?
-Hey, Kian.
You thought
you were replacing the boss, right?
-Yes.
-No, you're the newbie here.
JOB-FISHED
-I thought I'd be the manager.
-You're not.
I wish I could put you in charge,
but you don't know anything.
Listen to your superiors, okay?
FIRST, LET'S GO UP
-There's no door.
-What?
-You can do it, right?
-I'm sure you can.
I'll explain, so come this way.
THE PART-TIME WORKER'S FIRST OBSTACLE
-Did you design this?
-Yes.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE COME
-You're doing well.
-He's climbing.
I thought you'd find it difficult,
but you're getting there.
You have to get used to it.
Shit, this is so damn scary.
-Oh, Joon-bin is afraid of heights.
-This is horrifying.
-He's afraid of heights.
-Wait, don't pull me.
It's so scary.
THE PART-TIME WORKER
WHO'S AFRAID OF HEIGHTS
Give me a moment. I even got seasick.
PLUS SEASICKNESS
Come to think of it,
there are so many things here
that you wouldn't like.
I can't swim or climb, and I get seasick.
This place is perfect.
This place has everything you hate.
KIAN'S B&B IS TOO PERFECT FOR JOON-BIN
TEACHING HIM THE ROPES
Once the guests are out,
you have to clean up.
You have to clean and do the laundry.
PART-TIME WORKER'S TO-DO LIST
1. CLEANING AND LAUNDRY
Also, some people take off the straps
in their sleep.
-You have to keep an eye on it.
-Really?
2. CHECK THE BED SAFETY
You have to keep lining up the slippers.
It can look messy.
3. TIDY UP THE SLIPPERS
I'm usually the one
who cleans the bathroom.
4. CLEAN THE BATHROOM
-Can you clean it?
-Yes.
We need to clean now.
PUTS HIM TO WORK RIGHT AWAY
We need to do the laundry today.
We have to gather the towels.
I'll gather them. You guys should relax.
The boss taught me well.
Please give me your towels.
STARTING WITH THE LAUNDRY
-Towels.
-Please give me your towels.
PLEASED
This is fun.
They did this for a week?
That must have been tough.
-Do you need to wash it?
-I just need to rinse it.
-I'll do it for you.
-No, I'm going to wear it today.
How old are you?
-I'm 33 years old.
-So you were born in 1992.
THE SAME AGE
You can speak casually with me.
No, I can't do that.
Jin didn't hesitate at all.
Kian told me to treat the guests well…
Let me help.
JIN JOINS THEM
I'm tired.
Here you go.
THE LAUNDRY IS DONE
THE OWNER IS CLEANING THE KITCHEN
THOROUGH
WORKING HARD BEFORE HE LEAVES
FINDS SOMETHING
SOCKS AND TRASH
The socks are here?
THE TRASH GOES IN HIS POCKET
If trash falls out, I put it in my pocket.
I've gotten used to it.
I have to get rid of it first
because I want to keep it clean.
BUT THE SOCKS REMAIN ON THE FLOOR
SMELLS THEM WITHOUT THINKING
THE SOCKS GO IN HIS POCKET TOO
Shouldn't you go now?
-I'm counting on you, Jin.
-Okay.
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
DON'T WORRY, BOSS
I'm counting on you.
-Take care.
-Bye.
Good luck.
-Enjoy your stay.
-I will.
-Good luck.
-Bye.
Take care.
This doesn't feel right, though.
-Don't worry about a thing.
-Okay, I'll be back.
My heart feels heavy.
THE OWNER HEADS TO SEOUL
It's Kian's B&B without Kian.
KIAN'S B&B WITH NO KIAN
-Are you leaving?
-Yes.
We're exploring the area.
-I'll give you some recommendations.
-We want to go to a pretty cafe.
There's a foot spa cafe over there.
-That sounds nice.
-It does.
You can just look up
"Olleh Foot Spa Cafe."
A travel YouTuber knows his stuff.
AS EXPECTED OF A TRAVEL YOUTUBER
Let's go.
I hope they're in here.
CHUNG-IL LOOKS FOR SOMETHING
Where did the lenses fall off?
THE LENSES FELL OFF HIS SUNGLASSES
I bought these for this trip,
but you can have them.
Keep them.
-You're so generous.
-That's amazing.
What's your purpose?
Are you doing this to look good?
How can I wear these?
-Just wear them.
-Thank you so much.
-That's amazing.
-What an honor.
They look good on you, Chung-il.
He looks cool.
-You look great, Chung-il.
-Thanks.
It'll be a family heirloom.
Don't mention it. They really suit you.
Let's go, everyone.
It's time to leave.
You can get off now.
-Thanks, Ye-eun.
-Thank you.
Thanks for the ride, Ye-eun.
-Have fun.
-Enjoy your day.
-Okay.
-You too.
THE GUESTS GO SNORKELING
AND THE STAFF IS OUT FOR LUNCH
-What else is good around here?
-Barnacle kalguksu.
That sounds amazing.
-I'd love that.
-It's good.
LUNCH WILL BE KALGUKSU
RECOMMENDED BY JOON-BIN
Kian's incredible.
I never imagined it would look like that.
It's my first time coming this way.
It's pretty here.
The mountains are beautiful.
ARRIVED AT THE RESTAURANT
-This place is famous.
-I want porridge.
You need a porridge storage?
LOOK AT THIS GUY
Hey, Joon-bin.
I love puns like that.
Thank goodness.
I FOUND MY SOULMATE
Give me one, mate.
What happens when a king gets hit?
HESITATES
It's "King Gong."
HAHAHA
What does a king do
when he loses something?
He's a "search king"?
No, he's "look-king."
Do you have one, Ye-eun?
I got one.
What did one ocean say to another ocean?
Nothing. It just waved.
You got it right.
You're not there yet.
This place looks good.
Thank you.
-I'm excited.
-Thank you.
JOON-BIN'S RECOMMENDED RESTAURANT
The noodles are special here.
They mix in ground barnacles.
BARNACLE KALGUKSU
SEASONED WITH NUTTY BARNACLE INNARDS
One barnacle porridge.
One spicy squid salad.
DOKDO SHRIMP STEW
This is delicious.
The porridge is good too.
I crave this when I'm back in Seoul.
-Do you like it?
-Yes.
I want shrimp too.
The food here is great.
-Do you want me to peel it for you?
-Yes.
YES, PLEASE
You're pretty sweet.
SWEET JOON-BIN
What about me?
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
ONE FOR YE-EUN
ONE FOR JIN
Thank you.
Eat up.
It's so good.
I love this.
That was a good meal.
Let's go, guys.
I don't think you're aware,
but you've been here for a week.
It's been seven days already?
Should we have fun
to celebrate your seventh day?
Yeah, let's have fun.
The guests come back at 7 p.m.,
so we need to be back at the B&B by 5 p.m.
PONDERS
The staff also needs rest.
You're supposed to get time off
for working a whole week.
By law,
you have to take a break from work.
WAS THAT GOOD, YE-EUN?
Isn't it Monday today?
It's Sunday… No, it's Monday.
You didn't take the weekend off, so…
NO CHANCE
We came to the island on Tuesday.
It's only been six days.
-You worked as soon as you got here.
-Right.
Shouldn't we clean the floors
while Joon-bin is here?
I'm just a part-time worker.
I'll do what the boss says.
Let's go back now.
-I mean, what do you want to do?
-I want to go to a cafe.
-Okay, let's go.
-I'm so excited.
This place is pretty.
The view is really nice here.
AFTER ENJOYING A QUICK BREAK
The guests haven't had much to eat,
so I'll get some snacks.
We're going back then.
Let's go.
JIN AND JOON-BIN HEAD BACK
Off we go.
MEANWHILE, KIAN'S B&B
RETURNS TO THE BREAKWATER
MOVE COMPLETE
JIN AND JOON-BIN RETURN
I'll make the rice and stew.
-So we're doing the work?
-Yes.
I'll do the hard job.
I'll tidy up everything
before the guests arrive.
-Should I mop the floor?
-Yes.
TO-DO LIST
JIN: PUT AWAY GROCERIES, COOK
JOON-BIN: CLEAN THE INSIDE
AND THE BATHROOM
You're good at that.
It's heavy.
-Here.
-Thank you.
Good luck.
Who even drinks this much alcohol?
PUTS AWAY THE GROCERIES
What is this? I forgot to buy rice.
-Joon-bin.
-Yes?
Can you go to the convenience store
and buy some rice?
Should we ask Ye-eun?
-Ask her to get some.
-Got it.
YE-EUN, PLEASE BUY RICE ON THE WAY BACK
OKAY!
-I'm going to clean the bathroom.
-Okay.
I haven't gone there yet.
I'm the one who usually cleans
the bathroom. Can you clean it?
THE OWNER'S REQUEST
CLEAN THE BATHROOM
MORBID
PROPS THE DOOR OPEN
CLEANING BRUSH IN HAND
I should clean it while I'm here.
CLEANS EVERY CORNER
EVERY NOOK AND CRANNY
CLEANS THOROUGHLY
CLEAN-UP DONE
TONIGHT'S DINNER
STEWED PORK AND KIMCHI
Wow, the kimchi is fermented well.
LOTS OF KIMCHI
This is the pork.
AND LOTS OF MEAT
Hello?
-Hello.
We'd like to check in.
-Check in?
-Yes.
Can you come by 7 p.m.?
THE TEMPORARY OWNER GIVES INSTRUCTIONS
You have to come to Hyeonpo Port.
-Got it.
-Okay, see you.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
Hey, I think it's a couple.
-What?
-We have a couple.
-A cuddle?
-A couple!
-You want to cuddle?
-I said, "couple."
Cuddle?
Not cuddle but couple!
-A couple?
-Yes.
-It's a couple?
-I think so.
UNDERSTOOD
This will be
quite a memorable experience for them.
Seriously.
RESUMES COOKING DINNER
A little bit of soybean paste.
BOIL IT FOR A LONG TIME
It smells spicy.
I just need to wait for the rice.
PAUSES
You have to keep lining up the slippers.
It can look messy.
ORGANIZES THE FOOTWEAR
LIKE HE'S IN HYPNOSIS
IN A STRAIGHT LINE
It's messier than I expected.
Once the guests are out,
you have to clean up.
MOVES EVERYTHING TO ONE SIDE
AND THEN WIPES THE FLOOR WITH A RAG
CLEANING EVERY NOOK AND CRANNY
THOROUGHLY
THE AREA THAT WAS MESSY
It's clean now.
-I'll come down.
-Okay.
IT IS MUCH CLEANER NOW
COMING DOWN TO CLEAN THE FIRST FLOOR
Be careful on your way down.
Look at these cabinets.
It's so Kian-like. Unbelievable.
But, you know,
running a B&B is kind of nice.
You greet guests.
THE STEW IS ALSO DONE
It's quite fun.
I'm done.
DIZZY
We work well together.
I rushed over here.
MEANWHILE IN SEOUL
I'm not worried about Jin or Ye-eun,
but I'm a bit worried about Joon-bin.
What are you guys doing right now?
Grab it with your feet.
That's right.
Good job. You did your best.
I mean it.
I think I can do it.
-Put this on.
-Okay.
Wear it and strap it on.
What?
I think I can do it.
Give it another try.
SECOND TRY
That's it.
There you go.
I can't. Give me a hand.
Just a little more.
-Pull yourself up at three.
-Okay.
One, two, three!
It was no biggie.
Did you say "piggy"?
I knew you could do it.
Thanks for the help.
Joon-bin!
What's in your hand?
-It's a gift.
-Really?
CAME BACK WITH SNACKS FOR THE GUESTS
-Ye-eun is here.
-Okay.
Should I put the rice here?
-Ye-eun!
-Can I put it here?
-What is it?
-Gosh.
What's wrong?
THE RICE YE-EUN BOUGHT
Here.
-I can't go back up.
-No, I'm over here.
-Look here.
-I can't go back up.
-No, I'm here.
-Oh, there you are.
SORRY
-Over here.
-Good idea.
-Hey.
-I'm exhausted.
Did you buy bread for the guests?
Yeah, I did.
You can't come up this way.
Not this way. Go up that way.
HERE COMES THE NEW SLIDE POLICE
I think you're mistaken.
This is the way down.
You've got it, Joon-bin!
Hey, climb the wall.
-But it's raining.
-It's not raining.
Kian asked me to do this.
-Jeez…
-He said to stick to the rules.
Go that way!
THIS IS RIDICULOUS
MEANWHILE, THE GUESTS
This is crazy.
I'm really excited.
HAKPO PORT
I can't wait to dive in.
I can't wait. It'll be fun.
SNORKELING TOGETHER
-It's so nice.
-The water is so clear.
There's a ton of fish.
It's really cool here.
-It's emerald colored.
-Right.
Ulleungdo Island is beautiful
in a very unique way.
Chung-il, can you pick that up?
What is it?
CHUNG-IL FOUND A SEA SNAIL
CHANG-JUN ALSO FOUND ONE
This is amazing.
This is so much fun.
7 P.M.
I'll be right back.
YE-EUN GOES TO PICK UP THE GUESTS
-Let's go.
-Hello.
-Did you have fun?
We did.
We're going to wait for some new guests.
-Are they joining us?
-Yes.
That's exciting.
-That's a relief.
-I think that's them.
That must be them.
THE NEW GUESTS HAVE ARRIVED
Do you have everything, baby?
-I think that's it, baby.
-What?
-Seriously?
-I think so.
Hello, Kian's B&B guests.
Please get on the boat.
Get on the boat?
Hello, please get on.
Okay, we'll be there.
-Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
-Are you two a couple?
-Yes, we are.
HOLDING HANDS TIGHTLY
-I'm so jealous.
-Me too.
-Let's get going.
-Okay.
How old are you?
-I was born in 2001.
-Sorry?
-Did you say 2001?
-Yes.
That's right.
REALLY?
I was born in 2001,
and she was born in 1997.
KIM JEONG-HUI, BORN IN 1997
KIM BO-SEUNG, BORN IN 2001
SHE'S OLDER THAN HIM
They're so cute together.
Oh, that's cool.
You can get off now.
It really looks bizarre.
HOLDS HER HAND
Welcome, everyone.
Nice to meet you.
This is Kian's B&B.
There's no door on the first floor.
You need to climb the wall to get inside.
BEWILDERED
That's the entrance?
Yes, this is the entrance.
-Oh my.
-Let's go up first.
Do it like this. I see.
-Be careful, Jeong-hui.
-I will.
Just wait for your turn, baby.
-"Wait for your turn, baby."
-He's so sweet.
He cares more about her safety than his.
-You can do this.
-You've got this.
She's doing it so well.
CLIMBS UP QUICKLY
Why is she so good?
EXCITED
She's good.
Good job.
You've got this.
BO-SEUNG ALSO CLIMBS UP QUICKLY
THE OTHER GUESTS ENTER AS WELL
-Hello.
FIRST GREETING
Welcome to Kian's B&B. I'm Joon-bin84.
But why are you…
I'M TRAPPED HERE
Please help me up.
-One moment.
-We've got you.
-I got him.
-You got him?
-One second.
-Two, three.
CAUGHT A BIG FISH
-Nice to meet you.
-That was a weird entrance.
AN EMBARRASSING ENTRANCE
WELCOME TO KIAN'S B&B WITH NO KIAN
How do you know each other?
She's my girlfriend.
-You're not married?
-No.
-There's something more shocking.
-What is it?
-Are you younger than her?
-Yes, I am.
-He's four years younger.
-I see.
I was born in 2001.
-You're 24 and 28 years old.
-Yes.
-What do you do?
-I'm an optician. I make glasses.
What about you, Bo-seung?
I'm in college.
HE'S A STUDENT
FIRST COUPLE GUESTS
JEONG-HUI AND BO-SEUNG
Should we eat now?
But it's stewed pork and kimchi.
Should we give them spoons?
I think we should. This is really hot.
What are you talking about?
-We eat with our hands.
-"Give them spoons"?
WHY ARE THEY DISCUSSING THIS?
We usually eat with our hands.
But today's dish is hot,
so we should hand out spoons.
Let's just give them spoons.
What about forks?
LOGIC DESTROYED
Excuse me, Chung-il!
Please tell everyone
to come down for dinner.
-Let's go down for dinner, guys.
-Okay.
-The rice is awesome.
-Wait, how is she coming down so slowly?
-How are you doing this?
-This looks harder to do.
How is she doing that?
How are you coming down in slow motion?
-She's here.
-How did you do that?
BO-SEUNG'S FIRST DESCENT
-Be careful not to burn your hands.
-Okay.
-What do you call her?
-I call her "baby."
BABY
That's so sweet.
-Do you ever call her by her name?
-No.
Hey, Chung-il, my baby.
CHUNG-IL, MY BABY
Hey, Myeong-gyun, baby.
JIN'S BABIES
-She made that look so easy.
-She slid down at once.
This place is interesting.
-Hey, you have something on your face.
-Where?
-Sorry, I should've noticed.
-That's so sweet.
-So sweet.
-Oh my.
-Thanks.
-It's my fault.
Ye-eun.
Stop it.
DINNER WITH THE BABIES
TONIGHT'S DINNER
STEWED PORK AND KIMCHI
This is crazy.
Everyone was down for this.
We simply mentioned it, but you heard us.
We'll give you spoons tonight
because the food is too hot.
Thank you.
We've been eating with our fingers.
We ate with our hands here.
Back in my day…
We got lucky.
THEY'RE HUNGRY AFTER A LONG, FUN DAY
A BIG SERVING OF THE STEW
AND RICE
HEAPS
Ye-eun, come over here.
THE TEMPORARY OWNER
Thank you.
SCOOPS UP FOOD FOR THE STAFF FIRST
Come on, Joon-bin.
JIN GOES LAST
-This looks great.
-Bon appétit.
-Thanks for the meal.
-Enjoy.
-This looks amazing.
IT'S BOUND TO BE GOOD
It's delicious.
It really is.
The kimchi is great.
This is really good.
It's like I'm at a restaurant.
This is fantastic.
PLEASED
There was a lot more to think about
when I was in charge.
I was impressed with Kian
for what he's done.
Is anyone leaving tomorrow?
THE JOB-SEEKER TEAM
IS CHECKING OUT TOMORROW
-The four of you are friends, right?
-Yes.
-And you're here alone.
You're very brave.
-What?
-Excuse me?
Did you say "grave"?
I said, "brave."
Oh, we thought you called us depressing.
-"Brave."
-It stung.
It was a compliment.
-How did you…
-How did you meet?
I want to know.
-We…
-We met at work.
What kind of job?
We worked at a Thai restaurant.
MET WHILE HE WAS A PART-TIME WORKER
Who asked whom out first?
-I did, but…
-Yes?
We were walking,
and I asked her how she felt about me.
-But she said she needed to go home.
-Why?
So I convinced her for 30 minutes
to go on a date with me.
-You convinced her?
-How?
-I was convinced.
-You didn't like him at first?
-I know, right?
I also thought
we would end up dating anyway.
That's so cute.
I finished it so fast.
EVERYONE DOES THEIR OWN DISHES
Do you need something, Jeong-hui?
-Is this the only exit?
-Yes.
I'd better take my socks off.
Can I do this?
-Give it a try.
-We have a rescue team.
CHUNG-IL'S RESCUE TEAM IS ON STANDBY
I don't think I can do this.
WIPING IT SO IT'S NOT SLIPPERY
Step on my shoulder.
CHANG-JUN IS WAITING ON TOP
Here I go. Thank you.
Thank you.
This is…
LOGIC DESTROYED ONCE AGAIN
How do I do this?
THEIR SECOND RESCUE
We still have to climb a bit.
EYES TREMBLING
BO-SEUNG HELPS JEONG-HUI
LIKE THE RESCUE TEAM DID
Here we go.
What's this?
-What's this?
-Oh gosh, what do I do?
-Great.
-As expected.
RESCUE SUCCESSFUL
-Are your shoulders okay?
-Yes, I'm okay.
IT'S BO-SEUNG'S TURN
Grab it tightly and go.
GOES UP RIGHT AWAY
-Good.
-Just like that.
-You're doing well.
-That's it.
-There you go.
-Step on that.
You did it!
THE RESCUE TEAM'S JOB IS DONE
Let's clean up for the last time.
-Are we done now?
-Yes.
It feels like
we did a part-time job together.
I know. You have to help me up.
Okay.
I don't have the energy to go up.
-Do you want some help?
-Can you lift me?
-You are 60 kg?
-Yeah.
I can lift you since I'm 90 kg.
I never thought I'd need help. Thanks.
-Here.
-I should wear that.
TAKING THE JOON-BIN ELEVATOR
-Can I stand?
-Yes.
Stand up.
Here I go.
-Should I climb on your back?
-Yes.
JOON-BIN ELEVATOR'S SECOND PASSENGER
I'm getting up.
Trust Jin.
TRUST ME
I'm still here.
THERE'S ONE MORE
-Can you help us?
-Of course.
-He's going to jump.
-Okay.
-You just need to pull him up.
-Got it.
-Jump at the count of three.
-Okay.
-Jump as high as you can.
-Got it.
-Hold on to this side.
-Okay.
-You have to hold on for a moment.
TAKES OFF
One, two, three.
Damn it.
Thank you. Welcome to Kian's B&B.
That was so funny.
-Please choose a bed.
-We didn't choose yet.
This is where you sleep.
-We sleep here?
-Yes.
-Do we sleep outdoors?
-Did I hear that right?
-The top beds are empty.
-The top?
BOTH ARE EMPTY
-Through this window.
-I guess that's us.
The top is nice.
I couldn't believe
we were sleeping out there.
MEANWHILE, JEONG-HUI
LOOKS AROUND THE TOP FLOOR
WITHOUT HESITATION
It's nice, right?
-Do you get rained on?
-Yes.
-It hasn't happened yet.
-This is cool.
My dream of sleeping on a terrace bed
came true at Kian's B&B.
I really liked it.
-Let's sleep across from each other.
-The top is empty.
THEY CHOOSE THE THIRD FLOOR
I guess we'll sleep here.
-Where do I sleep?
-Joon-bin.
-Sleep there.
-It's Kian's spot.
THE OWNER'S SPOT
Can I switch with someone?
I have a severe fear of heights.
-I can, but there's a downside.
-Which is?
-It's hard to get up there.
-What?
You have to climb up.
-To where?
-You have to go up.
That's my spot.
You have to climb up from below.
-You're not afraid of heights?
-No.
Even if I were,
I would switch places with you.
-Damn.
-That's sweet.
-I mean…
-He's so sweet.
SO SWEET
Why are you so sweet?
CHUNG-IL, JOON-BIN
Let's make a toast.
Let's drink together.
-It's nice to meet you.
-It's great to meet you.
THE OWNER AT THE SAME HOUR
I just finished shooting,
and I'm on my way back.
I'm a bit worried
if everyone would be lost
without me there.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN "LOST"?
Jin!
CHEERING FOR THE TEMPORARY OWNER
PAYING THEM BACK WITH A SONG
With my backpack
The golden sun
The festival begins
Toward the wilderness
Toward the valley
Let's look for running water in a valley
Where we can hear echoes
Let's take a trip there
ONE MORE TIME
Let's look for running water in a valley
Where we can hear echoes
Let's take a trip there
CONTINUED BY A TALENT SHOW
We have a cameraman there.
THE CAMERAMAN AT WORK
CHAOTIC
THE FORGOTTEN OWNER CONTINUES
Without me there,
I'm worried that they're…
WORRYING
DON'T WORRY
THEY'RE HAVING A BLAST
-What the heck?
-What is that?
What the heck?
A WILD NIGHT AT KIAN'S B&B
I should go to sleep now.
My voice is cracking.
Wow, this is so cool.
I love it here.
I can't fall asleep.
This is a memory only we can cherish.
MORNING OF DAY 8
Hello, guys.
I'll ride the boat and head back now.
THE OWNER IS COMING BACK
See you soon.
I shaved.
SHOWING OFF HIS CLEAN FACE
I'm all clean.
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B
Subtitle translation by: Jane Oh