We seasonal
I know your name
Then you must be in the army
Relation
The relationship can't be talked about
But I do
A few friends in the army
Let me ask
Ask what
Just ask
Which army of the navy was that day
Who are the people who go to rescue
Anyway, the more detailed the better
Tang Xin, what are you thinking
How can you ask this casually
I don't ask about military secrets
You just ask me privately
Row
I try
If I can't ask
You don't blame me
You ask first
Row
What are you drinking, I'll order it for you
It's okay, thank you
Row
Hello
You two are fine
it is good
Okay, okay, okay
I didn't mean that
it is good
Row
Okay, see you
how about it
No information can be told
I didn't ask anything
No word
得
Didn't I ask you for nothing today
I'd better go to the blind date
Hello
I am Tang Xin, a reporter from Minghua Network
I want to save the day's big salt glue action
Do a special report
According to the program
Come to the war zone propaganda bureau
Submit an interview application
You register first
Let's verify
I found
I found things
This thing
Thank you
There are so many people.
Yeah.
So many people.
The sea is beautiful.
Let's take a picture.
Okay.
Come on. Stand there.
I'll take a picture for you.
Okay.
Who?
Stand still.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Look.
This guy is so handsome.
He is.
We are meant to be together.
Why don't you add me on WeChat?
Go.
Hurry.
Something happened.
I'll be back soon.
Hurry.
Go.
Why did he run away?
Look at your mom.
She's gone.
How about your mom?
Where's your dad?
Where's the armory?
Get out first.
Here.
You fail too.
Minggu first.
I...
You've changed your legs.
Changed?
You're a headshot.
You're something.
I...
Captain Song,
Xia Zhi is waiting to be eaten.
Remember,
don't be a gentleman.
It doesn't matter if you eat it.
Xia Zhi.
Captain,
I want to eat.
Captain.
Still not resting?
Do I have flowers on my face?
What are you looking at?
Come, come, come.
Let's go, let's go.
Come on, comrade Wu Si.
Tell me.
What?
What's the blind date?
Dad.
Dad, you can't be cold with me.
I admit,
I was just being mean to you today.
But it's not because of blind dates.
Because your target is a soldier.
I'll make it clear first.
I have no prejudice against soldiers.
I grew up in the military.
I admire soldiers the most.
But,
I'm from Chongqing.
To be a soldier is another thing.
Besides,
If you want to introduce me to someone,
you have to ask for my opinion.
Did I ask for your opinion this time?
Are you asking for my opinion?
Good guy.
The first time we met,
you and Uncle Wang
were like a couple.
That's to verify your own opinion.
I'm the only one who doesn't know
how to go on a blind date.
You're so naive.
Come on.
Why don't you remind me?
The 15-kilometer armed band is also on sale.
I dare to say.
Captain.
Is that girl pretty?
When did you pay so much?
Is it important whether she is pretty or not?
It's important.
You're so poor.
Are you so poor in front of Wu Ke'er?
All right.
Don't hide it from me.
Pack it up.
I didn't see anyone at all.
I told you.
You asked Uncle Wang
to find the person who saved me from the big fire.
How many games are there?
Tang Xin.
Are you having a grudge against me?
What grudge do I have against you?
I have no grudge against you.
I have no grudge against the soldiers.
But you want me to find the soldiers.
I don't want to.
Why?
All right. I'll ask you.
Which school did I go to in primary school?
Do you know that my middle school class teacher
is a man or a woman?
Do you know that I went to high school,
high school, high school, and high school?
All right.
Don't say a few words.
Mom, let me finish.
Look.
You can't answer it.
Come on.
Dad.
I love the country, the army, and the soldiers.
But
I can't be the heroine.
Xin Xin.
Do you remember
when I was a kid,
you went abroad for a few months.
You finally came back.
You went to kindergarten to pick me up.
I ignored you and called you uncle.
I'm four years old.
I don't even know who my father is.
Mr. Tang.
Do you know how long it took me to go back
to change Mr. Tang into a father?
Do you know how long it took me
to adapt to the existence of you in the family?
Do you know that even after I saw
you and my mom sleep in the same room for the first time,
I almost cried?
I
I even wrote a letter back.
It's all negative comments.
I'm going to the police station to report you.
All these silly things were in my childhood memory.
But I don't want to copy and paste these memories
to my own child.
Do you know what I think most in the army?
I miss you.
I miss your mother.
I think
it's because there are thousands of people like me
fighting in the air,
in the sea,
and in the border.
Only then can you live a peaceful life.
I know.
So I never blame you.
I was a kid.
I also took you to brawl with my friends.
I've been brawling with my friends.
But now I've grown up.
I have my own thoughts,
my own likes.
My own choices.
I don't want to find someone to arrange a boyfriend for me.
I don't want to live the life someone arranges for me.
Even if it's you.
I've waitedAll for this moment
after we lookетhe long and endless road
You've had to wait
Just look
Go
I'm leaving.
You're not leaving, are you?
Fine.
Next time,
come on.
Go, go, go.
I'm begging you.
Can you try it again?
Can you?
How do you know
the person I like
is not good?
Aren't you curious?
Stop.
Don't give me that hard time.
That's all.
That's all?
Try it.
Call him.
Okay.
What's wrong with my head
when pressed down by the ocean?
I keep remembering him.
Make me aware of her life
Intense
Turn around
I will tell you
What's this
This?
Is tr が form difficult for you
Yes
You should decide
You will have to do second shot
и
Dad
August
May you rest in peace
I may rest in peace
to pretend they don't even know about you.
Pretend
To point out
where not Everyone knows
So they won't know
that you're the one
who interfered to create an upheaval.
What is yours?
You,
You're the one who forever
doesn't even know
when you two can be together.
But I really don't know.
So
I have to prove it to you.
Captain, you've been sitting here since I came here.
Why are you looking at the pen?
Help me see what this name means.
Take the spare key.
I must open your door today.
Open it.
Okay, okay.
No need.
I'll change it, okay?
Open it now.
Well...
I've made up my mind.
I'll be honest.
I'll be honest for 24 hours.
Why are you looking at the strange things?
Don't click.
I'll tell you if you click on the record.
That's more like it.
Enough.
No more spare keys.
This letter is from Master Tr 그러?
I'm not going to investigate this matter.
But the ship was caught on fire on the way.
There's no gain in this trip.
I'll keep following up on this matter.
But the range of salt and pepper sea fish is too large.
It's really hard to investigate without a specific location.
If you have a ship with a sea fish escort,
please provide it to me.
conocen
What's your name?
It's good to be labeled under my bank account.
This is the dried relations tree you ordered.
Thanks.
There is no need to know my Nous.
I'm not everything.
Hello
You come alone?
It's boring drinking
milk tea by yourself.
We should add each other
on Facebook.
We can have a single life together!
There's no need. I don't know you yet.
Just add me on Facebook,
on your local Facebook.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm not a bad person.
Really.
What are you drinking?
Yangzhi dry deer?
You know,
every time I come here,
I always meet you.
Do you think this is a predestined fate?
I'm sorry.
I'm waiting for others.
There are so many empty seats here.
Can you go to another place?
I'm sorry.
But I like you.
The girl next to you.
Don't go.
I just want to know you.
I'm not a bad person.
Be civilized in public.
Who?
He's the one I'm waiting for.
Did you hear that?
No.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
It's my duty.
Wait.
Can we add a contact?
Okay.
My name is Zong Qing.
My name is Lan Yangyang.
Yangyang. I remember.
Goodbye.
Hello.
Is Tang Ji in our office?
Tang Xin?
Yes.
The second room on the left.
Thank you.
Mr. Han, you're here.
Hello, Mr. Han.
We have a meeting.
I'm here to see you.
What's the matter?
Hello, Hai.
We meet again.
You want to see Xin?
Yes. Is it convenient?
Yes.
Come with me.
Thank you.
I'm here
to thank you.
For what?
For saving your life.
The ship was on fire.
It was very dangerous.
But you chose to save me.
I didn't save you.
We were rescued by the navy.
It's different.
But I have to remember
our friendship.
Mr. Han, don't say that.
I'm embarrassed.
I asked you for help.
And I caused
such a big loss to your family.
If you say so,
I'm embarrassed.
It's all my fault.
I found such a bad ship.
I was too busy to help.
I almost threw you into the sea.
Let's not be polite.
Anyway, I can't afford
your ship.
This has nothing to do with you.
We investigated it after the accident.
It was caused by the engine failure.
It was accidentally caught on fire.
Then I don't have to feel guilty?
Of course.
Do you have time tonight?
I'll treat you to dinner.
I found such a bad ship
to make up for it.
But I'm your official person.
Report.
One hundred thousand yuan of money
is ready to be paid off.
Three.
Don't be in a hurry.
Hurry up.
Hold your hands tight.
Look at your feet.
Take it easy.
Don't be in a hurry.
Hurry up.
Where are your hands?
Water.
Report,
Keep it in the way.
Report, Yang Yang's lock- Taeàn performance is complete,
Attendant Ouyang's lock- Taeàn performance is continued,
Without the conforming.
This is I don't need?
Report, Gao Yang similar to Yang Yang.
A situation just according toavian rugby B根Yang Yang
need to quit with their spray guns.
They gave us template.
You can go to work now.
If it's impossible to go to work,
we can even go to work tomorrow.
Just trust me.
Tomorrow I come to Wenzhou for a business trip.
and the last one for you
are not the same at all.
Okay.
Take this pure youth
to the financial department first.
And this sister,
if you need anything in the future,
remember to find me, okay?
The secretly shot is still safe.
This time, let's learn from Zhong Xiaowen
to do a live broadcast.
Okay.
How good is this?
This one.
This one is good.
Hello, Miss.
What do you want to buy?
I'll get you what you like.
Look at this.
This one.
Miss, you're so sharp.
This jade is imported from Myanmar directly.
Look at this color.
It's green.
There's no box at all.
Our house is 1888.
There are thousands of shops in other houses.
Really?
Like this general jade,
it's all through manufacturers,
salesmen, wholesale merchants,
and brand merchants
to get to the counter.
Our house
is a first-hand goods source in Myanmar.
Without these middlemen,
we can only get these
cheap and good goods.
How about one?
Okay.
This one.
I'll wrap it for you.
Miss, would you like to take a look
at our jade bracelet?
It's a nice color.
You can take a look.
Okay.
Hello, sir.
This one?
This one. Take a look.
I'll wrap it for you when you pick it.
Okay.
Okay. Please wait a moment.
Let's go.
We're in trouble.
What's going on?
That girl took my jade bracelet away.
We're in trouble.
Don't run.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'll talk to you when the police come.
Here.
Please register your personal information.
Write a word
and see who
gave this jade bracelet to someone.
If there's no problem, you can leave.
Officer.
Not only this jade bracelet,
but also my camera.
I'll take a look at it.
Okay.
Where's my camera?
And,
officer.
I'm asking you.
Why did you come to me?
I thought you stole someone else's stuff.
I didn't have time to take this bracelet.
Even if you're brave,
you should observe the situation.
And there's someone
running crazy ahead.
Didn't you see that?
I really didn't see the person ahead.
I only saw you
running around.
Okay.
Although you're busy,
you're a very hard-working person.
I don't want to make things difficult for you.
You're a soldier?
Which army?
The Lu's.
My cousin is in your team, too.
His name is Li Xing. Do you know him?
Officer.
You can't start a relationship
in front of me
because you're in the same profession.
What makes you think
I'm in a relationship?
Besides, we're in the same profession.
Li Xing.
He went to their girl.
This Nanguan.
Wait a moment.
I just said he went to the Lu's team?
The strike at Taiyan Camp
the other day
was iT meddlesome.
I'm sorry.
I'll pay for it.
Comrade Zhang,
Then you should ask the shopkeeper for a price.
Comrade,
I brought this bracelet.
I'll pay for it.
I just came to ask for a price.
It's not a matter of money.
It's not about money.
After all,
it's a matter of a person's choice.
Don't let the good people be so cold-hearted.
Thank you for your kindness.
But our army has rules.
If you destroy something,
you have to pay for it.
Okay, then.
I'll pay for it.
But I have to trouble you
to fix my phone.
You're waiting for someone to come?
I'll fix it.
We'll contact each other.
Thank you.
My phone will be on for 24 hours.
I'll contact you when I fix it.
What's wrong?
You're paying for the bracelet?
Okay.
I'll pay for it.
Who are you?
Her boyfriend.
Why are you here?
The live broadcast is too boring.
So I came to see the drama.
I'll send you home later.
No need. I'll go back to the unit.
Then I'll send you back to the unit.
I may not be able to send the camera
after it's fixed.
Is it convenient to flash it?
No.
My camera is very expensive.
Let's meet face to face.
I can go to you.
I'll go to you.
Okay.
I'll contact you when it's fixed.
podcasts
wife
Let me take a look at you.
I miss you so much.
Stick the ticket on your forehead.
I want to tell you something.
want to seereview.
Will it be a new task?
What do you mean?
Honey,
I know it's hard to split up.
I'm busy with work.
I can't come to see you often.
Calm down first.
If you have any difficulties,
we can solve it together.
There's no way to solve it.
Our marriage
should have been over long ago.
What do you mean?
Our marriage should have been over long ago.
Why do we have to divorce?
All right, all right.
Don't be angry.
Don't say childish words.
I brought you a lot of things
you like to eat.
Come on.
I'm coming.
Take a look.
Sit.
Tian,
share this with your comrades.
And this.
We've been married for so many years.
We can count the days we spent together.
When you married me,
I knew very well
what you went through.
I don't want your life
to be affected because of me.
I'm telling you about this.
But you don't listen.
Well,
I'll call my parents
and ask them for their opinion.
Honestly,
we're both young.
You still have a chance to choose.
I don't find it strange
to have a girl who likes you.
Don't waste time on me.
I'm confident
to have a girl who likes me.
What if there's a guy who likes you?
Don't talk nonsense.
Since you're here,
let's settle this.
We're so close.
How can we talk about divorce?
Stop it.
I'm serious about the divorce.
I hope you can consider it seriously.
I'm leaving.
Stop right there.
I'm telling you, Wang Chen.
There's no way to get divorced.
I won't agree.
I'm leaving.
I'm sorry, Zi Jian.
I can't be so selfish anymore.
We've been living in separate places.
I can't leave the army and live with you.
And I've been
unable to give you a child.
How long have you been chased?
At least eight meters.
Good.
You were still young.
Dad, I'm telling you.
There are so many people on the street.
Otherwise, I can't catch up.
You're good, right?
You're a soldier.
You can't be so hard on him.
What if you get into trouble again?
You're so stubborn.
What's the point of this injury?
A soldier's family can't be so hurt.
You're right.
Watch your TV.
Don't take a shower these days.
It'll be better if you get some water.
I want to.
I'm going to Yangyang's graduation ceremony tomorrow.
Is your uncle Lan going too?
He wants to go.
But Yangyang doesn't allow him.
He's afraid that he'll be scared.
So his family status is the same as mine.
You've been
doing this for four years.
Do you understand?
You know how to fix it?
I know how to fix it.
But I've been in college for four years.
I fixed it for you with my eyes closed.
Come down.
Why are you standing so high?
Are you tall?
I'll leave it to you.
Please fix it soon.
Please. It's not a good thing.
Who did you fix it for?
A friend who is brave.
Okay. Look at the camera.
One, two, three.
We graduated.
Okay.
One, two, three.
Great.
You finally graduated, little ancestor.
Xi Xi.
When did you come?
You're here early.
We've been watching you for a long time.
You promised to come on this big day.
Can you not come?
I finally graduated.
It's such a big day.
How can we celebrate it?
Let's go and have some milk tea.
Military doctor?
The South China Sea Army started recruiting.
My dad sent me an application form every day.
He wanted to send it to the army directly.
It's not easy to be a military doctor.
You're a big uncle now.
Can't you shake your hand?
I can.
I'm not just shaking my hand, I'm also dizzy.
You're a medical student.
You're dizzy.
You have the nerve to say that.
It's not fair.
Uncle Tang asked you to choose your own major
and choose your job.
The gap between dad and dad is too big.
How about we change it?
Let's let Mr. Tang urge you to marry every day.
Feel it.
Did you find the life-saving man?
It's not that easy.
The confidentiality rules are so strict.
Wait.
Give me the paper.
No.
It's for you.
50 pieces of paper, a good collection.
Get lost.
Okay.
I'll take it back to comfort Cheng Yuan.
He's not the only one in our team.
No matter how you pick,
Cheng Yuan can beat you without calling you.
Didn't you say I wouldn't mention it?
Have you fixed the camera?
Yes.
Guess what I found when I fixed the camera.
You found the owner of the camera
was the one who taught you how to shoot with big eyes that day, right?
I recognized it on the first sight.
You haven't recognized me yet.
You won't recognize me in the future.
The mission is over.
We have no relationship.
I don't want you to get into trouble.
He has.
I'll make you suffer.
I took the camera from Qing a few days ago.
I happened to break the camera.
I asked the crew to fix it for me.
After fixing it,
I asked him to send it back to me.
And then?
And then it came back.
I didn't have a chance to create a chance.
You're so stubborn.
You'd better join the military camp.
There are so many people waiting in line.
Isn't this just a milk tea?
Which one you want to drink?
Why are you even here, waiting for a bingo?
The store is different.
You don't know.
Fanggin, earlier I told you
that this is my lucky shop.
What lucky shop?
In the car,
I Tob enchanted you
with a guy I used to know well.
We met here once.
You this lucky shop.
A guy.
So lucky.
Look.
How is it?
Isn't it very handsome?
It's very handsome.
But I remember that
you swore to marry a soldier since you were a child.
Did you understand the question
that the teacher just gave in class?
I didn't understand either.
I just didn't understand.
I think it's so difficult.
Really? I think it's so difficult too.
What if I have an exam soon?
What should I do?
Let's ask someone.
Okay.
What's wrong with you?
Help me take it first.
I can't take it.
I'm so tired.
Captain Song.
It's almost time.
It's time to go back to the team.
Well, you go first.
I'll be right there.
I'm back.
Are you a soldier?
I have a shopping today.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I'm leaving now.
You're leaving just after seeing me?
It's time to go back to the team.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Okay.
Don't laugh.
Is it that hard?
You don't understand.
Once love comes,
it's easy to be hurt.
I don't understand.
But the princess is happy.
We're happy.
Come on.
To celebrate that Lanyang
has achieved success in her new year,
she has a brother.
Romantic.
I'm so happy.
I have a brother.
Romantic.
Our military is so romantic.
Have you thought about
how your commander Lan
feels when he knows
you're in love?
He's been on the defensive for years.
He's afraid that Princess Lan
will join the early love.
Good.
She just graduated.
Tang Xin, I'm telling you.
You can't tell my dad about this.
I'll tell him myself.
Okay.
It's a secret.
No problem.
You have to help me.
If my camera
is not good,
I'll borrow
Ding's camera.
I'm so scared.
I'll borrow
Ding's camera.
I'm sorry.