[The Way Home]
[Episode 9]
Great-aunt,
you're losing track.
It's all over the place.
Great-aunt,
everyone here
follows your rhythm,
so you need to be steady.
You've been making the same mistake every time.
I'm sorry.
Let's do it again.
No.
How about this?
Let them rest for a bit first,
then we'll try again. Is that okay?
Okay.
All right, guys.
Let's take a 10-minute break
and grab some water.
Sound good?
- Sure. - Sure.
Great effort, everyone.
That was good.
Three,
two,
one.
Three,
two,
three,
four.
One,
two.
Take a break.
I'm quite dumb, aren't I?
I can't even get something as simple as drumming right.
Looks like I'm not just bad at studying.
I'm useless at everything.
Of course not.
This is your first time practicing,
and no one masters it on the first try.
Really?
The entry requirement for this training
is way too easy.
Literally, anyone can sign up.
Who are you talking about?
It should be obvious.
Ruonan,
it's fine if you're pursuing someone,
but isn't it a bit inappropriate
to let it affect our competition?
You're asking for trouble, aren't you?
Afu,
stop it.
It goes without saying
that once that woman gets on the boat,
she'll drag me down.
I dare you to say that again.
Sure, I'll say it.
My dad said
that in the past,
women weren't even allowed on the dragon boat.
If we lose after you get on,
can you take the blame?
This is a serious competition.
Who says women can't participate?
Besides, if a woman joins and the boat sinks,
and you guys are this useless,
it might as well just sink.
Chen Ruonan,
you should stop talking as well.
What?
Are you mad because I'm embarrassing you in front of others?
Don't lecture me about what's right.
Since we were kids,
I've always let you have the good things at home first,
and I've always let you pick the best things first.
You know full well why.
And today, I'm telling you,
I'm boarding this boat
for sure!
Actually,
this is Ruonan's first training session.
It's already impressive that she can keep up with most of it.
She just needs more time.
Also,
we're training together,
so we should be supportive of one another.
Supportive?
What do you mean by that?
You two are in perfect sync,
always looking out for each other.
When are you coming to propose to the Chen family,
the only one?
What nonsense are you talking about?
I swear I'll rip your mouth off today!
- Was I wrong in what I said? - Ruonan.
Didn't you say something wrong?
Say it again if you've got the nerve!
- Wait. - I dare you to say it again!
- Enough! - Jiahao.
What are you all doing?
Who are you?
Stand straight.
I forgot to introduce him to you all.
This
is the martial arts school's specially appointed coach,
who'll be overseeing your training camp.
You always make things difficult for me.
Didn't I tell you to stay in the office?
What are you doing out here?
Who
was causing a scene out there just now?
Sorry.
We shouldn't have fought
just now.
Let me tell you,
dragon boat racing
is all about teamwork.
Only by working together
can you reach the finish line.
And here you are, already fighting among yourselves.
It seems
that this boat will capsize before it even sets off!
Everyone, go downstairs
and run ten kilometers as punishment.
Ten kilometers?
Got a problem?
No.
Downstairs! Now!
Specially appointed coach, huh?
You really know how to cause me trouble.
I can't even make a complaint?
I'm here cleaning up your mess every day.
Maybe I should stop calling it the Chen family martial arts school
and just take the surname "He." Happy now?
Jiahao.
Thanks, Dad.
How was the training today?
Still keeping up okay?
It went well,
though my legs are a bit sore.
Have some more food.
But
the coach said I've improved.
Good,
but
finish your homework right after dinner.
No slacking off on your studies.
Got it.
Come on.
The kid knows what he's doing.
How come I'm allowed to drink today?
It's because we're in a good mood.
You can only have one can,
so go easy on it.
You're telling me to take it easy with just one can of beer?
You're something else.
Let's drink.
Drink slowly, all right?
Dad, take it easy. Here you are.
Dig in.
Have some more.
Eat some veggies.
Thanks, Mom.
Dad,
who says that after that illegitimate kid leaves,
the He family will be left with no heirs?
I think Jiahao
is much better than him.
That's Jiashu,
your nephew.
How can you call him that?
He's not my nephew.
I have nothing to do with him.
Listen.
I'm getting older,
and I've come to terms
with a lot of things.
Even though
he's not from our bloodline,
he's still
a part of the He family.
After all these years,
it's time
to let go of that grudge.
Why not
bring Jiashu back to the family?
What do you think?
Dad,
you should get some rest.
I'll head out now.
Jiahao.
Auntie told me to bring medicine to Grandpa.
All right.
Go ahead.
Dad.
Why?
What do you mean, why?
Why can't you accept my cousin?
He didn't do anything wrong.
How many times have I told you?
You don't have a cousin.
Try this.
Rong.
Why are you only having alcohol and no food?
Is it not to your liking?
Hello, who is this?
Lin Junrong,
when will you pay the outstanding amount?
If you don't have the money,
I'll give it to someone else.
Bro,
just give me two more days, please.
No more time for you,
today's the deadline.
If you don't have the money,
the deal's off,
and I'll look for a new buyer.
Fine.
Then refund my deposit.
What deposit?
You're the one breaching the contract.
It's clearly stated in the agreement
that the deposit is non-refundable.
What do you mean?
Are you trying to cheat me out of my money?
Listen.
Return the deposit to me,
or
I'll sue you.
Sue me if you like,
but the deposit won't be returned.
Hello?
What's wrong, Rong?
Why are you so worked up?
It's nothing.
Just some minor business issues.
The nightclub?
What's going on?
As I mentioned earlier,
I invested in a project,
and I'm just a little short of funds.
Xiqiao is so nice,
with gorgeous scenery and lovely people.
I really want to stay,
but if I can't find the money,
I'll have to go back home
and wrap up the business.
How much do you need to keep things going?
One million.
Fifty thousand is also fine.
You know I'm running a small business,
so I can't come up with the money.
But don't worry,
while you're staying here with me,
food and drink are all taken care of.
There's still one more dish.
I'll bring it out.
Penny-pinching.
Rong,
the shrimp today is really fresh.
Eat up,
then you'll be able to sleep.
Thank you, Jiashu.
It's so tasty.
Would you like another bowl then?
One bowl is enough for me.
Jiashu,
I was in such a rush when I came out,
I forgot my wallet.
I asked you to come out.
Do you think I'd let you pay?
Stop being silly.
Just eat.
Jiashu,
why do you think
everyone enjoys sweet food?
Is it because we all
feel a bit unhappy sometimes?
I guess.
Why do people get unhappy?
It's because
they think too much.
But you can't just not think at all, can you?
That would make you a fool.
What's wrong with being a fool?
Just look at Long.
Isn't he doing just fine?
Is he aware
of what you're saying about him?
If he is aware,
then he won't be a fool, would he?
That actually makes sense.
Go ahead and eat.
Jiashu,
I'd like another bowl of what you've got.
I think
I forgot to bring money as well.
You didn't bring any money either?
Then...
Then what are we going to do?
Sir.
Excuse me,
two more bowls, please.
Sure.
Dig in. My treat.
You're back.
Perfect timing. Come over for dinner.
I'm not eating.
Don't mind her.
Junli, come over and eat.
Junli.
How did the training go?
It went well.
By the way,
He Jiahao also went to train.
Is that so?
I was wondering why He Hongguang has been so confident lately.
Turns out this is the reason.
I've never heard of He Jiahao knowing how to row,
and He Jiashu never taught him.
What is the He family thinking?
They've put a rookie on the team
just to save face.
This is lowering the level of our village.
Dad.
Come here and sit down.
What exactly happened to the He family?
Why did He Jiashu leave?
You don't understand.
You were just a kid at the time.
Their family was a mess.
Why was it a mess?
He Hongxiao was cuckolded by his wife,
and that child
isn't even his.
He Jiashu
really isn't a member of the He family?
What's so surprising?
He Hongxiao was so sick.
It's no wonder his wife ran off with someone.
As for the details,
I don't really know
or understand,
but there are all kinds of rumors.
Some say she ran off with someone,
others say she took the money and left.
Either way, it's not good.
Listen to me, Junli,
their family's cursed,
so don't get involved with them.
Why say such things in front of the child?
What?
They have the cheek to do it, but I'm not allowed to talk about it?
He Hongxiao
was always sick,
yet his wife didn't even care
and she went out all the time.
I said back then
that something was bound to happen.
But I never expected it
to blow up like this.
Isn't this ruining the reputation
of our Xiqiao village?
If I were He Hongxiao,
I'd be furious too.
[Xiqiao No.1 High School]
[Parent-teacher meeting on Friday]
The parent-teacher meeting
should have been held after the last midterm exam,
but
the school kept having events that got in the way.
This week,
we will definitely hold the meeting.
Don't forget to inform your parents
after school on Friday evening.
The class is over.
What should we do?
[Junyilong Sports Club]
Today's training went well.
We'll continue tomorrow.
What's wrong?
Jiashu,
can you attend the parent-teacher meeting for me?
Our school is having one this week,
and my grades have dropped quite a bit.
I'm afraid if my dad goes,
he'll get upset and lose face.
If he gets angry, he might stop me from rowing.
So, Jiashu,
can you attend it for me?
I know
you don't want too many people to see you.
It's okay.
Don't feel pressured.
I
will just have my dad go instead.
I heard your kid did well in the exams this time.
Hao.
Jiashu.
You came.
Then I'll go in
and have a word with the teacher.
No need.
I've spoken with your teacher, Qiu Qiu.
Is this your classroom?
I'm going in.
[He Jiahao]
[Welcome, parents, and thank you for your advice and presence.]
All the parents are here, right?
Okay.
You are all here.
Now, Ms. Qiu Qiu,
could you pass out the report cards?
Okay.
This report includes grades for all subjects,
the overall score,
and the ranking within the grade.
Afu.
You are the parent
of Junli and Ruonan.
[Chen Junli, ranked 1st in the class and 1st in the grade]
Your son got first place.
That's impressive.
Oh, it's nothing special.
[He Jiahao, ranked 10th in the class and 19th in the grade]
Welcome, parents.
This is our first parent-teacher meeting
of the second semester of 11th grade.
As you've noticed,
the results of this exam
show significant changes
in many students' performances,
with some experiencing major drops in their scores.
Of course,
this is partly due to the increased difficulty
and intensity of the curriculum this semester.
Therefore, we encourage
collaboration
between parents and teachers
to keep a close eye on students' performance.
On a positive note,
there are also students
who have achieved great results
and made remarkable progress.
For example, Chen Junli
from our class
took first place this time,
and he's also the top student in the entire grade.
Now, let's invite
Chen Junli's parent
to share a few words
and some insights.
I'm sure you all know me.
You know our family
used to be in the transportation business,
and we were just some uneducated folks.
I never went to school
in my life.
But
the people I respect most
are those who are well-educated.
Back then, we didn't have the resources to go to school,
so it wasn't an option.
That's why now,
we're working ourselves to the bone to earn money,
so the next generation
can get an education
and change their lives with knowledge.
Don't you agree?
So, you could say
that the heavens have been fair.
My son is showing his worth.
He's the one putting in the effort.
I can't do much to help him,
other than offer
encouragement.
I just ask him,
"Are you really okay with always being behind others?"
Of course not.
Right?
People from Xiqiao Village
are known for their toughness.
We should always do our best to uphold our pride.
Isn't that right?
Do you have anything else to add?
Well,
I didn't see He Jiahao's father today.
I mean
Jiahao has always been the top scorer,
but he seems to have slipped this time.
About studying,
I believe
we shouldn't only share our successes,
but also our failures.
Don't you think?
So,
is Mr. He not here today?
He Jiahao's cousin is here.
His father is sick.
He's sick?
Such bad timing.
I've never seen him fall ill
when his son was top of the class.
I've never seen him fall ill, you know.
Anyway,
since his cousin is here,
let's have him
share some experience with us.
Let's give him a round of applause!
It's true
that Jiahao didn't do that well this time,
but it's not that bad.
Look.
He's ranked 10th in the class,
with dozens of classmates
behind him.
Besides,
no one stays at the top forever,
and no one is always at the bottom.
After all,
anything is possible.
Exactly.
My son Afu's performance isn't too bad either.
Right?
From the moment we're born,
the whole world starts scoring us:
doctors,
parents,
teachers, classmates, and even partners.
They all want us
to be flawless and live up to their ideals.
Gradually,
we start holding ourselves to the same expectations.
But
we are only human,
not omnipotent.
We can't please everyone.
So,
when I saw your exam results,
to be honest,
I was happy.
I wanted to take this chance to tell you:
Hao,
you're not "Number One"
or "Top Student."
You're simply He Jiahao.
♪A playful June drizzle♪
♪Shadows of trees can't fully cover♪
♪The fading little sun♪
♪The raindrops fall against our will♪
♪Passing in a flash♪
♪Hiding in the reflection of a mirror♪
♪Dreams too deep to wake from♪
♪Even moss wears a flowery coat♪
♪Listening to the rain fall here♪
♪We nod, like quiet sighs♪
♪Hearts weighed down, damp and heavy♪
♪Watching the relentless downpour♪
♪So unreasonable♪
♪A brief pause♪
♪And you come to mind♪
♪Watching the rainy season fade away♪
♪The summer breeze quiets down♪
♪I can't bring myself to lift my pen♪
♪Before I could♪
♪Tell you♪
♪It's bad weather♪
♪And I've rewritten the past all wrong♪
♪I wish I could hold onto that clearing sky♪
♪The mist rising as we pass through♪
♪Rain-soaked alleys♪
♪Watching the relentless downpour♪
♪So unreasonable♪
♪A brief pause♪
♪And you come to mind♪
♪Watching the rainy season fade away♪
♪The summer breeze quiets down♪
♪I can't bring myself to lift my pen♪
♪Before I could♪
♪Tell you♪
♪It's bad weather♪
♪And I've rewritten the past all wrong♪
♪Maybe luck is still on my side♪
♪Maybe my wild dreams♪
♪Can go on♪