We'll be going now, sir.
Yes, sir.
They're on their way.
What time is it?
Can I ask you something?
These are the supplies
for the shoot.
- Production?
- You can let him handle that.
Yeah, I'll take that.
Hello Direk, good morning.
Hello, where are you?
Yeah, I'm here at the location.
We're inside the building.
Come here for orientation.
Yes sir, will do.
Hello?
Yeah, just send me a link, I'll read it.
Bye! Call you later. Bye!
Ya?
Hand me my iPad, Ya.
Thank you.
"Beatriz, the Has-been Bold Star﻿"
Who wrote this?
"Time has finally caught
up to Beatriz the bold star"
"as she s﻿lowly withers away down there."
"Moralists can only grit their teeth"
as the brazen little
beaver goes on her way."
"So, what new trash
is this stupid broad--"
"--who was never really that pretty
to begin with--trying to do now?"
"She has a cameo appearance in a film"
"masquerading as a socially relevant
piece but is really just selling sex."
"It's a challenge to hold back vomit"
"seeing Granny Beatriz
banging on camera"
"in a project with a lesser known
starlet who can out-act her."
What the--
"The girl-on-girl action turns you off"
"because said bold star
is horizontally-challenged."
Excuse me?
"The screen is always
full because she's so fat,"
"and gravity's catching up on her,
judging by her saggy breasts."
"It's an embarrassment to her
scene partner's perky breasts."
"The worst element of
her cameo appearance is"
"the character she plays--a
woman of power who abuses"
"the weakness and
situation of her partner."
"She does not uplift her,
but instead corrupts her"
"and pays her for sexual trysts."
"Dear god, in this day and age,"
"do we still have to portray
women as the weaker sex,"
"who must sell their bodies
for money and pleasure?"
What the fuck?
Fucking "Alawi."
I'm going to beat you with my Urian award.
Why are you even
bothering with those?
They're doing their jobs.
Your job is to act
and you're good at it.
End of story.
If I see that writer in person,
I'll smack him with your Cinemalaya trophy!
Ya, get this out of my sight.
I might smash it to pieces.
My god, he makes my blood boil.
Looks like Direk Andoy is already here.
Have my things ready, alright?
Yes, ma'am.
Don't forget my makeup kit.
- Don't forget the extra bag too.
- Okay.
I'll be needing that later.
Yes, ma'am.
- I want those revisions done.
- Direk!
Beatriz!
Morning guys!
My brilliant actress!
So, how are you?
Still on the yummy side.
Oh yes!
You never fade and
never cease to amaze.
I only take after you.
You liar!
Oh I almost forgot,
thanks by the way.
If it weren't for you,
we wouldn't have gotten
Syquia﻿ Apartments as our location.
Well actually,
a lot of productions wanted the schedule
but I really fought for this.
You liar! You're lucky they said yes.
Yeah, definitely.
They were so concerned about
their image that they didn't want to.
So, guess what I did.
I broke out into an entire monologue
and went on until they got fed up!
What did they say?
What did you say?
I really can't remember.
But it was long. I improvised everything.
You're going to be proud.
But yeah, the thing is
I didn't sleep well last night.
We were shooting up until 5 AM.
And I came all the way from Tiaong.
So if it's alright, I want to ask the
crew to keep it down while they set up.
I just need some rest before
my scenes later, you know?
Of course, no problem.
I'll do it for you.
Whoever makes a peep on set,
gets his cock sucked.
You're such a pig!
Wait, we haven't discussed my role here.
Oh! Okay.
Since your scenes come
later in the day, so your role is...
Darling?
Yes, Direk?
Did you get all that?
Yeah, yeah, of course!
I remember, I've already read it.
I'm just really sleepy.
That's fine. Go get your beauty rest.
Oh, later then.
- Let's talk later, alright?
- Yes, we'll chat.
I'll have the PA call you later.
I missed you!
Well naturally, I missed you too!
Darling, come here!
Art Department!
What are you doing there?
- Set all that up here!
- Oh my god! -
We've actually worked
together on "Binayo."
- Oh yeah! I remember!
- Yes!
I used to bring you your
costume and the lav.
I think you've gotten bigger,
that's what threw me off.
Oh don't say that!
Actually, I've been cutting.
I'm on less carbs now
and I've been working out.
Good for you.
Oh, I almost forgot.
This is Roswill, he'll be
our script supervisor.
Casey's our PA.
You can ask her to do anything.
This is Jico.
He's our intern.
Be nice to him, alright?
Oh yeah, I'll be nice.
Hi Jico.
Hi.
Anyway, how've you been?
It's been what? Ten years?
Yeah, I think so.
Ten years since we last
worked together. Wow.
Do you remember our AP then?
Oh my god!
I honestly want to forget.
I know, right?
Oh my god, wow!
I'm so excited to work
with you again, Beatriz!
I'm so excited.
I'll be in my unit if you need me.
Alright, we'll call you
- when you're scenes are next, okay?
- Bye, Jico.
Alright.
Take care!
What are you standing around for?
What about you?
Why don't you start working?
What are you doing there?
Is that what we're paid for?
Staring out into space?
You're hopeless! Give me that.
Hello, hello, check.
Can you hear me alright?
Everyone gather round.
Ma'am, I'll be going now.
Oh okay, I'll call you later.
Take care.
Whoever fucks around,
will answer to me.
Is that understood?
Okay? Okay.
Before I forget, Roswil,
make sure Loretta learns her lines.
I want them rehearsed
until they're perfect.
Last time we ran those,
we took until Take 55!
We used up all the cards!
I want you on top of that, alright?
And Casey, what about,
what about catering?
Did you check on them?
Baby girl, get us some coffee please.
Jico,
how many copies of the
script did you print out?
Uh, three.
Only three?
What's wrong with you?
We have tons of paper.
And oh yeah,
I saw how Beatriz was looking at you.
- I didn't like that.
- It's nothing.
Don't worry.
Nothing? You were practically
showing off your dimples!
I noticed that, you know.
Stop that!
There, see?
You did that! Hey!
Be careful, she likes them young.
All I'm saying is concentrate on
work because it's your first day.
I don't want you to embarrass
yourself or even me. Okay?
I know how hard you work.
You'll do great.
Of course I will.
Just do what I do.
Because it's your first day and
we have to be in sync, okay?
Thanks.
Alright?
And keep your phone on silent.
Hey you, let's go.
We're going to see Direk.
Oh wow! Everything's
moving in slow motion!
Fuck, bro.
That Ms. Beatriz?
She's THE pornstar.
See how she passed by earlier?
She was like a fucking whirlwind!
How old is she?
She's getting on in years.
But before it all went digital,
she'd take on multiple shoots at once.
What a MILF!
I know, right?
I'd jerk off to every scene of hers.
What's that movie of hers?
Yeah, "Freakshow".
Did she play that
prostitute at the circus?
What the fuck? You saw that?
- I jerked off on that too!
- You motherfucker!
You should've said so.
That's my favorite film too!
What about "Paninda sa Suka ni Mang Juan"?
She was fucking great in that!
Bro...
Okay, so you walk through here,
wide-eyed and full of hope and dreams.
Right here.
Look around and then,
yes. Like that.
Look around the space, like that.
Hold his hand, here, like that.
This is where you
deliver your lines, okay?
Mind your marks, remember them, alright?
Don't miss them.
This is a tight frame
and this is where it's lit.
Because when it's bright, there's light.
Remember that.
Don't forget your lines too, make it count.
Ram, let's go! Let's go!
Actors, to your positions.
Roswil, aren't there
supposed to be two of these?
Art Department!
Weren't there two of these?
Move them there!
Why is Spongebob here?
Remove that!
We've got a lot to shoot.
Double time! Faster!
- Let's go!
- Right away, Direk!
- Let's go, now!
- Double time!
- Ready!
- This isn't a rehearsal take!
This is a take!
Okay, ready!
"Naked Heaven", Scene 16, Take 1!
Action!
Do not fret.
No one will know where we are.
That's not mine.
Where's it coming from?
Cut!
What the fuck?
Whose phone is that?
Speak up, right now!
You out there,
whose phone is that?
Anyone?
Will no one answer me?
Direk!
It was mine.
Sorry.
Hide it already.
Sorry, Direk.
You motherfuckers.
You're ruining my art.
Sorry, Direk.
I'll handle this.
Sorry.
From the top!
Direk, sorry. We didn't
mean to ruin your art.
Shut up!
- Let's go!
- Right away.
Double time!
Art Department!
Didn't you reset?
We're doing another one! Take two!
And...
We'll talk later.
Take two.
Can we move any slower?
Excuse me, Clapper, take two.
Take two.
Ready...
"Naked Heaven"﻿, Scene 16, Take 2!
Action!
Do not fret.
No one will know where we are.
Thank you. If it were not for--
Sorry.
- Sorry.
- She's sorry, Direk.
- Sorry, Direk.
- Cut!
My dear, you're driving me insane.
- Can we have her read--
- Right away, Direk.
Unbelievable! Why does--
Give me that!
See this? Read this!
Read it!
- Sorry, sorry.
- Are you okay?
You did great.
As for this one,
just go sit down and read that.
Read that!
Then, we'll go from the top.
Roswil!
What was that?
Why didn't she memorize that?
You had all day in the dressing room!
You had her retouch too much.
See? Retouching made her dumber.
"Another legend about
the homely woman is,"
"her inability cry for scenes
that need actual tears."
What the fuck?
This Alawi bitch, why would she say
I'm trying to stay relevant?
"...a job whore taking every mediocre
project she can get her hands on."
Say that to my fucking
nominations and awards!
You bitch!
You've got some nerve
calling me a job whore!
I don't take on every
project that comes around,
I'm just in demand!
You salty fucking dick!
Do not fret.
No one will know where we are.
My thanks.
If it were not for your cunning,
I would never have escaped
Father's ill treatment.
There is no need for that.
It is my honor and
responsibility as your beau,
to safeguard you from
suffering and harm.
And if you'll allow,
I will always be so, from now on.
If your wish is
that I be at peace
with our situation,
then do not, Anselmo.
I need not become your responsibility.
Cut!
Okay.
Good take.
Let's go.
I want this side now.
We're changing angles.
Okay, Direk.
Jason!
- Day for night!
- We need to talk.
That was unacceptable.
I told you to keep your phone on silent.
- Ram?
- Yes, Direk?
I want this all moved, alright?
Copy, Direk.
- Everything must be out of frame.
- Copy, Direk.
Also, day for night.
You all know what to do.
Well?
They're setting up out there!
What are you sitting around for?
You're playing MOBAs in here? Really?
- But we've setup in advance.
- Advanced setup?
There's no advanced setup!
Don't try to fool me!
As for you,
I've already been over this with you,
when we're at work,
keep your phone on silent.
You're making me look
bad in front of the director.
Sorry,
I really didn't mean to.
You know I'm doing this for you, right?
I don't want this kind
of embarrassment for us.
It's a bad impression
for your first day.
What if they replace us next time?
You know, I really don't--
I'm really sorry.
Sorry.
Just make a streak through here,
so it'll really look
like it's day, alright?
Okay, Roswil, come with me.
Where's Ram? Ram?
Yes, Direk?
Make sure it doesn't
happen next time, okay?
- Promise.
- Treat me to coffee later.
Yes, Direk. I'm coming, Direk.
I'll take care of it. Ram?
Yes, Direk?
Direk, this next one--. Sorry.
This next one--
Well? How many do we have left?
We still have five sequences
on day effect, exterior.
We then have eight on day effect,
all of them interior.
Two of those are the room scenes.
Bro,
Direk is asking for coffee.
What'd you say?
- Direk is asking for coffee, black.
- Direk's asking?
Are you ordering me to?
Maybe it's you asking for coffee.
"Direk" my ass.
There's the coffee.
It's staring you in the face.
Do it yourself.
You're new here.
Don't order us around like some big shot.
You're the intern, right?
Is this your first time?
- Yes.
- Yes, sir.
What about Beatriz?
When are we shooting her scenes?
Direk, after dinner.
There are three scenes here, so
two of those just need the
same setup as the room scenes.
They just need to be lit for night.
If we do it after dinner,
we can squeeze her in.
Alright, first thing after dinner,
set up her scenes, okay?
Okay, sir.
Let's do breaks in shifts so
everything happens at once.
- Then we'll do takes right after dinner.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Yes?
- Direk, here's your coffee.
Oh, he means me. That's mine.
How about you, Direk?
Would you like some?
Oh, I don't drink instant coffee.
Okay, get going.
The staff might need you.
So, Direk,
for our next three scenes with Beatriz,
we'll be back in the living room again.
As for the picture vehicle, I didn't--
What's his name?
You mean the picture vehicle, Direk?
- I mean, what's his name?
- Who?
Who do you mean, Direk?
What's his name?
- My god! You're blushing!
- Who?
Hey!
What are you? A flower?
You're shrinking like a flower.
Stop it, Direk!
Why so shy?
Girl, I can't even see you.
You're so small right now.
- No, Direk, he might hear us.
- Just say it. Say it.
- Jico.
- Wow, sounds foreign.
No, he's not Direk.
You know these foreigners,
they love themselves a Pinay.
Direk, stop!
He's from Pampanga.
We met him at the festival there.
Jesus Christ.
What's this all of a sudden?
It's nothing!
You're driving me crazy, Direk!
You're driving me crazy!
You're acting like a school girl!
God, why am I sweating?
You're sweating because you're fat!
- That's low, Direk.
- Why? Think I'm blind?
I don't even touch
rice anymore, Direk.
You replaced that
with beer, though.
What do you think of me, Direk?
It's the stress getting to me, is all.
Is that really stress or something else?
But, is he good though?
At what?
Huh? "At what?"
You slut!
Well, no, I just meant...
He likes to eat "kimchi".
That's a good one, "kimchi".
I can't, Direk!
"Kimchi."
How'd you even do that, Direk?
Sorry, sorry.
I just can't, oh my god.
- It feels amazing, Direk.
- My god, really?
Yes it does.
Is it something like this?
Direk, it's bigger than that.
Oh my! Really?
Yes, Direk.
Lord almighty!
He doesn't look it but,
it's so fat, Direk.
Stop with the revelations.
I can't handle this.
My gag reflex isn't even ready!
Direk, he's a grower too.
It's unbelievable!
I thought it was nothing
at first and then...
"Hello!"
It was looking for sunlight, Direk!
Hold on! Wait!
All wet!
Direk, I couldn't handle it!
Good thing I got to him first.
Better me than Poizon.
Poizon looked all menacing too.
- Yeah he does!
- Totally unlikeable!
I on the other hand was all...
I told you foreigners love
themselves a Pinay.
All I needed was a spear
and I'd have been an amazon.
I want you to line up
all that's left to shoot.
We have to work faster
when we resume.
I don't want things to stall.﻿ And
make sure all phones are on silent.
- Okay, will do.
- Phones. Silent.
You know,
back in the day,
I was there where you
are, PA and Script Con.
Who did you work for?
For whoever was there.
I've already lost count.
Joel Lamangan, Chito Roño, Mario J.,
all the old ones. I got to be on their set.
All of them.
I did continuity, locations,
and,
I even did utility and craft services.
Yeah, I know all those jobs.
I just loved the profession,
until one day I got to be the AD.
But the thing is,
nobody gives out an award for Best AD.
Right?
By the way,
when we resume,
give Beatriz a copy of the script
and go through lines with her.
Okay.
Just so everything goes smoothly.
Motherf--
Baby Girl!
What the--
What the fuck are these?
What kind of cheap
plastic did you get?
Did it break, Direk?
Unbelievable!
Can you change these already,
so I can finish and get back to work?
Hello?
Hi, babe.
I just came from taping,
and I'm resting right now
before I start shooting again.
Yeah, I've already had some sleep.
Oh, stop!
If you don't stop, I'll
tear your clothes off.
Well,
what am I wearing?
Do you remember my red robe?
Yes, your favorite one.
Yeah!
I'm wearing it right now.
Alright.
I'll send you a selfie later.
Sir Roswil, I just got upstairs.
Which one is Ms. Beatriz's room number?
If you're facing the set, go right.
If you're facing the stairs, go left.
Copy?
Left?
Jico,﻿ did you get that?
Yes, yes, copy.
Thank you, sir.
Would you like that?
Wait a second.
Ya?
Babe sorry, yeah. Someone's at the door.
I know, I know! I miss you too!
Wait.
Ya!
Sorry babe, we'll have
to finish another time.
I'm gonna call you back, okay?
Alright, bye!
Ya!
Ya?
Yaya!
Yaya?
Oh come on, yaya.
Unbelievable.
Why'd you do this yaya?
What the hell do you want?
Ma'am?
I didn't know it was you, handsome.
Ma'am, I'm so sorry.
I didn't know you were sleeping.
Oh that's fine.
I didn't know it was you, cutie.
Are you our PA on set?
I'm the intern, ma'am.
Oh you young interns,
you always get starstruck so easily.
Don't just stand there. Come in!
Sit down, don't be shy.
Oh, no need ma'am.
Don't be like that, have a seat.
- Sit.
- Okay.
Well you seem happy.
Was it something you saw?
Ma'am?
Wait, what's your name again?
Ji-Jico, ma'am.
"Ji-Ji-Jico?﻿"
Why are you stuttering?
Don't be so tense.
Oh not at all.
I'm fine, ma'am.
Was it something you saw?
Ma'am?
Wait, what are you doing?
Do you need anything?
Do you want anything?
I wanted to give you
your copy of the script.
Oh, is this my copy?
Oh!
Wait, can I get you anything?
Would you like some juice?
Would you like
some coffee?
No, no, I'm fine. That's okay.
I have some cold beer.
I'll just take a coffee then.
Jico?
Yes, Direk?
Where the hell are you?
I'm still with Ma'am Beatriz.
Hurry on back. They're looking for you.
Alright, I'm coming back.
Jico, here's your coffee!
Oh ma'am, I have to go.
Direk, needs me on set.
Oh, but I just made you your coffee.
Thank you ma'am, but I have to go.
Oh alright.
We wouldn't want Direk to be angry.
Bye, Jico.
Okay, good take. Next sequence!
80, 50, 35, 72 are all the same setup.
Cross out number 19 and 20,
and yeah, all of that too.
Uh, girl, go check
on the Wardrobe.
Direk will lose it if they
make any more mistakes.
- Direk, what about this?
- Oh!
By the way, that scene,
the one on the veranda,
we're dropping that.
And the one where Loretta's looking out
the window, we're dropping that too.
We won't be able to get to that.
I'll just check on with Direk, okay?
Baby girl, why don't you check if
anyone wants water you lazy bum!
Hey!
What?
Does she smell nice?
She does!
- What?
- She smells nice!
- What are you talking about?
- She smells so nice!
Did she touch you?
Did you see the rack on her?
Who do I even play?
I don't even know.
They're probably in the middle of a take.
Jico!
Ma'am?
Jico,﻿ could you come up?
I need your help, please.
Okay ma'am, I'm on my way.
Thank you.
Lucky bastard.
Come in.
So, you know,
I'd really appreciate some help,
and dine with me, I ordered some--
Oh, come on!
Why are you being so shy?
I just have some questions,
and I was about to have snacks.
Join me, okay?
Sit down.
Come on, here.
- Ma'am?
- Sit, come on.
Good.
I just ordered some
chicken wings.
These are so good.
On top of that, you're
going to shoot for hours later,
you need to rest.
Baby girl, is this your
first film working together?
Yes.
Wow, you guys' coordination is amazing.
You were ready with your
tongue in an instant a while ago.
You're so good, it's insane!
Yeah, she works different.
She does.
Girl,
the script says she's got curls!
Stop combing her hair.
You need rollers for her.
- Direk Ram?
- Yes?
Direk wants an update right away.
Oh he does?
Tell him we're almost ready.
Okay, get ready guys
we're starting soon.
Just move, double time, okay?
Actually, Jico,
I really need your help.
Because--
Who do I even play?
This is so embarrassing.
I don't even know.
Who do I play?
Uh, one moment ma'am.
Actually, ma'am, you play
Mariel.
Oh, Mariel.
- Nice name.
- She's getting on in years,
so she's mature.
But she chooses a younger
guy because she wants to try...
Try what?
Come on, tell me.
- Don't be shy.
- His... you know.
His what?
His...
His?
- What is it?
- His sexual drive.
Oh!
Is that so?
Oh my god.
What an exciting part.
Wait, let me see.
Oh wow, the dialogue
exchanges are amazing.
This is great writing!
Oh my god! Oh wow!
Is this scene really in here?!
In a period film?
Oh my god!
Oh my god, I'm really excited.
You know,
how exciting!
Wow!
It's all so intense!
The writing's so intense.
And I think,
this is exactly what I need.
It's perfect timing for me!
This is it!
Come here!
Come! Sit with me!
Come here! Hurry!
I want to share my excitement.
Wait, who was the writer for this?
You know,
I have a feeling that
the writer is bald.
Oh yeah!
I have an idea.
Why don't we go over the lines?
- Okay, ma'am.
- Yeah?
Yeah! Okay!
Umm...
Wait.
I feel like,
I feel like I'd be comfortable in my room.
Oh no, but Direk might need me on set.
My god, you think I
wouldn't look out for you?
I'll take care of you.
I want to throw lines but,
it's really hot in here.
I have air conditioning in my room.
Oh no,
this is a bad idea.
Come on!
It's just so hot in here,
I cannot concentrate.
We should be fine here, ma'am.
Maybe for you it
is but for me it's not.
Let's go to my room,
it's cooler there. Come on.
See? I told you.
It's so much more comfortable,
it's cooler here.
I can concentrate better now.
Okay, why don't you start reading?
Oh. don't be so shy!
This is exciting!
Mariel's foot slowly makes
its way to Bryan's thighs.
- Oh my god. Really?
- Yes, ma'am.
Don't stop now, keep reading!
Continue!
And then what happens?
Bryan's hand begins to
massage Mariel's left breast.
"Bryan's hand begins to
massage Mariel's left breast?"
Don't be shy. I need your help.
Why'd you stop?
I'm a method actor, you know.
I have to rehearse everything I
do before going on camera.
Just so it looks natural.
You get how method acting works right?
Yes, ma'am.
So, do you believe in method acting?
I do, ma'am.
You know, a lot of people are saying
that I can't even act anymore.
Do you believe them?
Not at all!
I thought you were great
in your Cinemalaya movies.
So,
you know what I do.
I do, ma'am.
So,
you understand my process.
I do, ma'am.
Good boy.
Alright, continue.
What comes next?
Jico?
Give me an update!
You've been there a while.
It's almost time for you.
We're still here.
We're here.
What?
Say again, Jico.
Hi, Ram.
What year do you plan to roll?
We're almost done setting up, Direk.
Setting what up? That's all
you've done today. Let's go!
- Let's go!
- Yes, Direk.
Finish up there, let's go!
I want an update on Jico.
Jico?
Hello, Roswil.
Where are you?
They're looking for you.
I'm here with Ms. Beatriz, we're...
We're throwing lines.
Okay, alright.
So what did he say?
He and Beatriz are throwing lines.
- Throwing lines? Why would--
- Let's go!
Yes, Direk!
Keep following up on them.
Okay, ready!
Slate!
"Naked Heaven"﻿, Scene 22, Take 2!
Action!
"Old Apartment, Night, Exterior,"
"Mariel slowly undresses Bryan,"
"and kisses him on the neck."
"Mariel's playful lips begin
to travel upon Bryan's body."
"She starts from the neck,
and creeps further down."
"Bryan winces as he begins to feel
the mix of tingling and pleasure."
"Mariel peels away all
of his undergarments."
"She then confidently puts his genitals
in her mouth and begins to suckle."
"Mariel relishes the act as the
man clings to his consciousness."
"Bryan returns the favor with his lips
and runs them from her neck,"
"all the way down to her genitals
already quivering with anticipation."
"Mariel struggles to maintain her sanity."
"As Bryan observes her contortions."
"he beams with pride."
"The oral play continues on the stairway."
"And why not?"
"Certainly, the tongue can reach
her button easily from this angle."
"As their tongues grow tired,"
"Bryan lifts her up on to the bed
and brutally makes love to her."
"Stroke for stroke, they
throw all caution to the wind."
Cut!
Oh my god!
That's so wonderful!
Hurry up!
Give them the robes!
That's so magical, I love it!
Did you like that, Direk?
You were so good! My god!
It's very organic! I love it!
Okay so now, let's proceed to
the next sequence. Let's go!
- Okay.
- Set this all up. It's time for Beatriz!
- Let's go!
- AC's, get the camera set up.
I want this angle, let's go.
What an amazing script!
I never thought,
I'd be given the part!
Oh, do you want some of this?
- I actually don't touch the stuff.
- Oh it's just one puff.
Come on. Now you say no? Really?
What did you think of my performance?
God! That was a well-written script.
It was good.
What they said about you was wrong.
- Huh?
- You are a timeless wonder.
You're still the best.
Of course!
Jico?
Yes, sir?
Is Beatriz ready?
Yes, she's ready
for her closeup.
Oh wow, where did that come from?
You know,
I've been blessed with
an amazing "acting coach".
It's wrong, all of it!
You're rehearsing the wrong scenes.
Look at this scene. This line,
- is merged with the last sequence.
- Hi, Direk!
Hi, Direk, I'm here!
- Where's Direk?
- He's on his way.
- Ms. Beatriz!
- Oh Direk!
I'm sorry I'm late.
I just got Jico﻿ to help with my lines.
You know me, I'm always prepared.
Oh yes!
- But why isn't she in costume?
- Yeah, I was asking that too.
Oh, Wardrobe hasn't given
me my costume yet.
Wardrobe?
Come here.
Where is the nun costume for Ms. Beatriz?
Uh, Direk, what nun?
Yes darling!
You're playing a nun. That's your role!
Wait, let's just cheat and
shoot the scene over here.
Over here, let's go!
- Set it up here!
- Which one is the XL size?
- Ram!
- Yes, Direk.
Come over here!
Yes, Direk! I'm coming!
Do we set up here?
Yes, set up here!
Coming, Direk!
Direk?
Do we set up here?
Art Department!
I don't want to repeat myself!
Direk, sorry, Direk!
What do you mean sorry?
I want a set up here not an apology!
You set up everywhere except where I need!