Moonlight of Qing
Episode 18
You two,
do you want to stay or sleep?
One room upstairs.
The cheapest room on the street.
Sir,
how noisy is the room next to it?
I'm a bed-sleeper.
I can't sleep.
You'll stay upstairs.
I'll stay upstairs.
Do you want me to say more?
No, no.
But
I'll stay upstairs.
You'll stay next to it.
It's not appropriate.
You're a weirdo.
I don't want to
give you back a sore thigh.
How do you know
I'll have sore thighs
if I sleep on a cheap bed?
I... I never told you before.
I didn't expect you to care about me so much.
It's okay.
You don't want me to take you back.
No.
Stop arguing.
There's only one room left
next to it.
It's okay.
We can just make do.
Sir,
it's important to take care of the case.
The room next to it is convenient for us to observe the situation nearby.
You can just make do.
I'm
Shaoqi.
I'm a good man.
We're not...
Thank you, sir.
Hmm?
Tell them
we're at the corner.
Why me again?
This is what a good man should do.
And
bring our luggage here.
I...
Hurry up.
Don't come over.
What's going on?
Give me back my luggage.
Give it back to me.
You're dying.
She's a lunatic.
Sir,
why do you keep this kind of goods?
Kill her and avenge your wife.
Kill her.
Don't hurt her.
It's not wrong to kill people.
But we should let the government handle it.
In a few days,
it'll be the day when Zhang Qilin disappears once a month.
I suggest
we lock him up temporarily.
What if he runs away?
We'll be in big trouble.
Kill him.
We can't let him die.
Calm down, everyone.
If we keep going on our own,
what's the difference between us and the murderer?
You're a woman from a foreign village.
You're in charge of our village.
We want to avenge our lives.
Avenge our lives?
We don't want to see him.
Calm down, everyone.
Kill him.
Linglong, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Dr. Li,
wait for Gao Wanzhou.
Say something.
I can't see.
They can't hear.
What's the difference
between saying it and not saying it?
Dr. Li.
Ling'er.
Don't be impulsive.
They're monsters.
They're beasts.
You can't save them if you go to Ban'an.
And you hurt yourself.
Yes.
He's right.
But I can't watch
Erguo get killed.
Ling'er.
Beat him.
It's raining.
Drink the soup.
It'll warm you up.
Get up.
The case is about to end.
Manager Zhang's organs
are being removed once a month.
We'll have to get ready for that.
But Si Makong's wound...
It's just a lie.
You want to stay.
How did you know?
You won't hide it normally.
You can figure it out if there's anything on your mind.
And you want to stay
and investigate the case?
It's the most important thing for us
to find out where your brother is.
If we miss this opportunity,
we'll have to wait for more than a month
before we can get out of here.
Actually,
I went to Wuzhen
not just for my brother.
Why did you bring me here?
When I found the corpse,
I came here with the villagers.
This is the corpse.
On the wall over there,
there are the scars left by the two dogs.
It's me.
I left
the scars.
Young Master,
everything is fine.
You've been through many hardships
to get here.
You just came to say hello to me?
No.
I found that
Geng Zhao of the Diancha Bureau
was guarding the dead outside the Zhangji Forest.
His purpose
should be the same as that of Lian Buci.
He just wants to get Lu Jiu back.
It's not enough.
I've found out
the information you asked me to find.
The protection
is Tian Luo's unique martial arts.
For the past ten years,
the leader of Tian Luo, Dugu,
has only passed it on to one person.
It's his adopted son, Fei Ying.
Fei Ying?
The first killer of Wu Xiang City
who disappeared years ago?
Before he disappeared,
Dugu sent him
to be the leader of the Dark Sect.
He was only 13 years old that year.
Thirteen years ago,
I got a serious illness.
I don't remember anything when I wake up.
Don't look at me!
The protection
is indeed the same as your previous martial arts.
But looking at the traces,
it should be a weapon like a knife.
I've never seen a knife with a shape of a tiger's paw.
Ever since I entered this village,
I've had a feeling of familiar.
I remember you said
you had a serious illness when you were a child.
After that, all your memories are gone.
Could it be that...
I'm not sure.
But
everything
should be related to Wu Zhen.
How did you know?
Follow me.
Let's go.
Before,
I found a map of Wu Zhen
in my brother's study.
That's why I and Sima Kong
went together.
And in my memory,
this map
appeared here.
Fei Ying was young at that time.
He was strong and powerful.
He was a good model for the Demon Realm.
But I'm afraid
Tian Luo's purpose
is not just to get some silver money.
You mean
the burial goods in the tomb
are related to the Wuxiang Treasure?
Send my brother to report to the master.
Yes.
But...
But what?
If the master asks,
how did you know about the tiger's paw?
One of the assassins who assassinated Lu Jiu
had used the tiger's paw.
That makes sense.
But...
What's wrong?
Young Master,
have you been
suddenly nervous
and blushed recently?
It seems to be.
Why do you ask?
It's a beautiful place
with a beautiful scenery.
It's easy for a man and a woman to have a relationship.
I only care about them.
I've never been in love with a woman and a man.
No.
I mean
Lu Jiu.
Lu Jiu and Lin Lang are in love.
If they have a relationship
and get together,
it'll be more difficult
for the young master to get information.
I see.
You may go.
Why are you back so late?
How is it?
Everything is normal.
Why haven't you slept yet?
I found that the top of the medicine cabinet
has many unusual drugs.
They're all broken.
So I reorganized them
and moved them to the lower level
so that it's convenient for Dr. Li to take them.
Miss Xu,
thank you so much.
I could see the medicine cabinet
in the past few years.
So I made it taller.
But I couldn't see it.
It's not convenient to move the cabinet.
So I put it down.
You could see it before.
Yes.
I was a childhood sweetheart.
I learned medicine from her.
But she suddenly left me.
I cried every day.
My eyes...
Speaking of which,
the cabinet
was built when we got married.
At that time,
she helped me to organize these drugs
like Miss Xu did every day.
It's been so many years.
Dr. Li,
thank you.
We've disturbed you for so long.
It's time to leave.
You're leaving?
I've checked it.
The steam will dissipate tomorrow morning.
We can leave now.
Since the death of my wife,
my stove
has been so busy for years.
I'm really reluctant
to leave you.
Dr. Li,
we'll come back to see you
after we're done.
That's good.
You have to leave tomorrow.
Have a good rest today.
I'll leave now.
It will take another 10 days.
I didn't have time to find you.
Don't add more drama to it!
Lu Qiao,
have you slept?
No.
Do you know
what is the most important thing
that a person
and my aunt.
Although she's determined to make money,
her feelings for her husband and child
are not comparable to that of other people.
It's a pity that she's not a good person.
She's pretending to be a man and can't make money.
She even made her wife sell herself for money.
In the end,
human emotions are the most worthless things in this world.
Do you think everyone is like you?
They measure everything with money.
Let me tell you. You...
Why are you so close to me?
I'm just afraid that you...
Why are you afraid of me?
Didn't you lock the quilt?
Can you two stop arguing?
I thought you two could sleep together
and have a romantic relationship and live in peace.
Who wants to live in peace with her?
Who wants to have a romantic relationship with her?
And sleep together?
Give it to me.
Where's Li Lang?
I haven't seen him since this morning.
Yesterday, Dr. Li was in the medicine cabinet.
He had a few patients.
Maybe he went up the mountain to collect the medicine.
Then why did you go there early this morning?
I went to see Dr. Li.
I was worried that he might be sick.
I went to see him.
What did you do there early this morning?
Dr. Li said he likes to drink medicinal wine.
I made him some.
He should be able to drink it in a few days.
I didn't expect you to do this.
You don't make money.
Lin Lang and I are both grateful and generous.
Unlike someone who eats and drinks every day
and does nothing.
Okay.
I'll go get you some water.
I can see Mr. Lu Jiu water it himself.
It's rare to see him eat and drink.
If you can also drink it,
you can do some easy work like making wine.
Let me tell you.
You are...
Lin Lang didn't go to collect the medicine.
In the village,
except you and Lin Lang,
only Li Mu can make medicinal wine.
But Lin Lang said
there's medicinal wine
when Er Gou hurt him.
I...
What is this place?
Why are there so many abandoned houses?
Which is the most bad way?
Shall we go?
Later that day,
I made you someга oil.
In six times,
would six describe the feeling
of some big decidedly?
Do you know
what Nine Silent Nuns say?
And what Taoism says.
What Taoism?
but the body lacks internal organs.
So that's the reason.
Look.
This is your favorite flower.
It's just picked.
Do you like it?
Miss Xu.
Since you're here,
why are you leaving so soon?
Lu Jiu.
How is it?
I asked everyone in their village.
They didn't show up.
Let's go to the tomb.
What did you do to me?
Don't worry.
It's just some soft bone powder.
It's just so your hands and feet can't move.
You're the one who killed Ji Ergou.
You don't believe
the story of the revival of the magical flag in the magical book, do you?
I was right.
Just a few words
can tell the secret.
Medical doctor, medical doctor.
You're using the magical book.
That's false.
It's said that
blood is like water.
Water until it penetrates into your
レ
You're a chinese medicine doctor.
I tried to Tesla many times.
Though with every trial
there should be one thing left.
It's still시다
Teacher,
I fried some Tableware for you.
You killed them and took the organs out
just to save your wife.
You're really a doctor.
Do you think I want to?
We promised to protect the world
and cure the disease.
So at first,
we all tried to cure ourselves.
Oh, right.
Li Mu,
it's because we couldn't see
and it was inconvenient to move the body,
so we asked Erkou to help us.
He wouldn't have taken Li Mu
to such a far place, would he?
You mean...
Your eyes
are so blind.
Even so,
I still couldn't save him.
I was wondering
if only the organs of a woman
could bring him back to life.
I tried to find
the strongest heart,
the most delicate fingers,
and the brightest eyes.
One or two,
two or three.
But then,
the organs needed were getting more and more.
I had to find a helper.
I'll see if you can see.
I'll beat you to death, you fool.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Remember.
You're not wrong.
They are wrong.
The people wrong should all die.
All should die.
Now it's your chance to take revenge.
Cute
душ
I want you to wait for me.
Why did you use Erkang?
He shouldn't have walked on this path.
I was helping him.
Without me,
he's still being bullied by those people.
They should all die anyway.
It's useless for me to help them.
It's not worth living for nothing.
I won't let you succeed.
Lu Jiu and Sima Kong will definitely come to save me.
Save you?
When they see you again,
I'm afraid they won't recognize you anymore.
What are you going to do to me?
I changed his internal organs for him.
But it's still useless.
Instead,
it's because his body is too burdened
that he can't continue to preserve it.
You're being too self-willed.
Don't worry.
When I was about to give up,
you came.
Your passion for it
and your strength to not admit defeat
are exactly the same as him.
So I thought
since I can't preserve his body,
it's good to preserve his face.
You're going to return my face to him?
Here.
What's this?
What lock is this?
Why is it so strange?
The most secret lock in the world is the Nine-Legend Ring.
If there's no key,
only the one inside the door can open it.
Don't you need a high-level memory?
Can you unlock it?
Yes.
But I need three days.
If you can open it like this,
why do you need the Nine-Legend Ring?
I have a better way.
Bridge of
siitä
What are you trying to give me?
YouOS!
I didn't.
Why didn't you go to the bedroom with me and do anything else?
We didn't make any trouble.
We didn't need to.
It will have been easy to kill out there.
Lyu Qu!
I- I am sorry!
Godfather!
weakness
Weakness
Oh no.
Lin Lang.
Long Jiu.
How are you?
Lin Lang.
I will definitely get you out.
If it wasn't because I...
Because I was locked up.
Open your mouth.
What do I do?
There's only one pill
that Sima Kong said.
You gave it to me.
What are you going to do?
As long as you're fine,
I'll do anything.
Luo Qiao!
What are you going to do?
Luo Ming!
Don't scare me, Luo Qiao!
Wake up!
I have so much to say to you.
I won't let you die.
Luo Qiao!
Luo Qiao, you're awake.
Don't worry.
For you,
I'll live well.
Sima Kong is still outside.
We have to get out of here.
We've waited for days.
Why is there no news?
Sir, why don't we...
Sir, you've been standing by for the past two days.
You must be exhausted.
Since everyone is here,
I'll send you two to the road.
It's not that.
This blind man is not good at martial arts.
I have to deal with him with some effort.
It's only worth three to one.
You've been in a bad mood.
You didn't take the pill. I gave it to Lin Lang.
I gave him the pill.
Luo Qiao,
bring Lin Lang here.
Leave it to me.
Cut the crap!
Luo Qiao!
Luo Qiao, take Lin Lang away!
We can't leave Sima Kong alone.
I know.
Luo Qiao, don't do anything stupid.
It's not stupid to let someone you care about
be in danger.
You said you'd protect yourself for me.
Luo Qiao!
Let me make a bet.
If I win,
you'll treat me to a lifetime of sweet and bitter.
Luo Qiao.
If I lose,
I hope you can remember
that there was a person like me
in your life.
You want to die?
I'll give you a life.
Stop!
You want to hurt him?
Have you asked me?
Why are you back?
I'm still watching the master.
I hired you.
If he bullies you, then he bullies me.
You're the one who's a dog.
Even if there's one more person,
he's not my opponent.
Who said there's only one more?
I'm not your opponent.
There's only one more.
And me.
You came back on your own.
Isn't the Nine-Legend Ring
not open from the outside?
Have you forgotten?
I've been in power for a long time.
I can easily open the door that you can't open.
You two are stupid.
I'm here to support you.
I didn't ask you two to come back and kill him.
Don't say so much.
Let's just get the gift back.
You three are really unworthy of your own power.
One round twoして, one round.
Captured!
I know.
He wants to exchange me with the corpse.
It's because the corpse
can't hold on for long.
Then we'll delay the time.
In this way,
his sword skill can't be obtained.
I'm sorry.
Linglong.
Are you okay?
So no time to utensil for your
feast is a well-gotten work.
It's a **** **
He has a good idea.
I'm gonna Speed-feed
it to him.
His sword Coastal Formation
can kill brimstone and sickle
by relatives.
I want to be with you forever.
If we can meet again,
how will it be?
Thank you for looking back at this moment.
I want to be with you forever.