Do you know how much it costs to renovate this kind of commercial street
every day?
If we fail to fulfill the contract,
we'll have to pay penalties to the merchants.
I've done the calculations.
Compared to breaching the contract,
keeping the guesthouses has more significance.
Nonsense!
It can be developed into
a unique cultural experience center for guesthouses.
In the future, it will not only attract tourists,
but also serve as a business case study
to guide more diverse cultural tourism investments,
and even become a focal point for such developments.
Create a popular cultural tourism and commercial district.
From a long-term perspective, the business potential is unlimited.
In the long run, the company doesn't belong to you alone.
Which shareholder is willing to put up the money
to take this risk with you?
If you think the risk is too high,
I can use my shares as collateral.
if it fails,
I'm willing to give up my shares
and resign from the board of directors.
Nonsense. Legal department.
Take the renovation contract to the guesthouse.
you must negotiate it down, it's imperative.
There's no room for negotiation.
Yes, Director Gu.
In my opinion,
from what I know about the chairman,
he's going to be ruthless this time.
As long as I'm standing in the courtyard,
I'd like to see who dares to touch a single brick of the guesthouse.
Wait, that's not right.
If the legal team arrives, won't your identity be exposed?
Then what should we do?
In my opinion,
Help!
I'm warning you,
don't interfere with this matter anymore.
Young Mr. Gu,
please don't put me in a difficult position.
I'm just an employee.
If the chairman finds out about this,
I can't bear the consequences.
Besides,
how am I supposed to explain this to my family?
Just tell them you were abducted by aliens.
This is no time for jokes.
Can you say something useful?
You're staying here for a week and not going anywhere.
I'll have someone bring you three meals a day.
That won't work, Young Mr. Gu.
I have a parent-teacher conference for my son tomorrow.
No problem, I'll go in your place.
The thing is, kidnapping me like this
won't do you any good.
Mr. Gu has also sent a lawyer.
What?
I guess
they've already arrived at Qimeng Residence by now.
Go quickly.
Hello.
Excuse me, are you Miss Song Qiyue?
I'm the legal counsel from Gu Corporation.
I'm here to discuss
some matters related to the renovation project with you.
Renovation?
Who's renovating?
Gu Corporation?
According to the agreement,
the corporation is willing to compensate the businesses
for losses caused by the project renovation.
How much can you offer?
According to professional assessment,
the converted amount is 2.3 million.
I'm not the one to make this decision.
It's up to our boss to decide.
2.3 million?
That's just a fraction of our annual rent.
It seems acceptable. Let's go with that.
What if we don't want money?
There's another form of compensation.
You can choose from our group's
all tourist attractions and core commercial centers
to select a storefront
and reopen your guesthouse on a one-to-one basis.
We can subsidize 80% of all initial costs
and expenses for opening the store.
But this place
holds our memories and emotions.
It's like home to me.
Go back and tell your boss
our minds are made up.
Some things can't be measured by money.
Even 4.6 million
can't buy our guesthouse.
Our boss sent me to inform you.
It's not up for discussion.
No one is negotiating with you.
Alright.
I will convey your decision to the group.
I'll take my leave.
Duoduo,
why are you gluing the contract?
This is the closest I've ever been
to becoming a rich lady in my life.
I'm not gluing the contract.
This is my heart.
If our little shop becomes popular,
I'll hang it in the store.
I'll tell everyone,
'This shop was once worth 2.3 million.'
2.3 million!
Can we ever earn 2.3 million in our lifetime?
I'm sorry.
I might have been too impulsive then.
Impulsive?
Who was impulsive?
What were you impulsive about?
Wasn't it Gu Ci'an who was impulsive?
He's just destined to be poor.
What does it have to do with you?
No one consulted with you.
Is that so?
I actually think
he was quite cute back then.
He's still pretty cute now.
Stick to your contract,
money, money.
July,
actually, my true identity is
the vice president of the group.
No, that's too stiff.
July,
the one who wants to renovate our guesthouse
is the group's president, Gu Buli,
who is also my father.
This is going to cause too much resentment.
July,
there's something I've been hiding from you.
I have to tell you now.
Actually, it's also my father's fault.
What about your father?
You heard everything?
I heard the gist of it.
You said you were hiding something from me.
Why is your face red?
I understand now.
You think the timing isn't right yet,
but your father has already started pressuring you.
I get it.
My mom has pressured me like this too.
Huh? What?
Is anyone at the guesthouse?
Dad.
You must be the owner, Song Qiyue, right?
Hello, uncle. Yes, it's me.
No need to call me uncle.
Let me introduce myself.
I am Gu Buli, the chairman of Gu Group.
May I ask,
when can our group start the construction?
Construction?
It's terrible, Qiyue!
There's a bulldozer parked at the entrance.
And there are construction workers too.
What's going on?
Dad, I hope you'll stop making things difficult for us.
You're the one making things difficult for me.
I regret it now.
letting you come here in the first place.
You didn't let me come here.
I was the one who first saw potential in this project.
You said you could help the company reclaim this place.
That's why I let you come.
Tell me, during this time,
what have you actually done?
You haven't made any progress on the relocation and renovation.
Instead, you've been helping out at the guesthouse.
Is this what a vice president should be doing?
Vice president?
Vice president of the Gu Group?
Gu Ci'an?
Is everything he said true?
July,
this is exactly what I wanted to tell you earlier.
But I swear I have never betrayed the guesthouse.
I'm asking you,
are you his son?
Are you?
Yes.
You were sent by the company to take back our guesthouse,
weren't you?
But I changed my mind later.
I'm asking if you were or not.
Initially, yes.
Hello, do you need any help?
Why did you help me today?
I guess you could call it coming to your aid.
Can you two girls handle such a big guesthouse?
Are you hiding something from Qiyue?
What could I possibly be hiding from her?
So you've been lying to me from the beginning, haven't you?
I...
No wonder you're so familiar with this town.
And here I thought you were different from them.
you really do like this place,
and truly wanted to support me.
But in the end?
I've been kept in the dark all along.
Qiyue, that wasn't my intention.
Listen to me, I hate being lied to more than anything.
This is the second time I've been deceived in this courtyard.
I originally thought you were sent from heaven to save me,
but you've been lying to me all along.
Do you know how ridiculous this makes me feel?
Qiyue, I really wanted to help you,
from the very beginning until now.
That's enough.
I'll never trust you again.
From today on,
I hope you can stay away from me,
the farther the better.
Vice President.
Cast
Taxi Driver: Yuan Yaodong
Colleague A: Yuan Quan
Construction Foreman: Zhou Wenyi
Customer B: Fang Ruotian
B
Old Lady: Gao Hua
Staff List
Producer: Guo Tong
Producer: Hou Junwei
Screenwriting Team
Casting Director: Cao Yanchao
Production Team
Photography Team
Lighting Team
Styling Team
Costume and Makeup Supervisor: Deng Yaomei
Art and Props Team
Sound Recording Team
Sound Recordist: Zhai Qiang
Set Management Team
Transportation Team
Opening Theme: 'Dream Promise'
Ending Theme: 'July Wind'
Post-production
Beijing August Film and Television Production Co., Ltd.
Foley Artist: Jia Haolin
Finance: Wang Le
Chengzhe Zhizao (Beijing) Film and Television Art Co., Ltd.
Beijing Jubang Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Poster Design
Shenzhen Qidian Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Production Company
Er Xin
Wuxi Guangxin Film and Television Animation Technology Co., Ltd.
Co-production
Lianying Media
Co-production Companies
Beijing Yicheng Tianxia Technology Co., Ltd.
Production Companies
Wuxi Huihe Cultural and Commercial Media Co., Ltd.
Wuxi Guangxin Film and Television Animation Technology Co., Ltd.
CCTV Video Convergence Media Development Co., Ltd.
Broadcasting Platform