Chairman, I really didn't lie to you.
Recently, young Mr. Gu
has been negotiating the buyback of homestays,
and it's going very smoothly.
Still being stubborn.
Don't move, don't move.
My feet smell.
Don't move.
I really didn't lie to you.
Chairman,
It's okay if you don't tell me.
I'll send someone personally
to check, and then we'll know.
From now on,
you can't go anywhere.
Just stay here
and wait for news with me.
Come, let's look at your love fortune.
The answer is right beside you.
Someone close to you has a secret crush on you.
This thing is just for fun.
You actually believe it?
Besides,
who else is around me except you?
Duoduo,
do you have
any inappropriate thoughts about me?
Well,
what about that Gu Ci'an?
Don't talk nonsense.
Come on, turn to the next page.
Hurry up.
Trust your intuition.
Look.
It's definitely him.
Gu Ci'an.
Come on.
Are you hiding something from Qiyue?
I...
What could I possibly be hiding from her?
See? Your book is not accurate.
Put it away.
Impossible.
I calculated it so accurately.
You must be hiding something.
Quick, come out now!
Wait, I have a stomachache.
You scared me.
Hurry up.
Don't try to trick me, I'm warning you.
Alright, alright.
I got it, I got it.
Hurry, hurry.
What are you looking at?
Haven't you seen a handsome guy use the bathroom before?
You're the boss.
Manage your own image.
This kind of small matter,
just leave it to me.
Rushing to help you with work,
could it be a sign of affection towards you?
That can't be, right?
Is there anything else?
How much did you pay to rent this homestay?
What do you mean?
I'll give you triple compensation.
It's enough for you to stay in a better hotel.
Pack your things and leave now.
Are you crazy?
I just unpacked and you're asking me to leave?
Are you looking for trouble or a bad review?
Five times.
You're not allowed to write a bad review.
How much money do you want?
You can stay at a different hotel.
I'll pay for this meal.
And I'll cover your hotel expenses.
Plus triple compensation for breach of contract.
Pack your things and leave immediately.
Don't test me.
I won't even give you
the chance to stay here.
Dear guest,
are you unsatisfied with our homestay in any way?
Oh, no.
I suddenly have some family matters to attend to.
So we won't be staying.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, excuse us.
Gu Ci'an.
What's going on?
They said they all have some family matters to attend to.
some said their children are sick,
some said their parents are hospitalized,
and some even said their house is on fire.
They're all rushing back home.
Family emergency?
And they seem so happy about it?
What's the situation today?
All the guests have left the hotel.
And everyone's grinning from ear to ear.
Didn't they say they had emergencies?
I could understand if it was just one person.
But how can everyone have an emergency at the same time?
Don't worry.
Out with the old, in with the new.
Then tell me,
where are the new ones?
They're all booked.
I told you not to worry.
You've been working hard lately.
I'll treat you to something nice.
let's relax a bit.
I think I'll pass.
After all, someone needs to stay at the guesthouse.
You two should go ahead.
Wait for me a moment.
I'm going to the restroom.
Hello, boss.
I'd like a room.
Um, we're fully booked.
That's impossible.
I've already placed an order.
That's impossible. We're fully booked.
Where did you place your order?
Look.
This can't be right.
Okay, here's what we'll do.
You cancel your order.
Triple the cancellation fee.
What do you mean?
Who do you think you're looking down on?
Five times.
Even ten times won't work.
I'm definitely staying here today.
If you keep talking nonsense,
I'll file a complaint against you.
Where's your manager?
Manager!
I am the owner here.
There's no such thing in this world as
a deal that can't be made.
There's only insufficient profit.
How much do you want to leave?
I've really seen something new today.
Since you've put it that way,
Twenty times.
QR code for payment, quick!
Gu Ci'an.
July, let me explain first.
Explain what? Causing trouble here,
driving away all my customers.
You must be bored, right?
I have my reasons.
What reasons
could make you act crazy here?
No, it's just that I saw you were too tired.
I wanted you to take a break.
Do you think I'm a three-year-old child?
July.
Fine.
I'll give you one more chance.
What are you really up to?
I really can't say.
It's okay if you don't want to say.
I sent someone personally.
you'll know when you go and see.
I really can't say.
Can't say, huh?
If you can't say it, then get out.
Ouch!
Ouch! Oh my goodness, who's this?
Uncle Zhang.
They're just concerned about you.
Was it necessary to drive everyone away?
Concerned about me?
Yet they're about to ruin my career.
If he likes me,
it would be the death of me.
I think
he might have something he's uncomfortable telling you,
that's why he's acting this way.
Stop.
Don't make excuses for him anymore.
You're my sister.
Sister, I'm just looking out for you.
You're right.
He is indeed hiding something from me.
Hiding from me that he's mentally ill.
That shouldn't be the case.
That's what the book says.
Cast
Clerk A: Yuan Quan
Construction Foreman: Zhou Wenyi
College Student B: Yin Haoran
Zi
Gao
Fiancé: Chen Ganyu.
Staff
Producer: Guo Tong
Executive Producer: Cai Yuaner
Writing Team
Directing Team
Production Team
Production Coordinator: Wu Yi
Photography Team
Lighting Team
Styling Team
Sound Recording Team
Sound Recording Assistant: Zhang Xinli
Set Team
Team Leader: Wang Bao'an
Transportation Team
Opening Theme: 'Dream Promise'
Ending Theme: 'July Wind'
Guitar: Zhu Yiming
Publicity: Liu Zheng
Post-production
Men Yue
Beijing August Film and Television Production Co., Ltd.
Sound Effects: Hao Jie
Foley Artist: Jia Haolin
Mixing Engineer: Zhang Keke
Chengzhe Intelligent Creation (Beijing) Film and Television Art Co., Ltd.
Beijing Jubang Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Poster Design
Shenzhen Qidian Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Production Company
Wuxi Guangxin Film and Television Animation Technology Co., Ltd.
Co-production
Lianying Media
Co-production Companies
Beijing Yicheng Tianxia Technology Co., Ltd.
Production Companies
Wuxi Huihe Cultural and Commercial Media Co., Ltd.
Wuxi Guangxin Film and Television Animation Technology Co., Ltd.
CCTV Video Convergence Media Development Co., Ltd.
Broadcasting Platform