It is said that
strange things that can't be explained
exist everywhere...
like the unsolved mystery
of what lies beyond death.
There are ghost stories
everywhere in every school.
They are told during the day
by one student to another,
from generation to generation.
They are told, retold,
twisted, and distorted
until their origins are lost.
Ghost stories are created from the dark,
from the fear rooted deep
in the hearts of students
who imagine the school at night
as a realm where spirits roam.
It's no longer somewhere they belong.
It becomes a place for...
ghosts.
Ghosts are created
from humans' unconscious fear of death.
Everyone has a fear of death,
so we created the idea of life after death
to go on existing and to become immortal.
But it's not real.
In modern science,
quantum physicists have stated that
humans are merely made
of particles and energy.
When the brain stops working
and the heart stops beating,
those particles will disappear.
Therefore, life after death,
spirits, and ghosts don't exist.
Statistically, almost 80% of people
who claim to have seen ghosts
are mentally ill.
GHOSTS
We said we'd meet up. Remember?
We did?
You know. Tonight at school.
Boyd, are you serious about this?
Of course. Am I the type to joke around?
Don't say you'll bail on me again.
You made me a promise.
Okay.
- Fine.
- Great.
What's this clip you sent me?
Fucking hilarious.
Come on, Boyd.
Don't you know the Jinx app?
Most teens are on it.
Oh, and about the students
who believe ghosts cursed them...
What app and what curse?
It's a place to vent,
a bit like Twitter.
Those kids believe ghosts order
the students in class M.6/4
to bring the books listed on the board
to class every day at 7:00 a.m.
If they don't do it, they'll die.
Students still believe that shit?
Old superstitions.
You're the only one trying
so hard to debunk ghosts.
Yeah.
Hey, Boyd. Why hasn't Tum joined us yet?
Right?
You're right.
But I'm meeting him at 10:00 p.m.
to prove that the ghost stories
that we've told at school for years
are all lies.
You're always teasing him.
- He'll piss himself.
- Damn wuss.
- Wow.
- Hey, Boyd.
Don't forget to go live.
We want to see Tum piss himself.
Sure. I'll go live for you guys.
- I can't wait.
- I'll make a meme out of it.
The whole school will see.
- He'll be famous.
- Good idea!
Awesome!
Earth!
TUM
Hey, Tum.
Where the hell are you?
I couldn't reach you.
I was helping my mom
deliver stuff to her customers.
Where are you now?
Are you at home? I'll pick you up.
I'm already at school.
You went without telling me?
I've been waiting for you.
Well, I forgot.
I thought you'd be here.
You said we'd meet at ten, right?
Fine. Wait there. I'm coming.
Don't chicken out and leave.
Yeah, yeah.
OPEN FROM 5:00 A.M.
CLOSED FROM 10:30 P.M.
TUM
Boyd, come on in.
I'm already inside.
How the hell did he get in?
Where is he?
Where the hell is he?
Tum.
- Boo!
- Hey!
Tum, what the hell are you doing in there?
Well, it's scary outside,
with all those ghosts, strangers,
and stray dogs.
When the guard wasn't around, I snuck in.
And then I saw you.
I thought you weren't afraid of ghosts.
That was quite a high-pitched scream.
Anyone would be scared
when you pop out of the dark like that.
Is that the guard?
Hey, get inside and hide.
Let's step back a bit.
Hey. Why are you trying
so hard to disprove ghosts?
People have believed
in ghosts for centuries.
Exactly. It's been centuries,
so I have to convince people like you
to stop believing old superstitions
and live in the present
to make progress in the world.
Hey.
You're too close.
Well, I don't want to get caught.
Whatever.
I think he left.
Let's get out. It's getting cramped.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Ouch.
- Go on.
- You go first.
- You can go first.
You go first.
No, you first.
- Together?
- Okay.
Okay. You go first.
- I'll go first.
- Okay.
- Hey, Boyd!
- What?
Where are we going?
We're gonna debunk old horror stories.
Hold on.
What?
- You take this.
- Huh?
And I'll take this.
There.
What is this?
Your job is to show me the way.
- And your job?
- I'm going live.
Get in the frame.
That's better.
Hi. It's me, Boyd.
Today, I'm taking you all
on a mission to debunk the ancient beliefs
that ghosts exist
and that every school has them.
The first stop I'm taking you to is
the traditional dance club.
Today, I'm with a friend.
This is Tum.
He's still a believer
in old ghost stories,
despite all the scientific theories
that have debunked them.
Today, Tum and I
will take you guys with us
to prove that those old tales
are all lies.
PIMRY: CAREFUL
Ready, Tum?
Yeah, he's ready.
TRADITIONAL DANCE CLUB
Now we are at
the traditional dance club.
- PANUMAT KTK: THAT'S HARDCORE
- LOL9: LET'S SEE WHAT HE'S GOT
KAYAVINE: PLAY WITH FIRE
AND YOU'LL GET BURNT
Tum, get inside.
Don't point it at my eyes.
Get in.
What are you scared of? Come on.
- Tum.
- What?
Light the candles.
- What for?
- To create the vibe.
Go on.
- Are you for real?
- Yeah, go on.
PANUMAT KTK: REAL HORROR VIBE
Go on. I'll get you on camera.
Good.
- FRRIEND TF: SUCH HYPE
- MWUANG CA: BUT IT REALLY IS SCARY
- ZEE SIRIKORN: SO MUCH HYPE
- MEBBAITOEY: SHIT. BOYD, YOU WFH-JK;PY'
BOATSEED: GUHPPP
Go on.
- There.
- I can feel the vibe now.
BOATSEED CALLING
MING ISSMINK CALLING
Hey.
Guys,
stop calling me.
I'm going live now.
And stop sending me
this alien gibberish.
I can't read it.
Type something I can read.
PIMRY: YEAH, DON'T KILL THE VIBE
MWUANG CA: THAT LOOKS ALIVE BACK THERE
What's up with my phone?
All right. You guys look out for me, then.
Tell me if you see anything.
PIMRY: IT'S GETTING EXCITING
Hey.
THAT LOOKS ALIVE BACK THERE
- Shit!
- What is it?
LOL9: HILARIOUS. HE SCARED HIMSELF
- Oi! What?
- Did you try to scare me?
Why would I do that? I'm scared too.
All right.
I'll tell you a story.
MWUANG CA: IT WAS SO REAL
The first story is called Love Letter.
PANUMAT KTK: SO SCARY
There was once
a young man who had a man's body,
but a woman's heart.
This person was quite ugly,
so they always got the part of Hanuman,
but they wanted to play Sita.
One day, they got
a love letter from an admirer.
It was full of sweet words
of his adoration for them.
YOU'RE SO CUTE.
ANYONE WOULD LOVE YOU AS I DO
But alas,
the letter was fake.
A letter from a secret admirer?
Who is it from? Do you know?
No clue, huh? You stupid bitch.
- Harsh.
- Look at yourself. Who'd like you?
Gosh. So mean.
Art, was it you?
- Oh.
- Did you write that?
- Did you?
- No, not me.
- You look suspicious.
Who would like him? He's so dark.
Don't ever think
I'd like someone like you.
Oh, but I thought you liked him.
Ew.
Leave me out of this.
You should cover your face
with a mask like this.
That's right.
- You ugly freak.
- You'd look better that way.
Oh, you're crying, dark boy?
Keep crying. Boo-hoo.
Let's go.
They were bullied
by the Ravana actor and the dancers
who had planned it all.
They were enraged,
so they decided to replace a prop
in their performance with a real weapon.
They stabbed the guy
who played Ravana on the stage.
He died on the spot...
during the scene
where Hanuman defeats Ravana.
Art!
No.
FRRIEND TF: DON'T TOUCH IT, DUDE
Oh shit!
Why are you so jumpy?
And this is the trident
I was talking about.
It's the weapon
that was swapped in the show.
But that's impossible.
Performers are not allowed
to change their props.
Besides,
the managers of the props
and costumes are the teachers and staff.
JAMES: SERIOUSLY?
The story that we hear
might be adapted from Macbeth.
Oh, one more thing.
The guy who played Ravana is still alive.
His name's Art.
Don't believe me? Check Facebook.
Nui!
- Hey, Boyd.
- What?
He's not the only Art around.
And the Hanuman story
was all over the news.
They said the dancers who were the bullies
all fainted in the theater.
Reporters even showed up to get the story.
What Tum just said was
about the dancers who were possessed.
They even told the reporters that
they could see
the ghost of Hanuman dancing with them.
This, in fact,
is called mass hysteria.
- PANUMAT KTK: THAT SHIT'S HARDCORE
- MWUANG CA: REALLY?
Do you understand?
Yeah.
Good.
We have more ghost stories to tell.
Stay tuned for the second one.
Ready to go, Tum?
Are you pranking me?
No, I'm not pranking you.
By the way, does your head hurt?
Why would it hurt?
Because of that.
Maybe I got scraped by the fence.
- Come here. I'll get it.
- Okay.
Thanks, man.
Done.
Come on. Let's get going.
Okay.
Are you ready?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
The second story is called
The Gym.
Tum.
- Tum.
- What?
Go over there.
Why?
Because...
I want you to tell this story.
Why don't you do it?
I want you to do it.
You can do it. Trust me.
Go on.
Just read it.
Hurry up.
- LOL9: HYPING IT UP?
- MWUANG CA: I LIKE IT
- Where?
- There. Right there.
TIME: ARE YOU TELLING IT OR NAH?
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
There. Right there. Stop.
Now, a little to the left.
To the left. Okay.
All right.
Go. We're all waiting.
- TIME: WE HAVE TROLLS
- MWUANG CA: I'M SCARED
"The second story is about the Gym Ghost."
SHAVED ICE: WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
"This is the story
of a national gymnastics team contender."
"They say a competitor who also wanted
to get into the national team put a nail
on the balance beam,
so the contender stepped on it
and fell over."
"Her head hit the floor."
"Her neck broke instantly."
"And ever since,
people would often hear someone running
and practicing in this gym."
And now for the facts.
LOL9: MY SCHOOL'S STORY IS MUCH SCARIER
Planting a nail on the balance beam
is impossible.
Before the practice session,
the space would be cleared first,
by either the coaches or the gymnasts.
Everyone practices on the beam
before solo practice, so they'd see it.
JAMES: YES, GO ON
All right? And the sound everyone hears,
whether it's the sound
of someone running or practicing,
when the guards and the students come
in here to check, they see nothing at all.
TIME: SHUT UP, SKEPTIC
The truth is, the sound
that everyone hears comes from the wood
that gets swollen because of the humidity.
Therefore, although it sounds
like someone running or practicing,
it's not real.
BEM: SO SCIENTIFIC
In short, this ghost story is
just another lie.
Believe me now?
Yeah.
Even Tum believes me now.
LOL9: YOU GOTTA SEE THE REAL SHIT
We'll take you guys on a tour
around the school one more time.
Let's go, Tum.
- For real?
- Let's go. Yeah, for real.
Damn it.
Come on. Let's go.
FIRE ESCAPE
Tum.
What?
Not so scared now, huh?
Leading the way, I see.
Do you believe me now
when I say that ghosts don't exist?
Have you seen any
since we started walking around here?
Hey, Boyd.
What?
Will you tell the other one?
They all talk about it.
I know every ghost story
in this school without exception.
I guess you're not
the expert that you claim to be.
What don't I know?
Hey, it's not a big deal.
- Why are you mad?
- I'm not mad.
I just wanna know.
What is it that you know that I don't?
Or are you just making it up to bluff me?
Well, it's the story
people are talking about.
They're talking about it? Okay.
So tell me.
What is this story
people are talking about?
Go on. Our friends are waiting.
Story number three.
Once, there were two best friends
who went to debunk
the school's ghost stories.
When the two of them
went to the last haunted spot,
which was the school's top floor
that was closed down,
they decided to play a game at that place.
The one who came up with the mission
told the other to pick heads or tails.
And the winner could order the loser
to do anything.
This is not a real story.
I know all this school's ghost stories.
Don't make stuff up, Tum.
I'm not making it up.
I heard it from someone else.
Who?
The one who told you.
Who was it?
Tell me, then.
Well... I... I don't know.
If you don't know...
then just shut up.
Let's say that today's mission
has been completed.
The two of us found nothing here.
Not even a single ghost.
And Tum already admitted
that ghosts aren't real.
Catch you guys later.
Come on, Tum. Let's go home.
Hey, Boyd.
How can you be sure
that ghosts aren't real?
Well, do you see any?
They're real.
We just didn't see.
Who's pulling this prank?
Traditional Thai music
and traditional dancers?
Clichés can't scare me.
Boyd.
Stop saying stuff
that you don't know for sure.
Well, I'm not scared!
Unlike you who's scared of everything.
Did you plot this prank
with the others behind my back?
If you're scared,
then stay here.
I'll go by myself.
Boyd.
Who the hell are you guys?
Boyd! Boyd, get back here!
Shit!
Boyd, run!
Hurry!
Be honest.
You guys pranked me, right?
Who would prank you?
I should be asking you.
Did you guys plan to prank me?
If I did try to prank you,
do you think the others would join me?
They are your friends.
And if I were not your friend,
they wouldn't care about me
or even be my friends.
I'm not buying it.
There's no way
the ghosts we just saw are real.
I bet they knew
I brought you to debunk ghost stories,
so they pranked us both.
Hide over there!
Hurry!
You said the stories weren't true.
This is just like the story we told.
Well,
I think
we should run.
Come on.
Boyd!
Boyd, hurry up!
Hurry up, Tum! Keep running.
- No!
- Hey!
- Let's find another way.
- Yeah, let's go.
- Hey, Boyd!
- Tum.
A way out!
- Hurry.
- Okay.
Hurry up, Tum!
Boyd. Upstairs. Hurry!
- Upstairs, Tum.
- Yeah.
Shit.
Hey.
Tum.
Boyd!
Hey. That way.
Yeah.
- Tum.
- Huh?
- Tum!
- What?
I think
we should go downstairs.
There may be another exit.
The ghosts are downstairs.
Wouldn't it be better to go up?
I'm not going.
I don't trust what's behind that.
Let's make a bet.
I'll flip a coin.
If you win,
we go down.
But if I win,
we go up together.
Stop messing around.
Now's not the time.
Right. We don't have time,
so I'm making you choose.
If you don't choose,
I'll choose first.
The side of the coin that I didn't pick
is yours.
And if I lose...
I'll do what you say.
No way.
I call heads,
so you're tails.
Wait!
Heads.
I win.
This time, we both go up.
Or do you want me to go first,
so you can leave me again?
Boyd!
Wait for me.
Boyd, where are you taking me?
The door's closed.
Fine. You're right.
Ghosts aren't real.
Let's just do this
so we can go home.
In that case,
let's flip a coin.
The loser does what the winner says.
I call tails. You're heads, okay?
Tails.
I win.
You go first.
After the winner
told the loser
to open the door
to take a look and see
if there were ghosts behind it,
the loser
had to comply.
But what he saw
made him cry out to his friend for help.
Shit! Help me!
- Boyd, help me!
- Shit.
He couldn't leave.
- Earth!
- Boyd!
Help me! Boyd, help me! Boyd!
The winner
heard his friend crying for help
and got scared.
He left him to face
what was behind that door alone.
After that, the abandoned friend
never came back to school again.
And the one who got away
resumed his normal life at school.
Remember what I said at the gym?
Just because you can't see it,
that doesn't mean it's not real.
You're just trying to turn a blind eye,
so you tried to find
every theory to debunk this kind of belief
just so you can move on with your life,
clinging to your own beliefs.
But deep down, you know...
those things are real.
Hey, someone's calling.
Pick it up.
Boyd.
Why didn't you take my calls?
I've called you so many times.
Are you with Tum now?
Yeah.
He's right in front of me.
I have something to tell you.
Look at the group chat right now.
That's all I'll say.
TUM HAD AN ACCIDENT ON THE WAY TO SCHOOL
Shit.
Today, Tum and I will take
you guys with us to prove
that those old tales
are all lies.
Ready, Tum?
PIMRY: CAREFUL
Yeah, he's ready.
BOATSEED CALLING
MEBBAITOEY: READ THE GROUP CHAT
Why are you calling?
MING ISSMINK CALLING
Guys, stop calling me. I'm going live now.
MING ISSMINK: RUN
And stop sending me
this alien gibberish. I can't read it.
Type something I can read.
- PIMRY: YEAH, DON'T KILL THE VIBE
- BOATSEED: STOP IT NOW
Tell me if you see anything.
Boyd.
This time, you lose.
Will you leave me again?
Hey, Boyd.
What?
We're about to graduate.
But I still wanna hang with you.
You're such a baby.
Well, I don't know
if we'll still be friends in the future.
Sure we will.
You're the only best friend I have.
I...
I will never leave you.
It is said
that every school has a story.