The Untamed
Episode 16
Wuji, you're so good.
Let me pull out the radish.
I can't pull out the radish.
Wuji, do you remember the stars I taught you last time?
You forgot?
The seven stars of Beidou.
You forgot, Wuji?
Come on.
Let's go.
Hurry up, Wuji.
The Untamed
Wuji
Episode 16
When the incense is burnt out,
your legs won't hurt anymore.
My legs don't hurt.
You can't fool me this time.
No.
I'm afraid it really hurts.
Then, little master,
you should think of a way.
The twelve kinds of western poison that the master has planted
are really lucky to see.
How can it be called lucky?
I've been doing this for days.
Finally, I found the antidote.
Then, you should hurry up.
But the master has taken twelve kinds of antidotes.
These antidotes are more rare and more toxic.
I haven't figured it out yet.
That is to say,
if he didn't take those antidotes,
it would be better.
Ranyi.
It's okay.
I know you have good intentions.
Little master will have a way.
These twenty-four kinds of medicine
have made the master's pulse disorder.
His martial arts are all gone.
Is the?
Maybe he won't live until tomorrow.
Life and death are predestined.
The blessing is in heaven.
Don't think that...
Little master, please save him.
Get up. Wake up.
Little master.
Please save him.
This is a protective pill.
It can keep the meridians.
It can keep the poison in the body for the master.
It won't attack the heart.
That's all.
I'll go find some medicine.
I'm afraid it's annoying to take care of you.
Little master, be careful on the way.
Go back quickly.
Chen Xing.
This is mine.
This is for you.
Okay.
I'll go find some medicine.
How many do you want?
One.
Good for you.
You...
You're good.
Why hasn't he come back yet?
Actually, it's good that he doesn't come back.
I'll go find some medicine.
It's been two days since I took the road.
How is Master doing?
I feel much better.
This is...
I'm Ma Da.
Master saved my family.
He almost died.
I'm willing to serve you
and repay you with my life.
Master must have a lot of merits.
I've received merits from the other side
yet I've lost merits from this side.
The effect of the medicine of Hu Xin Palace
has been delayed for two days.
I'm willing to serve you
and repay you with my life.
The effect of the P
has been on the heart for two days.
Little Master,
do me another favor.
I've never drunk with you.
You're really...
You must be very good at drinking.
I'm so tall.
I've never seen anyone who can drink better than me.
Shishi, here.
You're not lying, are you?
Are you sure
it's the wine that Little Master asked you to drink?
Don't worry.
If not, you can ask him yourself when he comes back.
Okay.
How is it?
A little spicy.
One more.
Go back.
Where did you play that duet?
That duet
is played in
that little forest behind there.
Do you know
how we call the empty-handed
and get the Easter dictator?
Why is the wine so strong?
Because it's not wine.
It's medicine.
It's like you're giving me a fume umbrella.
Now that Master is back,
I can detoxify.
I don't have to pretend anymore.
You guessed it right at the beginning.
I was the one who asked the Crown Prince to trick you.
But I didn't expect to be caught by you.
I was tortured by you.
I almost died from being poisoned.
I just want to wait until this day
to take revenge on you.
You still want to take the knife?
Wake up! Wake up!
Listen carefully.
I want to sell you to the farthest place.
I want to sell you to a criminal.
Sell to the deepest mountain.
I want to make everyone find you.
I'm sorry.
I'll send her back to Nuowu.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
I'm leaving.
Master.
You'll regret it if you do this.
Tong Yao is dead.
She won't have a chance to regret it.
But at least she's still alive.
I'm sorry.
Master.
Manager Leng.
Manager Leng is back.
Kot mining town.
Потому что если вы spicy.
S passage.
Simon Lambert.
We can't let him go.
We have to change the route.
But it's been a few days
since we've been walking around.
If we keep going like this,
we'll be in a big trouble.
Old man.
Eat it.
You're so handsome.
You're so useless.
What are you looking at?
Behave yourself.
You're bullying me again.
What are you doing?
Don't move.
Okay.
You have to get up.
Come on.
Thank you, sir.
You deserve this.
You're bullying me again.
I'll hit you once.
Do you hear me?
No, sir.
Sir.
What's wrong?
I…
I couldn't even bring myself
to say it,
sighs.
You have a18 letshif?
You wear so much
You've only been in Xianghu Village for a few days.
I've been in Xianghu Village for so many years.
I know them better than you do.
Do you understand?
You are my bodyguard.
Protect me.
Yes, Young Master.
Young Mistress.
Young Mistress, why are you here?
If you tell anyone about what happened today,
you'll come to see me.
Yes.
But Young Mistress...
Shut up.
Go and get me a horse.
Liar.
Go.
I've been watching you these days.
I've thought of a way to detoxify the poison.
But I didn't think of
a way to detoxify the poison.
I feel that my palm
is getting numb.
This poison
will make people become like wood.
And then you die?
How long will it last?
One or two hours.
One hour?
I'm afraid it'll take a long time.
Young Master,
please
go to the east side of Mount Jun's forest
and tell my father
that I can't do what he asked me to do.
I will do it.
And
find a beautiful willow tree
for you to drink.
Why are you looking at the reward?
What if I run into a real prince?
This is my 50 taels.
I've thought of a way to spend it.
30 taels for land.
10 taels for building a house.
10 taels for getting a wife.
Young Master, order.
Coming.
Uncle.
Young Master, what would you like to eat?
Young Master is here.
Here.
It doesn't look like it.
You're a follower.
Why are you sitting here?
Stand behind me.
Young Master, what would you like to eat?
Fish or meat.
Whatever you like.
Okay.
Wait a minute. I'll be right back.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
You're not a real prince.
Don't order.
It's not enough.
Eight steamed buns.
Just eight steamed buns?
Yes, eight steamed buns.
Thank you.
Okay. Wait a minute.
Are you worried that
we don't have enough money?
Of course.
Listen.
There are two ways to Mount Jun.
One is the main road that everyone knows.
And the other is
the small road that only I know.
As long as we start to walk on the small road,
I'm telling you,
at least we can save three...
Yes.
Young Masters,
may I sit with you for a while?
Please.
I heard you said
you were going to Mount Jun.
There's a quiet road.
I'm going to Mount Jun, too.
May I come with you?
Miss,
why do you want to go to Mount Jun
alone?
I'll give you this knife.
I'm not a prince.
I'm a beggar.
I live in the east of Mount Jun.
You can ask me
if you don't mind.
I don't care who you are.
I've made a bet.
You're mine.
I went to find my old friend.
He was kind to me
and saved my life.
We broke up later.
But I knew
he would go to Mount Jun.
So I wanted to go to Mount Jun
and ask him.
Why did you sell me?
I was sold.
I'm a poor man.
Come with us.
It's okay to have one more person.
Zhuang is here with us.
Thank you, Young Master.
If you want to eat meat,
just order.
I'll pay.
More wine?
Something bad happened.
What?
That girl can't be with us.
She has a problem.
What's the problem?
Think about it.
When we were eating,
there were so many empty tables.
Why did she have to eat with us?
And she invited us to eat.
And she went to Mount Jun with us.
Think about it again.
She's beautiful, single and rich.
Why is she with us?
Why?
There are two possibilities.
First, she's a female thief.
She stole some things from us.
Second, it's because of love.
She's not a female thief.
Then it's just love.
Do you think she likes me too?
I'm so confused.
Young Master, think about it.
Do you have any misunderstanding?
How could there be a misunderstanding?
Think about it.
Just now, she threw water at me with a horse brush.
It's a hint.
It's nothing.
Then,
she blocked me at the door and didn't let me in.
And she touched me.
All these signs show that
she likes me.
She likes me.
Okay.
Let's say she likes you.
She likes you so much.
Then why can't she be with us?
Xing, you once said
you want to learn the Eight Trigrams of Xiang Rong.
You want to be the leader of Beggar Gang.
You want to help the country and the people.
You want to help the evil and the good.
This is what we should do.
We shouldn't think about it.
Young Master,
I didn't expect that you...
Zuo Yi,
you should be blamed for this.
I'm afraid that after I go there,
the dark light will be blind and the lonely man will be a widow.
I'm not good at self-control.
So, you should go there.
You should tell her
I'm not suitable for her.
She should quit.
Okay.
Wan Ju.
Miss, can I come in?
Come in.
You have to hear
something ridiculous today.
Say it.
Young Master thinks you like her.
Wait.
Like her?
What?
It doesn't matter what you like her.
What matters is that
she thinks you like her.
You want to go to Mount Jun.
Yes.
She doesn't agree with you.
I don't want to listen to you.
Then...
There is a solution.
What solution?
She thinks you like her.
But she thinks she can't like you
because of me.
So, as long as you let her know
I have convinced you successfully tonight
to control your love for her.
And you should keep a distance from her
on the way.
But you can't go too far.
For example, you can touch her arm.
Then you can get close to her.
You can't let her go.
If...
Wait.
What are you talking about?
What do you want me to do?
You want to go to Mount Jun?
Yes.
She is the only one who knows the shortcut.
Then you have to cooperate with her.
What?
Like her.
But you can't like her.
You men are so stubborn.
Did you say it?
What?
I said it.
Well...
Zhuang.
Do you remember what I said to you last night?
Do you remember what I said last night?
Zhuang.
Do you remember what I said to you last night?
Do you remember?
Did you play a prank on me last night?
I did.
I didn't expect I would cry so hard.
You are so hurt.
There is one more.
Here you are.
Give it to him.
Why does she still treat me like this?
What's wrong?
Can't you see it?
She gave me the last sip of water.
Isn't it obvious?
Later, you can talk to her.
If not, just be direct.
Okay.
Wait.
I will give her some hints.
You have sent the guards out, can you check it again?
Good.
There are some things we shouldn't force.
Yes.
I gave him a...
A beggar.
How did you know?
You are really a team.
Liar.
Liar?
You still can't guess
who I am, right?
Your Highness.
You are not
the princess of the Nuo Wu Clan,
Miss Yi Huo.
I'm really sorry
for the escape.
You really went to the mountain to fight?
I know it.
I will meeting you
after the beggars are declined.
Xing.
Run!
There are dogs here!
I am bitten! Xing!
What a coincidence!
Exactly.
Such a coincidence.
How could this be?
I didn't know either.
Where is the person?
There's a place
It's hard to predict
Yes, he did
I'm asking you
He left
He left?
Where is the horse?
He left
He left too?
How can we leave?
Xing
Let's go
The time is up
Hold on
Wait, wait, wait
I said it was not too late
I'm sorry
You came too late
It's all your fault
I didn't even get to know your name
No, brother
Can we discuss it?
No
We really came all the way here
Tiao Tiao, Tiao Tiao
We came all the way here
We really got hurt on the way
That's why we took so long
No, look
You let me see
Take him away quickly
No
Brother, don't go
Brother
What should we do?
Where did you get this?
My friend gave it to me
What's your friend's name?
I forgot to ask
Where is he now?
I don't know
Did you hurt him?
You took this pocket
Uncle
I know your son
I'll tell you the truth
Hong Qi's mother died early
This kid is a thief
I didn't teach him well
Let's wait for her to wake up
Wait for her to wake up
Click
this
This
This kid
is like Hong Qi
He did these when he was little
He likes these
I just
This guy knows how to cause troubles
Uncle
that's warm hearted
Because he's so kind
I had to let him loose
But I almost with him
So we avenged each other
She's really
Come all the way here
to breastfeed the owner
to serve the country and the people,
to be good at both good and evil,
to practice martial arts,
and to be the best in the world.
You're so ambitious.
I underestimated your ambition.
But
it's not easy to learn the Eighteen-Handed Dragon.
It's much harder to be the chief.
To be honest,
the chiefs of the upper level
have been defeated by the attack.
They only learned one week to do their job.
Uncle, to be honest,
I won't come even if it's not difficult.
But
I'm still too late.
I'm the assistant,
but I always have the advantage of missing the chance.
I've arranged the registration
for you.
Thank you, uncle.
You're welcome.
Let's go.
Let's go out and have a drink.
Okay.
Thank you.
You and your brother
are my lucky stars.
My son always buys me this kind of wine.
He likes it the most.
Today,
I'll use it to welcome you.
Come on.
Okay.
Tonight,
we must have a good drink.
Okay.
Come on.
Aren't you here to fight?
Miss Yi Huo,
why are you here?
Why are you here?
I'm here to deliver a message.
To make friends?
You said you didn't collude with Hong Qi
and lied to me.
I didn't lie to you.
You're so rude.
You're so smelly.
Miss Zhao Yue,
what's wrong with you looking for your son?
Where did you hide Hong Qi?
Hong Qi?
He...
He didn't come back.
Really?
Yes.
Tell him
he doesn't need to come back.
Because I burned his house.
He can avoid the first day,
but he can't avoid the fifteenth day.
Don't.
Young Master.
I found it.
Shun'er.
What?
There was a pass by.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Young Master buried it.
Miss.
What's wrong?
Hong Qi...
He's dead.
What did you say?
Do you remember
the name of the star?
Yes.
The Northern Star.
Hong Qi grew up.
Enter Sophie die that year?
She is...
Miss you don't see.
and do something wrong with his power,
Jaeho will go under your cover.
Miss Yihua is right.
Qixiong and I do have a relation of great value.
Even though we met by chance,
we're as close as friends whom are like volts depend on.
Miss Yihua and Qixiong?
How did you know each other?
When you were drinking,
I drank with her
at the moon.
Brother,
cheering.
He taught me
the martial arts of martial arts.
Did he lie to you?
He taught me.
A dog hug
and the
You are the root of my heart
I can't return to the original place
You are the mountain that I can't cross
Even if we are wrong
Please don't retreat
I don't want to escape from you
Only you are here
Is this Yin Sword?
The master is still in Yang Jian
But he almost died
I remember I died
That was a fake death
The master said when he was buried under the liu tree
I suddenly thought of one thing
The worms covered by the yellow earth will all die
They can live in the soil for a long time
As food for their larvae
So I tried to bury the master in the soil
Let the earth in the soil help the master to warm up and detoxify
It turned out to be right
Little master
Let's detoxify the next poison
The master has changed today
I had a dream before I woke up
I saw someone in my dream
I want to see him again
Master, put your hand in
What are you biting me for?
The five snakes that just came out of the river
This poison needs to be controlled by the five snakes
The big snake is too poisonous
The master will die because of this
The little snake can be gradually killed
Seven days later, they can be released
The fusion of snake poison and poison
Is a more precious poison
Little master always collects the poison I've been eliminating
I don't know why
To be honest
The third child is in critical condition
So I'm not sure if it's a good idea
I came to the south this time
To find the poison
I couldn't find it for a long time
But I found it on the master
Speaking of which, I have to thank the master
You and I are a pair of lips
You and I are two medicines
How can we only have fate?
Is the cold poison working again?
How is it compared to the previous two tests?
My heart is starting to get cold
The air is empty
The oxygen is dissipating
If we don't protect the source of the master
I'm afraid we can't save our lives
What a pity
Then I can't help you cure the illness
Before life and death
But other people
The master is really a great person
I know a set of nourishing techniques
It can help you get over the cold
You can take a break
It depends on fate
Miss, have something to eat
Uncle said that the house is small
I can only temporarily set up the memorial tablet here
I hope the dead can rest in peace
This time
I have to be careful
The military and military competitions are not separated
The heroes and heroes of the five lakes and four seas are here
Why don't you go and see
I'm not interested
Brother Qi
At that time
We are going to be together
The five lakes and five seas are rushing to save people
Now I'm the only one left
I'm going to the station
I won't let you down
Let down
The villain got the power
Brother Qi was kicked out of the Beggar Gang
When we were together
We are going to reform the Beggar Gang
I didn't care much about the position of the gang leader
But now
I must do my best for Brother Qi
If I can be the gang leader
The first thing is to prove for Brother Qi
The second thing is to do everything
I will do my best to fulfill Brother Qi's wish
I wish you a successful career
Miss
If you can help me
I am very grateful
I will do my best
I will end my life
I will get back up
I will go back
I will go with Brother Qi
See you
Thank you
renovations
You are wrong
If you bring look you will find fault
า