[English subtitles are available]
[He who is unable to live in society, or who has no need because he is sufficient for himself, must be either a beast or a god.]
[Aristotle]
He wanted to take revenge on me.
He wanted me to ruin myself.
Then why didn't he just kill you?
[The Silence of the Monster]
[Chapter 1]
[A Girl Who Buried Her Heart in the Ground]
[Episode 1]
[Meet and Meet]
The real Kashmir sapphires
should be
purplish deep blue.
They enjoy a velvet and dream-like glow.
But this one
is too perfect.
Isn't it good to be perfect?
It's related to the laws of nature.
Randomness is the best.
Inside each gem
is its unique identity marker, mineral.
Excuse me, sir.
I really can't authenticate
fake things.
Right.
I understand.
How about
I won't buy it today.
No way.
You ruined
my business.
If you don't buy it today,
you can't leave here.
Will you buy it or not?
Yes, I will.
You can't buy it. It's fake.
I don't want to buy it either.
But life is more important.
Will you buy it or not?
-Yes. -Of course not.
Yes.
You can't buy it.
I'll buy it.
What are you doing?
Catch him! Stop! Stop!
Help!
SOS!
I'm not joking this time.
I'm really going to die.
An appraiser who only tells the truth.
You're capable.
You ran away with my customer.
Why did you run?
Tell me the truth now.
In this era,
few people can tell the truth.
You have to pay for the truth you told.
I admit.
I can't lie,
but in this world,
people shouldn't be too greedy.
Fine.
I'd like to see
how a blind man can be an appraiser.
♫I got a reason to live♫
♫I got a fire inside♫
♫I got something to fight for♫
♫Nothing can hold me down♫
[Locksmith: He Chufeng]
[Appraiser: Luo Bin]
♫I got a reason to live♫
Is this box heavy?
When did you buy it?
♫I got something to fight for♫
Stay away from me.
One meter.
♫I got a reason to live♫
One meter is so long.
How about 80 centimeter?
Deal with this kind of matter yourself in the future.
I can't deal with it myself.
I saw it.
♫I got a reason to live♫
Let me ask you.
You are dressed like this.
Did you do something special today?
Why are you dressed like this?
♫I got a reason to love♫
[Monster Vintage]
Granny, you're here.
I'm here to select jewellery.
Let me help you.
I heard you caused trouble again.
Why didn't you say the good things I did?
You really like tell others this kind of thing.
Granny, let me explain.
Here's the thing.
They asked me to authenticate jewelry.
Then we had friction.
But don't worry.
I'm a man.
This wound is nothing.
After waking up in the morning,
can you be quiet for a while?
How dare you ask me to be quiet?
The noise of you grinding keys every morning
is driving me crazy.
I just don't want to talk to you.
Talking promotes communication.
Communication promotes human progress.
Be quiet.
Granny,
you must check this bill.
I'm not worried when you're here.
How about this one?
This one is good too.
Try this first.
Okay.
But if you don't check it,
I don't think I did my job well.
What are you talking about?
Manager Luo.
Because you're here,
I can be so relieved.
Okay.
I'll check it tonight.
This one is really good.
All right, I'm leaving.
Goodbye, Chufeng.
Goodbye, Granny.
Granny.
The bill.
Bye-bye.
Goodbye, Granny.
[Apprentice Lawyer: Sui Yi]
[Promotion of Civil Law Knowledge]
I think I was scammed.
Lady, calm down.
Please tell me in detail
how you were scammed.
My wife
hates it when I snore at night.
You want me to persuade your wife?
It's useless.
Miss,
please be the judge.
He cheated at mahjong.
So many people were watching.
Who cheated?
I saw your title when you dropped it.
Which eye do you mean?
Stop defending yourself.
My son likes braised beef,
scrambled eggs with tomatoes,
and sweet and sour fish.
So I bought fish, eggs...
Lady.
Let's get to the point.
But I can't control myself.
We often quarrel over this.
I don't know what to do.
Look at the eggs. The point is
one is big and one is small.
What should I do?
I'm talking about how to stop snoring.
Let me help you find a way to solve it.
Don't come out and play.
He's unreasonable.
We know you.
Calm down.
Who cheated?
You cheated!
Stop defending yourself.
Do you know how to play?
Of course I do.
Xiaoyue will give a performance tonight.
When can I get off work?
Hello.
Is this Su Xiaoyue's dressing room?
Yes.
Who are you?
I'm a fan of Xiaoyue.
I like Su Xiaoyue so much.
I want to take a photo with Xiaoyue.
Is it possible?
Get out.
This is a workplace.
Why are fans here?
Why are fans so bold nowadays?
They even came to the dressing room to take photos.
This is crazy.
How can Xiaoyue
take photos with them easily?
Right, Xiaoyue?
It's okay.
Get ready for the show.
The show is about to start.
Go. Go. Go.
Let's go.
Xiaoyue.
This is a new phonecard and cellphone.
No one else knows it, right?
Don't worry.
I've sent you your new address
and password for the door.
Don't be angry.
Don't mind what they did.
They're just jealous of you.
Fans are waiting for you
-outside. -Xiaoyue. Xiaoyue.
I'm excited for you.
Xiaoyue. Xiaoyue.
Xiaoyue!
The new girl group, Star Moon Girls, appeared this summer.
There are many topics about the popular idol Su Xiaoyue.
Since she debuted as a member of a girl group,
Su Xiaoyue has been attracting great attention.
She has many fans.
She loves stages
and continues shining.
Su Xiaoyue said
being herself
is her biggest motivation
on this stage.
Come on, Xiaoyue!
♫Rainbow shines under the bright sky♫
♫Dreams sprout before I know it♫
♫Tick-tock, it's the countdown♫
♫I set out with a firm and brave step♫
♫Wipe away my tears, this is the price of growth♫
♫Don't be afraid if you've tried your best♫
♫Wave to the past♫
♫Don't be afraid of the big world♫
♫Grow♫
♫Don't leave any regrets♫
♫Shine brightly on the stage♫
♫The cheers have gathered all your expectations♫
♫Even if I fail♫
♫Rainbow dream, don't ask if you can♫
♫The destiny of fireworks to bloom in the sky♫
Hello?
Monster Key.
Please fill out the form.
Why?
I'm sorry.
This is the rule.
Show me your ID.
Why?
I'm sorry.
This is the rule of our industry.
If you don't show me your ID,
I can't help you.
Please take off your sunglasses and mask.
Can we start now?
Wait.
What I want is the most sophisticated,
state-of-the-art,
and secure electronic door lock.
It should be a high-tech lock
that no one can open.
What is this?
Many people trust electronic door locks
like you.
Should I
trust this primitive lock which is out-dated?
Miss Su,
your request is the most secure lock
that others can't undo.
Yes.
Electronic door locks are easy to be broken.
It was opened so soon.
The commonly used locks for doors on the market
are all smart locks.
As long as the signal affects the transformer
and destroy the password mechanism,
the lock core will be tricked.
No matter how complicated the lock core is,
it'll be easy to open it then.
So don't believe
new technology.
With regard to
Ms. Lin Huiying's civil lawsuit
against her son, Chen Silu,
through weeks of communication with Mr. Chen,
Ms. Lin was finally persuaded to give up the suit.
We're trying to let them settle out of court.
What do you think?
It happened again.
Sui Yi,
what do you think?
I've read the file on Ms. Lin Huiying.
Her life is a mess now.
She has no other
source of income to live on.
But if she insists on suing him,
she has a high probability of success
and can obtain coercion support
from the court.
But if she gives up
or withdraw the lawsuit,
at this stage,
she may not get a penny in alimony
and waste her time and energy.
This is the client's decision.
Accepting out-of-cout settlement during the appeal
is the decision made by the client
afte we showed her
all the possible terms.
The client has her own concerns.
Although you passed the bar exam at the first attempt,
you should know
as a lawyer,
if you just want
to increase the success rate of your case
by deliberately guiding the client to make a decision
regardless of her real will,
I think
this is very unprofessional behavior.
The fundamental reason that she sued
is because she can't make ends meet anymore.
If we only cares about her feelings
instead of solving her problem,
is this professional?
Also,
it has nothing to do with
whether I passed the bar exam
at the first attempt.
You two,
can you come to your senses?
What are you doing?
Please be aware of your position.
Who are you?
Apprentice lawyer.
Intern.
I asked you to attend the meeting
because I hope you can learn from it.
Don't overstep your bounds.
Either
listen carefully,
or
get out.
Let's continue the meeting.
Come in.
Please have a seat.
Please wait a moment.
Mr. Wang will be here soon.
Thank you.
I didn't expect
to come to Xiaoyue's company.
I wonder
if I can see Xiaoyue later.
Mr. Zhou,
at the meeting today,
I was not calm
and became emotional.
I will learn from my mistakes
and try to analyze cases objectively.
I won't be too emotional.
It's good that you realized that.
We're lawyers,
not psychologists.
The legal services we provide
should be neutral
and fair.
I see.
Thank you, Mr. Zhou.
Well,
you can try to answer the questions
which this company will ask later.
Me?
First of all, the other party's action
violated the portrait right of our entertainer.
Based on the evidence we have,
the other party has made over eight million yuan
in illegal profits
by using our entertainer's portraits.
If we keep investigating,
the amount of money may increase.
While investigating
the first case,
we found the entertainer's reputation was also damaged.
This is ridiculous.
Cyberspace is not a lawless area.
We can change public opinion
through lawsuits.
We think both cases
can be sued for.
Therefore,
we also prepared two plans for litigation.
These are the two drafts of litigation.
Judging from the current situation,
we can begin to keep the evidence
from the following aspects.
I want to talk to you.
Xiaoyue.
I'll go out for a while.
Go on.
No, no, no.
Let me recall
what I was doing.
Was I too stupid?
Not really. I think I did all right.
I was saying,
"we can begin to keep the evidence
from the following aspects."
Right.
Then she walked in.
My daughter is so pretty.
Come to your senses.
I can't be sensible about this.
She's so pretty.
My daughter.
I can't believe I saw my daughter.
[The Real Hair of A Member of Star Moon Girls Su Xiaoyue]
[DM Me If You're Interested]
These people...
No, no.
For my daughter,
I must get a license to practice law.
[You'll be on camera tomorrow. Take good care of your skin tonight.]
[Okay.]
Who is it?
Who's outside?
Hello?
Monster Key.
The lock you installed for me was forced.
That's impossible.
But it was forced.
Where are you? I'll come to you.
Okay.
I'll see you at the intersection of the neighborhood.
Where are you going?
To pick someone up.
Pick someone up?
That's rare.
I want to go with you.
Why is it rare to pick someone up?
I need to record it.
Stop filming me.
No.
We agreed to record it.
Don't film me.
No.
I'm using my own cellphone.
Then please don't film me with your cellphone.
Didn't we agree last time?
We have to record our life.
If you don't want to be scolded,
you'd better switch off your cellphone.
What's wrong?
Hello.
Let me take you to our shop.
Miss Su.
I know it's inconvenient for you to talk here.
Let's go to the shop.
Xiaoyue?
This cute lawyer...
I'm sorry.
You threw us to the ground
indiscriminately.
You're a special lawyer.
I thought
you were Xiaoyue's sasaeng fans.
Do we look like saeng fans?
I'm sorry.
I'll compensate you if you need anything.
You can solve your problem first.
The lock you installed for me was forced.
That's impossible.
But someone was in the room last night.
Someone must have come in.
I told you I wanted a secure electronic door lock.
You insisted on changing it to a normal lock.
It was forced easily.
There's no problem with my lock.
I live on the 46th floor.
If it wasn't for your lock,
could that person be Spider-Man
who can climb walls
and come in a room through a window?
That's possible.
Sir,
please answer
my client's question.
There's a security problem
with the lock you provided.
It affected my client's normal life.
Once we get proof
that there's a problem with your lock,
we can sue you anytime.
Don't infect others.
Thank you.
Don't always talk about suing others.
Problems are solved by people.
The most important thing now is to solve the problem.
Right?
Miss Su,
are you under a lot of pressure at work?
It might be caused by the stress.
Are you saying that I have mental problems?
No, no, no.
I didn't mean that.
Sir,
please don't make a subjective judgment
about my client's
mental state.
This is slander.
Also,
is this a regular unlocking company?
Do you have a business license?
How can you prove it?
We not only have a business license,
but also reported it to the Public Security Bureau.
Look.
If an acquaintance of me hadn't recommended you,
I wouldn't have come to you.
Xiaoyue.
Let's go.
I'll take you to a regular lock shop
to find a reliable locksmith.
People who run such a fancy shop
must be deceiving you.
Miss, as an apprentice lawyer,
please don't make a subjective judgment
about our professionalism.
This is also slander.
Let's go.
Wait.
My goodness!
I'm standing in front of Xiaoyue's home
with her.
No, no, no.
I need to be sensible.
Xiaoyue is in trouble now.
I have to protect Xiaoyue.
Go over there.
You blocked the place.
I know.
Look at them.
One of them is an idol.
No wonder you didn't allow me to record it.
That young lawyer
is definitely a fan of that idol.
Can you go over there
and have a chat with them?
Let me unlock it myself.
You're in my way.
You mean that young lawyer?
She doesn't look capable,
but she's really good at fighting.
She even grappled you to the ground.
Awesome!
What are you doing?
You're in my way. Get lost.
I've checked.
This lock has never been forced.
Can we go inside?
Come in.
You don't have to change your shoes.
What are you doing? Come in.
Balloon flowers.
They stand for eternal love
and hopeless love.
It might be placed here by my agent.
I don't remember.
The flowers are quite durable.
Don't you usually open the curtains at home?
How can entertainers open curtains at home?
What if the paparazzi take pictures of them?
It's such a tall building. How do they take pictures?
No matter how high the floor is,
some fans can still take pictures if they want.
But
she can't see the sunlight.
Privacy is very important to entertainers.
Privacy is important to everyone.
Can we enter your room?
Yes.
This is my room.
Isn't this Gundam's
collaboration with Hello Kitty?
They released cartoons together before.
Hello, sister.
Do you like the flowers I gave you?
I want to be with you forever.
Sister.
This is a gift set.
Look carefully.
There's a surprise waiting for you.
Get lost!
Are you done?
Thank you, sir.
Bean Bun is really important to us.
If we can't find it,
we will be so sad.
Where is room 4601?
Why can't I see that room?
They asked for it.
They said they want to protect privacy.
I don't understand.
Well,
can I watch the CCTV footage of the corridor?
And the elevators.
You said you're looking for a cat.
Do cats take elevators?
This is the last one.
The last one.
The CCTV footage is only stored for seven days.
And it didn't cover her home.
There's no problem with the lock.
Have you searched the room carefully?
Yes, I have.
But I found nothing.
Where could he be?
Did he go out?
But he was not captured on CCTV.
Then...
It's possible.
[Monster Notebook]
He's really something.
Let's go inside.
Let's go.
You stay here and watch him.
Don't let him make trouble.
That old man is really rich.
We're rich now.
We don't have to worry about the rest of our life.
Aren't you going in?
Hurry up.
Load more into it.
Things are rare to be divided
evenly.
It's full.
Look over here.
Load them all.
It's really money.
Let me help.
Why are you here?
Go and guard the door.
Hurry up.
Forget it.
Let's go.
He locked the door.
Do you want to die?
Open the door!
[Monster Notebook]
Grand Seiko.
This one was created in 1970.
This is a masterpiece.
It even surpasses Swiss watches.
Although it doesn't look as valuable as Blancpain,
and doesn't look as elegant as Patek Philippe,
it has a delicate mechanism.
This is a very practical item.
After being repaired,
it should be worth about 200 thousand yuan.
Really?
Thank you.
Steiff.
This Teddy bear was produced in limited numbers.
In 1880,
it was the world's first German toy company
to manufacture plush toys.
The appraiser is here.
Do you want to unlock something or authenticate it?
He Chufeng is not here?
No.
In order to distinguish them from imitations,
Steiff Company sewed a button and a tag
on each bear's ears.
It's real.
Do you want to sell it?
I can give you a good price.
OK.
I'll give you 50% discount.
Can you let me
see He Chufeng?
Normally, the first step in authenticating
a Louis Vuitton handbag
is to check the label.
The typeface of "Louis Vuitton"
and "Made in France" on the label
should be relatively flat.
The typeface of "Paris" should be slightly thin and tall.
I'm sorry.
This is fake.
Don't tell anyone that it's fake.
Otherwise, I'll report you.
I'm exhausted.
[To be continued...]