All I know is that the father is a
representative of a huge corporation.
They've been in the states a long time
so I wasn't able to get exact details.
Anyway I found their address,
write it down.
[Kim Jong Wook.
Woo Do Young.]
Woo Do Young, she had the
exact same name as Mrs. Woo.
Min Ki, what are you doing here?
Is this the house you moved into?
How did you know to
find this place?
Did you live in Yeon Jong Do,
before you moved here?
Why are you asking me
these questions?
Before your mother came to New York,
she was a painter too right?
Have you known Ms. Eun Jung Soo
from a long time ago?
Aunt
Go ahead and answer
your phone.
No, it's fine...
what did you just say?
I was wondering if you
knew Ms. Eun Jung Soo...
You're here.
I thought you'd be here
soon so I came out to check.
Mom.
Hello.
Director Kang, let's talk
about that at work later.
I'll go inside and you guys
can finish your discussion.
No mom!
I was just about to go in.
Sure... well then...
Goodbye.
Let's go in.
Did Min Ki bring you home?
Seo Hyun.
Yes?
I'm sorry mom,
what did you just say?
By any chance, are you two
seeing each other again?
No, it's nothing like that.
He needed to tell me something
about work that's all.
It can't be easy seeing
each other everyday at work.
I can't believe of all the places, you're
working at the same company as Min Ki.
Seo Hyun.
You and Min Ki...
I don't why you two broke up.
But your father and I
thought he was a great guy.
If Min Ki came here with the
intentions of asking you out again...
I told you it's not like that!
I'm sorry.
I'm just a little sensitive right now.
Who could that be at this time?
Who is it?
It's me!
Oh my, it's Seo Hyun's aunt... Hello!
I thought you went home.
Did you forget something here?
Yes, I did amongst other things.
- Did Seo Hyun come home?
- Yes, a little while ago.
Are you crazy!
What are you doing here
at this hour?
Then you should have
answered your phone!
I was panicking! I couldn't just sit
there and wait for you to call back!
Did something... happen?
Has that woman said anything to you?
Like what?
What is she supposed
to tell me?
For goodness sakes!
What happened?
Jung Soo saw that woman at the
department store she was working at.
Was it a glimpse or
did she see her face to face?
It looks as if she saw her
face to face.
Jung Soo was in a state of shock
so she lost her.
And that woman didn't
recognize her at all.
Now that she knows, she's going
to try to find her no matter what!
What are we going to do
about this?
Stop it... whatever we need to do,
we have to stop that from happening.
No matter what we can't let
those two meet each other!
No matter what!
By any chance, do you
know Ms. Eun Jung Soo?
What?
What are you talking about?
I've noticed at
the interviews...
you seemed uncomfortable
around Ms. Eun Jung Soo.
I'm not.
Ms. Eun Jung Soo is not
even a designer.
She's just a part-time employee that
will only be here for three months.
And what if that design really
belongs to Ms. Eun Jung Soo?
Then it's even more
imperative that we let this go.
Director Kang.
Did you something bad happen?
You don't look so good.
Nothing happened.
Did you have a tough time
searching all day today?
No, it wasn't tough at all.
Just knowing that I'll be
able to see Mrs. Woo someday...
Has given me energy
right down to pinky toe.
That lady... Did that family
have a daughter at all?
No, they weren't able to have children,
that's why they were trying to adopt me.
Why do you ask?
Oh it's nothing.
I just thought that information
might help in finding her.
I'm so sorry... I know how busy
you are to be concerned with this.
Ms. Jung Soo.
Have you known Director Kim long?
Did you know her before
you came to Shin Hwa group?
No... the first time I met
her was at Shin Hwa group.
I apologize for barging in
so late at night.
- No don't be, are you leaving?
- Yes.
By the way, did anything bad
happen to you?
No!
I was just in a hurry to
ask Seo Hyun about something.
- I'll be on my way then.
- Have a safe trip.
- I'm going to get a taxi for her.
- Good idea.
No, that's not necessary.
- It's all right aunt.
- No please, don't get up.
Goodbye now.
Why did you come out?
You've been like this for awhile,
what are you thinking about?
I think there's something
going on with Seo Hyun's aunt.
She came back so quickly after leaving
and I think Seo Hyun is involved too.
Oh, and Min Ki was here
a little while ago.
Seo Hyun said he just stopped
by for a moment due to work.
You think they are seeing
each other again?
I'm not sure about Min Ki but Seo Hyun
has no intention to see him again.
For the time being they see each other
everyday because they have no choice.
Well both of them are rational, I'm sure
they're handling it in a wise manner.
I told you to go in!
Why do you keep following me?
I'll get you a taxi, take the taxi home.
Are you that rich?
Besides, now these days they blast
the air conditioner in the buses.
There's no point in taking a taxi.
Go in...
Hurry and go in!
What is it?
What's wrong?
Mom... I'm scared.
What am I going to do if
everyone finds out the truth?
Jung Soo comes here tomorrow?
Also... if she finds out
I took her place.
What am I going to do?
That will never happen.
I'm going make sure that it doesn't.
I'll take Jung Soo and immigrate to
another country before that happens.
She will never see that woman.
So keep your mind clear
and ready yourself.
Also, don't ever think that
you stole Jung Soo's place.
You and the position that you have
right now, instead of Jung Soo.
It was fated for you.
Having it stolen?
That was Jung Soo's fate.
Be good to your adoptive parents.
Bend over backwards for them.
Even if by chance they find out
that you're not Jung Soo...
Make it so that they can't
ever kick you out.
Understand?
I know you had something
to say to me yesterday.
I'm sorry for cutting you off
like that.
I didn't want mom think
we were seeing each other again.
How did you know about the
previous house that we lived in?
And what was it that you
wanted to say to me yesterday?
I don't even know where to begin.
What is it that has you so frazzled?
You say... the first time you met Ms. Eun
Jung Soo was at Shin Hwa group right?
How many times do I
have to tell you?
I immigrated to the states
as a sophomore in high school.
And as you know we returned when
we found out grandfather passed away.
How could I possibly know
Eun Jung Soo.
Why?
Did Eun Jung Soo say
she knew me from before?
No... Eun Jung Soo said Shin Hwa
was the first time she ever met you.
I was wondering... Did your mother...
ever adopted a child?
- Adoption?
- Also, I don't mean any harm by this.
Your mother and father... are
they your biological parents?
Min Ki, what in the world has you
asking me these kind of questions?
Did you find anything
yesterday about Mrs. Woo?
I went to the community
center in Yeon Jong Do.
But they're not allowed to give the
address of where they currently live.
Is it vital you find that woman?
Why? So you can go back
and be their daughter again?
No, I'm too old for an adoption.
Then don't bother.
You're wasting your energy for nothing!
And once I found your place,
I was shocked.
The person Ms. Eun Jung Soo
was looking for... is your mother.
- Have you told Eun Jung Soo?
- Not yet.
There seems to be a story behind
this so I wanted to ask you first.
You should have!...
What's wrong?
What's wrong? Are you all right?
I'm all right.
Can you keep a secret?
Min Ki, I'll tell you everything.
But you can't tell anyone,
especially Eun Jung Soo.
Yes, everything you said
is true Min Ki.
My mom and dad...
They're not my biological parents.
17 years ago my parents
planned on adopting a child.
During the adoption process...
my mom got into a car accident.
When it was declared that she
was in a vegetative state...
They stopped the adoption process.
Dad took mom to New York.
And after eight years, mom
miraculously came out of her coma.
But at that point any means of contact
with that child had already ended.
Dad was worried about her health.
So instead of that child,
he adopted me.
Only my dad and I know about this.
My mom still thinks I'm the child
she originally tried to adopt.
Then... the child she wanted
to adopt at first...
- Was Ms. Eun Jung Soo?
- I don't know.
If the person Eun Jung Soo
is looking for is my mother...
Then yes it's a possibility.
Min Ki.
Do me a favor.
My mom's health is getting better.
And her memories are
slowly returning as well.
But if she found out the truth...
she'll go into shock.
So don't tell Eun Jung Soo.
Besides, you don't know for sure
she is the child that was to be adopted.
- Jung Soo!
- Honey!
Honey, come out here for a second!
You too Jung Soo!
- Yes uncle?
- Where did you go? What is that?
You think we can make a hundred
of these by the day after tomorrow?
A hundred by the day after tomorrow?
What are you talking about?
It's a bag for samples
and other products.
The business that was supposed to
supply these had a flood in their factory.
If we do a good job, we'll probably
continue to supply for this company.
- Let's do it! Of course we should!
- What luck is this!
Honey I'm impressed with your skills!
Oh my goodness!
The people there were in a hurry
so I wasn't able to get a pattern
You think you will be able
to make this?
This is nothing uncle.
Honey you know how talented
Jung Soo is!
Oh my gosh, this is great!
- Oh and if you look here.
- Yeah?
Your back is like an island.
The only island that I can
rest peacefully.
Wow Eun Jung Soo! Just one look
and she's got the pattern down!
I've learned from the best uncle!
- No chatter we have a hundred to make!
- We're on it!
This woman never picks up
the phone!
She's supposed to teach me an hour
everyday and I've gotten no word.
Is anyone home?
- Is anyone home?
- Yes!
What is it?
Who is it?
Behind the three sides,
you know where it is right?
- Yes, of course.
- Jung Soo.
This is a surprise.
What brings you here?
I'm suppose to learn how
to make bags starting today.
Please come in.
Bags?
Director Do, please
introduce yourself.
Starting today, the person who
will be teaching you is my uncle.
Me?... Wait, he wants to
learn how to make bags?
Why do you want to learn how
to make bags from a person like me.
- But it's nice to meet you.
- Yes.
I'm not saying this because
I know how to make bags.
And you'll know
what I mean later on.
But you won't find a better
group of people than us anywhere.
I see.
You came at the perfect time.
We need all the help
we can get right now.
When learning a skill you know you
have to start from the ground up right?
Well tailors start by
learning how to remove threads.
So have a seat and start
pulling those threads out.
Don't tell him to do that.
Honey bring us some refreshing.
Hurry! Be quick!
We don't have anything refreshing.
By the way, what's with the getup?
You won't be able to learn
properly dressed like that.
What's wrong with it?
I look great.
Yes, as your working
clothes it's quite unusual.
But it's stylish, it has style.
Please sit... I'll teach
you how to do this first.
I swear Jung Soo... this is amazing...
you drew this pattern down to a tee!
Why does it matter who teaches you?
Also, a teacher should be hard and
scary in order to learn properly.
You take me for granted and
think lightly of me. How will you learn?
This wasn't what we agreed on! I made
it clear you were going to teach me!
I'm pairing you up with a
challenging teacher, you don't like it?
If you want to learn then start
now, if not then just forget it.
We just got an unexpected
work order.
So giving you lessons at this
time isn't possible anyways.
We're really busy.
Promise my butt!
What was I thinking?
This is bull crap!
This is a called a neck.
This looks similar to a fork
so we just call it the trident.
There's one that has
two spears and there's
this one like a pick,
makes one hole at a time.
You have to make the holes good.
So that way it's easy to sew
and the stitching looks good.
Goodness... next time
dress comfortably!
- You must be hot.
- Oh... I'm fine.
Here, try making a hole.
Use those two right there.
What is it?
That thing... give it to me.
- This?
- Yeah.
What are you going to use it for?
I need it for the sweat on my forehead.
How should I wear this?
- This is pretty good.
- That was quick!
Since Jung Soo did the pattern
so well, we made this in no time.
- Director Do was a big help too.
- Not at all.
Hold on.
Hello?
Hello manager!
Yes, yes... a sample?
Yes, I understand!
Yes, I'll be right there.
That was the home shopping network,
They want to see one of the bags we made.
Why do they want to see a sample?
They think we can't make that simple bag?
They've never worked with us before,
it's understandable they don't trust us.
It's fine! We made
these bags anyways.
We'll just take these and
show it to them.
Kyung Ho took the scooter,
how are you going to get there?
I'll go uncle.
It's too hot outside for
you to carry these bags.
- I'll go.
- Uncle you need to make more bags.
We need to have 100 bags by the day
after tomorrow, you don't have time!
I can make it when I get back.
I'll go with her and I have
my motorcycle with me as well.
Motorcycle?
So that's why you're dressed like that.
I don't know what to say?
I appreciate this.
Thanks to you, we got here quickly!
- Will you be all right?
- Yes, I'll be right back!
That's tough...
I said that's tough.
Carry the bags from behind your back,
she always carries it in front of her.
Oh my back!
You used a different zipper
from the sample bag we gave you.
We checked the home shopping
bulletin board online.
And there were some inquiries on
the zipper malfunction of the bags.
Well I found out the zipper
used for the sample bags
is one that tends to break
easily around the ends.
The unit price was a little expensive.
But we went ahead changed it to a
zipper that caused less trouble.
There was hardly any difference
in the style of the design.
You're attention to details
is impressive.
We're more than happy to use
products of good quality.
But I heard you guys
were a small business.
Is it all right for you to
lose profit on the unit price?
Honestly, we're not
losing that much.
It's more important investing in quality
products and getting recognized for it.
And ultimately it's our duty to provide
that. My uncle is very firm on that.
Being a small business,
I was very worried.
But I feel confident in
trusting you now.
Just please make sure
it's done on time.
Yes! We'll do our best!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Yes!
- Did it go well?
- We passed!
They liked it! Once we're done, they'll
consider using us as their supplier.
- Aren't you thankful?
- Of course I'm thankful!
It's hard for a small time
business like us
to be considered as a supplier
for a home shopping network.
That's not what I meant.
Do you know how much
this baby costs?
Me and my Emma took you to an important
meeting. Shouldn't you feel honored?
Hey motorcycle, thanks for the ride.
But how did you get so
unlucky to meet this jerk.
What? What did you just say?
Nothing.
I heard you say something
about being unlucky.
I said how nice it would be to have
something refreshing on a day like this.
Hold on a second.
Yes Director.
I'm outside right now.
Yes, I know where that is.
Okay, I'll see you then.
- Let's go.
- Director? You mean Director Kang?
Yes.
Why are you meeting Min Ki?
Forget it! Don't tell me
if you don't want to.
Oh my gosh! What a jerk!
Manager Kang.
I won't be disappointed.
Just tell me.
I knew you had something
to say to me yesterday.
But I could see you were hesitant in
telling me so I waited for you to be ready.
Ms. Eun Jung Soo.
If you ever find that person again...
what do you plan on doing?
What do you mean by that?
You said there's a chance she
might not remember you at all.
Or what if, for some reason she
is not be looking for you.
I'm afraid, finding
that person might be...
more disappointing
and hurtful for you.
At this point, I'm not sure if
this is the right thing to say
But there's a saying that memories
should be buried as memories.
While finding Mrs. Woo...
I'm just worried that you
might get more hurt by it.
Ms. Jung Soo.
- All I want...
- To me Mrs. Woo... is not a memory.
Not once... was Mrs. Woo
a memory to me.
17 years may have passed.
But everytime I think about
Mrs. Woo...
I still feel the same way I did
17 years ago, it hurts, and I miss her.
Hey Bear... don't laugh.
I don't like you today.
So you're saying... Mrs. Woo thinks
the adopted daughter she has is me?
I don't know if this
will give you any comfort.
But that woman
had knowledge of you.
As soon as she came out of her coma...
she was searching for you Ms. Jung Soo.
Then the person who got
adopted instead of me.
Did you get a chance to meet
her personally Director Kang?
Yes.
How is Mrs. Woo's health
She's very healthy.
During her recovery, she did have
amnesia for a certain period of time.
But recently she has been
slowly getting her memories back.
I'm so relieved to hear that.
Director Kang.
Thank you so much.
I had no idea something
like that had happened.
If I eventually met Mrs. Woo...
Imagine how shocked she would be
if she realized her daughter wasn't me?
Thank you.
Don't think of anything
and just get some sleep.
Also... if you need my
help for anything, call me.
I will.
By the way, what is that?
Do you have a motorcycle?
No.
I just happened to have it.
It's really nothing.
Thank you for taking me home.
Jung Soo.
Jung Soo!
Look at all this sweat!
Jung Soo what's wrong?
Jung Soo! Wake up!
What's wrong with her?
Jung Soo! Jung Soo!
Oh this bad! Kyung Ho!
Kyung Ho! She's sweating like crazy!
- Take a look at her!
- Jung Soo! What's wrong with her?
Hey! Put her your back!
Hurry and carry her!
- What's wrong?
- Honey.
- What's wrong with her?
- Mom, get out of the way!
- Where are you going?
- Jung Soo wake up!
What in the world is
wrong with her?
Jung Soo did? Did she say
anything at all yesterday?
Okay mom, I'll talk to you later.
You didn't tell Eun Jung Soo
I was that child did you?
No, I didn't. I thought it would
be best if you told her yourself.
That's not going to happen.
It's not your fault with the
way things happened.
Also, even if the truth
is revealed, I don't
believe it's going
to change anything.
What is that you're so
scared of that you can't talk?
You're right, none of this
is my fault.
But I don't feel comfortable
standing in front of Eun Jung Soo.
If I can, I want to avoid
her as much as possible.
Is it wrong for me to do that?
I thought it was strange from the beginning.
If it had anything to Ms. Jung Soo,
you became extremely sensitive.
- I told you I'm not!
- The connection you have with Jung Soo.
Now that I know, I understand.
When we were in New York,
you were so lonely.
And I can understand now,
why you were so uneasy too.
What is it that you're
trying to say to me?
Ms. Jung Soo said for your mom's health
she won't try to see her.
So at least go to her and
offer her some comfort.
She's very worried and
curious about your mother.
Meet up with her and
give her some reassurance.
When did you get to know
Eun Jung Soo so well?
Have you ever waited
for someone for 17 years?
Of course not, to you that
would be pointless and silly.
You couldn't possibly fathom it.
Mrs. Woo.
What did you say?... Jung Soo.
Mrs. Woo... Mrs. Woo.
Mrs. Woo?
Are you awake?
Do you recognize me?
Uncle.
Here, eat.
Should I put the rice
in the soup too?
Sure.
Come on, dig in!
You don't even listen when I said
stay another day in the hospital.
Why would I check in at the
hospital when I'm perfectly fine?
The doctor said, all I need
is to eat and sleep well.
Well why aren't you sleeping
and eating well then?
You're too young to be
passing out.
Uncle.
Have we ever changed our
address or phone number at all?
Maybe our cell phones but not
our home address and phone number.
Mrs. Woo from the states
had tried to contact me.
Then what should we do?
Should we go apologize and
ask them to change daughters?
You really have a way
with words you know that?
Aren't you embarrassed to
even look up at the heavens?
Aren't you even scared of
getting hit by lightening.
No I'm not.
It's your fault that Kyung Hee and
I were forced into this situation
If anyone gets hit by lightening, it
will be you first. I'm not scared at all!
You were just as involved in this!
Where do you get off acting innocent?
Do you think by confessing now
it will justify what we've done?
The water has already been
spilled... and from now on...
It will continue to be like that!
One of these days, you, me and
Kyung Hee will regret this sorely!
You're right. I'm a wretch!
Five years ago, when I didn't stop
you and Kyung Hee... it's all my fault.
It's all my fault!
I've cleaned the
master bedroom already.
So you don't have to worry
about that room
Goodness! Master bedroom or not, that's
my job! You shouldn't worry about that!
- Then, I'll be on my way.
- Yes of course.
- Have a safe trip.
- I will.
Why is all this here wasting space?
It must be true, before the
accident she was a painter.
If you ask me, they don't
look that great.
This... is Jung Soo.
Besides that picture, what if
she remembers something else?
Her face hasn't changed at all.
If she see's that picture and looks at
Jung Soo's face... she'll know right away.
Mrs. Kim.
Are you heading home?
What are you doing here
at this time of the day?
Oh, I just happened
to get off work early.
Please, go in then.
Yes.
That was close!
Of all people, it had to be him.
- I'm home.
- Oh my gosh, you startled me!
Did I scare you?
- What is that?
- You don't need know.
A picture?
What do you mean Mrs. Kim
took a picture out with her?
I don't know why,
but it was picture for sure.
There's no way.
Are you missing something then?
Seo Hyun. Seo Hyun's picture is missing.
Seo Hyun's picture?
I drew a picture of Seo Hyun
when she was little.
That's the only one missing.
Why would Mrs. Kim take that?
Since it's a picture of Seo Hyun,
she probably just thought it was
a picture of her niece and took it.
But the strange part it is,
why would she hide that?
Study abroad?
You're going to pay for
her education overseas?
I found some decent schools.
Since I don't know what your
grades were like in high school.
No matter where you go, you'll have
to start with English language classes.
At the minimum it takes you
five to six years.
Who are you?
Where did evil wench Kyung Hee go?
Wait, is this all a setup so
you can bully Jung Soo more?
I appreciate the offer but it's
too late for me to study abroad.
With what happened in Dong Dae Mun
and business being slow at the stalls.
I won't be able to study comfortably
knowing what the situation is like here.
Also, I could never burden you
like that.
You should go now.
Jung Soo... don't worry about us,
just go.
And you... you're more than entitled
to take that offer from Kyung Hee.
Why am I entitled?
Pay it back! All you
have to do is pay it back.
When you come back from studying
abroad, just get a job and pay it back.
Why are you in such a hurry
to send her over abroad?
What am I suppose to do? What if she
decides to show up at my doorsteps?
First, I need her out the country.
Only then will I be able to breathe.
And when she does come
back from studying abroad?
She has no education and has
nothing to show for it right now.
But once she comes back she might
look and treat you differently.
How are you going to stand that?
I don't know.
I don't have the tolerance
to think that far.
Right now, all I can think about is
how I'm going to survive at this moment.
So you have to push her mom.
Encourage so she can leave
here as soon as possible!
I'll be going now.
I have know idea,
what any of this means.
Are you going to go?
I'm not sure, it just
came out of nowhere.
Hey, don't you think Kyung Hee
is acting strange?
She would never offer
something like this.
If anything, she'll want to take
what's already in your mouth from you
I'm relieved to see she's
showing some remorse towards you.
Don't say anything and just go.
There's action going on
here with Shin Hwa group!
The rumors about the stolen
design has been confirmed!
There are rumors spreading
about the stolen design sir.
We're trying to figure out the
source of the rumors.
Tell the public relations
team to block everything.
Do whatever you must to stop
this from getting out to the press!
Yes sir.
Isn't President Do and
Director Choi inside?
We don't know, we have
no idea either!
Is it true there was a meeting
with an investigation committee?
We don't know.
Are accusations a design was stolen
from a foreign company true?
- We're asking you a question!
- Say something!
[Shin Hwa Group, the best fashion company
in the country, tainted by stealing.]
Thank you for calling,
this is a Luna representative?
Yes... no, it's not.
- Yes this is Luna team...
- Yes?... no, it is not true!
- Yes, there will be an official report.
- Please check that again for me please.
Director Kang.
Starting now, everything involved
with this issue is off limits.
Mail, messenger, cell phone...
Any topic related to the
incident is prohibited.
We ask for your cooperation until
this situation has been taken care of.
- Yes sir.
What is this?
We can't even block one little lie!
We have reporters banging down our doors!
That is unacceptable!
Also, if there was a
scandal like that.
you should have resolved it properly.
Do you hear those reporters out there?
How long do you people plan on
just sitting there and be idle?
Does anyone have anything to say?
What is it?
Director Do is currently giving
an interview with the reporters.
What?
I'll say this again. Luna brand
did not steal any design at all.
There have been false reports
given by the press and media.
Shin Hwa will be pressing full
charges against these allegations.
Thank you.
Come in.
We found out who supplied
the rumor sir.
The Luna team is one thing but the brand
hasn't even officially made it's debut.
This selfish behavior of yours was a
little too reckless don't you think?
Yes, I agree my judgment was rash.
The news will only get bigger if the
company doesn't do anything about it.
- I couldn't let that happen.
- But denying it doesn't solve it either.
Min Ki, do you think Jung Soo
stole Red Milano's design?
Personally, no I don't.
But nothing has been
confirmed one hundred percent.
We still can't confirm if Red Milano's
design was been copied or not?
Think about it, when designing a bag
The handle, material, logo... these
little things make a huge difference.
What idiot would copy the design without
taking those things into consideration?
So are you implying that
fax was manipulated then?
I don't know how you received that fax.
But from a common sense point
of view, it's hard to accept.
What are you trying to say?
Then are you saying
I made that fax up?
Let's just wait and see.
I'm sure we'll get a reaction
from Red Milano soon.
You're insulting me.
In case, the design was stolen
and Luna's image is tainted.
Also if Sae Kyung takes a blow
for this incident.
You will have to take sole
responsibility for it Director Do.
Director Do, The President is demands
to see you over an urgent matter.
Do you realize what you've just done?
Even if it is an emergency.
You should when to interfere or not.
We did not steal the design.
Didn't you receive documented
proof that design was stolen?
On what grounds are you
declaring that it wasn't stolen!
I just know it's wasn't stolen.
President
Shin Hwa can't standby and let some
weak proof steer us away from the truth.
Just wait a little bit.
It won't take long for
the truth to come out.
You knew that the fastest way to get
Red Milano's attention was the press.
If that's the case...
Then Red Milano will reveal the
truth about the stolen design.
Are you doing this for the young lady
that got fired over the stolen design?
It's not solely for that reason.
I don't know why it's so important that
you clear her name of the false charges.
But to intentionally make Red Milano
look bad to boost our own image...
I'm really disappointed.
I don't know who will benefit
from this, but let's decide that later.
Strike and Reduce
Red Milano by pi.
Expand Shin Hwa group by pi.
Hopefully my calculation will work.
It seems Director Do's interview
has only added fuel to the fire sir.
At a sensitive time like this.
He should know staying out of
the limelight is the best solution.
If it's not someone from the
security department then who is it?
Are they still searching?
Red Milano released an official statement.
Red Milano's designs for the next season
has nothing to do with incident sir.
What is this?
Did Jin Hoo know all along?
The design was never leaked!
Right on the mark! Okay!
Why did you get such expensive zippers?
We won't have anything left!
Oh right! The baseball game
should be on right now!
I wonder which station
it will be broadcasted.
Shocking news, Shin Hwa groups allegations
of stealing designs has been revealed.
Jung Soo, are you watching this?
Red Milano has made an official statement
in regards to stealing their design.
Red Milano's fall designs for 2013.
Have never been leaked.
That means your name has been
cleared of the false accusations right?
How dare they try to blame
this on an honest person!
Hey! Hey!
Where is she going?
We still have a lot of work to do!
Come in.
What's with the serious look?
You knew from the very beginning
haven't you?
That the design wasn't stolen
and the fax you had was fake.
In fact, you planned that fax all along.
Stop talking nonsense.
Ms. Yoo Ah Rah.
It was already confirmed
that she copied my design.
Why did you go so far as to accuse us
of stealing Red Milano's design instead?
Why would she agree to do something
that wasn't beneficial to her?
She was probably embarrassed to admit
that she stole from a part-time employee.
Just confess that you planned
it so you could kick me out.
Just be yourself!
Don't delude yourself... I don't need
to play childish games to kick you out.
What's going on?
Director Kim, your mother is here in
the lobby. Where should I escort her?
I'll be right down!... No! Actually
please take her to the seventh floor.
A guest is here, I'm sorry but
you're going to have to leave.
- This way please.
- Yes.
Mom! I'm glad you're here.
Did I come at a busy time?
I was about to go home anyway,
your timing was perfect!
- Thank you... let's go mom.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Your father will be home late. Should
we go somewhere fancy for dinner?
Sounds good. But you're
responsible if dad get's jealous.