= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 2 =
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
Can I pay the bill now?
Sure.
Master, come here.
Come on.
Wait a second.
Why is this black screen again?
Am I playing Glory or the computer is playing me?
Master.
Is that man playing with your account?
He will probably steal your equipment.
Oh, no.
You bastard.
Won.
I saw the battle start,
so I played a round for you.
How long did it take you to win?
Forty seconds.
This is awesome.
I won.
Well done.
Master.
You just said Glory is more than a battle.
What is Glory?
Glory.
We know each other through Glory.
Glory is the world for all of us.
You need to pay the bill, right?
Sorry.
I'm looking for a job here.
What's your name?
Ye Xiu.
Ye what?
Your name is so similar to the name of the God in Glory
Interesting.
Do you have experience working as a network management?
No.
Can you log into the game for costumers?
Can you examine the network operation?
No.
Can you maintain the network equipment,
upgrade antivirus software and detect unsafe information?
No.
What the hell do you know?
Well.
I know how to Glory.
You are hired.
Let's get this straight.
You don't know anything.
If your performace is poor,
I won't hire you.
I am not running a charity here.
What a mess.
Not bad.
This is too good for me.
Sorry, but you are over thinking.
This is my room.
Your room.
There.
Right here.
This...
The condition here is not exactly good.
However, the staff dormitory is full for the time being.
It's okay. It's fine.
All I need is a bed.
The quilt is at the head of the bed.
Help yourself.
There is no rush.
OK.
Stop.
Hello.
Go and change the light bulb.
The light bulb?
There.
OK.
What's wrong?
Check the switch.
Network manager, where is the instant noodles I ordered?
Coming.
Sorry.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Gave me an extra hour.
Chu, Table 24 adds another hour.
Network manager, more instant noodles please.
All right. I am coming.
I told you to hurry up.
What the hell?
What is going on? Network Manager.
I am sorry.
We are closed for half a day.
Sorry. Come back tomorrow.
For the first time, I realise
installing a light bulb is a technical job.
I'll get someone to fix it.
Stop.
Let's talk about the loss you caused.
You can deduct today's loss
from my salary,
All right.
A full-time employee's monthly salary is 3,000 RMB.
You are still an intern.
You can only get half. That would be 1500 RMB.
Some customers did not pay the Internet fee.
That's 427 RMB.
The meal fee is 361 RMB.
The fee for repair is 500 RMB. The insurance costs 32 RMB.
Let's take a look.
This is today's loss.
Seems like that was just small mistake.
Master, I will go back to work now.
While repairing the Internet cafe, I have no choice but to close up.
You are responsible for that as well.
Looks like
you won't have any salary this month.
Today's loss is
9,892.5 RMB.
When I say I bear the loss, I mean
I'll pay for the light bulb.
I will deduct the change from the loss then.
Nine thousands.
9,892.
How are you going to repay me?
Don't have an answer?
If you don't have an answer,
then you have to listen to me.
From now on,
You will be the network management.
You are responsible for cleaning.
You are also responsible for hard labour.
I can give you a place to live and provide you with three meals for free,
but I won't give you a cent.
Master.
You will get remuneration according to the work you do,
I will deduct them from your debt.
Any problem?
I
No.
Come on and work hard.
Financial crisis caused by a light bulb.
= Jia Shi =
Go.
Get out.
Bro.
The club does not welcome reporters like you.
Bro, please listen to me.
We all know you a huge fan of Ye Qiu.
You have been snooping around here all day.
= Jia Shi Building =
That's all right.
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
= Leaf of Autumn =
This was just fine.
Wait a minute. Let me check,
It will only take a few seconds.
Turn around the screen.
Okay.
You know about computers as well?
Get me a bottle of water.
I will resolve this for you.
How much salary do you get working here?
Are they still hiring?
I am not your peer,
Call me if you need anything.
= Shocking =
I will go to the new District and defeat a newbie.
Let me change a mood.
Be careful, everyone.
When you are fighting on you own,
you will get a lot of rare materials.
Have you three played this game before?
Isn't this just open?
We are not very familiar with this game,
They even kicked me out when we entered the dungeon.
Here comes three newbies.
I will make you miserable then.
OK. You three can follow my lead,
There is nothing scary about Night Evil Cat, the wild cat.
A wild cat?
The cat is bigger than the three of us combined.
We couldn't even take one hit from it.
That's because none of you acted as the bait.
For example,
if I slap you right now,
you will hate me and
chase me around, right?
Right.
This time
he slaps you ten more times.
You will hate him even more and
chase him around,
right?
That's what I mean.
The one who causes the highest AD
will be the target of the monster.
The monster won't attack others.
If we just go and fight against a monster,
it will be a mess.
Night Evil Cat was supposed to attack me,
but it turned to attack others.
In the end, everything is out of control.
Got it?
Got it.
Understood.
I've been talking for a while now.
Have you teamed up yet?
Did you shout out?
We just need to find a Cleric and we are good to go.
I am designing a weapon like this.
I call this a thousand-machine umbrella.
How could you?
You have come up with the idea and
keep it away from me?
There are two materials left.
There are two forms
which cannot be adjusted freely.
When I finish designing,
You are going to kill like crazy and
make your name known by the world of Glory.
OK.
I am looking forward to
the day when the thousand-machine umbrella is made.
My research failed.
I've sealed off a thousand-machine umbrella.
Is there not enough materials?
I'm going to fight through all the dungeons and get the materials.
Wait for me.
Is there anyone who is interested in team up with us?
Have you teamed up yet?
Do you guys need a Cleric?
I will join you.
= Invite Player Yue Zhongmian to the Team =
This one has decent ATN.
He can be the bait very easily.
Let you be the first to be taken away.
This
I'll let you be the second one
who goes into hell.
You are the third.
The Cleric. He needs to survive for the time being.
Never mind. I don't care whether you will die or not.
I am in such a bad mood.
The reward from the dungeon
belongs to me.
Let's go.
= Players Yue Zhongmian, Dun Xing, Ci Sha Zhe, Yi Qiang Chuan Tou and Jun Moxiao Enter the Dungeon of Night Evil Cat =
Night Evil Cat appears.
The Knight.
Hit it.
The Sharpshooter starts shooting.
Everybody, go, go.
The Thief. You need to attack as well.
The Knight can hold up for a while.
Healing.
Don't you see he is hurt?
The agenda of Yue Zhongmian is too obvious.
Jun Moxiao,
are you pretending to be stupid or what?
Healing.
Jun Moxiao, heal the Sharpshooter.
Heal the Sharpshooter.
Jun Moxiao. What's wrong with you?
Can't you see he runs out of HP?
Healing.
What the hell?
Bro. Healing.
I can't.
If I do, the bait will be useless.
Listen to me and heal him.
I am the bait right now. What are you afraid of?
If you make a simple mistake and
can't be the bait,
Night Evil Cat will go after me instead,
just like the three of them.
Are you setting me up
on purpose?
You want to pocket the reward without sharing.
Isn't that your purpose?
The reward of this dungeon is quite rare.
I can't just let some newbies
get the reward.
You made a plan from the very beginning.
Using them to reduce the HP of Night Evil Cat.
Let them be the targets of Night Evil Cat.
I have to say
this is a clever move.
It's just the two of us now.
How about we cooperate and kill Night Evil Cat together?
I will give you half of the reward.
Half?
I prefer to take it all.
You're crazy. If I am dead, you won't live either.
Night Evil Cat has reached the stage of rampage.
You can't handle it alone.
This way no one will get the reward.
You are such a idiot. Jun Moxiao.
I will remember you.
Do you know how strong our Yue Lun guild is?
You're finished.
A man wants to kill Night Evil Cat alone.
He is only a Cleric.
Show me how you are going to kill it.
Congratulations to Players Yue Zhongmian,
Jun Moxiao, Yi Qiang Chuan Tou,
Dun Xing and Ci Sha Zhe.
They are the first team which passes the Green Forest dungeon.
The first. The first.
The first kill in this District.
You are God. Please friend me.
The first kill.
All rise and show your respect to the God.
You are God.
Impossible.
Jun Moxiao. Jun Moxiao.
Jun Moxiao.
How dare you stealing the first kill from me?
I am not a pushover.
Hey!
Hello, Director Cao.
Yes, it's me, Chang.
Reports.
I will send the reports to you tonight.
I have come up with the headline.
It is
“Shocking. Jia Shi Team Changed the Color of Their Uniform“
“Something huge is Happening in Jia Shi Team”
What do you think?
Too bad?
I have another one.
It's called “Why are Flowers so Red?"
“Because they are always accompanies by green leaves”
Wei Cao will not be happy about that.
Then
All right, I will go back immediately.
I shall revenge next time.
Mu Qiu.
No matter how rare the materials are and
how difficult to upgrade a weapon,
= Xing Xin Net Cafe =
I will do everything I can
to make your genius work come true,
I shall take it with me
when I reach the top of Glory.
What the hell?
Network manager.
Master.
I'm sorry.
Bastard.
I can see the God again.
Did he really retire?
You are not going to wait for him to change his mind?
I mean, what if he comes back?
You don't believe in yourself.
You still don't believe me.
What if people ask about this?
What if they think I am the reason
he chose to retire?
They will think I forced him.
They will think I drove away the most valuable player in Jia Shi.
That's good.
Take it as a praise.
Just let them talk.
I don't think this is a praise.
You forced the most power player in the League to retire,
which means you are even stronger than him.
As long as most people accept you,
the opinions of the minor
do not matter.
How many people do you think
will care about someone in the history?
Will it be so smooth?
You're too nervous.
You think you are inferior to Ye Qiu.
You think you can't be the captain of Jia Shi.
You also think Leaf of Autumn is out of your reach,
The title of the Fight God,
I certainly do not think that way.
Do you want people to say things like this?
Of course not.
If you don't do a great job,
they will say so sooner or later.
If you don't want this to happen,
show everyone your true strength.
You are the captain of Jia Shi.
Ye Qiu.
In a few months,
people will forget about someone who retired.
= Jia Shi =
Why are you here again? Get out.
I am a reporter.
= Jia Shi =
Get out.
I am sorry.
The flowers will be delivered soon.
Who are you?
We need to give flowers to our boss. It's urgent.
Get in.
Thank you.
Who are you?
I'm here to deliver the flowers.
Mr. Tao is waiting for them.
Go, go.
Hurry up.
The scene is all set.
Three. Two, One. Start.
Dear audience, hello.
Welcome to the press conference of
Jia Shi club.
Next,
let's give a big round of applause
to the owner of Jia Shi club, Tao Xuan.
He will tell us about
the new plans and strategies for the team.
Hello, everyone. I'm Tao Xuan.
I'm honored to
have the chance to
communicate with people
who support Jia Shi Team today.
Your enthusiasm
touches me a lot.
Meanwhile, I feel ashamed that
I am going to announce
something unfortunate
to you in this press conference.
= Press Conference =
The Bible in Glory,
our beloved captain,
Ye Qiu
decided to step down as captain
a few days ago.
About Ye Qiu's retirement,
as his boss
He really left?
We all know
the level of teams in the League of Glory
is rising dramatically.
The intensity of competition is getting stronger.
Players need to spend 80 hours a week to practice,
which has exhausted them and
given them great pressure.
The club.
How dare he.
I tried to persuade Ye Qiu
to be the consultant of the team.
Unfortunately, Ye Qiu has made up his mind.
We deeply regret his leaving.
But we understand and respect
the decision made by
the former captain of Jia Shi.
Master,
I am so sorry.
I accidentally dropped
some water on the floor.
It makes me mad.
How about adding 5 RMB to my debt?
Money is useless.
My God is not coming back.
As an experienced player,
Ye Qiu has accompanied Glory
for ten years.
For many people, including me,
Ye Qiu
is the legend of an era.
I will never get the chance to see Ye Qiu again.
He won three championship for Jia Shi.
Strictly speaking,
Ye Qiu is the one who retired,
but Leaf of Autumn
is still in Jia Shi.
Without Ye Qiu, Leaf of Autumn
is like an empty shell without soul.
Ye Qiu's retirement is regrettable.
However, Jia Shi needs to move on.
I will never see Ye Qiu again?
His retirement
doesn't represent the end of a legend.
How can you say this after what you have done?
He gives the baton to the next generation
so that they can continue the legend.
The one who takes the baton from him
Move. I can't see.
is the best newcomer of this Professional Alliance,
Sun Xiang.
Bastard.
Get me my computer.
Where is that?
At the bar.
It's an honor to
take the baton from Ye Qiu and
become the new captain of
Jia Shi.
On the very day when Ye Qiu left,
a newcomer
wants to replace him?
He has no idea what he is doing.
With the account, Ye Qiu also told me
something valuable.
Do you like eSports?
What?
If you like it,
consider all of this as a glory,
rather than a chance to show off.
He said to consider all of this as a glory,
Then why are you showing off?
We will come up with a new strategy
in the shortest time possible
to complete the transformation of Jia Shi.
Someone says I am rude.
Then I'll show you
what rudeness really looks like.
There are so many commentaries.
Here comes the keyboard woman.
Everyone is interacting with you.
Captain Sun Xiang.
You just took the position as the captain
from Ye Qiu,
do you think
you are truly qualified for this position?
In other words,
can you be just as good as Ye Qiu?
Just as good?
If that's all I want,
I would not have signed
the contract to transfer to Jia Shi back then.
Ten years ago,
all teams fumbled and moved forward step by step.
That's why they become strong now.
Indeed.
That's how Jia Shi
obtains the title as the best team in Glory.
First,
No, what I want to say is
if Ye Qiu entered the current League matches,
with his strength,
he probably wouldn't become the third winner.
This is the reality.
Strong players emerge from power teams.
If you are immersed in old achievements,
your career as an eSport player will become narrow and
eventually you will be left behind.
Since I have chosen to accept this honor
as the captain of Jia Shi,
I have one goal and one goal only.
From now on, when people talk about Jia Shi,
they will no longer mention the three consecutive championship.
They will think Jia Shi as the best team in Glory.
Leaf of Autumn belongs to Ye Qiu.
Good job.
Well done.
That was so exciting.
In fact, he is right.
What do you mean?
Old players retire and newcomers emerge.
It is the rule of nature. No one can change it.
Say it again.
However,
Old players are not deserted.
The newcomers are not invincible.
In the world of Glory,
there is no difference between the experienced and the newcomers.
Yeah.
In the world of Glory,
In the world of Glory, there is only our love for this game.
Ye Qiu no longer exists in the League,
but Jia Shi and Leaf of Autumn
will dominate the League.
No one can tell until they fight.
Yes.
You don't know until you fight.
Empty eyes. Slow movements.
How long has it been since I saw you?
This is how you abandon yourself.
I finally realised that there are things way more difficult
than playing Glory in this world.
So you are not abandoning yourself?
You want a new start.
I probably won't come back
as a successful.
I bring the things
you didn't take.
Did you watch the live broadcast?
I was too angry so I only saw half of it.
Then I just turned off the TV.
Don't look at it anymore.
Are you worried that I may not be able to stand it?
I am worried that Sun Xiang may not be able to stand it in the future.
My partner knows me the best.
The guild master took the first kill of Night Evil Cat.
When did he become this powerful?
The guild master pretended to be strong,
but he only did this because of that God.
Yes, everyone was dead.
He was the last one standing.
I heard that Jun Moxiao
killed Night Evil Cat on his own.
Jun Moxiao again.
Who is he anyway?
He is just like another Sun Xiang.
Have no respect for his predecessors.
As a journalist,
I am obliged to expose what you truly are.
Jun Moxiao is so despicable
he wouldn't heal other members of the team
so that he could have the reward from the hidden boss all to himself.
Watch out for him, everyone.
Jun Moxiao is so despicable
he wouldn't heal other members of the team
so that he could have the reward from the hidden boss all to himself.
Watch out for him, everyone.
Jun Moxiao is so despicable
he wouldn't heal other members of the team
so that he could have the reward from the hidden boss all to himself.
Watch out for him, everyone.
Let's team up.
Go and fight in a dungeon together.
We are one person short.
Let's team up.
You are the God.
What do you want?
I can't find anyone to team up
because of you.
Now you know your mistake, newbie.
You better learn from this.
Respect those who are more experienced than you.
Understood?
You do have a temper.
How about this?
We know each other now.
Let me join you.
We can cooperate together.
I won't let you off this easily.
I think he really wants to cooperate with us.
You believe him?
Sun Xiang even wants to surpass Ye Qiu.
I knew you are angry about
Ye Qiu's retirement.
Let him be the bait later.
None of us will help him out.
Let Lord Spider make him miserable.
Only if you are willing to be the bait.
What are you waiting for?
Let's go.
We're about to meet Lord Spider.
I will go and provoke it.
Okay, we will wait here.
Come to work right now.
Come with me.
What kind of trap is this?
Is he offline?
It's as simple as that.
What do you think?
He is pretending to run out of HP
to let us guard down.
Then he will revenge,
Looks like you were affected
by what happened last time a lot.
In this USB flash drive,
it is a collection of all the matches Ye Qiu played.
Go and play it on the screen so that everyone can see.
Is this thing even working?
Of course it is.
Wait.
Did I add
the side face of my God into it?
No. I need to check again.
It is about the competitions, not about his look.
What do you know?
Someone who plays Glory well
only has attractive techniques.
My God,
he also has charisma.