= The King's Avatar =
= Episode 7 =
Do you still need me to continue asking?
Here’s the thing, captain.
It's him. First, he said that
he wanted me to do the Dungeon with him.
So I told him that I wouldn't do that.
Then he threatened and lured me.
He also said that
he would use an unfinished item
to bring some kind of umbrella back to life.
He also said he would add a little excitement
to the present Glory.
- Wait a minute. - Even I feel like...
He really said that?
He actually said that.
I want to add a little excitement
to the present Glory.
That's exactly what he said.
He meant it.
If I lied to you, then I am Sun Xiang. That’s the truth.
I’m sorry, Lao Ye.
You’ve still got time to do the Dungeon after the match.
It seems that you haven’t received enough training from the team.
Captain, didn't you just say that
we wouldn’t talk about this?
You will keep your word, right?
Yes, I will.
Unless...
Unless what?
Unless you can blow out a thousand-machine umbrella.
It’s not stealing.
Captain, don’t you think
it’s a little bit shameless?
You see, our team Lan Yu
has always been righteous.
Will this...
How can you say it’s shameless?
We just want to borrow it and study a little bit.
After we’ve done, we’ll return it.
By the way, you may not be able to defeat him.
Captain, you should be responsible for what you said.
I can absolutely defeat him.
Let me tell you, according to my Combat Effectiveness,
I can make his umbrella become a stick immediately.
Believe it or not.
Good. Three hours. I’ll wait for you.
You really just give me three hours?
When can you finish the match with me
at the training camp?
Ye Qiu. Teacher.
Quickly, quickly, quickly.
Go, go, go.
Take it easy. I can do it.
You can't. Why are you so slow?
I don’t have much tricks left. Come on.
We’ve got a chance.
Good.
Not bad, great, boy.
How many matches have you won successively?
You see, Yu Wenzhou is weak.
He’s too slow.
How can I compare with you?
Be quiet.
I'd like to announce one thing to you all.
Our training camp will start the evaluation officially tomorrow.
The person who graded last in the evaluation will be eliminated.
Is everyone clear?
Don't go. Don't go.
Yu Wenzhou, you are the only student I’ve ever seen
who have never won in the regulation matches.
If you lose again this time, you would be eliminated.
If you want to have your own place in eSports,
then you have to work hard.
Got it.
All right, everyone.
Line up and draw lots to choose your opponent.
You first. Quickly.
I’d like to go back.
You first.
Don't be shy, draw one.
Don't be shy.
Come on. You even don’t know how to draw lots?
Come on. Quickly.
Take a look.
Who is it? Open it.
Quickly.
Come on, who is it?
Who?
Don't hide it.
Ye Qiu.
Ye Qiu?
You won the first prize.
You’ve never won, and he has never lost.
We even don’t need to guess.
Yeah.
Come on.
It's okay.
The laughings from my classmates
make me extremely self-contemptuous.
So I started practicing
all day long.
Warlock versus Battle Mega.
The situation is not good.
The only turning point
is whether I can release the Curse Arrow or not.
But it takes me ten seconds to chant
to get the maximum energy.
It is impossible for me not to be interrupted.
# Failure is just #
# the light of success. #
# It's okay for me to start again. #
The only possible way
is to completely control him for ten seconds.
# We are accompanied by self-confidence and strength. #
# Even if we're beaten back #
I can only stall for five seconds.
The chant would still be interrupted.
We must find a way to stall for another five seconds.
# We must try our best to win a battle. #
# We laugh, we cry. #
# We feel sad about setbacks. #
# We accompany each other and grow together. #
# This is our most glorious battlefield. #
# We should fight for our dreams and win nicely. #
# We hug each other and cheer because of success. #
# We spend countless shiny time together. #
# This is our most glorious battlefield. #
# We must try our best to win a battle. #
# We laugh, we cry. #
# We feel sad about setbacks. #
# We accompany each other and grow together. #
# This is our most glorious battlefield. #
# We should fight for our dreams and win nicely. #
# We hug each other and cheer because of success. #
# We spend countless shiny time together. #
# This is our most glorious battlefield. #
He's doomed.
There's no suspense.
He can't defeat Ye Qiu.
There is no suspense.
The game is on.
Dragon Tooth Sprint. Mr. Ye is so fierce at the beginning.
No mercy at all.
Sprint at the beginning?
Look up into the sky.
Mr. Ye Qiu, Mr. Ye Qiu.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Two minutes and eighteen seconds.
In this way, it became the driving force for me to work harder.
Ye Qiu also became the opponent
that I wanted to meet the most in the match.
It's done.
Captain, wait a minute.
What’s this?
The thousand-machine umbrella.
Captain, let me report.
I strictly followed the your instruction.
I successfully and quickly got it.
Mission completed.
So your team Lan Yu stole things so high-key？
It's an robbery.
Long time no see.
You two good friends
who both have strong hearts.
It's not easy for you to see each other,
maybe you can have a talk and improve your friendship.
I'll take it with me. Bye.
You're very interested in my thousand-machine umbrella?
I'd like to see the power of
the thousand-machine umbrella and Freelancer.
I owe you that. Two minutes and eighteen seconds.
I owe that to myself.
Two minutes and eighteen seconds.
Hide yourself to prevent interruption.
Very skilled.
You overpraised me.
Indeed it's an artifact.
It seems that your speed of chant has also improved.
But that's all.
You've got another move.
Did you try your best this time?
I try my best every time.
The thousand-machine umbrella along with Freelancer.
Maybe they can really change the pattern of our league.
It's just...
Maybe you can rely on the thousand-machine umbrella
and Freelancer's various skills to make a difference.
But how are you gonna pass the challenge in the Field of God?
Im not like you. You think too much,
which would cost many brain cells.
If you have the time,
I think you should think about
how to prevent Huang Shaotian from running around.
Ye Qiu.
I hope that the next time I see you,
you can add some excitement to the Glory.
We all suffer pains
while we're growing.
In this glorious world,
we've learned to reconcile with ourselves.
Okay, come on, let's smile.
Three, two, one
Okay.
Hold your chest with both hands.
Good.
Three, two, one.
Okay.
Let's look this way. At a 45-degree angle.
Here.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
No, still not good.
His eyes are too obvious.
One is big and the other is small.
Alright. It's okay. I'll adjust them again.
Make both eyes bigger.
Good, good
Let me try.
Hold it tightly.
Look at a 45-degree angle.
This time, the picture is good.
His eyes now look the same.
Captain.
Go ahead. What is it?
Recently, a guy called Jun Moxiao appears in the 10th District.
All the guilds are not peaceful now.
I suspect that
he's a professional player from other teams.
who tries to cause trouble for us.
This is the end of today's work.
Today's task is very arduous.
Are you ready?
- I'm ready. - I'm ready.
Forty seven.
Forty eight.
How are you doing?
Fifty three.
It's so unfair.
I can only fight one by one while you can fight a group.
Your attack speed is faster than mine.
This time, we're going to fight Toya.
It's not too difficult to defeat him.
But the reason why
he hasn't been defeated for so long
is because of the steps before we can fight Toya.
They're closely linked.
They are not only trivial but also time limited.
We can't make mistakes, Tang.
Mind your own business.
Tang and Bro Ye have been playing the Glory for a long time.
It seems that they cooperate quite well.
But Tang used to
play with us.
Why does she only
play with men now?
Go on.
Watch your steps.
Two guys in front of you.
Tang.
Speed up.
Guoguo, wait a minute.
Tang, let's make a Sky-stirke.
Okay.
Good.
Tang.
We need to try harder.
There's a new cake shop nearby.
I heard the cakes are delicious.
Let's go there together.
I'll go if I have time.
Watch your back.
What's the matter?
There are some questions that I don't know.
You're the only one who can solve them.
Can you teach me?
Of course. Why don't you write them down first?
I'll solve them for you later.
Let's continue.
You play computer games everyday.
Did I invite you to here to play Glory?
You'd better get to work now.
From now on, you just practice with Tang.
and improve her skills. And that's your job.
Go left.
Nasty guy., you're playing dirty.
Delete.
Don't.
- What are you doing? - It's my phone.
What? Who asked you to record it?
Guoguo.
Tang.
Let's go to eat something and play together.
Let's do something interesting.
It's my treat. Let's go.
All right, stop it.
We are now doing the Dungeon.
Can we go later? Okay?
Back off.
Use the best trick. Mind your HP.
Add some HP.
The training strength and difficulties of Team
are not suitable for you.
You should go back to the training camp.
After improving the your skills,
you can come back again.
My name is Qiao Yifan.
I'm an Assassin in the Wei Cao Team.
I am a professional player,
who is always the last one.
A professional player
who has never been on the battlefield before.
Come on.
Two, three.
Yingjie.
Come here and take photos with us.
Come on, come on.
Yingjie. Yifan went to the training school.
It probably will be very difficult for him to come back.
Leave this spot to us.
Get out of the way, all of you.
Let me take a nice-looking photo
with the future captain.
Come on.
Let me knock you out with a brick.
That's my monster.
It's winner's.
Everyone, let's take a ten-minute break.
The following Toya
is a tough battle.
Didn't you just say it wasn't difficult?
This jungle boss is designed
according to the standard of ten people.
Indeed it's not difficult.
But there are only three of us.
Crap.
This Jun Moxiao is doing
Toya's pre-task.
He's already in the last stage.
If nothing happens, he'll achieve another first-killing.
Is he?
All the teammates,
gather in the training room in ten minutes.
It's an emergency training.
Your performances in this training
will be included in this month's evaluation.
If anyone's absent, his score will be zero.
What kind of training? It's so exaggerated.
Absence means zero.
In this case,
If I could perform well in this training,
can I be in the starting line-up?
Let's go, Let's go training.
Go, go, go.
Let's go, Yingjie.
- Hello. - Hello.
Yifan, wait.
Yingjie.
We've got a new opportunity.
A new opportunity?
Let's go.
To where?
Hurry up.
Sorry.
No.
This is an activity led by the captain.
If you can perform well,
then maybe you don't have to go to training camp.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's go.
Captain.
Sit down.
Take a seat.
Yingjie, you go first.
I'll find you.
We'll start in five minutes.
I'll wait here to see your performance.
Go to the Place of Exile. We'll kill a guy called Jun Moxiao.
Thank you.
I have to find a computer
in five minutes.
then can I catch up with this training.
Stop.
What's wrong, boss?
There's an ambush.
Ying Jie, you're the commander. Do it.
Roger that.
Spread out and kill them one by one.
Liu Fei, stay in your position.
Don't lose the target.
Okay.
Yebo, pay attention to Bao Zi. Don't underestimate the enemy.
Xiao Yun, take care of Han Yanrou.
Conserve your strength.
Got it.
Take my brick.
I thought you would use the brick.
It's not bad that we died together.
You're good, Bao Zi. You got the first blood.
Come back quickly to help Tang.
She's stuck in a fight.
Got it.
No need.
You wanna compare APM with me?
I don't believe you can be faster than I am.
Got yourself killed?
I told you that you should wait for Bao Zi.
Jun Moxiao can insist for so long
yet not in the inferior position.
I think it's almost impossible to defeat him in the front.
That's right, Toya.
If they want to fight Toya,
they must pass through this cave.
The terrain here is complicated and is suitable for ambush.
Shadows.
Yingjie, watch your back.
Failure,
is what I expected.
But I didn't expect that
you can lose so fast.
Xiao Yun.
Rashness is your greatest enemy.
The match is never about
who starts first.
Okay.
Liu Fei,
it's good to care about your teammates.
But whenever a teammate is in danger,
you'll lose your correct judgment of the whole situation.
This is the main problem you need to overcome at present.
All right, captain
Ye Bai.
Captain, I'll practice my low-level account well.
I'll find that Jun Moxiao again tonight
and take my revenge.
You think the reason why you failed today
is because you used the low-level accounts.
I...
You all think like that, right?
You're regular members of a champion team.
But you have to get inside the Dungeon
to fight an common player.
It's not worth your efforts at all.
Right?
Yingjie.
How do you think of this Jun Moxiao?
He's very good.
How good is he?
He's experienced.
His attacks and skills are used properly.
All his judgments are accurate.
He is better than all of us.
Yes, better than all of you.
He's great enough to kill all of you.
So don't despise any enemy.
It's a good lesson today.
When you go back home,
take a good look at the video of the match.
I hope you'll learn something.
Who exactly is this Jun Moxiao?
What you've encountered today
is the greatest force in the history of Glory.
Ye Qiu.
- Ye Qiu? - Ye Qiu?
Look at this.
It's interesting.
Hang on, Yifan.
Ask him to stop.
I'll go get him.
You've got ideas, but unfortunately,
you didn't realize your problem.
What's that?
A master is a master.
I feel so hot.
The operation is awesome.
What are you doing?
It's today's training video.
Isn't it the part that Yingjie lost?
Yeah.
Yes, this is it.
It was a terrible loss, wasn't it?
Do you know what this?
It's called the shadows.
Yebo.
Let's watch it again.
Where is the captain?
I think he's gone.
Actually, it's nothing.
Captain's afraid that you might suffer a terrible loss.
After all, your opponent is the master Ye Qiu.
This is it.
Ye Qiu? Jun Mo Xiao is the master Ye Qiu?
A master is a master.
Yeah.
When do you think I can be like him?
Just keep practicing.
I've got no water. Yifan.
Can you pour me a glass of water if it's convenient for you?
Thank you.
One more, Yifan.
- Look at you. - Look at you, Liu Fei.
Look at you.
Look, you lost first.
Don't look at me. I didn't perform well today.
This is not my real strength.
Actually, I think it would be nice
for Yifan to go to the Glory training camp.
If he stays in our team,
it's even worse for him to be a servant forever.
Keep watching. Keep watching
This lost is even worse.
Let's work hard.
Liu Fei. Ye Bo. Here you are.
Thank you. Thank you.
Look at this operation. Awesome.
This is quite handsome.
Isn't that you?
Impressive.
But by the way,
what's the pointing of him being great?
Our Wei Cao Team is better than him.
Exactly.
By the way, Yingjie.
I heard that
the restaurant we always go to
is going to decorate recently.
We may not be able to
eat their takeout for a long time.
So you have to help me eat more these days.
# But I can have endless power when I'm with you. #
Why this expression?
I'm just going to train for a few days.
I will come back.
Come back early.
Of course.
When I come back,
you must defeat that Jun Moxiao.
I heard them say that the captain intends to train you
to be a successor.
Yingjie, come on.
You too. Come on.
I'm leaving.
# This is our most glorious battlefield. #
# We must try our best to win a battle. #
# We laugh, we cry. #
# We feel sad about setbacks. #
# We accompany each other and grow together. #
# This is our most glorious battlefield. #
Actually, I think it would be nice
for Yifan to go to the Glory training camp.
If he stays in our team,
it's even worse for him to be a servant forever.
# We spend countless shiny time together. #
# This is our most glorious battlefield. #
Okay, thank you.