"THE LOST TOMB 2 - Explore With The Note"
"Episode 28"
Granduncle Er and the rest
had remarkable lives.
They encountered thrilling adventures.
It's a pity that us descendants
don't know much about it.
We can only connect the dots...
through things they left behind.
Guess it's better than nothing.
When I'm dead,
there would probably be nothing left.
No possessions.
No memories.
Like smoke dispersing in the wind.
There's been unrest
in the circle lately.
Someone's wavering.
Is it because of what happened...
with Gua Qian Er and Ma Yu?
Yes.
There has been a rumor
circulating around...
about the untimely deaths
of the six men.
Another rumor...
said their pensions were reduced.
Some people are saying
that Gua Qian Er and Ma Yu...
lost their judgment.
We're no longer in pre-liberation.
Making use of connections
doesn't mean party favoritism.
It was handled too indifferently.
There are also those...
who criticized your ruthlessness.
You spared no sentiment
for your own people.
That you were being unfair.
Don't you think...
that they are like rats
in a dark sewer?
They have no capabilities...
and yet they drag others down.
As if their made-up rumors...
could win them some benefits.
Since their hearts are wavering,
why not...
I let them...
falter even harder.
Sorry, ladies.
My friend's here.
Why don't we chat next time?
-Okay.
-Keep in touch. Bye.
-Sure.
-Bye.
Why are you back?
Some things...
are better left in the dark.
Makes life more fun.
Why didn't you find me...
once you wee back?
Think of it...
as a surprise from me.
You've been back a while, right?
Yes.
You contacted others...
but not me.
I was going to find you
in a few days.
Didn't expect...
you to be so impulsive now.
I heard you were almost...
arrested by the FBI in the States.
I just snuck a peek...
at some politician's
personal mailbox...
and browsed their internal web.
Luckily, I was quick on my feet.
They couldn't trace me.
I really don't understand...
the fun of being a hacker.
You don't?
Let me enlighten you.
Say,
you wish to peek into someone's life.
Or perhaps you wish
to know who your men...
are talking to.
Forget about it.
Don't be so stubborn, bro.
It doesn't matter who
we're working for...
in this current society.
With Master Hua,
I get to make money
and keep my life too.
Even if I die,
someone would avenge me.
With you people,
I'd probably die
before I get the money.
I might even die
by our own people's hand.
You better be sure.
Jie Yu Hua's not going to last long!
Shut up!
Or maybe you'd like
to give your men...
a little surprise?
A lot of things...
can be accomplished...
with Internet connection.
This is what I consider fun.
What else do you know about me?
Anything to eat at home?
Nothing.
There's only the
Snake Eye Copper Fish.
Let's have Zihai Hotpot then.
You go ahead.
I'm not hungry.
Gosh, you.
Why are you picking fights
with your stomach?
We're home.
We should eat, drink, be merry.
Fine. I'll eat.
Let's have the crazy, spicy pot.
Sure. Watch the road.
Watch the road!
Looks like...
you're not happy with this present.
I'm telling you this is murder.
How could they say it was an accident?
Lower your voice. My head hurts.
Who cares about your head hurting?
Listen to me.
They were after our lives.
No.
What do you mean no?
Look at us!
Come here.
What?
What I mean is...
they seemed to be
looking for something.
Before I passed out,
I saw them grabbing our bags
from the car.
And, we've been body-searched.
They took the silk book?
And the sword too.
They were after the tomb.
But only the three of us know.
Nobody else does.
Yes, understood.
-Aunt!
-Si Ye.
-Something's happened.
-You can't go in.
-Si Ye.
-You need take charge for me, Aunt!
-Go away!
-The madam is resting.
-That's right.
-Aunt!
-What are you doing, Si Ye?
Go away! Get lost!
Let me in!
I want to see Aunt.
Where is she?
Granny is resting.
What's the matter, Uncle Si?
What does it look like to you?
You got beat up?
Aunt said she's taken care of it.
Is this what she meant?
A bunch of people
showed up at my office...
and started beating up everyone.
Where is the law?
Xiu Er.
Did you have something to do with it?
Why would you even think that?
Xiu Er, I've never done you wrong.
When you were a kid,
I always took you out to play...
and bought you goodies.
How could you...
What are you talking about, Uncle?
I wish for nothing more...
than your safety.
My safety?
Is this what you call being safe?
You've grown up,
priorities have changed.
Over the years,
Aunt has been very clear...
in wanting you to take over
the Huo family.
Did you ever wonder...
if a little, inexperienced girl
like you...
could hold up...
the enormous Huo family?
You'd break your back.
You've been living a fun-filled life.
On whose money?
It was from every one of your uncles,
earning them through our blood,
sweat and tears.
Who gave you the right to the helm...
just because of what Aunt said?
Are you saying I've only received...
and never contributed?
Perhaps my eye sight is bad,
but I sure couldn't tell.
Xiu Er, I urge you to know
where you stand.
The present society...
is ruled by the capable.
The way Aunt operates no longer works!
So what do you suggest?
Aunt, I'm...
This Huo family...
is forever plagued by misfortune.
This is a matter
from two generations ago.
It should no longer be of importance.
But the sword of the Huo family...
is always sharpened by the women.
Because women...
are always smarter.
Smarter than the men.
It's genetics.
I don't blame you.
All this time, your uncles,
aunts, brothers and nephews...
have all gotten along nicely,
and lived peacefully.
So,
why did you suddenly appear?
You're the bringer of misfortune.
One moment you like someone,
the next you don't like someone.
Trouble follows you everywhere.
Whose feathers did you ruffle?
Now you've caused trouble...
outside of the family.
That's because you weren't being fair.
I wasn't fair?
Let me tell you something then.
You have no idea.
Everything you get to enjoy today...
was exchanged through the lives...
of the Huo women.
Do you know that?
And yet you complain.
Haven't you been fed...
with only the best?
You have no gratitude.
I'm warning you.
I can forget about
what happened today...
but it doesn't mean
I'm cleaning up after your mess.
You need to pay the consequences...
for what you've done wrong,
understand?
Aunt!
You brought me up yourself.
You can't throw me to the wolves!
You.
You don't know how to be grateful.
You've abandoned
your loyalty and morals.
Tell me, what good are you to me?
No good. No good at all.
I wouldn't try,
for my own sake.
You created this mess.
You handle it yourself.
Whatever punishment you have coming,
you need to accept it.
Get out!
Get out of my sight.
Okay, fine!
If you're resolved...
to cast me aside,
I'll just have to expose you!
You think I don't know what...
the Mystic Nine is all about?
The Huo family is far from pure.
Look at that temper.
You could say that the Huo family...
is like having a jade...
pop out from a crack in the rocks.
The liverwort...
has taken root in the flesh.
If you don't remove it,
it would become a useless rock.
If you be more ruthless...
and cut it off,
it might...
have a chance at becoming
an icy jadeite.
Granny, the Huo family
is an Emperor Jadeite.
You're right, yes.
Emperor Jadeite, we are.
Wake up, Yao.
You set the alarm yesterday...
to wake you up at 8 a.m.
Wake up, Yao.
You set the alarm yesterday...
to wake you up at 8 a.m.
Yao, wake up right now!
You have a lot to do today!
You'll be in a lot of trouble
if you don't get up now!
Yao, wake up right now!
You have a lot to do today!
You'll be in a lot of trouble
if you don't get up now!
Why is the me yesterday...
so mean to the me today?
A well-established critic...
trying to learn opera?
Why?
Trying to be a double threat?
Best not overwork yourself.
What on earth is Jiu Ye thinking?
No matter what,
Jie Yu Hua is Jiu Ye's
biological grandson.
What era are we living in?
Who still cares about that?
Besides,
he's not the only one...
connected by blood.
Don't forget.
There's still that Zhai Xing Yao.
Wasn't Zhai Xing Yao...
adopted by Jie Yu Hua's parents?
Supposedly so,
but he's actually
the illegitimate son.
Really?
You see,
the biological son
was adopted by Jiu Ye.
Meaning the spot is there...
for the illegitimate son.
Yao and Yu Chen have never got along.
He recently left the country in a fit.
His friends and roots are here though.
In my opinion,
anybody but Jie Yu Hua...
is okay to take over.
The Xie family would have to
change their name to Zhai now.
Be it Xie or Zhai,
it is still a family
of Xie's descendants.
Master Hua,
several of the Xie seniors...
met with seniors of the circle...
concerning the official proceedings.
The last time they had a meeting...
was when you first became the head.
Now another one?
They're clearly breaking ranks here.
We can't let them.
Back then, Xie Jiu Ye
wanted to be democratic,
giving everyone
a chance to participate.
That's how the Xie family survived.
I don't see anyone else
having this rule.
And they're still doing well.
Yet, the Xie family rules...
has harbored greed among some.
What's the agenda of the meeting?
To change the head.
They want Zhai Xing Yao
to be the head.
That punk was adopted by the Xies.
He's far from qualified.
He's getting ahead of himself.
I heard he's been contacting those
who didn't like the way you operate.
I bet...
he's the one pulling the strings.
Yao.
We used to be so close.
Master Hua, your problem
is that you're too sentimental.
Too sentimental with the Huos,
and to Wu Xie.
Don't tell me you're the same
with Zhai Xing Yao.
You need to see if it's worth it.
Inform everyone.
I agree to the meeting.
Tomorrow night at nine.
At the Xie family home.
Wait, why do you accommodate them?
I'd just show them the door.
Since this is the Xie family rule,
as the head,
I cannot allow...
anyone to operate
outside of the system.
I suppose.
You have a point.
Actually, there's nothing to worry.
There are more who supports you
within the Xie family.
♪ Passing the peonies. ♪
Nice!
♪ In front of the fence. ♪
Lively and full of expression.
Look at him go.
He's got the chops.
I'm sure he'd be
a generational superstar.
Aiding you...
in collecting masterpieces
all across the land.
Looks pretty young.
♪ Unclasp your collar. ♪
Do you hear that voice?
So full and bright.
♪ Loosen the clothes. ♪
Bravo!
Let's go talk to him.
Looking for me?
The tea's cold. Get a new pot!
What's the time now?
Why isn't Master Hua here?
Is he going...
to leave us hanging like this?
It's only 7.50 p.m.
Why are you so anxious?
He's the VIP.
It's only right
to be the last to arrive.
I don't care.
Eight o'clock.
I'm leaving on the dot
if he doesn't come.
You can leave now if you want.
You need to walk the talk.
What are you saying?
Why don't you figure it out yourself?
Why are we here today?
I'm sure everyone knows.
But there's always some
who are clueless.
Believing that with enough ants,
they could take down the elephant.
Who gave you the right to speak?
How many years has it been
since you joined the Xies?
If it's experience,
I can't compare with you for sure.
But if it's abilities,
someone like you...
that only waits for the bonus
without lifting a finger...
has no right to criticize me.
Watch your mouth.
You little punk, you.
You're stepping out of line!
Come, sit.
Don't let him get on your nerves.
Come on.
What's the occasion today?
Everyone's here.
Sorry, Master Zhai.
Your spot is not here.
Please.
Everyone.
Which one of you today...
is going to give up your seat...
to Young Master Zhai.
Young Master Zhai,
why don't you sit here?
Today, I'll be sitting here.
Are we going ahead with the meeting?
Otherwise, I'm going to go.
Xie Yu Chen...
won't be coming today.
But it's okay that he's not here.
The official affair still proceeds.
Just because you said so?
Where do you stand?
Me?
I'm a year younger than Xie Yu Chen.
I guess I'm considered
his younger brother.
Since my older brother's not here,
it is only right for me...
to conduct the official affairs.
Any objections?
I object!
The head is not here.
No one has the right
to replace him...
and chair the meeting.
Isn't the agenda today...
to find a replacement for the head?
I believe everyone here...
is qualified for the position.
Remember what Xie Jiu Ye said before?
We need to be democratic.
Let's not waste any time...
and practice democracy.
Let's...
raise your hands to vote.
Come on.
Raise your hand if you wish
to replace the head.
You guys better be sure.
Even the American president
changes every 4 years.
So why...
can't the Xies change their head?
We need to be in tune with the times.
The only constant in life...
is change.
It's about time the Xie family
got some new blood.
All right, that's decided then.
Let's discuss the second agenda.
Who will be the new head of house?
My candidate is...
Zhai Xing Yao.
Those who agree,
raise your hand.
Those who agree, raise your hand.
♪ A pair of birds
sits on the tree... ♪
"Zhai Xing Yao"
A friend's betrayal is the worst.
Imagine if I sent
the photos to Yuan...
"Zhai Xing Yao"
These are records of everything...
you took from the Xie family.
It includes all the secret deals...
you conducted using Xie assets.
Did I miss out anything?
-Big!
-Small!
Make it a big!
-Give me a big!
-Small!
-Big!
-Small.
Do you even know what you're doing?
Look at this hand!
Stop whining just because
you're unlucky.
Mind your own business!
You're disrupting my game!
-Don't argue.
-Shut up.
Again, let's go!
-Again...
-Make your bets.
-I'm betting on small.
-Get on with it.
-Come on.
-I know it's coming.
Bet on small! Trust me!
Sign your name...
and all this money is yours.
I've borrowed from you
countless times.
Why did the interest go up?
Uncle Liu, times are challenging.
We need to eat too.
Still, 28 is too high.
I actually have a suggestion.
No need for you to pay any interest.
You are Master Hua's uncle.
That makes me Yao's uncle too.
I'll try to be objective.
For many years,
Yu Chen has worked hard...
to preserve Xie family's reputation.
His contribution...
is clear for all to see.
But it was really tough on him.
As his paternal uncle,
it pains me to see him like that.
Who can help lighten his burden?
It's Yao, of course.
Yao is capable.
Also, a descendant of the Xies.
He should do his part for the family.
Don't you all agree?
-Yes.
-That's right.
The head is not here...
and you guys run amok.
When Master Hua comes back...
I already told you.
He's not coming back.
What do you mean?
You dare endanger Master Hua?
Don't assume.
He's my brother.
You lot need to grow some balls.
Those in favor of me being head,
raise your hand.
You, you and you.
No one objects, right?
I object.
The Xie family does need
a new head of house.
But it shouldn't be a bastard child...
who would risk his brother...
in order to climb the ranks.
Fifth brother,
don't assume there's rain
when you hear the wind.
Yao and Yu Chen are brothers.
What brothers?
That's nonsense!
Yao's parents...
were friends with Yu Chen's mother.
They died in a car accident.
Yu Chen's mother took pity on him...
and adopted him.
You can get a DNA test
if you don't believe me.
Yu Chen's parents
brought him up with care...
and the Xies treated him
like their own.
And what does he do?
In order to become the boss,
he's thrown Yu Chen under the bus.
Such a character...
is not fit to be Xies' leader!
Yes, Fifth Brother is right!
I think Fifth Brother...
is the most fitting candidate.
If it's Fifth Brother taking over,
I support it whole-heartedly.
Fifth Brother, you claimed
that Yao hurt Yu Chen,
but what proof do you have?
He admitted it himself.
I was only kidding.
Why?
Do you also think
he won't come back?
I've been told...
that Yu Chen had been
attacked in the village.
You can't simply make up stories.
Perhaps he got stuck
in a traffic jam on the way.
Someone shot him!
This isn't the USA.
People don't go around swinging a gun.
That's enough.
Allow me to butt in.
We all know Fifth Brother...
and what he's done...
over the years.
This whole time,
he's been handling...
all the affairs on behalf of Yu Chen.
And, there is not even...
a single problem in the books.
That's why...
I think the new head of house...
should be Fifth Brother.
Don't you all think so?
Right?
-I agree...
-Me too.
I agree...
Fifth Brother was born to be
a prime minister.
So he should continue
being the prime minister.
But Yao has what it takes
to be the helm.
Sixth Brother.
I heard...
you've accumulated
almost 7 million in debt...
at Li Wei's casino.
You recently cleared the debt.
Where did you get the money from?
You accepted Yao's money...
and so you're defending him.
You sure are a very worthy uncle.
If that's the case,
those who support Fifth Uncle,
show your hand.
One, two, three, four, five.
Please keep your hands raised.
There are some people...
who have yet to raise their hands.
They don't support me...
nor Fifth Uncle.
Does that mean you guys...
continue to support Xie Yu Chen?
I won't bow down to anyone
but Master Hua!
That's right!
Good.
Are you sure?
A dead man...
can't protect you.
Master Hua is here.
Fifth Uncle.
Would you like an anti-anxiety pill?
You don't look so good.
Three things.
One,
the head of the Xie family is me.
Two,
assassinating the head of house...
means betraying the Xie family.
An unforgivable act.
You've got the wrong person!
It was Zhai Xing Yao's idea.
You don't have long to live.
Stop dragging your family down.
Make some money while you can...
so your wife and kids
can live a good life.
So long as you kill Xie Yu Chen,
you get to keep the 10 million...
no matter you survive or not.
Looking for me?
Master Hua!
How is my disguise, brother?
Fifth Uncle.
Is my brother's life
worth only 10 million?
How stingy of you.
You guys better not think
you're blameless.
Zhai Xing Yao and Xie Yu Chen
put on this show...
for only one purpose.
It's to find out...
those that do not support Yu Chen.
None of you are getting away!
Hand over the culprit
and recording to the police.
Three.
Those that doctored the books,
fix it within a week.
And I'll bury the hatchet.
After one week,
hand it over to the police.
Understood.
Yu Hua, you were too easy on them.
Fish can't survive
when the water's too clean.
Besides, the Xie family...
has never been a place for saints.
That's true.
Saints wouldn't be in
this business to begin with.
You're not actually a Xie.
We share the same account.
How am I not a member of the Xies?
You know what I mean.
I don't.
♪ We live extraordinary lives... ♪
♪ by exploring a new horizon. ♪
♪ Let's fly with faith! ♪
♪ Let's fight together! ♪
Don't forget the 10 million
from Sixth Uncle.
Why should I?
It's your deal.
Why should I settle it for you?
You're my older brother, right?
♪ Let our hearts ignite! ♪
♪ I'm fearless of danger. ♪
♪ I won't be ordinary! ♪
♪ I am the roaring waves! ♪
What's missing?
Laptop.
Some old playthings.
And also an archeology journal
I kept as a kid.
Nothing of value is gone?
That's it then.
It must be the same guys who hit us.
Think.
What else could they be after?
Could they be after...
my grandfather's notebook?
Your grandfather's notebook
is missing?
Before leaving,
I kept the Snake Eye Copper Fish
and the notebook...
in the safe at my parent's place.
Who could it be?
Qiu De Kao.
Ning, how's the investigation going?
We are still trying...
to track down those people.
Wu Xie nearly got run over by them.
The car and the house...
had been searched.
They were obviously
looking for something.
I did a check on the van.
Drunk driving
and running the red light.
It did look like an accident.
The other two cars...
were suspicious though.
They had fake plates...
with records of hit-and-run.
Even the police couldn't identify
who the drivers were.
Pause the investigation.
Now,
you need watch out.
We can't afford to lose Wu Xie yet.
Protect him.
Sir, any idea...
who they are working for?
Not at the moment.
This Mr. Zhang...
was a prominent figure in Changsha.
He came from a wealthy family.
He enjoyed watching plays...
and idolized Granduncle Er.
He supposedly invited Granduncle Er
to perform privately.
After liberation,
his family factory was handed over...
and he became a worker himself. But,
he's hidden away some money.
The man has a son.
Spoiled and obnoxious.
Addicted to gambling.
He lost everything
and accumulated a huge debt.
He forced his old man...
to use all his asset...
to pay his debt.
The old man ended up...
with nothing but that headpiece.
The son was going to sell
even the headpiece.
But the old man wouldn't let him.
He called it his lifeline...
and held onto it.
The latest update?
The old man is dead.
The son plans to sell the headpiece...
so he can continue to gamble.
You sure it's Granduncle Er's?
I've had it appraised.
It's the real thing.
The exact same headpiece...
was seen at Granduncle Er's place.
It should be real, yes.
Master Wu, everything's packed.
It's been so long...
that it feels foreign.
We've traversed the globe...
but nothing beats this place.
It's home.
Master Wu.
Aren't you going to pay...
Young Master Wu a visit?
Me, visit him?
He's not dead nor incapacitated.
No thanks.
What did you find out
about those people?
The ones who hit
Young Master Wu's car...
are the ones who broke in.
Same gang.
Not locals.
They are paid professionals.
They don't know
who the mastermind is either.
But after taking
Young Master Wu's things,
they did as the client wanted...
and left them in a drawer
at the mini market.
Surveillance at the area is minimal.
They can't find out who did it.
Master Wu.
Do you have any suspicions?
Tell me, I'll get it done.
No, now's not the time to react.
Young Master Wu is an open target,
whereas they're hidden.
If they try again,
I'm afraid Young Master Wu...
might not be so lucky again.
My nephew is not an idiot.
He still has his friends.
If they go for another bout,
who knows who would come out on top.
Master Wu.
Isn't it better...
to nip them in the bud?
I'm afraid troubles will follow suit.