"THE LOST TOMB 2 - Explore With The Note"
"Episode 36"
Uncle San Xing,
why are you here?
Why are you here?
Uncle San Xing.
Tell me.
What happened?
Nothing happened.
Hurry back, boy.
Your friends are waiting.
Uncle San Xing,
why?
Why are you still...
hiding the truth from me?
I'm Wu Xie, Uncle.
I'm Wu Xie!
If you don't go back now,
your friends are
definitely going to die!
Kids,
where is this?
Kids!
Come in, quick.
Quick!
Who is he?
We have to tell the chief.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Go! Go quickly!
Take a seat.
Who are you?
How should I address you?
I'm Jin Yang.
Besides me,
no one else will let you stay.
Why?
What is this place?
Why did you save me?
You came from a place
where you shouldn't have.
People here don't welcome you.
Check if you're missing anything.
If there isn't then...
leave quickly.
Thank you.
You really don't remember...
how you...
came to this place?
I really don't remember.
Also, once I think about it...
my head starts to ache.
How did I wake up to...
a snow mountain?
What is this place?
This is Dongbei,
Changbai Mountain.
Changbai Mountain?
Do you have a phone?
I'd like to make a call.
The chief has one at his place...
but the heavy snow has...
damaged the signal tower.
What about a computer?
You really don't remember...
how you...
came down from above?
Came from where?
Where you were from.
The Forbidden Land on
the edge of the mountain.
As far as I know,
no one...
lives or comes back from there.
What Forbidden Land?
Isn't that just a snowfield?
Besides snow,
there's nothing else there.
On the way here,
did you find anything?
Tell me,
how can I leave here?
How far away is
the closest train station?
Wait for the supply truck to come,
it'll be here next Tuesday.
It's so pretty.
That was shot by my sister.
She's the best huntress of
our village in these recent years.
Where is she?
Our village has a rule...
that women can't hunt.
So, she stole...
my dad's hunting riffle and...
went deep into the mountains.
She stayed there for a week...
and finally...
she hunted down this rare snow cattle.
This horn...
was her coming of age present to me.
As she gets better,
she gets braver.
She doesn't believe the myth
of the Forbidden Land.
She insisted to venture there.
As a result...
She never came back again.
I don't believe that...
she was ever stuck there.
But even if she comes back alive,
there's...
no place for her here anymore.
Your family...
didn't go looking for her?
There's only the two
of us in the family.
I've tried looking for her...
but before I could enter the paddock,
they caught me and took me home.
That place is not clean.
Once you go there and...
come back,
you are no longer yourself.
All right,
it's getting late.
You should get some rest.
The room is in there.
"Forbidden Land"
Wu Xie's diary.
Changsha?
Ning!
Drink some ginger soup.
It'll warm your body.
Spending a night in the snow...
will make you sick.
Thank you.
This...
looks rather precious.
This is my...
most prized possession.
Do you need help?
It's fine.
Can you tell me about...
the Forbidden Land?
The Forbidden Land...
is Changbai Mountain's...
root to the Dragon Vein.
Dragon Vein?
That's right,
Dragon Vein.
This is passed on from generation
to generation in our village.
It seems...
so noble and mysterious.
But to us,
it's very scary.
Due to it being the
root to the Dragon Vein.
Besides...
where the root lies,
everywhere else...
is a deathtrap of bad feng shui.
Barren mountains and unruly rivers,
evil spirited land form.
Not one blade of grass grows.
Once a wild beast enters,
it'll suffer magnetic interference,
triggering it's primal instincts,
losing all senses...
and lastly die from madness.
Same goes for humans.
If you're lucky enough...
to come back alive,
you'll still be infected
by an odd disease.
And...
it's infectious.
Many years ago,
a mountaineering team
once made a big offer...
to look for a guide.
But, no one dared to accept.
"2013, Fall"
Who is it?
Sir,
the man is on the move.
Anything we should do?
Ning,
aren't you a little too
concerned about Wu Xie.
You should know the affect of...
that Wu San Xing on him.
Wu Xie hasn't recovered yet,
he's not going anywhere.
You need to stay put.
Shun Zi on the other hand,
is a dubious character.
Keep an eye on him...
and report to me...
whenever there are new developments.
I understand, sir.
Little Master?
If I hadn't noticed you in time,
I would have...
shot you in the head.
Wait!
How did you...
Stop following me.
You may not have...
such good luck next time.
Little Master,
what's wrong with you?
I'm Wu Xie.
Don't you recognize me?
Little Master!
Save me!
Little Master! Watch out!
Little Master! In front of you!
Little Master!
Three more are coming up!
Let me down!
Little Master!
Don't go!
Here.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
This is the hunting grounds,
why are you here?
I saw someone I know,
so I followed him here.
You have someone you know here?
His name is Kylin Zhang.
He wears all black,
tall and skinny,
and doesn't talk much.
You're talking about...
that weirdo?
You know him?
I don't know him.
He's not from our village.
He came here three months ago.
Three months ago?
Hey pal!
You're being too unreasonable.
This car fare is too little.
Unreasonable?
The money I gave is more than enough.
This bit of money...
barely covers for gas.
Don't you know how far I've driven?
Brother,
quit bluffing.
As if I don't know
where Snow Village is.
This is my home!
I used to live here!
I'm just coming home from Beijing!
You went round and round...
showing off...
your driving skills,
twisting and turning there!
Obviously, that'll waste your gas.
Only because the snow
sealed up the road.
Hurry and pay up!
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
Let me tell you,
I'll go wherever I please.
I shoot bears with my eyes shut.
I'm telling you,
you're playing a fool's game here.
I've got money,
but I'm not giving you.
Come punch me if you dare!
Stand still!
Come back here!