If you had hoped
that the robot was a human,
fold a finger.
♫ Someone like me ♫
♫ Can someone like me do it? ♫
♫ I really am jealous ♫
♫ I am afraid of getting hurt more so I backstep ♫
I'm not a robot.
[Episode 15]
It feels like we got played by Sun Hye.
Sorry about that. It's all because she doesn't like me at all.
She is the only soulmate that Jo Ji Ah has.
Seeing Sun Hye's reactions, I must have really wronged Ji Ah.
It really feels like I'm in a one-sided love these days.
But we still came this far.
It's all thanks to you guys.
If only I didn't send that threatening mail to MIT at the time, then you wouldn't have gone through all that.
If you are sorry then you should hurry up and fix AG-3.
Okay.
The moon is so bright.
It's just a crescent moon though.
But why are you touching his ears?
This is the only way I can make him sleep. Sleep, sleep.
I think there is a problem with the pressure sensor.
I guess we just have to stabilize it.
Oh, it's moving. So is it all fixed now?
It needs time to stabilize. It also needs to synchronize with you as well.
Stabilize? And synchronize?
What that means is... AG-3, pick up the cup.
As you can see, the system hasn't stabilized yet.
It looks like the data you received for AG-3's deep learning has collided with AG-3's main system.
But Kim Min Kyu shouldn't find out that you and AG-3 were switched. If she's like this, we'd get caught right away.
I understand.
In three days you and AG-3 will be switched and the test will be over in no time.
And when that time comes, I will tell Kim Min Kyu everything as is.
Until then, you must make sure not to get caught for being a human.
This particular test result is very important to Kim Min Kyu, too.
Three days? Okay, fine. I will wait.
Oh, yeah. I have a favor to ask you.
Do you think you can allow me to come to work late in the evening tomorrow?
I have something to take care of during the day.
Sure.
Thank you for explaining everything to me in detail and taking away my curiosity.
I'm in Korea right now. It looks like I can finally meet AG-3.
I have an appointment in the afternoon, so would it be okay to stop by on the way?
You should come next time.
Why? Did something happen to the robot?
No, it's not that. Actually, something happened to me.
What sort of problem?
I was at ease since you haven't been asking for a sleeping pill prescription. Is there a different problem now?
The problem occurred unexpectedly and I am going to take care of it today.
All right, good luck with that then. Today's the day for your blood test, right? Send it right away.
Recently, he seemed happy that the robot liked him, yet...
I wonder if something happened within the last two days?
What should I say? What kind of expression should I have when I greet him?
Calm down. Calm down.
Master!
Where are you?
Go get changed. We are going out.
What should I change into?
Dress in something warm. We can't have your battery drain because of the cold weather.
[Lovely's Room]
That outfit won't do.
What's going on?
Could it be... a date?
From head to toe, as is.
Okay.
Carry that.
Let's go.
What the hell? He didn't even look at it. He didn't compliment how pretty I look either.
Why is he buying me all this if he's going to be like that?
Wait a minute. This way, please.
We will be bringing out the meal the way it was reserved.
Thank you for accepting my invitation.
I was the one that wanted to have a meal with you and Ri El.
I knew it.
But still. He should've let me know earlier so I could prepare myself emotionally.
How's the food?
It's very tasty. I'm quite fond of it actually.
I'm glad that the flavor suits you well.
It suits perfectly for me, too.
So, what is the important thing you want to tell us about?
Let's get engaged first.
I want to follow the right procedures for Ri El.
An engagement? I haven't even kissed you yet.
That's a good idea. Procedures are important.
- Dad.
- It's necessary for people to
officially recognize us as one.
That way, no one's going to make a vain effort.
I agree with you.
Hey, I'm the one getting married.
Can you listen to my opinions, too?
Let's eat.
Excuse me for a moment.
When have you started liking Ri El?
Fifteen years ago.
Ri El sent me a birthday card each year.
I really thank you for that.
Cards? When did I ever—
She tends to be very affectionate.
Dad, what was all of that earlier?
Did you send Min Kyu cards using my name?
Why would you do that?
If I sent it, it's the same as you sending it.
Dad, you can leave first.
I'm going to tell Min Kyu the truth.
Min Kyu said thank you.
If you tell him the truth,
it'll hurt Min Kyu a lot.
So annoying.
Oh, what's that girl doing?
It's hard to get an appointment here, and she came by herself. How mannerless.
Wasting money like that.
Get up. Let's go.
Are you okay?
About what?
You can't eat food that others make.
- So, earlier...
- Are you really worrying
or is it just dialogue cued by input?
Why did you bring me out today?
You had to be there.
Do you remember what you said last night?
I said that I wished you were human.
I remember all of what I said.
So? What does it mean to you?
Why?
Will you marry me instead?
If what I said bothers you, erase it just like last time.
It doesn't matter to me whether you remember it or not.
You're really not a good person.
I told you I'd reset you if friend mode appeared!
Reset me, then!
But I'm going to have to say what I need to say. Why are you doing this to me?
That's what I want to ask. Why are you doing this to me?
You're just a robot, yet why are you making me look after your feelings?
Why are you making me curious about your thoughts?
To you, who does not have feelings or thoughts. Why?!
Make a list of dresses
for Ri El to wear.
That is what a robot like you should do.
What's wrong with your face?
It's nothing.
Did something happen with Kim Min Kyu?
No, not really.
What did that punk do this time?
When I said I wanted you to be human.
So? What does it mean to you?
Why?
Will you marry me instead?
♫ I have been in pain for a few days ♫
[Hong Joo: Are you busy? Can you take Dong Hyun to the hospital?]
♫ Because my heart is overwhelmed by you ♫
♫  Breathing  ♫
♫ And falling asleep ♫
♫  are hard  ♫
♫ Even though I'm next to you, ♫
♫  my heart can't go next to you. I will always  ♫
♫  just long for you ♫
[To Min Kyu: Are you doing well? Happy 15th birthday. I'm in Slovenia right now! Have a happy birthday. From: Ri El]
[Have a happy birthday! From: Ri El]
[From: Ri El]
The handwritings are
all different.
♫ I want to call you  ♫
Why didn't you know all this time,
Kim Min Kyu?
♫ Repeating over and over the words of my heart ♫
♫  No matter how much I yell, ♫
♫ It doesn't seem like you can hear ♫
♫ Every day, only in my heart and only with my eyes ♫
♫ I could say ♫
♫ The words of love for you ♫
Customers who are visiting our store, welcome!
Welcome, customers.
Gosh, that scared me.
What the heck? It looks uselessly real.
Customers who are visiting our store, welcome!
♫  I want to tell you.  ♫
♫ I want to let you hear ♫
♫ Lingering right at the edge of my lips ♫
♫ Repeating over and over the words of my heart ♫
♫  No matter how much I yell, ♫
♫ It doesn't seem like you can hear ♫
♫ Every day, only in my heart and only with my eyes ♫
♫ I could say ♫
♫ The words of love for you ♫
Get out.
I don't have AG-3. Just stand there and tell me.
You've gotten a lot better. Get out.
I need to talk to you face to face.
What do you want to say?
I asked you to not use her carelessly before.
Not use her carelessly?
You're talking as if someone hurt the robot.
The robot's existence is special to me.
Isn't that the same for you?
You said the robot's existence cured your illness.
The robot doesn't even have emotions.
She is a robot that you're supposed to train.
You have to spend time and effort.
So what?
Did the robot form emotions?
The robot cannot.
In the end, it's nothing.
How is it nothing?
Are the times you spent together nothing?
Every action you took became a part of her.
How is that nothing?
If it isn't nothing,
then delete it.
It's that easy.
Hey, Kim Min Kyu.
It's not like he's going through puberty, so what's wrong with him?
A moment, please.
Ssanip ate food that was Jo Ji Ah's.
I witnessed her giving him all of her food to eat.
Repenting about how we must have underestimated Jo Ji Ah a little too much,
I, therefore, analyzed her data.
The reason why Jo Ji Ah started this part-time job is money.
But what's the reason for her to restart the part-time job even though she wouldn't get paid?
She said she was uncomfortable with getting too much money.
If we translate that liberally, doesn't it mean I've been on her mind?
Could that really be it?
At this moment in time, there is a need for us to analyze the items in her suitcase.
Her suitcase was for lodging and food. However, why did she bring two of the same heart lamps?
Why did she demand lodging and food here?
Because of me?
You are just a constant.
However, at times like these, a variable may control the situation.
Not too long ago, KM Financial hosted a competition for young entrepreneurs.
I found out that her heart lamps made it to the final rounds.
The heart lamp's prototype
made it to second rounds four years ago in an idea competition among college students.
I was able to find that out after looking it up online.
Jo Ji Ah treats these lamps as if they are artifacts.
Although you were unable to recognize these lamps, you fixed these for her.
This is the only thing that connects the past and the present.
I've deducted that these heart lamps could be your broken part that needs to be fixed.
Wow, it's really swollen. Does it itch a lot? Do you have a runny nose?
I'm okay. Relax, Aunt.
I'm sorry. My stomach was cramping up.
Little one, don't make it hard for your mom.
You don't have to go to the hospital?
They said that as long as I don't overexert myself, it's okay.
But... Dong Hyun has to go the hospital.
Did you eat yet?
That looks good.
Wow, that looks good.
This reminds me of the past.
At the picnic, the kids saw that you brought rice balls and made fun of you.
I thought my rice balls were quite delicious, but when I saw that no one wanted to eat them I was a little sad.
I know, right? Considering the fact that an elementary school student made them, those were really tasty.
It's good, right?
I made a special appointment at a university hospital for her.
I found a doctor who's the best at treating allergies.
Since it's her first time there, please explain well in my stead.
Dong Hyun, these patches would've been itchy but you did well enduring them.
It's not only peanuts, but it's also green grapes, egg whites, and tomatoes.
She even got an allergic reaction to ticks.
- Could you scan her?
- Yes.
Let's go.
Besides her allergies, her oxygen saturation level is low, so I'll prescribe you some medicine.
It's gotten worse recently so it's been worrisome.
This isn't very likely, but there could be an emergency, so I'll also prescribe you some epinephrine.
Can I ask a question?
I know this situation doesn't make sense and sounds very odd, but
by any chance, is there an allergy where you can't come into contact with other people?
There are only a few cases in the world, but that type of allergy does exist.
However, the problem is that due to its psychological cause, it's very hard to treat.
Why? Do you know someone who's like that?
No, no. How do you treat someone with a human allergy?
There has been a case where someone got better when he found someone he could fully trust.
The human mind is quite mysterious, right?
There really is an allergy like that.
Then does Kim Min Kyu have an allergy to human contact?
But I'm a person. I've seen him come into contact with people.
It doesn't make sense.
Since our Dong Hyun went to the hospital, here's a gift.
I have to go to the market. Hong Joo wants me to pick up some things.
Dong Hyun, Auntie will be back quickly.
Bring snacks when you come.
It's a secret from your mom.
Dong Hyun, I'm going to the bathroom and it will take a little bit of time. If someone comes in...
Got it. I'll hold onto them so they don't leave.
You got it, little Dong Hyun.
It's peanuts for me.
What?
I have a peanut allergy. What about you?
It's a stronger allergy than yours.
I have an allergy to ticks, eggs, and tomatoes.
I just have one. But it's really severe.
I'm Dong Hyun.
- What?
- Dong Hyun. Jo Dong Hyun.
My name. What's your name?
Kim Min Kyu.
My aunt doesn't have a boyfriend.
What does that have to do with me?
This is what my aunt made.
You want me to eat it?
It's mine.
When my aunt was around my age, she went on a picnic.
But she didn't know how to make kimbap, so she made rice balls
like this. That was the first time she made them.
Why would a kid make kimbap?
She said there was no one to make it for her. This is really good.
She must've been teased a lot by others. Your aunt, I mean.
No one ate the rice balls with her. But my mom did.
So my aunt became my mom's guardian angel.
Kim Min Kyu?
Thanks to your help, I'm getting engaged.
Does the person who stole your first kiss know about this?
Yes, she does. She was right next to me.
You bastard.
Pardon?
No, just a little bit ago a bastard walked past.
You idiot.
You must've not come here just to tell me that, right?
You said that the girl and I were flirting, right?
Sun Hye, from your viewpoint, did she appear to have an interest in me?
Yes, a lot.
What made you come to that conclusion?
I see you.
[Salted Sea Squirt]
That salted sea squirt is for our Masan native...
Researcher 1.
She always stared at you.
Where the eyes go is where the heart goes.
Heart. That is a baseless reasoning.
How can we check something that we can't see?
What someone feels is what's most true. That'll be all.
If I say anymore, I feel like I'll start punching things.
Do you have any plans for accepting her feelings?
No matter how her appearance might change?