and join the competition of this kingdom.
Asawatthewatin will compete too.
The son will compete in this kingdom.
In the law, it is not prohibited or said that women are prohibited from competing.
It will be fun if there are two people competing.
Practice a lot, brother.
Nothing is beyond our control.
And this is our grandson.
Asawatthewatin.
Please welcome Asawatthewatin.
Prince Kuneo.
Nice to see you today.
This is Ying-on.
She is from Thailand.
From Thailand.
I like your look today.
So perfect and gorgeous and so…
Thank you Ying-on for being here today.
Oh my god. It's my pleasure.
Nice to see you.
Excuse me.
Congratulations Prince Kuneo.
Bye. See you.
Thank you.
Your Majesty.
It's my honor to be able to participate in your party.
It's also my honor to be able to participate in your party.
I'm very happy to meet you, Your Majesty.
I'm Kaning.
I'm very happy to meet you.
Today Kaning plays the piano very gently.
Thank you.
I hope you enjoy today's party.
Good. Good.
I'm a representative of the Kingdom of Phuja.
I would like to express my congratulations to the King of Phuja.
You don't have to do this.
We are friends and we are friends.
I'm Kaning.
Soon we will have to ask the King of Phuja and Kaning
because Kevin, our son, is very interested in the University of Arts.
I feel very honored.
I'm very honored to be able to participate in the party.
Prince Kaning is blessed with musical talent.
I'm very happy to be able to participate in the party.
I've been interested in the instrument since I was young.
Good evening.
Good night.
As a representative of the King of Phuja,
I'm honored to be able to participate in this royal banquet.
I would like to congratulate you, Your Majesty, Prince Kaning.
We are very happy to have you here today.
In addition to his genius with music,
his skills with the violin are unbeatable.
We learned about the reputation of his Highness, the Prince, when he was in London.
Thank you.
The violin is a great part of my life.
I was taught about it since I was a child
because the people of Mali are known for the best violin players.
I'm very happy to be able to participate in this royal banquet.
Your Majesty, it's time for me to prepare the King for the dance party tonight.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Prince Kaning, it's a big job.
Come on, Ying. Let's dance together.
Let's dance together.
I'm just in a moonlight with you
Under the stars just as blue
With every beat, my heart's complete to you
You know my dreams come true
I'm loving forever with you
Hold me so tight all through the night
The King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden Ruler, the King of the Golden
all is possible thanks to the
Unexpectedly I knew that Acorn Jeff was a good guy.
Hey Acorn.
But then when Produce X 101 ended,
I thought that Acorn's hidden translated lyrics
was so crispy and sweet preparing my breath.
So, I also planned to go help someone.
Here.
Respectically.
I've got an appointment with somebody.
Hatheyyach它来着
KhunMing
Everyone is staring at you
As if it's been practiced
from the north.
Especially about Charan.
You don't have to answer.
I understand.
Chakri.
Charan.
I'll wait here.
I'm sorry.
Then, please come in.
I'm not used to it.
I'm here on behalf of Emily.
I'm pleased to welcome you back.
I'd like to ask you about your life
before you go back to Emily.
I grew up in London.
I never thought that
I'd be in a place like this.
I'm in a big palace
and I'm living a life I've never lived before.
I feel that I'm not used to this.
About the dance party,
I saw that you're very close to Charan.
Can you tell me about your closeness?
I'm sorry.
I've already made a lot of arrangements.
I have to go to work.
Are you tired?
Would you like to have some snacks or snacks?
That's good.
Thank you, Chakri.
You helped me a lot today.
Are you tired?
It's my duty.
Aren't you tired?
Come sit.
Here.
What is your duty?
To protect and take care of the family.
To keep and protect the family.
That's my duty.
You two don't have to use the word,
but you can use the word,
Your Majesty.
Yes.
Why didn't you go to the interview room with me today?
Answer me.
Why?
Because when we danced,
many people looked at us.
So?
What is more important to you?
Worrying about you.
You said it like this.
You said you were worried about me.
I'm worried.
Worrying about you.
Worrying about what?
Yes.
I know. I'll go see you.
Hurry up.
The internet people will definitely be mad at you.
Your Majesty.
Uncle Nin.
I forgot to take off the wireless.
I heard the close word of the couple.
It's like a play.
So this happened.
The king and the queen are very suitable.
What do you think about this?
I think it's impossible for the two of them to be together.
You are a smart person and feel good about yourself.
Do you think it's just a call?
When there is a news group,
people are suspicious.
Actually, it's a good call.
But I don't know if it's really an act or a cause.
It's true.
You can still smile.
Do you think this is a joke?
It's true.
According to the original rules,
it may not affect the competition of this kingdom.
But I don't think it's that bad.
Your Majesty, you have to change something.
I don't want to change anything.
So you have to find a coach to train more.
But I don't think it's appropriate.
Excuse me.
Are you worried about me?
I said I was worried.
I'm worried.
Worried?
In what position?
Please check the condition of the two passengers.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Sir.
Why is it so bright?
It's because the royal court is trying to create a new trend.
Come.
Do you know why I called you here?
You want to ask about the news, right?
I understand that now you have equal rights.
You are my nephew.
And that one is my nephew.
The relationship that is more than difficult
doesn't seem appropriate.
I understand.
My nephew and Sirun are just close.
It's because he was the one who took my nephew.
We have been through death together.
It doesn't look good, Sirun.
I'm sorry to say that I just take care of Sir Ka-nin
as a personal favorite of His Majesty.
I don't have any other thoughts with Sir Ka-nin.
I'm just a real person, Your Majesty.
I don't have feelings for Sir Ka-nin.
This is the time to open up, Ka-nin.
After this, you have to be more careful.
Yes, Your Majesty.
And what about the news?
I have a request to make, Your Majesty.
At this time, Sir Ka-nin has received a lot of support from the people.
Would it be good if you could present yourself as a person who is easy to get along with and open up?
I think it will make Sir Ka-nin the favorite of the people.
If His Majesty is in a hurry to fix the news now,
it will make the people wonder if it is a trick or a cover-up.
Maybe it's not good for His Majesty's image.
Smile.
Are you ready? Look at the camera and smile.
It's the end of the day.
Sir Ka-nin, would you like to send me some water?
So I can feel comfortable.
I'm fine.
Okay.
Let's go.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
Stop. I can do it myself.
You must be tired today. Go to rest.
You mean the pillow?
Yes.
Who let you go?
Fah-Barn.
We are alone now.
Yes?
You said to the
the
that you take care of me as a private person.
That's my duty.
But we are friends, aren't we?
If you have nothing to say,
please rest.
I'm sorry, Your Majesty.
Tomorrow morning, you have to go back to the country of Emily.
Thanks.
Good night.
Go away.
Who does She know?
He looks like the person that user Emily does.
The four clans joined forces and got the throne.
The prince Thanae of the royal family
announced the arrival of King Phrapeniphan.
He wanted to take the throne from there.
Where is the prince?
He went to the palace.
He went to the palace to see the prince.
No.
Never mind.
Just continue. I'm listening.
What I'm waiting for
after the new king of the modern kingdom
is the new king of the new kingdom
who is the king of the new kingdom.
If your king Thanae is the winner
then the last of those clans
will be the next king.
When the time comes,
the angel will come back to take us back.
I promise.
Before this,
the angel just wants you to be safe.
Safe to compete.
Actually, it's okay.
You and Chakri know
that we came back and agreed to compete
to find out about my father.
But we still don't know anything.
Can you promise me
that if you know something,
you won't do anything dangerous?
What do you know?
Promise me first.
Promise?
I promise.
I want you to find out the evidence
that I got from the murderer when I was in England.
As you can see,
you are a real police officer.
You are the best.
Come here.
This is the picture that the king used to use as a source of information.
I'm sorry, Your Majesty.
Apart from the police officer's record,
you are doing a very bad job.
But the person who did this is the real police officer.
It may be true or not.
Have you told the police?
I'll talk to you first.
Don't tell them yet.
I think we should find out about this first.
And I want to go to the real police.
The DNA is 99% accurate.
The king has appeared.
Kanin,
are you here to pick me up?
Ramin and I are very happy that you visited our city.
I'm here to pick you up, Uncle Ramin.
Kanin, I'm very happy
that you visited the city of Phuchong.
I'll let Ramin take you to see the city of Phuchong.
Okay.
I'll let Ramin take you to see our city.
Let's be close like this so you don't have to worry about me.
Thank you for your concern.
After seeing the city,
I'll let Ramin take you to see the city of Phuchong.
There are records about Emily's history.
You can study it.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I'm sorry.
If you have any questions, you can always ask me.
Because the city of Phuchong is the oldest city.
That's very interesting.
I have to thank you.
Let's go.
The city of Phuchong
Kanin, after I took you to see the city of Phuchong,
there is one more important place
that I want to take you to.
An important place
doesn't mean the city of Phuchong.
Besides the city, there is another important place
that is not open to outsiders.
It's the city of Phuchong.
It's said to be the city of Phuchong.
If he's not involved,
shall we go there tonight?
I think
Mr. Ramin may not know anything about the prince.
Or maybe
he's not the real prince.
I haven't told you anything yet.
But I think
don't trust him.
I'm sorry.
I don't trust anyone except you.
Are you really not going to let me follow you?
It's okay.
I don't dare to do anything to inform you.
I always remember
that you are the competitor in this competition.
Don't miss the chance.
I won't hesitate.
I'll call you if there's anything.
The place is so beautiful.
Didn't the younger generation
allow you to enter?
Sometimes,
it's not for everyone.
The younger brother may not know that his mother is here.
The princess, Ms. Nita,
is the daughter of the prince.
Ms. Nita
is the youngest daughter in the royal family.
Ms. Sak is the younger sister of my father.
Actually, we are relatives.
Please
let me give my brother a gift.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Ramminpay.
When I was young,
when I was upset,
I would come here alone.
But
it made me feel that I was small.
The pressure as a king
must have been very strong.
But
for you to be a water-singer like today,
please.
I'm sorry.
This is the royal painting.
It's a painting that our kingdom
has respected and worshiped for many generations.
You may feel familiar with it
because the most important thing in the royal family
is the model from this painting.
I'm sorry.
Can you compare the profit
that I gave you to it?
Huh?
What did my brother get?
The profit…
Did he get it in this area?
Perhaps…
When we receive something from someone,
we will keep it alive.
But it's okay.
I will go outside to check.
The way we came, you can find it around here.
Okay.
Mukanyokhe Salt Lake
The reward is high.
There are many opportunities to take revenge.
Hurry up and join the Macau New Beijing Entertainment City, 891891.com.
Please help me prepare the food for the young master.
You can wait.
Okay, Sir.
Thank you.
You can wait.
Okay, Sir.
Sir, why are you alone?
And Mr.Ramen and Mr.Kanin?
Both of them went to the forest to play.
How long have they been gone?
Four hours.
They must be back soon.
Kanin, Kanin is missing.
Her phone is out of reach.
Wait, Sir.
Why are you back so soon?
Don't you have to leave tomorrow?
But now is not the time.
We have to hurry up and find Mr.Kanin.
Okay.
Sir Kanin.
We are waiting for him here.
I'll go this way.
Sir Kanin.
You three come this way.
I'll follow you.
Okay.
Sir Kanin.
You.
You, right? I'm here.
Are you okay?
Yes.
The car crashed.
The bike is also broken.
So I'm waiting here.
Do you have a wound or bruise?
The one that crashed just now.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to make you worry.
It's my fault.
How can it be your fault?
It's an accident.
No, it's not.
It's my fault.
If Sir Kanin has fallen into danger
without my ability to do anything,
my duty to protect him
is just a word.
But…
Fahbad.
Fahbad is important to me.
More than you can imagine.
I'm sorry.
Sir.
Just clean the car.
You found this car?
Let's go.
Sir Kanin.
I'm sorry.
I went back to the cave.
I couldn't find him.
We might have met by accident.
And the profit.
I found it.
I'll return it to you.
I'm sorry, Sir Kanin.
Sir Kanin.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for letting you
and Sir Ramin
into the forest
and following you.
Ramin,
are you sorry?
I'm asking you.
Are you sorry?
Don't do this, Sir Kanin.
I'm not blaming you.
I think
it's not appropriate
for me to stay here tonight.
I'm sorry, Sir Kanin.
What are you doing?
You're stupid.
You don't have any idea.
You think I don't know
that you used that forest
as a signal
and the fire was gone
because of you, right?
No, Sir.
No?
Listen to me.
You can sleep
in the heaven
but don't do anything stupid
like that to Kanin.
And the reason why you're so stupid
is because
you're stupid.
I'm sorry.
Can I ask you a favor?
It's not your fault.
I'm the one who's to blame.
You just didn't make it to the game.
But I'm glad
that the one who found me the first is you.
I'm glad that I found you.
Thank you.
I think
that the two of them are not good
to the gods.
I feel strange.
But don't tell the god about
the person who was the police.
And I want to ask everyone
not to talk about this again.
I have nothing
that can be hidden from the eyes of the gods.
I can't live without you.
Sit down.
Why did you come back before me?
You've traveled enough.
I know that there's no place
that's safe for you.
Yes, sir.
Look at this picture.
What does it look like?
The two stars
are beautiful stars
in the sky.
It looks romantic.
I'm happy.
The two stars are
side by side.
But it's not easy.
According to the legend,
the star of Por Laks
is like the god of
Buddha.
And the star of Custer
is like a normal human
with a human age.
They can't be together.
If Por Laks doesn't want to lose his natural ability,
and if the story ends with death,
do you still think
that this story is still romantic?
I'm sorry, Phra Baan.
I have a feeling that
even though they're side by side
in the star of Custer,
it's still a legend
that shows an impressive love.
This restaurant is really suitable
for an artist.
Thank you, sir.
I almost forgot.
The Garwin of Mujar
will continue to study
the art of the Faculty of Arts of Charan.
I don't see anyone
who can be more important than Charan.
I'm afraid
that I don't have time
to study the art of the King.
You can go back
and do what you love.
And Kaning,
Phu will take care of him.
So he can have more concentration.
I hope you understand.
Yes, sir.
I think
what happened at the audience
is that
Kaning
shouldn't have asked Charan to tell him.
Never mind.
Nothing better than this.
Yes, sir.
Sometimes, if you can make Kaning
stay away from Charan,
it would be good.
Thank you.
Here, Kawin.
An exchange student from Mujar.
Please take care of him.
My pleasure.
What are you doing here?
Why aren't you with me?
My brain just follows the duty.
And the duty to protect and take care of you.
To keep and be loyal to the divine being that you used to say.
Come and sit here.
I think…
I told you to come and sit here.
Come and sit here.
Look at our secret secret.
This is good, right?
I'm so soft.
I'm softer than this.
I trust you.