Lawyer Luo, the base station is fixed.
It's just announcing the will.
You don't necessarily have to be there.
The will is with me.
I must deliver the will to them personally.
But the road up the mountain is still under repair.
Who knows when it will be fixed.
How about this, I'll contact them.
And explain the situation to them.
Okay.
Mr. Fang.
Aren't you going to say something?
What am I supposed to say?
The p-pendant?
She says it belongs to her daughter.
Well, I say it's mine.
Can we even clear this up?
That Ma Shan is crazy.
I don't believe a word she says anyway.
Her daughter is her obsession.
I don't think Auntie Ma is lying.
Mr. Fang.
If this pendant is really yours,
please explain where it came from.
That is my personal item.
I have the right to refuse to answer that.
I think you'd better explain.
Just to clear yourself of suspicion.
That pendant...
was given to me by Di Fu.
You mean...
my sister and Nana had the same pendant?
They were good friends.
It's not strange to have matching pendants, right?
When did she give it to you?
It was...
after Di Fu married Mr. Zhao.
This... this means...
my brother was a cuckold?
You adulterous couple!
You piece of trash!
And she left you an inheritance?
I...
Zhao Qihai!
You insist there's something going on between us?
Fine.
I'll give you what you want today.
We did have something going on.
So what? You want to kill me?
Enough, enough.
Why is everyone so angry?
Everyone.
How is Auntie Ma doing?
She just took her medicine and fell asleep.
Breakfast is ready.
Would you like to eat something first?
Uh...
let's have breakfast.
Please.
Have some breakfast and cool down.
Such a temper.
I checked.
I didn't find anything.
Fang Qiu said his door wasn't locked yesterday.
Anyone could have entered.
If that's really the case,
someone waited until he was asleep,
took the pendant off his neck.
Why didn't he react at all?
His explanation is that he was drunk.
If that's really true,
this person must know
that the pendant is connected to Nana.
That's why they put the pendant
by Auntie Ma Shan's pillow.
That's not all.
The ring. Why do you have it?
I found it at my door last night.
I think the person who left this ring
and the one who took Fang Qiu's necklace are the same person.
Who would know about these things?
Could it really be your sister?
Don't mind me.
I just said it without thinking.
Inspector Qi.
Miss Li.
Auntie Ma Shan is missing again.
Let's split up and look for her.
Meet back at the dining room.
Auntie Ma!
Still no news from Lawyer Luo?
Ah Qiu.
Did you kill Ma Shan?
I've been questioned by you all this time.
I wouldn't have time even if I wanted to kill her.
Auntie Ma
What's wrong?
Did I scare you?
How did you end up here?
I saw a man.
A man whose face I couldn't see clearly.
Let's go.
Auntie Ma, how did you end up here?
I don't remember either.
I woke up and I was here.
It must be Zhao Qishan's ghost that brought me here.
It's a ghost.
It's Zhao Qishan's ghost.
It was him.
There are no ghosts.
You're seeing things.
Miss Li, where did you find Auntie Ma Shan?
I found her in the study.
No.
Why were you looking for her?
I was...
I really, really...
I can't take it anymore.
Miss Li.
By now...
We still haven't heard your story.
I don't know where to start.
After all...
I haven't seen my sister in a long time.
Memories from childhood are very blurry.
Trying to brush us off again?
Of course not.
Since I promised...
I will definitely tell it.
The earliest home in my memory...
...had no color.
Xiao Ran, come here.
Look what I found.
Money.
Finally, I can buy a new pair of shoes.
And I can take you to eat a bowl of boat noodles.
Boat noodles! I want boat noodles!
I'll take you to eat right now.
But Xiao Ran, you must not tell Mom and Dad.
That we found money.
Understand?
You must not say a word.
You hopeless gambler.
You stole my money.
This is my hard-earned money.
I didn't! I'm not done with you!
Sis.
Let's just tell Mom and Dad.
Otherwise...
They'll keep fighting.
This is my money.
No.
We absolutely can't tell.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
Leaving? Where are you going?
You dare go find another man?
So what if I did?
There are plenty of men out there waiting for me.
Mom.
Don't leave us behind.
Xiao Ran.
Listen to Mom.
Mom will be back very soon.
Then I'll buy you lots and lots of new clothes.
And lots and lots of toys.
And take you to eat delicious food, okay?
Don't cry. Listen to Mom.
Really?
Really. Trust Mom.
Xiao Ran, take good care of your sister.
Mom, I beg you.
Don't leave us behind.
Don't go.
From that day on...
Mom...
I never saw my mom again.
Later I learned...
What a lie really is.
Children without a mom are pitiful.
My dad was a hopeless gambler by nature.
He didn't care if my sister and I lived or died.
Boss.
Without my sister...
I probably would have died long ago.
Vegetarian or meat?
Meat.
Here.
You two, stand still!
You stole something!
Little friend, is this your home?