Two, three.
- We Dem BOYZ. - We Dem BOYZ.
- PRIME KINGZ, baby. - PRIME KINGZ.
(Eight crews joined the Street Man Fighter.)
It's been six years since our crew was made.
- It's been two years for us. - It's been about ten years.
I've been working as a team for 12 years.
We've always worked together.
Young Jay, you can do it. Of course you can.
We can do it. Of course we can.
- I think our teamwork... - That's the spirit.
- and power of unity are better. - Nice.
You're cool enough.
- Do you know what I mean? - Yes.
It's okay if you make a mistake. Relax, okay?
He did really well.
I feel so reassured.
We sweat together and made an effort.
I know what we've all been through.
I'll really do my best.
I should really do my best.
We're a team that...
shows more strength when we're together.
I can see you when I dance this part.
I'll dance accordingly, so don't worry.
Okay.
When we're together,
other crews can't beat us.
Let's make sure that our confidence...
we felt is not groundless.
On top of that, if we win,
it'll make us so thrilled.
Let's write our history here.
("Young Forever" by TO1)
(Street Man Fighter)
(Benefits for the winning crew)
(50,000 dollars of prize money)
(Sponsored by Deutsch Motors: Electronic Sedan)
(Sponsored by KB Kookmin Card: The model for a finance platform)
(Class Mission dance videos were revealed last week.)
(Won first place in the topic of conversation for two weeks in a row)
(Became the most trending videos)
("Do You Watch SMF? Even BTS is into the Dance Battle of Men")
("SMF's Leader Class Dance Video Nailed It")
(Thanks to the choreography, the songs dominated the charts.)
(I should learn this dance in advance.)
(It'll go viral for sure.)
("Saebbing" challenge, Kang Daniel, Hoshi, Choi Ye Na)
(Yoo Se Yoon)
("LAW" challenge)
(Korea is having a Class Mission challenge fever.)
(During the worst dancer battle, PRIME KINGZ lost to Mbitious.)
(They lost 50 points as soon as they lost.)
(Losing 50 points means,)
(we are disadvantageous.)
(We might be eliminated.)
(Each crew starts the Global K-dance Mission with different scores.)
(I think that'll be really humiliating.)
(Being a backup dancer)
(We'll be backup dancers for PRIME KINGZ.)
(Seriously?)
(The winning crew of Copying Choreography Challenge...)
(will be able to make all the members of the lost crew...)
(as their backup dancers.)
(What did he say?)
(We'll just be their background.)
(It's really cruel.)
(I should be doing really well.)
(I'll have to focus.)
I did a lot of backup dancing.
(But...)
(I don't do that anymore.)
(Let's do it again.)
(Deukie and Dony do their best to avoid becoming backup dancers.)
We can never be their backup dancers.
(This is a battle of pride.)
Since I'm a world champion...
(I've never done...)
(backup dancing before.)
They're weak.
I'll make them bow in hanbok.
(Polite)
I think we nailed it.
We're in trouble.
(JustJerk versus PRIME KINGZ: Which crew will be the backup?)
Please just hold out for once.
I just need it to succeed once.
(What happened to Choi Young Jun of 1MILLION?)
(Who'll be the first crew to be eliminated from Street Man Fighter?)
We really did our best.
We've made it this far.
I thought, "So we're really getting eliminated."
I'm not here to be eliminated. Seriously.
I have so many things that I haven't shown.
That's what upsets me the most.
I can't speak.
(To be continued)
(Additional Points and Deductions by Crew)
From 1MILLION, Choi Young Jun,
Yechan, and Alexx too.
If they're all chosen as the worst dancers,
their score may turn to zero.
The Main Dancer of Middle 1 Class is...
(Main Dancers of Middle 1 Class, Nino, Yumeki)
(1MILLION gets 100 points added thanks to the main dancers.)
(But they were chosen as the worst in the other two classes.)
If 1MILLION loses and becomes the worst dancers,
they'll lose the additional points Nino and Yumeki made...
as the main dancers.
The two-on-two battle will decide the worst dancers...
for Middle 2 class.
From 1MILLION, Yechan and Alexx.
From JustJerk, Yejun and Hulk.
To be honest, I thought we got unlucky with the opponents.
JustJerk is dangerous too.
In the end, Yejun and Hulk are the ones...
who brought the sole loss to PRIME KINGZ.
(The only crew who won against PRIME KINGZ, JustJerk.)
PRIME KINGZ gets the first No-Respect Punch.
I hoped it would be any team but JustJerk.
But it's them.
(Burning with a passion)
- Look... - I think I seriously want to win.
- This one? - I was nervous.
Are we going to get 50 points deducted?
Or are we keeping the 100 points? This was the battle.
DJ, ready? Fight!
(Yechan and Alexx of 1MILLION kick off the battle.)
I didn't want to lose.
It can bring harm to our crew.
(I'm getting hooked.)
(Hulk and Yejun of JustJerk follow.)
This can affect our score,
so we'll show everything we can do.
(Like ninja)
(1MILLION takes a hit.)
The score is 32 to 9.
The worst dancers of Middle 2 Class are...
Yechan and Alexx of 1MILLION.
(1MILLION, 50 points deducted)
Are sub leaders next?
I think so.
That's why I became even more anxious.
(The pressure on sub leader grew after the two boys lost.)
If I lose, our points are deducted.
I felt sorry for bringing that anxiety to our team.
I haven't done anything...
to help out our team as the sub leader.
(The sub leader feels burdened because he wants to help his crew.)
(Keep it up.)
I know you can win. Don't worry.
Those points were hard-earned.
(By Nino and Yumeki)
How can the sub leader lose those points?
I must win.
The battle between two dancers begins now!
Ready?
Fight.
Let's go!
(Just jump first.)
B-boy!
(Choi Young Jun of 1MILLION kicks it off.)
He didn't know what to do.
Does he have one move to take the round?
I looked at the time to see when I should show my moves.
Let's go!
(Here comes my move.)
Keep it going!
(Don't be the worst dancer.)
(Whoa)
It was just disappointing.
He felt betrayed and flustered when Wootae chose him,
yet he couldn't overcome that.
I could see how he was annoyed by that in his heart.
His head was too full.
If he loses, he'll lose points.
Who could dance in peace in that situation?
The voting for Sub Leader Class just ended.
Two candidates for the worst dancer,
please turn around and check the result.
Three, two, one.
(Surprised)
(Hooray)
The result is 34 to 7.
The worst dancer for Sub Leader Class is...
Choi Young Jun of 1MILLION.
It's very embarrassing.
Whenever I took a step...
(Choi Young Jun, you fool...)
No, it's okay.
The result is 34 to 7.
Dony of YGX wins.
I felt bad for Koo Young, Yumeki, and Nino.
It must be painful for 1MILLION.
That's bitter.
That must taste bitter.
They should do better.
Sadly, 1MILLION lost...
all additional points.
They start over from ground zero.
This is way too cruel.
(Man...)
I couldn't lift my head.
I wanted to tell them sorry.
But I thought it'd kill our spirit if I kept saying sorry.
I feel like a fool now.
If someone nudged me a little,
I would have bawled.
(Holding back tears)
- I hope Young Jun isn't sad. - Three, two, one.
I think he'll be sad.
(Additions for the Main Dancer, Deductions for the Worst Dancer)
The worst dancer candidates of Leader Class.
TED of EO-DDAE and JRoc of Bank 2 Brothers.
Please come into the fight zone.
TED of EO-DDAE.
It's because he didn't stand out as much.
I'll consider that you chose not to see me.
I just need you guys to keep your eyes on me.
(TED shares his heart with his crew before the battle.)
(Choking)
Don't cry.
When he said that to us before the battle,
it really touched my heart.
He must have felt bad.
I was the only one who was chosen among my crew.
If I lose as the leader,
I don't think I can face them.
Look at the back of our leader.
- His shoulders are heavy. - The back of our leader.
I dread the thought of hurting my crew.
I really don't want to lose.
I can't lose.
- But you know, I'm not worried. - No.
I'm seriously not worried.
No matter which genre he brings, waacking can win against anything.
That's why waacking is scary.
You don't know how it'll change the flow.
And throw TED's moves on top? Then you'll surely win.
First off, he was in dance battles.
- He was known as... - Waacking Prince.
He was formerly called the Waacking Prince.
There's a family tree of waacking princes,
and he's the third generation.
Not only is he good-looking,
but you also can see that he's a prince through his attitude.
I'll trust my crew members and myself,
then win. I know I can win.
I need to win. I'll win and move forward.
(Worst dancer battle for the Leader Class)
(JRoc of Bank 2 Brothers kicks it off.)
He was good.
But I didn't lose my spirit.
I can just dance energetically.
From EO-DDAE, TED!
(TED of EO-DDAE calmly continues the battle.)
I thought he did a great job in his style. It was great.
He shouldn't look so relaxed for too long.
The battle is over.
The voting is over.
The result is 14 to 29.
B2B takes the victory.
I regained confidence in perfect timing,
before we moved on to the next round.
I could only see my crew members at that moment.
Great job.
- You did so well. - Good job.
I felt really bad...
and heartbroken.
No matter what the mission is,
I'll give it my all.
We can't take more deductions.
EO-DDAE begins the next mission with a disadvantage...
of minus 50 points.
(Additional Points and Deductions by Crew)
The potential worst dancer of the Rookie Class,
Kamel of We Dem BOYZ...
and Kim Jung Woo of Mbitious.
Please come out to the fight zone.
- Have fun. - Just have fun.
They told me...
not to feel burdened and show my dance.
I came out thinking...
I'll give Jung Woo a lesson.
Jung Woo, come and learn from me.
(Kamel of WDBZ kicks off the worst dancer battle.)
(Relaxed)
(Provoking)
He got very close to me and began to provoke me.
That's when I began to think I must stay calm.
Kim Jung Woo of Mbitious!
(Kim Jung Woo of Mbitious goes out calmly.)
Jung Woo, go!
I tried my best to listen to the music,
but I couldn't hear it.
(Slips)
Jung Woo wasn't himself today.
Kamel put up a good fight in his own way.
So he might have felt intimidated after watching him.
(Everyone except for 3 people voted Jung Woo as the worst dancer.)
I lost. It was clear that I had lost.
- Nice try. - Nice try.
- Well done. - It was a good fight.
Nice job.
More than anything, I felt awful for my crew...
because I wasn't much of a help to them.
You did a nice job. Remember what I told you?
You don't need to feel small because of this.
I'm sure this was tough on him.
To be honest,
he was the only real rookie out of all the so-called rookies here.
I'm sure he must have been under a lot of pressure.
There were times the other dancers looked down on me...
because I wasn't as experienced as them.
I'm sure there were better dancers...
than him.
I'm surprised that he was chosen.
Maybe, it's that guy. Jung Woo.
He does surprise me the most.
- Is Jung Woo the youngest? - Yes, he is.
What does he do?
I felt that their treatment toward me was unfair.
I just...
In the end,
I failed...
to make the best of all the moments.
I think it's my fault.
Wootae worked really hard to win these additional points.
(During the main dancer tryout)
It's Wootae.
(Jung Woo cost the crew 50 points.)
I felt bad for my crew.
It wasn't easy to win these additional points.
(In the middle of the shoot, Mbitious gathers around.)
(The crew members of Mbitious don't know what's going on.)
Well,
we've gone through several missions so far.
I feel that I didn't contribute...
to our crew with my performances.
- So things like this... - No. You don't have to be sorry...
- about that. No one thinks that. - Don't be sorry.
This... Gosh.
As for the next mission,
I'll root for you guys from the back.
And I need some time to think.
I'm sorry, guys.
No one here ever thought...
that you weren't good enough to be here.
So I don't want you...
to spend this time, thinking about that at all.
I hope you will spend the time wisely to improve yourself.
It was sad.
And my feelings were complicated too.
Whatever decision he makes,
I should believe in him and watch him.
That's the only thing I can do as his fellow dancer.
Put aside Street Man Fighter or "Be Mbitious."
Aren't you going to keep dancing?
- Right. Yes. - Right?
I hope you can nourish your inner strength...
with this opportunity.
I think this had been tough on him.
But I believe that he will get through this well.
(Additions for the Main Dancer, Deductions for the Worst Dancer)
All right. Being chosen as the worst dancers...
brought a painful deduction of 50 points to some crews.
Being chosen as the main dancers...
brought 100 precious points to the crews.
The eight crews will begin at different starting points...
for the third mission.
(Nervous)
After this mission, a crew will be eliminated...
from the show for the first time.
(Covering his mouth)
It's time.
No.
I should work really hard for this.
- Let's give it our all. - Right. Let's do that.
We're not here to get eliminated.
We're here to win.
"If this goes wrong,"
"we might end up going home." When that crossed my mind,
it was like getting a wake-up call.
A crew will be chosen to be eliminated...
for the first time after this mission.
It's called the Global K-dance Mission.
- K-dance. - K-dance.
K-pop artists impressed the world...
with their performances. And for this mission,
you will perform with their songs to battle it out.
(BTS, EXO, BigBang, SEVENTEEN)
Okay.
- Okay. - EXO and SEVENTEEN.
The choreographers who came up with the choreography are there.
The choreography for the idol groups.
Don't they have the grandfather of choreographers?
Check out their careers as choreographers.
Just look at the choreography those two came up with.
"EXO's choreographer." "KAI's dance teacher."
People called me with these nicknames.
He's known as the father of SEVENTEEN's choreography.
Choi Young Jun of 1MILLION.
Since the début of SEVENTEEN,
I made the choreography for all of their songs...
except for 3 or 4 songs.
- Except for 3 or 4 songs. - Except for them.
- That's so impressive. - Seriously.
They are just insane.
Two crews will go head-to-head...
with the same song for this mission.
The scores from the Fight Judges...
and the global popularity vote will be combined...
for their evaluations.
Your opposing crew and the song for your mission.
These two factors will play a major role...
in winning this mission.
And a dancer who will affect the fate of the crews...
is chosen by the Fight Judges. The Class Mission's best director...
will be that person.
(I forgot about that.)
- You get to pair up the crews... - That's a big benefit.
- and choose the songs? - This is no joke.
If I can watch...
only one video again, I would choose this video.
Who is the best director chosen by the Fight Judges?
(The main dancer of the Leader Class, Vata)
I think Mbitious will win.
- I think Mbitious will win. - No. You'll win.
- Hurry. Let's pray. - Please.
(The main dancer of the Sub Leader Class, Wootae)
I really want to win.
Please.
It's...
Vata of We Dem BOYZ for the Leader Class.
(Our leader won!)
Vata!
I told you!
Wait. Sit down.
I liked his video...
because the song and the dance harmonized well.
He gave everyone a chance...
- to stand out. - Right.
He added highlights for each dancer.
I feel great.
Of course, I was happy to be chosen as the best director.
But I seek practicality...
and benefits.
I was happier that I could pair up the crews...
and choose the songs. That made me happier.
(Vata was happier about the benefit.)
(Screaming)
(We Dem BOYZ walks in confidently.)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(They celebrate with a beer.)
- Let's do it again. - Do it again.
Let's go!
Gosh. By the way, this is staring right at us.
(We Dem BOYZ holds the key for the other crews.)
We need to think about this.
Can we listen to the songs?
(The 8 crews find out about the songs.)
(YGX's hideout)
- "Ko Ko Bop"? - "Ko Ko Bop" is playing.
Why this song?
Didn't Koo Young make the choreography for this?
They won't give this to Koo Young.
We don't know what Vata will decide.
In my opinion, giving that song to 1MILLION might be good too...
because that way, Koo Young has to come up with something new.
Right. He must make a new routine...
- for the song he worked on before. - Right.
None of these songs scare me. I'm fine with any song.
I did relax the moment we found out about the mission.
I really don't want to be paired up with 1MILLION.
By the way, 1MILLION might be the toughest crew...
- to beat in this mission. - Right.
There are seven other crews.
So we don't have to go up against 1MILLION.
I'm curious to find out with whom he will pair us.
- What? - Hey.
(The pairings chosen by Vata will be revealed now.)
- How did you pair us up? - The best...
(Shocked)
They want to go up against us?
(Crews for EXO: We Dem BOYZ versus 1MILLION)
- We got EXO's songs. - Come on.
I had no idea that we would be going up against them.
Hey, they must think we're a joke.
You heard what Vata said earlier, right?
We Dem BOYZ, which crew would you like to compete against?
Probably a crew we can beat, right?
(So it won't be us.)
We Dem BOYZ had the chance to pair up the crews.
But We Dem BOYZ chose us?
That's making me furious.
They must have thought we were a weak crew.
And this is our strong suit.
- Coming up with the choreography. - Right.
- But the others... - Why don't we go up against them?
1MILLION is a strong crew in the K-pop scene.
It's more than a shot. I know that we can beat them.
We're not making the choreography for some idol groups.
We have to perform.
To put it simply, I can crush them to pieces...
with the quality of my choreography.
(Crushing 1MILLION)
The best director, Vata of We Dem BOYZ,
decided on the pairings of the crew.
And I will announce them now.
Here are the two crews that will perform...
with the song of a global group, EXO.
They are We Dem BOYZ...
and 1MILLION.
We Dem BOYZ and 1MILLION?
We Dem BOYZ always tries to challenge themselves...
instead of taking a safe route.
They put 1MILLION with EXO's songs.
This means business.
We Dem BOYZ is confident.
"We'll be EXO's choreographers now."
We joined this show, so we can prove that we are...
the new generation of our industry.
So we chose a strong crew...
that is acknowledged by the other dancers.
We must beat this crew to prove ourselves.
So we chose 1MILLION.
He's a nice guy, but he can be harsh at times.
He's annoying.
First of all, do you think you can actually beat us?
(The atmosphere gets cold as Young Jun provokes him.)
(Trembling in fear)
- What did he say? - "Do you think..."
- "you can actually beat us?" - Gosh. He's serious.
- I think he's serious. - When I was around his age,
I was so eager.
I thought I was the best dancer. I looked down on other dancers.
When I saw the same attitude,
I could understand where he was coming from. But...
Why did they do something they would regret later?
I've been dancing for a long time.
To join this show, I had to leave behind everything...
I had earned so far.
We're going to do our best.
(Crews for EXO: 1MILLION versus We Dem BOYZ)
The two crews that will be competing with BTS' song are...
I think PRIME KINGZ should take BTS.
- Oh, "Fire." - Yes.
Then they should go against this crew.
- I want to see this. - Yes.
Hey, you're terrible!
Hey, you punk!
- Vata, you punk! - You punk!
- What? - "Vata, you punk!"
They put us against JustJerk? Is this the finals?
The combination is world-class.
- BTS, JustJerk, PRIME KINGZ. - Yes.
That's why I thought they'd give us BTS.
A long-awaited match...
between two world-class crews.
JustJerk is a crew that has experience directing choreographies.
I think they have a lot to lose.
But we are underdogs.
We have nothing to lose and we're confident.
We would like to show you that you can't win with just your energy.
(Gulping)
(Crews for BTS: JustJerk versus PRIME KINGZ)
Moving on, the two crews that will be competing...
using SEVENTEEN's songs are...
(Bank 2 Brothers' hideout)
- The song is good. - Yes, I like the beat.
I think "CLAP" is hard.
I also want to avoid SEVENTEEN.
- Me too. - We need to avoid SEVENTEEN.
I'm not confident in dancing to SEVENTEEN's songs.
It's YGX.
- SEVENTEEN. - It's SEVENTEEN.
This is bad. SEVENTEEN...
- No. We can do it. - I love SEVENTEEN!
- We can do it. - "CLAP."
I'm tired of versing YGX.
- How many times has it been? - I know, right?
It's Mbitious. I knew it.
Did we do something to make We Dem BOYZ feel upset?
Why do they keep putting us against Mbitious?
Are they telling us to keep fighting?
The No-Respect Crew...
(YGX and Mbitious versed each other during the No-Respect Crew battle.)
(Wootae chose Dony as a potential worst dancer...)
(of the Sub Leader Class.)
(MOOD DOK chose Jung Woo as a potential worst dancer.)
(They met in every mission as enemies.)
While watching Mbitious, I've not once felt like they were...
- enjoying the stage. - Same.
They look apprehensive while they're dancing.
I don't think any other crew...
can enjoy the stage like ours.
It's time for us to show our teamwork.
I don't think they'll have good teamwork.
But if you think about it, have we ever lost to Mbitious?
We haven't.
We have to cut them off no matter what, this time.
You guys are a crew that beat us...
and left us...
having to go through a difficult time.
I'll make sure you guys get a chance to feel...
the same disgrace that we felt.
We will use this opportunity to show you guys...
that the winner won't change.
(Crews for SEVENTEEN: YGX versus Mbitious)
(EO-DDAE versus B2B)
EO-DDAE!
I think we can win this match.
We can't lose against them.
Can we even lose against B2B?
The two crews that will be competing...
using BigBang's song are...
B2B and EO-DDAE.
I think it's our turn now.
We will bring back the points that were taken away from us.
I'm aware that there's already a wide gap...
between our points.
So we will make sure to maintain that gap and move on...
to the next round without going through an elimination battle.
(Crews for BigBang: Bank 2 Brothers versus EO-DDAE)
Global K-dance Mission.
There is a rule for this round.
Copying Choreography Challenge.
For one song,
there are two sections for copying the choreography.
Each crew will be in charge...
of a section and create choreography.
The opposing crew has to copy the choreography.
I'm most worried about their hat tricks.
We have to copy it no matter what.
We're going to have to bite our hat and throw it around and stuff.
That is not all.
I will explain the most important rule.
(Nervous)
After each crew is done making their choreography,
the winning crew, chosen by the Fight Judges,
will earn a backup penalty part...
where they can make the opposing crew be backup dancers.
My gosh. That's crazy.
(Speechless)
Backup dancers again?
(These dancers work as backup dancers for artists.)
(Which crew will become backup dancers for dancers?)
(Backup)
I didn't even imagine this.
I don't want to be a backup dancer.
It's funny because that is our job.
But if we're backups for other dancers, then we become sensitive.
No one came out on this show...
because they wanted to stand behind other dancers.
It will hurt our pride.
Also, the choreography for the backup penalty part...
created by the losing crew...
will not be revealed to the world. It will just disappear.
(No way.)
- It will disappear? No video? - That's crazy.
- That's harsh. - That's so harsh.
It'll be so annoying if we lose...
because we have to practice the backup part and stand in the back.
And our choreography will disappear.
This time, for real...
We have to work really hard.
So we have to make the choreography impossible for the other crew...
to copy, so that we can win and make them backup dancers.
We have to do that. "Go stand in the back."
I'm putting my life on the line.
This is crazy. This mission is not easy.
(The negotiation for the Copying Choreography Challenge will start.)
(The fight for winning the section that they want)
What if we add breakdancing?
I'll crack my ribs. I can't.
This is our chance.
(The war of nerves between the crews)
(Who will be the winner of the Choreography Copying Challenge?)
- We have to decide... - Who takes each part.
To be honest, for Young Jun and me,
we don't care which section we do.
Whatever you guys do for Part A, we can do it better.
(Shrinking slightly)
So if we're being honest, you guys want...
- Part A, right? - Yes, honestly.
Then we'll do Part B.
Since we're fighting anyway.
- Let's battle it out hard. - Yes.
- And once the winner is decided, - Sounds good.
the losing crew can do their best in the back.
It would be nice if you guys did, but you don't want to, right?
(Surprised)
Should we say which part we want after 1, 2, 3?
In 1, 2, 3.
- Part B. - Part B.
This won't be easy.
Part A is "BANG BANG BANG"...
and Part B is "GOOD BOY."
We thought Part B would be better...
for us to showcase our choreography.
We were confident in that part, so we tried to win it no matter what.
Our members really want this part.
What do you think of doing Part A?
(Look at you.)
We weren't going to say this...
(What is it?)
But you guys have 150 more points than us.
(Bank 2 Brothers received 100 points for becoming the main dancers.)
(TED became the worst dancer, which resulted in minus 50 points.)
(There is a gap of 150 points.)
(Now we feel bad.)
You guys are so mean.
It's the widest gap including all the other crews.
- The widest gap, seriously. - We know.
It doesn't look like you guys are willing...
to give us the part.
Not even a bit?
The way that they said it...
was so heartbreaking.
We earned those points with our strategy.
But they suddenly said, "You guys have 150 more points,"
so I became speechless.
But if we were to take Part B on top of that,
I felt like I wouldn't be able to sleep comfortably.
What should we do? Are we going to go with Part B?
I think we can just give them the part.
- To be honest. - That's what I think too.
You guys can have Part B.
(Bank 2 Brothers end up giving Part B to EO-DDAE.)
- We will give it to you. - You guys will be blessed.
Since they gave up the part for us,
I thought we should create a good performance.
- "Blood Sweat and Tears"? - Yes.
- This song needs more choreography. - Yes.
We can't krump to this song.
(Part B, "Fire")
- It's "Fire." - "Fire."
It's "Fire."
(This is it.)
From the way I see it, we have to win Part B.
- Okay. - That's the best option.
We have to do what we're good at.
We have to do Part B.
Can any of them do a backflip?
I think we should add a breakdancing skill.
I think we should add it to the end.
- Right? I thought that too. - Me too.
- Hello. - Hello.
We brought a present.
- A weapon. - A weapon.
- Should we talk first? - Yes.
- Go ahead. - We want Part B, of course.
- Part B? - We want Part B as well.
What?
- We want Part B as well. - Isn't it obvious?
We can do well, whether it's Part A or B.
- Then do Part A. - But,
- the problem is... - It's settled.
Let's say you guys learn Part B from us.
If you guys can do that part better than us,
I think it'll be a huge plus for you guys.
I want to do a good job at copying Part A.
Then Part A could be extremely hard for you guys to copy.
We're okay with that. Shall we do that then?
No, that's not what I mean.
(Why does it feel like PRIME KINGZ is getting the better of us?)
We tried grilling, convincing, and whatever to win them over.
(It won't work.)
Energy.
It's ours.
But he was so firm, so I thought it won't be easy.
Then since we can't reach an agreement...
- Come by after five minutes. - We'll visit your hideout.
- The two of you. - Okay.
We talked about it...
and you know how BTS got popular...
because of their synchronization?
I think we can do a good job with that.
People would have expected us to take on Part A.
Under the assumption that PRIME KINGZ...
will do a good job during Part B...
What they were saying didn't make any sense...
and we weren't able to communicate.
They were as stubborn as a mule.
I don't understand why they're being so stubborn.
I am extremely stubborn.
JustJerk exists now...
because of my stubbornness.
So we went back and forth about three times.
No matter how hard I think,
No matter how objective I'm trying to be,
in Part A...
For over an hour or two,
they kept arguing and persuading.
Like an innocent bystander getting hurt in a fight,
I sat there quietly.
(What's the conclusion of the BTS' round?)
I have to express my opinion.
Right. Then...
we'll make concessions.
(Young Jay's stubbornness reasoned PRIME KINGZ out.)
Yes.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Otherwise, we won't even start practicing.
- Right. - You're stubborn as a mule.
Without being this stubborn, I wouldn't be here right now.
- Really? - Yes.
But you don't have to be that stubborn.
Right.
(No stubbornness, no ice cream)
(Ice cream party)
Let's have a toast. Hurry up and open it.
JustJerk.
- Go. - Go.
This is so good.
- I like it. - It makes me feel good.
This is good just as I expected.
(Negotiation on...)
(Choreography-copying Section ends.)
I'm not standing behind artists...
but behind dancers?
It's a sensitive matter.
It's humiliating.
I'm having JustJerk as our backup dancers.
Now, focus on your practice. Don't go anywhere.
I've never tried the hat trick before,
but I have to do it nonetheless.
(A fight over a technique to avoid becoming backup dancers)
I can't stand behind them.
(All crews attack with advanced moves.)
I can do it.
I'd never want to be their backup dancers.
I'm going to make them go down on their knees.
(Growl, 1MILLION.)
I must win.
(Two extreme styles clash in BigBang's round.)
Yes.
But that looks too hip-hop. That's voguing.
Like a woman. Right now, that's too hip-hop.
(Bank 2 Brothers is struggling.)
We put in so much effort.
This part is darn hard.
We must win to take the penalty part.
I've already been their backup dancer before.
(Laughing)
I can't do it again.
(Meanwhile, this crew is facing a crisis during the practice.)
I belong here.
You stand in the back right.
This isn't how it goes.
What if I become a backup dancer again?
I'm never becoming a backup dancer again.
I hate it. That's ridiculous.
(All crews practice hard to avoid becoming backup dancers.)
(Drinking to quench thirst)
(Exclaiming)
(The day of the first elimination announcement)
(8 crews gathered in their hideouts on the day of the announcement.)
Did we record the highest views?
(1MILLION recorded the highest views.)
- It was worth the effort. - Yes.
We might as well...
get the most likes.
We have the highest views. Probably the same for the likes.
I never expected 1MILLION...
- to record the highest views. - Right.
I didn't expect them to surpass YGX or Mbitious.
I thought Mbitious would get the highest views.
- Me too. - That'd be easier.
Wasn't it over 1.4 million just before it ended?
- Yes. - I thought...
YGX has 100 points,
and we have 50 points.
We're behind them.
I want to beat Mbitious...
and cut off our ill-fated relationship.
But I want to prove ourselves to other crews.
That's why I want to win this.
They're perfectly ready for the battle.
(Ready)
I'm wearing this for nothing.
I knew we placed bottom in the popularity vote...
even before we got there.
Today, we're here with the attitude of an underdog.
We plan to rise in revolt.
(Street Man Fighter)
(Dropout Battle)
(Global K-dance Mission result announcement)
(Who will come up here for the Dropout Battle?)
This is huge.
We're the first to get here.
The winner takes it all.
- The winner takes it all. - Do we sit there?
(Very nervous)
One of eight crews is leaving.
That could be us.
Darn it.
No, we're not getting eliminated.
We're never getting eliminated.
We tried so hard.
I believe we proved we have more potential...
than YGX.
We're facing YGX.
Right. JustJerk and PRIME KINGZ are facing each other.
1MILLION and WDBZ are facing each other.
You're right.
EO-DDAE is entering.
(EO-DDAE enters next.)
I'm very nervous to be here.
I'm hoping to...
avoid the Dropout Battle.
We're behind in the number of views.
If we become the worst crew and battle against them,
I'm going to beat them all.
- Let's sit. - We're here?
Let's have fun.
Let's just battle. We can beat them in the battle.
- Where's my place? - Is it here?
We're never getting eliminated.
They're in front of us.
Mbitious?
They want to face us and fight?
(Nodding)
We have a high number of views,
but Mbitious is already well-known to the public.
That's what I'm worried about.
Hello. I'm your host Kang Daniel.
All eight crews here...
put on an intense battle...
to win in Street Man Fighter.
However, today, someone will have to leave...
before reaching his goal.
We'll have the first crew to be eliminated...
right here today.
Oh, my gosh.
That won't be us.
How is the first eliminated crew decided?
Let me tell you.
After two crews' Dropout Battle,
the first crew to be eliminated will be decided.
Two crews.
It's a battle.
The crew with the lowest score in the Global K-dance Mission...
will face the Dropout Battle.
Among four crews that lost in each battle,
another crew with the second lowest score...
will face the Dropout Battle.
That means, 7th and 8th places...
- will face the Dropout Battle. - 7th and 8th places?
We must win in the 1 on 1 battle.
We're not pointing them out but 7th and 8th?
We're not pointing them out.
- We still have a chance. - You never know.
I don't know. I'm not sure.
I'll explain how the Global K-dance Mission...
is evaluated.
The scores from the global evaluation...
and the Fight Judges are added.
Then the additional points and deductions are applied...
in the final score.
In the last Class Mission,
the crew with the main dancer received 100 additional points.
The crew with the worst dancer received 50 deduction points.
That will be applied in the final score as well.
Based on the current additional points and deduction,
in SEVENTEEN's round,
YGX is 50 points ahead of Mbitious.
In BTS' round,
PRIME KINGZ is 50 points behind JustJerk.
In EXO's round,
We Dem BOYZ is 100 points ahead of 1MILLION.
In BigBang's round,
EO-DDAE is 150 points behind Bank 2 Brothers.
Three Fight Judges will distribute 200 points for each round,
with a total of 600 points to both crews.
The global evaluation score was calculated through...
the official SMF channel, The CHOOM and Mnet Plus...
from July 8 to 6pm on July 13.
The number of views and 100 times the number of likes...
makes up the global evaluation score.
The crew that placed first in the global evaluation...
(What will 1st place in global evaluation get?)
will receive 1,000 points.
(1,000 point flex)
That's insane.
(Surprised)
That's way too high.
Wait a minute.
That's way too big.
That got me thinking...
it'll be hard to catch up with 1MILLION.
Will receive 1,000 points.
The gap between us and Bank 2 Brothers is 150 points.
I thought that would...
put the gap in the shade.
So, 100 points are really small.
(Their precious 100 points became tiny.)
From 2nd to 8th place,
they will get different scores depending on their places.
As of 6pm on July 13 after the voting ended,
the crew with the highest views is...
1MILLION with 1,435,187 views.
(Approved)
However, ironically,
1MILLION with the highest views...
didn't get the most number of likes.
(Surprised)
The number of likes...
It must be Mbitious.
- Yes. - Please.
The number of views may not be everything.
Hello.
We're wearing matching clothes today.
We're both wearing silver.
(You're wearing silver too.)
If BoA shows up wearing gold...
- Like a Queen? - Yes.
(Fight Judges gather to evaluate Global K-dance Mission.)
1MILLION and We Dem BOYZ are battling for EXO's hit song...
for Global K-dance Mission.
Who became the backup crew?
Here is the backup penalty part.
Part C? I wonder how that turned out.
Are those in the front from that crew?
(Shocked)
How cruel.
Is that the actual move?
That must've really hurt their pride.
They're not even allowed to raise their head. Hold on.
This is no joke.
Will this be aired?
- Of course. - It will?
That's what you've been doing since practice.
(1MILLION's Hideout)
(1MILLION and We Dem BOYZ are battling each other.)
They're going up against us?
It's time to do what we're best at, choreographing.
So doesn't this look neat?
We Dem BOYZ had the right to choose,
and they chose us.
Let's change the boss of the choreography.
We have Young Jun and me.
But they're claiming our era is over.
That crew is looking down on us.
I'm losing my temper.
Making it impossible for that crew to copy our moves is crucial.
We can have them stand at the back...
like shadows to back us up.
Their goal is to make us fail, win,
and make us their backup dancers.
We need to use everything we have.
Focus on how we can win.
I will risk my life on this.
(1MILLION versus We Dem BOYZ, Choreography-copying Session)
- Gosh. - Hey.
(We Dem BOYZ is warming up in a flashy way.)
What's wrong with them?
We're getting a head start.
Why is he doing a handstand? It's making me anxious.
Where did he learn those weird moves?
Here's what we need to look out for.
Everyone in that crew learned acrobatics.
And they will use those techniques.
We need to keep that in mind.
1MILLION is probably doing a circus.
It goes down down
I doubt we can catch what they're doing at first.
Feeling furious,
they could act cheaply.
A member in We Dem BOYZ has to take their microphone off.
(Look at them.)
He must be breakdancing.
(Amazed)
I knew it.
Darn it.
(Insun, We Dem Boyz's official B-boy)
1MILLION as well.
(1MILLION is next.)
- What? - See that?
(Shocked)
Why did you act all innocent?
Both of them are taking our microphones off.
Are you doing the 2000?
(Choi Young Jun mastered 2000 in the previous battle.)
(We Dem Boyz's Choreography-copying Section)
I expected that much.
(Insun is showing off a breakdancing technique.)
It wasn't bad.
But that's more dangerous.
The faster one copies the moves, the sloppier they get.
And they believe they can do it.
We can do what We Dem BOYZ is good at.
But what we're good at,
I doubt We Dem BOYZ can do it.
(1MILLION's Choreography-copying Section)
Root and Yumeki falling on their back...
looked doable.
(Choi Young Jun and Baek Koo Young break dances on the side.)
It was easier than I thought.
I wanted to avoid becoming backup dancers at all costs.
We could not lose.
Let's give it our all today.
Okay.
I'd rather die than become a backup dancer.
Memorize the moves first.
(Baek Koo Young leads We Dem BOYZ.)
(1MILLION is trying their best at copying the choreography.)
Okay, let's try again until this part.
(Practicing We Dem Boyz's choreography nonstop)
Again.
You must step back.
(With Baek Koo Young's lead, they advance fast.)
Why don't we try part A again?
They're not looking at the mirror.
(1MILLION tries We Dem Boyz's choreography without the mirror.)
(Keeping their hawkish eyes on 1MILLION)
(1MILLION has copied We Dem Boyz's choreography.)
They're really something.
(They're used to We Dem Boyz's choreography now.)
We should start too.
(We Dem BOYZ is speeding up,)
(while 1MILLION is quickly moving onto the next step.)
I cannot stand behind them.
Here is the evaluation result.
(Revealing the evaluation)
EXO's round.
(Let's go.)
Oh, my gosh.
Baek Koo Young is the original choreographer of this song.
So unless he tries his best...
It must be tough, especially since we're used to the dance...
- and song. - Yes.
(Choreography by We Dem BOYZ, Choreography-copying Section)
I like this choreography.
(Copying the break dance)
Break dancing is a must.
(Choreography by 1MILLION, Choreography-copying Section)
1MILLION's choreography is easier...
than I expected.
(1MILLION added breakdancing techniques.)
I think that was their focus.
I bet they thought,
"Can they do it?" And they actually did.
They copied the moves well.
(Who will win the Copying Choreography Challenge?)
The winner of the Copying Choreography Challenge is...
Hey, let's hold hands. Hurry.
Let's pray.
I hope it's our crew.
(One crew must become the backup dancers.)
I don't want to become a backup dancer.
Being a backup dancer is...
Let's win this once.
Let us win just this once.
The winner is We Dem BOYZ.
(WDBZ won.)
(The two crews' fate changes with the Copying Choreography Challenge.)
- What? - For real?
Good job.
- Great job. - Good work.
(Feeling bitter)
We Dem BOYZ became the owner of the Backup Penalty Part.
Automatically,
1MILLION became We Dem Boyz's backup dancers.
(Leader Baek Koo Young can't lift his head up.)
What a bummer.
I hated the idea of getting the Backup Penalty.
I have danced for 20 years.
And I did that at the back.
When I applied for SMF,
there weren't any videos of me dancing.
I make the choreography,
but I don't dance it.
"My life might end making choreographies for others."
That thought hit me all of a sudden.
One big reason I chose to be on SMF...
was to show the public my dance.
That's how much I wanted to be on SMF.
I was ready to throw everything away for this show.
Is anyone upset about the result?
(1MILLION became backup dancers.)
Objectively speaking,
we made more mistakes in the Choreography-copying Section.
I admitted it the moment I saw the video.
As backup dancers, I know we'll do our best.
But I was too greedy.
Koo Young let out the pent-up anger on my behalf.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
I love you.
When you cried,
I tried so hard to fight back my tears.
I was too greedy this time.
No. Honestly, I felt the same as you.
Even if I made the choreography,
it wouldn't have been much different from yours.
Before we start,
we have a gift for you.
We have a gift for you.
(That's a bit...)
Backup 1, 2, and 3.
Stick them on top of your name.
I had a mental breakdown at that moment.
You want us to cover our names?
Who would've thought...
we would have to stick the backup dancer sticker on top of our names?
This is really mean.
I want to go home.
I can't believe Koo Young has to stick it on.
I had a mental breakdown back then.
A backup dancer.
Please stand like this.
Honestly, I was more worried about my crew members' feelings.
I didn't want my guys to feel discouraged.
Why don't you all roll over?
(Yechan)
(Root)
(He's in pain.)
My body was in pain and exhausted.
But I still had to try my best...
with my name covered...
to make the other crew shine.
It felt miserable.
Nobody came on this show to backup someone else.
I hate the word "backup." Seriously.
Everyone was low in spirits.
Let's try again. Lean.
They were treating us like objects.
Like that. Okay. Lean and face him.
Seriously.
It was a choreography to literally trample on us.
Face forward.
Come and sit down.
Prepare to become our dogs.
You won't know until you back off
I didn't know why I had to be treated like so.
I became more desperate and wanted to do better.
As much as I was humiliated as a backup dancer,
I will pay them back.
Making us flip out was a good stimulant.
Just wait.
("Growl" by EXO)
(The full clip of the backup penalty part...)
(is available at The CHOOM.)
- Gosh. - That's so humiliating.
Goodness. They really treated 1MILLION as their backup dancers.
That's so harsh.
Gosh. They made sure we couldn't see 1MILLION at all.
My mom won't be able to spot me.
- Look. - Gosh.
- This is heartbreaking. - They bumped into each other.
As for Koo Young or Young Jun,
they must have blamed themselves.
It was a loss on our crew. It wasn't an individual loss.
It hit me really hard.
But it gave me a chance to make me stronger.
For the Global K-dance Mission,
1MILLION performed with EXO's songs.
Let's check out 1MILLION's dance video first.
(Let's go, 1MILLION!)
Let's go, 1MILLION!
(Global K-dance Mission, choreography by 1MILLION)
("Overdose" and "Ko Ko Bop" by EXO)
(That's so cool.)
(The time-delay choreography leaves an impression on everyone.)
(Choreography by We Dem BOYZ, Choreography-copying Section)
(Impressed)
That's so cool.
(The full clip of the Global K-dance Mission...)
(is available at The CHOOM.)
(1MILLION's dance video is over.)
Moving on, We Dem BOYZ also performed with EXO's songs.
Let's check out We Dem Boyz's dance video next.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Make some noise. - Let's go.
Make some noise.
(What kind of dance video will We Dem BOYZ show them?)
(Global K-dance Mission, choreography by We Dem BOYZ)
("Overdose" and "Ko Ko Bop" by EXO)
(Copying)
Come in.
We were good.
(He's imitating a clock. He really is.)
The clock thing is cool.
I love this part.
(Loving it)
(Nervous)
(Choreography by 1MILLION, Choreography-copying Section)
(The full clip of the Global K-dance Mission...)
(is available at The CHOOM.)
You guys were great.
I kept wishing to win this mission.
"Please." I kept praying like this.
I was really desperate.
"We can't get eliminated here."
We will now announce the results of the Global K-dance Mission...
with EXO's songs between 1MILLION and We Dem BOYZ.
Gosh, my heart.
I can't watch this.
In the last Class Mission,
Vata of We Dem BOYZ from the Leader Class...
and Nino and Yumeki of 1MILLION from the Middle 1 Class...
contributed to their crews...
by being chosen as the main dancers.
And their contribution brought 100 additional points.
They both had 100 points.
- But they lost points. - Right.
(Sighing)
The worst dancer...
(The worst dancer of the Sub Leader Class, Choi Young Jun)
(The worst dancers of the Middle 2 Class, Yechan and Alexx)
Oh, right.
(1MILLION ended up losing the 100 points.)
That's heartbreaking.
I'm sorry once again.
I still feel awful about it.
We lost 100 points.
However, in the global evaluation,
1MILLION had the highest view count.
Their video was viewed 1,435,187 times.
Gosh. How can we beat that?
Holy moly. Seriously.
- They got twice as many votes? - More than twice.
As I told you, 1MILLION didn't receive...
the highest number of likes, though.
What's important is the number of likes.
I didn't think we were safe yet.
I'm really curious about that.
Right. Same here.
Which crew will face the crisis of getting a step closer...
to getting eliminated between 1MILLION We Dem BOYZ?
I wonder who won.
- It's anyone's game now. - Seriously.
Don't you think 1MILLION won?
But We Dem BOYZ started with 100 points.
That might play a big role.
Let's check the scores from the Fight Judges.
I really don't know how the judges will evaluate us.
The Fight Judges. Gosh.
Their scores take up a big percentage.
Our crew is cool.
So the judges might have liked our performance too.
(Scores from the Fight Judges)
(During the Fight Judge evaluation)
- They're in sync. - They came determined to win.
- This is the 1MILLION we know. - Right.
I really think...
1MILLION did a great job of changing the choreography.
(Evaluating the Copying Choreography Challenge)
We saw a lot of moves like that...
- at our agency. - Right. We did.
- It's completely new. - They picked a great concept.
I could tell 1MILLION was really upset...
and they were resolute to win.
- I could sense that. - Yes.
This part.
- Gosh. - Gosh. This...
- Kamel... Gosh. - This was all him.
And they were copying 1MILLION's choreography here.
But they added their own style to this section.
They weren't desperately trying to do a good job here.
"This is our style. So we'll do it like this."
That's what I felt from them.
Let's see which crew received a higher score...
from the Fight Judges.
Gosh. I can't wait to see the scores.
(Nervous)
We'll now reveal the scores from the Fight Judges.
(Scores from the Fight Judges)
(Shocked)
Gosh. Look at the scores.
Gosh. They won with the scores from the Fight Judges
Gosh. The score difference is 40.
(We Dem BOYZ: 320 points, 1MILLION: 280 points)
Do you remember the time-delay move?
- We Dem BOYZ won that part. - It was eye-catching.
- Right. We Dem BOYZ took the intro. - Right.
It's the kind of performance 1MILLION is used to.
You're shocked when you watch...
something so original and fresh.
And We Dem BOYZ had that in spades.
- Thank you. - We got a higher score from them.
Right.
I didn't expect this from the judges.
To be honest, I was insulted.
Because they have high expectations of us,
they hold us at a higher standard than We Dem BOYZ.
Gosh. I have no idea which crew is going to win.
All right. It's time to announce...
the combined scores...
of the Fight Judges' scores and the global evaluations.
- Let's hold hands. - Let's hold hands.
Let's hold hands.
Gosh. I can't watch this. Seriously.
(I'm not going to watch.)
- 1MILLION won, right? - Their view count was high.
The public doesn't know about us.
So our view count wasn't high.
I wondered if we could overcome this obstacle.
If 1MILLION loses...
It was probably because of the point deductions.
If that really happens, I won't be able to face my crew.
Seriously. We must win this time.
We must keep going up.
We're not done yet.
Please.
We will now reveal the results for these two crews.
(This is crazy!)
(To be continued)
(The first elimination is at stake. What will happen to the crews?)
We will now reveal the results for these two crews.
(Jaw-dropping)
(What had the dancers drop their jaws?)
Here they are.
(Global K-dance Mission: the EXO round)
(An observer was present while the votes were tallied.)
(1MILLION wins the Global K-dance Mission.)
Nice. We did it!
With a total score of 1,080, 1MILLION wins the battle.
The crew has advanced to the next round.
The 1MILLION crew scored...
a view-count of 1,435,187 in the global evaluation...
and received 99,410 likes in total.
The global evaluation is what led them to win.
They managed to turn the tables.
The global evaluation saved them.
(The members of 1MILLION cry their eyes out...)
(thinking about the hard work they put in.)
You all did so well.
We came up from behind and won.
We had to be backup dancers.
Whether it was the Class Mission or the worst dancer battle,
we kept on losing.
I lost count of how many times we lost...
because we had lost so much.
The hard work we put in wasn't all for nothing...
which put a smile on my face.
(We Dem BOYZ can't hide their disappointment.)
- We did well. - Right.
We all did well.
- I kind of knew it. - We did well.
- Will they battle it out? - Automatically...
That automatically put We Dem BOYZ on the path to elimination.
We could end up going home.
And we couldn't tell who we'd be up against.
We Dem Boyz's final score...
will be revealed once we know who is going up against whom.
He's not telling us the score yet.
The losing team's score won't be revealed yet...
because we don't know who'll come in last.
The scores of the four losing teams...
will be revealed later on.
We don't know who'll be in 7th or 8th place.
- Exactly. - But I doubt it's them.
We don't know that since the score hasn't been revealed.
Losing is crucial in this round.
The winner of the EXO round was 1MILLION.
We Dem BOYZ lost,
and the two crews now face different fates.
We Dem BOYZ, please get ready for the Dropout Battle.
Think that we're going to win it. There's no such thing as losing.
We're going to knock out whoever we're against.
I'll carry my team if I have to.
In no way will we be the backup dancers.
Over my dead body.
Why would I be their backup dancer?
(The battle to avoid being backup dancers)
(Copying Choreography Challenge)
Practice until you make it your own.
I'll have JustJerk be our backup dancers.
That means you are the backup dancers.
(Who shocked everyone by becoming the backup dancers?)
Next up, JustJerk and PRIME KINGZ...
will compete in the BTS round.
I definitely think we did better than PRIME KINGZ.
In no way will we be eliminated.
First, let's see who will be the backup dancers.
Here we go.
This will be a fun round.
Especially because their styles are distinctively different.
(What kind of choreography has the two crews come up with?)
I hate how JustJerk seems confident.
(Confident level of 1,000 percent)
We'll deliver our choreography today...
and have them lose all their confidence.
That's bold.
There are techniques that only we can do,
and those were incorporated into our choreography.
(PRIME KINGZ's Choreography-copying Section)
(Roh Tae Hyun, Wootae, 5000)
(Drawing attention)
(Hat trick)
Will they incorporate a hat trick?
That's what I'm most worried about.
(Gosh...)
Hat tricks are seen as high-level tricks in battles.
And they added that in their choreography.
(He's trying to copy the trick.)
They're doomed. How can they copy this?
You're bound to make mistakes.
How can one do that?
They're doomed.
In no way could they do this.
(JustJerk shows them their choreography next.)
(Hard-hitting)
This is doable.
Yes, these moves they can easily do.
The moves can be easily done once you learn them.
However, we knew for a fact that PRIME KINGZ lacked...
when it comes to hard-hitting choreography.
Our goal was to have them make a lot of mistakes.
You'll have to practice a lot of the details.
They could be easily spotted.
(What will happen?)
We'll only need two hours to memorize the moves...
and another two hours to dance it in their style.
It seemed easy enough.
We had a good chance of winning.
We'll copy their choreography down to the last detail.
If we count the beats perfectly,
- it'll surprise the others. - Right.
Let's run over them like a bulldozer.
We'll have JustJerk be our backup dancers...
and make them our personal dragons.
(BTS round, Dance Studio)
(PRIME KINGZ learns the dance, and Trix takes the lead.)
It's really fast.
(With difficulty)
- What next? - Keep going.
I didn't think it'd be hard.
But the beat...
- Come this way right away. - Sure.
The moves just wouldn't come naturally.
That's not the right beat.
We need to practice hard. No mistakes are allowed.
Do it until you get it. You can't get this wrong.
Two and three and four.
(The members keep making mistakes during practice.)
One and two and...
Why are you slacking off?
(Frozen)
What do you think your problem is?
(Eyes dart all over the place.)
I hadn't seen Trix like this before.
He was on edge, I guess.
It was his job to manage this project,
- but things weren't going smoothly. - Again. Once more.
Five, six.
Let's try that again.
Again.
Again. We'll do it three times. Five, six.
It was brutal. That's all I can say.
Doing the same moves...
to the same song over and over again wore us down.
I believed we could do it.
It was the only way we could beat JustJerk.
(The intense practice sessions took a toll on them physically.)
I'll jump.
(Knucks endures the shoulder pain he suffered...)
(while repeating the move.)
Hurry.
Wait. Hold on.
- Just a second. - He has cramps.
Does he have cramps?
(How will PRIME KINGZ do in Copying Choreography Challenge?)
Take deep breaths.
Deep breaths.
(Who will win the BTS round of the Copying Choreography Challenge?)
Both crews need to show us what they're capable of.
Do you remember what we said about JustJerk?
We haven't been able to see them shine.
JustJerk, you keep flying in the middle.
(During the Class Mission, JustJerk didn't stand out.)
It's the same for PRIME KINGZ. They haven't done much since...
- the No-Respect Underdog Battle. - Exactly.
PRIME KINGZ, for you, it's one problem after the next.
(They showed their weaker side during the choreography battle.)
It must've been a challenge for PRIME KINGZ...
to copy the hard-hitting style that JustJerk is known for.
(Out of the two world-class teams, who will win?)
It's "Fire."
(Choreography by JustJerk)
- This is crazy. - No way!
(No way!)
This is JustJerk,
PRIME KINGZ can't hit the steps.
(PRIME KINGZ failed to copy JustJerk's steps.)
(Now, PRIME KINGZ change formation.)
(Trix is malfunctioning.)
(Making mistakes)
Please. Kyoyung Jr.
Look. They just can't keep up.
JustJerk did a better job.
Nice.
Trix fumbled just now.
It looks off if you're the last one to do it.
(Scoffing)
(PRIME KINGZ made serious mistakes.)
The whole situation seemed foreign to me.
I was upset, embarrassed, and angry.
There's not a word that can describe all the emotions I felt.
They totally crushed their opponents, right?
This...
This is an easy one.
The winner of the Copying Choreography Challenge is...
JustJerk.
(JustJerk wins.)
(Global K-dance Mission: the BTS round)
(JustJerk celebrates their victory.)
- Good job. - You guys did well.
(PRIME KINGZ's leader Trix can't seem to lift his chin up.)
Trix.
It's all right.
We all got nervous and couldn't dance it properly.
It's all in the past now, so let's move on.
It's all right.
(Sub leader Knucks comforts his crew.)
Crumping isn't a genre you can master in half a day...
because it requires you to pour your energy into the moves.
Maybe I got too greedy.
Did I drag my crew down a rabbit hole?
Did I push them too close to their limits?
I chose to be a leader who pushed his crew off a cliff,
and that's why we got crushed.
I'm the worst.
(The crew members haven't seen Trix be this crushed before.)
(He ends up showing tears.)
It's all right.
(He couldn't stop crying because the guilt was overwhelming.)
- I'm so sorry. - Don't say that.
- I'm so sorry. - I know how burdened you were.
- I'm so sorry. - It's all right, okay?
It's really okay.
All of us were lacking.
We're okay.
We don't have many opportunities.
We could get eliminated because of this.
To be honest, I don't think I'm even qualified to be the leader.
I feel so sorry for my crew.
We're covering the names?
They want us to cover the names.
("Backup" is on it instead of the dancer's name.)
(2face, Backup 3)
Backup...
PRIME KINGZ as backup dancers.
I have mixed feelings right now.
I was really offended by it.
Let's start from the top.
- Yes! - Yes!
(Young Jay leads the directing.)
(Performing silently)
Man, the members from PRIME KINGZ wouldn't give me an answer.
I get it, you know.
But shouldn't we at least do this?
It was so stifling.
(The practice at the dance studio is stifling.)
We made up our minds to give it a shot just once.
We decided to think that we're performing with them.
But they rubbed it in, you know.
The plan that I was thinking of is...
- for us to only dance in this part. - Okay.
Our own dance has to come out,
so the members of PRIME KINGZ have to simply follow.
We have no choice.
We strategized so that we would stand out more.
All right. Let's all give it a shot.
- JustJerk members, please step out. - Okay.
(What are they going to do?)
We're thinking of two people...
- spreading out the flag. - Okay.
(What flag?)
We're going to put "JustJerk" on that flag.
(Smirking)
Not our crew's flag, but the other crew's flag.
We did many dance performances promoting Korea.
Should we hold the Korean flag?
Since it's JustJerk's performance,
should we hold JustJerk's logo too?
Who would want to hold another crew's flag?
As backup dancers during the performance at that.
If you're backup dancers, shouldn't you be able to hold that?
Hold one flag up here.
Likewise, the two of you can hold a flag here.
When they made us hold the flag,
I felt like I was about to cry at that moment.
(Knucks can't raise his head.)
- You can spread it out. - Okay.
Darn it.
- Four, five, six, seven, eight. - Four, five, six, seven, eight.
We made our crew members go through that humiliation.
(Sub leader Knucks has a heavy heart for not protecting his crew)
When we actually started practicing,
we saw Knucks and Trix doing that...
behind JustJerk.
It felt like they were demeaning our PRIME KINGZ,
like we were below JustJerk.
We'll definitely win next time.
We got more determined.
(Director Crew, JustJerk)
(Versus Backup Crew, PRIME KINGZ)
(Crews for BTS)
("IDOL" by BTS)
(PRIME KINGZ enters with the flag.)
(The full clip of the Global K-dance Mission...)
(is available at The CHOOM.)
Hey!
(Laughing)
Is that for real?
Hey, that was so mean!
(What did we do? What was so mean?)
You guys.
That was mean. So mean.
You guys were too cruel.
- You guys were mean. - That was too cruel.
- They represented Korea. - They sure did.
They represented Korea all right.
They did what?
(Oh, my gosh!)
(Oh, this was it?)
I thought one would be of PRIME KINGZ.
- Me too. - It was the Korean flag.
- Gosh. - Gosh, that was bold.
(Trix had to hold the Korean flag behind JustJerk.)
The leader was holding it?
Did they make the leader hold it?
(Everyone is laughing at the flag ending.)
I was laughing, but I wasn't really laughing.
It was so humiliating to think that nearly 60 dancers...
were watching this with us,
and I had some mixed feelings too,
so I couldn't lift my head all of a sudden.
As this is a battle between two world-class teams,
everyone is keen to find out which team won.
Between PRIME KINGZ and JustJerk,
which team will be on the brink of elimination?
(He's desperate.)
Now, for the Global K-dance Mission...
(Please.)
We'll move directly on to BTS' round with JustJerk's video.
(Global K-dance Mission)
(Fight Club)
(During Choreography-copying Session)
(PRIME KINGZ showed the hat trick...)
(during Choreography-copying Session.)
How can we do that?
I have no words.
(Choreography-copying Section that JustJerk created)
Since they came at us strong, we'll come at them strong too.
We brought our weapon too.
I think the guy with the windbreaker is going to do something.
- By himself? - Yes.
(JustJerk's weapon is on standby)
(What could it be?)
Yejun's breaking skills.
It's a harmony between B-boying and acrobatics.
(He is in shock.)
We're in trouble.
I don't know how to back tumble. I'm in trouble.
Actually, Yejun was our strategy.
He is in charge of the breaking part of our crew,
so we have a lot of consecutive difficult skills.
I don't think the members of PRIME KINGZ could ever copy that.
That's how we felt.
This is what you must copy.
Can we re-watch Yejun's B-boying part?
Can I just do it?
Do the Thomas.
- Is he hurt? - I heard something pop.
(Yejun doesn't look well after showing the breaking skill.)
(He is worried.)
Did anyone get that wrong?
(He suddenly collapses.)
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
- I think he dislocated it. - What did he do earlier?
Yejun suffered a huge injury on his shoulder.
It's okay. I think we should send him to the hospital for now.
The hospital.
- Let's take you to the hospital. - Okay.
Is it really bad?
(JustJerk's hideout)
It's all right. Yejun will be fine.
(The crew members are in shock over Yejun's sudden injury.)
It's okay.
I think the members totally panicked...
when Yejun got injured.
I felt so bad for Yejun.
Since we had to win,
we needed a move that PRIME KINGZ couldn't do.
Yejun was the only one who could do those moves.
I couldn't tell him to stop.
That's what I was most sorry about.
I'm the leader.
In every situation, I had to keep my cool.
I thought that we couldn't stay sad at that moment.
It's okay. And Yejun will be back in no time.
We were being very ambitious,
and there were risks that came with it.
Yes, we can do it. We can do it.
It's okay.
"Let's change our strategy."
Seo Won said that he should do it.
Seo Won will replace him now,
and we'll change it to a standing move.
(JustJerk re-delivered the dance with S.ONE at the center.)
When we saw the changed choreography of JustJerk,
it became weaker than we thought.
It was easier for us to attempt.
We had no choice.
We had to do the best we could do.
Guys, don't lose your drive. It isn't over yet.
- Yes. - Be energetic.
Yejun was here.
As Yejun dropped out,
there were gaps in our choreography.
We tried to take out a lot of the moves.
Go in circles. In circles.
I think we can go like this.
I'll keep trying the hat trick.
- Four and five and six. - Four and five and six.
Let's do it again. Sorry.
- Two and three and... - Two and three and... Again.
We kept getting stumped.
(Young Jay struggles with the hat trick.)
I'd never done it before.
(Let's see how well you do it.)
How are we supposed to do that?
We have to do it despite that.
There wasn't a moment we could take a break.
I can do it. I just have to do the hat trick well.
I'll go and practice. You guys keep dancing.
Let the body remember. Don't use your head.
Let the body remember.
That kind of strategy may seem dumb,
but it works well sometimes.
Try it as much as I can.
(Young Jay practices without letup.)
Yes.
I have no intentions to eliminate my crew members.
It's okay.
At least for my crew members,
I have to succeed.
I will definitely succeed.
- Shall we try it with the music? - Yes.
(JustJerk rehearses the final performance.)
Hey, this is the copying section.
(He watches closely.)
I'm praying for Young Jay to make a mistake.
My prayer was answered.
My goodness. JustJerk is in danger.
It was a regretful rehearsal.
I'm going to do well.
I want to do even better.
We have to win.
(Global K-dance Mission, choreography by JustJerk)
(Exclaiming)
- It's an eye. - Open up.
("Blood Sweat and Tears" and "Fire" by BTS)
Oh, sexy.
Oh, that's sexy.
You're so sexy.
Oh, my.
- Look. - There he goes.
Let's go.
Let's go, Young Jay!
(Focusing)
It's coming out.
(Choreography by PRIME KINGZ, Choreography-copying Section)
- Yes! - Yes!
(Falling in love)
(Trix, are you watching?)
(Let's go, Young Jay.)
He worked hard.
(Choreography by PRIME KINGZ, Choreography-copying Section)
- Hulk did everything for this part. - Look at his face.
Hulk, rip everything!
He's clenching his teeth.
(Clenching)
Are your teeth okay?
He has beautiful teeth.
(Focusing)
(This is JustJerk.)
Hey.
(Everyone is dancing along.)
(The full clip of the Global K-dance Mission...)
(is available at The CHOOM.)
Hey.
(Clapping)
(Disappointed for no reason)
When JustJerk's video was playing, there was not that much cheering.
"We can win this."
We'll continue right away...
and watch the dance video for PRIME KINGZ.
- PRIME KINGZ, baby. - PRIME KINGZ!
(What will PRIME KINGZ's video be like?)
Thank you for enduring all the humiliation.
- Good job, everyone. - Good work.
While watching the video in the fight zone, I was so shocked.
(Fight Zone)
While watching the video,
I realized we were trying so hard to do choreography.
We were being too greedy...
when all of the best choreography teams are gathered here.
Our way of thinking was wrong.
I thought we were being greedy for no reason...
when we don't specialize in choreography.
"We should do what we're good at."
We have to change our mindset.
I think it's better for us to dance like ourselves.
Like PRIME KINGZ, like Knucks, like Trix.
That's how we can earn respect from other people.
(Agreeing fervently)
(The day of the dance video shooting)
Okay. Good.
One, two, three, start.
PRIME KINGZ has entered the studio.
Look at their makeup.
They have makeup on their mouths.
(PRIME KINGZ prepared skeleton stickers for their mouths.)
(Charismatic)
They had a weapon.
I didn't expect them to come prepared like that.
Isn't it a bit too much?
It was to show our own colour...
and distinguish ourselves.
Visually, we are able to showcase our energy directly,
and that is why we came up with that strategy.
Let's prepare a performance that can showcase our identity.
I hope people can feel the rawness from the stage.
(Global K-dance Mission, choreography by PRIME KINGZ)
("Blood Sweat and Tears" and "Fire" by BTS)
Their makeup is so cool.
I know, right? They covered it at first.
Their power is on another level.
How many spins was that?
(He puts on his glasses.)
They're so cool.
Gosh. They're so cool.
(Choreography by JustJerk, Choreography-copying Section)
- They're doing a good job. - Yes.
Why are they so in sync?
(Getting goosebumps)
- They're good. - Yes.
They're good at dancing to choreography.
(Choreography by JustJerk, Choreography-copying Section)
- Why are they so good? - They copied everything.
(Clapping automatically)
Wow, they're so cool.
(The full clip of the Global K-dance Mission...)
(is available at The CHOOM.)
Wow, he's like an evil master.
Wow, that was cool.
They're so cool.
(PRIME KINGZ's fans, We Dem BOYZ, are cheering.)
Knucks!
They're like werewolves.
(Another group of big fans, EO-DDAE)
They're werewolves.
(PRIME KINGZ smiles only after the dance video is over.)
(The expressions of the JustJerk members look complicated.)
They're good.
The reactions to their performance were better than ours.
I felt nervous.
(Global K-dance Mission, the BTS round)
I will announce the results for the crews for the BTS round.
The difference in the points between the two crews...
is just 50 points.
Oh, it's 50 points.
We made that gap.
(PRIME KINGZ got 50 points deducted after losing to Mbitious.)
I'm the leader, but I deducted 50 points for our team.
It's not that big of a gap. It's okay.
(Sighing)
I felt so bad for my crew mates.
Between PRIME KINGZ and JustJerk,
which crew will stand on the brink of elimination?
Which crew is actually world-class?
One Fight Judge...
gave 150 points to a crew.
(That's crazy.)
(Deuk and Don are shocked.)
- Please be us. - Please.
That means,
automatically, the other crew received 50 points.
(Nervous)
Which crew did the Fight Judges choose as the winner?
Please let it be us.
There was a huge difference between the number of views...
so we had to receive a lot of points from the judges.
- Please. Just once. - Please.
I can't predict the result.
- The scores of the Fight Judges... - We have to trust them.
(They also feel anxious.)
Please give us a good score.
Please, Fight Judges.
Fight Judges, help us.
will be revealed now.
(What are the results that made everyone surprised?)
Wow, eighty-what? What?
PRIME KINGZ won.
(Scores from the Fight Judges: 385 versus 215)
(Watching PRIME KINGZ's performance)
Wow, PRIME KINGZ.
- They did amazing. - That made me think differently.
Their way of expression is amazing.
They had a great concept,
and they did so well with the choreography.
Yes. They brought over the same moves,
but they changed them to make them look like their own style.
- They didn't lose their colour. - Right.
I thought their showmanship was so cool.
- They did a good job, PRIME KINGZ. - Seriously. They did amazing.
- They did well. - Yes.
(They watch JustJerk's performance right after.)
Why do they look so weak?
Why do they look so tired?
(Sudden silence)
This was...
Why do they look so weak?
I felt this.
The crew members must've noticed...
the leader's stress.
That stress...
gave them negative influence.
PRIME KINGZ looked better...
with that choreography.
What a twist.
That was unexpected.
No one saw that coming.
The scores from the Fight Judges are low.
We've got to show them next time.
It was regrettable.
We believe the result wasn't good...
because we weren't good enough.
That's a big score gap.
What's the score gap?
It's 170.
The Fight Judge score gap is huge.
One hundred and seventy? What's going on?
We won with an unbelievable gap.
So I had hope.
How will the number of likes...
change their fates?
We have our supporters.
We should trust them.
(Anxious)
Here's the result...
after combining the scores from the Fight Judges...
and the global evaluation score.
Come on!
The die is cast.
It's driving me crazy.
Who would win?
JustJerk, probably.
There was a huge gap between their number of views.
But you never know. Their number of likes may be low.
Will they be able to turn the tables?
Dear All Mighty. Give me power.
I don't want to get eliminated.
I'm never getting eliminated.
The Global K-dance Mission.
- Please. - Please.
Seriously, I'm so desperate.
The winner is...
(Who's the final winner of BTS' round?)
(The result shocks everyone.)
JustJerk.
(JustJerk wins in the Global K-dance Mission.)
(JustJerk won against PRIME KINGZ.)
JustJerk.
The global evaluation score must've been huge.
Right.
JustJerk won with a total score of 915.
They recorded 1,034,215 views...
and 67,238 likes.
The global evaluation changed the result.
Let's move on. We can move on to the next round.
Well done.
Good job.
We think we barely made it.
(PRIME KINGZ lost despite their hope.)
It's okay.
PRIME KINGZ must be sad.
Their Fight Judge score is way higher.
What a shame.
There's nothing I can do about the global evaluation score.
PRIME KINGZ automatically...
becomes the potential worst crew.
That breaks my heart.
- Worst crew? - Yes.
(Sighing)
It's fine. We still did well.
PRIME KINGZ became the potential worst crew upon their defeat.
How do you feel to be on the brink of elimination?
The Fight Judge score gap is 170 points.
I want to tell my crew members...
that I'm proud of them for doing a great job...
against JustJerk, a globally famous crew.
(Respect)
(Approved)
And...
battles are what we're good at.
(Scared)
That's intense.
(Nervous)
That's really scary.
(Scared)
If we battle with them, there will be no chance.
I get scared even thinking about it.
I'll say no more.
We're prepared for the battle.
You may look forward to it.
(Feeling guilty)
Whoever has to do it is doomed.
One who has to do it is doomed.
Oh, my goodness.
They said they're prepared for the battle.
PRIME KINGZ. Please get ready for the Dropout Battle.
Okay.
- Let's get ready for the battle. - Okay.
They'll come back alive from the battle like zombies.
That's what makes them scarier.
The current potential worst crews are...
We Dem BOYZ and PRIME KINGZ.
Mbitious first. YGX.
(Mbitious and YGX met to exchange the choreography.)
Honestly, I'm not...
looking forward to it.
No.
We're not looking forward...
to seeing your choreography either.
(I can't watch this.)
I never expected you...
to be able to copy our choreography.
(Groaning)
You might as well just enjoy watching.
(They nailed it.)
"Enjoy watching."
They have no idea.
I don't get them.
YGX will never be able to copy our choreography at all.
It's hard.
I'm good at copying choreographies.
I tend to memorize choreographies fast.
But this part is pretty difficult.
I wonder what YGX did.
I'm expecting it to be funny.
They'll probably be flippant.
What if they suddenly put on a skit?
(5000's skit)
Will they be able to copy ours?
I can never imagine them doing it.
We have seven choreographers.
But that's not the case for them.
No matter how intense and difficult they make it,
it won't be that hard.
I'm expecting a lot of techniques.
What do you mean by a lot of techniques?
(Choreography-copying Session begins.)
Mbitious!
(Mbitious presents Choreography-copying Section first.)
(It's not that bad.)
(Mbitious presents the floor moves.)
(Grinning)
It's easy.
It's way too easy.
"What is that? Did they really think we won't be able to copy that?"
"That choreography?"
I thought they were joking.
(YGX's Choreography-copying Section)
Copy them.
We must copy them.
They're trying to confuse us.
They twisted it with a time lag.
(Waacking attack)
I knew they'd to waacking.
- I knew they'd do that. - It's not that bad.
It's not bad.
(Staring)
(YGX's choreography is nearing the end.)
- It's not bad. - It's not that bad.
- It's easy. - They're done for.
They were very confident during the interview,
so I was worried, to be honest.
I was like, "What makes them think we can't copy that?"
They tried to hide their low quality...
with the structure.
What upset me was that...
we did all kinds of things,
but they didn't put in much effort.
Compared to our efforts,
they were very insincere.
Their choreography looked too easy for me.
Why did they make it so easy?
What on earth are they thinking?
I was like, "Are they serious?"
I know. I don't get it.
They say that because they never tried it.
To be honest,
how can they copy my choreography?
How can they do that?
That was our aim.
Once they start copying,
they'll be like, "What's this? What's wrong with the beat?"
This isn't hard at all.
Do they really think this is hard?
If they mean it, they're crazy.
If they mean it, they're not real dancers.
I don't care what YGX does.
I can't be their backup dancers.
We've got to hurry up.
We have to win the backup penalty part.
That's going to be humiliating.
- What is? - Being their backup dancers.
Right.
I can never accept that.
(Mbitious and YGX gathered to practice SEVENTEEN's round.)
I haven't been to the airport for so long.
Where are we practicing?
Raise your hands when you're crossing.
I didn't have to say it.
Raise your hands, guys.
We don't have much time left.
- Shall we start? - What's this?
Are we practicing together?
- What's going on? - Let's hurry up.
Don't pay attention to them.
Oh, I stand here.
I think I'm between them.
- I'm in the middle. - But the line...
That's not it.
They were standing diagonally.
They were standing in the diagonal direction.
- What's the matter? - What's the issue?
You're standing back right.
Me?
"What on earth is going on?"
We weren't originally a crew.
We're still learning about each other.
Let me get this straight. Look at me.
On the beat, back to your positions.
I have an opinion. Why don't we do that same move...
and come in like this, not like this?
- I think that's better. - I think...
For this move... Boom, boom.
- We all move forward. - Yes.
Instead of everyone moving...
Should we stand in the same line?
- Hang on. - Can we change it?
- No. - MOOD DOK was standing in the back.
- He's in the back? - He comes forward.
We were stuck,
whereas things were going smooth...
for YGX.
We were in the same space, but things were completely different.
We were stimulated by them.
I didn't know YGX were in perfect sync.
"How is that possible? It's as if they practiced it in advance."
That really stirred me up.
(Mbitious begins practicing.)
(Closing his eyes tight)
We have to do well,
but I kept thinking it won't be possible on the quiet.
(5000 struggles to focus.)
It was sad to watch him.
He wasn't leading the group, but rather,
"I shouldn't cause my crew any damage."
Wootae. At the end,
how do you move your arm?
I told Wootae...
to take the lead.
We'll have to support Wootae...
for him to keep it going.
I felt bad for Wootae.
I'm the leader,
but all I'm doing is sitting down.
I have not once fulfilled my duty as a leader...
until now.
If I had shown what I had got...
when I needed to...
since the battle mission,
it wouldn't have impacted me much...
no matter what had happened next.
The constant sense of responsibility and pressure...
made it hard for him.
And watching him from the side was upsetting...
and heartbreaking.
Everyone's elimination...
depended on me.
That got me a little scared.
(5000 of Mbitious is having difficulty breathing.)
- Can I get some fresh air? - Yes.
(5000 is unable to continue talking during the interview.)
You can do it.
The more missions we did,
the smaller 5000 became. And he kept walking on eggshells,
which we started doing too.
5000 became weak, and so did we. And that's a fact.
Darn it.
I'm having a mental breakdown. So I can't remember the timing.
I witnessed 5000 falter today.
I might have a breakdown too.
And that made me falter a bit too.
Honestly, I told 5000 that it was a mess right now,
which was harsh.
The person we think...
is our pillar doesn't think he is one.
Wootae was about to lose it,
but he knew the sub leader shouldn't.
So I could tell he was suppressing it.
(They tried much harder to overcome the limitations of a project crew.)
I'm sorry.
What should we do first?
We experienced how all of us can break down when our pillar does.
So if that pillar holds us tight,
we could become one.
I should pull myself together...
and properly act as a leader should...
once again.
- It's SEVENTEEN's round. - SEVENTEEN's round.
Mbitious versus YGX.
Here's what I find interesting.
In the last battle, Hyunse...
and 5000 fought each other, and YGX won in the end.
And they're fighting each other again in this mission.
King Vata.
(How is their choreography?)
They're really...
(Choreography by Mbitious)
It's by Mbitious.
It's really...
They gave them a really easy choreography.
What now?
(YGX easily copied Mbitious's Choreography-copying Section.)
YGX copied the choreography better.
(Choreography by YGX)
- They're really witty. - That was witty.
Roh Tae Hyun missed some of the waacking moves.
This was...
- It's them. - Yes.
Here is the Fight Judge's evaluation result.
I'm getting really nervous.
My hands are getting numb.
My fingertips are numb. What do I do?
Stretch them like this.
I'm going nuts.
The winner of the Copying Choreography Challenge is...
Seriously.
We had to win it no matter what.
Nothing is going to be more humiliating...
than becoming the backup dancers.
I'm going to lose it if we become...
the backup dancers.
- Please. - YGX.
(YGX wins the SEVENTEEN round of the Global K-dance Mission.)
- Okay! - Gosh.
(YGX wins, Mbitious loses)
(YGX cheers after checking they won the Copying Choreography Challenge.)
- We knew it. - We did it.
(Meanwhile, the crew that lost, Mbitious, is left speechless.)
When can we stop being backup dancers?
It's infuriating.
Great job, guys.
- Good work. - We did well.
Why do we always suffer like this?
To become really strong.
It's about time 5000 gets his act together.
- You're right. - As a leader,
he needs to wake up...
for the sake of his crew to lead them.
They need to humbly accept what they lacked...
during the Copying Choreography Challenge...
- and get back on their feet. - Yes.
I hope this will give them motivation.
The more choreographies we got, the more I felt...
I kept dumping my burden onto you guys...
because I wasn't competent enough.
But even if we get eliminated after working our buttocks off,
I'm going to risk my life trying to win this battle.
So don't worry. We won't get eliminated.
But actually experiencing it is infuriating.
This is the worst-case scenario.
I will have to experience the most destructive.
Something I'm not sure why I have to.
When we practice, let's do it fast.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Before we start, - Yes?
please stick this on.
We were done for.
I couldn't help but laugh...
because the reality was absurd.
Are we sticking it on top of our name?
You need to keep your crew name.
So our names are being denied.
Is our name "backup?"
How cruel.
Let me help you.
It was the most humiliating thing since I started dancing.
I believed we were in this situation...
because I failed as a leader.
So I felt really bad.
- The part when you step forward. - It's the most crucial part.
Can the dancers in the same class wait behind?
- Okay. - Here, Wootae.
- Okay. - Behind him.
You're mine.
You'll become a really stylish and cool hanger.
So you have to...
Keep your facial expression in check.
(YGX is using Mbitious as their human hanger.)
And leave.
(Breathing out)
The hanger part is too much.
This is going too far.
I danced for years, and yet, I'm a hanger here.
Making someone a part of structure...
was what really set me off.
Being a hanger was very humiliating.
I was looking at MOOD DOK, and he was laughing.
It made me feel extremely small.
How dare they make us a hanger?
We were posing there like some old trees.
- Let's fix the pose to this. - Okay.
I'm done. I got my pose.
(Will Mbitious overcome this sadness?)
Who dares stick "backup" on top of my name?
Seriously. I feel terrible.
I will make them pay...
for the humiliation we felt.
(The members of Mbitious are on stage as YGX's backup dancers.)
("Adore U" by SEVENTEEN)
(The full clip of the backup penalty part...)
(is available at The CHOOM.)
Me dancing as a backup dancer annoyed me,
but the fact that my crew members...
were humiliated together...
as backup dancers annoyed me more.
That was obnoxious.
I'll get back at them for this humiliation one day.
I seriously don't get what they want from us.
(Mbitious felt more humiliated after the stage.)
The studio we were at was huge.
But despite its size, I felt stuffy.
Even though we were monitoring together,
all I could see was my name as a backup dancer.
I'm not a backup dancer.
My name is Kim Pyoungya of Mbitious.
From now on,
I will try my utmost best not to experience...
such humiliation again.
Believe in me and march forward.
Let's keep winning.
Looks
(Leader 5000 cheers up for the main stage.)
Again. Wootae, can you step in faster?
- Okay. - Let's go.
There were many ups and downs,
but I will wake up and overcome them well.
And then I will do my best to pay YGX back for what they did to us.
- One. - If it were me,
I wouldn't have been able to come to my senses that easily.
He's an amazing person.
We're in sync now.
(Mbitious became stronger with 5000's care.)
- You got it wrong. - Are you okay?
- Hurry. Let's do it. - Because of this...
I should pull myself together.
It's fun at this moment practicing.
I'll do anything...
to save Mbitious from being eliminated.
All right. Let's watch the crews for SEVENTEEN.
Let's watch the dance video of Mbitious first.
- Let's go! - Let's go.
- Yes. - You can do it!
Mbitious.
(Global K-dance Mission, choreography by Mbitious)
("CLAP" and "VERY NICE" by SEVENTEEN)
(Oh, clap, clap, clap, clap)
Their facial expressions are amazing.
Wootae is smiling.
(Very nice!)
Roh Tae Hyun is singing.
He's a singer, after all.
Idols are great in facial expressions.
(The full clip of Mbitious's dance is available at The CHOOM.)
Ending.
(Great ending poses)
(Wootae is embarrassed.)
(They uproar with the unexpected ending.)
(My eyes!)
- Don't look at Wootae. - Oh, no.
The ending fairy.
(The ending lingers for a long time.)
Let's see YGX's dance video, crew for SEVENTEEN.
- I'm getting nervous. - You can't be.
Seriously.
(Nervous)
(Crews for SEVENTEEN: YGX versus Mbitious)
(Global K-dance Mission, choreography by YGX)
(Fight Club)
(Mbitious versus YGX, Choreography-copying Session)
(I'm good too.)
(YGX and Mbitious are copying with SEVENTEEN's songs.)
We really want to win.
We lost to you before.
So honestly speaking, we really want to win you guys.
No matter what it takes.
I want to make our choreography too hard and high in level...
so that you can't copy it.
They said they'll make it so hard...
that it'll be impossible for us to copy.
I'm wondering if he made a choreography following his words.
I'm very curious.
(Mbitious demonstrates the Choreography-copying Section.)
(The Choreography-copying Section includes floor movements.)
It's easy.
For choreography copying,
we're at the top among them.
Grab and cut through.
Spin and...
He copies immediately.
Like this?
Oh, like this?
Oh, nice.
Then, go forward.
(Increasingly anxious)
It's good.
(Thumbs up)
We've done so many choreographies so far.
We tried funny and cute choreographies.
We also experienced really cool...
and complex choreographies.
So with this mission,
we're at an advantage...
because we learn faster than them.
Let's memorize the choreography within an hour.
- First, let's copy exactly. - Yes, exactly.
There are the hand moves.
Kick and lower down.
(One demonstration...)
(is enough for them.)
(Oh, yes.)
(He's good,)
Our choreography must've been really difficult.
I think so.
Why does the choreography made by Mbitious feel so easy?
(After one hour of copying choreography)
(YGX is almost done copying the choreography made by Mbitious.)
In 5, 6, 7, 8.
(Nervous, anxious)
How can they copy it within the same given time?
How is it possible for them to copy it...
as if it's customized for them?
Honestly, they were a bit annoying.
I felt too good.
They looked down on us.
(During the first meeting)
(YGX was chosen to be the first predicted dropout crew.)
- Gosh. - I knew it.
They passionately dance Lee Jung's choreography at the back.
YGX is really...
(YGX is like a bonus stage.)
I want to break everything.
In battles, which we weren't good at,
we were at the bottom.
(Final Ranks for the Battle)
(8th place, YGX)
This mission is advantageous to us.
We need to take this with us.
(Will YGX succeed in copying the choreography perfectly?)
- Soft drinks... - Yes.
and something like chocolate?
Yes, they're hungry.
- Let's try this. - This looks delicious.
I think that's enough.
(It's a convenience store shopping time.)
- Thank you. - Yes.
I forgot to bring my wallet.
People don't bring around wallets anymore.
What's this with your phone?
What is it?
Nowadays, you can easily pay without your card.
You chose this photo.
Yes, but I'll change it to one with six packs.
I don't think that's possible.
- Look, but... - I've never seen it with a photo.
Right? It's his first time too.
(Payment is easily made.)
Are you twins?
- Yes. - Oh, yes.
You two look alike.
We saw earlier...
how Mbitious changed the choreography.
(During the dance video rehearsal)
(Mbitious changed the choreography except for the copying section.)
(Dumbfounded)
I think they were influenced a lot by our choreography.
The whole flow.
(YGX made the concept of the song clearly visible.)
We thought the concept of the song should be clearly visible.
After showing the humorous and exciting side,
then we danced like we were having fun.
(Enjoy it!)
For Mbitious, it was just a cool performance.
It didn't go along with the song.
The first choreography by Mbitious that we saw...
was totally different.
("VERY NICE" choreography that's remade by Mbitious)
Didn't they copy ours too much?
They copied our concept.
They saw our choreography and realized something.
They focused a lot on their facial expressions too.
What's this? Are they copycats?
(YGX practices before the video shoot.)
One, two, and facial expression.
Facial expression.
One, two, three.
In the video, our facial expressions,
vibes and teamwork will be shown.
I don't think we'll lose on these.
Don't look at the ground.
Look at the camera and lip sync...
or constantly show your facial expressions.
- Don't let your guard down. - Yes.
I hope we win at all costs.
Honestly, I hope we win significantly.
It's our turn.
It's a given that we must do well with our dancing,
but the humorous elements...
are what we're most confident about for this mission.
I think we'll win.
We must win.
We have to beat Mbitious.
We should win neatly...
and end the bad relationship.
That'll be a clean battle.
Next, let's see YGX's dance video,
the crew for SEVENTEEN.
(Amazed)
- This is fraud. - Fraud!
It's a mirror.
(Like this.)
They're good-looking.
Oh, my. Who's that?
Let's go.
I'll really do my best.
- Me too. I'll do my best. - Thank you.
Anyway, we have one stage.
- Let's do this. - We can do it.
It's a performance in the end.
I'll do my best as a crew member.
They're ten years older than me.
So I was thankful as they really did their best.
I also thought about not being a cheater.
I think we should just think of it as another performance of ours...
and show them what we got.
We had to work together for this performance.
I wanted to harmonize with PRIME KINGZ.
We should pay more attention to the side when we do this move.
- It was fun. - It was fun.
We wouldn't have done that in real life.
(A crew will be eliminated for the first time next week.)
The Dropout Battle will begin...
to decide a crew that will be eliminated first.
- Please. - We have to battle it again here?
We feel great about the battle. Our battle will be amazing.
I want to stop losing.
We won't be eliminated.
There's no way we will be. And we won't.
You can all watch and learn how a battle should be.
I plan to give it my all.
PRIME KINGZ never loses.
"We must win no matter what."
My heart keeps pounding like crazy.
He must be so nervous.
The first crew to be eliminated...
is...
What was that?
This makes no sense.
I was shocked after hearing the results.
"Why does this crew have to get eliminated..."
"after the first Dropout Battle?"
It wasn't easy to make this decision.
I would like to thank both crews...
for putting on great performances.
The first crew to be eliminated from Street Man Fighter...
You may leave the fight zone.
This is so cruel.