This film is based on historical facts blended with artistic fiction.
The ever-unchanging traitor
is Suyang who now sits upon the dragon throne!
In 1452, Yi Hong-wi ascended the throne at the age of twelve.
The following year, his uncle, Grand Prince Suyang, rebelled, seized the throne, and proclaimed himself king.
The treacherous minister Han Myong-hoe,
who deceived His Majesty and threw the realm
into chaos, shall surely face the wrath of heaven.
Han Myong-hoe!
Your treasonous conspiracy and
usurpation of His Majesty's throne
shall not escape the wrath of heaven.
Your Majesty.
Please eat.
Take the table away.
Your Majesty.
You must eat.
I said take it away.
You must eat, Your Majesty.
I said take it away!
Your Majesty,
the Royal Secretary, Han Myong-hoe,
requests an audience.
Your Majesty,
your servant Han Myong-hoe seeks an audience.
Come in.
I hear this is your second day of refusing food.
Why do you reject your meals?
Is it my turn now?
What do you mean, Your Majesty?
I mean,
is it my turn to scream like they did?
Those men were great traitors
who plotted rebellion behind your back.
They deserved to scream.
Your Majesty, you are guilty of nothing.
Why should you scream?
You knew nothing of their treasonous scheme,
and even if you had,
you would never have allowed it.
Isn't that so?
Or
was it otherwise?
What
should I do?
Now!
Shoot!
Will you shut up? Be quiet!
Catch it!
Now you won't even get a scrap of meat.
Which way did it go?
Why do you always start fighting
the moment you meet?
Spread out.
Damn it.
I told you to breathe quietly,
but you just ignore me.
No respect for your village chief at all.
Chief!
Where are you?
What's that fool going on about now?
No way.
Help!
What are you doing lying there?
Want to take a nap?
Honestly,
everyone's running around
trying to catch a roe deer,
and look at him, fast asleep.
Oh dear, oh dear.
Yeah,
he's been a heavy sleeper
since he was little. Let's go.
A tiger! There's a tiger!
Father, go on and rest.
Sleeping in the middle
of a deep mountain. Oh dear.
Help!
You brat!
I...
Sir!
What's this place?
Is that real?
Is that white rice?
Looks like I really am dead.
I've made it to paradise.
This one
is real!
He's awake! He's awake!
You collapsed in a valley.
Lucky to be alive.
Yes, yes.
But you're a stranger.
Where are you from?
I'm from Gwangcheon Valley.
Gwangcheon Valley?
What village is this?
This is Norugol Valley.
Ah, Norugol Valley.
How did you end up here?
I wanted to catch some roe deer, so...
Catch roe deer?
Yes.
Why would you catch roe deer?
To eat, of course.
You eat roe deer?
Yes.
Roe deer meat is so gamey. You eat that?
People only ate that in the old days.
We have no meat. We're starving.
Hey, is there some big celebration in the village?
Such a big feast.
Today is my son's birthday.
You throw such a big feast
just for a child's birthday?
Just some simple food.
Who is this kid?
Such a big celebration for his birthday.
It's a happy day. Have a drink with us.
Eat some meat too.
Oh my.
Oh my, can I really eat this?
This isn't roe deer meat.
Good.
Oh my, grabbing it with bare hands.
I'm really starving.
In our village,
we don't even have a bite to eat.
We're dying of hunger.
How can your village eat so well?
You look like an uneducated country bumpkin,
so I'll let you in on a secret.
One day, an old man with
a long beard came to our village.
He used to be a Minister of Justice.
Good day, my lord.
The Yangban Lord from Hanyang
was exiled to this deep mountain forest.
We had to give him a house to live in,
Bring me something to drink and eat.
tighten our belts to prepare his meals.
Catch that for me.
That chicken.
And on top of that, that damned Yangban
acted like a real high official,
treating villagers like servants.
But one day,
he started bringing in wealth.
How did the wealth come?
By donkeys.
Donkeys?
Yes.
Donkeys.
Donkeys loaded with full packsaddles
lined up to Norugol Valley.
Meat, rice, cloth, fine silk.
Those Yangban Lords in Hanyang
have sharp instincts.
They guessed that this exiled Minister of Justice
would soon return to his post.
But the minister grew bored
and began teaching the village children to read.
Before long,
the illiterate country kids
memorized the Thousand Character Classic
and mastered the teachings of Confucius,
Mencius, and the sages
Just as those Yangban Lords
expected, not long after,
the minister's exile ended
and he went back to Hanyang.
He took a few bright children to
study further in the capital,
and one of them even passed
the highest civil service exam.
In short,
Norugol Valley struck gold.
We made it!
-Gold? -Gold?
That's right.
That could
happen here in Gwangcheon Valley too!
How?
Not long ago, things changed in Hanyang.
The old king was deposed,
and a new king was put on the throne, right?
That means there will be plenty of
Yangban Lords sent into exile.
I hear one of them
is being sent right here to Yeongwol.
Don't spread this around yet.
Who is it?
Anyway, he must be
an extremely high-ranking official.
A magnificent man
with a thick, long beard.
What good does that do?
He'll just go to Norugol Valley.
No.
We must bring him to
our Gwangcheon Valley by any means necessary.
If we serve that Yangban Lord well,
then other Yangban Lords will
come flocking to us like
strings of yellow croaker fish.
Yellow croaker must taste good.
No!
Do you think those exiled Yangbans
will ever repent and see the light?
Oh please! They spend their days
drinking and harassing women.
The slightest thing goes wrong,
they run to the county office
and get the villagers beaten.
Exactly.
With those exiled Yangbans,
we have to give up our houses,
cook for them, serve them,
and watch them every day to
keep them from running away.
If anything goes wrong with him,
our whole village will go up in flames,
just like this tree.
Hey, keep your voice down.
Look at you, so poor.
Those slouching little brats,
what do you feed them?
When they're hungry with nothing to eat,
you just smack them a few times,
give them water,
and send them to sleep.
But in Norugol Valley?
Just because a little kid had a birthday,
they had meat soup and white rice.
The whole village ate together
till their bellies were round.
Chicken, pork, everything you could want.
And it was just a child's birthday!
That white rice,
it was steaming hot, damn it!
The grains were separate,
white and fragrant.
I truly thought I'd reached paradise.
Seriously, when was
the last time we had white rice?
-Remember? -Probably
on my wedding day.
When that Yangban comes here,
it might be a bit hard at first,
since he's new here.
But after that, donkeys loaded with meat
and rice will come every single day.
We'll have meat soup and white rice every day.
We'll eat our fill every single day.
I want to try white rice too. Hot white rice.
Me too.
Oh dear, oh dear.
Mo-tong, I swear I'll get you white rice.
Hey Gwangcheon!
What's the Chief of
Gwangcheon Valley doing here?
I heard something urgent happened
over on the other side of the mountain...
no, over in Ansan.
But why are you here?
I came to the county office
to welcome another Yangban Lord.
Ah, a Yangban Lord. I see.
-Is that guy with you? -What?
You bastard!
Stop that thief!
-Governor! Oh dear! -Governor! Governor!
-Please hear me first.
-Me first please, Governor!
Quiet!
I'll speak quietly. Just listen.
I'm one step ahead of him.
Please let me speak first.
All right, all right. You go first.
-But quietly. -Yes.
Have you ever heard of Cheongnyeongpo,
deep in Gwangcheon Valley?
What's Gwangcheon Valley?
And what's Cheongnyeongpo?
You see, even you don't know it.
That's how remote it is.
Within Yeongwol's territory,
hidden deep in a mountain valley
is Gwangcheon Valley,
and the most secluded spot in
Gwangcheon Valley is Cheongnyeongpo.
So?
So what I'm saying is
Cheongnyeongpo is the perfect place for exile.
-Don't talk nonsense! -You!
The exile site in Yeongwol has
always been Norugol Valley.
Everyone sent there has been very satisfied.
Some even said they didn't want to leave.
Changing the exile site all of a sudden
is absolutely unacceptable, Governor!
I beg you to make a wise decision.
Then
the exile site
-shall be Norugol Valley. -Governor!
Hey you!
Governor! Governor!
Please listen to me!
I've heard enough.
Get lost! Didn't you hear me?
Throw this bastard out immediately!
-Please give Cheongnyeongpo one more chance!
-What's all this commotion?
A madman is causing trouble here.
I'm throwing him out.
That's not true. I'm not mad, My Lord!
My Lord!
I am Eom Heung-do, former head of Yeongwol's household registry and now Chief of Gwangcheon Valley.
What are you standing there for?
Throw him out right now!
Stop.
-Eom Heung do?
-Yes, yes!
Tell me. Why do you want your village
to become an exile site?
It is a place so remote
that badgers lose their way
and raccoon dogs faint.
An island within a land, Cheongnyeongpo.
In summer, it is stifling hot and humid,
swarming with dark mountain mosquitoes.
In winter, the cold wind howls off the river
and the chill from the cliffs bites down.
It is a place where living itself feels like dying.
I believe there is no better place for
a man to repent his crimes.
Having lived there long, from the moment
I open my eyes in the morning
until I fall asleep at night...
Set the exile site there.
Thank you, My Lord! Thank you, My Lord!
No matter who comes, can you handle it?
Yes, of course. I can handle
whoever comes, My Lord!
I will come to you again carrying a blade
in one hand and a reward in the other.
Which one I give you
depends entirely on you.
Yes, I will remember that.
I will do everything
in my power to make it perfect.
Prince Nosan, the criminal. By royal decree:
The treasonous conspiracy of Song Hyeon-su,
father-in-law of the Retired King, has come to light.
The traitors Seong Sam-mun and
Bak Paeng-nyeon are executed by slow slicing.
Grand Prince Geumseong, involved in
this treason, has been sentenced to exile
Yet acts of rebellion,
great and small, have not ceased.
Now Song Hyeon-su's treason
is fully revealed and undeniable.
Accordingly, the Retired King is
hereby demoted to Prince Nosan
and exiled, so as to quiet public sentiment
and secure the stability of the kingdom.
Are you just going to sit there?
Hurry up! People can't work.
Put the roof tiles on.
So noisy.
Oh, honestly.
A great man is coming from Hanyang.
Not a single thing can go wrong.
Bring me a bowl of water.
-What? This? -Yeah.
Oh, come on.
You heard her. Go! Hurry!
-Hurry and carry it over. -Here.
No time to drink water.
The Lord arrives any moment.
Time is precious. No time to dawdle.
No time for water!
But, Grandpa.
What was this place before?
Ah, a shaman used to live here.
-A shaman? -Creepy, right?
-So never come in here again. Got it?
-Okay.
Oh, you're still fooling around!
Watch it!
Didn't I say watch it?
Do you know how much that one tile costs?
-And... -Come down!
-never grow up to be that kind of man.
-Get down!
I won't.
Get down!
The raft is cleaned and ready.
Now we only await the Lord's arrival.
Welcome, My Lord!
Please, this way, this way.
Yes, this way.
Oh dear. And donkeys, too.
Sharp as always, My Lord. This way.
Donkey, you can't come in.
Unload the baggage there.
This way, My Lord!
So scary.
You boy! You won't read, just fooling
around with that damn bow all day.
Tae-san, you knew
the Thousand Character Classic at six,
math at eight, and the Tonggam at ten.
Why waste all that talent on this?
Don't go on like this.
It's not too late.
Prepare for the civil service exam.
Father, do you even know
what the exam really is?
You think I don't want to take it?
In this deep mountain,
do we have the Four Books and the Three
Classics? Or a teacher who can teach me?
There is a teacher. That Yangban Lord
is coming from Hanyang.
A high official. Learn from him,
and you can take the exam.
If you please him,
maybe you can even go to Hanyang.
A Yangban would help us?
Have you ever seen such a Yangban?
So you wanna?
Looks decent enough.
Good work, everyone.
But who's coming?
The Chief put in so much effort.
-Should be a good Yangban Lord. -You bet.
I have a bad feeling.
Probably another wasted effort.
Don't start with that kind of talk.
Listen up, everyone.
This is about life and death
for the village, right?
Don't do anything foolish.
Even if the Yangban acts up,
smile and bow.
I see a horse. Someone's coming. Over there.
Quick, quick. Looks like they're here.
The gold mine is here! Gold!
Smile, everyone, smile!
You expect me to cross
this river on this flimsy raft?
Yes, My Lord.
The sedan chair and the ladies will board.
The rest of you will swim across.
What are you staring at?
You row the raft.
Yes, My Lord.
Bring the sedan chair.
-Where is the beard? -Ready!
Ready!
-Pull! -Let's go.
The raft is drifting down.
Pull harder!
-Why isn't it moving?
-What's wrong?
-What is it? -It's stuck again.
It's stuck. Pull harder! Harder!
-What are you standing there for?
-Damn it. Stuck on something.
Pull together!
Pull!
My Lord!
Your Majesty!
-Jump! What are you waiting for?
-Are you all right?
-My Lord! -My Lord!
Don't move. Don't move.
Go! Hurry up! What are you doing?
Come on, Tae-san. Try putting it here.
Here?
But the big-bearded Lord didn't come.
Instead, a filthy little kid showed up.
What's going on?
Right. What crime did such a young child
commit to be exiled like this?
Hey, Chief. What's that little Yangban's name?
His name is Nosan. Nosan.
What? Nosan?
He probably won't last a month.
A month?
You mean Nosan will kill himself?
Such a young boy,
with no father, no subjects,
no palace, no throne.
How could he endure?
Well said.
But don't forget,
Grand Prince Geumseong, Nosan's uncle
and the king's younger brother,
is right there beside him.
Sunheung
Exile Site of Grand Prince Geumseong
Your Majesty,
we swear to follow you to the death.
-To the death! -To the death!
I am most grateful.
You're up? The meal is ready.
Eom Heung-do, your Bosu Juin, requests an audience.
Bosu Juin: local officer in charge of
monitoring and caring for exiles
It was such a mess just now.
Damn raft got stuck on a rock.
If I hadn't pushed with a pole,
you'd have been swept downstream.
Barely avoided disaster.
To recover your strength, start with breakfast.
The villagers prepared it with all their hearts.
-Before it gets cold... -Leave us.
What?
I said leave.
Did he just say leave?
His Lordship is in a bad mood.
You withdraw for now.
I'm the Bosu Juin here.
It is my duty to pay my respects in the morning and evening and to report to the government office.
-I haven't even seen him, and he tells me to leave.
-Didn't he say leave?
You dog! Didn't you hear me tell you to leave?
Take the table and get lost!
Quick, go!
He's got a temper.
Didn't you hear me say leave? Get lost!
He called me a dog.
Just because he's a Yangban,
a snot-nosed brat with no manners.
How dare he speak to an elder like that?
Forget it. Whatever he says, just smile.
Smile, say yes, and bow.
Really.
Such delicious food. Why won't he eat?
Oh my!
At this rate, his cheeks are going to burst.
It's a misunderstanding! Misunderstanding!
I didn't eat because I wanted to.
I found a bug this big in there.
Misunderstanding!
Governor!
-Governor! -What?
Why did the soldiers leave?
You don't know?
No.
Guarding the exile site isn't the soldiers' job.
It's the Bosu Juin's job.
So don't forget to report on the first
and fifteenth of every month.
Everything, big or small, must be reported.
Yes, I understand.
At least take this away.
Honestly.
Hey, did you hear?
They say the Retired King
was exiled to Yeongwol.
I heard something like that.
Some place called
Cheongnyeongpo or something.
Cheongnyeongpo?
How is it?
What?
Does the food suit his taste?
Didn't touch it.
-What? -Didn't touch it at all?
Nope.
We saved that food for him.
Seriously?
Maybe he's unwell.
Or maybe he has no appetite.
No appetite?
With food this precious?
What's going on?
And it's not like he didn't touch it,
looks like someone already ate half.
Well, he didn't eat. There's that maid.
She ate it, and I caught her red-handed.
But she swore she didn't.
Her cheeks were so stuffed
they looked like they'd burst.
Honestly.
So can we give this to Mo-tong?
Yeah.
I never throw away leftovers.
Mo-tong!
He ate it.
The bite marks match his teeth perfectly.
Forget it.
Gwangcheon.
What brings you all the way here?
Let's talk nicely.
I understand how you feel,
but that doesn't change the facts.
I didn't come here to fight.
This hen was raised on
nothing but good grain.
Here, take it.
Deodeok. Give him the deodeok too.
-Here, fresh deodeok. Deodeok.
-What's this for?
Why are you giving me this?
You took the heat for me.
What's a hen compared to that?
No, took what for you?
This is our Norugol Valley specialty,
lion's mane mushroom.
No, no. Why are you giving me all this?
Thank you so much.
Those lunatics said thank you
and left me all this stuff.
Father.
Yeah?
Do you know who the exiled Yangban is?
Yes. Nosan.
Right. I'm asking if you know
who that Nosan really is.
Yes. Nosan is Nosan.
Who else could he be?
He's Prince Nosan Yi Hong-wi. Yi Hong-wi.
Until recently, he was the king of this country.
Did you eat something strange?
What king?
King.
King?
No matter who comes,
you can handle it?
Your Majesty!
-King? -King?
You mean that boy was once the king?
So I've heard.
Wait. If he's a king, a king?
Can a king be exiled?
Can a Retired king be exiled?
Look. Nosan became king through
succession from his father.
But after his father died,
Grand Prince Suyang rebeled and became king.
I heard that all the officials
who followed Nosan were executed.
He was demoted to Prince Nosan and exiled here.
But even so, they don't usually
exile a man who was once king.
And there are many who pity him.
Perhaps poison will be sent soon.
-Poison? -Poison?
That poison, you drink it and die, right?
Then what happens to us?
If something happens to Nosan, we...
If something happens to the exiled,
the exile territory will also face trouble.
I heard that everyone who followed Nosan
was dismembered, tortured to death.
Their property confiscated. Children like Mo-tong
and Ae-dong were taken and sold.
Oh my god!
-What do we do? -What did I tell you?
We're as good as dead now.
It's all because of the Chief!
As good as dead?
What do you know? Stop yelling.
I heard it clearly from
Lord Han Myong-hoe himself.
Prince Nosan will soon return
to Hanyang and be restored.
Are you telling the truth?
You know me.
I come from a distinguished family.
Even with a sword at my throat, I never lie.
That must be it.
Just a rumor. A rumor.
Your Majesty.
Your servant Seong Sam-mun...
Why did you abandon us?
Do not grieve too much.
I will come to you soon.
I never wanted fame or fortune.
Just a bowl of white rice to live.
I wanted my son to learn,
to live like a decent man.
Of all the Yangbans, why does it have to be you?
I begged everyone to have you here.
I suffered so much for you.
Why you, of all people, you scourge?
Where have those scourges gone?
It's a misunderstanding.
I failed to recognize you before.
But why are you here so late at night?
It's dangerous there. That's a cliff.
What are you doing?
Come this way.
No.
Why are you doing this?
Let go.
Please.
Let go of my hand.
You must not.
If you die, our whole village dies.
Never mind.
What?
Yeah.
What did you just say?
The exile tried to kill himself.
Who?
Prince Nosan.
Last night I went up to Yuryuk Peak
to check the waterway.
I saw him about to jump off the cliff.
Jump off a cliff?
Yes.
Then what?
I ran over quickly and
barely managed to save him.
If not for me, it would have been a disaster.
Do not tell anyone
what happened yesterday. Understand?
Yes.
And you will closely monitor
every move of Prince Nosan.
Yes.
I will.
Hey.
What's that?
Dried yellow croaker.
White rice.
Where did you get such precious things?
From the coast. For the Lord.
Tae-san.
The Lord must be happy.
Go and deliver it.
Me?
The Chief said he had official business at the county office, so he asked you to go instead.
Who are you?
I am Tae-san, son of Eom Heung-do,
Chief of Gwangcheon Village
and Bosu Juin.
Why are you standing there?
Why aren't you leaving?
I have to watch you eat before I go.
I hear you haven't eaten.
I suppose a nobleman used to delicacies
looks down on the food we eat just to survive.
Insolent!
Stop talking.
If I bring back the untouched table,
those who have nothing to eat
should be the angry ones.
But instead, they worry whether you're unwell,
or if the food doesn't suit you.
Then you eat it.
Any orders?
Deliver a message.
What?
I ate well.
Yes.
Harder.
One more time.
I'm back.
How did it go? Did he eat?
Ate it all.
All of it?
Yeah.
He finished it all?
Yes.
Strange.
The Lord told me to tell everyone
that it was delicious.
How grateful.
He's got some warmth to him.
Yes, human warmth.
Yeah.
I'll go next time. I'll go.
What is this?
A letter from Grand Prince Geumseong to you.
Why don't you open it?
My Lord.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid of the letter's contents and the fact
that it was delivered to me.
That guy...
What brings you here?
Did you see Prince Nosan?
No.
Wasn't he in that house?
He wasn't
there when I got back from the county office.
I searched everywhere.
No sign of him.
Then...
Let go.
Let go of my hand!
Damn it! I tried so hard to save him!
A letter from Grand Prince Geumseong to you.
Do you want to die that badly?
What did you say?
The whole village is worried about you,
running around like crazy looking for you.
And you only think about yourself, trying to die.
Why are you so clueless?
What?
How dare you...
Yes, yes. It's me.
Are you out of your mind?
Crazy. Crazy.
How could I not be?
To feed this village,
to let my son study,
I went through hell to
bring you here and serve you.
And all you do is think about
jumping off a cliff and dying.
How could I not be crazy?
Aren't I right?
You dog!
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Careful! It's dangerous.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
What happened?
No idea.
The king.
The king is over there.
Not that king. That king over there.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Don't move.
-What do we do? -Do something!
Sorry.
It takes only one person at a time.
Once it eats, it won't touch anyone else.
-Where are you going? -Hey!
I've lived long enough.
Everyone stay healthy
and live well.
Here I go.
Where are you going?
Tae-san! Tae-san!
You beast!
I'm the one you're up against.
My Lord!
-My Lord! -My Lord!
The tiger was killed by Nosan?
That's right.
It was a close call.
My hands are still shaking.
A close call.
So this time, you saved Nosan again?
No.
This time, Prince Nosan
saved me and the village.
Nonsense. Lying.
I'm not lying.
It's all true. Not a single word is a lie.
Prince Nosan was like this.
Stretching?
No. Drawing a bow like this.
Prince Nosan?
No!
Why would he roar! Damn it!
Prince Nosan said, I'm the one
you're up against.
The tiger understood. I think it understood.
As soon as he said it,
the tiger ran at him and roared.
Then Prince Nosan shot his arrow.
Hit.
Hit, right between the eyes.
The tiger fell off the cliff.
Nosan...
Incredible.
After yesterday,
now I can barely lift a spoon.
I wonder how he's doing.
So do I.
He hasn't had a proper meal
since he got here.
And then he collapsed yesterday.
Yes, yes.
Such a thin body yet such great courage.
To step forward and risk his life against a tiger,
only someone who truly cares for
the people could do that.
After all, he was once the king.
Excuse me!
Has the Lord woken up?
Is he all right?
Don't trouble yourself.
Leave the table and go.
At least let me see if he's alright.
Didn't I say leave the table and go?
Wait. Why are you so cold to me?
Yesterday...
What?
Don't you remember
what you did yesterday?
What?
A man may lack learning
but he should still know manners and limits.
How dare you insult my lord
and grab his collar?
How could you?
Me? Grab his collar?
I did this.
And how do you know
if I have learning or not?
Do I even need to ask?
Even so, even if I have
no learning,
you don't say it to my face, do you?
I don't want to talk to you. Go now.
My Lord, are you all right?
I'm hungry.
Are you gonna wait until I finish eating?
No. I'll take my leave.
But, My Lord, if it weren't for you,
my son and the villagers
would have met a terrible fate.
How can I repay this kindness?
I worried about you all night.
Let me at least see you eat a little before I go.
If you permit, I'll wait outside.
Your tone is different from yesterday.
You're the first person to rage at me like that.
My Lord.
And you even grabbed my collar.
When did I grab...
Damn!
What?
What did you just say?
Did I say something?
You just said damn.
When did I say damn?
I was saying the Dawn, the starting point of
my new acquaintance with Your Lordship.
How could I have said that curse word?
That giant tiger truly
was the very Dawn of it all.
But what do you mean by
becoming the exile site?
What?
Yesterday on the mountain, didn't you say it?
I absolutely cannot tell you.
But the one who came was me.
You were hoping for a Minister of Justice.
Instead, I came, no connections to send donkey caravans of gifts, no way to advance anyone's career.
Is that so funny?
I imagined how you must have felt
when you learned who I really am.
I honestly didn't expect it
to be so complicated.
But here I am.
Far from filling the villagers' bellies,
I've only been consuming what you provide.
You're too kind.
As long as you eat happily, that is enough.
He's here! He's here!
How is Prince Nosan?
What's wrong? Why are you sighing?
One bowl of rice.
He ate it all in one go.
Look at you, so startled.
It must have suited his taste.
What did I tell you?
That's the spirit of a king.
Look at you being scared.
But he asked about you.
He asked about me?
Who made this soup?
I got up before dawn and caught
freshwater snails from Dongjiang River.
You cooked it yourself?
No, I caught them myself.
I asked who made the soup.
Her cooking is even better than
the royal kitchen's head court lady.
It's Mo-tong Mom. She's a good cook.
Though sometimes there's hair...
Is she called Mo-tong Mom
because she's Mo-tong's mother?
Yes. Mo-tong is young,
but very clever and capable.
Oh, and this porridge
is made from river fish
the kid caught in a fish trap.
And these pancakes,
they have mountain pepper,
picked by the oldest elder
in the village from the Yuryuk Peak cliff.
And this meat, Long caught a rabbit.
The wild ginseng root sprinkled on top
was treasured by Mo-tong's father.
The raspberries are from a widow
named Cheongsan of Icheon family.
She picked them from
a place full of snakes.
I see.
But all of this was done
under my strict and careful direction.
I must make that clear
The snails were caught by me personally.
All right. I see.
I noticed you only asked about the person who made it, not the ingredients.
I caught this before dawn myself.
Alright, I'll remember that.
Oh my, the King actually mentioned my name.
Your Highness is so young, yet you already understand women's hearts.
What “Your Highness”? Don't call me that anymore.
Just call me Nosan, or Prince Nosan.
There are no outsiders here anyway.
Does it really matter whether you call him Your Highness or Prince?
Right?
You could tell from the way he faced that tiger.
A king indeed lives up to his title.
If someone hears you, it'll be trouble. Don't keep calling him King.
Chief, someone's coming over there.
Do you know where Cheongnyeongpo is?
This way…
Who are you people?
We came from Haeju in Hwanghae Province to pay respects to His Highness…
We came to see Prince Nosan.
Hwanghae Province…
But why
have you come to see him?
Your Highness…
How could such a bolt from the blue happen?
We, your unworthy subjects who failed to serve you,
please forgive us.
You mustn't call him “Your Highness.”
If the authorities hear it, it'll be trouble.
Your Highness…
You mustn't call him that.
Stop them, don't let them go down.
You mustn't call him “Your Highness.”
Your Highness…
I said don't call him that.
You can cry, but you mustn't call him “Your Highness.”
You can cry.
Please accept this.
Stop, stop!
Raise your head.
Was the letter delivered?
As you ordered, I personally handed it to the court lady, Your Highness.
Go to Yeongwol again.
Hang a white garment on the tree of Mt. Cheomgak, directly across from His Highness's residence.
Then His Highness will tie a reply to an arrow and shoot it back.
Yes, Grand Prince.
They just keep drifting in endlessly.
Be careful.
Village chief.
How did you come up with such a brilliant idea?
Truly admirable.
Alright, we can haul in the net now.
Let me see what treasures we've got.
What's this?
Ginseng, ginseng!
And dried yellow croaker.
Bigger than my palm.
Look, dried meat!
What's this?
Didn't I tell you?
Even without a caravan, we won't go hungry anymore.
Didn't I say so?
You did.
Not just anyone can be a village chief.
I've always believed in our village chief.
How shameless.
That startled me.
It's so late. What brings you here?
Sir.
The prince has arrived.
The prince is here! The prince is here! Sir!
Why so flustered?
As if you've seen a ghost.
Who is that man?
Mo-tong, you can't speak like that.
My name is Yi Hong-wi.
So you're the one who catches fish with fish traps.
Alright.
Mo-tong…
She's Granny Icheon.
Granny Icheon.
Raspberries.
Raspberries, raspberries. The ones I picked a whole bowl of.
So you're the Granny Icheon who picks raspberries.
Yes, sir.
She's Mo-tong's mother.
So you're the one who cooks the food, Mo-tong's mother.
Yes.
The ginseng you sent tastes excellent, Mo-tong's father.
I'm Mo-tong's father.
Then the one who catches rabbits is…
Sir, that's me, Long.
I hear you run very fast.
When this kid runs, no one in Yeongwol can catch him.
The mountain peppers you sent have a superb spicy flavor.
Though drying them is a bit troublesome.
By the way, what are these behind?
These are all food sent to you by the villagers.
Before giving them to you,
we were just checking if any had gone bad.
We didn't take any, please rest assured.
No.
Since these have been delivered to Gwangcheon Valley,
they should belong to you.
Such precious food for you, sir...
We must be crazy, how could we…
What a generous heart.
I want to learn to read and write.
Please be my teacher.
I heard you usually have no interest in studying.
Why the change of heart?
For a rustic commoner like me,
I want to study but have no books to seek.
I want to learn but have no teacher to follow.
Even if I did learn,
I would still feel there's no hope of passing the exams.
But if I were taught by someone like you,
I believe I could break through that slim chance.
So I wish to enter the court and bring change,
to create a world where even those with no connections,
ignorant country folk, even commoners and servants,
can have a fair chance.
A world of fair opportunity…
Alright.
Then let's give it a try.
Virtue is not left to stand alone; it always attracts companions.
A person of virtue is never alone,
they will surely have like-minded friends.
Over there, over there!
-Put it here. -Put it here!
Oh my.
Come.
Such boundless grace.
They say the fish head is the tastiest part. Please enjoy it.
Keep the good things.
Even if I'm unlearned, I can't do that.
Such precious food. Let's share it together.
Write these characters with me.
“Yu” as in house, “Zhou” as in all time past and present.
“Hong” as in flood, “Huang” as in desolation.
You wouldn't believe how much came.
Everyone was stunned.
They brought a whole pile of things.
I just went over and tapped it.
This bowstring is made from silk spun by silkworms that eat mulberry leaves.
Its toughness is unmatched by other bowstrings.
The one who made the lacquered bow is a servant.
My grandfather and father both took pride in learning from him.
Learning knows no rank. Status doesn't matter.
What?
Move aside.
Where for me to go?
On the night before the wedding, you must not share a room…
A wild boar charged at me.
Mo-tong, which one do you think is better?
This one?
Mo-tong can write too?
Did I write it correctly?
That's right, that's right. Our Mo-tong did well.
Dad, I hung it up.
Well done.
It looks great.
Over here. This spot works.
Is this okay?
Our Mo-tong is really amazing.
I heard
Nosan fought a tiger.
Someone as timid as a mouse?
That must be some ridiculous story made up by those who love to exaggerate.
Who would believe it?
Their negligence is what allowed us to seize power.
If left to grow, it will become a great tree in no time.
You
keep a close watch on Grand Prince.
I will go to Yeongwol.
His Highness will surely be comforted by your loyalty.
Your Highness…
The time to set history right has finally come.
I, Geumseong,
together with Prefect Lee Bu-geun,
Governor Ryu Gi-san of Anju,
and Vice Director Jo Yu-rye and others,
are planning an uprising.
The local magistrates are also of one mind.
However,
without Your Highness's approval,
we dare not act rashly.
We earnestly request Your Highness to grant us a reply of consent.
You say the letter delivered to Nosan...
Its sender is Grand Prince Geumseong?
Speak.
What is written in the letter?
You rose to high office by
fabricating history with nothing but false merit.
Would someone like you care about the truth?
As the family of a traitor,
the fate is either exile
or becoming slaves.
But I will do it myself.
I will tear your family to pieces
and scatter them across the provinces.
Han Myong-heo, you wretch...
Never in all eternity
has there been such a criminal who defiles the state.
Anyone who communicates with Nosan
must be executed.
He's gone missing.
Yes.
He was sent to Yeongwol on the Grand Prince's orders several days ago.
Not only has he not returned, there's not even any news.
You go to Yeongwol.
Go and check the mark.
Yes, Your Highness.
From today onward, tighten security around the exile's residence.
This is an order from the court.
Four men in front will guard the gate in shifts day and night.
Four men in the back will patrol the residence.
From now on, we will strictly guard the exile's residence.
Yes.
Where are you going?
Prince Nosan has nightmares every night.
I heard gastrodia helps,
so I'm going to dig some up.
You care more about him than your own son.
If there's any left, give me some too.
What do you need it for?
Do you have nightmares too?
Of course I do.
Terrifying nightmares.
I dream about my father.
You brat.
You dreamed of your father.
Why call it a nightmare?
That's a good omen, you fool.
What is this?
This...
It's essays the village children wrote using proverbs.
Prince Nosan said he wanted to see them,
so I brought them from the children.
Take them to him.
After seeing them, he'll surely be very pleased.
You're really something.
Take care, Father.
Alright.
What are you hunting this time,
drawing the bow so tight?
I'm aiming at my own weak and foolish self,
who failed to protect my people.
You call yourself weak, sir?
If you were weak, how could you kill a tiger,
such a huge one at that?
And if you were foolish, how could you teach the illiterate to write,
and do it so well?
So, sir, you are neither weak nor foolish.
Yes…
Now that you say it, that's true.
Of course it is.
Just a moment. I came to see the village chief. Just a moment.
-Village chief. -Long!
-Tae-san has been taken to the authorities. -What?
Wait, wait, village chief!
Stop!
I've come to see the Governor.
Please… let me go in.
-Where do you think this is? -Let me in!
I came to see the Governor.
Eleven strokes.
Twelve strokes.
-Thirteen. -Tae-san. Tae-san.
No, no!
-What's going on? -Father!
What on earth is happening?
I heard someone was entering and leaving the exile's residence without permission,
so I had him arrested.
He is my son.
He did not go in and out without permission.
I sent him.
I said that except for the appointed guardian, no one may enter or leave the place of exile.
One hundred strokes of the rod.
Since I sent him,
I will take the punishment.
Please release my son.
What are you all standing for?
Take this ignorant fool away.
Yes.
Please let my son go.
Sir!
Every time I come,
it's always this man causing trouble.
Sir.
It was my ignorance that caused this mistake.
Please forgive me.
I heard strange rumors, so I came to check.
And indeed, your behavior is peculiar.
Yes, that's right, it's all my fault.
Punish me instead.
Please release my son.
Violating the strict laws of the state is punishable by death. No more words.
Yes, that's true.
What you say is reasonable.
But
one hundred strokes...
Even if he doesn't die, he'll be crippled!
Continue the beating.
Sir!
What are you waiting for?
Continue.
-Yes. -Sir.
Thirteen strokes.
Stop!
Release him at once.
He entered and left the exile grounds without permission.
Perhaps he was stealing,
or even plotting harm against Prince Nosan.
I called him here.
Life in exile is lonely. I wanted someone to talk to.
I called him, so
release him now.
What should we do, Inspector?
Continue the beating.
Sir.
Please, sir…
Beat him to death.
Sir!
Han Myong-heo, how dare you insult the royal family!
Nosan.
He still thinks he's king.
Han Myong-heo, you wretch!
Beat him!
Beat him to death!
I said stop!
Prince Nosan,
if you do not return to the place of exile immediately,
he will be beaten two hundred, three hundred times.
That man will be beaten to death today.
Sir,
if you act like this,
we will suffer even more.
Please go back.
We can't let Tae-san be beaten to death.
Please… go back.
What are you waiting for?
Escort Prince Nosan back to the place of exile.
I'm a lowly wretch.
Forgetting my place and doing what I shouldn't.
I forgot whom I should follow and whose orders I should obey.
I forgot who the king of this country is now.
We cannot delay even a moment.
Nosan's eyes have changed.
Those weak, sickly eyes.
Here,
they've turned into blazing eyes.
The criminal, Prince Nosan.
That man still thinks he's king.
Beat him.
Beat him to death.
Your Highness.
We earnestly beg you to grant us your consent in a reply.
Grand Prince Geumseong is raising troops
to depose the current ruler
and restore Nosan to the throne. This is now clear.
Contact more local magistrates and officials willing to join.
Keep it as secret as possible.
After today, Nosan's resolve will only grow stronger.
He will surely join the rebellion.
Only if he dies
will your son live.
And
the village will survive.
You must obtain evidence of the rebellion.
All forces for the march on Hanyang are ready.
We can delay no longer.
Even without His Highness's consent, we must rise.
What is the situation?
Uncle.
I am no longer a weak exile,
but a witness to history,
who will stand shoulder to shoulder with you.
If a successful rebellion becomes the master of history,
then Joseon from this day forward will be a blood-soaked struggle for the throne, led by blades and spears,
lasting for decades, even centuries.
Even if the uprising fails,
we will fight to the death,
and the record of our attempt to correct history
will be passed down to future generations.
Uncle, please remain in Sunheung.
I will go there instead.
To the great tree at the shrine on Mt. Madae that you mentioned.
To correct history once more,
for the ancestral altars of Joseon and the peace of its people.
Nosan is secretly corresponding with Grand Prince Geumseong.
Something unusual is happening in Sunheung.
A storm of bloodshed is coming.
Prepare at once and set out.
Yes, sir.
Everything is ready now.
Go to Mt. Madae immediately
and escort His Highness here.
I, Jo Yu-rye, Vice Director of the State Council,
will faithfully carry out this order.
Move out.
-Yes, sir. -Yes, sir.
The time to set things right and end the false history is today.
Today,
we will cut off this treacherous age
and establish a new Joseon that cares for all its people.
I will remain here
and join His Highness upon his arrival.
All forces, led by the Geumhwa unit,
are ready to present proof.
Charge!
Absolutely not.
What do you mean by that?
Lord Han Myong-heo told me
that Grand Prince Geumseong is inciting you to rebellion,
so I was ordered to report your every move.
If I detect any suspicious signs,
I must report to the authorities.
So
have you noticed anything suspicious?
Yes.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Someone took away a letter written in your own hand.
Stop here.
And if I refuse?
If you insist on going ahead,
then I…
will report it to the authorities.
Do you know
what it feels like to live a life not your own?
By my father's decree, I was made Crown Prince
and ascended the throne,
yet I was driven out by my uncle's ambition
and reduced to this state.
But now,
I finally understand
why Heaven has kept me alive until this day and
why I must live on.
And the ones who awakened me to this truth
are you and Tae-san,
and the people of this village.
I will not stop.
As for you,
go to the authorities.
That way,
you and everyone in the village
can escape safely.
Sir.
Sir!
Are you really determined to go?
I don't want to lose
everyone I cherish because of myself ever again.
Please convey my regards
to everyone.
Does that
include me as well?
You said you don't want to lose those you cherish.
Am I one of them too?
Am I not, to you?
Of course you are.
How are our troops moving?
By now, our forces should have passed Danyang and reached Jecheon.
Another unit, scheduled to rendezvous, has already been waiting here.
All troops,
advance immediately!
Once the two forces join, our momentum and morale
will soar to the skies.
The combined army will advance along the route,
pass through Yeoju, and gather at Maebong Mountain,
awaiting orders from His Highness and the Grand Prince.
Once His Highness reaches the assembly point at Maebong Mountain,
we can reach Sungnyemun in Hanyang before dawn.
From Sungnyemun to the royal palace will take no more than half a quarter-hour.
The gate commander has already secretly allied with us,
and there are only two hundred enemy troops in the palace.
We have eighteen hundred soldiers.
Victory is only a matter of time.
By now, His Highness must have successfully made contact.
He must safely meet the Vice Director of the State Council.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I suddenly remembered when I first met you, sir,
at Cheongnyeongpo.
Is that so? What was I like back then?
What do you think you were like?
Truly elegant and strikingly handsome.
In terms of looks, I was clearly better.
Let's go.
We're almost there.
This is the City God Shrine.
Wait here for a moment.
There's no one around.
This should be the place.
Who's there?
Who is it?
Your Highness.
I am Jo Yu-rye, Vice Director of the State Council.
You've traveled a long way. Well done.
Everything is ready for the uprising.
Your Highness, please depart.
Let's go.
Why the rush?
Han Myong-heo.
Do you know why I exiled Geumseong and Nosan to such nearby places as Sujin and Yeongwol?
It was to wait for those with ill intent to collude and meet
and then
eliminate these vicious traitors all at once.
You all protect His Highness.
I'll hold them off here.
-Yes, sir. -Yes, sir.
They should have arrived by now. Why are they still not here?
We can't delay any longer.
The longer large-scale troop movements take,
the easier it is for the enemy to notice.
That's right.
We can't just sit here and wait, Your Highness.
Hold the line at all costs.
Pursue them with full force.
Head to Mt. Madae in Hanyang.
We'll personally escort His Highness there
and then advance on Hanyang.
Protect His Highness at all costs.
Sir!
The more you resist,
the more your followers will bleed and die in vain.
Han Myong-heo, do you truly wish to be remembered as a criminal in history?
I told you
I would come back to you with a sword in one hand and rewards in the other.
Yet you dared
to take up arms and betray your word.
You and your son, needless to say...
Your entire village will be wiped out.
Then you might as well kill me.
You traitor!
You read my secret letter,
pretended to guide us
so it was all a trap you had prepared.
You swore loyalty to Han Myong-heo.
What did he promise you?
Was it to make your son an official?
You shameless wretch!
Sir.
No need to say more.
At this point, it no longer matters.
Arrest the traitor.
-Yes, sir. -Yes, sir.
I…
Sir!
Sir…
The traitor Geumseong,
is to be given poison.
Your Highness.
it is I, Geumseong.
I am incompetent
and failed to protect you.
Please
take care of yourself.
Sir.
Why did you do this?
Why bear everything alone?
Come in.
This way, please.
Have you been well?
I often think of the jelly soup Mo-tong made.
I wonder if Mo-tong has finished memorizing the Thousand Character Classic.
I also worry about Tae-san, who was beaten.
Have his wounds healed?
Everyone is well.
And
more than anything, they miss the face of their guardian.
Are you referring to my handsome face?
Look again closely.
It truly is quite remarkable.
I have something important to entrust to you.
Yes.
Please give your orders.
The traitor Yi Hong-wi is to be given poison.
The rebel Yi Hong-wi,
despite receiving the boundless grace of His Majesty,
conspired with Grand Prince Geumseong in a treason punishable by heaven and man.
Therefore, poison is bestowed upon him.
This is a royal decree, come out and receive it.
No… that's not true.
Drag the criminal out.
-Yes. -Yes.
Insolence!
How dare you invade a royal residence!
Am I, an old man,
unable to deal with a single traitor? What nonsense is this!
Give me a moment.
I will drag that traitor out.
No…
Your Highness.
I am Eom Heung-do, your guardian.
Now,
it is time to cross the river.
When the moment comes,
use that bowstring.
You must
kill me with your own hands.
I do not wish to die at their hands,
nor by the poison they grant.
Even in death, I would not accept that.
I beg you,
with your own hands,
send me across the river.
Your Highness.
Alright.
I will send you across.
Let's go.
Alright.
Your Highness.
It is time to depart.
Please endure a little longer.
We're almost there.
We're almost there, Your Highness.
We've reached the riverbank.
It is time to depart.
Your Highness.
Anyone who collects or buries Nosan's body
will have their entire family exterminated.
From the time I first learned to walk,
you were always by my side.
To me, you were a dear friend, an elder sister, and like a mother.
Leaving behind these cherished years,
I will depart.
If we meet again in a distant next life,
I hope we can once again be close friends.
And when that time comes, I will gladly stay by your side.
Sir.
It's cold, isn't it?
Let's go. Let's get out of here.
Let's go somewhere warm.
Let's go.
A court attendant
who had long served Prince Nosan volunteered for the task.
He tied a long rope to the bowstring
and pulled it tight through the gap behind the seat.
That year, Yi Hong-wi was only seventeen.
— Records of the Yeollyeosil, Annals of King Danjong
When Prince Nosan was killed, no one dared tend to his body.
A local official, Eom Heung-do, went to mourn him,
personally prepared a coffin, and buried him.
The present-day royal tomb stands on that very site.
— Annals of King Hyeonjong, Year 10, January 5
Despite many trying to stop him, Eom Heung-do said:
“To uphold righteousness and suffer misfortune is something I willingly accept, not something I fear.”
— Biographical Records of the Joseon Dynasty
Two hundred forty-one years later,
Yi Hong-wi was restored as King Danjong,
and Eom Heung-do, recognized for his loyalty, was posthumously honored as Lord Chungui.
Today, their graves stand together in Yeongwol.
The King's Warden
Yoo Hae-jin
Park Ji-hoon
Yoo Ji-tae
Jeon Mi-do
Directed by Jang Hang-jun