[English subtitles are available]
[Mysterious Lotus Casebook]
[Episode 4]
I've heard people on the verge of death always see ghosts.
I'll help you remember.
Are you crazy?
It wasn't a ghost.
It was that fake miracle physician, Li Lianhua.
Li Lianhua is the Medicine Demon of the Jinyuan Alliance.
He was the one who killed Happy.
He... He must have killed
the Second Young Miss of Yu City too.
Stop killing people.
It's not like that.
Who is Li Lianhua?
I am Li Lianhua.
Take Li Lianhua in.
What are you doing?
We don't know what's going on yet.
Don't kill the innocent.
Take the rest back to the prison.
Yes.
You...
Hurry!
Young Master.
Don't you also suspect that fake miracle physician?
Didn't you also say he did it?
We can't be sure yet.
If he is innocent,
he would have been framed.
Is Madam inside?
Madam is interrogating a suspect in the hall.
Could it be Young Master Zongzheng?
[Zongzheng Mingzhu]
Do you remember me?
I am Fang Duobing.
My father is the Minister of Revenue, Fang Zeshi.
We met at your grandfather's birthday banquet.
Your grandfather also mentioned
your engagement with the Second Young Miss of Yu City.
We meet again so soon.
It’s really Young Master Fang.
You are...
Second Young Miss Yu was killed
at Xiaoyan Inn while we were there.
It's a long story.
Young Master Zongzheng,
could you please...
It's a misunderstanding.
Untie him.
Yes.
Thank you so much.
Shuang was killed
and her body was destroyed by a fire.
Sister Hongzhu was too sad,
so she reacted strongly.
Please forgive her.
My father is an old friend of the previous Castellan.
Shuang and I grew up together.
I'm here to prepare
our wedding next year.
I didn't expect Shuang...
Yu Qiushuang's body was indeed destroyed.
My condolences, Brother Zongzheng.
I have something urgent to attend to.
I have to go.
Madam Yu
is such an enthusiastic host.
Cut the crap.
I told you.
I have a bad temper
and no patience.
I'll let you have a good taste
of what Shuang went through.
Tell me.
Why did you pretend to be the Medicine Demon?
Madam Yu really believes me.
Do you know who the Medicine Demon is?
Who are you to question me?
Do it!
Are you okay?
What do you think?
I didn’t expect Li would rat you out.
I'm here to save you.
Who are you?
It was all a misunderstanding.
Sister Hongzhu.
This is the son of Minister Fang,
Fang Duobing.
So you are the Young Master of Tianji Hall.
Excuse me.
I'm impressed by
Yu City's hospitality.
Young Master Fang.
Everyone in Yu City is sad about this tragedy.
I didn’t mean to get you involved.
I'm really sorry.
You should be sorry towards
the innocent lives you took.
Madam Yu said your guards are your slaves,
and their lives are for you to take.
But the owner of Lotus Tower is not from Yu City.
He is also
the renowned and well-respected Physician Li.
Are you going to
kill him without considering the law too?
Young Hero Fang knows how to flatter me.
You’re famous.
It'd be a waste not to use it.
But it doesn't mean you're innocent.
Tianji Hall has never participated in disputes of the martial arts world,
but Young Hero Fang is quite nosy.
But
I'm just handling family matters.
I don't want to make an enemy of you.
Since it was a misunderstanding,
I'll ask someone to prepare a carriage
to send Young Master Fang and this physician
home.
Madam Yu,
please just send my maid back
to let my family know that I am well.
I don't plan to leave.
What do you mean?
In terms of personal affairs,
my servant was killed.
I must find the person who killed him.
In terms of official affairs,
as a detective of Baichuan Court,
[Baichuan Court]
I must investigate the murder
and catch the murderer.
So,
before we find out the truth,
please don’t hurt anyone else.
When did I allow you to investigate the case?
Young Master Fang,
don’t push your luck.
No matter how remote Yu City is,
you must follow the legal code of the Great Xi.
What do you think?
Brother Zongzheng.
Sister Hongzhu.
Detectives from Baichuan Court indeed have the right to intervene.
Madam Yu.
Since you don't believe your sister was killed by an evil spirit,
do you just want to kill and vent your anger
rather than find out the truth?
Killing the innocent will only cover up the truth.
The murderer who killed your sister
could escape.
Are you really okay with that?
I have no patience.
I will only give you one day
to find out the truth of my sister's death.
If you can’t find out the truth one day,
please leave Yu City immediately.
I will bury everyone here with Shuang.
It's not up to anyone to judge
Yu City's rules!
One day it is.
Young Hero Fang is really unpredictable.
You said I killed someone,
but now you're saving me.
I've only temporarily ruled you out as a suspect .
I was afraid you'd be wrongly executed by Yu Hongzhu.
Really?
You ruled me out so quickly?
As you said,
the body of Yu Qiuhuang was indeed destroyed by the fire.
If you really did it,
you didn't have to give me any leads.
But even if you were not the murderer at Mount Xiaomian,
you might still be the Medicine Demon.
Young Hero Fang is really smart.
Since I’m no longer a suspect,
I'll take my leave.
Wait.
If we don't solve this case,
those people in prison will die.
You have to stay to investigate the case with me.
I have to stay?
Young Hero Fang.
You agreed to solve the case,
not me.
Why should I stay?
Besides, I hate getting involved
in the martial arts world's affairs.
If you dare to run,
I will dare to incite Madam Yu
to hunt you down
and find everything there is on you, old fox.
Also,
look at this.
I didn’t expect your dog to be so loyal to you.
He followed you all the way to Yu City from Xiaomian Inn.
What a pity,
I found him first.
Let me tell you.
I'm really not the Medicine Demon.
Fox Spirit is just an ordinary dog.
It's too bad that its owner is heartless and wants to abandon it.
Do you think
I should stew or braise it?
It should taste good either way.
Why are you picking on a dog?
I'm not a detective.
Why are you clinging onto me?
Aren't you a miracle physician?
If you can save Yu Qiushuang,
the case will be solved.
I can't revive the dead.
Then be my coroner.
You are so cunning,
you will be useful at something.
You'll let me go once you find out the truth, right?
Second Young Miss's body was originally placed in the hall
while waiting for Madam to come back.
I don't know why a fire suddenly started and burned half of it.
Madam couldn't bear to look at it anymore,
so she put it in the Ice Room.
Please look at it carefully.
Thank you.
That's it?
You want to be a detective when you can't even stand this?
Just go home.
What's wrong with something as minor as this?
Is there a problem?
The smell is so strong.
Is it because the body was burned?
Burnt fat doesn't smell like this.
What's strange is
it's only been a day.
The body rotted so quickly.
The meridians on her neck are intact.
There's no pressure or damage.
She wasn't strangled by the ghost's hands.
Happy was strangled to death,
but Yu Qiushuang was different.
See?
There's a blood clot.
Her abdomen was injured.
Looks like this ghost struck hard.
The blood clot hasn't dissipated after so long.
It seems that
Yu Qiushuang has long been dead.
There is another cause of death that is hard to detect.
See?
The second spot
has a golden needle that went straight through the heart.
Golden needle?
A golden needle and a palm strike...
Aren't these two wounds contradictory?
You're smart.
Palm strikes are close combat.
Needles attack from a distance.
If she'd been struck, why attack her with a needle after she'd run away?
If she was killed from a distance,
there was no need to strike her again.
It's very contradictory.
Also, don't you think it's too aggressive?
Indeed.
I've heard Yu Qiushuang's martial arts skills were only average.
With her ability,
there was no need to kill her twice, and so aggressively.
The murderer killed Happy
to make Yu Qiushuang being killed by a ghost
look more believable.
If Yu Hongzhu hadn't come back in time,
the cause of Yu Qiushuang's death
would have been pushed to the ghost.
Happy died unjustly.
If there was a ghost,
it was someone pretending to be a ghost.
As long as we find the murderer,
we can seek justice for Happy.
It wasn't a ghost?
The only ones in Xiaomian Inn who had inner skills and could use secret weapons
were Yun Jiao and the escorts.
I think they colluded
to kill Shuang.
Madam Yu, it's too early to come to a conclusion.
We’ve checked all the rooms
in the inn.
Young Miss Yu's window couldn't be opened because
it got sealed shut by tree sap from years of ill maintenance.
There was no secret passage
that can lead into the room either.
And there were guards outside the room at all times.
So
whether it was Miss Yun Jiao
or the escorts,
they had no way
of transferring Young Miss Yu.
That makes no sense.
How could a person disappear
from her room
and die somewhere else?
Master Yu's analysis makes sense.
May I ask
why Second Young Miss Yu ran away from home?
When did she leave?
She disappeared a few days before the Ghost Festival.
I didn't see her in the morning.
Her maid, Qingling, said
she was depressed that day
and wanted to go out alone.
She didn't want anyone to follow her.
But she didn't come back at night.
Yes.
My sister's face was bitten by poisonous insects
and was left with a scar.
We thought we could cure the scar
before the wedding,
but we couldn't.
That's why she was depressed
and ran away.
It was my fault for not realizing how she was feeling.
We sent people to search for her all day,
but we got the news that she had been murdered.
Take a look at this.
Do you recognize this?
This golden needle
was found in Second Young Miss's heart.
This needle can kill people?
This is... the Soul Snatching Needle?
How did it get out?
Madam Yu, do you know where this needle came from?
The assassin, Jia Si,
was paid a lot of money to take my father's life.
He was killed by my father.
The Soul Snatching Needle fell into my father's hands
and was placed in the Armory.
It's been ten years.
No one has touched it.
Bring me the Armory's records.
Madam,
I've checked.
The Soul Snatching Needle,
including the device and twenty golden needles,
has been missing since six months ago.
Who took it?
It was...
Second Young Miss.
You may leave.
Yes.
Qiushuang has never entered the Armory.
Yun Jiao must have
asked Qiushuang to borrow it.
She loiters around Yu City all the time,
saying Qiushuang's like a sister to her.
Did she really think I didn't know
why she was sneaking around?
Yun Jiao must have killed Shuang.
Madam Yu,
why do you say that?
If Shuang doesn't die,
how can she get what she wants?
Young Hero Fang,
I think the case is closed.
Write the concluding report.
The Yun family won't be able to keep this girl alive.
I'll make her suffer
like Shuang did.
I'll burn her alive!
Let's go.
[Light clouds cover the moon]
I knew it.
It was you who killed Shuang'er.
If you don't confess,
I have thousands of ways to make you suffer.
Tell me the truth.
Stop!
Madam Yu!
Are you going to torture her?
Look at her acting crazy.
If I don't torture her, how can I make her talk?
Ever since Miss Yun Jiao got traumatized at Xiaomian Inn,
she has been dazed.
If you want to ask her a question,
I'm afraid she can't respond.
Physician Li can even revive the dead.
Surely madness is not an issue.
Physician Li,
do something.
Young Hero Fang,
you’re so funny.
Young Hero Fang said Master Li is a renowned miracle physician.
Good.
I also want to see how your medical skills are.
Whether she's really mad or not, she can be cured, right?
Of course.
If he can't cure her,
you can hang him up again
and roast him.
I won't plead for him.
Then I'll give it a try.
Don’t play tricks.
Didn’t Young Hero Fang ask me to show my real skills?
Be careful.
You care about her quite a bit.
Sister Hongzhu.
I...
Looks like Miss Yun is seriously ill.
You can't cure her?
That's not it.
Then why don't you hurry up?
I just need
to find some herbs in Yu City.
There is medicine in Yu City?
I think there must be.
We'll just need to find them.
Hurry up.
This Yu Hongzhu is really overbearing.
If she didn't kill those guards,
we would have witnesses.
Miss, come out.
Miss.
That bowl of porridge...
Miss Yun Jiao is not from Yu City,
but you've taken good care of her.
May I ask
why your Madam doesn't like Miss Yun Jiao?
Don't be afraid.
We're asking because
we want to find the murderer.
Don't you?
At first,
my Madam was nice to Miss Yun.
But once, Miss Yun secretly wrote a love poem
and got caught by Madam.
Madam tore the love poem apart on the spot.
Miss Yun's face was so red,
it was like she was going to bleed.
Since then,
Madam stopped liking Miss Yun.
What was in that poem?
I remember two sentences were,
"The pearl in my heart is hard to undo,
Flying flowers and willow make me miss you."
Pearl?
Miss Yun Jiao has a pearl on her heart?
He's Yu Qiushuang's fiance.
No wonder Madam is angry with her.
But didn't Second Young Miss notice?
No.
Second Young Miss and Miss Yun are close.
A few days ago,
Second Young Miss specially picked
a piece of warm jade for her
as a birthday gift.
Thank you.
[Mysterious Lotus Casebook]
Are you looking for herbs to cure Yun Jiao?
What do you think I’m doing?
You look so careless.
You must be thinking about clues.
You're wrong.
I'm looking for herbs.
Excuse me.
Young Master.
Where are we?
These are Madam's quarters.
The osmanthus flowers here are blooming very well.
Madam
likes osmanthus.
In Yu City,
only her quarters have osmanthus flowers.
Thank you.
What are you looking for?
Come and have a look.
Red mud.
Petals.
I've seen these on the soles of Yu Qiushuang's shoes.
This red mud is red pottery clay.
These flowers are osmanthus flowers.
I don't think these two things are common in the north.
Do you remember the weather at Xiaomian Inn?
It was raining.
If there were mud and flowers from Yu City
on her shoes,
they would have been washed away by the rain.
Then why had they been preserved?
There's only one possibility.
She died here.
She died in Yu City.
But first,
if she really died in Yu City,
how did she appear at Xiaomian Inn?
Besides, she looked like
she had just died.
Second,
in Yu City,
there are so many martial arts experts around.
Who could have killed her without anyone knowing?
without anyone knowing?
Once you figure out these two things,
we'll know.
No.
One more thing.
When we were at Xiaomian Inn,
we saw Yu Qiushuang enter the inn
with our own eyes.
Are you sure it was Yu Qiushuag?
What do you mean?
Qingling said it just now.
There was a scar on her face
that she didn't want seen by others.
Do you remember that night,
when Yu Qiushuang came in, her head was held up while she made a fuss,
as if she was afraid others won't notice
she had a scar on her face?
You mean someone pretended to be Yu Qiushuang?
Think about it.
This woman
showed up at Yu City and Xiaoyan Inn
at the same time.
Yun Jiao.
She's acting crazy too.
She must be involved.
Not bad.
You could see she was pretending to be crazy too.
You waved a needle so dramatically
in front of her eyes.
Even a lunatic would hide.
She must have been pretending.
But she was close with Yu Qiushuang.
Why would she harm her?
Is it really related to Zongzheng Mingzhu?
It's simple.
We'll know after we cure Yun Jiao's madness.
Madam Yu,
we've found the herbs for Yun Jiao.
These herbs
need to be boiled into soup
and dried into a paste.
She'll recover after taking it.
These small weeds?
Physician Li,
are you kidding me?
How can I fool Madam Yu?
I promise she will be cured.
I've checked.
Yun Jiao is the only person who has been in contact with Qiushuang recently.
It'll be good if you cure her.
If you don't,
I'll make her talk no matter what.
Guards.
Boil Physician Li's herbs.
Madam, wait.
To be honest,
my herbs are a bit special.
After they have been dried into a paste,
I need to make a special primer
for it to be effective.
Why didn't you tell me just now?
When will the primer be ready?
Madam Yu agreed to give us until tomorrow
to solve the case.
It's just right.
Didn't you say that Yun Jiao will be cured today?
Why did you change it to tomorrow?
Too straightforward.
What?
I didn't sleep well last night.
I need to rest.
The issue hasn't been solved yet.
How can you sleep?
Young Hero Fang.
Solving the case is important,
but your health is more important.
You know
I cherish my life.
Look at you.
You have dark eye circles
and a heaty liver.
You'll get sick if you're too tense.
You may leave.
You're always like this.
You can always keep a distance.
But I can't.
When I close my eyes,
I can only think of
what happened in Xiaomian Inn.
The murderer set everything up a long time ago.
Xiaoyan Inn was just a stage.
It made us watch
a ghost kill a person as if it were a game.
But the people have gotten involved are innocent.
Happy...
Have a drink.
If you hadn't insisted
on taking him on an adventure,
or
if you had kept him under your nose
and kept an eye on him,
he would be fine.
Is that what you think?
No matter what,
I failed to take good care of Happy.
When people are young,
they are at their most energetic.
You always think
it is your responsibility to protect the world.
And you always feel
you can protect everyone around you.
But the truth is
many things
are not as simple as we think
and are out of our control.
Your servant's misfortune
made you very upset.
But you don't have to
blame yourself for everything.
People
must learn to forgive themselves.
Here.
Have some tea.
Are you comforting me?
Didn't you say that everyone in the Jinyuan Alliance
are evil and vicious?
Why are you are so kind?
I told you.
You misunderstood me from the beginning.
But I still think it's wrong.
If Yu Qiushuang really died in Yu City,
she has been dead for more than seven days.
Why was the body still bleeding
when we saw her?
Try it.
Fresh frozen watermelon.
You're still in the mood to eat melon?
The secrets are all inside.
Secrets?
Secrets.
Try it.
It's only been a while.
Why has it gone bad?
The rotten body.
You're quick.
Frozen watermelon always goes bad faster.
No wonder Yu Qiushuang's body
was fine at Xiaomian Inn,
but rotted as soon as we arrived in Yu City.
It turns out she was put into the envoy box together with ice cubes.
The ice cubes
should have been made of blood.
I'm afraid blood was frozen
so that it could melt into blood
and create the illusion that Yu Qiushuang had just died.
It's so detailed.
No wonder it was burnt.
It can't be hidden.
This is just the first mystery.
Think about it.
If Yu Qiushuang died in Yu City,
why would she appear at Xiaoyan Inn?
Because from the beginning,
Yu Qiushuang was in the box.
Let's go.
Xiaomian Inn.
I need to go to the kitchen.
Why?
I think better in the kitchen.
The blood footprints that day are still here.
Come.
Come and have a look.
I'll show you blood footprints too.
Excuse me.
What's going on?
Paste made from red twilight grass is colorless.
But once it encounters water,
it will turn red.
Isn't this the herb
you wanted to use to treat Yun Jiao that day?
Yes.
Red twilight grass
grows in the yard in Yu City.
She picked it, made it into a paste, and painted it into ghost footprints.
Of course she'd recognize it.
After she sees the medicine,
she'll recover naturally.
What about the green ghost?
Everyone in the inn saw it that day.
Fireflies?
She sealed fireflies in the window.
But how did she turn
Yun Jiao into Yu Qiushuang
right under everyone's noses?
Smell it.
Hemp?
The water here
is mixed with hemp
to make people tipsy.
It's easier for Yun Jiao to make the swap
when people can't see properly.
What are you looking at?
Don't look at me!
After she puts down the veil,
everything will be fine.
Yun Jiao put a lot of effort into it.
Unfortunately, we didn't come here
to find evidence of Yun Jiao's crime.
Then what?
To prove Yun Jiao's innocence.
Here.
It's the same as the golden needle that killed Yu Qiushuang.
But this jade is...
It the jade Qingling said
Yu Qiushuang gave to Yun Jiao.
Someone wants to kill her.
It's such an elaborate show.
Yun Jiao couldn't have done it alone.
It hasn't been destroyed yet.
Shadow puppet?
This case
reminds me of a small sect.
The Pu family of Hujiang.
Over ten years ago,
the Pu family of Hujiang were renowned
for their shadow puppetry.
But unexpectedly,
they were destroyed overnight
due to gambling debts.
After that, they disappeared.
The silk strings are very thin.
It seems that as long as the person who holds the strings is skilled,
they can manipulate the puppet from outside the room.
That's right.
Yu Qiushuang died in Yu City,
but her body was sealed into the escort box together with blood ice
and sent to the escort agency.
The murderer then bribed Cheng Yunhe,
claiming it was the body of a prisoner.
Cheng Yunhe didn’t want to be exposed,
so he wouldn’t check the boxes one by one.
So Yu Qiushuang's body
was transported to Xiaomian Inn.
Yun Jiao brought the guards there under the guise of searching for Yu Qiushuang
so she could move in one day early
and set everything up at night.
The next evening,
she came in as Yu Qiushuang
and used shadow puppetry to fabricate a conversation between the two of them.
The guards in the distance
would only think their Second Young Miss had really returned.
The escort boxes were airtight since they were made of cold iron,
so the blood ice melted after exactly six days.
When the goods were carried into the inn,
blood seeped out of the boxes.
Once someone approached, they would notice something was off.
At that time, Yun Jiao took off her disguise
and went down to take a bath alone.
When blood seeped down,
she pointed everyone to the second floor
so the guards would find Second Young Miss missing.
The bloodied escort boxes would be opened.
Yu Qiushuang's body would thus be revealed.
This show of a ghost killing a person
would be complete.
This show needed
someone else killed as a lead-in.
But unexpectedly, Happy happened to be on the second floor.
He was very unlucky.
Yun Jiao was on the first floor,
so it was the person hiding in the shadows who killed Happy.
The person who could make Yun Jiao play so many tricks
and pretend to be crazy...
is Zongzheng Mingzhu.
Yun Jiao went this far,
but how could she know
the murderer wants to kill her too.
What are we waiting for?
For the murderer to strike again.
Before we set off,
didn't you set up a trap
in Yun Jiao's room?
You know that too?
You're really cunning.
Now,
we can only wait for the murderer to get caught
to solve my last question.
What question?
That needle and that palm.
Why did the murderer kill Yu Qiushuang twice?
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
Turn around and show your face.
It's me.
Master Yu?
What are you doing?
You want to kill Yun Jiao.
You're the one who killed Yu Qiushuang?
I was just worried about her condition,
so I came to visit her.
Yun Jiao has been crazy for two days,
but you came here only now.
You're afraid she might say something wrong, right?
Watch your language.
Don't forget our statuses.
What's happening in the middle of the night?
Madam.
Young Master Fang.
What are you doing?
It's a misunderstanding.
Why are you here?
Madam Yu, you came at the right time.
The murderer who killed Second Young Miss is right in front of you.
What?
Wasn't it Yun Jiao?
Yun Jiao
was just trying to help Castellan.
Yun Jiao helped Yu Mulan?
Castellan Yu
has a close relationship with Miss Yun Jiao.
Miss Yun once wrote a poem,
but got found out by Madam Yu.
"The pearl on my heart cannot be untied,
flying flowers and willow catkins make me miss you."
Wasn't this poem for...
Wasn't this poem for Young Master Zongzheng?
Pearl can have many meanings,
I don't dare to monopolize all of them.
I'd like to hear your explanation.
The flying flowers and willow catkins
are what Miss Yun really loves.
It's related to
the dandelion pendant on her writst.
The Pu family of Hujiang has the dandelion as their family emblem.
It seems that Master Pu is very loyal to the Pu family
even after marrying into Yu City.
So you're the one she likes.
Pu Mulan.
You played me like a fool.
You haven't let go of the Pu family.
The Pu family earned a lot of money
through shadow puppetry in those years.
Unfortunately,
the late master was a gambler.
The Pu family wanted to revamp themselves
to gain a good reputation.
Thank you, Miss.
Madam, this shadow puppet
was found at Xiaomian Inn.
The murderer wanted to use shadow puppetry
to create the impression that a ghost was the murderer.
And the other shadow puppet
was found in Master Yu's study.
The Pu family has a unique skill called the "Thousand Transformations of Fire"
which allows the puppeteer to control their strings from afar.
Wouldn't using your ancestors' prized skill to commit murder
make them unrestful?
You just dug up my past
to frame me.
I have no grudge against her.
Why should I kill her?
Fine.
Even if I killed her,
I could have ditched the body far away.
Why would I go to all this trouble
to expose her body?
Of course you had a reason.
Pu Mulan.
You were born with a predilection for gambling
because of your father.
He lost all his assets,
so you could only marry into Yu City.
Unfortunately,
you are a gambler.
In order to avoid Madam Yu,
you could only repay your debt by faking the accounts
while guarding the jade mine.
Unfortunately, Yu Qiushuang holds half of Yu City's property.
According to the rules,
if Yu Qiushuang goes missing,
the mines are still hers.
Only by proving that she's dead
can Madam Yu inherit everything.
Pu Mulan.
Only you
have the chance to fake the accounts to repay your debts.
Yu City is famous.
Maybe it's too rich.
Pu Mulan,
am I right?
You’re slandering me!
Young Master Fang.
The Fang family has banks everywhere.
I asked around
and it was easy to find this gambler's accounts.
Pu Mulan.
I'm afraid you owe money
to all the gambling dens within a hundred li radius from here.
Pu Mulan,
you traitor!
I thought you had changed those bad habits
after marrying into my family.
I didn't expect you would
kill my sister for money.
Madam,
how can you believe these two swindlers?
I didn't.
You didn't?
Castellan Yu really didn't leave anything to chance.
You knew that as long as we investigated Second Young Miss Yu's body
and talked to the guards that were present,
we would definitely find the loophole.
So, you burned the body at night.
But you never thought
Madam Yu would come back early
to rescue the body before it had been burned completely.
Unfortunately, Madam Yu,
you were angry
and killed all the guards.
They never had a chance to speak.
Your disregard for the guards' lives
was exactly what the murderer wanted.