[English subtitles are available]
[Mysterious Lotus Casebook]
[Episode 34]
Everyone!
Back to the mountain manor now!
Mother, activate the mechanism!
Leave this to me.
Okay.
Hurry!
Everyone! Attack!
You didn't expect a magnetic arrow
could turn your Xianri Sedan
into a pile of scrap iron, did you?
You stole the Cloud-chasing Carriage from Tianji Hall
and turned it into a killing weapon.
Did you think I couldn't find its core?
Since I came back from Shishou Village,
I've been studying this.
What other moves do you have now?
Good.
My son, Tianji Hall has really taught you well.
Demon Monk!
Li Xiangyi?
Aunt!
Xiaofeng!
Director Di.
You're late.
What do you want?
If you want her to live,
give me the Rama Heavenly Ice.
Your memory has been recovered?
You traitor!
You ungrateful man.
You've colluded with the Wansheng Clan.
We just work together for what we each want.
Give it to me.
I don't have much patience.
You won't get what you want
by getting blood from a stone.
Cut it out.
Xiaofeng!
Aunt!
Shan Gudao!
If you want to achieve great things,
don't care about trifles.
Hand it over.
Fang Xiaobao.
Give him the Heavenly Ice.
Where's the other piece?
Aunt!
If I give it to you,
you must release her at the same time.
My son.
It seems that Tianji Hall didn't teach you well.
You want to bargain with your father?
You're not qualified to bargain with me.
Xiaofeng!
Aunt!
Hand it over!
Xiaofeng.
Are you okay?
Thank you for your help, Director Di.
As long as I have you, Director Di, by my side,
everything's much easier.
Senior.
This is the last time I'm calling you this.
In the past,
I've never fought with you for anything.
In the future,
I'll take your life
and return it to Master.
Let's see if you are lucky enough
to live to that day.
Finally.
I finally got all four pieces of Rama Heavenly Ice
in my own hands.
Burn your body.
Exorcise your soul.
Sacrifice Sui and Yan for fire.
Karmic fire burns the sky!
Congratulations, Master.
Once I open the Rama Vessel,
everything in the world
will be mine.
Di Feisheng.
What are you doing?
I've helped you get it done.
As for this...
I'll take it.
Di Feisheng.
Don't be so rampant.
This is the Wansheng Clan.
This isn't somewhere you can
come and leave as you wish.
So the ranking of martial skills
in Who's Who of Martial Arts can't be trusted.
Director Di, you're right.
You two also did a good job.
In the whole martial world,
how many masters of martial arts
can beat you,
Director Di?
So I'd very much like
to work with you, Director Di.
If you really need it for emergencies,
I can lend you
the Rama Vessel and Rama Heavenly Ice, Director Di.
There's one more thing.
I heard that you sent people to investigate
the whereabouts of the Styx Flower, Director Di.
What a coincidence.
I happen to have the Styx Flower.
I think you must be very interested, Director Di.
Are you serious?
These leaves are the leaves of the Styx Flower.
You can ask the Medicine Demon to identify them.
As long as
you return the two things to me
as soon as possible after you are done with them, Director Di,
I'll gift the Styx Flower to you.
What do you think?
It's not a bad idea.
Keep the Styx Flower well,
and wait for me.
So I'm still the one who knows
the best way to handle my man.
How's that?
I told you about the Styx Flower.
It really worked, right?
My efforts of sending people to search everywhere
and getting the Styx Flower
into my hands one step ahead paid off.
Sect Leader Shan.
I've let bygones be bygones and worked with you again.
You should know
what I want.
Rest assured.
After I make the best of Di Feisheng,
he'll be yours.
Rest assured?
I still remember vividly what happened before.
Last time, it was just a stopgap.
You saw it yourself, too.
Di Feisheng was pressing me,
so I had to pretend to obey him.
If both of us fall out with him,
it will be bad for Nanyin's cause.
I think
we should keep the sharp knife for now.
You don't have to
make kicking off the ladder sound so nice, Sect Leader Shan.
If I hadn't sent the message
and asked Snow Master to save you,
who would know where you were locked up?
Moreover,
we are from the same clan.
We are both descendants of the royal family of Nanyin.
We should be even more united.
[Ninglan Hall]
Saintess.
Are you really working with Shan Gudao again this time?
I, Jiao Liqiao,
am not someone who'd suffer in silence.
I just want to take down Di Feisheng
with his help.
Di Feisheng.
After this is done,
I'll definitely
get even with him.
Your martial skills have improved a lot lately, Kid.
When did you do that?
Just now.
When I slapped back
the waves you set off.
How's that, Master?
This time I passed the test, right?
Fine.
Go down the mountain with your senior.
Thank you, Master.
I'll make sure to use the sword in my hand
to help the weak and suppress the overpowering,
become a big shot with honor,
and bring glory to our sect.
I don't want you to be a big shot.
I just want you and your senior
to eat well,
and live well.
Remember.
When you come back,
bring me a new flask,
and fill it with fine wine.
Master.
I've fixed the wine gourd for you.
I promised to have a drink with you,
but there's no such chance anymore.
Everything
should come to an end.
You knew you are injured,
yet you forcibly used your inner power so many times just now.
Do you really want to die?
Just minor injuries.
It's okay.
It's okay?
When we were on Yunyin Mountain,
you told me the poison had been detoxicated.
I actually believed it.
You are blaming everything
on yourself again.
I said it's not your fault.
The cause of it is that I didn't see through or doubt the people who work for me.
So, it is my fault.
If you want to forget your identity as Li Xiangyi,
you should face your present self truthfully.
Why are you still holding onto the past?
It's been too long since I let go of the past.
Li Lianhua has lived a carefree life for ten years.
It's time for it to end.
For what to end?
From back when we were on Yunyin Mountain to now,
I'm afraid the poison in your body
has already...
I'm afraid there's less than a month left.
The most important thing now
is to find a way to save you.
You know?
Fang Xiaobao.
Bicha Poison
can't be detoxicated.
Who said that?
I've sent people
to look for the Styx Flower everywhere.
There must be a way to save you.
In this life, I, Fang Duobing,
recognize you, Li Lianhua, as my only confidant.
I won't let you die.
Don't worry about anything else.
Xiaobao.
I don't have much time left.
That's why I need to complete what I want to do
before I die.
Shan Gudao.
I must stop him.
[Tianji Mountain Manor]
[Mysterious Lotus Casebook]
[Tianji Hall]
There's no way I can stop you, right?
If you really want to go,
I must go with you.
You also have to promise me that
you won't use your inner power anymore.
I'll protect you.
Okay, I promise you.
You agreed so readily.
It's hard not to doubt that you have other thoughts.
Is it wrong to agree readily?
So where are you going now?
To find out what Di Feisheng is really up to.
I don't think he would have worked
with Shan Gudao for no reason.
If we can find him,
maybe there's still have a chance for us to get the Heavenly Ice.
Do you have any clue?
I checked the background
of Di Feisheng ten years ago.
He's from a hidden place in the southwest
specially built for Death Sorcerer training.
Do you remember the day we ran into him
when he just lost his memory?
Why?
Why do we have to kill each other?
So you suspect the reason why Di Feisheng did this
has something to do with his background?
Di Feisheng
has been famous in the martial world for so many years,
but he never mentioned his background.
Don't you think it's strange?
Let's go to the southwest and investigate it.
Stand up!
Stand up and fight me!
Stop!
Stop running!
[Qingxin Hall]
So it's really the similar mind control techniques.
Karmic bugs are the most powerful of all mind control bugs.
Now that the mind control techniques in my body have been removed,
I'm going to repay
your kindness to me as I grow up.
It's you.
I couldn't do anything to you when you were in the Jinyuan Alliance.
I couldn't kill you traitor even though I sent people there several times.
Since you've come to me today,
don't think about leaving here alive.
The Di family always trains the Death Sorcerers
to take money and do their job accordingly.
Today, I'll buy this cheap life of yours.
You know no limits.
I'll show you
what happens when you betray the Di Fortress.
Surprised?
Without these mind control bugs,
how could you make those Death Sorcerers yield to you?
You think you can kill me?
I'm the head of the family.
I'm the one who's been training you since you were little.
When I was little,
did you ever spare me
when I was tortured and begged for mercy?
Don't kill me.
Please.
I'll hand over the Di Fortress to you.
Kill you?
It'll be too easy for you.
I'll destroy all your meridians.
There will be one more useless person in the world.
You can neither live well or die.
From now on,
there will no longer be any threats from the Di family.
The world is vast.
You can go anywhere and do whatever you want.
[Di Fortress]
[Di]
My Lord.
Have you got it done?
The karmic larvae can't be killed by any method.
Only Snow Mountain Crystal Salt can dissolve them.
The Medicine Demon has gone to look for it.
Give it to me once you find it.
We can't keep them.
Yes.
Also,
I've found the thing
you asked me to look for, My Lord.
I've checked.
This Styx Flower is real.
The box and the flower itself are neither poisonous.
Shan Gudao wants to threaten me with the Styx Flower.
Now I have both the flower and the Rama Vessel.
Let's see what else he can do.
Go find Li Lianhua.
My Lord.
Guess
whether you can leave or not?
Jiao Liqiao.
What's wrong?
Stay away!
The Styx Flower is not poisonous.
That's because I put the poison
on him, King Xunming of Yama.
Otherwise, how could I have fooled you, My Lord?
I was negligent.
I implicated you, My Lord.
You want to die?
What a great show.
Director Di.
Last time, you said the disciples of Demon Monk
are no match for you.
So today,
I've invited Rank 1 on the Who's Who of Martial Arts,
Buddhist Three Saints, here
to go a few rounds with you.
Are you satisfied today?
My Lord fought the three of them alone.
If it weren't for the poison on King Xunming of Yama
that accidentally splashed on him
and controlled his inner power,
you might not have been able to beat him.
My Lord.
You threw me
into that horrifying bottomless pit,
and had my face scratched.
How could you?
It took me a long time
to find such a suitable face skin.
Don't worry.
Although you are heartless,
I don't blame you.
Your flexor tendons are broken.
My Lord.
What should I do?
In that case,
I have to...
Jiao Liqiao.
You didn't kill me.
You'll regret it.
How could I bear to kill you?
Enough.
Beauty Jiao.
Have you had enough fun?
Don't worry.
Shan Gudao won't be here for long.
He wants to use you to suppress me.
But I'm not as stupid as you.
Outsiders
will always be outsiders.
Shan Gudao has the wishful thinking of dominating the world.
Let him be.
When his ego inflates out of its limit,
he will die.
Looks like a fierce battle took place here.
Let's go.
Let's go in and have a look.
Help me!
So the Di Fortress
used similar mind control techniques
to make people unable to resist the Master.
So the reason why
Di Feisheng agreed to cooperate with Shan Gudao
is that he wanted to get the karmic bugs
to expel the mind control techniques inside of him.
Now that Di Feisheng has solved
the matter of the Di Fortress,
why didn't he show up and look for me?
Maybe he had an accident?
Or, could it be
Di Feisheng really colluded with Shan Gudao?
Looks like we can only study that human skin first,
and find a way to suppress the karmic bugs.
Master.
Since you know the mind control techniques,
do you know how to suppress it?
The karmic bugs
are of different levels.
Big ones can suppress small ones,
and mother bugs can suppress child bugs.
The karmic bugs are of the highest level.
As far as I know,
all mind control bugs can be suppressed by karmic bugs.
Mother bugs can suppress child bugs?
Could the way of suppressing karmic bugs
be the mother bugs
themselves?
Could the tattooed cyan human skin left by Liangyi Fairy
be pointing to the location of the mother karmic bugs?
It seems
Shan Gudao and I are looking for the same thing.
Welcome, Master.
Rise.
How is it?
My Yulongniuma Gang
is more interesting than the Jinyuan Alliance, right?
Since the first day
I saw you,
I've been hoping you could completely be mine.
I didn't expect that
my wish finally came true.
Come on. Drink with me.
You really have a temper.
Drink mine first.
So pretty.
Look at you.
So beautiful.
Yeah.
So pretty.
Have a drink with me.
Drink mine.
Don't be ungrateful.
Guys.
This girl wanted to steal our precious and practice her martial skills.
Unfortunately,
she's not good enough.
She can be my bedmate.
You want to touch me?
Dream on!
Wicked woman.
Go to hell!
Guishou Fenglie.
What's your rank on the list of who's who of martial arts again?
Who are you?
Rank 10.
Unimpressive.
Now, I'm the new Rank 10.
I wanted to marry you,
but you didn't even look at me.
I honored you as my lord, and you still wasn't satisfied.
Alright then.
From now on,
you'll be my wife.
OK?
Take him to my room
and hang him up.
Take good care of him.
Why didn't you make any move?
I would, if it's ten years ago.
You're swift in making moves.
Looks like you've almost recovered.
Thank you for saving me that day.
I'll remember your kindness.
You don't have to.
You can buy me a drink another day.
Your sword is already broken.
Why do you still keep it?
A sword isn't bad just because it's old,
and friends don't have to be new to be good.
It's a good sword,
but I don't deserve it.
Why?
A precious sword is meant for a hero.
But I'm no hero.
Then tell me.
What is a hero?
As long as he's alive, he'll keep the sword safe.
He'll never give it up till he dies.
Where is your Shaoshi Sword?
You're not going to get it back?
Some people discard their swords like throwing out garbage,
while some carry their swords with them for a lifetime.
People's faiths
are different after all.
People do have different faiths.
I was wrong.
You really have changed.
Li Xiangyi wouldn't talk like that.
Things are different, Zhan Yunfei.
It's been ten years.
People change.
Besides,
over the past ten years,
you've also become a different Zhan Yunfei.
You wore your hair up.
It doesn't look good to me at all.
I'll keep the sword.
I'll buy you a drink another day.
The outermost circle of this pattern
looks like a wall.
Then what are these inside?
I've almost emptied my father's study these days.
There are only these local records of Great Xi left.
See if they can be of use.
Compare this book
with this one, which records Nanyin's culture.
This symbol should stand for gods.
Does this pattern mean that
the karmic mother bugs are kept somewhere
related to gods?
When you forget about your physical body, you can enter paradise.
Your spirits can ascend to the fairy land.
This poem is actually related to gods.
What does it mean?
Could it be that
the place related to gods
is a building,
a temple,
or an immortal mansion?
The outermost circle does look like a wall.
Could the shape of the tattooed cyan human skin
be a city?
I happen to have a map of the city.
Let's check it thoroughly.
We've searched everywhere,
but we couldn't find a place
that matches the shape of the human skin.
Did we guess it in a wrong direction?
Xiaobao.
Father.
You...
You've brought the entire collection
of my precious books here.
-Don't worry./N-You...
I'll put them back in order
-in a few days./N-You...
Calm down.
Why do you have the map of the city?
Lord Fang.
You know this map?
This is the map of the Imperial City from 100 years ago.