[English subtitles are available]
[Mysterious Lotus Casebook]
[Episode 40]
It's windy up here.
Put it on.
Thanks.
I know you're going to Sigu Sect.
Have you really made up your mind?
There are some things that I have to solve myself.
I have to end them myself too.
♫This world is too hasty♫
♫It can't wait for the end of time♫
♫The future is long enough♫
♫To return a wish from the gods♫
♫This world is too hasty♫
♫Tattered clothes and brocade clothes♫
♫Who doesn't walk alone♫
Everyone.
Have you heard?
The leader of the Sigu Sect, Li Xiangyi, is not dead.
Really?
Yes.
The traitor, Yun Biqiu,
conspired with Jiao Liqiao repeatedly
and almost overturned the whole martial world.
Fortunately, the Sigu Sect leader,
Li Xiangyi, resurfaced the martial world
and curbed the chaos.
I heard that the Sigu Sect is going to interrogate the traitor, Yun Biqiu.
Why don't we witness it together?
Let's go.
I'll go with you.
[Sigu Sect]
You hid these letters in the daily mail
[To Wu Shengming]
and sent them out of Baichuan Court.
A kind of concealing potion was used on these letters.
With them, you leaked out everything
pertaining to the location and layout
of Baichuan Court's 188 prisons.
What else do you have to say?
Biqiu. Oh, Biqiu...
Ten years ago, you were bewitched by Jiao Liqiao's beauty.
All these years,
you stayed at home and refused to travel,
as if you were punishing yourself.
I really thought that you'd grounded yourself
to repent your mistake.
Who would have thought that,
after ten years,
you are still so stubborn?
You even harmed the Sect Leader
again for that witch.
Baichuan Court is known as the martial world's court of justice.
It has brought countless villains to justice in the past years.
But if there is a traitor among Fo, Bi, Bai, and Shi,
who will harm the martial world,
then who will uphold justice in the martial world?
Today, be it Sigu Sect,
or Baichuan Court,
you must give us an explanation.
Yes.
Give us an explanation.
Give us an explanation!
Kill him! Kill him!
Everyone.
Kill him!
Yun Biqiu is one of the four masters of the Baichuan Court.
He harmed the martial world
and betrayed his duties.
He tried to kill the Sect Leader many times.
It's unforgivable.
Baichuan Court has always been strict with punishments.
We never make exceptions.
So, from today onwards,
Yun Biqiu is expelled from the Baichuan Court.
As for the murder he committed,
he will pay with his life.
Everyone, please bear witness.
Yun Biqiu.
You can only blame yourself
for ending up like this.
Today, I'll help Sigu Sect
and Baichuan Court remove a sinner,
and avenge Sect Leader
and my fallen seniors and juniors.
The Shaoshi Sword!
Li Xiangyi?
Li Xiangyi!
Sect Leader.
It's really him.
How many years has it been?
Greetings, Sect Leader.
Stand up, everyone.
I'm no longer the leader of the Sigu Sect.
You'll always be our leader.
We'll follow you to the death!
Is this what you wanted to see?
Hanfo.
Tell everyone to get up.
Biqiu.
Since I'm not dead,
why must you be so stubborn?
Sect Leader.
I've let you down.
I poisoned you back then
and severely wounded you recently.
I am too ashamed to live on.
What about the good things you did?
Why didn't you mention them?
You defamed yourself
and used the map of the 188 prisons as bait
to earn Jiao Liqiao's trust.
You found the details of her defenses
and deliberately disclosed them to Fang Duobing.
That's how everyone was able to find and save me that day.
It was also you
who pretended to be bewitched by her beauty
and made Jiao Liqiao let her guard down.
You induced her to make flawed mechanisms
and destroyed half of Shan Gudao's foundation.
Am I right?
Sect Leader,
are you telling the truth?
Everyone,
these are the mechanism blueprints
found in Jiao Liqiao's hideout.
They are all written by Yun Biqiu.
You can verify them.
Anyone who knows how to design mechanisms
can tell what Yun Biqiu did to them.
When I saw the layout of the statues on the roofs,
I knew something was weird about them.
All the traps we encountered along the way
had their mechanisms exposed.
It was very obvious.
Any designer would know that
the mechanism should be hidden.
And this mechanism...
Someone deliberately placed this mechanism here
for people to see.
He even buried 18 fire bombs around the court,
saving everyone from a bloody battle.
I see.
Biqiu.
You did all those things.
Why didn't you tell us about it?
Sect Leader was poisoned and fell into the sea because of me.
Later, he was also stabbed by me.
58 members of the Sigu Sect died because of me.
No matter what I do,
I cannot amend my sins.
Biqiu.
When you stabbed me that day,
you purposely missed the spot by half an inch.
You originally asked me out that day
to tell me this information.
But unexpectedly,
Jiao Liqiao had secretly sent someone to spy on you.
I'm not talking about the past.
I'm sorry
for the present.
Only by stabbing me can you get Jiao Liqiao
to lower her guard against you.
That way, she no longer doubted
the mechanisms you placed.
So,
you helped me find Jiao Liqiao's place,
and I was able to catch all of them at once.
What you did back then
was not your intention either.
Since you wish to repent,
we shall
let bygones be bygones.
Sect Leader.
I don't deserve your forgiveness.
Master Yun.
In order to clear your name,
that man named Li Xiangyi
had to come back from the bottom of the sea.
And that man called Li Lianhua
can no longer be
a carefree wandering physician anymore.
Sect Leader...
How is he?
It's Xueronghua.
What is Xueronghua?
It's Snow Master's dark skill.
Jiao Liqiao must have done it
to control Biqiu.
The only way
to detoxify the poison is
to circulate his blood with Snow Master's inner power.
Otherwise, the poison will reach his heart and kill him.
Jiao Liqiao and Snow Master are both dead.
Xueronghua is now a lost skill.
Then Biqiu...
He won't last long.
He knew that,
but he didn't stop me from killing Snow Master back then.
Xiaobao.
Does Tianji Hall have a secret branch in this vicinity?
Can you help me find a way
to cure the Xueronghua?
Okay.
I'll contact them now.
[Roam with a Noble Spirit]
The rest of you may leave too.
We'll plan after Biqiu wakes up.
It's not that I don't care about my life.
But Li Xiangyi said back then
that he would protect everyone in Sigu Sect.
And yet, 58 brothers died
in the East Sea battle.
If I let Sigu Sect lose another member now,
how will I face my fallen brothers
in the Netherworld?
At least my last bit of inner power
is useful in the end.
I really shouldn't have been wasteful
when I was young.
Then I wouldn't have had to
put my life on the line
just to do some good with my inner power.
Sect Leader.
You're awake.
Did you
cure the Xueronghua for me?
Do you
feel better?
I...
Biqiu.
Back then, at the East Seaside,
I fought the Jinyuan Alliance alone.
I had no way out and no reinforcements.
I sank the ship with everything I had.
But the Bicha Poison struck
and I fell into the sea.
Back then,
I really hated you.
After I made my way out of the sea alive,
I swore
to take revenge
even if it would land me in hell.
I...
Deserve to die.
Actually,
after the battle at the East Sea,
I went back to Sigu Gate.
While in hiding,
I saw the sect crumble and fall apart.
I also heard
complaints I'd never heard of before.
I was confused
and lost my direction.
I thought about it for a long time.
Maybe that failure was caused by
my own stubbornness.
No.
It doesn't matter anymore.
I don't want to go back to Sigu Sect.
Let me tell you something funny.
Back then, I had no money on me,
[Pawn]
and I was injured.
So I pawned the only valuable
item on my body
for 50 taels of silver.
It was the Sigu Sect Leader token.
A token that could spare or take a life at will,
a token that everyone in the martial world
knew about.
Biqiu.
Don't you think it's funny?
Such a powerful token was only worth 50 taels.
At that time, I thought
I would redeem it
as soon as I was better.
But at one point in time,
I started growing turnips instead.
Growing turnips?
It's so that I won't starve anymore.
It was spring then.
I thought the turnips were growing too slowly.
I looked at them every day,
and counted them every day.
When I saw the turnip bellies
poking out of the soil,
I was so happy,
I almost cried.
Before I knew it,
I somehow saved up 50 taels of silver.
It had been three years
since I fell into the sea.
I took the 50 taels of silver to the pawnshop
to redeem the token.
In a poor fishing village,
no one knew what it was.
The token was still there, but I hesitated.
It turned out that I'd forgotten the martial world.
I no longer yearned to be the best
or to be admired by everyone.
I kept myself fed
and even kept a dog fed.
Such a life
was perfect.
When I thought of you one day,
I suddenly forgot why I hated you.
The past doesn't matter anymore.
Sect Leader.
If those are not important,
what is?
What matters is your future life.
You've always liked studying.
You can become a scholar,
or get married
and live a peaceful life.
Biqiu.
Live well.
Live for yourself.
Okay.
I'll listen to you.
I'll live well.
What about you?
What about your Bicha Poison?
Don't worry.
I can even cure your Xueronghua.
Let alone
a mere Bicha Poison.
[Grand Hall]
Li Lianhua!
What's wrong with you?
You saved Yun Biqiu with Yangzhouman?
You truly hold no grudge
or resentment against him.
Those who truly repent
deserve a second chance.
No.
You can't delay any longer.
You need to take the Styx Flower now.
Where is the Styx Flower?
I've kept it locked in here
since Di Feisheng gave it to us.
Where did it go?
Li Lianhua,
how did His Majesty cure his poison?
Did you use the Styx Flower to save His Majesty?
Fang Xiaobao.
You now...
Don't you know that there's only this one Styx Flower
left in this world
that can save your life?
I knew you would be angry.
To be honest,
the Styx Flower
only had 30% of the chance to detoxify my poison.
It will be a waste to use it on me.
I might as well give it to someone who needs it more.
Right?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
I'm here today
to present this to Your Majesty,
to help clear Your Majesty's poison.
No wonder His Majesty let my father go so quickly.
No wonder he's no longer afraid of you.
Li Lianhua,
so many people work so hard to get you to live.
But what about you?
Don't you care about your own life?
No.
I won't let you die.
I'm lucky... to have you as my disciple.
[Lotus Tower Medical Center]
You're awake.
How do you feel?
Good.
Your pulse has stabilised.
This is the Taisui Restoration Pill
from Tianji Mountain Manor.
Although it can't cure the poison in your body,
it might be able to help get you through for a while.
Here, eat it.
Didn't you just check my pulse?
You said that it's good.
Why do I still have to eat this?
No need.
No.
You have to eat it. Come on.
Hurry up.
Here, have some water.
People die without a shadow.
You can't keep a dying man.
My Erya Sword has killed even the King of Hell.
I can still save your life.
I'll go find Guan Hemeng now.
He must have a way.
Wait.
These are the recipes that I wrote
through years of culinary experience.
It's very precious.
I'm a little hungry now.
Make me a meal.
Fang Xiaobao, what are you doing?
I know no one can stop you if you're trying to run.
But for just this one time,
can you think about your health,
and stop sneaking away, please?
I'll be back soon.
Fang Xiaobao, this is too embarrassing.
Come back!
No matter what,
I was once a hero that everyone admired.
Fang Duobing!
Let go of me.
[Royal Palace]
[Mysterious Lotus Casebook]
Mian,
what are you doing?
Are you leaving me just because
Li Xiangyi is coming back?
What happened between me and Xiangyi is in the past.
This has nothing to do with him.
You once gave me this jade bangle.
Now I'm returning this to you.
From now on,
let's go our separate ways.
Take care.
Fox Spirit.
From now on,
I can't cook delicious food for you anymore.
Here.
You are so fat.
You should eat less in the future.
Eat less, okay?
But
you have to stay here
and wait for Fang Duobing to come back.
Miss,
is this the Sigu Sect?
Yes.
Someone asked me to give this to you.
♫This world is too hasty♫
♫It can't wait for the end of time♫
Sect Leader.
♫The future is long enough♫
♫To return a wish from the gods♫
[Sigu Sect]
♫This world is too hasty♫
♫Tattered clothes and brocade clothes♫
♫Who doesn't walk alone♫
♫The fragrance is slowly dissipating♫
♫But the wind is blowing stronger♫
♫Where the ashes are scattered it fills anger and greed♫
♫Beads fall onto a jade plate♫
♫A life of grace and a sigh♫
♫My hands are unable to warm your heart♫
♫A push of the wine glass and one leap♫
♫I enter the mortal world♫
♫As I wander the world carelessly♫
♫I reach the peak of the clouds♫
♫Gathering and parting happens in a blink of an eye ♫
♫We share affectionate words as we watch the moon♫
Fox Spirit!
We're back.
Where is Li Lianhua?
♫I only hope that we think of each other and never owe each other♫
Why are you barking?
These are the recipes that I wrote
through years of culinary experience.
It's very precious.
I'm a little hungry now.
Make me a meal.
This is the sword technique of the Xiangyi Swordplay.
He is passing Fox Spirit
and everything he's learned to me.
He wants to...
In a few days, it will be the day
he and Di Feisheng agreed to fight at the East Sea.
He should show up then.
Li Xiangyi will.
But it's hard to say for Li Lianhua.
My eyesight really is getting worse.
[Wangjiang Pavilion]
I went the wrong way.
Li Xiangyi.
Where did you hide Mian?
Do I look like
I'm hiding her?
Stop quibbling.
You are a hypocrite.
You said that you would never come back,
that you wouldn't steal Mian and the Sect Leader position from me.
In the end, you still showed up
in front of everyone with Shaoshi Sword.
You just want to tell everyone
that you’re back.
Weren't you trying to intimidate me like this?
Zijin,
you've misunderstood the situation.
Sigu Sect doesn't need two leaders.
There's no need
for a dead Li Xiangyi
to stand between me and Mian too.
Draw your sword.
I'm going to fight you to death today.
It's been ten years.
Let me see your Shaoshi Sword again.
Li Xiangyi may be dead,
but his sword is still alive.
It's easy to conquer the world,
but it's not easy to stop using Xiangyi Swordplay.
It's not that easy
to be a dead person too.
I don't have much inner power left.
I'm no match for you.
I'd rather kill myself.
It's not appropriate for you to kill me.
You...
Some people will admit defeat easily
but some will never.
Everybody's faith
is ultimately different.
What are you talking about?
I have let many things down in my life,
but I'm most sorry
to Shaoshi Sword.
Zijin.
Now that Shaoshi Sword is broken,
there will be no more Li Xiangyi in this world,
nor will there be Xiangyi Swordplay.
You can rest assured.
As for Mian,
it's your suspicion and lack of trust
that disappointed her.
There's nothing I can do.
Don't do things like this
in the future.
Sect Leader!
Li Xiangyi!
Guess what?
This Li Lianhua from Lotus Tower
who can cure the dead
is actually the one who challenged
the entire battleship of Jinyuan Alliance alone ten years ago,
the Sect Leader of Sigu Sect, Li Xiangyi.
Li Xiangyi?
Li Xiangyi came back from his death under the sea,
and lay in wait for more than ten years,
just to foil the schemes
between Wansheng Clan and Nanyin.
With his white cape behind him,
[Discussing the past and present]
he reappeared in the martial arts world with Shaoshi Sword in hand,
and held the leader of Wansheng Clan at swordpoint.
Bravo! Bravo!
What happened after that?
Go on.
Tomorrow is the day.
Fox Spirit,
do you think he will come?
Did this Li Xiangyi not come
because he's afraid?
Who is this Li Xiangyi?
I think this is his deliberate tactic used
to mess with Di Feisheng's emotions.
Sect Leader, do you think something has happened?
Excuse me, may I know who is Di Feisheng,
and who is Fang Duobing?
I am.
Someone asked me to deliver a letter today.
Sir, where are you going?
Where am I going?
Let me think.
If the boat sinks and I spend the rest of my life here,
that doesn't seem so bad either.
Ten years ago,
at the Great Battle of the East Sea,
I couldn't win even though
I had the weaponry advantage and used the sinking of the boat.
Your valiance
is rare in the world.
I sincerely admire you.
It's been years now,
I am ill of health,
my sword is broken, and I will be gone.
It is with great regret that I can't attend
the promised meeting at the East Sea.
I'm grateful for the Styx Flower you gave me,
but I have failed you ultimately.
Years have passed
and things have changed.
When it's time to go, it goes.
When time comes, it comes.
I have passed my skills to Fang Duobing.
He is talented,
and no doubt
will surpass me one day.
You have no intention of chasing victory,
you just want to reach the peak.
Now that I'm gone,
if you are unwilling to accept this,
please ask Fang Duobing to stand in my place.
Last regards, Li Xiangyi.
His sword is broken and he is gone?
Li Lianhua.
What does he mean?
He was fine, why would his sword break?
Is Li Xiangyi really not coming?
He sent his last regards.
Li Lianhua's Bicha Poison
never had a cure.
How could this happen?
Then could he really be…
He told me
he had a way to cure the Bicha Poison.
But...
I should have known.
I really misunderstood him.
So it's true.
But how is that possible?
He survived it.
How could he have died?
He was fine
the day his sword broke.
The day his sword broke?
When did you see him?
A few days ago,
at Wangjiang Pavilion.
I forced him to draw his sword and fight me.
He then broke Shaoshi Sword
and jumped into the river.
Was he trying to–
He never cared about the position of sect leader at all.
Why didn't you trust him?
It's all our fault.
We didn't even notice.
We thought he was fine.
Miss Shi.
Since Li can supress
the poison in his body for ten years,
he might be able to do it for another ten years,
and another ten more.
I'll go find him now.
I'm afraid it's too late.
I've checked his pulse.
He only has less than a month to live.
He used his martial arts
too often for the Shan Gudao incident.
If he didn't take the Styx Flower in time,
I'm afraid by the time he wrote this letter he would have...
Impossible.
Li Lianhua is not dead.
No matter what you say,
as long as we don't find his body,
I won't believe that he is dead.
I will find him,
no matter what it takes.
Xiaobao.
Li Xiangyi.
No one can replace you
in our promise.