[English subtitles are available]
[One and Only]
[Episode 24]
Throughout my life,
I've never let anyone down
but Eleven.
[Eleven]
General Cui,
have you decided?
A soldier must be upright above all else, even if it means death.
I believe my parents
will understand and forgive me.
Let's go.
Under the heavens and in front of the three armies,
I make an oath that
I will give up my family name Cui
and give myself the surname of the Junior Prince of Nanchen and follow him.
For the state,
for the people
and for those generals and soldiers
who sacrificed their lives.
We will start the rebellion in Shouyang today!
Rebel! Rebel! Rebel!
That night when my husband left,
it was snowing heavily
in Qinghe,
just like this.
Your Ladyship,
we've got news from the young master.
He gave up his family name Cui
and started a rebellion in Shouyang.
His Majesty issued an edict to
offer amnesty and enlistment to the young master
and that he shall not be killed.
Now that he has given up his family name Cui.
Will it displease His Majesty?
Knowing Feng's personality
he will not submit.
Since he has made his decision,
then let him be.
But,
he gave up his family name
at will
to follow the Junior Prince of Nanchen.
How unrestrained he is.
Yeah.
He's not like us
who have too many worries.
Is there any message from Mr. Huan?
Not yet.
Let's wait for some more days.
Yes.
Your Highness, were you awake all night?
Prepare some tea.
Yes.
It's indeed hard for you
to accept the fact that
the royal mansion has rebelled.
Here, have some water.
Your cousin has also rebelled.
If you don't believe me, you may ask your mother.
Among your six branches,
only Wushui branch
has hundreds of members
taking posts as Royal Guards in the royal court
and posts in different counties and prefectures.
How many people will die
as Cui Feng rebels?
The Gao family was eliminated due to one person.
The Qi family was destroyed due to one person.
Do you want the Cui family
to follow in their footsteps?
Here, drink some water.
Go get breakfast ready.
Yes.
When I was a kid, they said
you were good at Qin and painting.
I planned to ask you to play the Qin
on the day when you are conferred the title.
Now it seems
you won't be able to do it.
I'm going to summon the imperial doctor.
She didn't utter a word before me.
Why doesn't she
think for me?
He's been a Regional Prince
guarding the Western State for over 20 years.
No emperor would dare to keep him alive!
Your Majesty.
Zhousheng Chen.
But I ordered
him to be killed by dismemberment
in front of all people.
Your Majesty.
She is the Crown Princess,
while I am
a fake Crown Prince.
Do flowers bloom in lunar December?
I saw Shiyi's wound in her hand.
If Your Majesty wants to have the support of
the Yang family and Zhangsun family,
then do not agitate her anymore
before the conferment.
I have only one daughter.
Everything I do is for her.
Lady Cui Wenjun.
She doesn't believe me.
She has been living in the royal mansion for many years.
It's impossible that she would believe in such a short while
that the
royal mansion rebelled against you
If Your Majesty does not have enough patience,
why do you force her to stay in the palace?
I know my daughter the best.
Leave her be for several days.
She will figure it out.
I understand.
Honored Concubine ate a lot in the morning.
She watched the snow in the yard
for an hour.
She also ordered the servants to find a ladder,
intending to go up to the roof of the side palace hall to watch the snow.
But she was stopped by
Lady Li.
As Cui Wenjun said,
she will come to her senses slowly.
Ultimately,
a mother would know their daughter best.
Clean the roof of the side palace hall
and have the Royal Guards stay guard.
Let her watch the snow if she wants to.
From today on, as long as she doesn't go out of the palace,
she can do anything she likes.
Yes.
The royal army is back.
Why do you stay in Pingyin?
Flooding of the Jiang State.
The fierce battle in the Shuo State.
Six expeditions to the Dai State.
They all forgot your deeds.
They only remember you were upright, handsome,
and were praised by the people
which threatened them.
I'm here to send the news of victory.
I heard that you didn't sleep well
for more than ten days for it.
Congratulations on the complete victory.
[Throughout my life, I've never let anyone down, but Eleven.]
All your life you had no wife and no children.
And for what?
Your Majesty.
His Majesty ordered that
you can't meet the Honored Concubine.
He became the emperor because of my family.
Don't you know that?
Get out!
The Wushui branch migrated southward secretly.
My father sent troops
to trap them within the border.
No one knows this
besides His Majesty and me.
Your family name is very prestigious
among the scholars.
If your family moves southward,
Beichen will truly perish.
Why do I tell you about this?
Perhaps I want to
threaten you with the lives
of the Cui family,
because I'm afraid you would kill
Liu Zixing on your wedding day.
If so, I wouldn't be able to become the empress.
Or because
we were friends
for a night.
If I were you,
no matter how painful it is,
I must know the whole truth.
Thanks.
In the past,
no Honored Concubine
has had such a grand conferring ceremony.
Others don't know
His Majesty's heart,
but I, as his wet nurse,
knows that he cares very much about you.
You'll be busy for a whole day tomorrow.
Please sleep early.
-Please.
Please.
Everyone.
Lady Cui Wenjun.
It has been a long time since we last met.
General Yang is as strong as before.
Today, Honored Concubine Cui will be conferred with the title.
It's truly something joyous.
Thank you, General Zhangsun.
Though, she's not conferred with the title of empress.
Even if the Jin family has the title of empress,
they can't hold on to it for long.
In our eyes, only Honored Concubine Cui
deserves the position.
-Yeah.
Generals, please come with me to the palace.
Please.
-Please.
It's not until today that I truly think
I will marry you.
Lady Cui Wenjun.
I want to have a word with her Honored Concubine alone.
Yes.
Your father appeared in my dream last night.
He had never shouted at me
from the day when he married me
to when I gave birth to you
and to when he was forced
to leave.
But last night,
he blamed me.
He blamed me for sending you to the palace.
He said if you stayed in Zhousheng Chen's royal palace,
you would have lived a free life.
Shiyi,
I was wrong.
I am sorry.
Mr. Huan is waiting for you in Nanxiao.
When you reach the south,
do not turn back.
Mother,
please forgive my disobedience.
[Chengming Gate]
Outside the gate of Great Xia,
there are over 2,000 scholars of well-known families
from places outside the capital.
They are waiting to kowtow to Your Highness.
Greetings, Honored Concubine Cui!
The Prince of Pingqin is waiting for you
behind the scholars.
When they kowtow to you later,
you only need to
run out along the middle path.
The scholars dare not stop you as they don't know about the truth.
The generals and soldiers are all my trusted subordinates.
Today, I will fight a way out
for you.
His Majesty has issued a proclamation.
Honored Concubine Cui was born into a noble family
and has the support of scholars.
Today, she will be conferred the title of Honored Concubine.
People in Beichen are allowed to
pay their respects to her outside the city gate.
Greetings, Honored Concubine.
When Miss Cui runs out later,
we will rush in.
Got it.
Miss Cui.
Why is Miss Cui going back?
She doesn't want to get us into trouble.
Why is the Honored Concubine going up to the palace gate?
I guess she wants to see
the people in the city more clearly.
As a woman,
It's a great honor for her
to be able to go up to the city gates
and be worshiped by the people.
Mom, I know
you want to save me
with your own life.
But I can't escape.
I can't let you die for me,
nor can I put
nearly 1,000 family members in Qinghe County into trouble.
♪The horse's hooves sound on the battlefield♪
♪I am griping a great ambition in my hand♪
I, Yang Shao,
will see you off.
♪I am willing to stick to a ray of light for a lifetime♪
♪Never wish to have my fame spread far and wid♪
Since I went to the Nanchen Royal Mansion,
my master had given me lessons
♪Never wish to be the unmatched in the world♪
while my senior brothers and sisters cared about me.
I have never been able to return the favor.
Now my master has died unjustly
♪Half of my life is spent guarding the frontier♪
and my senior brothers and sisters have been killed.
My enemy is near to me but I can't kill them.
♪Never regret it♪
It is already painful enough.
I really can't marry him.
♪I got ambitions in the palm of my hand♪
I'm sorry for letting you down, mother.
Thank you for raising me up.
Please allow me to
give up my family name Cui.
Please remove my name from the family book.
Thus,
there is no unfilial daughter in the Cui family.
♪I am willing to stick to a ray of light for a lifetime♪
Shiyi
is just Eleven of the Nanchen Royal Mansion.
I haven't figured out how to teach you.
Because you're the first disciple
I accepted seriously.
When I acknowledged you as my master,
I couldn't call you Master.
I will make it up today.
♪I swear to take the burden to protect my homeland♪
Master.
When I come back next time,
try to call me Master, okay?
You may also call me
Zhousheng Chen.
I've liked someone
♪The sun and moon know my heart♪
since my childhood.
I've never mentioned him to anyone else
besides my mother.
I dare not tell others.
♪There will be a grand scene of prosperity♪
♪I don't expect people to praise me, and I just want to have a clear conscience♪
Nanchen Royal Army,
from its chief commander
to every soldier,
are all loyal and devoted to
serving the state and people.
God will uphold justice and punish the evil.
The injustice Nanchen Royal Army suffered
will be cleared someday.
Zhousheng Chen,
I'm here to marry you.
If we meet again in the next life,
hope you can come to marry me.
Will you?
I will take your silence
as a yes.
Eleven!
♪The shadow lingers, the sudden downpour comes♪
♪Seen long waiting♪
♪Picked up a dream, coming for whom♪
♪My concern is put on the inkstone♪
♪Can't bear it, my heart is burning♪
♪The dependence I feel♪
♪I'm suffering with you♪
♪Suffered so much from this sea of pain♪
♪I can leap down for you♪
♪Stain my painful love red♪
♪The rivers and mountains, the ostentatious world♪
♪Swords and horses, leave the dust of this world behind♪
♪Stories scatter like smoke and flowers♪
♪The snow falling, the sand flying♪
♪It's hard to leave him unattached♪
Shiyi!
What happened to Shiyi?
Miss...Miss Cui.
Tell me!
Miss Cui jumped off
the city gate.
General.
[The third year, Emperor Dongling used the reason that Jin Zhen'er had given birth to a baby]
[to invite Jin Rong to the palace and ambushed him.]
You...
[After Jin Rong died,]
[Emperor Dongling overtook Honored Concubine Cui as the empress after her death.]
[In order to build a good relation with Nanxiao, Princess Xinghua asked to marry there herself.]
[Not long after that, vassals from around the world launched an offensive and the Central state is helpless.]
[Emperor Dongling is worried and outrageous.]
[And He died in the Palace in the Central State without a son.]
[Three years later, General Zhangsun Jie and Yang Shao negotiated a peace treaty,]
[to support Liu Zizhen as the emperor and help him establish the capital in the Central State.]
Hail!
Long live the emperor!
Hail once more!
Kowtow!
[Western State]
You don't want revenge anymore?
His Highness was right.
One seeks vengeance as he can't let it go.
I have let it go.
Feng Qiao,
bids you farewell.
Please take care, Advisor Xie!
[Decades years later]
General-in-chief, let me help you.
Leave.
Yes.
The generals have left.
Even General Xie wouldn't stay?
I don't have any families
in the Western State.
Why would I stay?
General-in-chief.
This is...
No need to introduce me.
Yes.
This is my old friend.
He's about to travel far
and has come here to offer incense.
It seems
you have a close relationship with our temple.
Yeah.
I don't feel safe
if I don't come here before departure.
[Azure Dragon Temple]
This place has been abandoned for a long time.
♪Maybe it's the snow falling without a sound♪
It'll be a good deed if we can rebuild it.
We did some surveying just now.
♪Maybe it's the flower in the mirror without a trace♪
With this place as the axis,
a gate and halls could be built there.
♪I've seen all the scenes of the passing years♪
Front yard.
Back yard.
Around it we can build
♪They're not as good as you, not as good as you♪
Hall of Four Great Heaven Kings.
Hall of Ten Judges of Hell
♪There is grace in your eyebrows♪
and an Arhat Hall.
♪I'll spend my whole life looking for it♪
♪Don't blame me for the sporadic sweet talk♪
Yun.
♪I wake up from my dreams and I'm even colder♪
Master, let's go in.
♪My heart that can't stand being away from love♪
♪Hides nothing from you♪
[Azure Dragon Temple]
♪The scene I look down for♪
♪gets clear after saying goodbye♪
♪every glimpse means missing you♪
♪even if to be a stranger to you♪
♪Seen a mediocre person all my life♪
[Shiyi]
♪I just want you won't feel sad when looking back♪
♪when everything is calm♪
♪I can see who's under the moon♪
♪Turns out we've already been destined♪
[Feel happy to be with you.]