[Live Surgery Room]
[Adapted from a novel by Qidian,
an imprint of China Literature]
["Live Surgery Room" by Zhenxiong Chumo]
[Episode 6]
[People Who Mend. Emergency TIPS Surgery]
[TIPS: transjugular intrahepatic
portosystemic shunt]
Ms. Su.
Has the fever gone down yet?
Ready for surgery.
OK.
Mr. Lin.
Let Dr. Zheng take over for you.
I've done
hundreds of choledochotomy operations.
This
is not a problem.
The forceps.
What's wrong with Mr. Lin today?
Isn't choledochotomy
a grade-3 surgery?
Every surgery is important
and carries risks.
The choledochotomy
and the common hepatic duct
sometimes change their shape
and structure
due to inflammatory leakage.
Once the common hepatic duct is severed,
the damage is irreversible.
Does that mean
this surgery is difficult?
But,
I can use a choledochoscope.
Clean your hands.
Mr. Lin.
Mr. Zhang
is over 90 years old.
If anything goes wrong,
our hospital can't account for it,
and it's not good for your reputation.
Mr. Lin.
Ms. Su has a point.
He is so old.
Most importantly,
we don't know
how to use choledochoscope.
I can do it.
Dr. Zhao.
Tell the patient's family.
Mr. Lin is not feeling well.
We need a new surgeon.
[Emergency, Inpatient Building,
Chest Pain Center, Trauma Center]
[Haicheng Hospital]
Go back and rest.
This surgery was a lot harder
than we thought it would be.
If Zheng Ren
can't do it,
you can come back and save the day.
Don't say that to comfort me.
People
are really conflicted sometimes.
As a doctor,
I really hope Zheng Ren
can pull off this surgery
and the patient
can get off the table safely,
but from my personal point of view,
I don't really want Zheng Ren
to succeed.
That way,
it could at least
mean that the surgery
is really difficult
and not that I'm old.
Don't think like that.
When I was young,
if I couldn't complete a procedure,
I sat outside like this
and waited for someone inside
to save the day.
I vowed then
that one day,
I would be the one
to save the day.
And then,
I really became
that one.
Because of the old directors'
shaky hands
and outdated skills,
something like that,
I was called in to take that over.
I felt really good
at that time.
It's been 30 years.
The cycle has begun again.
The person
with shaky hands and backward skills
is me now.
Congratulations to Mr. Zheng
for completing the surgery.
[Emergency. Inpatient]
Morning, Ms. Su.
Morning.
[Nurse Station]
[General Unit]
First signs of success.
He.
See you later.
Thank you, Feng.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[Chang Feng MIO]
Explain.
[Xiao: Happy with Miss Hua]
This is Hua Yingying,
Chang Feng's North China GM, right?
Is she close to your wife?
One of the things I agree with most
about Bu's management
of Haicheng Hospital is
that our doctors
are strictly prohibited from dealing
with medical representatives.
That's right, Ms. Su.
I didn't.
Who brought you here just now?
Actually,
I was suddenly
called for an operation,
but the bus was late.
Then I ran into Feng,
so he brought me here.
No kickbacks?
No.
Absolutely not.
Go on.
[My baby is a real money killer.]
Your daughter's special class costs
tens of thousands of a year.
Your mortgage payment
is tens of thousands.
And your wife will stock up
on tens of thousands of yuan worth of
goods for her WeChat Business.
He Qian.
I didn't pay you
such a high salary.
Ms. Su.
Didn't you
make a ranking?
I've been involved
in over 1,300 surgeries last year.
Some patients complained
that you took a bonus from them.
Which...
Which patient?
There seem to be many of them.
No, Ms. Su.
I didn't get a bonus.
Sorry, I did,
but it's complicated.
You're fired.
[1. Zheng Ren. Interventional Department.
Overall rating: 98]
[Surgical success rate: 90.6]
Okay, I get it.
[1. Zheng Ren. Interventional Department.
Overall rating: 98]
[Surgical success rate: 90.6]
Ms. Su, let me explain.
The patient's family is wrong.
You need to investigate.
- Ms. Su.
- Get out!
- Ms. Su!
I've been in the O.R. 24 hours a day
all these years.
I've worked hard
even if I didn't get the credit.
You can't do this to me.
I can.
Mr. Lin.
Ms. Su.
An operation needs He Qian.
Find another one.
He's fired.
Why?
He broke hospital rules
and had dealings with a medical rep.
They drove him here.
He's a veteran
of Anesthesiology.
A skilled worker
and a hard worker.
What kind of doctor
can't work hard?
A verbal dismissal is ineffective.
Go prepare for the surgery.
I'll talk to Ms. Su.
OK.
Stop.
Ms. Su.
You're the most data-oriented person.
He came in first place
in anesthesiology
on that list you made.
Do you really need to fire him
for taking a ride?
And for bribery.
What, Mr. Lin?
Do you have proof?
Prove it,
and we'll deal with it
according to the rules.
I won't sign
without proof.
Mr. Lin.
Go wash your face.
Don't let the youngsters laugh at you.
Go prepare for the operation. I'm here.
Stop.
Mr. Lin.
Are you going to protect him?
Yes.
What if I decided to fire him?
We'll go together.
Please don't.
As Vice President,
if I can't dissuade
the President's insistence,
defend my colleagues'
legitimate rights and interests,
or call a halt
to the existing
absurd reforms,
what's the point of me
being the Vice President?
Good.
Present your resignation letter
with his.
Ms. Su.
Mr. Lin.
I'm not worth
all this.
She'll regret it.
What's going on?
The patient was vomiting at home.
He's getting a blood transfusion.
Mr. Pan?
Mr. Pan vomited blood in the afternoon.
C.T. shows
that it's due to cirrhosis of the liver.
I'm afraid of making a mistake,
so I asked you to come over.
Hemorrhagic shock.
Hepatitis B-related
decompensated cirrhosis.
Yes.
Also persistent ascites, pleural fluid,
and electrolyte metabolism disorder.
I saw he's had
a splenectomy
and portal vein dissection.
Yes.
In the ambulance,
we're going conservative.
Three sets
of intravenous hemostatic drugs
and oral ortho-renal ice saline.
Three sets of hemostatic drugs.
That's a lot.
They didn't dare to add more.
Not only may it be ineffective,
but it will also be even more difficult
if there are complications
such as cerebral
or cardiac infarction.
What else can we do now?
There are only two treatments.
One is splenectomy.
Mr. Pan has already had it.
The other one
is
TIPS.
TIPS?
It's an interventional operation.
Call Zheng Ren.
You're here.
Have a seat.
Start with the information.
The patient is Pan Shihai.
He vomited blood this morning.
Hepatitis B-related
decompensated cirrhosis.
He's had a splenectomy
and portal vein dissection.
[Hospitalization Records]
We are
recommending TIPS.
His cirrhosis
was caused by drinking.
Yes.
Dad,
why did you
pick cactus?
Because cactus
relieves me of stress.
Doctors
are very stressed.
We need to have all kinds
of ways to de-stress.
Some choose alcohol.
Some choose cigarettes.
Like Dad's teacher.
He loved wine.
When he was young,
he was a hard worker.
He operated every day and never rested.
Let me ask you one question.
Was Pan Shihai there
when Li Aifang was operated?
Yes.
What do you think, Zheng Ren?
Can you do this surgery?
For this surgery,
you'll be my assistant.
Me?
Why?
I guide you.
Try to learn something.
What?
Haven't you been
practicing interventions?
Who said that?
The computer records
in the virtual operating room.
What?
You dare to challenge yourself
on the computer
but not in the real world?
Why don't I dare?
I'll show you
that Su Yun is better
than Lin Ge
and that any surgery can be done
after I watch it once.
OK.
Prepare for the operation.
Yun.
Wait a minute.
What?
Are you really going to operate?
Are you afraid I won't make it?
I may not be able to use a scalpel,
but micro guidewire is not a problem.
Are you transferring
to the Interventional Department too?
I just want to do the surgery.
You know that.
I've always wanted to do surgery.
Okay.
Then just do it.
Zheng Ren is there for you.
Hua.
No wonder Lin Ge is angry with you.
Do you know
how humiliating your words are
for a doctor?
He feels humiliated
because he doesn't care
about the patients.
When the patient saved
by Zheng Ren is Mr. Pan,
will you still feel humiliated?
You'll only be grateful
and glad that he's here.
During TIPS,
once a patient
inhales vomited blood,
it can be fatal.
Let's be careful.
Jugular vein puncture.
Catheterization.
You can do it, right?
Don't worry.
I've done it many times.
His cirrhosis
was caused by drinking.
Yes.
Doctors
are stressed.
We need to have all kinds
of ways to de-stress.
Like Dad's teacher.
He loved wine.
He didn't have many good friends
or teachers.
We didn't deserve it.
Done.
Puncture needle.
I read about this procedure
in a textbook.
Everyone agrees
that hepatic vein portal vein puncture
is difficult to accomplish.
It's a little off.
It was a failure.
But it's normal.
It's only the first puncture.
Xiaofeng, assist me.
Prevent him from inhaling blood.
Mr. Pan is still vomiting blood.
Irritation of this biological nature
cannot be avoided artificially.
We can only
maneuver quickly
while the patient is vomiting.
Now.
It's done.
Retain the stent.
Covered or uncovered?
Covered.
Why?
Because it prevents
short-term embolic plugging.
Doesn't that
demand more of you?
He inhaled vomit.
Come on, the aspirator.
Don't do it now.
Give me ten seconds.
Blood oxygen's dropping, Zheng Ren.
Why don't we aspirate the vomit first?
Zheng Ren.
Mr. Pan is dying.
[Boundless Medicine]
Let me ask you one question.
Was Pan Shihai there
when Li Aifang was operated?
Yes.
Zheng Ren, come on.
Zheng Ren.
Dad.
What are your rules for being a doctor?
[Boundless Medicine]
Saving lives always comes first.
It's there.
Su Yun.
It's done.
Come on. Aspirate the vomit.
Surgery completed.
Nicely done.
It's so exciting
for me
to see
such wonderful TIPS.
[Haicheng Hospital]
Saving lives
always comes first.
[7 messages from 2 contacts]
[Chang Yue]
Peng Jia was diagnosed
with caffeine overdose.
OK, I lost.
When do you want to drink?
Right now.
Eight o'clock, same place.
You probably won't drink
half as much as I can tonight.
I won't take people like you
who can't eat four dishes
at a meal seriously.
[Fang Lin]
Hey, Fang.
How's it going?
Is there anything
I can't find out?
Everyone at Nanhai No. 3 Hospital
says Zheng Ren is great.
He's known to be a hard worker.
He's desperate when it comes to surgery.
Everyone thinks he deserves to be good.
No wonder he's amazing.
After all, he's an orphan.
He's on his own.
He's an orphan?
That's right.
Oh, by the way, I have a gossip.
About his father.
His dad's name is Miao, and his is Ren.
Make the two together. Get anything?
His dad is a doctor too?
His name is Zheng Miao?
No, he took his mom's last name.
His dad's name is Chen Miao.
Zheng Ren.
Miao Shou Ren Xin.
[*Skillful and merciful]
How interesting.
[Boundless Medicine]
[Chen Miao]
[Digital Archives Management System]
[Chen Miao, Li Aifang, Pan Shihai,
Calf amputation, car accident]
[Serial Car Accidents at Haicheng.
Misdemeanor doctor saves the rich first]
[Unable to cope with public pressure,
doctor jumps to his death]
[Chen Miao]
Chen Miao.
[Pan Shihai, Li Aifang
Huang Aguo, Bu Ruotian, Su Li]
[Pan Shihai]
Come here.
You said you'd beat me today.
This is all you got?
If I wasn't in a bad mood,
do you think
you'd still
be sitting here watching me?
Are you hesitating about transferring
to the Interventional Department?
Interventional Department.
Why should I go there?
I have a friend.
Not really a friend.
We didn't know each other that well.
But as we got to know each other,
I thought he was a good man.
A very good man.
Suddenly one day,
I found out a secret about him.
He showed up
with a purpose.
I can't read him.
I don't know
if I should continue to trust him.
If it were you,
would you?
Everyone has secrets.
Some secrets
can only be borne by their owners.
When that secret is told,
your relationship
will change.
If it were me,
I'd figure out
if I could handle the change.
If I could,
I'd say it out.
If I couldn't,
I wouldn't.
Yue.
What's your secret?
Tell me.
I've never told you,
but...
But I studied medicine
because of you.
You're so arrogant.
What is it
that makes you willing
to put all your passion into it?
I didn't hold back,
so I looked.
I realized
you could see the whole starry sky
while I
could only see
a little dust close by.
Maybe
I can't be a trailblazer
like you,
but I can clean up the dust
right in front of me
to allow sick people to breathe.
That's what I'm studying medicine for.
So,
I've always had one thing
to say to you.
Thank you, Su Yun.
Thank me?
For what?
You can't beat me,
can you?
Come on, keep drinking.
Come on.
[Emergency]
Yue.
Yun.
What's wrong?
Acute alcohol poisoning?
He said he wanted
to drink with me until death.
There's nothing I can do about it.
[Bu]
I've been in Haicheng Hospital
for more than ten years.
Thanks to you
and your father
for caring for me.
Now,
your father's retired
and doesn't care.
You're not here, either.
Haicheng Hospital has changed.
It's good that you're not here.
I'd be embarrassed
if you were here.
Bye.
Bu.
Hello, Ms. Su.
Hello.
Hua.
I heard that a dozen directors
along with Lin Ge
are pressurizing you.
What are you going to do now?
Don't worry.
Different emperors
have different ministers.
I'm prepared for this.
I've looked out
for good doctors before.
I just need to recruit new people.
But Lin Ge
has a lot of VIP clients.
So what?
Every hospital
has its own niche.
Since Mr. Pan retired,
Haicheng Hospital's orthopedics department
has been going down.
It's because it
doesn't have the unique skills anymore.
But now,
We have
late liver intervention embolization,
as well
as TIPS.
From now on, Haicheng Hospital
is going to be known
for its famous doctors.
Does Zheng Ren give you confidence?
Yes.
That's why
the Star Doctor Team exists.
[Resignation list]
I can talk to them.
Not all of them may stay,
- but at least...
- No need.
Just stall for a while.
Stall?
They quit a little early.
I haven't found
other candidates yet.
So,
stall for a while.
You want to fire them all?
That's not what I had in mind.
I've racked my brain
and referenced national
and international success stories
to make them competitive
instead of relying on their past credits
and waiting to retire.
This is the age
of transparent information
about applications.
If we don't keep up with the times
or make changes,
we are doomed to be out.
You're right.
So
I gave them a chance,
but they didn't appreciate it
and questioned my training of Zheng Ren.
Is Zheng Ren the one
they want to get rid of?
No.
It's me.
You still
won't give up on the hospital?
I'm not someone
who runs away from things.
From the day I decided to reform,
I knew
these old staff would cause trouble.
I trained Zheng Ren
and fully supported
the Interventional Department
for this day.
As long as Zheng Ren is here,
I'm not afraid of them making trouble
or leaving.
Speaking of which,
I'd like to thank you
for giving me
such a good student.
Hua.
Zheng Ren is Chen Miao's son.
What?
♪Like soil,
we clutch at the hope of roots♪
♪Remove the white halo,
he is mortal too♪
♪In each other's eyes♪
♪We forget sorrows, joys,
and separations♪
♪What is that in your eyes?♪
♪Too many regrets
left behind with no answers♪
♪Life is fleeting,
like the willow's seeds♪
♪We fly high yet drift far away♪
♪Time is fleeting,
but we have a long way to go♪
♪Love alone is the dawn's light♪
♪Breaking through the hardships♪
♪Sometimes whispers beckon from afar♪
♪Even if we stand close to each other♪
♪With arms clutching
to the vine between us♪
♪Against the pitch black♪
♪Only by holding on to what's dear♪
♪Can we let go without remorse♪
♪Life is fleeting,
like the willow's seeds♪
♪We fly high yet drift far away♪
♪Time is fleeting,
but we have a long way to go♪
♪When stubbornness turns to faith♪
♪We march bravely on♪
♪Life is short,
like the firework's splendor♪