Live Surgery Room
[Adapted from the novel
"Live Surgery Room" by Zhenxiong Chumo]
[Published by Qidian,
an imprint of China Literature]
[Haicheng Everyday]
Hello, everyone.
Today,
the cooks for a steel factory
mistakenly used nitrite
as table salt,
resulting in 236 workers hospitalized
for food poisoning
after lunch.
The workers
have now been treated.
We believe they'll get better soon.
This has been Haicheng Everyday.
I'm Sun Zeli,
reporting in from Haicheng Hospital
with the latest updates.
Do you feel better?
How do you feel?
It's quite hard
to be a healthcare worker.
Yes.
Not everyone
can be a healthcare worker.
Let's head back and edit the footage
and write them a good article.
Ms. Hua.
I heard you
took the storage's Methylene Blue
to Haicheng Hospital.
And then?
And...
they all got better
after being injected with it.
I'm not asking about this.
You brought out something vital
during an important moment.
Ms. Su...
She paid.
Who cares about the money?
It's a great chance,
yet you wasted it.
Fool.
Still, Ms. Hua,
I saved a lot of people today.
Is it better?
How is it over here?
Eat slowly.
[Emergency]
[Bu Ruotian]
I saw the news report.
Congratulations.
Li,
you're doing much better than I did.
[Episode 13]
[Mass Incident II - Hysteria]
Why are you laughing so loudly?
Yun, you're up.
Show it to me.
Was it that chaotic then?
Why do I look so haggard?
Wait, Yun.
It was a little messy at first,
but through
your heroic guidance,
you were in control of everything.
Later on are all moments of your glory.
Is that so?
[Many workers suffering
from nitrite shock]
I have a new idea.
You want to use
an interventional needle?
I look like a dog running here
while you call that moment of my glory?
How cute.
It's really glorious later.
Later on...
The series of injections...
All were filmed?
It was very cool.
Look.
Cool, right?
Dr. Su,
what have you learned from this rescue?
Dr. Su!
Look, you fainted.
Yun.
It was you.
No, no.
Let me teach you again
how to administer first aid.
How is it done?
Wait.
No way.
I can't.
Did you hear something?
What is it?
Bad news, Dr. Su!
We have another wave
of poisoned patients.
Why are there more? I...
Get up now.
Make way.
Hurry.
Move aside.
Why aren't their faces blue?
Other than vomiting,
are there any other symptoms?
None for now.
Zhou,
prepare the saline drips.
Label the vomit samples.
Tell the lab to hurry up
with the bacteria cultures.
- Hurry.
- Yes.
- Hold on.
- How many?
Around 50.
500!
Open the door, 500!
Stop sleeping, 500!
What? It's the middle of the night.
Wake up.
I know you're tired.
I'm tired too,
but reality is harsh.
Left then right.
We have another wave of patients.
What?
Put on the left side first, then right.
Put it on yourself.
I said, we have another wave
of patients,
and the number has doubled.
It's not nitrite poisoning this time.
Be there in ten minutes.
[Emergency]
Grandma.
Grandma, why are you sick?
Talk to me.
Doctor,
save my grandma.
- Let me through.
- Save my grandma.
Hurry.
- Grandma.
- How are you?
Hold on.
The doctor's here.
Can you hear me?
Slowly.
Zhou Litao.
Ms. Su.
What's going on?
They're family members
of the poisoned workers.
They've all been vomiting.
- Coming.
- The first was an old woman.
She had severe vomiting.
Then, the factory called us.
They say more family members
are vomiting.
Where's Yun?
Looking at the scans with Zheng.
Here, paper towels.
Slowly.
How's the situation?
Ms. Su.
Is it linked to the nitrite?
Those vomiting patients
don't have blue-gray skin.
Also,
they live in the family dorms
where most of them cook for themselves.
That's why their food
isn't the same as the workers'.
What are the test results?
We've done everything
from blood tests and lung function tests
to digestive tests.
Nothing unusual was found.
What do the other hospitals say?
They're also looking for the cause.
I hear the higher-ups
now know of this matter.
Could it
be a new viral outbreak?
Wouldn't all of us
be in danger then?
Hua,
should we consider
an emergency mobilization
to establish a major epidemic
command center?
The old woman's lung scans are out.
It's not the respiratory tract.
Nor is it the digestive tract.
Could it
be a bacterial infection?
No.
The scans are fine.
But that old woman
is weak from vomiting.
We've just been notified
over 100 more family members
of the workers
are showing the same symptoms.
How are the staff in contact
with the patients?
No abnormalities yet.
I'll head back.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Hey, Mr. Pan.
We're already preparing.
Okay. Got it.
The city mayor has instructed experts
from the guide groups to rush over
to consult with the hospitals
so that we can
find out the cause of the illness.
The guide group's leader
wants our hospital
to retrieve samples from the scene
for lab testing.
Yun,
transfer the vomiting patients
into the Emergency Department.
Treat them in quarantine.
Okay.
Before we find the cause
of their illness,
we'll try to stay in control
until the experts arrive.
Emergency Department staff
will have to work hard.
Be on shift for 24 hours.
No one is to go in or out
as they please.
Yes.
Su Yun,
go with Chang Yue
to the patients' homes.
Check their food.
Perhaps we'll have some new discoveries.
I leave the Emergency Department to you.
Be quick.
Yue, let's go.
Hello?
Li,
I heard from Mr. Pan
the mass incident has worsened.
We're searching for the cause.
Don't forget to come back
for your follow-up in five days.
I remember. See you in five days.
See you in five days.
Don't move.
Ms. Su,
you can't move right now.
Get a stretcher
and send her to Emergency.
Emergency?
Why to the Emergency?
I suspect
you suffered a sudden heart attack.
500? Speak.
What? Heart attack?
Get operating.
I'll handle the procedure once I'm back.
Hey, Zheng Ren.
Please.
Who has a heart attack?
Hua.
Her heart had no issues.
It must be due to exhaustion.
Hua is too stubborn.
She could have
chosen a more carefree life.
Do you know
why I call her Hua?
The hospital
is the most painful place on earth.
Despairing patients,
stunned family members,
exhausted doctors,
and haggard nurses.
When you're there,
the only thing left in the mind
is to keep living.
Keep living, not live.
I don't just want to survive.
I want to live.
That's right.
It's why
I must doll myself up.
I want everyone to know
what it's like to live.
Only by seeing the beauty in life
can you endure the torment of living.
Don't worry.
She'll be fine.
It's a family of three.
The place is so small.
There's not even a room divider.
How do they live?
Family dorms are all like this.
They just need shelter.
We need to find what poisoned them
to find the right cure.
Don't miss out on anything.
Keys.
Have you found anything?
No. Just some samples.
What about you?
Nothing.
Hello?
I see.
Okay.
What is it?
You tell me.
I can handle it.
Two out of three coronary arteries
are blocked.
The operation was a success.
Don't worry.
You talk so slowly
that has me scared.
Come on. Next place.
[Operating]
Two out of three coronary arteries
are blocked.
Thank goodness we made it in time.
If we had been slower,
Ms. Su wouldn't be able
to meet the experts.
I'm wide awake.
Ms. Su,
I did say we found out in time, right?
When you're in surgeries,
do you also talk
to the patients?
I'm livening up the atmosphere.
Ms. Su,
do you want to install stents?
Don't install stents.
I feel much better now.
When can I get up?
Ms. Su,
your injuries may be light
but you're not in the clear yet.
You can't do that.
So many people outside are waiting
to be transferred in,
yet I'm lying here.
I even waste your time.
I can't accept it.
Ms. Su, if you don't want
to install stents,
we'll send you to the ward soon.
I have to be hospitalized?
You don't want the third artery
to be blocked too, right?
Don't jinx it.
Okay.
How's the situation outside?
Keep me updated.
Do you hear me?
We hear you.
Have you slept?
I'm not tired.
I'm not tired too.
Everyone,
I come from Beida Hospital.
I'm the deputy leader
of the guide group,
Kong Yumin.
I'm here in Haicheng
to lead the group
on the mass poisoning.
Please speak up in order
to express your views.
Let's brainstorm
and find the truth as soon as we can.
We have all the samples. Let's go.
I went through our list
of samples to collect.
Over a hundred individuals
were vomiting.
Other than water,
there's nothing in their food
that matches with each other.
If it's a problem with the water,
it's impossible
for just one area's residents
to be poisoned.
Say,
when something big happens,
how do you think the factory
notifies all the people living here?
Call them one by one?
No need to call.
Just shout through the loudspeaker,
and everyone will know.
That's true.
How did you know?
I've lived here before.
You really don't know me well.
Let's go.
[Do not use gas]
[Medical Record]
To sum everything up,
everyone unanimously agrees
that it's food poisoning.
Well, we still need to investigate
what food it is.
Where did Zheng Ren go?
Why isn't he back yet?
I don't know.
Do you feel better now?
Vomit here.
Zheng Ren.
Well? What discoveries?
We've brought back some food.
Chang Yue is sending it to the Center
for Disease Control and Prevention
for testing.
I hear the guide group
arrived early.
How's the discussion?
I didn't sit in.
As expected of you.
I have made no other discovery.
What do we do next?
Well,
we can only use our last move.
[Su Yun: No obvious reasons found.]
[Be prepared for the worst.]
Dear leaders and experts,
let me introduce myself.
I'm Lin Ge, the Vice President
of Haicheng Hospital.
It looks like
all of our opinions
are one and the same.
If the problem
is not in the food,
then the only possibility
is a large-scale infectious disease.
Everyone,
we must always
be prepared for the worst.
To avoid any chances
of an outbreak,
Haicheng Hospital
will have all our staff
undergo quarantine
in our Emergency Department.
During this time,
we can contact each other
through the Internet.
Every day,
we'll keep you updated
on the victims' symptoms.
As for the medicine needed
and ways to diagnose a person,
we can still contact
through video conferencing
to communicate with each other.
Except for the possibility
of a large-scale viral outbreak,
as the vice president of this hospital,
I will work hard in the front lines
to serve as backup.
To avoid any uncontrollable situation.
I have a question.
What if it's an unknown viral disease?
What do we do?
We have prepared
the protective wear.
Until now,
we have
accepted 52 patients of this kind.
Haicheng Hospital,
as the isolation unit for this disease,
we will do our best
to kill the disease here.
Sir, please approve it.
Lin really
is quite dependable
when push comes to shove.
What does everyone think?
I think
that Mr. Lin has a great idea,
but
things might not
have developed so far, right?
Can we
keep searching?
What if the disease spreads?
Who will be responsible?
How about this?
If there are no objections,
the guide group
will be based in Haicheng
to fight with Haicheng Hospital
until the danger is over.
I have no objections.
Youhao Hospital
will send our medical team
to fight beside our comrades
at Haicheng Hospital.
I have no objections either.
We at Haicheng No. 5 Hospital
will also fight with everyone.
Let me make a statement.
Before we came here,
we were already prepared for this.
We have no objections either.
Please sit.
Everyone,
I trust you all
to remember
the massive outbreak
from 14 years ago, right?
Don't let your guard down.
Plan for the worst.
Fight the hardest battle.
No problem, right?
No problem.
Okay. Dismissed.
Kong, you are...
We are brothers in arms,
my old classmate.
Reject all news interviews.
Safety is our utmost priority.
But Sun Zeli
has already reported on it...
Go tell her,
that's all for now.
Also, notify everyone
to call their families
and say goodbye.
Tell them the staff can't go home
in the next few days.
Remember.
Don't let anything slip.
Okay.
Then...
Can we go back?
I don't know.
Don't be scared.
After all, we have all
done the emergency drill many times.
During the massive outbreak
14 years ago,
we couldn't make it.
So many of our seniors
gave themselves to protect us.
This time,
it's our turn
to protect the next generation.
For our family.
For family.
[Vice President's Office]
[Unforgivable]
[Don't let it slip even though
you may not say goodbye to your mom.]
There's a complex case.
[Honey]
I'll have to work with our daughter
to figure it out.
For the next few days,
we'll be staying in the hospital
and not going home.
Working with our baby?
That's great!
I can't believe there would be a day.
Hurry. Take this chance
to repair your relationship.
Lin Yuan.
Must you be a doctor?
Yes.
It's very tough.
What job isn't tough?
It's also very dangerous.
What job isn't dangerous?
Because I'm a doctor,
I don't want you
to continue down this path.
Quit then.
I'll believe you
when you're not a doctor.
You can't even do it.
Why should I give up?
It's not fair.
I'm scared.
What are you scared of?
You were afraid
we would die here together,
leaving Mom alone.
Hello?
Baby,
is that you?
I just knew
you would call me.
Your dad told me
you'll be working together.
If you team up,
you'll be invincible.
Baby,
once you come back victorious,
I'll make your favorite dishes.
Wonton.
I want wonton.
Mom.
Okay.
I'll make you wonton.
Get back to work with your dad.
[Mom]
Meimei,
study hard.
Prepare for the semester exams.
Once I get home,
I'll give you a huge present.
Okay.
I'll end the call
and eat my meal.
Bye.
[I'll be working overtime
at the hospital for a week.]
Hey, Mom.
Don't worry.
I can rest after this period.
I will be able to go on that date.
Take good care of yourself.
Relax.
The hospital has a lot of girls
who like me.
Okay.
I'm hanging up.
He's burning up.
Let me take a look.
Don't rush.
Test him again.
Remember to drink more water, okay?
I'm sorry.
I asked you to help, but...
I'm already here,
so let's work hard.
If anything happens to us,
you can still save me.
I can't go back
and risk my mom, right?
Look.
It's not bad.
My next month's grant...
Don't worry.
It will be fine.
I...
I suddenly thought,
why do the studious type like you
insist on being a doctor
instead of anything else?
You can't eat or sleep well.
You stay up late and work late.
There's even a risk of infection.
Also,
we'll meet family members like you
who are unreasonable.
Actually,
being alive is already
quite hard to do.
We work hard
because we want more people
to live on
in good health.
Aren't you the same?
Does anything else hurt?
Remember to keep your mask on.
Zheng Ren.
You shouldn't come out.
Go home and rest.
Do you have anything
you want to say to me?
I pledge myself
to the medical profession,
to respect my mentors
and uphold the ethics of the profession.
I will do everything in my power
to eliminate diseases
and aid in good health.
Forever refining my skills,
never content.
The patient
always comes first.
Sixteen years ago,
Haicheng couldn't
properly handle the massive outbreak.
This time is different.
Please witness
this day for yourself.
[Rescue Command Center]
[Sincerity in healing,
kindness and morality first]
[Haicheng Hospital]
[Meeting Room]
Nothing wrong with this.
Well, comrades?
Any new discoveries?
There are no problems at all
except for the nausea.
I believe it's likely to be hysteria.
Hysteria?
After a whole day of discussion,
that's it?
What else?
What ideas do you have?
Either way, it can't be hysteria.
Why can't it be?
Hysteria is a mental illness.
It's a mental disorder
that makes them ill
due to a conflict between reality
and what they think
through suggestions
by others or themselves.
Prodigies are one of a kind.
You recite that bit so easily.
However, that's only if they're alone.
It doesn't happen
in groups of two or three,
let alone in over 100 people at once.
Of course it does.
It's mass hysteria.
What?
Summer of 1518.
It happened in Strasbourg.
Out of nowhere,
the dancing plague appeared.
Do you remember?
No.
A woman started to dance
down the street.
After four days of dancing,
the number of people dancing
reached 30 to 40.
Within a month,
over 400 in the city
had started dancing.
The entire city was congested.
It sounds fake.
It's not fake.
Mass hysteria
mainly happens in schools and factories,
places with strict rules
and high stress.
Have you watched Forrest Gump before?
I have.
Many people started running
alongside Forrest.
Don't you find that strange?
That was an artistic expression.
I don't think so.
Sometimes,
a powerful psychological suggestion
and certain factors
could lead to strange situations.
For example?
An animation.
You watch animated shows?
Animation?
At 6:30 PM
on 16 December
1997,
a lot of people
were watching the 38th episode
of the latest hit animation series.
The Porygon episode.
He not only remembers the name
and which episode.
But he also knows
exactly when and what
it was shown.
At around
6:50 PM,
the screen turned very bright
from the special effects.
Then, the kids started showing symptoms
from difficulty breathing
to nausea and cramps
to hallucinations and more.
Within half an hour,
over 600 children
were sent to the hospital for treatment.
Back then, they were diagnosed
with photosensitive epilepsy.
The cause was the special effects
within the show.
That's right.
It's because
of an animation technique known
as "paka paka".
Simply put,
swapping repeatedly
between different colored lights
would create a tense atmosphere.
Just like this.
While that does not explain
why the first batch of kids
would be affected,
since everyone was watching at home
by themselves.
But the current research
is leaning toward
an example
of mass hysteria.
Listening
to your discussion
makes me feel like I studied seven years
for nothing.
Yue,
could you understand them?
Wait,
so you think this time
the families are vomiting
not because of an unknown bacteria,
but because it's mass hysteria?
Yes.
When we meet the guide group,
will you say that too?
That's the guide group.
They're the best experts in the country.
What about it?
We're all doctors.
We're all here to treat the patients.
I believe it's mass hysteria.
Argue if you disagree.
Wait.
I suddenly thought of evidence.
What evidence?
Ignore me. Go in first.
Chang Yue, come with me.
Currently,
we have excluded food poisoning.
All that's left are infectious diseases.
As of right now,
we've not detected any viruses.
It's not a virus.
It's mass hysteria.
You are...?
He's Zheng Ren,
the head
of the Interventional Department
at Haicheng Hospital.
The young know no fear.
Very courageous.
Alright.
Tell us then.
Why is it mass hysteria?
I believe it's mass hysteria
because there are similar examples
in the past.
At 6:30 PM
on 16 December
1997...
Hurry.
Are you sure it can be used?
I'm certain.
I've played it before.
I'll search this side.
You search that side.
Even now, mass hysteria
is an illness
without logical explanation.
Those who research this phenomenon,
the doctors,
philosophers, and anthropologists,
have not been able to correctly
define mass hysteria.
is contagious,
but that does not mean
mass hysteria
is dreamed up by the patients.
They're not pretending to be sick,
but that doesn't mean
it is not mass hysteria.
Yes.
With modern neuroimaging technology,
we do see unusual activity
in the hysteric's brains.
They are unlike
the patients who pretend
to be sick.
Throughout the 20th century,
this situation
typically happened
among groups with strict rules.
Patients will feel nausea, dizziness,
headaches, and motility disorders.
It is extremely similar
to the situation
with the workers' families.
My speech is done.
Well...
Your approach is quite different.
Unfortunately,
medicine depends on proof.
We have proof.
This is a test result of the food found
within the residential building.
Among 94 families
and 252 ingredients,
the only ingredients used
in every family
are water and salt.
The lab results show us
that these two ingredients
are perfectly fine.
That is to say,
the chances of food poisoning
are actually the lowest.
That still does not prove
that it's mass hysteria.
The proof of mass hysteria
is right here.
A loudspeaker.
Yesterday morning,
the workers were poisoned
and sent to the hospitals for treatment.
By noon,
after the factory managers
found out it was nitrite poisoning,
they thought it important enough
to have their team
announce it
to every family living there.
They used this.
What does this have to do
with mass hysteria?
Everyone, we're all doctors here.
When we were studying,
we would think
we had the same illness
as whatever we studied.
I believe everyone here
has experienced it once.
We have never encountered
anything this massive before.
Rather, why not say you're young,
and this is for you
to learn from?
We've tried all the possibilities.
Our final conclusion
might not seem likely,
but it might be the truth.
Is it mass hysteria?
We will naturally know
in one week.
[Observation Zone]
[Recovering Zone]
How do you feel now?
I feel much better.
Slowly.
[Haicheng Hospital]
[Observation Zone, Recovery Zone]
[Office Building]
[Meeting Room]
They're here.
Just how is it?
Hurry. Don't keep us in suspense.
After seven days of isolation,
103 patients
have shown no new symptoms.
The new blood test results are also out.
No problems at all.
As per the epidemic prevention rules,
on behalf of the guide group,
I declare
that we can all leave.
- Great.
Mr. Lin,
you've worked hard.
You've worked hard as well, Dr. Lin.
500,
challenge successful.
Let's celebrate.
I don't have the time.
I have a backlog of surgeries.
Oh, you.
You're so boring.
As Hua said,
life isn't just about being alive,
you also need to live.
We want to live,
so the patient can't be alive.
Zheng, Su.
You have time, right? Let's chat.
Like soil,
we clutch at the hope of roots
After taking off the doctor coat,
he is an ordinary man too
In each other's eyes
We forget sorrows, joys,
and separations
What is that in your eyes?
Too many regrets
left behind with no answers
Life is fleeting, like fluffy catkins
We fly high yet drift far away
Time is fleeting,
but we have a long way to go
Love alone is the dawn's light
Breaking through life challenges
Sometimes, whispers beckon from afar
Even if we stand close to each other
With arms clutching
to the vine between us
Against the pitch black
Only by holding on to what's dear
Can we let go without remorse
Life is fleeting, like fluffy catkins
We fly high yet drift far away
Time is fleeting,
but we have a long way to go
When stubbornness turns to faith
We march bravely on
Life is short,
like the splendor of fireworks