[Live Surgery Room]
[Adapted from the novel
"Live Surgery Room" by Zhenxiong Chumo]
[Published by Qidian,
an imprint of China Literature]
[TAXI]
It's cardiac interventions
that make up half of the market.
Secondly, peripheral neurovascular
intervention consumables.
That special line
for Rudolph's prostate consumables
was just a waste.
You can throw it away after it's served
its purpose as a knockout.
I think Wansheng's focus
is still on the share
of cardiac catheter stents.
Integrate Changfeng and stand firm.
I'm more than familiar with Changfeng.
Just watch me.
Are you the mole?
What mole, huh?
I jumped ship.
Yesterday you were rushing me.
I thought I'd stay at Changfeng
if you succeeded.
Who knew the country's doctors
were so useless?
Lose to the foreigners.
I can't just sink with the ship, right?
I'm in a hurry.
Wait a minute.
Do you know that after Wansheng
enters the domestic market,
Changfeng will go out of business?
A lot of domestic consumables companies
are going to die.
In market competition, the strong wins.
That's very reasonable.
The consequence of it
is that China no longer has its own
consumables company or production line.
All surgical consumables
will depend on imports.
Surgical costs
will be significantly higher.
Surgery costs several times over.
More people will not be able to afford
to see a doctor.
- What's it got to do with me?
- You...!
Don't try to kidnap me with that
if you don't retweet it,
you're not a Chinese trick.
I'm just working for someone
to make a living.
Having food on the table
is the most important thing.
Hello, Mr. Peng.
Hello.
Boss.
It's no good.
Our live broadcast
of Professor Rudolph's
prostate intervention embolization
caused patriotic doctors' backlashes
for using Wansheng's consumables.
They all left comments below.
They even hacked our servers.
[How much did you get
for such betrayal?]
[Helping the foreigners to screw
our compatriots?]
[China's Best Healthcare
Interactive Platform]
Dad.
What's your vision?
Will Mind And Soul Garden become
China's Best Healthcare
Interactive Platform?
[China's Best Healthcare
Interactive Platform]
Have you eaten yet?
Wang Long said he found
a special restaurant
and wanted to take us there.
Yeah, I know.
Until the problem is solved,
I don't deserve to eat.
I'll get back to him.
I just got a call
from Director Kong of Beida.
Saying that three days after surgery,
Wang Yuanshan had bladder weakness
and urinary retention.
So, he had to continue
to wear a urinary catheter.
Really?
You were right.
He wanted another operation.
And Director Kong promised
to provide us with a place to practice.
What are you waiting for?
Let's get practicing.
Not eating?
It's alright?
I've broken up with fun
since the day I met you.
Let's go, demon of surgeries.
Seven-minute abdominal pelvic exercise.
The belly is gone.
What?
The losers haven't given up yet?
Zheng Ren, Su Yun. It's those two again?
Using a Changfeng guidewire?
Not to mention the fact that domestic
guidewires have no advantage.
Those two kids can do better
than Professor Rudolph?
What they're doing
is expanding the publicity
for Wansheng's new guidewire.
I'd love to.
Yun.
I will have my revenge.
Just you wait.
[Episode 17]
[Prostate Artery Embolization
Competition (Part 4) - Breakthrough]
Packing?
I heard you
had a good follow-up today.
You're looking good too.
Yeah.
Live in the countryside,
soaking up the sun
and working in the fields.
Working the fields?
I contracted a few acres of land.
and rented a tractor.
Cultivate and sow
my own seeds.
But,
I missed the rainy season.
This year, I'm afraid
there's no harvest.
However,
I've learned one thing.
It's not easy to be
a good farmer.
Yeah.
Sometimes
we make things look easy.
So,
do you want to help?
I'm sure
you'll have a lot of experience
by the time next spring rolls around.
Without this year's attempt,
there would be no next year's.
Same for me.
[Outpatient]
[Beida Hospital]
Today's going to be fantastic.
The great Zheng versus the great Jin.
It's exciting to think about.
And both of them
are using domestic guidewires.
Dare to challenge high-tech,
world authority.
Awesome.
There's more.
Do you know
who Zheng's patient is today?
Who?
Wang Yuanshan.
Oh, my goodness!
I thought this surgery
was hard enough.
Give Wang Yuanshan a second surgery?
If he succeeds,
he'll be famous.
If he loses,
then all the honors are gone.
Director Kong.
- Director Kong.
Hello.
Take a seat.
Director Kong.
I can't believe
Professor Rudolph's
operation failed after all.
Prostate intervention embolization
may seem unremarkable.
But it's a surgical procedure
comparable to TIPS.
The industry is still figuring it out.
Even if Rudolph's post-op patients
had complications. It's not a failure.
At best, it's a little bad.
But
it gives us a chance to catch up.
Right?
Watch these two surgeries.
Zheng's technique
is as clean as ever.
Jin Yaowu is fast too.
But I still think it's a big challenge
for them to take on Rudolph.
That's weird.
Zheng was quite fast when he did
the liver cancer intervention.
Why is he so slow today?
Compared to this,
Jin Yaowu is really fast.
The difficulty with this procedure
is not who is faster.
It's the handling
of the four branching vessels
above and below the bladder
and the adaptation
of the capillary network.
Zheng's guidewire is entering
a branch vessel of the bladder artery.
Slow down.
Zheng has stopped.
Looks like
Changfeng's guidewire he's using
has reached the limit.
Jin Yaowu is still going on.
The wire is still going on.
Rudolph super-selected a deeper spot.
Jin
is using a domestic guidewire.
I don't know
if he can get to that spot.
For Zheng,
this is not his limit.
This is the limit
of Changfeng's micro guidewire.
Wait a little longer.
Jin Yaowu has reached
the same spot as Rudolph.
That's right.
He actually used a domestic guidewire
to reach Wansheng's guidewire's spot.
Jin Yaowu is going to break through
Rudolph's spot
and go on?
Diligence makes up for talent.
Medicine is not mathematics.
It's about to stop?
But I see that Jin
wants to continue.
He stopped too.
It's been difficult.
After all,
there's a material difference.
Jin did this surgery
better than Prof. Rudolph.
That's right.
And we're using domestic guidewires.
That means
we make up for the material gap
with skill.
Right?
Director Kong.
You are a great teacher.
I haven't done anything.
It's all his effort.
But if we stop there,
we'll still have the same after-effects
as Professor Rudolph.
Chatterbox.
What's Yun doing here?
Thick guidewire.
What's with the thick guidewire?
He's using the same technique
used during Lin Jiaojiao's surgery.
But such a thick micro guidewire
will probably cause damage
to the branch blood vessels
and result in intraoperative bleeding.
Young people have grit.
He's got a lot of guts.
Jin Yaowu has finished embolizing.
Contrast agent.
Time to show some real skill.
Fish through the coral.
Fish-head,
don't be so stupid as to wear out
the coral.
I think the dumbest thing is a fish
on a straw rope.
Don't think I don't understand.
The traditional character for "su"
is the character for "grass"
plus the character for "fish".
What a bad joke!
That's amazing.
It's a miracle.
Skilled.
Who can do that?
- How many surgeries did he do
- It's almost like a machine.
to achieve this?
That's too precise.
Now.
How is that possible?
He actually overtook Rudolph's position
with Changfeng's guidewire.
Yeah.
That's the way.
A brand new technique.
Nice.
Contrast agent.
The location is fine.
Embolic agent.
Yes!
It's done.
Micro guidewire.
That's amazing. He's still going.
Here, sit.
Why is it still going on?
The surgery was a success
by all accounts.
He's not stopping.
They've opened
a second vascular network.
Still going on, Fish-head?
It's only just begun,
greenhorn.
Micro guidewire.
He's really going at it.
I don't think
Zheng's technique
is as fast as before.
But it's still...
Very agile, very flexible.
Right?
I feel like
the guidewire has grown eyes
and is becoming conscious.
Surgery's been going on for so long.
After dealing
with three arterial branches'
capillary network,
his hands are still as steady as ever.
So young, so talented.
It's been so long.
The fourth set of embolization
is also complete.
Yeah.
Oh, my!
He's super selecting the fifth.
Yes!
For preoperative 3D reconstruction,
there are six groups of coral reefs
that need to be done.
It's all finished now.
On my first day in Haicheng Hospital,
the pancreaticoduodenectomy I faced
told me one thing.
What is it?
Never rely too much on machines.
Contrast agent.
Alright.
Continue for the seventh group.
[Beida Hospital]
They're here!
Yun!
Zheng!
- You're so great, Dr. Zheng!
- That's awesome!
Awesome!
Perfect!
Good!
Zheng!
- Outstanding!
- Wonderful!
Zheng!
Excellent!
So great!
- Awesome!
- Perfection!
Good job!
That's awesome!
Amazing!
Perfection!
So amazing!
What's the prognosis
for the surgery?
Within 24 hours,
after the acute phase
of prostate necrosis and edema,
the urinary catheter can be removed.
Are you so sure you'll be able
to remove the catheter in 24 hours?
Jin.
Let's make a bet.
If we can't pull out the tube
within 24 hours,
we'll go back to Haicheng
and never come back to Beida again.
But if we do,
quit your job
and never set foot in Beida again.
Want to bet?
What's there to bet on?
You all did a great job today.
It's hard work.
Get some rest.
Let's all go home and rest.
Let's go.
Get some rest already.
You're all soaked.
It was brilliant.
It was a real eye-opener.
Yeah.
That was brilliant.
Let's go.
- Go.
- Come on.
You guys go ahead.
I was wrong.
Mr. Kong...?
As Wang Long said,
once the branch vessels
and capillary network
of the superior bladder artery
were done,
the operation will be a success.
The next steps are totally
the icing on the cake of the adventure.
Could have not taken the risk,
but he did it anyway.
Why?
Because
he's not confident?
No.
Because in Zheng Ren's eyes,
there's only surgery.
Reputation, status, future...
He does not care
about any of that.
Oh, Jin.
Diligence is important,
but the road
to the top
requires focus.
If you see too much,
you won't be able to go fast.
You and I
should reflect on that point.
So, I'm very happy with it.
Zheng.
Your surgery today
was a great success.
Did Beida
and domestic consumables
a great favor.
We need to celebrate it.
I'd like to meet you
for a meal tomorrow.
What do you think?
Mr. Li's treating us.
We must come.
That's great.
Zheng.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking
about the surgery.
It all worked out.
What's left to think about?
Still thinking about group seven
capillary network?
By the way.
Wang Long said when you did
the pre-surgical CT yesterday,
there were six groups.
Why was there another group?
I made a discovery
during the operation.
I thought there should be another.
So I gave it a try.
Validated some of my own thoughts.
Mr. Li.
If there's a suitable
liver cancer patient
or prostate patient,
please let us know.
We've discovered
a brand new guidewire
intervention technique called Zheng.
To publish a paper on the subject,
we will need more patient cases.
So Mr. Li,
please.
Alright.
We'll be waiting for your news.
No problem.
Alright.
Right, I'll let you know
when and where.
Okay.
Alright, Zheng.
I'll see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
Beida
needs a talented person like him.
Hello?
Ying.
Zheng Ren's team tackled
prostate interventional embolization
with domestic guidewire
at Beida Hospital.
What?
Domestic guidewire?
Yes.
How is that possible?
The report went out this morning.
I've sent it to your phone.
Check it out.
[Beida interventional team performing
interventional procedures]
Yeah, I'm almost out of the hospital.
I'm getting out of the hospital today.
What else is new?
What?
Zheng Ren and his guys made it?
Got it!
That brat
really made it!
I'm furious.
That's enough from you.
You're still so angry
at your age.
Dr. Zheng is great.
It's a great honor
for Haicheng Hospital.
I've heard
it's not an easy operation.
You should be
happy about that.
Yeah.
I have to be glad.
It's a good thing they're doctors
from Haicheng Hospital.
Otherwise,
I really can't do anything
about them.
Listening is one thing.
Mostly you have to watch.
Be sure to watch more videos.
How did we find the breakthrough?
It was watching videos.
Mr. Li.
Let me tell you something, Yun.
When the video of your surgery
came out,
our department
was shocked.
It's so awesome.
Here.
I must give you a toast.
Yun.
You're absolutely right.
Halfway through the meal
and he's reading.
He's so studious.
I'm not kidding you, right?
I'll learn from him.
Look at Zheng.
He's really hardworking.
Eat, but don't forget to study.
That's very diligent.
Zheng.
Have you thought
about coming to Beida?
Zheng.
Say yes. Come on.
Quick. Say yes.
Why?
Because we're Beida.
Don't you want to come to us?
Yeah.
It's Beida.
I'm sorry, Zheng.
Beida.
I've got a place for a doctorate,
if you want to come...
Don't want.
Aren't you trying to pump up the number
of surgeries for your thesis?
That's what Su Yun wants.
I'm not really interested.
But
if you have a patient,
I can always come here to operate.
I really don't get it.
Haicheng is so small,
with so few patients
and poor equipment.
Haven't you thought
about moving?
I had a deal with someone.
What kind of deal?
That's enough, Mr. Li.
Don't make it difficult for him.
I'd like a toast to you all.
Come!
Come on!
Thank you, everyone!
Cheers!
Here!
Let's drink up.
- Here, cheers.
- Here.
Let's eat.
I have eaten or drunk
so much today.
Yiren.
Where have you been?
We just went out on an errand.
And then, thinking you're almost done,
we came to pick you up.
See.
Is she still
the little instrument nurse?
She's a proper secretary.
So are we going back to Haicheng?
That's right.
Under all the troubles,
we still stand out.
Break through all obstacles.
Return in glory.
Don't listen to him.
It wasn't.
It's because there are no more surgeries
to be done here.
That's the truth, isn't it?
Teachers and students
at Hope Primary donated by Mr. Bai
drew this for you
to thank you
for saving Mr. Bai.
Mr. Bai?
Bai Li, right?
The patient with SHCC.
And these melons.
They grew it themselves.
It's a little gift from them.
He, it's Crookneck pumpkin.
That's good.
Nutritious.
How do you eat it?
I know.
Baked pumpkin with egg yolk.
Pumpkin honey bean buns.
And pumpkin cheese balls.
Dr. Zheng, what would you like to eat?
You might as well ask a plank of wood.
Pumpkin pie.
You can order now, huh?
I ate pumpkin pie before.
My mom made it.
Alright.
Pumpkin pie then.
I'll make it when we get back
to Haicheng.
We're going back home.
Let's go.
[Haicheng Hospital]
[Welcome Zheng Ren, our Director
of Intervention Department]
[Bringing a team to Beijing
to successfully tackle new PAE procedures]
Welcome home.
Hua, I've missed you so much.
Come on! Give me a hug.
How's your recovery going?
Let me see.
I'm fine. Just like you.
Funny you.
Welcome back, everyone!
You did a great job
at this seminar.
One step closer to the dream
you have in mind.
[Office building]
How is Beida?
Crowds, traffic jams.
Thanks.
Hot and noisy.
But there's a lot of patients.
A lot of medical conditions.
I got a call from Beida.
They want to transfer you to them.
I've already declined.
But I was told that they want
to make Haicheng and Beida
mutual assistance partners.
They'll send each other's staff
to learn from each other.
What's that supposed to mean?
That means
they're sending a couple
of emergency doctors
to help our hospital.
In exchange,
Su Yun and you
are going to study there.
To be honest,
Beida is the top three-alpha hospital.
I'm not going.
Zheng Ren.
This is a great opportunity.
You need to think about it.
I've thought it through.
I'm not going there.
My father's wish
hasn't been fulfilled yet.
I'm going to create
China's Man'ou with you.
It'll not be in Beida
or anywhere else.
It'll be here.
Alright.
Then we have an agreement.
Impossible.
All my predecessors have stopped
at the arteriae vesicles superiors.
I believed I made a great leap forward
with my ultrafine guidewire,
thinking it's impossible
to improve upon.
And long comes this guy,
who's able to clear all the blockages.
His guidewire is so thick,
so crude, and it...
How is he able to penetrate
into such a small area?
You need to get me this guidewire.
I must have a try.
Yes sir.
[Professor Hummel]
Good morning, Professor Hummel.
Rudolph.
I just saw a surgery video
from the East.
It was done perfectly.
Did you see it?
Yes, sir. I did.
Initially, I thought your surgery
was great.
It gave me hope.
But after watching that video,
if it weren't for my assistants
stopping me,
I would've been on a plane
to China by now.
Please, Professor Hummel.
Try to relax. I will personally
go to China
to find the doctor
who performed the operation.
Rest assured.
I will procure for you
the safest possible method of surgery.
Okay. Thank you for your effort.
It's unbelievable!
Unbelievable!
I spent years
in preparation for Professor Hummel's
prostate surgery.
My surgical methods were superlative.
I believe it was impossible
to improve upon.
What did this crazy Easterner do
to this stupid prostate?
How are things?
Can Professor Rudolph do another
better operation?
What?
He wants to use Changfeng's guidewire?
I got it.
[Zhou]
Ying.
I just heard that a lot of hospitals
have signed up with Chang Feng MIO.
Because Zheng Ren used their consumables
for that operation.
The little assistant named Feng
was promoted to manager.
[Mr. Wang]
Mr. Wang.
Hello, Hua.
Hello.
Here's the thing.
In view of the current situation,
I think our co-operation
should end here.
So you're saying
I'm fired?
You can read it that way, too.
Sorry.
[Certificate of Honor, Hua Yingying,
Outstanding Employee Award]
Sales Leader]
Twelve units!
I performed
all using the same
Chinese guidewire.
I was unable to reproduce
any of the same results.
It's not just the guidewire.
There has to be some other
methodology that we are unable
to learn from the video.
I cannot perform the surgery
on Professor Hummel
until I've mastered
all of the necessary skills.
Book me a ticket.
I have to go to China.
[Dr. Lin]
[I'll come to China to find Zheng Ren.]
[Is he at the same hospital as you?]
On this trip to Beida,
in addition to settling
prostate intervention embolization,
we've developed a new procedure.
Hua.
We need a lot of research cases.
I'm counting on you for this.
Oh, by the way.
Prostate intervention embolization
can also be carried out
in Haicheng Hospital.
Use the guidewire from this company.
Here's the rep's number. Contact him.
[Feng Xuhui, Sales]
We tried it.
What happened?
We've come home victorious.
Why is the long face?
Mr. Dong died of an acute heart attack.
Mr. Dong?
The one who's going to invest
in our hospital?
So now what?
Any other candidates?
I'll see what I can do
about that.
There's something else
I need to ask you.
Do you want to join Zheng Ren's team?
When I asked you before,
you refused.
After this seminar,
you've made a difference together.
Did it change your mind?
I really think you two
complement each other.
Perfect for a partner.
But what am I supposed to do
within the team?
Conjoined twins separation surgery
requires a top cardiothoracic surgeon.
Zheng Ren and Chang Yue's
reserved candidate
has always been you too.
All this time
they've been waiting for you.
You know this very well.
Forget about it.
I don't want to take up
everyone's time.
OK.
So, do you
want to join the intervention?
The trip to Beida proves that you're
no less gifted at intervention
than you are at cardiothoracic.
It's time to let go of the past
and set new goals.
[Zheng team]
Hurry up and grow it out.
Of course.
You're doing a great job in Emergency.
But at the moment, our hospital
is known for interventional procedures.
Just like you said,
patients like this will increase
dramatically in the future.
Zheng Ren
and the few available technicians alone
will definitely not be able to keep up.
I need more
skilled intervention doctors.
♪Like soil,
we clutch at the hope of roots♪
♪After taking off the doctor coat,
he is an ordinary man too♪
♪In each other's eyes♪
♪We forget sorrows, joys,
and separations♪
♪What is that in your eyes?♪
♪Too many regrets
left behind with no answers♪
♪Life is fleeting, like fluffy catkins♪
♪We fly high yet drift far away♪
♪Time is fleeting,
but we have a long way to go♪
♪Love alone is the dawn's light♪
♪Breaking through life challenges♪
♪Sometimes, whispers beckon from afar♪
♪Even if we stand close to each other♪
♪With arms clutching to the vine
between us♪
♪Against the pitch black♪
♪Only by holding on to what's dear♪
♪Can we let go without remorse♪
♪Life is fleeting, like fluffy catkins♪
♪We fly high yet drift far away♪
♪Time is fleeting,
but we have a long way to go♪
♪When stubbornness turns to faith♪
♪We march bravely on♪
♪Life is short,
like the splendor of fireworks♪