(Lee Na Young)
(Jung Eun Chae)
(Lee Chung Ah)
(Honour)
(Supported by the Culture Ministry and Korea's Creative Content Agency)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
(Final Episode)
- I'm in. - Okay, I'm on it.
I put the cameras on a 20-minute loop.
You have to be out before then.
Authentication successful.
Dong Je, you remember what I said, right?
As soon as you're done, go to Ra Young and Hyun Jin.
Authentication successful.
So, the reason you haven't caught Han Min Seo...
was right here.
(Security alert: Main server access)
(Admin biometric authentication approved)
(Access log, User group: Legal Team)
(Legal Team)
(Kang Shin Jae)
Because of the security network, it needs external authentication.
That way, if Baek Tae Joo snoops around, he'll never find it.
It will activate tomorrow when you enter the code.
All done.
Good. Baek Tae Joo must know by now.
You need to leave right now.
You turn up in the strangest places, Shin Jae.
Like Bukgwang Hospital yesterday.
And the server room today.
What were you doing in the server room?
If you're so curious, find out for yourself.
Was this your plan all along?
Because your methods are wrong.
But you were on board with my plan, weren't you?
- That's why you took down Haeil. - That was my burden to bear.
But this whole thing with Connect In is different.
Did you say we were essentially the same kind of people?
Because we are fundamentally the same kind of people.
People who carry paradise in their hearts,
but are willing to walk into the fiery pit.
Sure, we may be similar, and have been through similar things.
But the path I chose...
was to save the people trapped in that fiery pit.
No matter what kind of paradise you think you're protecting,
the moment you dragged other people into your fiery pit,
you just became another monster.
Just like the countless people you've destroyed.
I wanted to give you one last chance.
But in the end, you...
are no different from the rest.
Fine.
This is our fiery pit.
Do your worst.
Are you crazy? Why are you only telling us now?
Shin Jae told me not to say a word until after it was done.
If I'd told you sooner, she would've killed me.
Did it ever occur to you that I might kill you myself?
You just left her with Baek Tae Joo? What if something happens?
No, she's safe for now. With Min Seo gone,
he knows I won't just sit back and do nothing.
You can track Shin Jae, right? Where is she now?
I put a tracker on her.
She's in the server room at the IDC.
What'd he say?
It'll be difficult to get a warrant right away.
- Then what do we do? - I'll go to the demo venue.
Then Hyun Jin and I will go to the data center.
I'm counting on you.
The final scan is complete, sir.
The hash check came back clean.
Are you sure? Any backdoors or viruses?
None whatsoever. It's completely clean.
This is an apartment complex in Mujin.
It appears we have an intruder.
With a conventional system, the victim or a witness...
would have to report the crime before police could be dispatched.
A missing person was reported, and they were last seen here!
This is a restricted area. You can't enter without a warrant.
Fine, then at least show us the CCTV footage!
Come on, you can at least show us that, right?
All right, I get it. Calm down.
- Come on, you can do that much... - I told you, no!
- Just a second. - Sir, please, listen to me!
Unbelievable. A warrant just to see footage...
But in a city run by The Prime, things are different.
The Prime's OS...
analyses movement and behaviour patterns,
identifying them as a threat within five seconds.
This information is sent instantly to the police control center,
and the closest security team is dispatched.
Before a crime can even be committed,
the threat is eliminated first.
Thank you. After a short break,
we will commence the QnA...
and The Prime's Smart City Demonstration.
Here to congratulate me?
Notice how Shin Jae isn't here?
Aren't you curious where she might be right now?
Pressing this instantly releases a clean agent fire suppression gas.
It will remove all the oxygen from the room Shin Jae is in,
bringing it to zero percent within three minutes.
I wonder how many minutes she can last without oxygen.
If you don't want to find out,
keep your mouth shut.
I just got here.
"Is this just a new form of Big Brother?"
I completely understand the concern you've raised.
But I don't call this surveillance. I call it protection.
If we can keep our families safe by giving up a little privacy,
isn't that the best this era can offer, rather than control?
We have all witnessed too many tragedies.
What the victims of those tragedies needed most...
wasn't privacy. It was survival.
I'm in.
I found Shin Jae.
She's safe.
We found Shin Jae.
Okay, I'm starting on my end.
The system you created.
I wonder how it would assess your threat level.
Because right now, in this hall, in this very city,
the most dangerous person...
is you, CEO Baek.
Innovation has always been the greatest threat...
to outdated conventions.
So, shall we find out how threatening our system can be?
(Releasing suppression gas)
Darn.
I'm talking about...
a man who trampled on human dignity...
behind the vague ideas of innovation and justice.
A man who, for his own gain, created the Connect In app.
A man who used that app to make countless victims suffer.
The man standing right in front of me.
CEO Baek Tae Joo.
What was the authentication code Shin Jae set up during the demo?
For our 20th anniversary, shall we go to Jeju Island? The three of us?
Just Jeju? We should go to the Maldives, at least.
You set a trap using prostitution as bait?
Think of the outcome, Shin Jae.
If this can completely clean up this rotten system,
- Gosh, this is driving me nuts! - isn't that an outcome you'd want?
Why on earth isn't this working?
That's nonsense.
Do you even hear yourself right now?
That means you used the victims as bait.
What about the victims' pain?
- I said, turn it off! - You don't care what happens?
The system is frozen. I've lost control.
You know how it is, Shin Jae.
How do you cut out a festering wound without shedding blood?
(Emergency)
What's that?
It's a person!
The video you're watching now...
shows CEO Baek Tae Joo attempting to murder a witness...
to cover up his own crimes.
What is that? Is that a person?
Is this for real?
What is going on?
That's a person!
Seon Kyu, can you hear me?
Seon Kyu!
Honey!
Hyun Jin.
Hyun Jin!
(Emergency elevator)
We are one step away from a whole new world.
Why must humans ruin everything...
because they can't bear to shed the last drop of blood?
But the path I chose...
was to save the people trapped in that fiery pit.
No matter what kind of paradise you think you're protecting,
the moment you dragged other people into your fiery pit,
you just became another monster.
(Sehan Hospital)
So, what happened?
The Maldives.
So it all worked out, then.
How could you think of betting your own life?
What if something had gone wrong?
That's why I sent Dong Je to you.
Was this your plan from the start? Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Too many things were tangled up in it.
To unravel it all, this was the only way.
Are you okay?
You've been through so much.
I'm asking if you're okay.
If you're asking about Haeil...
Even if I'm not okay, I have to live with it.
That's why I did all this in the first place.
Go to my place, Ra Young.
Min Seo is waiting for you.
Okay.
But before I do,
I want to check on Hyun Jin.
(Put the used gowns here.)
(Authorized personnel only)
Hyun Jin!
(Intensive Care Unit)
You came that day, didn't you?
To the hospital.
I was going to call and tell you I was okay,
but Attorney Kang told me to wait.
I heard.
I'm going to turn myself in.
And I'm going to tell them everything Baek Tae Joo did.
Okay.
I'll go with you tomorrow.
But before that,
let's go home.
Here, I'm giving this back.
Can I...
sleep with you tonight?
This will be the last night I sleep like this.
Starting tomorrow, I'm going to try...
sleeping in the bedroom again.
Are you scared?
About turning yourself in tomorrow.
A little.
You know how in the movies,
no matter what their child has done, they'll do anything...
to hide them.
Do you wish I would do that for you?
No.
Just come with me.
That's all I need.
Okay.
I will.
Hey.
I still...
haven't been able to forgive anything.
I don't understand why I had to go through all of this.
But if this is the end,
it would feel so terribly unfair.
After all the hating,
and the loathing,
and the pain...
I want to see...
what's on the other side.
So until then,
can you wait for me here?
Yes.
I'll be right here, waiting.
It might take my whole life.
I'm just so broken.
You're not broken.
We've just had to go through...
a deeper...
and darker tunnel than most people. That's all.
The important thing is that, despite everything,
we're here...
and we...
survived.
What are you doing here?
(Sehan Hospital)
You idiot.
How long are you going to keep sleeping?
Wake up. That's enough.
I refuse to be a widow.
You are not allowed to die like this.
I won't let you. Got it?
Did they say it was okay for you to leave this early?
I'm fine. Nothing's seriously wrong thanks to Seon Kyu.
How's Seon Kyu?
Same as yesterday.
They want to observe him for a few more days.
We'll come every day for a while. Let's wait together...
until Seon Kyu wakes up.
Have you talked to Min Seo?
A little.
It looked like she was planning to turn herself in.
Yes. I'm going with her today.
Her sentence won't be light.
She knows. I think she's prepared to face it.
Shin Jae, what are your plans now?
We got an office space.
We're moving in next month.
Come back to us.
And we need to get serious about the Connect In lawsuit.
I'm...
not going back to LnJ.
At least, not for now.
(Courthouse)
Can I have a word with her for a moment?
Did you come here...
just to watch me get locked up?
I came to give you what you wanted so badly.
Your position...
Give it to me.
From now on, I'll take charge of Haeil.
Do you think I was trying to leave you...
nothing but a pile of ruins?
Someone has to take responsibility for this mess and clean it up.
And as your daughter,
that's my responsibility now.
It took all of this for me...
to finally live as your daughter, Mom.
Ever since you were little,
you've always been so much like me.
I still am, Mom.
Ma'am, the review results are in. The arrest warrant has been issued.
You'll have to be transferred to the detention center now.
What do you think you're doing?
If you're going to endure this, then do it without wavering.
The work you're about to take on...
is exactly like this.
What is your relationship to the suspect?
I'm her lawyer.
And her family.
(Sehan Hospital)
Hyun Jin.
(Intensive Care Unit)
Attorney Yoon, what are your thoughts...
on today's verdict for the Connect-In defendants?
I believe this is the worst possible outcome.
- Can you tell us why you think so? - What are your reasons?
Ten years for soliciting murder, five for bribery and abuse of power.
But what about the sexual assault charges?
In the end, every defendant got off with a fine on prostitution charges.
Punishment was only handed down for corruption by those in power,
while totally ignoring the suffering of the victims.
We will absolutely not accept...
this half-measure of a verdict.
(Courthouse)
Seriously? Have these jerks lost their minds?
And Judge Kim, has he lost his mind? I mean, this was a sex assault case,
and he says to add prostitution to the indictment?
Don't even get me started on the prosecutor.
He just went along with it like a coward.
They'll appeal, right?
We have to force their hand.
- This is just the beginning. - You think we'll let this go?
The civil suit hasn't even really started yet.
(Mujin Forensic Science Institute)
(Forensic Analysis Department)
What do you think?
It's hard to tell if it's CEO Baek Tae Joo just by looking.
The body is in such...
It's severely decomposed.
Still, I asked you to come, just in case.
I was hoping for a visual ID before the results come in.
And this.
These are the personal effects found with the body.
This looks similar to the one CEO Baek used.
The clothes, the physical build...
It's looking more and more likely that it's CEO Baek.
So the police are assuming that CEO Baek is likely dead?
There have been no signs of life since he vanished...
on the night of the demonstration.
No record he left the country, and no reported sightings.
Given the circumstances, we suspect this was retaliation.
It wouldn't be surprising if the users were behind it.
(Morgue, Autopsy Room)
So is that body really CEO Baek?
I'll let you know as soon as the DNA match results are in.
Thanks for your help today.
It's great seeing you reinstated.
I heard you went to bat for me.
I only restored...
what was wrong to its original state.
Still, thank you. Let's go.
Attorney Yoon, you really dressed up today.
But there was video evidence of the assault, wasn't there?
There was also drug use and duress, so how was this verdict possible?
They ruled the blatant felony was the sole crime of Park Je Yeol,
the deceased prosecutor.
And they let the other perpetrators get away with it.
This ruling is dangerous because the court has given perpetrators...
a playbook on how to get away with it.
You can assault and abuse anyone as long as you pay them off.
This doesn't just victimize them all over again,
but it will also set a precedent creating many more "Connect Ins."
(Late Prosecutor Park Je Yeol, a sole perpetrator)
("A Questionable Verdict, Public Outcry")
("Movement for 'Anti-Connect In Act' Grows")
The special bill under review in the National Assembly...
is focused on closing two major loopholes.
First, it expands the definition of an accomplice.
If someone purchased sex within an exploitative system,
they'd be considered an accomplice to sexual assault.
Second, it enhances penalties for special circumstances.
In cases like this one, with organised threats and coercion,
any monetary transaction would not be legitimate consent.
That's the core of this new bill.
That's a powerful swing for someone with spinal stenosis.
- Who are these people? - Go ahead.
Hey, that's a limited edition! Keep your hands off it!
Hey! Do you have any idea who you're dealing with?
I know exactly who you are. A sex offender.
You're aware of the civil suit against you, right?
We're here to seize your movable assets...
before the verdict comes in, in case you try to hide them.
And we've already paid a visit to your house.
("Former Minister Yeo Min Seok...")
("Feigning Illness in the Hospital Bed")
("LnJ Declares War Against the Users of Connect In")
(If it's a war, see it through. There's no backing out now.)
When did you get here?
A little while ago.
You should've called. We could've grabbed a bite.
It's no big deal. We can eat some other time.
She's right. She'll probably be back tomorrow anyway.
Hey, for your information, I don't come here every day.
They're right. You probably come here...
more often than I do. And I work here now.
Kang Shin Jae, you should start chipping in for rent, you know?
We're taking every case we can get just to keep this place afloat,
we're working ourselves to death. And living with this empty desk...
is making this place feel cramped, it's killing me.
Hey. I brought this for you instead.
This is the good stuff.
- This feels like a bribe. - Here you go.
It's a bribe.
Thanks.
What is this? A health potion? I feel so recharged after one sip.
I heard you got your business cards. Let me see!
Here you go.
You're a team manager? What about your team?
- It's a team of one. - Goodness.
Attorney Kang, you're here.
Are you back from the courthouse?
Yes. I was showing Su Eun how to copy the case files.
- Hello. - How have you been?
How are the others doing?
Yes. Da Eun's back in school, and Min Jae just became a manager,
so he bought us a meal to celebrate.
I miss seeing them all.
- And how's the internship going? - Good. I'm still learning,
but I'm really enjoying it.
It's rewarding too.
Once something's in her brain, she instantly recalls case numbers.
- She'll be after my job soon. - That's what I like to hear.
In that case, Ye Ji, you can come back to Haeil with me.
I've been struggling to hold down the fort by myself.
- And it's so exhausting. - Listen to you.
Trying to steal our star player, are you?
Instead of me going back, why not come back to us, Attorney?
I should get going.
Don't you give my spot away.
- Then you'd better hurry back. - After I'm done cleaning.
Attorney Kang looked so drained.
She's facing a ton of lawsuits.
And the amount she'll have to pay for fines and damages...
is astronomical.
She must be under a lot of stress these days.
Part of me just wants her to quit...
and come back here without a care.
But that's not who Kang Shin Jae is. She'd never do that.
Look at you, doing so well for yourself.
What strings did you pull?
Pinning the murder-for-hire on Park Je Yeol...
and framing my mother for Haeil's corruption...
That shouldn't be enough for you to be walking around scot-free.
Let's just say I cashed in an insurance policy.
I've had a few things tucked away for a rainy day.
You talk as if the verdict is already set in stone.
Time will tell.
Here. Take a look at this.
(Complaint)
(Claim for damages)
- What is this? - Connect In members hurt by this...
have filed a class-action lawsuit against Haeil.
Astronomical penalties on top of damages.
Haeil won't be able to afford that in its current state.
You're telling me you're behind this lawsuit?
I'm merely an advisor.
The company looked like a wreck on my way in.
You're finally starting to get it, aren't you?
The real consequences of your choices.
You poached all of our key attorneys,
and now you plan to cripple the firm with a lawsuit?
What do you really want?
This room.
That seat.
That's what I want.
Is Haeil still the same company it used to be?
Why are you so obsessed with Haeil?
Because it was my life's work.
I poured my blood, sweat, and tears into building it.
To see Haeil crumble so pointlessly due to your childish recklessness,
I will not tolerate it.
I'm going to rebuild it from scratch.
The right way, this time.
By cutting out all the rot at its core.
Fine. And in return,
you'll be buried under a mountain of debt.
Remember this, Shin Jae.
Justice is expensive. Like a supercar.
At first glance, it's flashy and looks cool,
and you might feel great behind the wheel,
but it costs you an absurd amount to get to the same destination.
Good. I like that it's expensive.
If it were something cheap and easy to get,
what would be the point of fighting for it?
Soon enough,
you'll be ready to throw in the towel.
We'll talk again then.
(VVIP invitation)
(Incoming call)
Yes, Kwon Jung Hyeon speaking.
You look even better in person, Yoo Na.
And your look is fantastic.
I can see why our client picked you.
Thank you.
So, what's the brand name exactly?
I tried looking it up, but nothing came up.
Of course you couldn't.
It's not a brand for the general public.
It's a high-end brand invested by the Middle East royalty.
Only a handful of VVIPs know about it.
The guests at this party...
are beyond anything you can imagine.
These are people you'd never share the same room with in your lifetime.
If you post just one picture with them,
it'll completely elevate your social media status.
Here's the invitation.
The time and location...
will be revealed on the event day for security reasons.
(First class board)
It's a first-class ticket.
Like I said, it's on a whole other level.
All you have to do is show up and have a good time.
(VVIP invitation)
(Haeil Law Firm)
(CEO Kang Shin Jae)
(The late Seo Ji Yoon)
Take a look.
All you have to do is sign.
I've been thinking. And I can't agree to the divorce.
If you really want one, sue me. That is, if you think you can win.
- Hyun Jin. - That doesn't matter to me anymore.
Call me shameless or point fingers at me,
none of it matters to me anymore.
I don't care if I have to be awful, selfish, and cruel.
Just please, don't leave me.
If this is about what I said before...
I was being flippant.
I had no idea what it'd feel like to lose you.
Acting like I wouldn't care if we broke up.
Like I'd be fine.
Back at the hospital,
I was the most scared I've ever been in my life.
That was the scariest moment for me too.
I was losing consciousness,
and I thought I'd never get to see you again.
I realised that if we see each other and smile every day,
nothing else in the world matters.
That's how I felt.
Then...
you'll stay with me, right?
Because I'm never letting you go again.
Why didn't you come out for the last visit?
Just because. I didn't want to see you.
But I sent you so many letters.
I couldn't be bothered to read them.
What?
This is just who I am.
Selfish and rotten to the core.
Did you think if you just said a few nice words,
I'd burst into tears and cry, "Mommy"?
Are you frustrated it's not going the way you planned?
That's not it.
I'm just glad you're healthy and safe.
That's what I came to see.
We're mother and daughter,
but we have nothing to talk about, do we?
Looks like our time is about up.
I'm going now.
Min Seo.
It's okay.
You can be even more selfish, even meaner.
And if you're still upset after all that,
that's okay too.
I'll just...
be here again next week,
waiting for you.
I once couldn't bring myself to tell someone to keep on living.
When faced with the pain they had to endure every day,
how irresponsible those words would have sounded.
(The late Jo Yoo Jeong)
("Lee Jun Hyeok Murder Case")
("The Late Jo is No Longer a Murder Suspect")
("Police Confirmed Her as an Innocent Victim")
(The late Jo Yoo Jeong)
Sometimes, I would lie, hoping the lie would come true.
Don't you dare die. You kill them instead.
You have to live with that fire, tenaciously, just to spite them.
However,
now that it has come to this...
You'll never be free from that night.
Because I can crush you like this whenever I want.
The reason I couldn't speak...
about what happened...
After all,
you're not going to say a word.
You never could back then, either.
- Because I was scared. - Because I was sexually assaulted.
You did well.
In the end, I survived.
And now,
for those of you listening to my voice,
I truly hope...
that you will keep on living.
It's not because the pain will suddenly stop one day,
or because of some miracle that will wash your scars away.
We can never get back the things we've lost,
(CEO Kang Shin Jae)
and sometimes we must bear...
the weight of our lives all by ourselves.
But despite all that,
as long as you are alive,
please remember that you will always be the victor.
Look. What happened to you...
ended up happening to your daughter all over again.
As long as you are still breathing,
the malice of those wanting you harmed will have failed forever.
What took you so long? I was freezing to death out here.
- It's freezing. Let's go. - Have you been waiting long?
And so, for us who live on with our scars,
every moment of every day is brilliant...
and honourable.
(One way)
(Law Firm Listen and Join)
So he got probation again?
I guess our judge thought the assailant's apology letter...
was a work of literary genius.
Diminished capacity, first offence, a family to support.
It's always the same old song and dance.
Seriously,
how can a father with a daughter do something like that?
Gosh.
How's your mom?
Yes, you know my mom. I visited her last week,
and she's got more energy than I do.
I got resignation letters from three associates today.
There's no room left in my drawer. It's overflowing with them.
Sounds like tteokbokki is here.
Already? We ordered less than ten minutes ago.
I'll get it.
Please help me.
Why don't you have something warm to drink first?
Well, I...
saw on social media...
(Honour)