♪Wine banners flutter, carriages pass by♪
♪The streets ablaze with revelry♪
♪His name in gold, proud blooms adorn♪
♪Who lingers now♪
♪Seek one true peace♪
♪Yet fate hangs on a thread so fine♪
♪Longing has taken root♪
♪Like flowers yet not♪
♪Words fall too short♪
♪So I ride far♪
♪To chase the dream beyond the skyline♪
♪No regret♪
♪Through the flow of years♪
♪Over waves and cliffs♪
♪Where worries end♪
♪May winds bear word of who recalls♪
♪But fate cries loud♪
♪Envying a world too pure to keep♪
♪Seasons bloom, yet lips grow weak♪
♪Through dust of time, all mortals stray♪
♪As seasons weave their gold and grey♪
♪I roam the earth and heavens freely♪
♪Why ask the road back home to be♪
♪Sun and moon part, stars remain silent♪
♪Through endless night, dawn paints its art♪
=Serendipity=
=Episode 29=
(Jianglin Prefecture)
Welcome, Reviewer Lu.
Greetings, Prefect Gao.
You honor me too much.
How dare I accept the courtesies
of the new top scholar?
This is overwhelming.
I have long heard
of your triumphant success in the capital.
Although I'm stationed in Jianglin,
I rejoice in your achievements.
Prefect Gao, you flatter me.
I came to Jianglin
on Prince Rui's orders
to investigate the Jian Family massacre.
I trust that you will help us
close this case quickly.
But the bandits
who slaughtered the Jian Family
have already been executed on the spot.
Exactly why this case
remains in doubt.
At that time, you convicted
(Jianglin Prefecture)
the Jian Family of conspiring with bandits
years ago,
what was the evidence?
Those bandits were eliminated
after the massacre.
Were any confessions recorded?
All the matters raised by you
have been thoroughly documented.
Should you require them,
I can provide them for your review.
Don't worry.
I'll fully support
the Supreme Court's investigation.
Didn't I tell you to be careful?
Lu Chang's questions
about the Jian Family made you panic.
Do you want him to suspect me?
I dare not.
I only prepared answers
about Su Changhua's case,
never expecting him to ask
about the Jian Family massacre.
No one has mentioned
that case for years.
Nowadays, the Supreme Court
wants to check it.
If he finds out that
the case is related to us...
Enough!
He won't find anything.
Before I left Jianglin,
I asked Uncle Feng
to investigate
the Jian Family massacre in detail.
Any clues?
My father said the authorities
closed the case in a hurry,
and even the commoners
found it too horrible
to discuss.
It's truly difficult to find any clues.
However,
heaven rewards the diligent.
He found jade ornaments
in the market.
A former Jian servant
recognized them
as belonging to the ladies
of the Jian Family.
The case files mention that
all Jian Family's property
has been stolen
by bandits.
These ornaments must be related to them.
Who sold them?
It was Gao Shicai's cousin, Gao Wan.
He used to wear
my late mentor's jade pendant,
and now trades
in Jian Family's belongings.
Clearly, Gao Shicai
has no control over his cousin.
Let's follow
this lead.
How will you proceed?
Gao Wan, dressed like that,
where are you going?
Reviewer Lu,
I know you're the celebrated
new top scholar,
but don't forget
I'm Prefect Gao's cousin.
You arrest me for no reason.
My cousin won't let you go!
Silence before Reviewer Lu!
For no reason?
If you are innocent,
why run in advance?
We've arrested merchants
from the Linlang Pavilion
who confessed that
you sold them
Jian Family's jewelry.
Where did you get them?
Speak the truth.
Guards! 50 strokes.
Wait!
Spare me, Reviewer Lu. I'll confess.
I'll confess.
I was blinded by greed.
After the massacre, I heard that
there were many treasures in the house.
So I sent servants to steal them.
Reviewer Lu, if it's okay,
please punish me alone!
(Such a quick confession.)
(There must be secrets lurking beneath.)
Why do you
still see me?
I don't like you,
but you must understand that
losing one's family
feels like a bone-deep agony.
I think I know how you feel.
That's right.
Since Father's death,
pain and hatred
have burned me daily.
Every time I think about it,
I'm in pain.
Countless times
I've wished for death
to reunite me
with them.
But no.
With revenge unfulfilled
and injustice unresolved,
I have no face to meet them.
Jian Mingshu,
how fortunate you are.
You have no painful memories.
You can't feel the pain.
Why am I telling you this?
You remember nothing anyway.
That's why I want
to do soul-summoning rituals again.
Now that I know everything,
I don't want to live blindly.
I want to remember
the faces of my family
and my past, everything
that made me
Jian Mingshu.
But that foreign physician is dead.
Even if you try soul-summoning rituals,
there's no chance.
What's more,
your brother would never allow
such forbidden arts.
I won't give up.
I have to find the killers of my family
and avenge them.
Lu Chang!
What did you find?
Soon after we arrived at Jiang,
Madam Gao
brought Gao Wan's
Concubine Qiu
to live with her.
A few days later, they announced
Qiu's pregnancy.
After hearing this news,
Gao Wan, childless for years,
rejoiced.
But Gao Shicai
kept Qiu imprisoned.
On the night of Gao Wan's arrest,
Gao Shicai immediately
sent Qiu away.
Now she's missing.
It seems that Gao Shicai
is using the unborn child
to threaten Gao Wan.
Gao Wan will endure the punishment
to preserve his lineage.
That's true.
We must find Qiu as soon as possible
to remove his reluctance.
Then he'll reveal everything.
What are you drawing?
Mingshu blames herself for forgetting
the family's appearances.
I'm drawing them
to comfort her.
Who knew you had such tenderness?
(Tomb of Master Jian Jinhai, Jianglin)
These are your family portraits.
Though forgotten,
at least you should know them.
(Jian Jinhai)
(Tomb of Master Jian Jinhai, Jianglin)
These are
all drawn by you, right?
(Jian Jinhai)
Do I look
more like Mother?
Thank you, Buddy.
It's comforting
to know their faces.
The departed rest.
Now we can only
look forward.
(Tomb of Master Jian Jinhai, Jianglin)
Father, rest assured.
I will not drown in grief
nor waste
my second life.
I will catch the murderers
and avenge you.
On my next visit,
I'll restore your tombstone
and worship you properly.
(Tomb of Master Jian Jinhai, Jianglin)
We've found
Gao Wan's Concubine Qiu's whereabouts.
My investigation
shows no pregnancy.
So Gao Shicai is cheating Gao Wan.
He fabricated the child
to trick Gao Wan into taking the blame.
If Gao Wan learns
the truth of Gao Shicai's lies,
he might be able to tell the truth.
It's not that easy.
To convince him,
we need proof.
Can you save Qiu?
Gao Shicai is
watching her closely.
A violent rescue
would alert him.
All defenses have weaknesses.
Besides the guards,
who else attends Qiu?
Someone else?
There is a matron
who cares for her.
She's obsessed
with fried dough sticks from back alleys
and buys two at dawn.
Do you even know this?
Well...
Qiu isn't pregnant?
She...
Didn't the physician say
she was pregnant?
I've been serving around Qiu.
She's really not pregnant.
Last month, she menstruated.
Others might be deceived,
but not me.
My cousin deceived me?
Without deception,
how can you take his guilt
and die for him?
Die?
I only stole
the Jian Family's treasures.
A few years' imprisonment at worst!
They were
bandits' booty by the robbers.
It's stolen goods.
Besides, the Supreme Court suspects
collusion
between officials and bandits.
Selling them
makes you
an accomplice to both theft
and conspiracy.
Both are punishable
by death.
Gao Shicai!
You betrayed me! Demon!
We know
you only helped as a backup.
You can testify against him
for leniency.
But if you stay stubborn,
only death awaits you.
Reviewer Lu!
Reviewer Lu, I'm innocent.
Reviewer Lu,
please save me!
That depends
on your innocent evidence.
Yes!
I have proof!
Gao Shicai feared my embezzlement.
He personally wrote lists
whenever he gave me treasures to sell.
And...
I also kept ledgers
of all transactions!
(Law and Prudent Punishment)
The Supreme Court is investigating!
Who dares to obstruct?
(Supreme Court)
Search.
(Qinmin Hall)
(Law and Prudent Punishment)
Reviewer,
entire premises searched.
No sign of Gao Shicai.
As expected,
my mentor asked
for Jianglin officials' records
since he became the prefect.
He seemed to have prepared.
Although Mr. Su was from Jianglin,
most capital officials
avoid provincial posts.
Yet he requested to return
to investigate.
(Su Residence)
(Child)
(Prudent Thought, Clear Discernment)
The current laws
deviate from the governance
of the ancient sage kings.
As the ancients said,
benevolent intentions
that don't benefit the people
are the result
of not following proper governance.
(This is my mentor's manuscript.)
(At that time, confiscators
overlooked this treasure.)
(Fortunately, it survived.)
(Thatched Cottage Notes)
(I vow to continue my mentor's reforms)
(and complete his unfinished work.)
Under Gao Shicai's orders,
Gao Wan sold most of the loot overseas.
Would they flee
by sea?
Here are market records of goods
and recent merchant fleets.
Look.
(Tea. Silk. Hongyuan Trading House)
Look, I've compared
several trading houses.
Only this Hongyuan Trading House's
sea departure records
match the ledger's depreciation dates.
It's very likely
this Hongyuan Trading House
colluded with Gao Shicai
to dispose of stolen goods.
But shouldn't Hongyuan Trading House
be in the tea business?
When did they start dealing in silk?
Let me offer a different perspective.
Silk functions as hard currency
in foreign lands, like silver.
It serves both
as a discreet means of escape
and as portable wealth.
Who wouldn't want that?
If your theory is correct,
Gao Shicai converted
his family's wealth into silk
to avoid suspicion
and planned
to convert it back into money abroad.
Sister Mingshu,
your business acumen
is also useful in solving cases.
I'll take someone
to Hongyuan Trading House immediately.
I'm sure we'll find out the details
of Gao Shicai's ship
and the departure date.
Wait!
Acting rashly will alert our targets.
Then what should we do?
I have a plan.
(Hongyuan Trading House)
Welcome, esteemed guests.
Your presence honors
our humble establishment.
How can we
help you?
Sir, greetings.
My Lady has come from Yavadvipa
to trade,
but is stranded with a damaged ship.
Right now, we need to transfer
some Sky-Blue Glazed Brush Washers
from the Ru Ware
back to our country.
I hear you have an imminent departure,
could we secure passage?
Come here, let's discuss it upstairs.
Please.
(Golden Promise)
This is our records of distant voyages,
listing recent departures.
The Voyage Log.
Lady, which ship
would you like to charter?
We want the best, of course.
Price is not an issue.
Dear guests, take your time.
(Porcelain)
(Liufang Ship)
The Liufang ship appears to be the largest,
already carrying porcelain.
Should we choose it?
It's fully loaded.
It's not safe to add more cargo.
Please consider other options.
My Lady, why don't we take another look?
Please select.
(Master Zhang, Silk, Yongxing Ship)
This Yongxing Ship carries less cargo.
We'll take this one.
This...
This ship is booked. Booked.
My Lady, please don't be angry.
We must have this ship.
Did you hear?
My lady insisted.
You just have to load our goods there
before they leave.
No, but...
We'll double
the price.
How much?
Double the price?
(Hongyuan Trading House)
Gao Shicai...
Gao Shicai
must be escaping via Yongxing Ship.
How is that possible?
The Voyage Log shows
that only Yongxing Ship
is carrying silk,
and not at full capacity.
What's the nature of a merchant?
Profit-seeking.
Who sails under capacity?
Except for other desires.
And it was chartered.
It must be Gao Shicai who did it.
He agreed to our shipment
when he saw our deep pockets.
In that case,
we'll catch him like a turtle in a jar.
Arrest him!
Reviewer Lu, save me!
You again.
Kill him!
Protect Gao Shicai!
- Yes!
Watch out!
Mingshu!
Mingshu.
Retreat!
Guard him.
- Yes!
Mingshu!
How is Mingshu?
Injured.
- Mingshu!
- Wake up!
Mingshu!
Her lips are purple.
Is she poisoned?
I'll get a physician.
Lu Chang!
Guard Gao Shicai.
♪May heaven and earth show mercy♪
♪Let mortal ties never fade♪
♪As time quietly slips away♪
♪Don't let us miss growing old together♪
♪May this heart stay true
as the first day♪
♪I'll wait through blooms and dew♪
♪Let greed and wrath fade with the wind♪
♪If all scenes fade to view♪
♪Will you return♪
Buddy,
I heard from Mr. Ying that
the poison-sucker
would also be infected.
Shut up!
What use is my life if you die?
♪Silhouette in sight♪
♪If the moon above the sea is full♪
♪Will you return♪
♪In years left, wait for me♪
♪With a beginning and an end♪
♪May time inscribe our names♪
♪Where vows remain♪
♪As if it were yesterday♪
Buddy...
♪Together we'll traverse♪
♪Through grandeur and adversity♪
♪When clarity arrives♪
♪Destiny's threads entwine,
Karma's path refines♪
♪In glances back♪
♪Our story's told♪
♪If the moon above the sea is full♪
♪Will you return♪
♪In years left, wait for me♪
♪With a beginning and an end♪
Physician, hurry up!
Neutralize the poison!
♪Where vows remain♪
♪As if it were yesterday♪
Why am I here again?
So the place in my dreams
was the Jian Family.
It's my home.
(Accumulated Virtue)
It's you again.
In previous dreams,
I have never seen your face clearly.
Today,
I have to see who you really are.
Actually, why should I obsess about
who you really are?
You're only a dream shadow.
Before,
I didn't understand my own heart,
hence the obscurity
of your identity.
Now that
I see clearly,
your identity doesn't matter anymore.
I already know
who holds my affection.
Mingshu!
♪Two swallows dart through the drizzle♪
♪A lonely shadow bars the window♪
♪Thoughts lie concealed♪
♪With no one to talk to♪
♪Things will be changed♪
♪At least, I have your shoulders♪
♪Always by my side♪
♪Shining bright as fireflies♪
♪Heart is like a web of silken twine♪
♪Fate brews its sweet romance♪
♪Go on a long trip♪
(So Mr. Green Robe in my dreams)
(has only ever been Buddy.)
(And he has always been)
(the one I love.)
♪Brief as dawn, vast as eternity♪
♪The moon shines♪
♪One glance spans eternity♪
♪Human world is infinite♪
♪Far away, but under one moon♪
♪Willows weep where waters web♪
I don't need you to repay me!
Can't you see
my true feelings towards you?
♪We huddle under an umbrella♪
♪I'll travel with you♪
♪Through seas and peaks♪
Shut up!
What use is my life if you die?
Thank you for your favor.
I already have a betrothal
in my hometown Jianglin.
I can't break my vow.
♪Heart is like a web of silken twine♪
♪Fate brews its sweet romance♪
♪Go on a long trip♪
♪In pairs♪
♪Hearts share a silent thread♪
♪Brief as dawn, vast as eternity♪
You call me Buddy.
Family should be like this.
(But Buddy said)
(he was deeply devoted
to thin Jianglin maiden.)
(What am I)
(to him?)
Mingshu? You're awake.
Why don't you go in?
Mr. Ying!
Well...
About Buddy's beloved
Jianglin maiden...
Jianglin... Jianglin maiden?
Who is she?
Is she in Jianglin now?
Well...
She... exists.
But Lu Chang is here.
Why ask me instead of him?
Mr. Ying,
you know Buddy's temperament.
If I ask, he'll scold me.
I have to ask you.
Yes.
Sister Mingshu, I really want to say.
You know,
I'm terrible at keeping secrets.
I feel terrible.
Then tell me if you want!
I just woke up and I'm still weak.
Why do you torture me?
No!
You have to ask him yourself.
What's this?
Buddy, you're awake.
Are you all right?
Let me have a look.
Your poisoning was worse than mine.
If you're all right, how can I not be?
Fear clouds judgment.
Let me fix this for you.
(What am I thinking?)
Buddy,
how is
your unforgettable
Jianglin maiden?
Still in touch?
She...
Lu Chang!
Prince Rui and his wife are here
with County Princess Wen'an.
Why did they come?
They were worried about you
and came with Prince Rui.
Mingshu,
we rushed here when we heard.
As sisters,
we couldn't comfort you
in your darkest hours.
Please forgive us.
To see you safe
is comforting.
Your care
and visit across miles
prove the value
of our sisterhood.
You're such a sweet talker.
You seem better.
Though shocked by my origins,
I'm surely sad.
But that's my life.
I must face the truth.
With Gao Shicai captured,
justice for my family
is near.
Now that you know your true parentage,
can you still treat Lu Chang
like a brother?
Shujun,
do you remember when I asked you this?
When I didn't know
we weren't siblings,
I avoided him.
I might have been...
It's exactly what we thought.
And what about his feelings?
All I know is
he'd risk his life
and career for you.
But is it a fraternal concern
or more?
We don't know that.
You have to decide.
And...
And that Jianglin maiden...
We don't know her condition.
Neither do I.
Mingshu,
as for...
as for my cousin,
even though you rejected him,
I think
his feelings remain.
After all, he treats you sincerely.
My hasty return to Jianglin
caused you to pass on messages.
That was inappropriate.
Don't worry.
I'll settle this personally.
(Jianglin Post Inn)
I've captured Gao Shicai.
He's a key figure
in both
the Jian Family's case
and Su Changhua's case.
Through him,
the truth
is getting closer.
Good.
You're for this matter.
Be sure to handle this thoroughly.
Yes.
Until now,
you still remain calm.
So admirable.
Innocence needs no defense.
My government
has been upright.
I don't fear your review.
In that case,
why did you flee
via Yongxing Ship?
I...
I merely visited the docks.
Your cousin Gao Wan's ledger
records your transferred lists
of the Jian Family's assets
in every transaction
and the details of your disposition.
It's very clear
one by one.
Last year, you declared the Jian Family
colluded with bandits
and they were wiped out
in a booty dispute.
Why does your name
appear in the loot?
Mere pages of this ledger
can't convict
a prefect.
Lu Chang,
you're new to politics
and have a poor understanding
of officials.
I advise you
to stop wasting your time.
This ledger
was found in Wei Xian's hidden box.
(Ledger)
It records
his dirty dealings with various parties.
Can you guess
the most common location
and participant?
It's you,
Prefect Gao of Jianglin.
They're all
the Jian Family's possessions.
Still claiming innocence?
You deserve to die
for the Jian Family massacre alone.
Instead of lecturing me,
consider
how to save yourself.
What do you mean by that?
I want to know
who sent assassins
to kill you.
Who ordered the Jian Family massacre?
And who
instructed you to frame Su Changhua?
Framed Su Changhua?
I don't understand.
At first, you and Wei Xian
framed Su Changhua together.
And then the person behind you
learned that Jian Jinhai had proof
of Su Changhua's innocence
and ordered you to exterminate them
in the name of banditry.
Your loyalty
is rewarded
with an assassination attempt
instead of saving.
Why still keep your mouth shut?
Without us,
you'd have been dead yesterday.
Even if you're telling the truth,
I have to say
that I'm innocent.
Even if I confess the whole thing,
would you protect me?
I'm tired.
If you want to negotiate,
you're
unqualified.
Since he's unqualified,
what about me?
- Prince Rui.
Gao Shicai,
I've come to see you in person.
Am I qualified to judge you now?
♪May heaven and earth show mercy♪
♪Let mortal ties never fade♪
♪As time quietly slips away♪
♪Don't let us miss growing old together♪
♪May this heart stay true as the first day♪
♪I'll wait through blooms and dew♪
♪Let greed and wrath fade with the wind♪
♪May life's towers stand tall♪
♪With love that outlasts all♪
♪Together we'll traverse♪
♪Through grandeur and adversity♪
♪When clarity arrives♪
♪Destiny's threads entwine,
Karma's path refines♪
♪In glances back, our story's told♪
♪If all scenes fade to view♪
♪Will you return♪
♪Through years with sincere love♪
♪May all enigmas grow clear♪
♪Counting endless nights♪
♪Yet never your♪
♪Silhouette in sight♪
♪If the moon above the sea is full♪
♪Will you return♪
♪In years left, wait for me♪
♪With a beginning and an end♪
♪May time inscribe our names♪
♪Where vows remain♪
♪As if it were yesterday♪