[♪ upbeat theme music playing]
Are You Sure?!
[exclaims]
Let's get going!
We're already going.
"Jung Kook and Jimin's reality show,
Are You Sure?!"
They had a big appetite from the beginning
[exclaims]
-Isn't it good?
-It's fantastic.
[Jung Kook exclaims]
It's like a painting.
Jung Kook even sacrificed (?) himself
for laughs
Don't laugh by yourself.
Always full of laughter
With everything they do
[Jimin] I think it's good I came here.
"A wonderful first day together"
"But then!"
There was an unexpected nose injury (?)
"And a stomach bug"
[Jimin] Please
remove the toxins from my body.
[Jung Kook] Come on, make your wish.
"Will today be better?"
[Jimin] Hello.
I'd like to order takeout.
Two jjamppong, please.
Jung Kook looks cute on that bike.
This was filmed safely
in compliance with traffic laws
This feels great!
I love the breeze.
[Jimin exclaims]
He looks good.
He's driving well.
He's been riding motorcycles a lot lately.
Who would've thought?
-Hello, Jung Kook.
-[Jung Kook] Yes.
There will be more cars, so be careful.
I'm good.
You can just say okay.
[Jung Kook] I love this!
He likes being cool.
+ Added cool sunglasses
[Jimin] He looks like a proper American.
[Jung Kook] The breeze is nice.
[whoops]
He's cute.
[humming]
[Jung Kook] ARMY would get worried again
if they saw this, right?
I think they'd like it.
Don't worry, everyone.
I'm very careful when riding motorcycles.
[♪ playful music playing]
If we shoot washer fluid
on the windshield, will he get hit?
What's with this spray?
[laughs]
[Jimin's laughter over phone]
This is too much, Jimin.
Was that washer fluid?
I didn't want you to get too hot.
-Right.
-[Jimin] Yes.
-I actually haven't washed up yet.
-[Jimin] Right.
It's good since it's too hot out
and you haven't washed up yet.
That worked.
I can't believe that worked.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[Jung Kook] Is that a gas station?
Do I see a gas station?
Yes, I think we're getting there.
All right, a gas station.
[Jimin] Okay, we're here.
[Jung Kook] "Gasoline."
[exclaims]
[Jimin] What's that?
[motorbike beeps]
[Jung Kook] That's full.
Good.
We're all good.
[Jimin] Let's get going.
[engine starts]
[Jung Kook] Let's go!
On the road again for the hiking trip
The weather's amazing.
It's totally different
from driving in Korea.
[playful pop]
Saying hello to some friends on the road
That's two bikers already.
I waved to both of them. I feel great.
[giggles]
[Jung Kook humming]
[Jimin] We're here.
"Park"
[Jimin] Shall we go?
-I haven't gone hiking in a while.
-Right.
Where are we now?
Right now, we're…
Are we here?
[Jung Kook] No, I don't think so.
I don't know. Let's just go.
-Let's go.
-Let's just go.
-[♪ playful music playing]
-[exclaims]
[Jimin] The scenery is amazing.
[Jung Kook] It's all so green.
It's nice and cool here.
I like it.
Wow.
[Jung Kook] It's so green.
Wow, it's beautiful.
Let's relax and enjoy the view.
[humming]
[Jimin] When I went hiking
when I was young,
I always walked fast
and tried to finish first
to prove that I was good at hiking.
But it's actually nicer going slow.
But is this too slow?
Jung Kook's already gone far.
The trees are very tall
which makes everything prettier.
It's a dense forest.
It's so beautiful.
[Jung Kook] Isn't it beautiful?
Wow. So pretty.
I'm so good at taking videos.
[amazed exclaim]
It's insane. It's insane.
What the…
[chuckles]
Jimin…
Can you see where Jimin is?
-[Jung Kook chuckles]
-[♪ cheeky music playing]
My goodness.
[Jung Kook coughs]
[soft grunt]
[chuckles]
Let's go slowly and enjoy the view.
You're making a 50-minute course
into a 2.5-hour course.
No, I'm not.
[Jung Kook] You're not?
How come Jimin is so funny?
[chuckles]
[giggles]
Why, hello.
-[Jimin] Hello.
-[Jung Kook] Hello.
Are you hiking?
-No, just strolling.
-[Jung Kook] Strolling?
-Yes.
-[Jung Kook] Do you live nearby?
[Jimin] I sleep anywhere around here.
-[Jung Kook] Really?
-[Jimin] Yes.
I just lie down and sleep
whenever I get tired.
[chuckles]
Hey, mushrooms.
[Jung Kook] Wow.
I've never seen wild mushrooms before.
There are a lot of mushrooms here.
[Jung Kook exclaims]
[Jimin] That's a pine mushroom.
A big one.
Wow, that's so cool.
[Jung Kook sniffles]
I've never seen wild mushrooms before.
This looks like a cartoon character.
Hey, a yellow one.
[Jimin] Wow. There's a giant spider here.
[Jung Kook] Yeah?
[Jimin]
There's a giant spider behind this tree.
[Jung Kook] Oh, that one's poisonous.
That one? That one's not poisonous.
I would know. I live here.
-What's that one's name?
-[Jimin] That one?
-"Ddochi."
-[Jung Kook] Ddochi?
Does Ddochi have friends?
It does. I'll show you them later.
He's hilarious
[Jimin] This leaf is Colombo.
-[Jung Kook] You named these too?
-[Jimin] Yes, of course.
-[Jung Kook] Wow.
-[Jimin] What?
-[Jung Kook] That's huge.
-[Jimin] How can it grow so big?
-It's so much bigger than us.
-[Jimin] Hold this.
[playful tune]
[Jung Kook] Wow.
Look at the height difference.
[Jimin] It feels even bigger up close.
[Jung Kook exclaims]
[Jung Kook] Here.
It's so huge.
Looks like something on Harry Potter.
[Jimin] That's actually
how I get to my school.
-Your school?
-[Jimin] Yes.
-I'm an alumnus.
-Of Hogwarts?
-[Jimin] I didn't go to Hogwarts.
-Then where did you go?
-My school is called Apartment Building.
-[chuckles]
How many floors
did you have to go up to graduate?
You just have to go up each grade,
and every grade has a different floor.
Our school has
elementary, middle, and high schools.
-[Jung Kook] In one building?
-[Jimin] Yes.
[Jung Kook] Ah.
You can be a professor right away
or just leave school
and live in the outside world.
You can be a professor
straight out of high school?
-Of course.
-Wow.
You can teach elementary school kids.
[Jung Kook chuckles]
[Jimin] Should we listen to some music?
[♪ upbeat music playing,
Jung Kook (feat. Latto) "Seven"]
[mouthing]
[Jimin sings along]
[humming]
[Jung Kook humming]
-[cameraman] Jung Kook.
-[Jung Kook] Yes?
[cameraman] Mr. Jung Kook.
[sings "Seven"]
[♪ song fades]
-Do a cover for me.
-[Jimin] Okay.
I'll start working on it.
Oh.
It's a brook.
[Jung Kook] The water seems so dark.
-Ooh.
-[Jimin] Oh.
[Jung Kook] Oh.
It looks like there would be alligators.
Oh, yes.
"[Shall we take a break
before we go back?]"
[Jung Kook] It's nice and cool.
So breezy.
[♪ cheeky music playing]
[chuckles]
[Jimin grunts]
-[leaves rustle]
-[Jung Kook] Wow, the breeze.
It's so cooling.
[Jung Kook] I love it.
I miss our members.
[Jimin] I'm a member.
Hello.
I'm Jimin of BTS.
Pretending he didn't hear
-[Jimin] Shall we head back?
-[Jung Kook] All right, let's.
[Jimin] I got a mosquito bite already.
-Just now?
-[Jimin] Yes.
I got another mosquito bite.
Why do mosquitoes love you so much?
[Jimin] I don't know.
It sucks that I got a bite on my face.
Let's go.
It's like
you're getting all my bites too.
[Jimin] Oh, these stupid mosquitoes…
[birds chirping effect]
I guess your blood is clean.
My blood does taste delicious.
-[chuckles]
-[Jung Kook] You tasted it?
Even I found it delicious.
-[Jung Kook] I guess it's really good.
-It is.
-It's like an omakase.
-[Jung Kook chuckles]
[Jimin]
I'm giving them every part of my body.
My thigh, shoulders, forehead…
My forehead tastes the best,
and they got to it.
You served the entrée first.
[Jimin] I rarely serve it.
[Jung Kook] You must be famous.
[Jimin] Oh, man. And it's all free too.
Oh, come on.
I don't get a lot of mosquitoes
but I get a lot of fruit flies.
Dung flies like you too.
-Dung flies don't like me.
-They called me yesterday.
Oh, yeah? Do they miss me?
They can't get over you.
[Jung Kook] They can't get over me?
-Oh, man.
-[Jimin chuckles]
I told them to stop.
[chuckles]
[Jimin chuckles]
I told them not to call.
I can't believe they called.
[sniffles]
[exclaims]
You just gave me butterflies.
-[Jimin] What?
-You gave me butterflies,
holding onto my back like that.
-Really?
-[Jung Kook] Yes.
Think whatever you like.
This is quite tiring.
-[Jimin] What?
-It's tiring.
This is to help me not get tired.
[Jung Kook] Well, it's tiring.
Can you let go?
No, sorry.
I'm still sick. You understand, right?
All right.
I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
[Jung Kook sighs]
Thank you, Jung Kook
-[Jimin] Mr. Jung Kook.
-[Jung Kook] Yes?
[Jimin] I got bitten again.
-Again?
-[Jimin] Yes, here.
-It pierced through that?
-[Jimin] Wait, I caught it.
It was sucking my blood
and wouldn't let go when I shook it.
-Really?
-[Jimin] Yes.
The mosquitoes here are strong.
[Jimin] There's another one.
Why are they doing this?
You're the hottest place in town.
[Jimin] It's driving me nuts.
[groans]
[frustrated groan]
[Jung Kook] Yes, just run.
[Jimin] There's another one here.
I really am an omakase.
Another one.
[chuckles]
Just how delicious is your blood?
Let me try.
[Jimin] I'll give you some later.
"Awesome"
[Jimin] But just a bit.
Don't ask for too much.
[Jung Kook] Jimin's starting to go faster.
[both chuckling]
He wants to get out of here.
A different pace from earlier.
[Jung Kook chuckles]
We're here.
This is it.
[Jung Kook groans]
We did it.
[Jung Kook] That was a lot of cardio.
-I loved it.
-[Jimin exclaims]
[Jimin] We enjoy a yacht ride!
[♪ peaceful music playing]
[Jimin] This is amazing.
[Jung Kook] Awesome.
"Marina"
[Jimin] Wow, it's a marina.
[Jung Kook] Are these all personal yachts?
There are a lot.
Wow, insane.
-[Jimin] The yacht looks great.
-[Jung Kook] It's amazing.
-Are you ready?
-[Jung Kook] Yes.
[background chatter]
[Jung Kook] Toe socks.
[sniffles]
-[in English] Nice to meet you.
-Welcome onboard. Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
[in Korean] Oh, a tour.
Whoa.
-There's a room too.
-[Jung Kook] There's a room?
And a bathroom. Wow.
This is awesome.
[Jung Kook exclaims]
-[Jung Kook] There's one here too.
-[Jimin exclaims]
It has a lot of places to relax.
[Jimin] I haven't been on a boat
in a while.
I hope you don't stay in the bathroom
the whole time again.
-I'm really hungry…
-[coughs]
…so I have to eat something.
Should we leave it to fate?
I'll try to eat something.
It is your fate though.
I'm definitely eating something.
I'm eating something too.
You looked great when you first got here,
but you're looking more and more tired…
[laughs]
…as the days go by.
[This is just too funny]
[laughs]
[Jung Kook] It's hilarious
how tired you're looking.
[instructor in English]
When the boat is moving,
you cannot jump off
or you cannot go down there.
When the boat is moving. Never, okay?
-Just have fun.
-Okay.
[instructor] If you need anything,
let me know, okay?
-Okay.
-[instructor] All right.
-[in Korean] Let's go.
-[in English] It's nice to have you.
[Jung Kook] Oh, yes.
Let's go!
[Jung Kook in Korean] I love it.
"We boarded the yacht with a safety expert
after going through a safety training"
[relaxed groan]
It's so breezy.
[Jimin] I love this.
This is just my style.
[♪ lively music playing]
I bet I can sleep like five hours on here
if we keep moving like this.
Wow, this is perfect.
I feel so free.
-[Jung Kook] I feel so free.
-[Jimin chuckles]
[wind blowing]
[♪ calm music playing]
Jimin's asleep.
He's dead.
[Jung Kook] He's gone.
[♪ music fades]
I just love this.
-Do you like boat rides?
-I do.
[Jimin]
We're literally in the middle of nowhere.
There's nothing around us.
We've come so far out.
[♪ peaceful music playing]
[relaxed exhale]
I really love boat rides.
I think I could stay on a boat for days
if there's enough food.
Wow. This feels amazing.
[in English] Good.
[exclaims]
[shouts in Korean]
I feel so free!
[Jung Kook exclaims]
[Jimin] It's liberating, right?
[Jung Kook] It really is.
[Jimin] I love this so much.
[Jung Kook sings "Seven"]
A sudden showcase on the yacht
[continues singing]
Did you really hit me there
when I have a bad stomach?
[sings and giggles]
Titanic.
[humming]
[continues humming]
No, you might crap yourself.
-You shouldn't.
-I know.
[♪ playful music playing]
-[Jimin] Looking for mosquito bites?
-Yes.
[Jimin] Stop that.
[both chuckle]
You're obviously looking for bite marks.
-Come on.
-[Jung Kook giggles]
[Jimin imitates punching]
[Jung Kook] You're beating me up?
[laughs]
-Oh, no.
-[both laugh]
You can't.
It's coming out.
No, you can't.
What should it be?
"Suddenly thinking of the show title"
This is the process we go through
before making a show.
Can I be the main star
so we could call this my adventure log?
-So I'm a guest star?
-Yes.
The stomach bug.
The bruise on my nose.
Or we could say you abducted me.
So it would be,
"I Tried Abducting Someone."
No.
How about "We Feel So Free" or "Freedom"?
"That's How Free We Feel."
"Daily Life Escape Number 1."
"Want to Meet?"
"What's Up? Let's Hang Out."
"Let's Hang Out. Okay!"
[chuckles]
That sounds okay.
[Jimin in English] Are you sure of that?
[in Korean] How about "W…"
"WC."
Like the bathroom!
"Eureka!"
That's fate.
[Jimin chuckles]
[Jimin] Aren't you eating?
-[Jung Kook] Are you really going to eat?
-[Jimin] I'll try.
[Jung Kook] You can't poop your pants.
Whoa.
-Oh, I love this.
-[Jimin] Me too.
[Jung Kook] Yeah, taco, taco.
Yeah, guacamole, guacamole.
Do you have food there?
"Worried about the crew"
Do they have food there?
They don't? I feel bad.
[Jung Kook in English] Come on.
[groans]
[straining]
[security shouting]
-Okay.
-[applause]
Yeah, I did it.
[in Korean] All right. Delivery complete.
[in English] Yes!
[in Korean] This is going to be good.
Finally eating without any worries
Is this avocado?
It's guacamole. So yes, avocado.
[♪ cheerful music playing]
[satisfied hum]
You feel something in your stomach?
[Jimin] Yeah.
Well, there's a bathroom.
This is so delicious.
[Jung Kook] Right.
Taco, taco.
[♪ playful music playing]
-Is it good?
-[Jung Kook] Yes.
A big bite
Going full speed
He's eating so well.
Do you like it?
[Jimin] If I eat any more,
I might experience hell.
I know I'm going to regret it.
[crunching]
[Jung Kook] Mmm.
That's great.
It's amazing.
Are you okay?
Yes, but I feel a bit iffy.
I want to drink a ton of water.
If I eat dinner too,
how long will I be in the bathroom?
You were totally fine until yesterday.
-Is this right?
-Are you sure about this?
[shouts]
Am I sure?
[chuckles]
This isn't what I came for.
At least it's authentic.
[Jung Kook] That's it.
That's our title.
[clapping]
[Jimin] "You Sure?!"
[Jung Kook] "Are You Sure?!"
[♪ lively music playing]
[both chuckle]
[Jung Kook] We have arrived.
He's willing to show everything on camera.
I guess some fans would like to see this.
Jimin, we're here. Let's go.
What?
[Jung Kook] We're here.
[mutters]
I sleep so well on boats.
[Jimin] All right. I'm a lot better.
I guess you didn't get
much sleep last night.
I was awake almost all night.
I kept waking up every 10 minutes.
I got nightmares too.
[Jimin] Let's go.
"To the next destination"
[Jung Kook] Let's look at the playlist.
"Korea's Top 50."
Oh, Seven is in first place.
[in English] Oh, Seven. Oh, Seven.
[Jung Kook] Damn.
[in Korean] Like Crazy is in third place.
Like Crazy is in third place?
[Jung Kook]
The English version is in fourth place.
-I've still got it.
-Angel Pt. 1 is in fifth place.
-[Jimin exclaims]
-Set Me Free Pt.2 is in sixth place.
-[shouts] Wow, Mr. Jimin!
-[Jung Kook exclaims]
I've still got it!
You've still got it.
They were actually released a while ago.
This is great.
[Jung Kook] I did quite a lot actually,
with Dreamers and all.
[Jimin] You did a lot.
You know, I actually think
it's more efficient to receive
songs written by someone else.
I worked for a whole year
for just one album
-and couldn't even take a break.
-[Jung Kook] Mm.
But it's not like I did a lot more
than everybody else.
[Jung Kook]
I think the end goals are different.
-[Jimin] They are.
-[Jung Kook] It's still important to me
to sing about my own story,
but these days,
I want to see how far I can take
a pre-written song with my voice.
That's important too.
[Jung Kook]
That's been important to me these days.
I want to let people
hear many different kinds of songs
with my voice,
and I want to be acknowledged
for singing them well.
That's my biggest goal right now.
I know it's important to tell my story,
but I honestly don't have much to tell.
I don't really…
go about my life
with a lot of thoughts in my head.
I don't really jot things down.
I don't really get inspired by things.
I just want to do well in my role
of using my talent
to express different things,
because it's the singing itself
that I enjoy.
[Jimin] I want to try writing my own song
as well as getting songs written for me.
I actually enjoy writing songs.
We're here.
[Jung Kook] That's it.
[Jimin grunts]
That's it.
[exclaims]
I'm quite amazing at parking.
[Jung Kook] Let's clap.
-One, two, three.
-Oh, like a clapboard?
-Yes.
-I thought you were applauding me.
"Self-applause"
Hypermarket
Walmart.
[exclaims]
-[in English] This is Walmart.
-Walmart. What's up?
[in Korean] So it's a wall mart.
That needs another "L."
I was just kidding.
-[Jung Kook] All right, "Wall Mart."
-[Jimin] You're no fun.
It's like this was waiting for us.
-[Jung Kook] Oh, my. What's this?
-[Jimin chuckles]
It came ready with a camera.
-It's waiting for us.
-Shall we go?
Let's go.
[Jung Kook]
They only open when you acknowledge them.
Let's go to the food section.
[Jimin] The self-checkouts were fun.
[Jung Kook] Have you tried them?
Of course I have.
Where's the food section?
I don't think it's here.
Let's go this way.
Would you be embarrassed
if I rode the cart?
-[Jung Kook] Yes.
-[Jimin chuckles]
I want to squeeze in and ride this.
-Don't.
-[Jimin chuckles]
You'll get scolded.
By who?
By the audience.
It won't even make the final cut.
[laughs]
[gasps]
-No, don't.
-[Jung Kook] This is tasty.
"Jimin abandons Jung Kook"
There's a lot. Wow.
-Hang on.
-No, let's get some actual food first.
-Wow. They have this!
-Hey, someone's passing through.
"Jung Kook can't hear anything"
[coughs]
[in English] My favorite.
[in Korean] You're such a snack addict.
I love these so much.
Oh? If Jin were here,
we'd definitely go fishing.
Well, this is…
Make me pasta.
-[Jung Kook] Do you want pasta?
-There's some sauce here.
[Jung Kook] Pasta's not bad at all.
There are noodles too.
Let me take a look.
All right.
Four to five minutes.
Do you prefer thin or thick pasta?
-Me?
-Just eat this one.
-Is that the thin one?
-It's average.
How about we have some meat with pasta?
Let's put some meat in the pasta.
Where's the meat?
[♪ playful music playing]
There's bacon. We could get bacon.
The ones with a lot of fat are better.
Let's get this. And then…
This is actually enough. And black pepper.
We need black pepper.
Black pepper?
Black pepper.
[in English] Pepper, pepper, black pepper.
[in Korean] Black pepper.
Where were the spices?
Hang on.
"Getting further away from Jimin"
The spices…
They must be here somewhere.
Jung Kook keeps wandering off
to get snacks.
He always stops by the chips. Jung Kook!
[Peeking]
[birds chirping effect]
The food…
Are there any parmesan?
Cheese.
Jung Kook.
[sighs]
Jung Kook, Jung Kook.
Cheese, cheese, cheese.
What weird thing is keeping him now?
This looks tastier though.
[sighs]
Seriously.
He never comes when I call him.
Where did Jimin go?
Look at that. He wandered off
and didn't even get anything.
[exclaims]
There he goes again.
They're finally reunited
[Jung Kook] Helicam.
Do we have to scan everything?
-Yes.
-[Jung Kook] That sounds fun.
-What?
-I forgot how to start this.
Just start.
[Jimin]
Should I just start scanning right away?
-[machine beeps]
-[both] It works.
[machine continues beeping]
That's cool.
That's cool. So cool.
This is super fun.
[Jimin] I told you it's fun.
The bill. Get the bill. Yes.
All right. You're good.
You're good at this, Jimin.
Get in there.
[grunts]
We're done grocery shopping.
There's our car.
[Jung Kook] ♪ Let's go, let's go
Our car is shining ♪
Are you sure? Are you sure? Are you sure?
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[Jung Kook hums]
[Jung Kook laughs, sings]
Do you know that one? Stand there.
[Jung Kook imitates whooshing]
[Jung Kook laughs]
[♪ music ends]
"To the house after a short dance break"
Our faces aren't showing on the camera
because it's too dark.
-[Jimin] We can always do this.
-[Jung Kook] Turn on the light?
That's a good idea.
[exclaims]
I like it.
You can see our faces, right?
You're smart.
Taking a nap earlier really helped,
the more I think about it.
I didn't know you slept that well earlier.
I slept very well.
[♪ soft music playing on phone,
Jung Kook "My You"]
I think it's this way.
Arrived at their final accommodation
[Jung Kook] Well done.
Take the camera on your way out.
-[Jimin] Okay.
-[Jung Kook] One, two, three.
[clanks]
[♪ gentle music playing]
-[Jimin] Let's go.
-Okay, we have
-arrived!
-[Jimin] Arrived!
I like it, I like it.
[both exclaim]
-[Jimin] This place is great.
-[Jung Kook] It's amazing.
[Jimin]
Let me take a picture of you by the door.
[Jung Kook] Welcome to my house.
[camera shutter clicks]
[Jimin] Let's go inside.
[both] Yeah.
[Jimin] This is great, Mr. Jung Kook.
I love this place.
[Jung Kook] Is that the kitchen?
Wow, it's awesome.
Jimin tours the house first
[Jimin exclaims]
[Jimin] The rooms are great.
There are four beds and a bathroom here.
I love it.
[Jimin] Another here.
And I think this is a bathroom.
It's a closet.
If you go in here,
there's a bed here and another here.
Having a mirror there is kind of scary.
[♪ playful music playing]
Do you know what this is?
Do you know how good this is?
It's junk food.
There was a movie called…
Was it Zombieland?
There was a shotgun-wielding
crazy dude in there
who ate this.
So I've always wanted to try this…
and I was able to,
thanks to being part of BTS.
[Jimin] Hey, I'm hungry.
Jung Kook.
I'm hungry.
Why are you eating that?
We're having dinner soon.
I really wanted to try this.
[Jimin] Is it good? Do you like it?
I love it.
[Jimin] Then make me some pasta.
[Jung Kook] All right.
Jung Kook's authentic carbonara
Step 1. Separate the egg yolks
Step 2. Grate a whole lot of cheese
Step 3. Grind some pepper
Okay then.
I'll grill the skewers.
The duck face of concentration
[Jung Kook] Mr. Jimin, that smells great.
[Jimin] It's the smell of meat.
It might not taste as good.
[♪ relaxing music playing]
Is it good?
Mmm!
-[Jung Kook] It's good.
-[Jimin] Yeah?
It's time to put the pasta together
[♪ cheerful music playing]
We don't have garlic, do we?
No, we don't have garlic.
[Jung Kook] We don't have garlic?
[Jimin] No, we don't.
Aah. In that case,
I'll just use garlic powder.
[Jimin] Do we have garlic powder?
Garlic powder…
is right here.
[Jimin] This place has everything.
Are you sure? Is that right?
[sniffs]
[Jung Kook in English] Shake it, shake it.
[singing]
[in Korean] The cheese is a bit salty.
I'm sorry. I wanted to make you
an authentic Italian carbonara,
but the cheese is too salty.
[Jung Kook] I'm sorry.
I have no choice.
This looks like
something I saw at a hotel.
-I'm sorry.
-[Jimin] No worries.
I'm just honored to have your food.
[Jung Kook] Done!
"The carbonara is complete
after some ups and downs"
Turn the fork and lift some up.
-How?
-You know…
-[♪ whimsical music sting]
-[Jimin exclaims]
[♪ playful music playing]
I haven't had carbonara in a while.
Isn't it different
from the usual carbonara?
-No?
-I guess it tastes a bit different.
-[Jung Kook] Right?
-Yes.
The authentic way
is to use only egg yolks.
All the ingredients you need are
black pepper, egg yolks, bacon, garlic,
and some sugar.
[Jimin] And cheese.
Yes, cheese. Just those.
Apparently that's the authentic way.
Right, from Italy?
[Jung Kook] Yes.
This feels like a foodie trip.
I should try to eat less tomorrow,
when we have a slower schedule.
No.
But it's our last day together.
Where's the fun if you eat less?
[Jung Kook] I'm a great chef.
[Jimin] He's not answering.
"Pretending he didn't hear"
Maybe I should always put milk in.
It's actually delicious with milk.
Excellent.
What are we going to do now?
What?
I'm guessing you're tired
-because your eyes are half-closed.
-[♪ lullaby music playing]
It's because I'm full.
[laughs]
How did I get so puffy in two days?
You really
live life by your instincts, don't you?
You're sleepy because you're full?
Are you a baby?
[laughs]
"Embarrassed laugh"
It's food coma.
That's how babies are.
They do whatever they like and get sleepy.
[sighs]
[crickets chirping]
Let me hear it.
Trying to get Jimin to play his new song
-You said it's good.
-[song plays briefly]
No.
Hey!
[Jimin] Come on.
-This song is like my baby.
-No, thank you.
[♪ upbeat music playing on phone,
Jimin "Who"]
Here's a tip. You need to growl more.
No, don't.
-I've already finished recording.
-Let me listen.
I've already finished recording.
-Just play it.
-[Jimin] But…
You could've listened to it earlier!
Why are we doing this after everything?
I'm listening to it now.
[♪ upbeat music playing on phone,
Jimin "Who"]
Wait, okay. You sang well.
[sings along]
-About that last "more."
-[Jimin] It was intense.
You were flipping the note over
when you were singing it,
but it'll be better
to just sing it straight.
[Jimin] That's really hard.
-[vocalizing]
-[Jimin] So this time…
[grunts]
Not like this.
[Jimin laughs]
[both vocalizing]
-Don't go like that.
-[Jimin chuckles]
[vocalizing]
Don't squeeze it out.
-Sing it straight.
-[Jimin] I have to practice singing a lot.
It'll sound a lot better if you do that.
[Jimin vocalizing]
-Yes, don't do that.
-[Jimin] Right, I know I shouldn't.
I like the song.
I have a good feeling about it.
Thanks. This is the first time, isn't it?
-It is.
-Yes.
[Jimin sings "Who"]
[Jung Kook]
I can't wait to hear the finished version.
-[Jimin] Me too.
-[Jung Kook] This is going to be big.
Should I sleep next to Jung Kook tonight?
Will he hit me again?
[door opens]
[muffled chuckle]
[Jimin] All right.
[Jung Kook] I'm sleepy.
Let's go to sleep.
Good night.
[dings]
[♪ lullaby music playing]
I'm up.
"Heading straight over to Jimin's room"
[Jung Kook] Excuse me, sir.
[Jimin] What time is it?
[Jung Kook] Half past 11.
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry. I'm hungry. I'm hungry.
Should I turn this camera off again?
A snack to ease the hunger
[♪ playful music playing]
Uh-huh.
This is my foodie trip.
After I'm a bit full,
Jimin's going to say he's hungry,
and I'll be eating again.
I'm in trouble.
I shouldn't eat anything in London.
Did you think I was done?
[satisfied hum]
I'm full.
Jimin is still fast asleep
How about an episode
of me abandoning Jimin?
It's going to be hilarious
[Jung Kook whispers]
Mr. Jimin.
"Jung Kook decides not to abandon Jimin"
[Jung Kook grunts]
[Jimin] What time did you wake up?
[Jung Kook] Half past 11,
when I came in earlier.
Messing with Jung Kook 1
Messing with Jung Kook 2
Immediately overpowered
[groans]
We have to get a sponge.
-For washing dishes?
-[Jung Kook] Yeah.
"Couldn't wash the dishes yesterday"
Let's buy a sponge tomorrow.
This isn't working.
[Jung Kook beatboxing]
[Jung Kook exclaims]
[♪ quirky music playing]
[♪ playful music playing]
[Jung Kook] Should we go now?
We have to decide on
where we're going first.
-[Jung Kook] Walmart.
-What are you going to do in Walmart?
-[chuckles]
-[Jung Kook] Buy a sponge.
How many times do I have to say it?
Let's go get some burgers after Walmart.
Either burgers or fried chicken.
Are we sure about going out
just to get a sponge?
♪ Sunscreen ♪
Sunscreen - Composed and written by Jimin
[Jimin continues singing]
[Jimin] Sunscreen to block the UV rays.
Your face color is the same as my mom's
when she puts on foundation.
[Jung Kook] This is tone-up cream.
"Getting a hint of Jimin's mom
from Jung Kook"
[Jung Kook straining]
[Jimin] Let's go.
It's raining. Let's go.
Are you ready?
Let's ride!
[♪ upbeat music playing]
"To the supermarket"
[Jimin] Let's go!
It's hot down there, so be careful.
-Sorry?
-It's hot down there, so be careful.
I already got burned.
-Be careful with your legs.
-It was very hot,
so I learned my lesson.
Spread your legs out.
People who ride Harleys
aren't spreading their legs for no reason.
-It's because it's hot?
-It's because it's hot.
[Jimin]
I thought it was a masculine thing.
-No, it's because it's hot.
-It is?
-I can't believe that was it.
-That's right.
[whooping]
[Jung Kook humming]
Isn't it nice and cool?
[Jimin exclaims]
[Jimin] Yes, I love it.
[♪ upbeat music continues]
It's raining a lot.
[Jimin chuckles]
[Jimin] This is youth.
[Jung Kook]
Yeah, a little rain can't stop us.
This is youth!
[Jimin] Other than the fact
that the rain is hitting me a bit harder,
everything's good.
-Right.
-[Jimin laughs]
[Jimin] There'll be a storm
by the time we buy the sponge.
[Jung Kook] Let's just enjoy it.
[Jimin] All right then!
[Jung Kook] Are you good?
[Jimin] I'm good!
[Jung Kook sings "Seven"]
Please show lots of love to Are You Sure?!
[Jung Kook] This is youth, right?
-[Jimin] What?
-[Jung Kook] This is youth, right?
-What did you say?
-Youth, youth.
Booth?
"Booth."
This is booth!
[Jimin] Smooth?
[Jung Kook] I like smooth.
[Jimin chuckles]
[Jimin] There's no one around!
[Jung Kook] What are you talking about?
[♪ cheerful music playing]
It's fun, right?
[Jimin] I can't open my eyes.
[♪ cheeky music playing]
That stings.
Hey,
-the raindrops…
-Yes?
…are on attack mode.
Yes, they're hurting me.
[Jung Kook] It feels like hail.
"The raindrops are getting more vicious"
It hurts.
[Jung Kook] I don't care about the pain.
[Jimin] Okay.
[Jung Kook] I just want my sunglasses.
Rain, please.
Please stop.
-Please.
-What?
I'm telling the rain to stop.
-To shop?
-To stop.
-To stomp?
-To stop!
-To stop?
-Yes.
-Stop what?
-The rain.
-The rain?
-Yes.
-[Jimin] But this is all your fault.
-[Jung Kook] No.
-Well, maybe.
-It's all your fault.
I guess so.
[Jimin] Yes, that's good.
"Finally arrived through the heavy rain"
Let's go.
[in English] I'mma buy.
-[Jimin groans]
-[exclaims]
[in Korean] Oh, no.
-[groans]
-[Jung Kook chuckles]
[Jung Kook] I'm sorry.
[Jimin] I didn't come here for this.
Did I come here for this?
[Jung Kook] Are you okay? I'm sorry.
You tore off some of my skin.
[Jung Kook] I'm sorry.
[whines]
Why are you doing this to me these days?
It's at least once a day.
Why are you doing this every day?
Are you sure about this?
[Jung Kook coughs]
I'm sorry. Should we get some ointment?
Wow, sunflowers.
We have too much meat back at the house.
We don't need more meat.
-How about some toast?
-[gulps]
There was some bread.
Yes, there was.
[both exclaim]
-Take one.
-Lobsters.
"Some eye-catching lobsters"
[Jung Kook] Hi.
Those two are fighting.
"So exciting"
[Jung Kook] It's a battle.
Who's going to win?
The one on the right is retreating.
-It's…
-Hey.
-[Jung Kook] It's going in again.
-[Jimin] Hey!
[Jung Kook] These two are fighting.
[Jimin] Come back here.
[Jung Kook] The right one got overwhelmed.
The left one wins.
Why did we bring a cart
just to buy a sponge?
Well, it's youth.
[chuckles]
How is this youth?
The sponge might want to ride this.
Are those samples?
No, they're not.
Let's get some of this.
[exclaims]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
"Smells so good"
-Does it smell that good?
-This is potato.
-This looks good too.
-[chuckles]
-You said you wouldn't eat.
-Well…
[Jimin laughs]
-I swear you said you wouldn't eat.
-Get this too.
[Jung Kook] Fried chicken…
Aren't these two different?
Are they the same ones?
I want to eat what you're eating too.
-[Jung Kook] I see.
-[Jimin] You understand?
-There's some fried chicken here.
-[Jimin] I think this is potato.
[♪ music ends]
A pizza booth just next door
Doesn't this one look the best?
Yes, this one looks the best.
Do they cook this up for us?
I'd ask if I could speak English.
[hesitates]
"Fire it up"?
[chuckles]
[salesperson 1 in English]
Can I ask you a question?
Yeah.
[salesperson 1] Are you from South Korea?
-Maybe. Yeah.
-Yeah.
[in Korean] What do you mean "maybe"?
She… might not know who we are.
[salesperson 1 in English]
Wait. Are you BTS?
-[Jung Kook] Maybe.
-Yes.
-[salesperson 1] No way.
-"Maybe"?
[both laugh]
Hi.
-Hi.
-[Jimin] Hi.
-[Jung Kook] Wow. ARMY.
-My god.
-Really?
-[Jung Kook] Yeah.
[Jimin] Nice to meet you.
[salesperson 1] Nice to meet you.
[in Korean] We met an ARMY here.
She has an ARMY tattoo.
[in English] I want… it. But…
could we… use oven?
[salesperson 1] Yeah.
-[Jimin] Really?
-Cook?
-[salesperson 2] You want it cooked right?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
[in Korean] Oh, you can just say "cook."
Yes, I said "cook" just in case.
[laughs]
-That was great.
-To get my point across.
This would be perfect for a light meal.
-We just need the sponge.
-Let's get the sponge.
This looks great. Let's eat it here.
-[Jung Kook] Eat it here?
-Yes.
-[Jung Kook] Right now?
In that case, I'll go get the sponge.
I have a feeling I'll have to go
searching for you after I buy this.
It's a big place. Let's just go together.
We can meet at the entrance.
-[Jimin] Should I just wait there?
-Yes.
See you later.
"Jung Kook goes to find the sponge"
The sponge…
[in English] Sorry.
[exclaims]
[in Korean] Oh, of course. Of course.
There was something I wanted to eat.
I swear I saw it somewhere.
"He forgot about the sponge right away"
I definitely saw it here.
I definitely saw that avocado thing.
[gulps]
I saw the avocado here after the pickles.
After the watermelons.
That's strange.
I swear I saw it.
I definitely saw it
in a plastic container.
[exclaims]
Here it is.
"Got guacamole instead of a sponge"
And nacho chips. I need nacho chips.
[background announcement]
Nacho chips.
Where are the nacho chips?
"I have to dip them in the guacamole…"
"Meanwhile… Jimin is waiting
for the pizza"
I'm so hungry, so everything looks good.
[Jimin exclaims]
[Jimin] The sandwiches look great.
The salads look great too.
"Gulp, looks delicious"
[in English] Thank you.
-[salesperson 2] Have a good day.
-[Jimin] Thank you.
[in Korean]
I think the chips are here.
He was just here.
I just saw Jung Kook here.
[♪ lively music playing]
Where did he go?
"An unexpected game of hide-and-seek"
There he is.
Everyone who has siblings
has done this in the supermarket.
Searching for their younger siblings
from the end of aisles
going, "Where are they?"
-Did you find it?
-[Jung Kook] No, I didn't.
What did you get?
[Jimin] What did you get?
This? It's guacamole.
You were supposed to look for the sponge.
We can find one now.
You promised to get it.
You should've kept your promise first.
I was looking for a sponge.
[Jimin] And then you just wandered off.
No, no, no. That's not it.
Don't you need nacho chips to eat this?
Yes, I'm looking for them right now.
No, I'm looking for a sponge.
I knew it. I knew it.
Aren't these nacho chips?
They are.
Right? They're here.
Okay. Got them.
-Let's really get the sponge now.
-[Jung Kook] Yes, the sponge.
Let's go look for sponges.
I remember reading
something about kitchenware here.
Jimin, it's aisle 17.
Here it is.
-Some dish soap too.
-[Jung Kook] Get a tiny one.
[Jimin] Yes, a tiny one.
Let's go.
-Shall we?
-[Jimin] Yes.
[Jung Kook] It's raining like mad.
I'm hungry, let's eat
This is because of my curse.
[mouthful]
It's all your fault.
What is this?
Who cares about the rain? Let's eat
[exclaims]
-This was cheese.
-[Jung Kook] Mmm.
It's good.
-Let's go.
We need to put this away.
"Jung Kook runs away with the umbrella"
[birds chirping effect]
-[coughs]
-[Jimin] Seriously?
Don't!
"Dancing in the rain
after messing with Jimin"
This is fun!
This is freedom!
"Going by car because of the rain"
[Jung Kook]
It's raining so much all of a sudden.
Wow, is this okay?
It goes with the theme of the show.
-What theme? The title?
-Yes.
[chuckles]
Are we sure?!
I can't believe it's raining so much.
Are we sure about this?!
How is this possible?
[rain pattering stops]
-Huh.
-[rain pattering]
It went mute.
Seriously…
[Jimin] This is more comfortable.
I don't think there's been a day
where I didn't get wet.
I want to show this on camera.
You can turn it forward.
"Jimin's point of view"
[Jung Kook] Does it show?
[Jimin]
No. The weather looks clearer on camera.
It's raining so much.
The sound is insane.
I think our audio would get mixed up
with the rain sound.
[raises voice mildly]
Speak louder.
JK.
[Jimin] I can't see anything.
-[Jimin exclaiming]
-[rustling]
This is the pizza our ARMY made.
That's right.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
How is it?
"It's super delicious"
All right.
-It's delicious.
-Yes, this is my favorite.
We made the right choice.
How can this be your favorite?
This is the first thing you ate.
[♪ music stops]
-[♪ playful music playing]
-I meant we made the right choice.
You said it's your favorite.
I really like it.
We made the right choice.
You just "like" it?
[chuckles]
It's definitely
more delicious because our ARMY made it.
Yes, I wanted that kind of response.
[Jung Kook]
When I go back to work after this,
I'm only drinking water.
They finished their mission
of washing the dishes
-[Jung Kook] Let's go, Jimin!
-[Jimin] Shall we?
-I'll drive.
-[Jimin] I can drive.
-Do you want to drive?
-[Jimin] Yes.
Thank you.
-It's our last time in this car.
-That's too bad.
[Jung Kook] Say goodbye to it.
What's its name?
Well, my car's name is Ppongdaengi,
-so how about Boongdaengi?
-[beeps]
[Jung Kook] Boongdaengi?
[chuckles]
I don't like how that sounds.
Thanks for giving us a ride, car.
[coughs]
Let's go enjoy our final meal.
[Jung Kook] Let's go!
[Jimin] Let's go, Mr. Jung Kook.
"Heading to their final meal
with Boongdaengi"
It's still raining a bit.
I'll have to starve myself from tomorrow.
Don't do that.
You should eat at least once a day.
Eat chicken breasts or something.
Once a day is enough.
I'm getting rid of all sugar and carbs.
It's fine to eat once a day
if you work out.
-[Jung Kook] That's true.
-Is that too much?
Yes, too much workout
might mess with my throat.
That was great.
I can see why you wanted to ride it.
-The motorcycle?
-Yes, I liked it.
Feeling the breeze was great.
It'd be nice and safe riding here
where there's less traffic.
No rain would've been better.
It's supposed to be hot this time of year
-with a lot of rain.
-[Jung Kook] It's very humid.
[Jimin] Yes.
I think we're here.
I'm right. It's very close.
[Jung Kook] It is.
And it's our final stop.
[Jimin] Right.
We'll have to enjoy it to the fullest.
I heard the food's great here.
[in English] We got here. We got here.
-We got here.
-[Jimin in Korean] I can't turn this on.
Let's go enjoy our final meal.
[Jimin] We're eating our final meal!
I got fatter.
Whenever I'm on a variety show like this,
I always get fatter.
-[in English] Hello.
-Hi.
Nice to meet you.
[in Korean] This is nice.
This view is amazing.
Wow, that's going to be delicious.
[chuckles]
That smelled great, right?
-It did.
-[Jimin grunts]
Let's show the view first.
-[Jung Kook] I'm already getting it.
-[Jimin exclaims]
What's that person eating?
[Jimin] Mr. Jung Kook.
I love this.
I heard the lobster sandwich is good.
This one, and…
What's "Korean beef taco"?
What's that one?
[♪ playful music playing]
[Jung Kook] What are they eating?
It kind of looks like
the short rib grilled cheese.
It's not a sandwich.
Is it like a salad?
"What on earth is it?"
-What is it?
-Should we
ask them to give us a bite?
[laughs]
-[in English] "Could you give me some?"
-[Jimin laughs]
[in Korean] Should we get some beer?
I could go for that.
Okay then.
Let's get the sandwich.
Let's get the mac and cheese thing.
-The lobster mac and cheese.
-One of that.
We're Korean,
so we should get the Korean beef taco.
-[waiter] Hello. How are you doing today?
-[in English] Hello.
-[Jung Kook] Good.
-Good.
-Lobster mac and cheese, one.
-Yeah.
Lobster salad roll.
-Korean beef taco.
-[waiter] Korean beef taco.
-Yeah, one please.
-[waiter] Okay. Okay.
-Two Heineken, please. Yep.
-[waiter] Two Heineken.
-Yeah.
-[waiter] Thank you so much.
[Jimin] Thank you.
[in Korean] Everyone…
I love it here.
I love the atmosphere.
What are they? Oh, they're birds.
[♪ serene music playing]
-[Jung Kook in English] Thank you.
-[Jimin] Thank you, sir.
[in Korean] You have to pour beer
like this instead of pouring it slowly.
I saw that video too.
-[Jung Kook] That's how…
-[Jimin] And so…
-[Jung Kook] You don't get bloated.
-But mine is…
[chuckles]
Mine has too much foam.
[Jung Kook] See? Mine's perfect.
Cheers. Well done.
Look at my foam.
"Cheers to the last day!"
[Jimin] This was a great trip,
Mr. Jung Kook.
[content grunt]
[Jung Kook] This is great.
-I like it.
-You look cool, Jung Kook.
Why don't you go for a swim?
[Jimin] I just took a shower,
so I can't join him.
"A guy who knows how to enjoy the rain
with a beer in hand"
[Jung Kook] Being in the rain
like this gives me inspiration.
The rain and a glass of beer
Yes…
I'm getting inspired
[Jung Kook] I like it.
"I go where my feet take me"
[Jung Kook] Dear heavens…
please let go of your wrath.
Why do you…
weep so profusely?
I like it. It's great.
The end of Master Jung Kook's monologue
You're doing this all wrong.
"Getting an earful for just sitting down"
Wearing slippers?
Don't I look like a local
who lives around here?
-No, like this restaurant's owner.
-[Jimin] I'm not all cool
like you from earlier.
[laughs]
[both exclaim]
[Jung Kook exclaims]
-[Jimin in English] Oh. Oh, thank you.
-[waiter] You're welcome.
[in Korean] Let's dig in.
-[waiter in English] Enjoy.
-Thank you.
[both exclaim]
[in Korean] This is it.
This one. This one.
[Jung Kook] This is the Korean beef taco,
the lobster mac and cheese,
and the lobster sandwich.
-[Jimin] The lobster salad…
-[Jung Kook] Wow.
…roll.
[hissing]
"An excited Jung Kook's wild camerawork"
[Jung Kook chuckles]
-Perfect.
-Can we eat now?
-[Jung Kook] Let's eat.
-Okay.
[amazed exclaim]
This looks delicious. My goodness.
[Jung Kook] The cheese. Oh, yes.
[satisfied hum]
[whistles]
[Jung Kook] It's so good.
This was made for me.
This is amazing.
We have to eat this now.
[Jung Kook] We should try it.
"Next is the lobster salad roll"
[Jimin] I'll hold it.
[exclaims]
[Jimin] There's this too.
-It's good.
-[Jimin] Is it?
This is
Super delicious
Oh, wow.
[Jimin] This is amazing.
[amazed hum]
Cheers to how delicious they are
[exhales sharply]
Alert
[Jung Kook] That was great.
[Jimin] Wow, this was delicious.
[Jung Kook] I'm so happy.
We'll come back with a new season.
We've eaten a lot.
We've eaten a lot and gotten sick a lot.
See you again.
[sighs]
[both] Are you sure?!
[chuckles]
We started this
because we just wanted to do it,
and now it's actually started.
I don't know how many times we'll do this,
but I hope we can travel a lot
so we can show you
a lot of our traveling adventures.
How many more should we do?
-I'm thinking at least season 12.
-Season 12?
Let's practice being better entertainers
so the two of us can continue doing this.
-Even after our military services?
-Yeah.
Until we turn 50.
[in elderly voice] Oh, Mr. Jung Kook.
Slow down.
[in normal voice] Let's become
world-renowned entertainers.
"We shall continue until they become
world-renowned entertainers"
Hello, everyone, this is Jimin.
[breathes deeply]
There was
a ramyeon I really wanted to eat
during this trip.
Tomorrow…
I'll be going on a plane to Korea.
I could've just eaten this there,
so I actually don't understand
why I'm eating it now.
But I was really craving this.
Thanks for following us along
on this trip.
"A ramyeon to reward myself
after a tough few days"
[exclaims]
"Finished it in just a couple of bites"
Wow, I finished it.
I'm puffy already.
My nose is still swollen.
That was a fun trip.
I'll have a safe ride back home.
Best of luck to Jung Kook's Seven.
Are You Sure?!
Translated by Yenny Kang