(Episode 22)
I don't want to be stuck in this hospital.
It's like a cage in here.
Sister Xiaomeng.
Can you take me home?
Tiankong, what's wrong with this place?
Look.
All these big sisters are here
to play with you.
And a big brother too.
No. It's not nice at all.
I don't want injections,
I don't want pills,
and I don't want surgery!
Sister Xiaomeng.
I'll behave.
Please don't send me here again.
I hate this place!
Alright, Tiankong. Don't cry.
Why don't I take you out to play?
Tiankong,
I know a place that's really fun.
Do you want to go there?
You're not lying, right?
Where is this place?
Come, let's find out.
Let me help you get changed.
Here, put these on.
These will protect your eyes
when you go out.
Sister Xiaomeng, are we in a park?
How did you know?
I can smell it, and hear it.
I can smell the grass, and the flowers.
There are many trees and birds here.
You're so smart, Tiankong.
You're completely right.
Sister Xiaomeng, why did you take me here?
Because you're the most well-behaved
and the bravest boy ever.
Over the next few days,
Sister Qiao Zhen, Brother Xiao, and I
will all play with you.
-Alright?
-Yes!
Tiankong!
Are you okay?
Sister Xiaomeng.
Are you doing this
because I'm about to do my surgery?
Sister Xiaomeng,
I know you're doing this just for me.
But I'm really scared.
I don't want to undergo surgery.
I heard some people couldn't see
after they did their surgery.
Sister Xiaomeng,
talk to the doctor for me.
Tell him not to do the surgery, please?
Tiankong.
Let's not think about anything today.
Let's just play and have fun, okay?
Yes, let's play together.
You're flying!
Is this fun?
Yes!
Tiankong, don't you feel
like a bird flying?
Very much!
Let's fly!
Little bird fly!
I'm flying!
Tiankong.
What are you thinking
in that little head of yours?
I was thinking if only I was a bird.
I could fly to wherever I want to go.
Tiankong, you know?
I want to be a bird too.
I want to fly freely
in the sky.
Sister Xiaomeng, let's fly together.
We'll fly across the sea
all the way to the clouds, okay?
Yes. I will go with you.
Let's fly! Fly!
Brother, can I really be a bird?
Of course you can be a bird.
You can fly in the sky,
and touch the clouds.
When you look down from the sky,
you'll see the green grass,
the red flowers,
and the sparkling rivers.
But I'm about to lose my eyesight.
Tiankong,
do you want to see this beautiful world?
Yes. But I don't want to do surgery.
Do you know what I do?
I know. You're a doctor.
I am a doctor.
That's why I can promise you,
after your surgery,
you'll recover very quickly.
Will I be able to see everything
after my surgery?
I promise you.
Look at this flower.
After your surgery,
you will see
its red petals and green leaves.
Tiankong,
what do you want to be when you grow up?
I want to be a painter!
But if I can't see anything,
I won't be able to paint anymore.
Tiankong, I have faith in you.
When your eyes get better,
you'll definitely be able to paint again.
You'll paint such a colorful world.
But I'm afraid of the pain.
People say surgeries are painful.
Remember what Sister Xiaomeng said?
You're the bravest boy
in the world.
If only it wouldn't hurt at all.
I'm a doctor.
I know this surgery well.
It'll be like going to sleep.
When you wake up and open your eyes,
you'll be able to see Sister Xiaomeng
and Director Lin clearly.
Really? Will it not hurt at all?
Of course!
He's a doctor. He's always right.
We'll be with you the whole time.
We'll be rooting for you.
Sister Xiaomeng. Will you be with me
during the surgery too?
Of course, Tiankong.
I promise you.
All of us will be with you.
After your surgery,
you'll be able to see all of us
and continue painting.
You'll be a painter again.
Sister Xiaomeng. I'll do as you say.
I'll do the surgery.
After the surgery,
I'll be able to see you,
Sister Qiao Zhen, and Big Brother.
Oh right, and Mommy Lin too.
Also, I want to continue painting.
Tiankong, you're the best.
Good job, we're so proud of you.
Thank you, Sister Xiaomeng.
Thank you, Sister Qiao Zhen.
Thank you, Big Brother.
Tiankong,
the person you should thank the most
is Big Brother.
When my eyes get better,
I'll make a drawing of you.
Make sure you make him look handsome.
He's so ugly.
Big Brother, are you ugly?
I'll make you better looking.
Don't get mad. Here.
Have some fruit. You'll look better.
I'm not angry.
You're right.
Tiankong.
Let's eat fruit too.
Are you ticklish? Are you?
Are you ticklish?
Dr. Xiao, Senior.
Thank you guys for staying with
Tiankong and I these last few days.
Thank you so much.
No worries.
We had a lot of fun too.
I haven't had so much fun in a while.
You were with Tiankong all day today.
You haven't eaten anything at all.
How about I'll treat you dinner later?
Xiaomeng, I'm a doctor.
It's my job.
Take Qiao Zhen out,
I'll stay
That's so impolite.
Xiaomeng wants to treat us.
How could you turn her down?
Exactly. Both of you have to come.
Alright then.
But I don't think
it's right for you to pay.
I'll pay instead.
Sure.
Xiaomeng will take us out.
Dr. Xiao will pay for it.
Perfect.
That'll make me happy.
Sister Xiaomeng, where are you guys going?
I want to come too.
Tiankong, not tonight.
It's getting late.
You should go to bed soon.
Alright, I'll take Tiankong to his ward.
You guys wait for me in the restaurant.
But I want to be with Sister Xiaomeng
a little longer.
Sister Xiaomeng, take me back to the ward.
-Okay, okay.
-Be good.
Tiankong.
You must listen to me.
How about this?
I'll take Tiankong back,
you guys can go ahead.
I'll join you later.
That sounds good.
Dr. Xiao, let's go.
But...
No buts.
He'll be safer with Xiaomeng
than any doctor.
Come on, let's go.
Don't worry. Let's go.
Xiaomeng, hurry up!
Alright, I will.
Let's go.
Tiankong, let's go back.
Dr. Xiao, you don't mind
paying for our dinner?
Of course not.
You wouldn't mind paying
for Xiaomeng of course.
But now there's just the two of us.
I don't know if you'll mind.
What are you talking about?
Alright then. It's a deal.
I'm going to order
the most expensive stuff.
I'll order the entire menu.
Qiao Zhen. Actually a doctor
doesn't make nearly as much
as people say we do.
Go easy on me.
You're so cute.
Come on, let's go.
Sister Xiaomeng,
why don't you tell me your favorite story?
Alright, I'll tell you a story
about a playground, okay?
Yes!
I want to go to a playground.
There was a girl named Wendy.
She really, really liked playgrounds.
Her brother Jack adored her.
And so,
Jack built a mini playground for Wendy
in their own house.
There were many
cute little things in that playground.
Such as a little train filled with eggs.
At night, all these toys
all came alive.
(A Yan)
I'm busy. What is it?
Well,
Tiankong's surgery is tomorrow.
I want to stay
at the hospital with him tonight.
Is that okay?
A Yan?
Alright, sure.
Go ahead.
But...
I'm a little worried about my mom.
She's alone at home.
I'll get Guang and Sister Hua
to take care of her.
-You...
-Yes?
Be safe.
Okay, I will.
Take a break and have a coffee.
I'm almost done. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Um...
there's a new Japanese restaurant
on Xingfu Street that's very authentic.
I was thinking...
Qingyan.
President Zhou.
Thanks for your hard work.
Once you're done with the documents,
go home and get some rest.
Tomorrow will be another tough battle.
With you around,
we're not afraid of any battles.
Bye, President Zhou.
Alright.
Qingyan, you were saying something
about Xingfu Street?
There's a very authentic
Japanese restaurant on Xingfu Street.
-I was thinking...
-Sure.
Tomorrow will be a long day.
Let's relax tonight. It'll be my treat.
Really?
Sure, I'll go get ready.
Unlocked. Please open.
It's so late.
Is Xiaomeng coming?
Hello, Xiaomeng?
What? You're not coming?
Alright. Take care of Tiankong
at the hospital then.
Okay, bye.
Xiaomeng said she isn't coming.
Come, let's keep drinking.
Cheers.
It's getting late.
We shouldn't drink anymore.
I'm in a good mood today.
Don't take my beer away.
Don't take my beer away!
Please stop drinking.
Dr. Xiao...
do you have a girlfriend?
No.
I like you.
I don't care if you like anyone else.
Will you be my boyfriend?
♪Pounding breathes♪
♪Innocent sweetness♪
♪Used to be♪
♪The secrets that we shared♪
♪The path of life♪
♪Was rippled because of you♪
♪Once I thought about
leaving everything for you♪
♪Should I lament♪
♪Or resent our fate♪
♪The causeway of destiny♪
Come, let's sit down.
Come, let's drink some more.
Sit down.
Sit down!
Were you shocked?
You fell for it, didn't you?
Listen.
I used to study theater in school.
I even won a prize.
I used to--
Don't take it seriously.
Don't you take it seriously.
I was just kidding with you.
Look at you.
I'd never fall for you.
You're just a dork.
♪I just wish♪
♪I could let go of my longing for you♪
♪All the hurt in the past♪
Don't worry. I won't take it seriously.
I know you'll never fall for me.
That's good.
Oh, no!
I forgot I had to work at the station.
I should go.
Are you okay?
I'm okay, Dr. Xiao.
Don't worry about me.
Please. Alright?
Shall I take you there?
Take this. My treat.
You don't have to.
I said take it.
I'll grab a taxi with you.
No...
I'll grab one myself.
Please enter the combination,
followed by the pound key.
Unlocked. Please open.
Oh my gosh, how embarrassing.
Qiao Zhen, what have you done?
You were supposed to restrain yourself.
What should I do now?
How am I going to talk to him from now on?
Qiao Zhen!
I drank too much last night.
I drank so much.
I have work to do, bye.
Nothing happened last night.
You left your purse with me.
Thank you, Dr. Xiao.
See you.
Qiao Zhen.
Come with me.
(Be my girlfriend)
♪A sudden crack♪
♪Got on my nerves and caused me pain♪
I reconsidered a lot last night.
It's my fault.
I was too cowardly when it comes to love.
I've lost so many chances of
moving forward with you.
Qiao Zhen, please give me one more chance.
I don't want to lose you.
Would you give me a chance
to take care of you from now on?
♪Take back my heart♪
♪Take back my soul♪
♪Don't make me cry♪
♪And leave me in sadness♪
♪There must be
a parallel universe of love♪
You mean...
you want to be my boyfriend?
♪I make my confession♪
♪There must be buttons of love
in parallel♪
♪And a reason for our love at this moment♪
♪Because I love you♪
I looked at some shopping guides
and your social media.
I found a picture of you
and Xiaomeng with facial masks on.
You said you'd get strangely happy
after putting on a mask.
So I bought some this morning.
I don't know what these masks do,
but I hope
you'll look radiant every day.
I didn't think you'd be so thoughtful.
Facial masks?
♪a parallel universe
of love on my sadness♪
♪to make up for the lost moments♪
Tianmei Decor.
Let's quote $30,000.
Okay.
Shuili Engineering.
You're here. Come on in.
President Zhou.
The auction is about to begin.
We should go.
Tiankong, don't be afraid.
Remember what we said yesterday?
You'll go to sleep, and when you wake up,
the surgery will be over.
Director Lin.
I'm here. I'm here.
If the surgery goes well,
can I call you Mommy?
Of course. Of course you can.
My Tiankong.
You're the bravest kid around.
Xiaomeng and Mommy
will be waiting for you here.
Mommy, Sister Xiaomeng.
I'm nervous.
Tiankong, be good.
Don't be nervous or afraid.
It'll be over soon.
Wait.
Tiankong, look.
This is my protective charm.
I'll give it to you.
Here, put it on.
It'll keep you safe.
Everything will go well.
My mother left this for me.
Now I'm giving it to you.
(Hospital)
Dr. Xiao, your coffee.
Thank you.
Qiao Zhen.
Director Lin, have some coffee.
Thank you.
Xiaomeng.
Here, have some coffee.
Thank you.
I was in the area.
I heard Tiankong's surgery was today.
So I came to visit him.
How's everything going?
The doctor's still in there.
We don't know yet.
Xiaomeng, don't worry.
You're always so good to him.
I'm sure the surgery will go well.
Don't worry.
Jiang Ze, thank you.
Thanks for hiring the specialist
from overseas for Tiankong.
How about this.
I'll buy you dinner next time.
Well...
don't worry about it.
But I'll hold you to your word.
You're taking me out for dinner.
-Okay.
-I have work to do.
I'll go back to work now.
If anything happens, call me anytime.
Don't forget, okay?
Okay.
-Bye.
See you, Director Lin.
Bye.
Congratulations to Shenghai
for getting the bid.
It's all thanks to you
for raising the price for Mr. Jiang.
I feel bad for your President Zhou.
He's going to pay hundreds of
millions more now.
He'll definitely be mad later.
Make sure you appease him.
You don't have to worry about that.
Doctor.
Did Tiankong's surgery go well?
How is he?
Don't worry, everyone.
The surgery went very well.
He'll wake up
once the anesthesia wears off.
If he recovers well,
he'll be able to see
normally again very soon.
He'll be fine.
-Great!
That's so great!
Senior.
Did you two...
Could you check for me?
President Zhou, I was the only one
who knew about that document.
But I never--
Alright.
I trust you.
Okay, thank you.
Okay. Thanks a lot.
President Zhou.
Flights are all very full
so we can't switch.
We can only go back to Nanyue as planned.
Okay.
-Here you go.
-Hello.
Thank you.
Just put it down.
Enjoy.
The food's all here.
Dr. Xiao.
I want to propose this toast to you.
If you hadn't put in a request
to Director Lin about Tiankong's surgery,
things wouldn't have happened so fast.
You can't drink.
Drink this instead.
Xiaomeng, actually I--
Alright, you're just being modest.
But it's not all praise for you today.
I'm not pleased about one thing.
Did I do something wrong?
Why didn't you tell us anything
about you and Senior?
Senior, you too.
How can you call yourself my best friend?
You didn't say a word.
I've been so busy with Tiankong.
I didn't have time to tell you.
Dr. Xiao,
you've found the right person.
My senior is the kindest
and warmest girl in the world.
You must be good to her.
I want to make a toast to you today.
Here's wishing you happiness.
Okay.
You drank everything.
Drink slowly. You have a small mouth.
After what Xiaomeng said
-why aren't you drinking?
-Dig in.
Director Lin, have some of this.
Have some of this.
It's tea.
I changed it to tea for you.
Aren't you driving me home later?
This is very good.
You shouldn't drink if you're driving.
I'm too happy, I forgot.
I want to--
Dr. Xiao.
It's my turn now.
Dr. Xiao,
I want to toast you
for saving Tiankong.
You saved his life
and you saved our home.
Director Lin.
Please don't say that.
I grew up on welfare myself.
It made me what I am.
You're so modest.
This toast is on behalf of Tiankong,
but I also want to congratulate
you and Qiao Zhen.
I just heard about it.
You're such a good match.
I wish you all the best.
Thanks Director Lin.
Dr. Xiao and I
will come by the home a lot more often.
You must.
Let's make a toast to Director Lin.
Okay.
Why are you toasting me?
I'm the oldest here.
Xiaomeng,
Qiao Zhen and Dr. Xiao,
you three are so kind.
I'm so lucky to have met
the three of you.
If only there are more people like you,
this world would be so much better.
Director Lin,
stop flattering us three.
It's making me dizzy.
Come, let's eat.
-Let's eat.
-Why are you looking at me?
Let's stop talking and eat.
Senior, let's drink another glass.
Okay.
Cheers to all of us.
-Sure.
-Here's to happiness.
-Okay.
This restaurant is so good.
Yes, it is.
How are we leaving?
Senior,
you've been so busy the last two days.
You must be tired.
You don't have to come
to the hospital tomorrow.
I can take care of Tiankong myself.
It's been really busy at the station.
I really should get back to work.
Xiaomeng, where are you parked at?
In the parking lot behind.
I'm parked there too.
Director Lin, Qiao Zhen,
-I'll get the car.
-Wait here.
-Go ahead.
-Okay.
-Go.
-Bye.
Dr. Xiao, I never thought
you and Senior
would get together so quickly.
I already knew Senior likes you.
But you were always so slow.
I tried to give you hints so many times.
I'm such a dummy.
But I knew how she felt.
I was just too cowardly
when it came to love.
I must thank Qiao Zhen.
She gave me the courage
to make the leap.
Look how far we've come.
We did the art show,
and you and Senior got together.
Tiankong will be able to see too.
So many happy things have happened.
How wonderful!
What's wrong?
Xiaomeng.
Something has been weighing on me.
What is it?
The person who actually
helped Tiankong wasn't me.
You've told me before.
It was Jiang Ze who helped.
He got in touch with
the specialist from overseas.
I'll buy you all dinner soon.
It wasn't him.
It wasn't Jiang Ze?
Then why did he say yes when I told him
I wanted to thank him?
I don't know.
He probably doesn't want to miss
a chance to have dinner with you.
If it wasn't Jiang Ze,
then who was it
who helped so much?
It was the boss of Shenghai Group.
You mean A Yan?
Xiaomeng,
I'm just an average doctor.
I don't have the power to get
Tiankong a cornea donor.
Many people wanted to help Tiankong.
But the person who helped the most
was Mr. Zhou.
He was the one
who got in touch with cornea centers
and cornea donor organizations.
He found a donor organization in Sri Lanka
who agreed to give Tiankong a cornea.
I was shocked too when I found out.
But that's the truth.
The person we should thank the most
is Zhou Yanzhao.
Then why didn't you tell me earlier?
He didn't want me to.
I think he has his own plans.
Xiaomeng,
you should sit down with him
and clear your misunderstandings.
I don't know
if I'll ever get the chance to do that.
(Qiao Zhen)
Qiao Zhen's calling. Let's go.
-See you then.
-Okay.
Your car's here.
Director Lin, let me take you.
Thank you.
Be safe. See you.
Director Lin,
Tiankong will be able to see again
in a few days.
I'll come to the hospital
to see him often.
So don't worry.
I really don't know
how to thank you, Xiaomeng.
You didn't have to do so much.
You've done so much
so that Tiankong can see.
If it hadn't been for you,
I don't know what would've happened.
It was fate for me to meet Tiankong.
When I was feeling down,
he also helped me a lot.
That's why, Tiankong is lucky
to have a sister like you.
You're his mother now.
He's really lucky to have you.
Yes.
But this surgery was very high risk.
I kept reassuring Tiankong,
but deep inside
I was still worried.
I'm sure
it was the ring you gave Tiankong
before the surgery
that brought him good luck.
Tiankong.
This is my protective charm.
My mother left this for me.
Now I'm giving it to you.
Director Lin.
This is Zhou Yanzhao from Shenghai Group.
Mr. Zhou, nice to meet you.
I had a child
when I was younger.
But I lost him after all.
(Facial recognition system processing...)
(Complete)
(Test Results)
How...
How could this be?
(97% maternity match suggested)
That means...
Uncle Zhou...
really wasn't A Yan's father?