(Episode 44)
Hello?
Where are you?
Wait for me.
Father, where are you going?
Something came up. I need to go out.
Xiaomeng, there's one more thing
I need to apologize to you for.
It's about the spread of
your indecent photo on the internet,
I was the one who shared it.
Don't blame me for not reminding you.
Men are no doubt
good at flirting.
But look at what you are like now.
Check your email.
Okay.
Get it done. It's a must.
Don't worry.
But why...
Why did you do that?
I wanted President Zhou so badly.
I adore and look up to him.
But I don't know how to get him.
I was too silly.
Xiaomeng, after this incident,
you two must get along well.
Only you can make him happy.
I wish you the best.
Boss, boss.
Is this really the last resort?
Listen, the police are suspicious
about me, you know?
You don't need me
to tell you what to do, do you?
It's time to return my favor
when I saved your life outside the casino
five years ago.
Boss, my life is not worthy.
It can be gone anytime.
But I have family to take care of.
If I'm gone, they--
Don't worry.
I've thought it through for you.
I've transferred a big sum of money
to your wife's bank account.
It's enough for her
to spend for decades, you know?
Actually this isn't
what I expected as well.
If anyone is at fault,
Zhou Yanzhao is to be blamed,
right?
Yes.
Right.
You sure it's him?
Okay, thank you.
A Yan, what's wrong?
Nothing.
We had a deal.
No matter what happens,
we shouldn't hide things from each other.
Jiang Qingcheng's assistant...
has just died.
What? He's dead?
The call was from the police,
saying that he jumped off the building.
I think there's something fishy
going on here.
Jiang Qingcheng must've
suspected something.
In that case,
he can blame all the fault
onto his assistant.
Dead men tell no tales.
Guang,
follow Xiaomeng closely for now,
don't leave her alone.
Brother Yan, are you worried that
they might move in on Xiaomeng?
Jiang Qingcheng is ruthless.
I'm afraid he might do something else.
So for the time being,
you have to follow Xiaomeng closely.
Don't ever leave her alone.
Don't worry.
A Yan, Jiang Qingcheng now sees you
as his worst enemy.
So you should be more careful.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
Have you seen the news?
Someone jumped off the building just now.
That's normal.
There're many cases like this.
No. I've seen this person before.
He was always here to look for
Vice President Jiang.
Jumping from such a height,
what an awful death.
I'm going back to work.
Okay.
Secretary Zhao, where's my father?
He didn't come to work today.
I don't know where he is either.
I'll get back to work.
Rubbish!
How could this happen?
Didn't you say so confidently
that there's no problem with
the company's operation?
What excuse is this?
Three days. I'll only give you three days.
Solve the problem immediately.
I don't care how you do it.
I only want the outcome.
A Ze, why are you back?
The statement of
Dikai Commercial City's project shows
an unusual transaction.
After checking,
it was you who approved it.
What did you do
with such large amount of money?
This day has finally come.
You can discuss business matters
with me already.
Father,
I don't wish to see you make mistakes.
A foreign subsidiary had problem
with its capital turnover.
It was used to deal with the emergency.
Is that really all?
Son, with so many things happening,
I feel really old
and tired.
Maybe it's time for me to retire.
After I retire,
I'll pass the company to you.
I'll go fishing, play sports,
live the life of an elderly person.
Father, why don't...
you reconcile with Zhou Yanzhao?
The matter is getting critical by day.
It'll be out of control if this continues.
Son, we must not reconcile.
This is our last chance.
Discharge one
when he has served his purpose.
Now it's not about choosing
to advance or retreat.
Instead we must fight till the end.
It's not only for the Jiang family now,
but also for your future, you know?
Father, if we continue fighting,
we may lose everything.
If we retreat now,
we can still start over.
I'm old already.
I have no more chance to start over.
But you still have me.
I've made up my mind.
Stop persuading me.
(Your period has been delayed for 45 days.
You might be pregnant.)
(Got it)
(Period has been delayed for 45 days)
This is the recording
my sister passed to me.
Also the bank statement that shows
the money Jiang Qingcheng
transferred to me.
If you want to litigate,
I'm willing to be the witness.
If you had told me this earlier,
things would have not ended up this way.
It's too late to talk about the past
that cannot be changed.
I made a mistake, so I should be punished.
President Zhou,
thank you.
I'm really lucky to have met you.
Don't worry.
I'll plead to the judge.
When you come back,
the seat outside is still yours.
There's another reason...
I came here today.
♪I am not sure if your hands♪
♪Will hold on to the past♪
Have you thought it through?
I have no reason to stay.
Okay.
I respect your decision.
You really decided to leave?
I've heard something from President Zhou.
But...
why did you leave so suddenly?
Even if President Zhou wants you to leave,
I can ask for his forgiveness.
I decided to leave.
I've worked here for such a long time.
It's time to move on.
-Lingxi, I--
-I'm leaving.
I'm glad to have you as my colleague.
Don't be a workaholic.
It's time to think about your life.
(Shenghai Group)
♪A sudden crack♪
♪Got on my nerves and caused me pain♪
♪Everything has become pale to me♪
♪Diving with my happiness♪
Lingxi.
Please don't go.
♪Our silent and broken past♪
♪Is awaiting you to touch it
Once in a while♪
♪Take back my heart♪
♪Take back my soul♪
♪Don't let me cry♪
♪And leave me in sadness♪
Lingxi!
♪A parallel universe of love♪
♪Making amends for the mistakes of time♪
♪Take back my heart♪
♪Take back my soul♪
♪Don't let me cry♪
♪I make my confession♪
What's wrong?
I...
I have something to tell you.
Lingxi.
I've been keeping this
to myself for a long time.
But I must tell you today.
Lingxi.
No matter what happens,
regardless of the mistakes you made,
I hope we can face it together.
Because I like you.
I've liked you all this while.
Can you give me a chance
to take care and protect you?
You don't have to answer me now.
I hope you can really consider it.
No rush.
Qingyan.
Thank you.
Thank you?
Is this how you're going to reject me?
Qingyan,
you're kind and friendly.
You treat everyone well.
You're a great man.
It's just that I'm so messed up now.
I really can't jump into
a new relationship yet.
But I'll always remember your kindness.
We can be good friends forever.
You know what, Qingyan?
Love needs to be unlocked
with a fingerprint.
But not everyone...
can unlock it.
I understand.
Everyone needs to find the right person
to unlock their heart.
Unfortunately,
you're not the one I'm looking for.
Lingxi!
Qingyan, I wish you happiness.
You'll meet a better girl.
Lingxi!
♪Will hold on to the past♪
♪I want to say I love you♪
♪Everything stops then♪
♪It ought to be the farthest love♪
♪With our backs against the sea♪
♪We enclose the memories in our hearts♪
Come in.
Tired at work?
Xiaomeng, why are you here?
I made you lunch.
You don't have to do that yourself.
By the way,
Sun Lingxi came today.
She passed me the recording.
Did she say anything?
She resigned.
It's to be expected.
She has a strong personality.
She has got a mind of her own.
By the way, regarding Jiang Qingcheng,
what do you have in mind?
Anything you say.
At this point,
there's no point in fighting
over anything.
I only hope
he could realize his mistake
and never harm others.
Should I talk to Jiang Ze then?
That'll be fine.
After all, he is Jiang Qingcheng's son.
Okay.
I know what to do now.
Let's eat.
I'll go home first.
Come home early.
Got it.
President Zhou, I just got dumped
and you're so lovey-dovey.
Qingyan,
I think you still have a chance.
It's just that Lingxi
can't think about it yet
given her current condition.
When it comes to courting a girl,
if you fail once, try it again.
Don't give up if you really like her.
Don't worry.
I'm just not in good condition lately.
But I won't give up on Sun Lingxi.
What's up?
This is the operational report of
Dikai Commercial City.
As we collaborated with their competitor,
putting pressure on them,
Dikai Commercial City decided
to engage in a price war.
Now they can't make ends meet
and are in debt.
Our initial objective is starting to work.
In less than a week, Dikai Commercial City
will be investigated by
regulatory departments
due to capital chain issue.
Let's stop it.
Wait.
What did you say?
Stop it.
Don't push them to the edge.
But I don't understand.
If we pull out now,
won't all our hard work go to waste?
I understand what you're trying to say.
But now, I don't want to do this anymore.
Give them a chance.
President Zhou,
ever since you're married,
you've totally changed.
It's often said marriage can change a man.
I didn't believe it.
Is that so? After being married,
one will become more careful,
and be afraid of losing.
I don't like the idea of
letting Jiang Qingcheng go.
After all, he'd caused us so much damage.
What can you do if you don't let him go?
Intriguing against each other is tiring.
I only want Jiang Qingcheng
to realize his mistake,
and put an end to this matter.
I want to stop taking revenge.
We need to put our focus
on the Commercial Integrated Sports Center
and the Guest House project.
This is Xiaomeng's wish, as well as mine.
Shenghai needs to move forward.
Got it, President Zhou.
I'll do as you said.
Go.
Hello.
Are you free?
Let's meet tonight.
-Get me a drink.
-Okay.
What's up?
(DK Commercial City Project
bank statement)
What do you plan to do?
How long have we known each other?
Quite long, I suppose.
You're my friend.
Even though your father deserves it,
I don't want to push him to the wall.
I've talked to him earlier, but he--
The situation is different now.
I believe you know it well.
At the moment, Xiaomeng and I
chose not to report to the police.
We hope he could give himself up
to the police.
So that he could
gain back his self-respect.
A Ze.
Don't let him stray further.
Thank you, A Yan.
Father.
I'm your son.
Have you ever thought for me?
Why did you suddenly say so?
Are you going to abandon me
for your own sake?
Nonsense.
You're my son.
I can do anything for you.
Don't you understand?
Since young, I've been watching
how you treat others and me.
Do you know why I'm unwilling
to join your business circle?
Because I don't want
to be under your thumb forever.
I want to start my own business.
Did you ever support me?
With you, I have no freedom at all.
Freedom?
You're too selfish.
What did you say?
Zhou Yanzhao and Xiaomeng
have got all your evidence of crime.
You misappropriated company funds.
They've known it.
They haven't reported to the police yet,
hoping that you could surrender.
Father, please surrender yourself.
So that we can gain back
self-respect for Jiang's family.
Surrender, surrender.
By now, there's no more self-respect.
Father, you taught me yourself.
Men aren't afraid of making mistakes.
Once you've done it,
be it a mistake or a crime,
you can't run away.
Doomed.
Jiang's family is doomed.
No, Father.
You've owned so much.
Why aren't you letting go?
You've harmed so many people.
You put Shenghai in a critical situation.
You ruined Ronghui.
You unscrupulously took over Lingtian.
Look at your greed. What have you done?
What have I done?
Did I do all these for my own sake?
It was for you.
To get more leverage for your future.
I don't need these.
These aren't what I want.
Have you truly thought of what I want?
It's not that I'm not interested
in business.
I like internet entrepreneurship.
But the deceptions and battles
in your business circle
aren't what I want to get involved in.
What I want to do is
to catch hold of the current trend and
use my own ability to make money.
Father, please surrender yourself.
Surrender?
Do you know what surrender means?
Son, you're pushing me
to the prison.
You're already in prison.
Your desire and greed
have already trapped you.
Only if you surrender,
you get a second chance.
That's the father whom I respect.
I just wanted to go higher.
I didn't expect I'd come to this point.
Father, you're too extreme.
Success isn't earned
at the expense of others.
It's not too late to turn around.
Father, I beg you.
Please surrender.
All right, son.
I promise you.
I'll surrender to the police.
Okay.
I'll get you the best lawyer and team.
Don't worry, father.
I'll leave it to you.
You decide.
Leave me alone.
Father, don't worry.
I'll take care of everything.
Book me a ticket to Singapore.
Today's flight.
No return ticket.
As soon as possible.
-A Yan, eat more.
-Thanks, Mother.
(Jiang Ze)
-Hello?
-Hello.
Xiaomeng, it's me.
My father booked
a direct flight to Singapore.
Got it.
Xiaomeng, what's wrong?
It's Jiang Ze, right?
He told me his father booked
a direct flight to Singapore tonight.
Is he...
Jiang Qingcheng wants to run away.
A Yan, I go with you.
Xiaomeng, you stay with mother.
It's easier to act alone.
A Yan, you've to be careful.
Don't worry.
Mother.
Don't worry, he'll be fine.
Let's eat.
Come on.
That way.
Okay, then you go the other way.
-We meet here.
-Okay.
A Ze.
-Found him?
-No.
The airport is too big.
I couldn't find him.
What do we do now?
Is that your father?
Yes, it's him.
Father.
Call him, quick.
Uncle Jiang
(Father)
Turn on speaker, quick.
Hello.
A Ze.
Father.
Great.
Son, I've been plotting all my life,
never thought I'd fall into
my son's hands.
Father, I never wanted this to happen.
This is not the outcome I want.
I've talked to you earlier.
If I let you go today,
that's not what I should do as a son.
You want me to bow before him?
No. Never
Uncle Jiang.
At this point,
it's not about something personal.
Both Jiang Ze and I don't wish
to see you stray further.
You've to take responsibility
for your own actions.
Please surrender.
Perhaps the offense might be mitigated.
Father.
You care only for your own interests.
But above all,
there're still right and wrong.
Listen to me.
Trust me this time.
I'm right.
Zhou Yanzhao,
you thought you'd win
with A Ze being on your side?
No, you'll never win!
Uncle Jiang, Jiang Ze was right.
Right or wrong is always
more important than interests.
What I'm doing now
is to protect you, father.
The earlier you quit,
the less consequence you've to bear.
I beg you.
Surrender to the police.
Okay, A Ze.
I'll listen to you this time.
I won't leave.
Get up.
I go get my father's luggage.
Jiang Ze.
Bring him to the police
as soon as possible.
In case he harms himself again.
Okay, got it.
When we were at the sports field,
we used to compete to win.
But now,
there aren't such standards.
I know how you feel.
We're the same.
There's no winning or losing.
How was it? Have you found him?
Jiang Ze was at the airport.
He managed to stop Uncle Jiang
and talked him into surrendering.
But will Uncle Jiang really
listen to Jiang Ze and surrender?
Maybe it was Jiang Ze's tears
that touched him.
I guess Jiang Ze did this mainly
for Uncle Jiang's own good.
What's wrong?
I don't know why
I somehow think that Uncle Jiang
won't give up so easily.
Will he really surrender?
I understand your concern.
But what we can do now
is to let Jiang Ze decide himself.
I believe he knows what to do.
But your concern is valid.
We have to be careful.
Will you let Jiang Ze stay at Shenghai?
Why not?
The construction of sports center
needs manpower.
We talked about this before.
He's always wanted to do
internet entrepreneurship.
I think the Guest House sector of
Yunnan resort
seems to have a prospect
towards online business.
You mean you incorporated Guest House
in Yunnan resort project?
Yes, I can even help you
develop your art space.
Being able to help my loved one
to realize her dream
worth more than anything else.
Xiaomeng.
Nothing can hold us back now.
Maybe not long after,
Shenghai can come back stronger.
A Yan, I believe you can do it.
Xiaomeng, it's all over now.
Everything will be fine.
Nobody will ever hurt you again.
I'll make it up to you
with all my love, okay?
By the way, I have something to tell you.
Yes?
I'm not sure...
if you like boy...
or girl?
This...
I only found out after using
a period tracker app.
(Period has been delayed for 45 days)
But it's only been 35 days.
Come, lean on it.
Whether it's a boy or a girl,
I'll be equally happy.
As long as both of you are safe.
We need to find time
to officially announce this news
to our friends and family.
You don't know this.
The elders say we can't spread the news
during early pregnancy.
It's ominous.
There's such a saying?
Sit down.
Hello, A Yan.
My father's gone.
Take it easy. What's wrong?
This morning,
I planned to take him
to the police station.
But he'd gone right after breakfast.
Are his luggage and passport still there?
All his belongings are still here.
It's like he went out for a walk.
I've searched everywhere
but didn't see him.
Call the police.
If you don't want to report
your father for murder,
report him as missing.
Jiang Ze.
We have to find your father
for his own good.
Okay.
A Yan, what's wrong?
Your concern is valid.
Uncle Jiang didn't surrender.
Now nobody knows where he is.
Then what should we do now?
I suppose Jiang Ze will report
to the police.
A Yan, how will things end up later?
Uncle Jiang refuses
to realize his mistakes.
I wonder how this will end up
in the future.
Leave all of this to me.
Your current main task
is to take care of yourself
and the baby.
Got it.
By the way, don't you need to work today?
How can I be at ease to go to work
with you like this?
I've decided to move my office
to the study room for the time being.
I'll work from home.
How can you do that?
You don't need to be so anxious.
Sister Hua.
The doctor said Xiaomeng lacks nutrition.
It's very risky.
From now on, our meals
should include ginseng, velvet antler
and bird nest.
Prepare tonic twice a day.
Sister Hua.
Your current main task is
to help Xiaomeng gain 10kg.
No. 15kg.
A Yan, since when did you learned
how to care for people?
Don't worry, I'm experienced.
I know how to take care of
pregnant ladies.
-Just wait and see.
-Xiaomeng.
-Don't worry.
-Okay.
-A Yan is back.
-Mother.
-How was the checkup?
Don't worry, mother. Everything is fine.
That's good.