You have to show them that
you can live all by yourself.
Don't forget that, Mookie.
You have to fight.
In all instances,
you have to fight.
Why did you do that, Mookie?
I thought you were different
from the rest.
That's enough, Mooks.
I wish I have the guts
to face my daughter.
I miss her so much, Logan.
DJ!
One more, please!
That's Mookie's voice!
- Let's go!
- What do you want?
You don't want me
to be your friend anymore?
Then don't!
Nobody's forcing you to do this!
Why are you still so affected
with Emma?
How can you forget about her
if you still keep those?
I am worried about Mookie.
I think she is carrying
a heavy load.
And I am not beside her
to make things a bit lighter.
Emma!
- What do you want?
- I'm so sorry.
I thought you were someone
I know.
Emma...
What's up?
How have you been?
I want to come near her.
I want to confront her.
I want to hurt her!
I want her to feel how much
she had hurt me!
But when I saw her...
Why did I back out?
I wasn't able to do anything,
Logan!
It must be your trauma
from that woman.
She did a handful on you.
But don't you worry.
The day will come when you will
be able to face your fears.
Time will come when you can face
her without fear.
I became even more worried
about Mookie when I saw Jade.
Maybe I can come near her
even just for a bit?
I just saw this photo earlier.
I don't know what's happening
to her in Jade'shouse.
Whether she's happy,
or is she sad?
Is she going through something?
Did that woman do something
to her?
We already have a venue
for Artemis's anniversary.
But we're just waiting
for confirmation.
Jade, if you need anything,
just let me know, okay?
Actually, there is.
But it's not about the company.
It's...
It's actually something
personal.
Okay. Maybe I can help.
What's that?
You know Emma Joseco, right?
Mookie's mom?
I need your help in finding her.
Why?
I saw Emma at the mall earlier.
And...
she seemed different.
Her attire.
Her stance.
Everything about her,
it's just different.
She's not the same Emma
that I knew.
What do you mean?
She's not like how she used to?
Yes! Exactly!
And I wonder
how did that happen?
How did she become
the way she is now?
I don't know.
But why would you want
to find her?
You're already a happy family,
right?
And you are already engaged
with Danilo.
Well, yeah, that's true.
But...
I am not like my sister, Ollive.
Of course, I still want Emma
to see her family.
Just for closure.
And one more thing...
I don't want Mookie
to have grudges with Emma.
Because no matter what we say,
Emma is still her mother.
Wow, Jade, you are so sweet
and thoughtful.
It's good to know
that you are that compassionate.
Unlike Olive.
She was so paranoid
and overdramatic.
So, are you going to help me?
Sure.
I will find Emma for you.
Thank you, Astrid.
But can you please keep this
between the two of us?
I want to surprise Danilo
and Mookie.
Of course, I still want Emma
to see her family.
For closure.
And...
I don't want Mookie to keep
grudges with her mother,
Emma, right?
You are so gullible, girl!
Of course not!
Why would I do that? Hello?
I thought you have become weak.
Well, that's just drama!
Bravo, Jade!
Bravo!
Of course!
More so now!
Now that Danilo and I
are engaged!
I will for sure not let Emma
ruin my family!
I know, right?
Mom Ligaya...
no matter how much tears
you shed,
you cannot do anything.
This is your fault!
If you did not give me
away before,
maybe I would have loved you
the way I love Danilo
and Mookie.
I will do everything...
if it means Danilo and Mookie
will stay with me forever.
And I will do everything...
to make sure Emma
will never ever meet
Danilo and Mookie ever again.
You will see.
No, you won't see.
Because you are trapped
inside here.
Don't worry.
I will keep you posted.
Goodbye!
Do you have what it takes
to be a cheer dancer?
If you really want to be
a cheer dancer,
prove it!
Prove it all!
We will do a one-on-one
cheer dance.
Wannabes versus the sqquad.
Who wants to go first?
Me.
All right, Mookie.
Since you are an attention
seeker, you go first.
You versus me,
the squad captain.
Deal!
Bring it on!
Places!
Music!
Let's go, Mookie!
You're out!
What do you mean I'm out?
You tripped me!
Oh, do you have proof?
Maybe you're just such
a weakling!
Maybe you're describing
yourself?
- Mookie! Stop that!
- Stop! Stacey!
Stop that!
- Stacey, let her go!
- Mookie!
Stop that!
- Now what?
- That's enough!
Calm down!
Can you please stop them?
- Mookie! Enough! No!
- That's enough! Now what?
Let her go.
- Approach them.
- Mookie!
- Mookie! That's enough
Stop that!
No!
What?
That's enough!
Come on!
Now what?
Enough!
You will never come near
my niece again!
I am not yet done with you!
You better watch out!
I will report you
to the principal,
and I will make sure
you will pay for this!
Go!
Let's go!
Are you ok?
If you did not stop me,
she would have been bald by now!
You did the right thing, Mookie.
It's just right
that you fought her.
She deserves it.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes.
Let's go.
My bag.
So annoying!
Mookie!
I hate you, Stacey!
- Mookie, dear.
- You are so annoying!
Baby girl!
I hate you so much!
Calm down.
It's okay.
That's enough.
She's so annoying!
I hate her so much!
Mookie!
Danilo...
I will just talk to Mookie.
Let's go.
Your principal just called me.
They said you got into a fight?
You physically hurt
your classmate.
She started it.
She tripped me.
It was her fault.
Maybe she thought I would just
let it slip.
Of course not!
That's enough, Danilo.
I saw how that lady undermined
Mookie.
Your daughter did
the right thing!
No.
That's not right!
Mookie, come here.
What is happening to you?
Your mom and I did not raise you
that way.
That's because I learned
how to fight, Dad!
Should I always be
the bigger person?
Mookie, you do not have
to get even at all times!
You don't have to fight all
the time!
And not at all times,
they can bully me, Dad!
Do not talk back to me
like that!
And do not raise your voice
at me.
Mookie, I am still you father.
Did you think I wouldn't notice
what you're doing?
You always go out,
and drink alcohol.
I just let you.
But that's going to stop.
Because as soon
as your classes ends,
I want you to go home straight.
You will not go out
with your friends!
Do you understand?
Am I grounded?
Yes! You are grounded!
So go to your room now!
Go inside!
Danilo, just relax...
I don't understand, Auntie!
Why do I always feel like dad
does not understand me anymore?
I feel like I have no one
on my side.
I think you are the only person
who understands me.
Of course, baby girl.
I am by your side forever
and ever.
I have an idea.
Let's just pretend
that you obeyed your father.
I got you.
You can still do whatever
you want to do.
And I'll be the one
to cover for you.
Is that okay?
Really, Auntie?
Yeah.
Just make sure you will
tell me everything you do
and the places you go to.
What?
So that I can tell you
what I told your dad.
We have to be in sync
with our alibis.
- Yehey, thank you!
- You're welcome!
This is not right, Logan.
Jade is already poisoning
my daughter's mind
and whole persona.
That woman is a pest.
She didn't change.
She chaged a lot.
I want to talk to my mom
about this.
But I cannot reach her.
I also want to call Wiro
and Kutsy to ask for updates.
What if I just ask mom
for a meet-up?
Don't.
Don't to that.
If Jade finds out,
you might be in danger.
Just don't.
Wait until you meet with Jade.
I think this is the right time
for me to confrotn Jade.
What's your plan?
Go to her house?
I received an inuiry
from Artemis.
That's Olive's company
and now Jade is running it.
They want to book
the bar for an event.
I want to accept the offer
because I think
this is the right time for me
and Jade to finally meet.
This is the right time
to get Mookie back.
You still haven't found Emma?
I'm sorry.
I still don't have any lead.
And I've been busy
with the event.
The bar has finally confirmed.
Now we're sure that we have
an event venue.
That's good to know.
I thought you would also fail
in that aspect.
Mookie, my child,
let's eat.
Your breakfast is ready.
Mookie...
Love...
- Jade...
- Just let her be.
I am just worried with Mookie.
I feel like it's my fault
why she is acting this way.
No. Don't think that way.
I feel like it's my fault.
I encouraged her to fight.
I didn't think she would
overdo it.
Maybe it's because of her
trauma with my sister.
Just let her be for now.
Don't worry too much.
Of course, I want the two of you
to get along.
And the time will come
that that will happen.
Let's have breakfast now.
I will not be easy on you, okay?
Logan...
Okay, okay, okay! It's fine.
Okay now.
I'm done in the gym.
I will go see Mookie now.
I just want to see her.
What if Jade is there?
You will get caught.
I will be careful!
Emma...
No matter how careful you are,
if you do not have anything
to protect yourself,
you are just like a beggar on
the streets who sells eggs.
If someone wanted to get you,
they will.
Put your bag down.
We will teach you basic
self defense.
No matter how angelic
your face is,
you have to know how to fight
back when they hurt you.
Marco, come here.
Real danger is not always
visible.
Sometimes, it's just right
behind you.
You have to be alert
all the time.
So you can fight the enemy...
And control him, so you can find
their weakness.
That's where you will strike.
Let's try it?
Thank you, Marco.
Ready?
Sorry!
Hello, Astrid?
Why are you not yet
in the office?
Where are you?
What hospital?
You fell?
Wow, Astrid!
Right in the middle
of our workload?
Fine! Update me!
Ma'am Jade, you have a visitor.
She wanted to get inside.
- Who? Let her in.
- She's there.
Leticia?
What are you doing here?
Jade?
I'm guilty.
I was a bad best friend
to your sister.
She's now gone,
and I did not visit her.
That's fine.
I'm sure Olive has already
forgiven you.
No.
I know your sister so well.
She does not know
how to forgive.
Of course not.
Olive is such a good person.
No. We both have mental issues.
That's why we're close!
We have the same personality!
You are the only
bad person here, Leticia!
Olive trusted you!
You were the only one she ever
had when everybody left her.
But what did you do?
You turned your back away
from her.
I am guilty of that, Jade.
That's why I'm here.
I want to ask for forgiveness.
You don't deserve
to be forgiven!
You left me!
Just when I needed a friend,
you betrayed me!
Left you?
What are you talking about,
Jade?
You even made a promise!
Best friends for all eternity!
But you cannot fulfill
that promise!
Back to back, soul to soul.
Never apart.
Always whole.
Wait a minute...
Do you still remember that?
Wait...
How did you know that?
That's our secret code.
My god, you're not Jade!
Olive?
Please. You have to help me
look after Mookie.
I heard Stacey and her squad.
They are planning something
against her.
What?
We have to learn every step
Jade takes.
So we can strategize how
I can fight against her.
Just observe her.
You have to know her every move.
Her name is Emma Joseco.
If I find her, what shall I do?
I want you to get rid of her.
I feel bad for Mookie.
She doesn't have Emma.
Her grandmother is missing
in action.
Don't you have any news
about Mom Ligaya?
What's that?