Please tell me what to do
so you can forgive me, Olive.
I'll take your offer on that.
Find Emma.
Poor Mookie.
She has no mother.
And even her grandmother
is missing in action.
I want to check
what that noise is.
Then let's check it.
We have lots of rats
in our basement.
Did you check if the people
who adopted us were good?
Dear, I'm begging you.
Shut up!
Every punch you throw,
be it a jab or a kick,
must come from within.
So you can show
what you're fighting for.
Give me five days to find her.
Why did you hire someone
to look for Emma?
I just want closure.
That's all I want.
What the hell!
Let go of me!
Help!
Let go of me! Help!
Mom!
- That's Mookie!
Come on!
- Dear?
- Mookie?
Mookie!
What happened to you?
Dad! Something bad happened
to Mom.
Relax, baby girl.
It's just a bad dream.
- Yes.
- I know, Auntie Jade.
But I can't help
but worry for Mom.
My heart felt so tight
while seeing her getting hurt.
And I hate myself for feeling
this way.
But it pains me.
Don't worry, baby girl.
I'm sure your mom is happy
wherever she is.
She never came back for you,
remember?
But, Auntie Jade,
what if my dream is real?
What if she really needs help?
What if something bad
happened to her?
That's enough.
Stop overthinking.
I'm sure she's fine.
Damn you, Emma!
Why don't you leave
my family alone?
Show up to Altair!
So he can remove you
from our lives.
I talked to Mrs. Ramirez
of Ramirez Lab.
And she told me there was
an agreement last year
that Artemis Pharmacy would
spearhead the product launch
of their multivitamin brand,
Activora.
She doesn't know I'm Olive.
I invested in the research
development of that product.
Because I want to be part
of a phenomenal product
that will change people's
lifestyles and improve
their quality of life.
People will have time for their
family despite being so busy.
Is it because your parents
had no time for you?
Because that's how
I am with Mookie.
I spent all my life on her.
But someone suddenly
took her away from me.
Good thing she's with me again.
That's why I still want
to handle that launch myself.
And I appreciate that
you're helping me run
Artemis Pharmacy
and other things.
Of course.
Ma'am, excuse me.
You have a visitor.
Altair, any update?
Emma's dead.
She's not coming back anymore.
What?
Emma's dead?
This is where I buried her.
Tell me, Altair.
How did you kill Emma?
I covered her head with plastic
until she ran out of breath.
Here's her picture
before I buried her.
That's enough, Altair.
Good job.
Congratulations, Olive.
No one's getting
in your way now.
Thank you.
Leave me and my sister for now.
Let's go.
Hello, my dear sister, Emma.
I hope that you rest...
No, no, no.
I don't want you
to rest in peace.
Because you don't deserve that.
I hope...
that you rot in hell.
Dear.
I can go home by myself.
Dear, I don't like this.
I don't like it when we fight.
Your Aunt Jade called.
She's on her way here.
She said she had something
important to tell us.
Mookie, don't get mad at me,
please.
Let's stop fighting.
Love!
I'm so sorry.
Hi, baby girl.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I met with the private
investigator.
He has news about Emma.
So you still hire him
to find Emma?
I'm so sorry, love.
I feel restless that I know
nothing about my sister.
And here's the thing.
Unfortunately...
Emma's not coming back.
She went with another man.
- What?
I know.
I'm so sorry.
But that's what the private
investigator found out.
And you know what?
It makes a lot of sense.
She left because she went
with another man.
She would've come back to us
if she hadn't done that.
She would've shown up to us
a long time ago, right?
But no.
Maybe it's about time
we should accept
that Emma's no longer
coming back.
She's never coming back...
ever.
I told you, Emma.
I told you to stick with me.
But son of a gun.
You still left without me.
Look what happened to you.
So, Mom really has abandoned us.
Let's stop hoping
she'll come back.
- I'm sorry, dear. Mookie!
- Love, love.
Let Mookie be for now.
Let her process.
Let her grieve.
It won't help if we keep
following her.
I'm sure she's going to be fine.
That's enough, Boss.
Don't you feel chills?
I can't believe it.
Don't I look dead
in that picture?
So, please don't get mad
that I left without you.
Nothing bad happened to me.
Good thing Marco and I
sensed it.
But wow.
This picture is impressive.
I can't believe
we pulled this off.
- It looks so real.
- Right?
I actually felt chills
when I saw that picture.
Our plan was successful.
This wouldn't happen
without your support.
So, thank you.
You're very much welcome.
But remember, this is all you.
We only support you.
We must know Jade's every move.
So we can strategize
how I can haunt her.
I thought of suggesting it,
too, Boss.
Oh, really?
Keep an eye on Jade.
Know her every schedule.
Yes, Boss.
Emma.
The people Jade is talking
to look suspicious.
They seem like high-class goons.
She even handed him
a picture of you.
Are you just a private
investigator?
Actually, he's not just
a good investigator.
He's also a good...
hitman.
Good.
Once you find Emma,
I want you to get rid of her.
She's getting in the way
of my plans.
Besides...
Mookie has only one mother.
And that's me.
I'm sure she's planning
something bad against me.
The man Jade hired is leaving.
I'll call you again.
You know what to do.
Be safe.
What will you do
if Jade does that to you?
Presence of mind.
Your first reaction is to panic.
The first thing you should do
is to step on her foot.
Let go of me!
You'll give it all
your strength.
You will use the anger you feel
towards Jade.
Help!
You will elbow my side.
A strong one.
What if she doesn't let go?
You will introduce your elbow
to her jaw or nose
to expose her weakness.
Help!
Remember, a waris a mind game.
You must strike first.
How are you?
I remember what happened.
What if I got killed?
What if the man Jade hired
killed me?
What would happen to Mookie
if I died?
Marco, water.
Listen to me.
I'm with you now.
You're safe.
Jade failed.
So take a deep breath.
Okay?
Breathe in, breathe out.
Now, go back to your plan.
Your plan to haunt Jade.
We'll ruin her plan.
All of her plans!
We'll drive her crazy!
So that no one will believe her
once you expose the truth
about what she did to you.
Now, think about it.
Who are you doing this for?
Tell me.
- I'm doing this for Mookie.
- For Mookie.
So you can take Mookie back.
Gather all your anger
towards Jade.
Consider yourself the winner.
Darn you, Jade.
If you think you've won,
you're mistaken.
Logan,
I'm sorry that you're getting
dragged into my mess.
I wanted to get dragged
into this.
Because I want to help
you get even with Jade
and take Mookie back.
Are you ready to face him again?
Logan!
He's here.
Let him in.
Wake up.
Don't!
I said wake up!
Why do you want to abduct me?
What did Jade tell you to do?
Answer her.
Plan B.
Sorry, I have to do this.
What did you do to my family?
So you've finally spoken,
you bastard.
We didn't do anything to them.
Well, we haven't done
anything yet.
But we've done something
to you already.
So you're a model husband
and father to your family.
Your kids look up to you.
But poor children.
Looks like they're going
to lose their idol.
Jade wants Emma dead.
Jade's crazy.
She's a demon.
Please, don't kill me.
My kids are still young.
I can kill Jade if you like.
It's so easy for you
to kill someone.
But you're afraid to die.
You're a bastard.
What do you want me to do?
Just tell me.
What do I do?
Convince Jade
that you killed me.
Keep the end of your bargain.
Make sure my family's safe.
Don't worry.
We didn't hurt them.
We don't do that.
They're staying in Hem Till
Resort in Laguna.
We made it appear
that you surprised them.
And that you'll follow
them there.
Did you think we brought them
in a stockroom?
Tied and tortured?
We don't hurt children.
I also have a kid.
And she's with the monster
who told you to kill me.
Love.
Don't worry too much
about Mookie.
She's fine.
I've talked to her,
and she just wants some space.
Does your private investigator
know the man Emma went with?
Does he know where they went?
Why do you ask?
Why do you want to know
if the private investigator
knows where Emma is?
Is it because you want
to see her?
Jade, I won't lie to you.
I really want to see Emma.
I want to clarify
so many things with her.
What?
Hold her.
Hey! What are you doing?
Stop!
Leave me alone!
Say hi! We're live!
What the heck!
Imagine it as your enemy.
And you need to protect
yourself.
Emma's not coming back anymore.
So if I were you,
I wouldn't waste my time on her.
What's that?