Don't go near me!
I might accidentally stab
Mookie!
Please stop!
You have a twin!
What a shame!
There's two of you
in this world?
Go ahead!
- Sis!
- Mookie!
Mookie!
I'm coming with you.
You might be your crazy sister's
accomplice.
Then you might end up
killing us, too!
Someone's following us.
What?
Drive faster!
Hurry up!
They're coming after us!
You have nowhere to go, Mookie!
So you might as well accept
that we'll be together forever!
No!
You want to be difficult,
don't you!
What else do you want?
My Mommy Emma!
No!
You won't be seeing her ever
again!
Don't you realize
what's going on, Mookie?
She caused all this mess.
No!
We're in this mess
because of her!
Because she brainwashed you!
You're the reason why I'm always
weak!
The reason why I'm always sick!
The reason why I didn't get
to enjoy my life!
For seventeen years, Mom!
I thought I'd be miserable
all my life.
Imprisoned in our own house!
I thought I would die
if I didn't take the medicine
you'd been giving me.
Stop.
But when I met Mommy Emma,
she gave me hope!
I finally had someone
on my side!
No!
She's the one who comforted me.
Stop it!
She treats me like her own
child!
Stop it!
She loves me, and she will never
hurt me!
Stop it!
I said stop it!
Look, Mom!
Is that how a mother should
treat her child?
Because a real mother could
never hurt her child.
So go ahead, hit me!
Hurt me, Mom!
Mommy Emma's coming here
to save me anyway!
Olive?
Olive!
Mookie!
Olive, get out here now!
Mookie?
They're not here!
I knew that they were not here.
There's no car outside.
This is insane!
She fooled us again.
Or is it you who fooled us?
You brought us here.
Excuse me, can you stop being
pessimistic?
Like you, I'm just trying
to find them here.
Can you stop accusing me?
What if I'm out of time?
I might not find my daughter.
Emma, don't lose hope.
We will find her.
Don't worry.
How about this.
I'll look around to see if she
left a clue.
I'm gonna go through her papers.
That's right!
Hey, wait.
You might try to fool us.
Your family has some trust
issues.
Because you are Olive's sister.
Let's look outside. Let's go.
- Go, look around.
- Okay, let's go.
No!
No.
Hello Astrid, send people
to the ancestral house.
I have a good feeling that Emma
and Jade will be there.
Okay.
But what makes you so sure
that they're together?
They don't know each other.
But they have one common
enemy...
And that's me.
Knowing Jade, she always gets
involved.
So she will be helping Emma.
Make sure to do everything
to stop them.
I'll call you when I need you.
What are you planning to do?
Mommy, no!
I believe that's none of your
business.
No! No!
What the heck!
You almost hit me!
I'm sorry.
You leave me with no choice,
Mookie.
- Sorry, Sorry, Mommy!
- Hold her tight!
- Sorry, Mommy!
- You, too!
Lock her up in her room!
No!
No! Mommy, please! No!
I'm sorry,
but I know nothing about
the Caparas family's property.
Olive hasn't told you anything
since she was a child.
No, we're not close like that.
Especially those twins.
Olive is such a brat.
I hope you find your daughter.
I hope we'll find her, too.
I will never forgive myself
if we don't find her.
We've lost her once.
I grieved for her for years.
I can't lose her again.
Make sure that she can't escape.
There you go.
She can't escape for sure.
She better not.
You can leave now.
I'm sorry if I almost hit you.
But it's nothing compared
to what you did to me.
After all you've done,
do you still wonder why
I don't like you?
You're getting on my nerves,
Mookie.
I tried to be nice.
But unfortunately,
you did not like that.
So now, we're back
to our normal life.
You are my patient,
and I'm your doctor.
And I will make sure that we'll
be together forever this time.
Oh, my!
Why don't people send a message
first before calling?
Why don't you take the call?
It could be important.
Probably not.
It could just be Manny.
Manny?
Manny...
as in "Manny-ningil".
But I don't have "that's
entertainment" to give them.
So, I'll just ignore
the "Judith"
Manny?
That's entertainment?
Judith?
Oh, poor you, you don't know
anything.
Manny... "Manny-ngingil"
meaning debt collector.
"That's entertainment" meaning
money I didn't have.
So I'll just ignore Judith,
meaning due date.
I can't pay them,
so I'll have to ignore
the due date of my bill.
So, I'm ignoring the call.
I get it now.
Your name is Ligaya, right?
Call me Joy.
But we're in the Philippines,
so you can call me Ligaya.
Mommy, I'll get out
of this place.
Just wait and see.
When I was young,
I pretended to be brave.
Why?
Because no one else would
help me but myself.
I want you to be brave, too.
Because I won't always be there
to help you.
I know it's not easy,
but you have to be brave.
You're my stronghold,
Mommy Emma.
You're the reason why
I learned to fight.
I must stay strong.
I need to get out of this place.
We were so cute in this picture.
So cute!
You're right.
You both look cute.
It reminds me of my twins.
Twins?
Emma has a twin?
Oh, no.
But my firstborns are twins.
They're a year older than Emma.
Where are they now?
They've been gone
for a long time.
My condolences, Ligaya.
Thank you, but I hope
they're not dead.
I mean, I don't know
if they're dead or alive.
Okay, hear me out.
I was a negligent mother.
I'm useless.
I can't take care of them,
so I gave them up for adoption.
But you know what,
I think you're the same age.
When I saw you with Olive,
I thought...
What is it?
When I saw you with Olive,
I thought...
What is it?
I'm such a fool.
I'm so stupid. Get a hold
of yourself, Ligaya.
I'm sorry,
I was reminded of my twins
when I saw you with Olive.
I'm sorry about that.
What now?
Are you going to let them
take Mookie away from you?
No!
I won't let them!
They can't take Mookie
away from me.
I am her mother!
Good!
Now, you have to tighten
the reins and control her!
Do whatever it takes
to keep her with you.
Yes.
Good.
Are you okay, Jade?
I'm fine.
It's a bit dusty.
Excuse me!
Bless you.
My babies, I'm sorry this
is all I can give you.
I'm sorry, my babies.
Reggie, please give this
to their adoptive parents.
What's this?
It's a letter.
I hope my babies will read
them someday.
Where are you, my children?
If you are still alive...
I hope you can forgive me.
Mookie, time to eat.
Here.
What?
You don't want to eat?
Fine, it's up to you.
You'll get sick.
Come on,
just one spoonful,
say ahh.
Mommy, I cooked this for you.
Try it.
What do you think? Is it good?
You didn't like what I made
for you.
You just pretended that you did.
If my mom can make me believe
that she ate what I cooked.
I can pretend, too.
Good girl.
Here, I brought you milk.
Cause I know that this is good
for you.
Very good, Mookie.
Do you want some more?
Hey,
what is this?
Doctor of Medicine?
Oh wow!
Your parents are doctors?
What kind of doctor?
Are they pediatricians
or surgeons?
They were heart specialists.
Heart specialist?
The best in town.
So that's why Olive wants
to be a doctor, too.
Oh yes...
Wait, how did you know that?
Of course, we know everything
that's going on with her.
We know that she's not
a real doctor.
We also know that she's
experimenting on Mookie.
My granddaughter.
She did the same thing with me
to make me dependent on her.
Doesn't she realize that
what she's doing is wrong?
Why is she doing that?
I have no idea.
She told me that I'm indebted
to her.
Because she got my life together
after she ruined it.
I feel bad for Mookie.
I hope she'll stop hurting
Mookie.
This is your favorite.
Cream of mushroom soup. Right?
Yes, Mommy.
I missed it.
Do you remember making
this whenever I'm sick?
You're always there for me.
You just don't appreciate
what I do for you.
Because you love someone else.
You have your Mommy Emma now.
That's not true.
I felt guilty when
I tasted the soup.
It reminded me of our
happy memories together.
I miss you so much, Mommy.
Really, Mookie?
And you expect me
to believe that?
Not too long ago, all you talked
about was Emma.
You kept telling me
how happy you were with her.
That I'm the reason
why you're miserable.
Mommy.
I just said that to make you
jealous.
Because I feel like you don't
love me anymore.
What?
What makes you think
that I don't love you?
Because you were hurting me.
But, Mommy.
Believe me, I love you.
I want things back to how they
were before.
Just the two of us?
Without Emma around?
Yes.
You know what, Mommy?
When I was at Emma's house,
I realized that I didn't want
to stay there.
It's dirty and crowded.
The bed was stiff,
and they didn't have air
conditioning.
I miss my comfortable life.
I miss my room.
And I miss you so much, Mommy.
Mookie.
Did you think you could fool me?
It was very clear to me that you
choose Emma instead of me.
No, Mommy.
I'm telling the truth.
I was lying about what I said
with Mommy Emma.
I will prove to you that I'm
only telling the truth.
That I am loyal only to you.
That I love no one else but you.
Really?
Right on time.
Astrid just sent me a message.
The bodyguards who will
take care of Emma and Jade
are there already.
What?
Manny won't really leave me
alone! What the heck!
Just answer it.
I will or else he won't stop
calling.
Ma'am Alice?
Why did you call me?
Ligaya, I have gathered
new information.
What is it?
The couple who adopted
your twins are doctors.
What?
But there are a lot of doctors
here in the Philippines.
What kind of doctors?
I know.
They said they were cardio...
Cardio...
they specialize in heart
disease.
Hey! Who are you?
Let me go!
Let go of me!
Ligaya, help me!
Ligaya! Help me!
Let her go!
Jade!
That's a shocking revelation!
Are you trying to say that Olive
is your daughter?
I have a strong feeling!
I just left for a second,
and you're sending Emma
a message!
Why?
Are you asking her to save you?
Look at this.
This is one of the two necklaces
I gave the twins
before I gave them up
for adoption.
We're here to find Mookie
because her life is in danger.
Can we focus on helping her
for now?
Jade may be your sister.