I know Olive very well,
she will shoot me!
Mom! Mom! Mom!
I'll take care of her!
What the heck!
Why is the car stopping?
No!
What am I going to do?
Olive, please stop this!
No matter where you hide,
the law will find you!
They will never stop until they
put you back
- in jail!
- Let me go!
Olive!
Come on, hold on tight!
Help me, Olive.
You must die.
Hurry up! Let's go!
Mookie.
Mom!
Mom! Dad!
What happened? Why...
We got in an accident.
But we're fine, Dear.
Don't worry.
Ma'am, how are my twins?
Have you seen Jade and Olive?
We haven't found them yet.
But we're gonna look for them
inside.
Let's go, we'll help you look
for them.
- This way.
- This way, let's go.
Emma, Danilo, are you guys okay?
We're okay.
I feel a bit dizzy,
but we have to go, come on.
- Let's go.
- Let's go, Kutsy.
Come on.
Thank you very much.
Rest in peace, Jade.
I mean...
Olive.
Officers.
We've been searching all day.
Perhaps we can find them faster
if we spread out?
Okay.
Where should we start?
Let's look over there.
Yes.
Wait a minute. Let's think first
where we're going.
God, please help us.
Where should we go?
Please show us the way...
What is it, Emma?
Look at my mom.
She's so concerned
about the twins.
She didn't even ask me
if I'm okay.
Emma, try to understand her.
You're fine anyway.
You have to understand your
mom's situation.
God, please help me.
Over here!
There's someone here!
Where?
Where are they?
They could be my children!
Stand still, it's dangerous.
It's quite deep.
I need to see them!
It could be them!
- Let me see.
- Wait, Ma'am.
It's not safe, Ma'am.
- Let me see!
- Is that them, Ma'am?
Olive!
Jade!
Let's go to them!
We have to go down there.
Let's go! I want to go to them!
Come on!
What are we going to do?
They're down there...
Jade! Olive!
Ligaya!
Olive!
Jade!
Olive?
- My child!
- Ma'am, don't touch them yet.
-Let me go!
-We have to wait for the medics.
Jade! Olive!
Why? Wake up!
Let me go!
Don't try to stop me!
My child, wake up.
Wake up, Olive.
Olive.
Jade.
Jade? My child?
She's alive!
She's still alive!
She's still breathing!
Hey! Help us!
Help my daughter!
Call for help, hurry!
Jade...
Olive, Jade...
My child...
Mom?
Jade, dear?
How are you feeling?
Olive?
Your sister?
Where is she?
Don't be shocked, Jade.
What?
Olive is gone.
Olive is dead.
No!
Jade.
Olive can't die!
Mom!
Mom, my sister!
It might be harmful to your
condition, Jade.
It might be harmful to you.
That's enough, Jade.
Excuse me, Ma'am.
- Hello.
- Miss Jade Caparas,
can we talk to you?
We just need to hear
your statement.
I'm sorry,
but can you talk to her later?
She needs to rest.
Mom.
It's okay.
Are you sure, Jade?
I don't remember...
what happened exactly.
I just remember talking
to my sister
and asking her to surrender.
But she doesn't want to do that.
And then...
she got mad at me.
And when we were at the cliff...
She pushed me off.
I got hold of her hand.
And then...
we both fell off.
Olive!
Mom, my sister!
My sister is gone!
Mom!
Ma'am, here are your belongings.
Excuse me.
you can now look at the remains.
Thank you.
Mookie!
Dear, stay here.
Why, Mom?
I'm just trying to protect you.
I don't want this to add to your
trauma.
Emma.
Olive is dead.
She can't harm anyone anymore.
Mom, that won't erase the fact
that she hurt my daughter.
Why do you want her
to see her remains?
To remind her of all the trauma
that woman caused her?
Emma, I understand what you're
coming from.
I know that Olive did you wrong,
especially to Mookie.
I'll understand if you don't
want Mookie
to be around on her wake.
We're not gonna be there either.
What?
Come on, Emma.
Olive is my daughter.
She's your sister.
If you can't accept her
as your sister,
please respect her
as a human being.
She's gone now!
No, Mom.
She never accepted you.
And she stole our daughter.
Mookie almost died because of
the experiments
Olive did on her.
And you want me to forget what
happened now that she's dead?
I'm sorry, Jade, but my
daughter's connection
with your twin ends here.
And her connection with you too.
Let's go.
- Emma.
- Let's go home.
Emma, wait.
Emma, it's Olive's burial.
Let our daughter see her
for the last time.
Since you didn't let
her go to Olive's wake.
You know the reason why.
Emma, you're not protecting
Mookie,
you're depriving her of her
right to see...
To see the woman
who tortured her?
Dan, she did Mookie wrong.
How are you?
Oh wow.
That looks good!
Sweetie....
I'm sorry...
if we didn't go
to Olive's wake.
Your mom doesn't want us to go.
But...
do you want to go
to her burial?
I want to see her.
I understand why Mom
doesn't want me to go.
And I respect her decision.
But you know, Grandmother...
I just feel guilty.
Emma, Mookie has been with
Olive for seventeen years.
You must respect the dead.
Why? When Olive was alive
did she respect our daughter,
did she respect us?
No!
I don't think it's disrespectful
to keep my daughter
from the person who took
my right to be a mother
for seventeen years.
Despite everything she did
to me,
to us,
she's still my mom.
And I can't change that.
We've been together for so long.
And even though
there were times that she hurt
me over and over,
she's still a big part of me,
Grandmother.
And I will never stop
loving her.
That's why...
I want to go to her wake.
To see her one last time.
Hello?
Auntie, customer!
- I have to go somewhere.
- Hello!
- Wait a minute.
- I want to buy something.
Auntie, customer!
- Hello?
- Let me do it. Wait a minute.
I want to buy something.
- What is it?
- How much for that color green?
The color blue? Ten pesos.
Because it's two pieces,
that would be 10 pesos.
Emma, I understand
why you're mad.
But did you ask Mookie
what she wants?
Did you ask how she feels?
Did she not want
to see Olive?
Emma.
Mookie?
Dan!
- What?
- Mookie's gone.
Look, why is her stuff her?
Dan!
- What?
- Mookie's gone!
Look, this is her stuff.
Wait, she probably
just went somewhere.
Someone could have
kidnapped Mookie!
Emma, who would kidnap her?
Olive's people!
Olive is gone.
How is that possible?
What if she told her people to
take Mookie
no matter what happens?
- Wiro, have you seen Mookie? -
Here's Wiro.
She was just here earlier.
She's with Ligaya.
I saw them get
in a car earlier.
They get in a car?
Here we are.
Zayn, thank you for helping us.
You're welcome.
Grandmother, my mom
might get mad.
Don't worry,
she won't get mad.
As long as she won't find out.
Good morning, my dear family!
How are you?
I can't wait to show you
what I have in store
for all of you!
Are you all ready?
Cause I am so ready!
Hi, Jade.
I have been practicing
to be like you.
And look, I've mastered it.
They got in a car?
Who kidnapped them?
Calm down...
okay? Just calm down.
You're a bit too exaggerated.
It was Zayn.
Ligaya asked him to bring
them to Olive's burial.
What?
Emma, sweetie?
What's going on? Why?
Hello, Mom.
I know that you took
Mookie to Olive's burial.
Wiro told me.
Can you go home now?
Grandmother, I think we
should head home.
My mom might get mad.
I don't care.
She can be mad at me.
She can fight me.
This is my last chance
to see my oldest daughter.
I will never see her again.
You're so stupid, Jade.
If you sided with me,
you wouldn't be
where you are now.
Too bad.
But don't worry.
Now I have more reason
to take revenge on Emma...
because you got caught
in our feud.
I will make sure...
that I slowly send Emma
to her grave.
So...
thank you...
for my new identity, Jade.
Don't worry.
I will make sure...
your sacrifice
won't be in vain.
No one else will know.
It's between you and me.
Olive?
You have to find
a new apartment.
My new tenant has already paid
six months in advance.
And she paid double for it.
No matter where you go.
I will make sure
that you'll end up with me,
Emma.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Danilo!
This is for you!
Welcome to your new house, Emma.
This time, I wouldn't
just take Mookie from you.
I will take everyone
that you love.
You're extraordinary, Jade!
Miss Generosity of the year!
I want to thank you
for letting us live here.
I've been dreaming of this.
To be with you,
all my children.
Just enjoy your happy moments
while you still can, Emma.
This won't last long.