What did you do?
Why did your employer get mad?
I just went
to her daughter's room.
She's grumpy
because her child is sickly.
It's tough for a mother
to take care of her sick child.
I hope that one day,
I'll meet you in person.
And I hope I'll also get
the chance to comfort you.
The person I saw in the park?
Wait, I think that's her!
You're probably Madam Olive.
I hope you forgive whatever
my daughter has done.
Go.
You never learn!
You deserve to be punished!
Come here!
That's what you deserve
for being stubborn!
You always disobey me!
- So this is what you deserve!
- Ouch! Mommy!
Mommy!
Mommy, please!
I'm begging you, Mommy!
No!
- Mommy!
- You never learn!
You will never change,
no matter what I do to you.
So your horn should be cut off.
Please! Please!
Let's see if you still
don't learn your lesson.
Emma.
You're thinking
about Baby Kayla again.
Mookie reminds me of her.
Mookie, the kid
you told me about?
Your employer's daughter?
Dan.
I think her mom's abusing her.
I want to help her.
Let's report it to the police.
Wait, wait. We're not sure
if your employer is hurting her.
Let's not be impulsive.
Why does she seem
to be suffering?
Maybe it's how
her mother disciplines her.
Don't worry about it.
And you were not
in the actual scene.
You'll be in hot water
if you don't stay out of it.
That's enough.
Don't think about it anymore.
Dan, you know what,
Mookie seems
to be a good person.
Look.
Look at her letter for me.
She's a very sweet kid.
It seems easy to love her.
But why does it seem like
she's longing for love?
Emma, that's enough.
Please stop.
I can't explain.
I don't understand.
Mookie isn't in any way
related to me.
I also want to stay out of it.
But why do I seem to get hurt
whenever I hear Mookie crying?
I can't explain it, Danilo. Why?
Why do I seem to get hurt?
I don't want to feel this.
Emma, please stop.
That's enough.
You're making me cry, too.
Please, stop.
It hurts.
Good morning, Mookie.
Mommy?
Mommy, what's happening?
Mommy, why is my leg like this?
Looks like it's edema caused
by the build-up of fluids
in your body that could lead
to infection and wounds.
Edema?
Mommy, how did that happen?
I don't understand.
I'm taking all the medicines
you give me.
That's one of the complications
of someone who
has a spinal injury.
In your case, you're paralyzed,
and your mobility is limited.
And yet...
you insisted
on moving yesterday.
That's why it resulted to that.
It's swollen and sore.
You see, sweetie?
You're making
your illness worse.
If you only obeyed me,
that probably wouldn't happen.
Mommy, please tell me,
how can I get better?
Don't worry, Mookie.
Mommy will find a way.
Just like I always do.
Do you know what can happen
if it gets worse?
What?
It's your fault.
This wouldn't happen if you only
did everything I told you.
If it gets worse...
your foot will get amputated.
Mommy. Mommy, please, no.
Mommy, please!
Please tell me you won't do it.
Mommy, please.
I don't want it!
Mommy, please. I don't want to!
Mommy.
- Mommy, please.
- It's okay.
Mommy, I don't want to!
It's okay, Mommy's here.
We'll find a way, okay?
Promise, Mommy?
I promise.
- But you must always obey me.
- I will.
Emma?
Ma'am Olive has already left.
I'll just clean her room.
Will you be okay here?
- Of course.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- I'll leave you for now.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Mookie?
Mookie.
Emma, is that you?
Yes, Mookie. It's me.
How are you?
Hold on, Emma.
How are you feeling?
Emma?
Mookie...
I will listen to you.
You can treat me as your mom.
And I'm willing to carry
all your burdens.
I'm right here.
I also went through a lot
like you.
Why, Emma?
What happened?
I lost my child.
She's now in heaven.
Sorry, Emma.
I shouldn't have asked.
Sorry, too.
I shouldn't be telling you this.
No, it's okay.
I thought I wouldn't recover
from that.
But I'm here now...
with you.
Talking to you.
I'm also happy...
that I get to talk to you.
I know that...
someone is watching over you,
and that is your baby.
I hope, Emma...
I dream of her.
So I can tell her
how good of a mother you are.
And...
I also hope...
I can talk to her.
And ask her...
if I can treat you as my mother.
Will you let me?
I'd love that, Mookie.
But...
What?
We're not living
in the same world.
I'm just your laundress.
You're my employer's daughter.
We're not supposed
to be talking like this.
Your mom will get mad
if she finds out about this.
But, Emma,
I feel happy talking to you.
You know what...
you're the only person
who makes me feel better.
I feel glad
when I'm talking to you.
So, please, Emma.
Emma, please.
Don't get tired
of talking to me.
Please, Emma.
A mother and daughter are living
in the middle of the forest.
Lily, and the kid, Rosie.
Rosie is a scaredy-cat.
One day, Rosie got attracted
to a firefly.
She followed it
until she realized
that she was already in the
middle of a dense forest.
Mom?
Lily got worried
- when Rosie wasn't home yet.
- Mom?
So even though it was dangerous,
she went to the forest,
carrying a lamp, to find Rosie.
Meanwhile,
Rosie was very scared.
She thought she would never be
able to go home to her mother.
- But she became hopeful
- Mom!
when she saw
the light from the lamp.
Mom?
- Mom!
- Rosie!
Mom, I thought
you would never come.
I thought I would never
see you again.
There's nothing a mother
won't do for her child.
I don't want to lose you.
So I'll never leave you.
From then on,
Rosie's fearfulness disappeared
because she knew that
her mother was there
to take care of and protect her.
Because you disobeyed me,
you'll stay in the dark room.
Mookie, are you okay?
Didn't you like the story
I told you?
I liked it, Emma.
Why do you seem so quiet?
I just remembered something.
And...
I just can't believe
that someone's reading me
a storybook.
We have the same book.
Amazing!
I bought this for my daughter.
Too bad she isn't here anymore.
But you know what, Emma?
It's only now that
I appreciate this book.
You read it for me.
I always got scared whenever
I read this book back then.
I imagine myself as Rosie.
I wonder what will happen
if I get lost in a forest.
Just like now, I can't walk.
I don't want to be alone, Emma.
You're not alone, Mookie.
Rosie's mom came
and saved her, remember?
That will happen to you, too.
There are people around you
who care for you
and will never leave you.
I'm afraid of the dark.
I don't like that.
When you feel
that everything is dark,
just look at the sky.
You'll find at least
one star shining.
And you'll realize
there's light.
Thank you, Emma.
I will keep this.
I will always look at this.
It feels good.
It's like having a mom
hugging me.
Remember...
don't lose hope.
Hang in there.
Who knows?
One day, you'll be able
to walk again.
What if I can't walk anymore?
Don't think like that.
That won't happen.
Mookie, I have to go.
I still need
to finish something.
Bye, Emma.
Mommy!
I'm glad you're awake now.
Mommy,
is my leg getting better?
Unfortunately,
your infection is getting worse.
Maybe we need to go
and see another doctor.
What for?
I'm a doctor.
I don't seem to get better.
Flor, leave us for now.
I can handle this.
- I'll call you when I need you.
- Okay. Okay, Ma'am.
We have to clean it.
It hurts!
Mommy!
Mommy, please!
This wouldn't have happened
if you had followed what I said.
Mommy, please!
Mommy!
Ma'am, please sit down first.
Do you want water?
- No, it's okay.
- Juice?
- Thank you, thank you.
- Okay.
Mommy!
Mookie?
Ma'am Olive said
you wait for her here.
I think I heard
Mookie screaming.
She only had an injection,
Ma'am.
- Mookie!
- Ma'am! Ma'am!
- Ma'am.
I'll be the one to get scolded.
You can't go there.
Astrid!
Where's Mookie? Is she okay?
She's fine.
She's already asleep.
I heard her screaming.
Did something happen?
Oh, no.
As usual, she's still
not used to injections.
I gave her a flu shot.
May I see her?
We'll be late for our meeting
with the supplier.
I still need to get my car
at the repair shop, remember?
Let's go.
It hurts.
Emma. Here's more.
Wash this, too.
- Flor.
- I'll help you. Yes?
Why does Mookie's clothes
have blood?
Yeah. The wound
on her leg got worse.
I feel bad for her.
Has she been checked
by a doctor?
She may need to be taken
to the hospital.
No need.
Oh, yeah.
You don't know about it.
Ma'am Olive is a doctor.
Doctor of what?
I wonder, too.
I don't know.
But I saw a lot of certificates
around the house.
Maybe Ma'am Olive
is a good doctor.
So why doesn't Mookie
seem to be getting better?
I know.
It's because
that kid is stubborn.
She was told not to try to walk,
but she still tried
to leave the room.
- Flor.
- What?
Maybe Mookie is struggling
to get out of her room
because she's feeling
suffocated.
Maybe you need to bring her
out to the garden.
Maybe, but I did that before.
Ma'am Olive didn't want it.
She got mad.
I don't understand.
And I will never disobey
Ma'am Olive again.
I don't want to lose my job.
My family depends on me.
There you go.
I've put everything here.
Take care of this, okay?
- Flor!
- I still have things to do.
Flor, wait!
Let's talk again later.
I still have things to do.
I'm so busy.
Here, Mookie.
Just one bite. Come on.
Please, Mookie. You need to eat.
- I don't want to, Flor.
- Come on. Just one bite.
Your mom will scold me
if you don't eat.
Come on. She's on her way home.
- Just one bite.
- Flor, just bring me
to the hospital, please.
I want to get better.
I can't bear it anymore.
Why? How are you feeling?
Let me see.
I can't bear it anymore.
Oh, no! My God! You're burning!
You have a high fever.
Stay here. I'll call your mom.
Wait, okay?
Hey, Emma. I saw Flor.
She was going to buy a medicine.
She said Mookie
was having a high fever.
What?
If I were your mom,
I would never neglect you.
You can call me your daughter.
It's you, Ma'am!
Fate is really something.
We always meet.
Maybe we were close
in our past lives.
You were the only one
who made me feel like
someone was taking care of me.
And it feels good.
I want you to be my mom.
Who told you that you can
come here during off-hours?
Ma'am Olive
must know about this.
I'll tell her to fire you!
Come on!