That's enough!
Why are you flirting
with my fiancé?
Face me!
Go and like someone else.
I don't care even if I like you.
Because the old Mookie
will never return.
You like me, too?
Why don't you want
to show me your face?
Emma?
Isn't that our plan B?
Marie will come to the rescue
if everything gets tough.
Stop fooling me.
I know you're Emma!
I won't allow us to be
anything less than okay.
Let's go!
Emma!
Even just for your daughter.
Do you think she'll come back?
She's gone forever!
She left you for another man!
She loves someone else now.
And that's not you.
Promise me that we will never
talk about Emma ever again.
Please.
Tell me the truth.
Do you still love Danilo?
Why are you asking me that?
And why are you raising
your voice on me?
Nothing.
I'm sorry.
I'm just worried.
Emma...
let me remind you.
We're in the middle
of the fight.
I need to know
all the weaknesses
that can ruin your defense.
If you love Danilo,
all our plains will fail.
Everything we prepared
for will go to waste.
I don't care about Danilo.
All I want to take back
from Jade is Mookie.
Logan, just Mookie.
Good.
That's all I want to hear.
Thank you, Emma.
Why the long face?
Are you crying?
No, I'm just happy.
Even though our plan
almost got ruined,
we successfully executed it.
It feels good to see Jade
crumbling like a wall...
losing herself,
confused, and speechless.
We've only started, Emma.
Are you ready
for your next move?
Loida, please call Mookie
if everything is ready.
Hello?
Danilo left early.
He didn't tell me where he went.
Stop being paranoid.
Haven't you reconciled already?
That's not the point.
I just have a bad feeling
about this.
Danilo has been acting
differently after the launch.
I think he's looking for Emma.
Why don't you tell him that
Emma's dead so that he'll stop?
No!
My husband and daughter
will grieve.
And Emma will be the star again.
I'll be left out again.
No way.
Besides, how will I explain
the picture, Leticia?
What if Danilo has
it investigated?
You should calm down.
Let's do something
to relax later.
I'll hang up now. See you in the
office. I saw a cutie here.
Bye.
See you.
Hello, Leticia.
Hello?
Leticia.
Hello, Leticia.
Why don't you say anything?
Hi, Sis.
How are you?
Emma?
How nice it is for you
to remember my voice.
I'm calling from the grave.
Leticia, this is not funny.
Stop this prank call
because it's not funny.
Who's Leticia?
I said stop it!
Stop, Leticia!
I'm warning you!
Will you also kill her
like what you did to me, Sis?
How are Danilo and Mookie?
How are my husband and daughter
that you stole from me?
No.
No, no.
You're not real.
You're dead, Emma.
You're dead.
This is impossible!
Because you killed me.
No!
Am I hallucinating?
I'm only imagining things.
This is not real.
Oh my God!
She's dead!
No!
Hello, Jade?
Leave me alone! You're dead!
I know you're dead!
- No! No!
- Aunt Jade.
- Mookie.
- Jade, what's happening?
Keep that away from me!
- Don't touch that!
- Aunt Leticia?
Mookie.
What's happening?
Auntie, what's going on?
Put that down, Mookie!
No!
Auntie...
No! Keep that away from me!
No!
Jade, can you please
stop pranking Mookie?
The kid is getting scared.
Leticia?
Yeah.
You're so silly.
Don't ever pull
that prank again.
Bye. I'll see you at the office.
Okay, okay.
What the hell?
Are you okay, Aunt Jade?
I'm so sorry, Mookie,
that I scared you.
It's Leticia's fault.
It's just...
it's an old prank that
she's been pulling since
we were younger.
I'm so sorry.
Are you ready to eat?
Wait for me there, sweetie.
I'll have the food
brought there.
I'll just change my clothes.
I'll see you there.
I'll get back to you.
Tell me the truth.
Are you working with Emma?
What?
Are you serious?
Then explain to me that call.
I don't know.
Maybe I tapped the button.
You were my last call.
Jade, I'm getting worried
about you.
It was your second time.
You're hallucinating again.
So, please.
Take your medicines already.
No!
It's been a long time
since I last took Pryvaxil.
I haven't had episodes
like this in a while.
You know what?
Maybe I'm only getting
stressed because of Emma.
But I shouldn't.
Because I won't let a dead
person defeat me.
Take this just in case.
Please.
Fine.
Let's go.
You know what, Olive?
Emma is the only cause
of your stress.
Why not focus on other things?
Happy things like your wedding
with Danilo.
Oh, yes.
My wedding.
Do you know what my dream
wedding is?
The backdrop is a waterfall,
which symbolizes the abundant
flow of water.
It's like the abundant flow
of Danilo and Mookie's
love for me.
That sounds nice.
But I wish you would also
think about your mental health
for your life-long happiness.
So, please.
Take your meds.
Leticia, listen.
Danilo and Mookie are my meds.
Thank you.
Oh, yes. I will stay
for a few more minutes.
As for me, I'll check their
other services.
I need a manicure.
- See you later.
Syndicates and criminals use
Necrosol
to make their victims
fall asleep fast.
Anyone who takes this will fall
unconscious after a minute.
Ma'am, your tea is here.
Thank you.
This is good.
What tea is this?
Hi, Sis.
Did you miss me?
Emma?
Hi, Sis.
Did you miss me?
No.
This can't be.
Emma.
Stop it.
You're not real.
I'm only imagining this.
This is just my imagination.
You're not real.
You're dead.
I'm sure you're dead.
No!
Mooks, sorry.
You didn't make it.
But for sure, Stacy rigged
the tryout results.
It's okay.
I don't want to be
a cheerleader, anyway.
Sorry, Mooks.
My class got finished late.
Let's go.
Why are you holding
each other's hands?
You, two.
Oh, she's so thrilled.
Hi, Mookie.
Stop it!
Hey!
Leave Zayn alone!
Stop!
Zayn.
I was right.
That was them.
Look at his shoes.
What do you mean?
They're the ones who attacked
Mookie and beat me.
What?
Zayn!
Come here!
What's your problem?
Let me go!
Did Stacy order you to do that?
Answer me!
Let's go, Zayn!
Let's just forget what happened!
Let's go!
No, Mooks.
I wouldn't mind
if it was just me.
I can fight all day, all night.
But I won't let them hurt you,
too.
Zayn, chill.
I'm sorry.
Mookie, I'm sorry.
So you're admitting it?
You were the ones who attacked
Mookie?
Who told you to do that?
It was Stacy, right?
Did Stacy tell you to do that?
What?
Yes.
Stacy wanted to get even
with Mookie.
Stacy!
I'm warning you.
You'll regret it if you hurt
my girlfriend again.
Oh my God.
So, are you two together?
Please, Cacai.
Save that for later.
Again, Stacy.
Leave her alone.
Are you okay?
Yes, Cacai.
We're in a relationship.
I knew it.
That's why you're so sweet
with each other.
You're even holding
each other's hands.
No.
You're not real.
Go back to your grave
because you're dead!
Are you going to kill me again?
Yes, I will.
I will do that again and again
just to keep you in the grave!
How shocking is that?
You're so afraid of the dead.
But what's scarier is that
you're very much alive,
yet your heart and mind
are shrouded in darkness.
Your sowing of terror is over.
Because I'm here.
And I will be the one
to bury you in the grave.
Go ahead and try.
Go!
You're not real.
You're not real!
You're only in my imagination.
Stay away from me.
Pryvaxil?
What's your illness, Jade?
What happened?
Olive?
Wake up.
Olive.
You've been here
for an hour now.
What happened?
It's so messy.
No! You're not real.
- What is it this time?
- No!
- Olive?
- Where is she?
- I knew this would happen.
- I saw Emma.
She came here. She was inside.
Olive, you're hallucinating
again!
No, I'm not!
I saw Emma!
- What are you talking about?
- I saw her.
I saw Emma.
Stop!
How dare you slap me!
How many times should
I tell you she's dead?
I saw Emma!
Olive! Emma's dead!
Come on!
What's wrong with you?
No.
I can still feel her.
Oh my gosh. Olive, that's
enough.
I'm sure with what I saw.
That's enough, Olive. Stop!
You're getting crazy, Olive.
Please!
Take your medicine.
No!
This is all in my mind.
This is not real.
No!
Where is it?
It's just my imagination.
You're not real!
Hasn't Dra. Samson replied yet
on what the medicine is for?
Not yet.
Why?
Nothing.
I'm proud of you.
You did it alone.
You don't need me anymore.
You can do it on your own.
I still can't, Logan.
I still need you.
I need your help.
But I'm happy that you're proud
of me.
And I know you'll be even
prouder of me
because I have another idea
on how to haunt Jade.
Wow.
Really?
Go ahead.
Tell me.
I changed her ringtone.
How will you use
that to scare her?
Good morning, Ligaya!
Are you saying something?
Wait.
What is it? What are you saying?
Please stop.
Stop.
Don't you enjoy this?
Let's party, Ligaya!
Mookie!
Danilo!
- Mookie! Danilo!
Go ahead and scream.
No one can hear you.
Flor, I need your help so
I can get even with Jade.
Game!
You know what, Emma?
In a battle, there's something
called disarmament.
You first target the opponent's
weapons before you attack.
It might be better if we change
the contents of the bottle.
Zintrixa-X or ZX.
We will replace the tablets
with it.
In short, it'll make her crazy.
Mom is here.
I will fill the void left
by Maria Angela in your heart.
I will love you.
I will never leave you.
I already know who owns the SUV.
Will I finally see Emma?
Bro, here's the car.
Here's the house.
You're the one keeping watch
over our house, right?
Danilo, calm down!
Where's Emma?