Why are you doing this to me?
Is it because I became
close to your daughter?
You did this to yourself, Emma.
- Go get that woman.
- Why are they arresting Emma?
You planted all that!
Even the necklace in the room!
Sometimes, I wish Emma
was my mother.
I was accused of theft.
That's wrong.
Are you going to extort
money from me again?
My daughter is innocent.
So, I'm begging you.
Please drop the case.
And why would I do that?
Let's go to a radio station.
Mom, I don't want to ruin
the kid's name and dignity.
I just wonder how my necklace
ended up in the dark room.
I know Emma isn't
that kind of person.
Unless she was framed up.
Emma's poisoning your brain!
You're growing horns too!
Are you taking Emma's side?
Mommy, no!
No, Mommy!
No, no!
- No, Mommy!
- Are you really like that?
- You're ungrateful!
- Mommy, no!
Mommy, no!
- No, Mommy!
- Ma'am!
Ma'am, please stop!
Ma'am! Have mercy on her!
Ma'am!
Ma'am, please stop!
Did you hear how she
talked back to me?
You ungrateful child!
Unappreciative!
I sacrificed
everything for you!
I gave up the best years
of my life to raise you, Mookie!
I gave you everything!
Don't try my patience.
Because you don't know
what else I can do to you.
Ma'am.
Please, stop.
Mookie, are you okay?
I'm sorry.
They are Elsa and Eva.
Mom, you never mentioned
anything about them before.
I didn't mention them because...
I feel like...
I'm a bad mother.
I'm a worthless woman, Emma.
Mom, that's not true.
That's not true.
You're not perfect,
but you raised
and nurtured me well.
And I don't judge you
on what you did.
I know you have a reason
why you did that.
I understand.
I won't always be there
to help you.
I know it's not easy,
but you have to be brave.
Mommy said I have inner
strength and resolve.
I need to be brave.
I need to be strong.
I need to pick myself up.
Hello?
So, you're still alive.
What made you call?
I told you to stop calling me.
What?
And why would you
come home, Jade?
Mom.
Can you go home?
Please get me some clothes
so I can change.
Okay.
That coffee might keep
you awake all night.
I can't stop thinking,
no matter how I close my eyes.
Thinking?
Of who?
Are you thinking
about Mookie again?
I told you so many times
that you have no reason
to return here.
Stay there in Japan, Jade.
You no longer have
any business here.
And for the last time,
stop calling me.
What's that?
A mouse?
Is there a mouse here?
Mooks.
Are you okay, Mooks?
You look pale.
I'm just shocked, Zayn,
but I can manage.
I will get up and walk
for Mommy Emma.
Probably nothing.
Like a deck of cards,
you're so easy to read.
Ever since your child died,
that look in your eyes...
that kind of look...
it's like you're always
searching
for something that you've lost.
You've always had that look.
It's always there.
If Kayla were alive, she would
be the same age as Mookie.
You know what, Mom?
Every time I take care
of Mookie,
I feel like I'm the one healing.
She healed the wound that I had
been carrying for a long time.
You're lucky.
In the game cards,
you were given the card
that you needed.
I feel better whenever
I'm with Mookie.
I wish I could see her now.
I asked my dad for help.
He talked to the general
that he knows.
He said we could go
to the police station.
Are you okay, Mookie?
You can tell me if
something's bothering you.
I hope my mom won't
go into my room.
No offense, but maybe she
won't expect you
to get up and walk alone.
I struggled so hard earlier.
I crawled and fell.
But while doing
all those things,
I keep hearing Mommy Emma's
voice in my head.
And I won't give up
no matter how hard
and painful everything is.
I can do it because I'm brave.
Sorry, it's not my intention to
air out my grievances to you.
I'm sorry.
No, no. It's okay.
I'm your safe space, Mookie.
I'm here for you.
Mom!
Mookie!
Dear, you can walk
on your own now.
Yes, Mom.
Because you're right.
I just really need
to try and believe.
I can do it too.
I believe in you.
You're my inspiration, Mom.
You're the miracle worker
in my life.
My best medicine.
You are the miracle in my life.
You are the light...
in my mind and heart
whenever I'm sad
and feel hopeless.
I'm here for you, Mom.
I'm so happy that you
and Zayn are here.
I just wish I could hug you.
I could hug you tightly.
I'm sorry, Mom.
You shouldn't be here.
I'm apologizing for
what mommy did to you.
I'm really sorry, Mom.
Sorry, sorry.
No. You didn't do anything
wrong, dear.
What are you doing here?
Did you escape from home?
I need to fix this mess, Mom.
I want to tell the police that
you didn't steal my necklace.
Dear, I didn't like that
you sneaked out
even though I wanted to see you.
I don't like what you did.
I know you have good intentions,
but...
go home before your mom
finds out you left.
Go on.
Mom.
I don't regret coming here.
Because you matter to me.
Don't give your mom
a reason to hurt you.
Why?
What happened?
It's nothing, Mom.
Mookie.
It's nothing, Mom. I promise.
A bruise?
Why do you have a bruise?
Where did you get that?
Mookie?
Mookie!
What happened?
Why do you have a bruise?
It's nothing, Mom.
I just bumped into the door.
Don't worry about it.
Dear, don't be afraid to talk.
Tell the authorities.
The police are here.
Speak up.
Did your mom hurt you?
I'm sorry, Mom.
I need to go home.
No matter the reason, she
has no right to hurt you.
Always remember, okay?
I'm here.
I'll help you.
Sorry, Mom.
We really need to go home.
Zayn, thank you for coming here.
Please take care of Mookie.
Make sure she's safe.
Don't worry, Miss Emma.
I'll take care of Mookie.
Mookie, let's go.
Mommy Emma...
I will always pray for
and think of you.
Me too.
Be safe.
Sorry, Mom.
Come on, Mookie.
Flor?
Flor!
Flor, come on!
I'm coming, Ma'am!
I'm coming!
What's going on, Ma'am?
Why are you calling me?
Mookie's missing, Flor!
What?
Mookie's in her room, Ma'am.
- How...
- Are you stupid?
She's not there!
Call the guard!
Hurry!
Okay, okay.
Number...
Where did that kid go?
He's not picking up.
Ma'am, what if Mookie
has been kidnapped?
Here it is.
He already answered.
Hello, guard!
Yes. This is from
1 Hillview Lane.
Yes. Please help us.
My employer's daughter
is missing.
Please send a guard here.
Hurry!
Please hurry up! Yes!
Yes, yes.
Okay. Thank you.
Ma'am, the guards are
on their way here.
If Mookie left...
How?
I don't know, Ma'am.
I was already sleeping
in my room, Ma'am.
Did she go to Emma?
Get my cell phone and car keys.
Hurry! It's in my room!
- Move!
- Yes, I will.
Darn you, Emma.
You can't take my daughter
away from me.
You've been quiet.
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
Tell me if I'm overstepping
boundaries.
But did you really get
that bruise from the door?
You don't need to say anything.
I get you.
Miss Emma is right, you know?
Some people can help you.
Tell me if you need help.
But...
How do I tell other people
about my mother?
It's difficult.
It's painful.
It's painful to think
that she's hurting me.
Something...
I couldn't admit
to myself for a long time.
I make excuses whenever
she hits me.
Sometimes, I think....
maybe she's just
not in the mood.
Or maybe she's also having
a hard time understanding me
because I'm stubborn.
Or maybe she's getting
tired of me.
Or it's my fault why
she's hurting me.
Sometimes, my parents
get mad at me too
but they never laid
their hands on me.
You could've told
Miss Emma the truth.
the police about it.
But...
But it feels like...
I'm betraying my mom.
I legit hope she doesn't
hurt you again.
If your mom hurts you again,
don't be afraid to report her.
Careful, Mookie.
Can you do it?
Mookie!
Come here, you little brat!
Where did you go?
Come here!
You?
You again!
Do you know I can sue you?
Mommy, he's not doing
anything wrong.
I was the one
who asked him a favor.
If this person had brains,
he wouldn't help you escape!
How are you, Mookie?
Are you okay, dear?
Where's your wheelchair?
Mommy, I can walk now.
You can walk?
Since when?
Flor, help Mookie.
Don't force yourself!
And, you...
Why are you still
standing there?
Leave!
And you stay away
from my daughter!
Leave!
- Ma'am, we safely...
- Leave!
I'll call the cops!
Mommy, I don't want that.
It hurts, Mommy.
- We need to do this.
- Mommy! I said I don't want it!
Really, Dan?
You reported her to the
barangay?
Yes, Emma.
You know I can't ignore you.
We received a complaint
against you.
About what?
About possible child abuse.
Be careful with your answers.
May we know how you got
your bruise?
Do you think she'll talk?
Will she confess?
Is there something
you want to tell us, dear?