I've noticed Emma has been more
irritable these past few days.
Maybe she's just in a bad mood.
I hope that's the only reason.
Not something worse.
You don't have to worry
about me.
I'm okay.
But what you did to our daughter
isn't okay.
She's been going through
a tough time,
and you've made it worse
by hurting her.
That wouldn't happen if Jade
stayed out of it.
Let's push your paranoia
to the limit.
Who's the crazy one?
It's you!
Why are you still alive?
Emma, it's me, Jade.
I will kill you.
- Ms. Emma!
- Mom!
Mookie!
Emma, why did you hurt your
child?
What did I do?
I can't understand what I feel.
I need to go back to my family.
Danilo, Mookie.
Will they suture my wound?
Stop crying, dear.
You can do it.
Mom taught me to be brave.
And yet she's still hurt you,
baby girl.
Dad...
Dad, what's going on with Mom?
Did I do something wrong?
Or is there something
I didn't do?
Dear, don't blame yourself.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Mookie, Danilo, I'll leave you
for now.
I'll call the pharmacy's
security agency
so they can look for Emma.
Why? Where's Mom?
Don't worry, baby girl.
I will do everything
to find your mother.
I promise you that.
I won't lose you again,
my child.
Thank you, Nurse.
Dad.
I wonder what happened to Mom.
I'm worried that something bad
might have happened to her.
Dear.
Your mom is brave and strong
like you.
So let's trust that she's okay.
Mookie.
Jade.
Danilo.
I'm so sorry.
Sorry for what?
I feel that it's all my fault.
Maybe I should've gotten
Emma checked
when I noticed she's acting
strange.
What do you mean?
Obviously, Emma is not in her
right mind.
She's gone insane.
I'm just very lucky
that I survived.
But you, Mookie.
She hurt you, too.
I can't forgive myself if
I let Emma's condition worsen.
We need to do something.
What are you suggesting, Auntie?
We should get Emma confined
in a private psychiatric clinic
once we find her.
Emma doesn't know
what she's doing.
She almost killed me.
She also hurt Mookie.
Wait. Hold on.
I can't...
I can't decide about
that right now, Jade.
I know, Danilo.
But we need to decide
what's best for Emma.
Are we going to wait for her
to do something worse?
What if she hurt other people?
She's even a danger to herself.
Maybe Mom can have a therapy
session at home.
She can manage that.
I promise.
Let's get Mom treated at home.
Mookie, baby girl.
I know it hurts.
But we have to face the reality.
Even I feel sad every time
I think about it,
but your mother has become
someone we don't know.
But, Auntie, I don't want to.
I don't want to get separated
from her.
Wait. Let's not talk about this
yet.
Let's look for Emma first.
I'm sorry.
I'm so worried about my wife.
It's okay, Danilo.
You don't have to apologize.
You have every reason
to be upset.
And don't worry.
I'll help you find Emma.
It's a promise.
I am Olive Caparas's sister.
You mentioned it over the phone,
Ma'am.
But you didn't tell me
your name.
You don't need to know.
There's something I want you
to do.
What is it, Ma'am?
You need to find her.
Her again?
I want you to scare her
once you find her.
Make her paranoia worse
until she goes crazy.
So I can get even with what she
did to my sister.
The police almost caught me
the last time, Ma'am.
This will cost a lot.
Don't worry.
I know your price.
Do you want me to bring her
to you alive?
Don't ever hurt or kill her.
Just bring her to the place
that I will tell you.
Make sure she's already insane.
She must not recognize you.
And don't ever tell her
that I had her kidnapped.
Understood?
Okay, Ma'am.
Good.
Bye!
Hello, Jade.
Can you come home?
So that Mookie won't be alone
here.
I want to look for Emma.
I'm feeling restless.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Mookie and I will wait for you.
Okay, Jade.
Dad, any update?
Did they find Mom?
They still haven't found her,
Dear.
Is what Aunt Jade said true?
Does Mom already have
a mental problem?
What if Mommy Olive and Mom have
the same mental illness?
I know your mother.
She's not violent.
But I don't understand
why she became like that.
This is the first time
it has happened to her.
Will you let her be in a
psychiatric clinic
once we find her?
If that will bring her back
to her old self, I will.
Where are you going?
Who are you?
Don't you recognize me?
I'm the Reaper.
You're not funny.
I'm not trying to be funny.
I'm begging you.
Whoever you are, let me go.
My family needs me.
I need to go back to my family.
Leave me alone.
Oh, no!
Sorry.
Oh, no.
Baby girl!
Don't touch that!
Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- Loida, please clean this up.
Yes, Ma'am.
I'm really sorry, Auntie Jade.
- It's okay.
- It slipped into my hand.
I'll clean it up.
It's okay, Sweetie.
Everything's good.
Are you okay?
Why do you look so tense? Relax.
I worry about my mom.
She's been missing for hours.
Do you have any updates
about her?
What did they say?
Did they find her?
The security agency hasn't given
an update yet.
But let them do their work,
Sweetie.
Don't worry about it. Okay?
I'm sure she's fine.
What matters is for you
to eat and get some rest.
So you'll recover.
I only want to know if Mom
is safe.
I know.
Me, too.
I've been worried sick all day,
especially knowing that Emma
can't take care of herself.
Anyway, go on.
Eat this.
Stay in your room.
I'll have someone bring you
some juice.
Okay.
Go on.
Go, baby girl.
I'm begging you.
Leave me alone.
What did I do to you?
Leave me alone!
I'm here to pick you up.
Are you ready?
Ouch! Crazy!
Wait.
Don't shoot.
I have a family.
Who are you?
Take your mask off.
Mookie!
I told you to shut up!
You are Olive's henchman!
Why are you here?
Why did you follow me?
Who ordered you to do it?
Olive?
Why are you still alive?
I'll kill you!
Emma!
Emma, stop!
- Emma!
- Mookie!
Emma, why did you hurt your
daughter?
What have you done?
Is Jade the one behind this?
Is it her?
Jade will kill me.
I'm not crazy.
I was right all along.
Jade will kill me.
Mookie and Danilo should know
about it.
She will kill me.
I'm not crazy.
I was right. She will kill me.
I should tell Danilo and Mookie.
I must go back to them.
I'll go back to them.
Mookie!
I told you that she shouldn't
recognize you.
You were so dumb
for a gun owner!
You're useless.
Emma will come here for sure.
Hello.
We'll proceed with the plan.
Come here as fast as you can.
You know what to do.
There's still no news
about Emma.
Auntie Jade, is there no one
we can ask for help from?
To look for Mom?
I know we agreed not to report
it to the police.
But I now want to ask them
for help.
Me too, Danilo.
But Emma isn't considered
a missing person yet.
She hasn't been missing
for 48 hours.
I can't just stand here
while my wife is missing.
You're here for Mookie, Danilo.
Your daughter needs you, too.
And I know we still haven't
finalized it yet.
But I've already called
the medical team
of the mental health clinic.
What for, Auntie Jade?
They need to talk to us about
your mom.
They have a pre-assessment
interview
regarding Emma's mental health
condition.
Mookie!
Mom?
- Danilo!
- Emma!
- That's Mom!
- Loida, is that Emma?
Mom!
Emma!
Mookie!
Mom!
Emma!
- Mom!
- Where have you been?
What happened to you?
Emma, I was so worried
about you.
We've been waiting for you,
Emma!
I'm glad my prayers have been
answered!
You're home!
I can now execute my plans
against you, Emma.
You're a poor mouse walking
into my trap.
Demon!
Emma!
Mom!
Why? What did...
How dare you drag God into your
evilness!
Mom?
You're going to kill me.
She's going to kill me.
She almost killed me.
Emma, what are you talking
about?
Danilo, she seems
to be paranoid.
Stop denying it!
You told Olive's henchman
to follow me to the woods!
Let go of me!
-Mom!
-Emma!
What are you saying?
Olive is dead.
Maybe you're just imagining
things that happened before.
But she's gone.
Danilo, believe me.
Believe me!
I saw it.
I saw Olive's henchman.
I saw him.
Mookie.
He's the same man who abducted
us before.
He was wearing a scary mask.
He looked like an old man.
An old man! He was so scary.
You will kill me!
Mask?
Abducted?
Emma.
Emma, what are you talking
about?
Danilo, look what's happening
to Emma!
She needs help!
- Emma!
- Mom!
I'll kill you!
Mom!
Emma, stop!
Jade didn't do anything wrong
to you!
She's actually so worried
about you!
She's just pretending.
She's fooling us!
- I'm not doing anything to you.
- Mom, what's happening to you?
This is the second time you
hurt Aunt Jade.
I didn't know you could do
such a thing!
Mookie, believe me.
I'm telling the truth.
She's the bad one!
You're no longer the Mommy Emma
I knew.
What's happening to you, Mom?
Danilo, you need to make
a decision.
Look at what's happening
to Emma.
- This is not right anymore.
- Dear, it's still me.
Shut up!
Mookie, it's still me.
Dear!
Hey, what's this?
I'm not sick!
Dan!
Emma, what we're going
to do is for you.
This is for you.
Dan! What are you doing?
I'm not crazy!
Don't let them do this!
Mookie!
- Mom! I'm sorry!
- Mookie!
Mookie, it's still me!
Dear!
Hey!
What's this? I'm not sick! Dan!
Emma, what we're going to do
is for you.
This is for you.
Dan! What are you doing?
I'm not crazy!
Don't let them do this!
Mookie!
Mom! I'm sorry, Mom!
- Sorry!
- Mookie!
Don't hurt her!
You're right, Emma.
I'm a demon.
Welcome to hell.
Mookie!
Danilo!
I don't want to come with you!
Mookie!
Danilo!
I'm begging you.
Mookie.
Let go of me.
I don't want to come.
I don't want to! I'm not crazy!
I'll follow Emma.
Dad!
Dad, I'll go with you.
Please, Dad.
- Let me go with you.
- Mookie, no.
You'll only get hurt when you
see your mom's condition.
Dad, please.
- Let me come with you.
- No, no.
We'll go instead.
Mookie.
I'll take care of your mom.
I won't neglect her.
I'll take care of her.
I promise you that. Okay?
Auntie, please.
Please, make sure my mom gets
better there.
I will.
I'll take care of your mother.
Okay?
Danilo, I'll change my clothes
first.
Okay, okay.
Mookie.
Stay here, dear.
Stay here.
Let go of me!
Mookie!
Dan!
I don't want it anymore.
She's so insane.
They're demons. Kill them.
They'll kill you.
They're evil.
You need to take care
of yourself.
Don't forget that Mookie
needs you.
And I'm also here to help you.
It's time for your medication.
I saw you and Jade!
You're in cahoots!
Don't!
You're mind is making that up.
That's why you need medicine.
I'm just thinking if we did the
right thing in putting Mom
in a psychiatric clinic.
Behave.
Your family is here.
- Emma!
- Mom!
They're planning something
evil against me.
Emma!
You're a monster!
I will kill you!