Emma?
If possible, please don't tell
anyone the patient is here.
Okay, Logan.
That's also how it was with
Jade.
You love saving women.
How are you?
Who are you? I don't know you!
The man who helped you escape
from the yakuza in Japan.
Oh, no, Madam.
Danilo's here.
Tell him Emma escaped
on her own will.
And she has no intention
of seeing them.
She said you didn't want her.
That's why she wanted
to go away.
That means Mom doesn't want us
anymore.
I'm ready to fill in Emma's
shortcomings with you
and Mookie.
Even if it means that I have
to be Mookie's mother.
I'll help you, Danilo.
You promised me you
wouldn't be like Mommy.
You told me you wouldn't hurt
me.
You said you wouldn't leave me,
no matter what happens.
But what did you do?
You shouldn't have looked for me
if you would only leave us.
I wish I hadn't met you.
I don't want you anymore, Mom.
I don't want to see you again!
I hope you don't come back
anymore!
Mookie!
Mookie?
Mookie, dear!
Mookie!
- Mookie, dear! Where are you?
- Son of a...
Mookie!
You haven't recovered yet.
Go get some rest.
Let go of me!
You need to rest!
My daughter needs me!
She's in danger!
Your daughter isn't here!
Come on! Get some rest.
Mookie! Mookie!
That's enough.
You're lucky I found you.
Poor you.
No one seems to care for you.
Don't worry.
I'll help you.
I'll take care of you.
Wait, wait.
Jade, Jade!
Jade.
We shouldn't be doing this.
This is wrong.
We shouldn't do this.
Don't you like me, Danilo?
Because I like you a lot.
Please accept me.
Emma?
Logan, here's the food.
Please put it over there,
Manang.
Okay.
- You can go.
- Okay.
You're awake.
You're safe here.
Go on and eat.
Regain your strength.
Then, I'll give you
your medicine.
I don't want to take any
medicines.
I'm not taking it!
No, no.
This isn't the wrong medication.
This will help you get better.
Don't worry.
You won't get harmed.
I'll help you get better.
Danilo.
Jade!
Jade, sorry.
Sorry.
This is my fault.
Jade.
No, no, no, Danilo.
It's my fault.
It's my fault that...
I don't know how it happened.
I'm such a bad sister.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, Danilo.
I shouldn't have done this!
Forgive me, Emma.
I hope you can forgive me, Emma.
Bastards.
You're so big, but you let
a drunk man knock you down.
What's your salary for?
If this happens again,
I will knock you down myself.
I'm sorry, Boss.
Sorry, my foot.
What are you blabbering?
What nonsense are you talking
about?
What can your sorry do?
Get out of here
before I beat you.
Stupid.
Boss.
Yes, Marco.
Any updates on Mr. Uy?
He hasn't paid his debt yet.
He hasn't even given me
the interest.
He asked for an extension again,
Boss.
My lending business will go
bankrupt if this continues.
What about the thing I told you
to investigate?
That's why I'm here, Boss.
I got information about
the woman you're helping.
What is it?
I paid someone in Haven Wood.
But she could only give me
a little information.
The woman's name is Emma Joseco.
Emma Joseco.
Emma.
I heard she's married
and has a child.
But I don't have any information
about the two.
The people I asked around
are scared.
Doctor Samson said they
probably gave her
the wrong medication
in Haven Wood.
You're doing it right.
Continue investigating.
I want to get to know
that woman better.
Emma.
As I said, the patient's
withdrawal symptoms
from the medication she received
won't go away quickly.
Are you sure it's alright
with you that she's here?
Yes, Doc.
Taking care of a psychiatric
patient isn't easy, Logan.
And I can't promise you
I can treat her fast.
Why don't you transfer her
to another psychiatric center?
Okay.
I have to go.
I need to do my rounds
in the hospital.
Thank you, Doc.
Be safe, Doc.
Please don't bring me back
to Haven Wood.
They're making me crazy.
I won't get better there.
On one condition...
You'll cooperate
with the treatment.
You'll trust me.
And most of all,
you'll eat and get stronger.
Let me.
Today...
Soup, fish, rice, juice...
You don't want it?
Okay.
Hello, Haven Wood.
Yes, I'm sending a patient
there.
Maybe it'll take 30 minutes...
Never mind.
These are some of the
foods I learned to cook
when I was still in Japan.
But I'm worried about
you getting tired of my cooking,
so let's eat out.
Let's go somewhere.
Really?
Don't worry, Mookie.
Even though your mom isn't here,
I'm here.
I was also a mom.
I mean, I tried taking care
of my friends' kids in Japan.
I can't promise I'll be as good
as your Mommy Emma.
But I'll try my very best
to take good care of you
and your dad.
So, I hope you'll also treat me
as your mom, baby girl.
Is that okay?
Auntie Jade, thank you.
I don't know what to do without
you.
Anything for you, baby girl.
Let's eat!
The food will get cold. Come on.
Yeah. The food you cooked
is good.
Try the gyoza.
You can go now.
It's normal.
The doctor said
it's withdrawal symptoms
from the wrong medicines
you took.
Why are you helping me?
Because you need it.
I found you unconscious
on the street.
Anyone would do what I did.
But if you don't trust me,
please tell me where you live.
I'll have someone bring you
home.
I don't think there's a family
that wants me.
They even let me be brought
to a psychiatric center.
I can't blame them
because I hurt them.
I feel like they don't want me
anymore.
Because they never came back
to Haven Wood to see me.
But I really have a bad feeling
about Jade.
Wait.
Jade?
Jade Caparas.
I just found out that we're
sisters.
But I have a bad feeling about
her.
I know she's the same as her
twin, Olive.
Where are you going?
What's this?
Mookie!
Danilo!
I don't trust Jade Caparas.
She's planning something bad
against me.
She'll kill me.
She'll kill me
Emma.
I'll touch you, okay?
I'll be gentle.
I'm here.
Trust me.
You need to regain
your strength.
Because once you recover,
we'll go and see your child.
I promise you that.
They'll just bring you back
to Haven Wood if you do it now.
Do you want that?
No, right?
I'll help you bounce back.
Just trust me.
So, for now, get some rest.
Get stronger.
I'll just take this call.
Marco, what's up?
Go on and eat.
- Baby girl, come on and eat.
- I will, Auntie.
Auntie, I'm sorry you've
had to take care of us.
Yeah, Jade.
What you've done for us
is more than enough.
It's okay.
Actually, in a way,
you two make me happy.
Because it's my dream
to have my own family.
I didn't feel the love from my
and Jade's adoptive parents.
I mean Olive.
That's why I told myself I'd do
everything once I had a family.
Eat, baby girl.
Son of a gun!
So, Emma's telling the truth.
She's not only connected
to Jade.
She's her sister.
Based on the information
I gathered, Jade's twin sister,
Olive Caparas, stole Emma
and Danilo's daughter.
That's why the kid is still
using Olive Caparas's name.
Olive and Emma share
the same mother.
But I heard Olive Caparas
is already dead.
So Jade has a twin sister.
Looks like fate is playing
tricks on you, Boss.
But it seems that you're already
falling for Emma.
Unfortunately, she's no longer
available.
She has a husband.
Are you sure it's Emma's
husband?
Yes, Boss.
The man's name is Danilo.
And Mookie is the kid's name.
Dan, wait.
I didn't notice I was being
messy.
- Sorry.
- Keep eating.
Dan, wait.
I didn't notice I was being
messy.
- Sorry.
- Keep eating.
Look, Boss.
Jade seems to like the father.
Look how she cares for them.
I don't care if it's the man
Jade is going crazy for.
What matters to me now is Emma.
Do you mean you won't tell
them that you have Emma?
We don't know the whole story
yet.
Emma should stay with me
for now.
Is that really the reason
you're helping Emma?
Aren't you falling
for her already?
After six months of
dedicated treatment,
therapy, and perseverance,
you're now healed.
Well, what can I say?
I'm not surprised.
Thank you, Logan.
Thank you so much.
This is the only time I've
felt like having a whole
and happy family.
Danilo and Mookie fulfill
that dream of mine.
I wonder how they're doing.
I wonder how my husband
and child are doing.
Can I see them?
I don't think it's
the right time.
But I'm okay now, Logan.
I'm healed.
I miss them so much.
Dan, will you take this journey
with me?
Will you let the two of us
and Mookie be a family?
Mom?