[English subtitles are available]
[Ji Jin-hee]
[Yoon Se-ah]
[Kim Hye-eun]
[This program includes virtual
and indirect advertisements.]
[The Road: The Tragedy of One]
[All characters, groups,
and events are fictional.]
[Day of Choi Joon-young's death,
7:40 p.m.]
-Yes!
-Awesome.
Darn it.
Are you Soo-hyun's son?
See you around.
Go on and play.
Why didn't you tell him he was wrong?
Where are you going?
[Staff]
What's up?
[-You never call me first.]
-How could you do this without asking me?
-What are you talking about?
[-Yeon-woo.]
You did it, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
It wasn't me.
Then...
where's my Yeon-woo?
[We need to talk.]
[I have nothing to talk about.]
[What's wrong?
Do you feel something's off too?]
[What are you talking about?]
[I thought you knew too.]
Come here.
Gosh.
This is awesome.
-Let go.
-Come on.
-I'll kill you if you tell Dad.
-Hey.
Come here. I said, come here!
Where did this prick go?
Just wait and see.
Something huge will come up.
Hey! You're not supposed
to just jump in like that.
You're the driver.
Hey, stand up.
Come on.
Where do you live?
Where are your parents?
Could you drive me home?
Your home? Hang on a second.
Gosh.
Here.
About the upcoming overhaul.
I was thinking
of an interview or an article
of the new face of the seven o'clock news.
Right. I heard Kwak Young-seo
would be the anchor.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I'm not sure if that's actually true.
I shouldn't have said that.
Please excuse me for a second.
I'm trying to give you a better position.
Don't you understand?
I feel like you're excluding me
on purpose.
[That's just a misunderstanding.
I hate being misunderstood.]
And I hate being a substitute,
let alone being a concubine!
If that's how you're going to use me,
I want you to stop.
Seo-young. Please don't do this again.
Come to the hotel by 10 p.m.
I can't promise.
[Come.]
Or our relationship is over.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes.
Around tomorrow or the day after,
I'll visit your parents.
Don't come over.
They'll only scold me.
Are you serious?
All right, then. Go on.
Be careful.
[You won't be able to keep your job
if I go down.]
[So come in right away.]
[The original file
wasn't at Soo-hyun's place either.]
Yeon-woo.
I'm hurt.
Aren't you worried
that your friend got hurt?
Take a pill then.
You take them all the time.
Will this do?
Are you really not going to
talk about that anymore?
Stop lying!
Just get lost.
You felt the same thing that I did.
[15 minutes before
Choi Joon-young's death]
[Day 40]
Seo-young.
[Final Episode]
The person you should punish is me.
I am...
the other person who is responsible
for Joon-young's death.
No.
That can't be.
-It's all a lie!
-Yeon-woo.
-Dad.
Come this way.
Only you can put a stop to this.
As Joon-young's father.
"Father"?
Do I even have the right
to be called that?
All right. I'll do anything.
Should I tell the truth?
Not right now.
In order to keep the child safe,
we must make Ms. Cha give up.
That's what comes first.
Please follow my instructions.
Do not be surprised by whatever you hear.
I'll ask you one last time.
Is everything you said true?
It is.
I am...
not the accomplice.
You were a lawyer, so you must know
that you'll be punished
for changing your statement.
I'm aware of that.
When did you find out that Choi Joon-young
is Baek Soo-hyun's biological son?
What are you talking about?
Joon-young is my son.
You promised that I could see my wife.
I'd like to see her now.
Okay.
-Take him to her.
-Yes, sir.
[BSN Anchor Cha Kidnapped a Young Boy]
[Anchor Baek Soo-hyun's Son Kidnapped]
[Baek Soo-hyun is the Father
of the Royal The Hill Victim]
We should've ended this long ago.
What is this?
I'm sorry.
You've suffered enough.
Don't deny it.
That's how I see it as your dad.
Baek Soo-hyun...
Baek Soo-hyun is now done for.
I'm going to make everyone
point their fingers at him.
-Wait and see.
-Dad, please.
You can't do this anymore. Divorce him.
Some things need to be forgotten,
and some things must not.
Don't get them mixed up.
In the end,
I knew nothing.
Your financial issues,
Congressman Hwang's threats,
and your deal with Chairman Seo.
You even pretended to be the accomplice.
I knew nothing at all.
You must've thought I was despicable.
You must've resented Joon-young and me.
No.
You're wrong. That's not true.
From the moment Joon-young was born
until now,
I was his father.
The reason you married me,
your affairs.
I forgot about them all
the moment I saw Joon-young.
You don't have to believe me.
I don't care about that either.
The business trip at that time.
It was a lie.
[I actually followed you.]
[I wanted to see everything myself]
[and end everything.]
[But]
[the moment I saw your face,]
[I was stuck.]
[Congressman Hwang Tae-seop]
Yes, sir.
[And I saw my lowest.]
[While Joon-young was dying,]
[I was holding onto a worn-out life rope]
[-and was doing that stupid thing.]
-Harder.
Hit me harder.
Right here at the pit of the stomach.
I like the suffocating feeling.
Here.
Why? You can't do it?
It's not so easy
to be exploited by a pervert.
The more you say something like that,
the more pleasure I feel.
Hurry and hit me.
This is what I'm talking about.
[I couldn't give up even after that.]
[I tried so hard to the point
that it was disgusting.]
I realized only after I lost everything.
What I was holding in my hands
was a handful of sand.
Give me a chance.
The last chance to remain
as your husband and Joon-young's dad.
I'm begging you.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you still here?
I don't know where to go.
The case isn't over yet. You know that.
I don't care anymore.
Baek Soo-hyun.
A guy like me can't reveal the truth.
Atonement.
From the beginning,
I didn't even have the right to do that.
Close the case first.
And try your best
as you always talked about.
Kneel down in front of the family and beg.
Beg for their forgiveness.
That's how people live.
Is it...
-the original file?
-I'll leave it to you.
Do it for me.
You're
not going to regret this?
Not anymore.
[Director]
What?
Shim Seok-hoon went back to the scene?
Okay.
Things might go easier.
[Jaekang]
[Regular savings account, Debt Collection]
Why did they have to die
because of this little thing?
[Chairman Seo Ki-tae]
[-It's me.]
-Go on.
There must be many things to hear and say.
I'll visit you right now.
All right.
Okay.
So what you're saying
is that the main culprit of all this
is me?
The way you've been living
indicates that.
The money you lent to Baek Soo-hyun
and got back from Oh Jang-ho.
You retrieved it
and invested in Choi Joon-young's
father's company.
It gives me chills.
Is that your theory?
You can investigate
according to your narrative.
What are you doing here?
The original file. I have it.
I knew it.
Is that all?
I thought you would bring up the old debt.
Why are you not using that card?
I have two children as old as you.
My daughter
also doesn't have a mother like you.
She's my only family.
But there's nothing I did for her.
Even though there's nothing more precious
than a family.
Don't you think so?
Yes.
You know it at a young age.
I'm helping you because you said
it's about a friend
who you treat like a family.
For Yoon Dong-pil, you, and Baek Soo-hyun,
everything will be fine.
Thank you.
I will pay you back
no matter what it takes.
Later.
You will have a chance to do that
in the far future.
You can pay me back then.
I called you to have a meal together.
Thinking about the past
like you said as well.
Eat. The food is getting cold.
The Chairman wanted to give you this.
[Divorce Agreement Confirmation]
[Baek Soo-hyun, Seo Eun-soo]
How is Eun-soo doing?
Hurry up.
If you really care for her.
[Baek Soo-hyun, Seo Eun-soo]
[What's embarrassing
about having a crush on someone?]
[You don't like showing your work
before your exhibition, right?]
It's the same.
You can be quite fussy sometimes.
You take after your dad.
If Dad finds out, he'll tease me again.
It looks like he's already figured it out.
[Soo-hyun: I know nothing I say
can put things right.]
[I'm so sorry
that you had to suffer because of me]
[and that you found out this way.]
[I'm really sorry. I'll leave tomorrow.]
[Royal The Hill
Master Key Analysis Report]
Right.
I thought I have changed since then,
but I was wrong.
Laugh at me all you want.
I failed in everything, after all.
I'm sorry, honey.
I should've apologized to you sooner.
You can resent me all you want.
Blame me and curse me.
I just thought
everything would be fine
as long as you and Yeon-woo
didn't find out.
I thought I had been living my life
atoning for my sins,
but no.
After all, I was a selfish jerk
who only cared about himself.
I beg for your forgiveness.
I don't care if this is just a dream
or an illusion.
I beg you.
I'm sorry.
So please...
Please forgive me.
Soo-hyun.
This is neither a dream
nor an illusion.
Why are you here?
I came to talk to you about something,
but I'm not sure anymore.
I don't care.
There's something I want to tell you.
I don't want to lie to you anymore.
I want to tell you everything.
This is going to be
an excruciatingly lengthy excuse.
My father was
a murderer.
Baek Soo-hyun!
[Just kill me right here and now.]
[-That will solve everything.]
-Run.
[-What?
-You can't be here.]
[This is the answer to my effort.]
[Tell Dong-pil.]
You're the one who did it! Tell them!
[Just don't try to do anything.
It disgusts me!]
You know everything about me now.
I was always aware
that there was something within you
that I didn't know about.
I had no idea what it was,
but I've waited
for the moment
when you'd show me your true face.
I didn't care what kind of person
you were and what kind of life
you had led, but...
But why didn't I know that back then?
I'm sorry.
I should never have let you go.
[Trusted Police Force]
[Records of Jaekang Group's Slush Fund]
[The file has been copied and moved.]
[Mild Soju]
Hey, you're still here.
Right. I forgot something.
-Okay. I'll be off then.
-Okay. Bye.
[Shim Seok-hoon: I think Chairman Seo
has another plan. Be careful.]
[I'll go buy groceries.]
[Let's eat together.]
Is everything ready?
Yes, sir.
I thought my sin would weigh
more than this.
When this investigation is over,
I want you to go somewhere abroad
and stay there for a few years.
The legal team will take care of it.
What is it?
Nothing, sir.
What brings you
all the way here, Mr. Choi?
I'm here because of Seo-young.
Seo-young is doing all right.
No, she isn't.
Why don't we talk somewhere else?
Let me ask you a question here.
The day Joon-young died,
you met Seo-young privately, didn't you?
And before that,
you visited Royal The Hill.
Did Seo-young say that?
The case has been transferred
to another department,
and she's now under investigation
for child abuse.
Your confirmation will turn the tables.
What do you mean by, confirmation?
We need someone
to prove that Seo-young
didn't see Joon-young,
and that she didn't give him any drugs.
I guess
this is being recorded.
I'm not falling just yet.
Which is probably
why I don't feel like doing it.
Are you saying you're not going to help?
At least Seo-young will understand me.
Please tell her I said sorry.
And please also tell her
that I'd be waiting somewhere even higher.
I mean every word I said.
I see.
Stop bothering Director Kwon.
We've done enough.
Eat up.
I just got something simple.
You have only 12 more hours to go.
And then?
I'll be sent to custody.
I did everything I could.
Most of the charges will be mitigated.
Don't worry.
You're such a fool.
I know.
[Police]
Well...
Today, I'm going to turn myself in.
[The Chairman of Jaekang Group, Seo Ki-tae
appeared at the Prosecutors' Office.]
[The Culprit of Royal The Hill Abduction,
Chairman Seo Ki-tae]
[Seo said he feels strongly responsible
for the Royal The Hill Abduction.]
[He promised to disclose
the original file about the slush funds,]
[which was the cause of the whole issue,]
[and the original file
about the illegal political funds.]
What in the world...
What's going on?
Sir.
Yes, sir.
No. I'm also trying to figure it out.
Yes.
Gosh, what's with all the fuss
at this early hour?
The confession will be no use now.
You're right.
I guess that's what he was going for.
Well, we know the culprit now,
and it means the case will be
wrapped up soon.
Looks like everything went well.
What are you doing?
You were an informant.
How much are you involved in this?
Was it also you
who sent the photo to Oh Jang-ho?
Do you have evidence?
Answer my question!
You're not any different from me.
You came to this team
because of an order from a higher-up.
I know everything.
Because of that photo, a person died.
How could you say that?
Wasn't it you who leaked
the information about the investigation
and put Baek Soo-hyun in that house?
You're the one
who messed this all up!
What are you doing now?
What else did you do?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Captain, you understand what I mean.
Why don't you stop bothering people here
and just drink?
Drink like a fish, like you used to do.
Get out.
With pleasure.
[Mild Soju]
[Kang Jae-yeol: Answer the phone
or watch the news.]
[What happened to the original file?
Watch the news now!]
[Chairman Seo Ki-tae Turns Himself In and
Prosecution Acquires the Original File]
An abduction case?
[Yes.]
[I need your help.]
[Okay. I'll join the team.]
[Seo Ki-tae Turns Himself In,
Prosecution Secures Original Files]
[Why did he hand over the original files?]
[The reason why he revealed them
instead of destroying them.]
[The reason why he got me involved
in the abduction.]
It took longer than I expected.
You owe me one, remember?
You told me then
that they were like family to you.
That Yoon Dong-pil and Baek Soo-hyun
needed help.
So I helped you, didn't I?
You wouldn't deny that now, would you?
You promised me then
that you would make it up to me.
People have died,
and you want me to repay you now?
No. Later on.
You need to cover up
just one thing for me.
[Just one thing.]
[He said I need to cover up
just one thing.]
I thought you'd bring up the old debt.
Why not use that card?
[She's my only family,]
but I've done nothing for her.
[He made the same face.]
[The face of a father.]
Family.
[Seo Ki-tae Turns Himself In,
Prosecution Secures Original Files]
No.
[The reason why he revealed the files
instead of destroying them.]
Honey.
Eun-soo!
[Seo Ki-tae Turns Himself In,
Prosecution Secures Original Files]
[To Soo-hyun, To Yeon-woo]
[I'm sorry, Soo-hyun.]
[It would've been better
if you had lied to me.]
[Lies are stronger than you think.]
[With just a bit of hypocrisy,]
[you can deceive yourself]
[and go on as if nothing is wrong.]
[That is]
[what I did best.]
[But then the moment]
[you said you loved me
with an innocent look, I realized]
[how cruel and heavy the truth can be.]
[I'm not the kind of person
you think I am.]
[I must stand before you as a lie
even until the last moment.]
[I waited a long time for you to love me,]
[but I don't deserve it.]
[I'm sorry,]
[Soo-hyun.]
No.
No, it can't be.
[The world in a snow globe
does not change.]
[It's always beautiful,]
[and it's always full of happiness.]
[I wanted to become
that kind of mother and wife.]
Yeon-woo.
You really didn't know?
What?
I don't want to hear it, so just leave.
You also know
that your dad
is my biological dad.
Stop it! I don't want to hear it!
Yeon-woo.
Joon-young, what were you talking about?
Who told you that?
Everyone knows.
I bet Yeon-woo knows it too.
Say it's not true.
Mom.
Say it!
Wait...
You're mistaken.
You know it too.
That's why you always give me that look.
-That pity in your eyes...
-Please!
You should go home.
Why should I leave?
This is my dad's home.
Don't do this, Joon-young.
Then tell Yeon-woo to leave too.
He's not your son anyway.
No.
Yeon-woo is my son.
-He's my son.
-You...
You're just the same.
Mom...
Please leave.
I won't.
I won't leave.
I'll stay here until I die!
Please stop it!
[But at that moment,]
[I saw my true face.]
[My old and dark face.]
Hello.
[If he were to disappear,]
[the world in the snow globe]
[would stay beautiful forever.]
[My other face whispered it to me.]
[Just like that, an innocent boy]
[died.]
Eun-soo.
Oh, no. What do I do?
Yeon-woo.
It's okay.
Take your time and take slow breaths.
Take your time.
One more time. Slowly.
There you go. Slowly.
That's it. Breathe slowly.
There you go. One more time.
Take your time.
There you go.
Yeon-woo calmed down now. Tell me.
What happened?
Joon-young fell
by accident. No.
I think I killed him.
Leave it to me.
I...
will save you.
[If you think it's okay, it becomes okay.]
[If you think nothing happened,
it becomes nothing.]
[I prayed hundreds of times,]
[but it was no use.]
[My dark, worn-out face
is disgusting, evil,]
[and even bloody.]
[The room where I exchanged my sin]
[with an innocent child.]
I'll do the rest.
Just remember.
That you're Yeon-woo's mom.
[The sin that can't be forgiven,]
[which makes me not worthy of redemption.]
[And...]
[My true face.]
[That I can't reveal
even at the last moment.]
[I hope]
[you burn]
[my true face that I faked.]
Calm down.
Soo-hyun, calm down.
Let go of me!
Baek Soo-hyun!
That night, I had my son's body in my car.
Joon-young's dead body.
I was the one who took him to the place
where he was kidnapped!
Stop.
How? How could it happen?
Yeon-woo is here. Stop!
What do you mean?
Yeon-woo.
Yeon-woo, what I said is...
Let's stay outside until Dad calms down.
May I continue, sir?
Oh, yes, please.
Can you tell me the reason why
you decided to turn yourself in?
The reason.
[There are things you have to forget]
and things you shouldn't.
Don't confuse the two.
Yeon-woo.
He says nothing.
He doesn't talk
and acts like he doesn't know.
Just like how I always lived my life.
I can't do this anymore.
If you give up like this now,
you will lose Yeon-woo again.
Is that okay?
I already lost everything, Father.
No. Not for me.
You and Yeon-woo are still the same to me.
If you fall,
I can't endure it, Eun-soo.
I'm sorry, Father.
I always was.
Mr. Prosecutor.
It's the first day.
Let's finish the first investigation now.
I'm too tired.
Okay.
[We found your daughter.
The situation isn't good.]
Why?
How is Eun-soo?
Hurry up and transfer her
to a different hospital
without the police and the hospital
knowing.
Did you do it?
Yes. It was me.
Where is Eun-soo?
Why do you ask me that?
Eun-soo. I asked where she is.
You will never find out.
Why? Do you think it's unfair?
Then you should've not pulled off the mask
to see what's under it.
You should've not acted like a hypocrite
who wanted to find the truth.
While you were turning the world
upside down to find the truth,
what do you think my Eun-soo did?
While you were shagging another woman,
when her child appeared
in front of Eun-soo,
what do you think Eun-soo did?
Your best? Atonement?
Your selfishness
that only cared about yourself
is the cause of all this!
I will find her.
-I will find her and...
-You'll find her?
Then what?
Answer me.
I'm going to find out the truth,
the whole truth.
You?
How dare you! Do you think
you have the right to do that?
You're going to find out the truth?
Okay. Then how about this?
Your father didn't go missing.
He was murdered.
Even at this moment,
you're going to keep lying to me?
Your mother kept her mouth shut
all her life
so she could protect you.
That can't be.
See?
This is who you really are.
You've lived your entire life
not knowing anything at all.
So from now on,
don't do anything.
Do not look for Eun-soo
so that she can continue living
inside her never-ending dream.
As for Yeon-woo, send him to me.
I'll tell him everything
when the time is right.
You deserve to stay in the dark
for the rest of your life.
Do you understand?
[You will never know.]
[Okay, I'll try.]
What is it?
No, it's nothing.
[Your best? Atonement?]
[You only care about yourself.
Your selfishness]
[got us in this mess.]
Don't be ill. That's all I ask for.
I'll try harder.
Stop making me look like a fool.
How much more will you hide from me?
To Yeon-woo.
That's where I belong.
[You've lived your entire life
not knowing anything at all.]
I don't want you
to get hurt anymore.
I came to talk to you about something,
but I'm not sure anymore.
[You deserve to stay in the dark
for the rest of your life.]
[Do you understand?]
So your departure is today?
Yes.
Just forget
what happened that night.
I think you should go home.
Make sure you keep your mouth shut.
Don't worry.
I don't want to get involved anyway.
Gosh, we should...
It's too late.
But he's still alive.
Pull yourself together, Jung-wook!
You won't remember anything
tomorrow anyway.
It's okay.
So don't do anything.
That's the only way we can live.
Okay?
Your job is done.
I'll take care of the rest.
-No.
-Go home now
unless you want to see me dead, okay?
Forget everything.
Bury it deep inside you.
And just keep going.
That is the only way
to never lose what's yours.
[Police]
[VIP Patient: Seo Ki-tae]
[Despite the ongoing criticism]
[about the law always turning a blind eye]
[to the rich's unlawful acts and crimes,]
[Chairman Seo Ki-tae]
[has been given
a stay of execution of arrest.]
Whose car did they scrap?
It was the car Seo Jung-wook drove
on a regular basis.
Did you take care of Soo-hyun's car?
Yes, sir.
Bae Kyung-sook, that darn little...
Looks like we need
to shuffle our priorities.
For now, forget about the original file
and Yoon Dong-pil.
[I kidnapped and killed
Baek Soo-hyun's son]
[due to my misjudgment.]
[Wait and see.]
[You will die lonely]
[in the kingdom
that you built for yourself.]
Even the day my son died,
[Defendant, Defense Counsel]
I was busy thinking about myself.
[Choi Nam-gyu]
I haven't looked directly at myself,
and therefore,
I wasn't able to look
directly at my son's death.
[Defendant, Defendant's Counsel]
Or maybe I was scared
of mourning his death,
because that would be
admitting my sin.
I admit
all the charges against me
without making any excuse.
[Court in Session, Court 416]
-Slow down. We might get in an accident.
-Let go of me.
Hey, I'll drive. Pull over.
I said, pull over.
What's going on?
A blackout, obviously.
Hey! In front of you!
Was that a person or a dog?
A person.
It was a person.
[Court in Session, Court 416]
Gosh.
You went there
while your wife was being interrogated?
Don't you have patience?
I need to warm up before going back.
The by-election is just around the corner.
You don't know anything.
Hey, I'm the most famous candidate
at the moment.
I was even wrongfully imprisoned,
which can be a perfect campaign method.
What do you know?
Right.
-What about the court?
-I'm not going there.
And I'm going to be
the next Chairwoman of the foundation.
So you used that card?
Everyone has a secret.
Which is not a bad thing,
unless it's revealed.
Gosh.
You're always so well-prepared.
You creep me out sometimes.
Hey.
What is it?
A present from me. Open it.
My gosh! What are you doing?
Are you surprised?
I told you. It's not bad to have a secret
unless it's revealed.
Don't forget that we're a team.
You little...
[Blue House]
The President said the following
at the beginning of his speech.
[Hey, it's me.]
Just do what you've been doing.
[Open the door
of the Blue House and walk in.]
[Let's see what happens from there.]
The President also made a comment
regarding the upcoming election,
that the Blue House and the government
must remain politically neutral.
Thank you.
[Mild Soju]
Enough, please.
You called me because you know
you can't control yourself.
Stay out of my business, sir.
You shouldn't do this anymore.
[Special Investigation Unit]
I didn't know you were religious.
I thought I might be able
to find the answer here.
What's
your question?
I thought I was lost,
but it turned out
I've never even started walking.
Where have I been standing until now?
Eun-soo.
You found her, right?
I thought
I should tell you first.
I heard she's brain-dead.
That's where the hospital is.
About your question earlier...
Don't wait for too long
for the answer.
Soo-hyun.
Where are you going?
Where should I be going?
[The Road: The Tragedy of One]
Where's Mom?
I'll read it later.
[Thank you for watching
The Road: The Tragedy of One.]