[English subtitles are available]
[Ji Jin-hee]
[Yoon Se-ah]
[Kim Hye-eun]
[This program includes virtual
and indirect advertisements.]
[The Road: The Tragedy of One]
[All characters, groups,
and events are fictional.]
[It's been 37 days since
the Royal The Hill Abduction happened.]
[Forensic police]
[The entire nation criticized
the police’s poor investigation.]
[Then last month on the 11th,]
[Documentary Director Oh, who was
one of the key suspects, was murdered.]
[The case seemed to become
more and more of a mystery.]
What?
[But the evidence found
on the crime scene proved]
[that Director Oh was the culprit
of the Royal The Hill Abduction case]
[and the murderer of Reporter Park.]
[The evidence was the weapon he used.]
["For Eun-ho"]
[Written by Oh Jang-ho]
[He planned it all for one day,]
[A charity event
will take place on May 1.]
[which was the day of
Royal The Hill's charity event.]
[May 1]
[Sponsored by
Jaekang Foundation of Culture]
[Resume, Name: Lee Hyeok-su]
[Using a fake ID,]
[he applied for the service company
that was supposed to host the event.]
[That's how he broke in.]
Seok-hoon.
[For Eun-ho]
No way.
[What's even more shocking is]
[the evidence found in his notebook
and laptop,]
[which are wiretapping records,]
[plans for the abduction,]
[and multiple record files of himself]
[practicing the abduction.]
["For Eun-ho"]
[His excessive obsession
with the miniature artist, Ms. Seo,]
[This story is not about an abduction.
It's about a man's love.]
[the sense of guilt he got
from abandoning his own child for money,]
[his distorted paternal love,]
[and his wrong belief
that he could make a new family]
[caused this disaster.]
[But then something unexpected happened,]
[In-Depth Report
of Royal The Hill Abduction]
which made this incident
a complete tragedy.
The culprit kidnapped the wrong boy
and
even killed him.
Someone suspected Oh
before the police did.
It's the former anchor of News Night,
Baek Soo-hyun.
He was not only related to Oh,
but also involved with him
regarding a lawsuit,
an assault case, and even a family issue.
That's probably
[why Baek chose to break into Oh's place]
[instead of asking
for the police' cooperation.]
[Disregarding his work ethic,]
[he collected evidence illegally]
[and got into a scuffle with Oh.]
[When the police arrived,]
[Oh, the suspect, was already dead]
[and Baek was unconscious.]
Let's make a call now.
Yes, sir.
[On the day of the incident,
Oh's house was technically a locked room.]
[According to the surveillance
camera footage,]
[the two were the only ones
who entered the place.]
[Then Baek's fingerprints were found
on the weapon.]
[A month ago,
he said he'd make a dangerous media.]
[It turns out
he became a dangerous person himself.]
[At the moment, Baek is booked
without physical detention.]
[He insists he was unfit
due to short-term memory loss,]
[denying all the allegations.]
[As everything seems to fall into place,]
[the police disclosed the progress
of the investigation to the press,]
[even though the case
hasn't been closed yet.]
[The police also have expressed their will
to solve the case as soon as possible.]
[Oh Jang-ho of River Pictures,
suicide or murder, Baek Soo-hyun]
You know YouTubers, the press,
[Reporter Park Sung-hwan
of "What's Up News" died.]
and even the people are
making fun of the police now.
This is the commissioner's order.
Wrap up the Baek Soo-hyun case first.
Make sure to investigate
everything thoroughly.
Understand?
We have fair suspicions,
but we don't have hard evidence.
Was there anyone else caught by the camera
other than Baek Soo-hyun?
Well, there are some blind spots, so...
Except for Oh Jang-ho, Park Sung-hwan,
and Baek Soo-hyun's,
were there anyone else's
fingerprints or bloodstains found?
He's got no solid motive for murder.
It'd be hard for us in court
if we just wrap up like this.
Baek Soo-hyun suspected his wife
when he cheated on her himself.
Then he found out
Oh was the kidnapper
and accidentally killed him.
Isn't that hard evidence?
If we conclude that some rumor
from the internet is the motive,
everyone will laugh at us.
You should've gotten a confession
from him when he was arrested.
Next time you investigate him,
please make sure to end this for good.
Stop messing with a finished case
and wrap it up as soon as possible.
That's the only way we can survive.
Do you understand?
-Yes, sir.
[News Night Secret File]
[Police Files on Oh Jang-ho's Death Case]
[Shim Seok-hoon]
[Baek Soo-hyun]
[Oh Jang-ho killed himself.]
I didn't kill him.
I only fell into a trap.
[Evidence Bag]
Your fingerprints are all over it.
Next. This is the same knife
Oh Jang-ho used
to kill Park Sung-hwan.
Isn't that why you used this knife
to kill him?
I fell into a trap Oh Jang-ho set for me.
I didn't kill him.
Let me tell you what the police think.
You
stabbed Oh Jang-ho with that knife.
He hit you while fighting back,
and you blacked out.
Then you forgot everything.
We found your belongings at the scene.
[Baek Soo-hyun]
Its general side-effect is insomnia.
Its rare side-effects
are hallucinations
and fragmentation of memories.
You must know better.
No.
No, it can't be.
How much of it did you take?
[You've gotten out of control.]
[Shim Seok-hoon:
You need to be questioned further.]
[We'll also need to question you
under hypnosis.]
[Call Records]
[River Pictures Oh Jang-ho's Death]
[But you saw the scene yourself.]
No one tried to escape or called for help.
I know.
But as of now,
the person with the strongest motive
to kill him is you.
-And you've tried to before.
-But that was...
Oh Jang-ho wants to punish me.
He wants everyone to believe
that I'm a murderer
so that I'll be tormented.
That's how far he planned all this.
Why does he want to punish you?
Because you took Yeon-woo?
Or is it because of Eun-soo?
She has nothing to do with this.
Whatever the reason,
neither of those is
a good enough reason to punish you.
What is it?
Is there something I don't know?
You're hiding something from me even now.
I told you.
Each time you keep silent, someone dies.
How long will you do this for?
For how long?
Still, it wasn't me.
I didn't kill Oh Jang-ho.
[Oh Jang-ho's phone]
[Oh Jang-ho's call records]
You didn't go for dinner?
Are you still wondering
if he killed himself?
Who would go that far to kill oneself?
Well, I'm not saying
it's definitely suicide.
There was only one stab wound.
Before he died of excessive bleeding,
he had enough time and energy to escape.
But there was no blood on the door handle,
which means he didn't even try to escape.
He could've been in shock.
[Oh Jang-ho's phone]
He didn't even call for help.
[Receiver: Lee Mi-do]
Other than the text he sent Lee Mi-do,
there's no call record.
But still, look at it.
They are all evidence
of abduction and murders.
I bet he couldn't put it away
because it happened suddenly.
Besides, Baek Soo-hyun isn't even a cop.
What would drive him to kill himself?
He has no reason to.
Keep a close eye on Lee Mi-do.
But we got her statement
the day Oh Jang-ho died.
She might know about the accomplice.
The accomplice?
[Mi-do, you must've suffered a lot.]
[I'm sorry for being like this.]
I'm sorry, Jang-ho.
I had to
protect our baby.
I'm sorry.
The accomplice is
[the one who stood on the basement stairs
on the day of the abduction.]
[The one who moved the body
into Baek's car.]
[Also, right before Oh Jang-ho
attacked me in my car,]
[Unknown]
[the person who texted him a photo.]
Whether Oh Jang-ho was killed
or killed himself,
we must find out who the accomplice is.
That's only when we can close the case.
Would Lee Mi-do tell the truth now?
She might
tell the truth now.
Do as I said.
Okay, sir.
[Seoul Nambu Police Station]
I told you not to come in person again.
So how are things among the police?
They're trying to
close the case fast
as per the commissioner's order.
I guess it had to go this far.
He should've let some things slide,
that fool.
The problem is that Baek Soo-hyun
has the original file.
No.
If we cannot eliminate the weakness,
then we should get rid of the one
who knows the weakness.
Yes, sir.
Send it off well.
Also, Mr. Choi will be dealt with
next week.
[NQ Investment]
I told you that you won't
suffer any consequences.
Chairman Seo will send over
a new CEO next weekend.
The financial problems
will be solved by then as well.
Yes.
I'll see you when all of this is over.
Okay.
[CEO Choi Nam-gyu]
[Here's the draft
of the memorial ceremony video.]
[Tell us before noon tomorrow
if you wish to make any changes.]
[Hello, this is Cha Seo-young from BSN.]
I heard you usually make documentaries.
Can I have the director's number?
[Director Oh Jang-ho of River Pictures]
I can't reach Mr. Oh.
Can I have another number?
You're making that face again.
Did I?
I worry about you. You know that, right?
I do.
You're the only one who worries about me.
And how can you act like this?
Why do you look more dispirited each day
when you got this far?
Our ratings are higher
than any other show.
They're even higher
than when Soo-hyun was here.
We've never been this high.
After Joon-young died
and until we caught the culprit,
you stayed here and delivered the news.
I admire you for that.
So,
shouldn't we do something as well?
Everyone is doing it.
We should do it as well.
Are you telling me to do
that Oh Jang-ho special?
The real victims are here.
Isn't it weird not to do it?
Oh Jang-ho's appearance, his story,
everyone in the country
is pitying that murderer,
which is driving me crazy.
And you want me to make them
sympathize with him even more?
You know someone else has to do it
even if you don't do it, right?
Act like a professional
especially in times like this.
I'm running out of patience
waiting for you.
I arranged a meeting.
Do some warm-up for that.
[Notice of Disciplinary Action]
[Baek Soo-hyun, suspended for damaging
the reputation of the company.]
I mean they have to make him attend
the disciplinary committee at least...
to judge the reason.
Did everyone eat
a gold nugget or something?
This isn't good.
According to the guys
at the police office,
Soo-hyun will be reinvestigated.
They're torturing us inside and outside.
I'll keep following them.
Yes, please do so.
He doesn't answer my calls...
and doesn't respond when I visit him.
What are you going to do with the meeting?
The meeting.
Darn it.
[For Eun-ho]
[Identification Card]
These are all the internal files
we got from the police.
Okay.
-Anything new?
-Oh, yes.
To track Oh Jang-ho,
I tracked Mr. Baek's location.
Mr. Baek?
Several days before Oh Jang-ho died,
he stopped by a hotel.
A hotel? He did?
Hey, isn't it too much?
Why would you track the victim's location?
Are we yellow journalism?
Keep going.
Gosh.
It seems his car had been there
since the day before.
Many people saw him visiting the hotel
to bring his car back.
It's the video from the informant.
He got the car on Saturday, May 8.
The car had been at the hotel
since the day before.
What's strange...
is Mr. Baek didn't visit the hotel
that day.
By that day...
May 7?
It's Seo Eun-soo's car.
After parting at the cafe,
she went up to the hotel room?
I missed you.
[I said to have patience!]
[Don't push me away.]
It makes me want to keep checking.
[Those two...]
[They had an affair.]
[For a long time.]
[Did you feel guilty?]
Then you should've told me
not to tell him.
That's what friends do.
What is there to keep it a secret?
I know you act all innocent,
but dirty on the inside.
You're at a disadvantage.
[She never denied her relationship...]
[with Oh Jang-ho.]
Jae-yeol.
Yes.
Let's talk just the two of us.
She's the last person to suspect.
Eun-soo was desperately searching
for Yeon-woo that day.
How can you say that?
Is that so?
Did you see it yourself?
Did you call her?
What's the matter with you?
I know it's hard for you.
But this isn't right.
Isn't it strange?
Oh Jang-ho's house was filled
with Seo Eun-soo,
his madness, and obsession.
But there isn't a single line
saying Seo Eun-soo.
-What?
-If he was a stalker that obsessive,
there would've been a letter
or a journal talking about her at least.
But there was nothing.
There should be at least something
he scribbled with anger.
What are you talking about?
That's...
Think about evidence of crime.
It's all organized.
As if it's telling us not to look at
anything else as he's the criminal.
What do you want to say?
The situation is the same.
As if
the strategy to hide something else
worked perfectly.
So what you're saying is...
Oh Jang-ho did that
to hide the affair with Eun-soo?
What if he was trying to hide
not only the affair,
but also her crime?
Are you...
The kidnap wasn't a mistake.
Seo Eun-soo.
She's an accomplice.
You went too far.
It doesn't make sense.
I should ask her myself.
Yes.
That would be better.
Hey, where are you going?
Why did you come?
My family and Yeon-woo.
Do you still want to torture us?
May 7.
Did you enjoy the secret rendezvous
you had at the hotel
after parting with me?
You're not denying it again.
What are you doing?
On the day my Joon-young died,
what did you do?
Did you meet Oh Jang-ho?
Joon-young caught you two shagging, right?
That's why you killed my baby.
-Cha Seo-young.
-If not,
why did Soo-hyun
try to kidnap Oh Jang-ho and kill him?
Why did he go into that house
and suffer like that?
That day...
Jang-ho tried to kidnap Yeon-woo.
Jang-ho?
If you two didn't plan it together,
what did you do in the meantime?
What were you doing
when your boyfriend killed my baby?
It's not what you think.
He's not my boyfriend!
If not,
what did you jerks do?
Tell me right now!
Yeon...
Yeon-woo.
-Go.
-Where are you going?
-Go to your room.
Where do you think you're going?
You can see.
Are your memories back as well?
You saw something that day.
Your biological dad? Your mom?
What are you doing?
Just say something!
If you saw anything,
please tell me, Yeon-woo!
[-Yes.]
[-Okay.]
Is it you? Soo-hyun's son?
See you again.
Have fun.
Why didn't you tell him that you're not?
Where are you going?
Hey, where are you going?
Yeon-woo!
When did you
get your vision back?
Is there
anything you remember?
I can't tell
whether they're just dreams or reality.
My head hurts. I want to sleep.
Okay. Get some sleep.
[Medical Certificate]
[TVC]
Is this Reporter Namgung Hyuk?
My name is Seo Eun-soo.
I got your number
from Director Jo Moon-do.
What about the other charges?
They already have the culprit,
so what is the prosecution waiting for?
-What is it?
-The hit-and-run charge.
There was a car accident.
But I told you. It wasn't a hit-and-run.
I kindly dropped him off at his home.
Hey! I am paying you
to prove these things!
Bae Kyung-sook hasn't withdrawn
her statement yet.
Does she still claim
that I picked up Kim Seok-pil's body?
Jeez, that stubborn woman.
-What about Mr. Choi?
-Forget about him.
He's even stepped down as CEO.
The evidence of his embezzlement
is useless now.
He must've struck a deal
with Chairman Seo.
Darn it.
It's time for you to use your cards.
It'd be simpler that way.
They have the culprit,
so why would I give myself away?
Worry about yourself.
Bae Kyung-sook sued you
for bribery and embezzlement.
Get that sorted out first.
The investigation will go on for a while.
The case might even go to trial.
But then again, it might end soon.
I bet you have something up your sleeve.
A card that I don't know about.
Right?
Looks like it's something
that can save me.
The agreement on the additional shares.
You signed it, right?
Yes.
According to Lawyer Kim,
it's already legally effective.
Good.
-What about Choi Se-ra?
-Choi Se-ra?
I don't know.
My friends say
she's leaving the country soon.
So you haven't heard from her again?
No additional requests from her?
No. Nothing, really.
She hasn't asked for anything more?
That's unlike her.
I think
you should go home.
Make sure you keep your mouth shut.
Don't worry.
I don't want to get involved anyway.
Keep an eye on her
until she leaves
so she doesn't get up to anything.
[Seo Jung-wook, This account is private.]
[Seo Jung-wook]
What do you want?
Hey, why are you still in Korea?
-What about you?
-Me?
I'm in Gongju now.
What's gotten into you?
Why are you visiting your mom so often?
[Trying to be a good son now?]
Hey, you'd better not be
plotting something.
The same goes for you.
Don't or you'll die.
Worry about yourself.
Okay?
[News Night Team Confidential Document]
[Royal The Hill Resident List]
[Royal The Hill Suspects]
[Call Transcriptions]
[4 calls between Baek and kidnapper]
[Do as I say from now on.]
[Cryptocurrency worth 2.5 billion won,
500 million in cash]
[Where is the money?]
[Oh Jang-ho,
June 17, 1981 - May 11, 2021]
[Oh Jang-ho]
What brings you here?
I have a few questions for you.
Will you cooperate?
[Oh Jang-ho:
It must've been so hard for you.]
[I'm sorry for everything, Mi-do.]
Why do you think Oh Jang-ho
sent you this text message
right before his death?
I don't know.
Perhaps
he found out the truth about me.
After getting this text,
did you think he was going to confess?
That's why you became anxious
and contacted his accomplice.
What do you mean?
What accomplice?
Oh Jang-ho's death
may have been a suicide.
The accomplice you're talking about...
Could it have been
for that person?
Do you have someone in mind?
Someone who was just as desperate
as he was, I suppose.
In a situation like this,
most people would ask me
why I think he took his own life.
But right now,
you look like you saw it coming.
The real reason you met
with Director Jo at the hotel.
Did Chairman Seo order you
to spy on Oh Jang-ho?
So you approached him
pretending to be blind
and reported everything to Chairman Seo.
Enough. I have no reason
to be interrogated like this.
The things you saw with your eyes.
Just tell me what you saw.
Whenever I was with Jang-ho,
my eyes were closed.
I didn't see anything.
[Jaekang Group]
You can't just be standing here.
Lee Mi-do says hi.
[Oh Jang-ho was a dangerous man then.]
Especially to Ms. Seo and Yeon-woo.
You may be right.
Maybe it wasn't just a coincidence
that Lee Mi-do approached Oh Jang-ho.
But that Lee Mi-do
fell in love with Oh Jang-ho
and conceived his baby was a coincidence.
It shouldn't have happened.
Why do you want
the case to be closed soon?
Didn't you put Baek Soo-hyun
into Oh Jang-ho's home?
Why are you getting in our way now?
The Chairman asked me
to deliver this message to you.
"I want you to keep"
"the promise you made."
What's all this?
Did you forget?
We're having a memorial service
for Joon-young tonight.
These are what we need for the service.
Cancel it.
I can't do it.
We've postponed it so many times.
We can't cancel it now.
I need to know the truth.
I can't do anything until then.
The truth?
The accomplice.
It's not your job to find that out.
It's the police's job.
At first,
I thought it might be Seo Eun-soo.
But now...
Everyone is suspicious.
They all know something
about Joon-young's death.
Everyone has
a piece of the puzzle in their hands.
Why did you lie
about Congressman Hwang's testimony?
You met him that day.
That's why you gave me the photo.
Does it have something to do
with Choi Se-ra?
-Does it?
-Are you suspecting me now?
Where did you put the things
that were here?
The files and everything.
I threw them away.
You threw them away?
Where?
How could you throw them away?
Please!
Everything is going your way.
The case almost wrapping up,
so please
let's just not make a big deal out of it.
Let me breathe.
You're just running away until the end!
You're going to regret this.
I'll let you cancel the memorial service,
but don't do anything else
that you'll regret.
[Special Investigation Unit]
This is from Financial Crime
Investigation Unit.
They handed this in too late.
I know it's meaningless now, but...
It's about Joon-young's father, right?
Yes, they were already investigating him.
That might be the reason
why they handed it to us late.
They shared only a part of it though.
Why were they investigating him?
I think they're suspecting
his master funds.
They're making unreasonably high profits.
I think even the internal audit department
was keeping an eye on it.
Even a bank was involved,
but they still found it suspicious.
[NQ Investment's Master Fund,
Financial Crime Investigation Unit]
I see. Thanks.
No problem, sir.
[Rate of Return
of NQ Investment's Master Fund]
[List of NQ Investment's Transfers
to Netherlands ANG Bank]
Captain wants you to let
the Office of Public Information know
as soon as Baek's case reopens.
Ignore it.
Disclosing it to the press
won't do us any good.
Yes, sir.
What about Joon-young's father?
I think he had a problem
regarding his company funds.
[Royal The Hill Abduction,
Seoul Nambu Police Station]
[CFO: A detective called
Shim Seok-hoon visited.]
[He asked about the fund,
2.5 billion won.]
It is expected
that people in their 20s and 30s
will decide the result of the election,
and all parties are paying keen attention
to their movement.
[BSN News Night]
[The murdered child is suspected
to have been neglected and abused.]
[Today, we're covering
the hidden sides of the abduction case.]
[Anchor Cha Seo-young
Suspected of Child Abuse]
[Exclusive on TBC.]
[Anchor Cha Seo-young
Suspected of Child Abuse]
Hey, have some manners, will you?
[Director Kwon Yeo-jin]
You're supposed to give us a heads-up
before you break a scoop like this.
Hey, Kim Tae-sik.
I'll consider this as war.
Give me an alternative.
Otherwise, it will be your face
all over the news tomorrow.
Do you understand?
[Cha Seo-young]
[-The person you've reached is not...]
-Darn it.
[Good work, everyone.]
[Trending Search Words,
1. Cha Seo-young]
[2. Cha Seo-young son abuse,
3. Cha Seo-young mental illness,]
[4. News Night Cha Seo-young,
5. Royal The Hill Abduction,]
[6. Cha Seo-young's medical record,
7. Choi Joon-young's cause of death,]
[8. Cha Seo-young's son]
We need to talk.
-Later.
-Now!
[No smoking]
What a scene, right? Get back to work!
Let me ask you something. Is that true?
That's not important.
Cha Seo-young, get a grip.
Nothing is more important than this.
They're clouding the issue.
What are you talking about?
Oh Jang-ho's house.
Did it make sense to you?
He didn't destroy
any evidence that could play against him
right after the abduction.
Do you understand
why he left it like that?
It was like a gallery
rather than a secret room.
Like he was crying for people to look.
The spot Joon-young was found
was like that too.
It was a place
that was easy to spot.
Let's say you're right.
What does that have to do
with your issue from the news?
Joon-young.
Kim Seok-pil, Park Sung-hwan,
Seo Jung-wook, Bae Kyung-sook,
Hwang Tae-seop, Oh Jang-ho.
Soo-hyun also.
Don't you think they're moving in circles?
As if they're trapped in a circle
someone created?
Tell me, Director Kwon.
You got out of it.
You're being too sensitive.
I'm sorry for saying this, but this case
is a combination of tragic coincidences.
-You know that too.
-What if...
Someone created them to hide something?
If you're going to talk about
the original file like Baek Soo-hyun...
No, that's not it.
Something else.
But don't forget
that I'm Seo Ki-tae's daughter.
I can get your and Joon-young's
medical record
anytime I want.
Just like how
Oh Jang-ho displayed the evidence
to hide all traces of Seo Eun-soo,
they're using me to cover her tracks again
this time.
What were you doing
when your boyfriend was killing my son?
It's not what you think.
We're not like that!
You can see.
Just wait and see.
I'll make Seo Eun-soo
tell the truth herself.
[Cha Seo-young Suspected
of Long-term Child Abuse]
You started it.
Back then
and even now.
[Cha Seo-young]
[Cha Seo-young: I know a secret
that will destroy your lives.]
[Unless you want me to]
[speak in front of Yeon-woo,
meet me alone.]
[Seo Eun-soo]
[Meet me at my workroom.]
I couldn't get his psychiatry records.
They demanded a warrant,
so we're waiting for one.
The hypnosis was useless too.
-What?
-Nothing, sir.
Darn it.
Yeongsan.
You said you dealt with it
the best you could.
Do you still think
you did the right thing?
Kim Hyun-seo.
The girl your father killed.
You knew everything,
but you destroyed her body
and the evidence.
Then you kept silent, just like now.
This is the answer to my effort.
Tell Dong-pil that I kept my promise.
Dong-pil
was falsely accused
because he was seeing Hyun-seo.
He was released for lack of evidence,
but he was branded as a murderer.
If you had told the truth,
Dong-pil wouldn't have had to
leave his hometown,
and maybe,
he'd still be alive.
What you wanted to find in that house,
was it really evidence of abduction?
The evidence of Oh Jang-ho
and Eun-soo's affair.
-Wasn't that what you were after?
-Stop the nonsense.
He stalked her. Eun-soo wasn't involved.
Then cooperate with us
if you don't want her to get involved.
Tell me.
Why did Oh Jang-ho torment you?
Do you want to see another victim?
If you don't, then talk to me!
What do you mean by another victim?
I found the accomplice.
[The person you have reached
is not available.]
-Speak.
[-I'll change the location.]
Come to the rooftop of Life Building
in Hanseo-dong.
I'll get to find out everything there.
Don't worry.
It's because there's something
only you can tell me.
You want to help me as well, right?
Excuse me.
Where is Yeon-woo?
He went to consultation
and didn't come back yet.
Do you want me to call the chauffeur?
[Seo Eun-soo]
This is Shim Seok-hoon.
[I'm sorry. It's an emergency.]
[Soo-hyun is in the middle
of an investigation, isn't he?]
[Can I talk to him?]
Hold on.
Take it. It's Eun-soo.
What's the matter, honey?
[Yeon-woo...]
[He disappeared.]
-Where are you?
[-Honey.]
[Yeon-woo...]
What do you mean he disappeared?
[I think it's Seo-young.
She said she wants to know the truth.]
[About that day.]
Where are you now?
-What's the matter?
-Yeon-woo got kidnapped.
Sir.
-Follow Baek Soo-hyun.
-How about you?
What are you doing? Follow him!
Are you cold?
A little.
I can see
but I can't remember.
I'm serious.
I know that you're lying.
If you won't say it, your mom will.
Ma'am...
Yeon-woo. It's late,
but thank you
for the balloon in our garden
and the letter for Joon-young.
You're welcome.
Because I've done many wrong things,
I think I was scared
to think about Joon-young.
But I want to know now.
About why Joon-young had to die like that.
Do you understand me?
Mom.
Yeon-woo.
Yeon-woo did nothing wrong.
Please don't do this.
Don't come close. I won't do anything.
Seo-young, please.
Answer me over there.
What happened that day?
Okay.
Just send Yeon-woo to me.
Not before you tell me the truth.
I was never loved.
Soo-hyun
was always looking somewhere far.
One day, Jang-ho appeared in my life.
At first,
I thought he was seeing dead Eun-ho in me.
I pitied the guy
who lost both his wife and child.
So? Is that why you cheated on him?
And you wanted to hide it?
Our relationship isn't like that.
You're misunderstanding.
He loved me one-sidedly
to the point that it made me sick.
It was a burden to me,
but I saw myself in him.
Because he looked like me
looking at Soo-hyun.
I pitied him. I sympathized with him.
That's all.
Maybe
when things were hard for me,
I took advantage of his feelings.
You know that too.
Answer my question right now.
Ms. Cha, it hurts.
Why did Oh Jang-ho
who was crazy for you kill my son?
Why did my son have to die like that?
You know why.
Tell me
as it is.
Hold on.
Wear this so we can judge the situation.
You might be very worried about Yeon-woo,
but please just listen and stall for now.
Everyone will be here in five minutes.
You shouldn't provoke her until then.
That's what Detective Shim told me to say.
Wait.
We're entering the helipad.
Dad.
Release Yeon-woo.
If I don't have Yeon-woo,
you guys will try to fool me again.
I can't let that happen.
I know why Joon-young died.
Please promise me
you will let Yeon-woo go.
No.
You tell me first.
Even now when I took your son
to such a high place,
you're staying silent.
Will you speak if another dies?
No!
It's because of me.
I'm the cause of all of this.
Oh Jang-ho wanted to punish me.
He kidnapped Yeon-woo to punish me
and things went wrong. Then...
he killed Joon-young.
Eun-soo and Yeon-woo have nothing
to do with it. So please.
Why did Oh Jang-ho want to punish you?
Say it!
I'll give you a signal later.
Okay.
How's the situation?
[Cha Seo-young is asking Baek Soo-hyun]
to say the truth
about the day of the incident.
How about the rescue team?
[They're getting ready
but need more time.]
Connect to the scene.
[Tell me right now.]
Joon-young...
What about him?
Go on.
Keep talking.
Talk!
Because Joon-young is my son.
Jang-ho found out
that Joon-young was my son.
Stop! Yeon-woo is listening!
So what?
What did he do when he found out?
When he found out
that he kidnapped the wrong kid,
he probably remembered that.
I'm guessing that's why he killed him.
And the accomplice?
Then who was the accomplice?
That's...
Yeon-woo!
Don't you dare.
Yeon-woo didn't do anything wrong.
Please stop!
My son didn't do anything wrong either!
Ms. Cha...
I'm scared.
Dad, Mom!
I know that you don't want
to hurt Yeon-woo.
So please.
Stay away.
I've warned you.
Yeon-woo.
Mom.
[This is Detective Shim Seok-hoon.]
[I'll tell you what you want to know.]
[Here's what we know
about the accomplice so far.]
[The day of the incident,]
[the kidnapper asked for 2.5 billion won
in cryptocurrency.]
[Send cryptocurrency
worth 2.5 billion won.]
Cryptocurrency worth 2.5 billion won
and 500 million won in cash.
And 500 million won in cash.
[List of NQ Investment's Transfers
to Netherlands ANG Bank]
[Then on May 2,
the day after the incident,]
[Ms. Cha's husband wired]
[a total of 2.5 billion won
to an offshore account.]
Where did you put the things
that were here? The files and everything.
I threw them away.
Please, let's just not
make a big deal out of it.
[Then the next day, May 3,]
[he withdrew 130 million won
from his domestic account.]
I believe he gave the money
[to Congressman Hwang
to stop the blackmailing.]
[Hwang Tae-seop: Wire the money by
tomorrow. Answer this if you read this.]
Chairman Seo is scarier than prison.
Ms. Cha, it was all done by your husband.
[His company has been struggling
financially for two years.]
[He started spending the company funds,]
[and he got caught by two people.]
One of them was
Congressman Hwang Tae-seop,
and the other one was Oh Jang-ho.
No.
No way.
That can't be.
[Your husband was
in desperate need of money.]
[However, it wasn't only about money.]
Oh Jang-ho told your husband
the truth about Joon-young.
The secret behind Joon-young's birth.
I am Joon-young's biological father.
So what you wanted to hide...
It was this?
All this time?
Atonement?
Is this how you atone for your sins?
No!
You are just
committing another sin.
Do you realize that?
That was the biggest motive for him
to get involved in this.
[Reset SD card]
[The two people]
[who wanted to see Baek Soo-hyun suffer,
joined forces.]
No, that can't be.
[I knew you had no sense of guilt.]
Why do I have to feel guilty
when I'm not the killer?
Do you know what I did
after Joon-young died?
[Even at the moment he was dying...]
I...
[I'm sorry.]
I'm sorry.
I could've just revealed everything
from the beginning and give up.
What kind of son was Joon-young?
I can't do this anymore.
Please...
It has to be Oh Jang-ho and Seo Eun-soo.
Seo Eun-soo.
It has to be you.
Seo-young.
[The person you should punish...]
Is me.
I am...
the other person who is responsible
for Joon-young's death.
No.
That can't be.
-It's all a lie!
-Yeon-woo.
-Dad.
-Dad...
-Are you all right?
It's okay. Don't cry.
[The Road: The Tragedy of One]
[Baek Soo-hyun is now done for.]
I'm going to make everyone
point their fingers at him.
Dad, please.
[I need a witness.]
I'm not ready to fall yet.
Why are you doing all this?
[Only after losing everything,
I finally learned]
[that all I had was a handful of sand.]
[I didn't care what kind of person
you were and what kind of life]
[Divorce by Mutual Consent]
you had led, but...
[From now on, don't do anything.]
Do not look for Eun-soo.