No one can crush my curiosity and passion.
My curiosity never dies!
The customer should be here soon.
SEVENTH BOOK:
THE GIRL WHO WROTE LONELINESS
What's all this?
DELICIOUS FOOD FOR THE SOUL
- Hello.
- Oh, what?
Who are you?
PARK SANG-YOUNG, NOVELIST
I'm here to sell a book.
- - You're here to sell a book?
- Yes, I am.
Hold on!
- - It's you, right?
- Sorry?
That novel!
You're a great author!
- - Well, I guess.
- Oh, my goodness.
Come take a seat.
- - Right here?
- Yes.
You're an author, aren't you?
- - Yes, I am an author.
- Right? I knew it.
Let me introduce this place.
This is the cutest neighborhood
in the world,
Kangho-dong.
Here, I read people like books.
This is Hodong's Bookshop. Welcome.
Yes. It's nice to meet you.
- - You look familiar.
- Right.
You were on a lot of TV shows, right?
That's right.
- - Yes.
- I was
on five shows as a regular cast member.
- - As a regular cast member?
- Yes.
But surprisingly, no one recognizes me.
- - Considering the frequency of exposure?
- Yes.
Even though I've been on a lot of shows
on most broadcast channels...
- - No one recognizes you?
- No.
You're such a famous author, though.
When I take a look at you,
you don't look like an author.
Right, you would never guess I write.
It surprises a lot of people.
- - Are you sure we've never met before?
- It does feel familiar.
I hope you don't mind me saying this,
but I kind of feel
like I'm looking into a mirror.
- - There's something familiar about you.
- Right.
Your demeanor feels very familiar.
I see it all the time.
The way your lips are pursed,
the way you move, and so on.
Now, let's get into it.
What's your name?
- - My name is Park Sang-young.
- Right.
And your pen name?
- - I don't have one. I use my real name.
- I see.
I wanted to make my name
known to the world.
That desire to seek attention motivated me
- - It did?
- to use my own name.
Who gave you your name?
My uncle...
HESITATING
...sought a guru similar to you.
That's where he got it.
HOCRATES WAS ONCE THE KNEE-DROP GURU
He paid handsomely for it.
- - A guru similar to me?
- Yes.
Someone from your previous profession.
- - Your eyes disappear when you smile.
- Yes.
- - People like us
have to smile,
- - That's right.
- or we look scary.
- - People think I'm angry.
- Right.
- - Even when I'm calm and happy,
people ask me if I'm feeling all right.
- - You just weren't smiling.
- Right.
I just wasn't smiling. That's all.
Did you practice your smile in the mirror
to look likable?
- - I never practiced. I was born with it.
- I see.
- - You know what?
- What?
I hope you don't mind me saying this,
but you're either born cute or not.
You're right. I couldn't agree more.
Pursed lips like ours
can't be learned or performed.
- - What are "pursed lips"?
- Pursed lips.
Pursed lips.
It's your specialty.
You've been doing it for 30 years.
You have to be born with that.
GOODNESS
Could you tell me
what your best-known work is?
My best-known work?
It's called Love in the Big City.
Many people remember it
by Kim Go-eun's smile in the film poster.
I'm the author who wrote the novel
that the film is based on.
It was also adapted as a TV series.
I wrote the script for that myself.
A BESTSELLER THAT SOLD 150,000 COPIES!
BOOKS THAT SELL OVER 10,000 COPIES
ARE CONSIDERED BESTSELLERS
IT WAS SO POPULAR THAT IT RECEIVED
FILM AND SERIES ADAPTATIONS!
I think I'm in love.
A NOVEL ABOUT HOW YOUTH IN THE BIG CITY
Are you seriously talking about "love"?
It's all because of dopamine.
LOVE IN MANY DIFFERENT FORMS
Instead of worrying about those things,
I'm going to do everything I can.
SANG-YOUNG'S SPECIAL STORY ABOUT LOVE
I thought it was foolish
RECEIVED SCREEN ADAPTATIONS
to believe
AND CAPTIVATED READERS ALL OVER THE WORLD
there'd be everlasting love.
Even though you're together,
it doesn't feel that way.
You watched both, right?
I watched them carefully multiple times.
So, the film versus the series.
Which did you like more?
I liked the series more.
Because I wrote it.
THE AUTHOR HAS NO HESITATION IN CHOOSING
Was Kim Go-eun's acting
- - not good enough?
- That's not what I meant.
- - Why didn't you like the film?
- No, it's not that.
- - I loved the film.
- Okay.
I really enjoyed it. I mean it.
When I saw Go-eun on the screen,
she was portraying Jae-hee
exactly as I imagined her.
It's like she came right out of my spine.
- - Really?
- Yes.
I seriously got the chills.
- - Are you watching, Go-eun? I love you.
- Then...
HE THOUGHT THE GUEST WOULD BE MORE SERIOUS
SINCE HE'S A NOVELIST
You don't hesitate.
I love her. I really love Go-eun.
But in spite of that,
because it's queer literature,
in terms of depicting queer experiences,
it was done a bit better
in the series adaptation.
THE SERIES WAS CLOSER TO THE ORIGINAL
Please brag about the awards you won.
- - The awards?
- Yes.
- - You have many.
- I debuted in 2016.
I was in my late twenties.
- - There's a publisher called Munhakdongne.
- Yes.
It's one of the biggest in Korea.
- - Right.
- Yes, I won
their New Author Award that year.
- - Right, I see.
- I debuted through that.
I also won the Grand Prize
of the Young Author Award
and the Sin Dong-yup Prize for Literature.
I was also on the 9 o'clock news once.
I wondered what it was for.
ONE OF THE WORLD'S TOP 3 LITERARY AWARDS
It was for the International Booker Prize,
- - which I didn't win,
- I see.
- - but I received a nomination in 2022.
- You were nominated.
Yes, Love in the Big City
was nominated for it.
The Booker Prize is hosted in the UK.
- - Yes.
- It's highly prestigious.
It wasn't international before, was it?
No, the international prize
was created recently.
- - Right, I heard.
- The first winner after the change
- - was Han Kang.
- Right.
She won with The Vegetarian.
I recall it wasn't long since the
International Booker Prize was announced.
When I was nominated for that,
it felt amazing.
Even after that,
there was the Dublin Literary Award
and the Prix Médicis.
I was nominated
for those European literary awards.
So, many people have been reading my work.
- - I feel awkward saying it.
- It's okay.
- - You need to promote yourself.
- Yes.
Is the Booker Prize your favorite?
- - Actually, to be honest,
- Yes?
I think my life
can be divided into two parts.
It's after I won
Munhakdongne's New Author Award
and before I won it.
Before that, I was someone
who just wrote by myself.
But after that,
- - I was recognized as an author.
- Yes.
- - You were officially recognized.
- So nothing could compare to
the joy of winning that award.
Personally, I have a favorite award.
The Grand Prize you won?
- - No, not that.
- Okay.
When I work hard,
the viewers give me
- - the "Always Award." That's my favorite.
- I see.
I hope you keep winning it.
- - Always?
- Always.
- - I always want to be loved.
- I see.
- - I enjoyed reading the book,
- Yes.
- - and I loved the film and the series.
But I didn't like your essay.
- - It made me sad.
- Why?
It was called
I Better Not Eat Before Bed Tonight.
Well, it's hard to fall asleep
on an empty stomach.
I couldn't agree more.
I completely agree.
I can't sleep at night.
- - I like to say "FBSE."
- Right.
- - "Full Belly, Sleep Easy."
- Yes.
It's true. No sleeping pill
is more effective than a food coma.
When you eat a lot of carbs and lie down,
it makes you feel peaceful and relaxed
in a way no sleeping pill can.
- - We're not encouraging this.
- Of course.
I even wrote a book called
I Better Not Eat Before Bed Tonight.
READ TO SEE IF HE DID DO AS THE TITLE SAYS
- - Of course, I don't encourage it.
- Yes.
So, you're a well-known author.
When you have a new book out,
do you go to the bookshop
to see if it's doing well?
I'd like to know.
- - A lot of people would be curious.
- Right.
I think most authors
go and check at least once.
Somewhere like Kyobo Book Center
in Gwaghwamun.
- - Rightfully so.
- Right?
It's not even blood, sweat, and tears
that go into it.
- - It's blood and pus.
- Exactly.
There's pain like you're squeezing out pus
- - Right.
- behind every sentence.
You're absolutely right.
Some people lose teeth while writing.
When Kim Hoon
was writing Song of the Sword,
he spat out a molar into the trash can
after he wrote the fourth chapter.
He was so worn out that a tooth fell out.
He probably had gum problems already.
I'm sure he'd been suffering before that.
But writing is also that hard.
It's hard work writing
and publishing a book.
He literally gave it his all.
He was clenching his teeth
from trying so hard
that a tooth fell out.
- - I think so.
- He was bleeding.
- Yes.
- - That's how a work of art is born.
- Right.
- - That's why you'd want to know
- Yes.
- - if people like it
- - or if it's being overlooked.
- That's true.
- - Of course, I'd like to know.
- Right.
So, you're at the bookshop
and you don't like
where your book is placed.
Have you ever taken it
and put it where more people will see it?
Sneakily and subtly.
Honestly, I have.
WE HAD A FEELING HE'D SAY THAT
I don't do that these days.
I did when I was younger.
- - Anyone would want to.
- Yes.
The books that are
on what we call the display table
are the selected few
among many, many other books.
Most books get put
in the new arrivals section
and then the shelves
before they disappear.
This all happens
within a couple of months.
This even happens to books by
authors who've been around for decades.
For example, I'd take it from the shelf
and put it on the table.
I'd drop it in the bestsellers section.
I wouldn't put it there,
but I'd just drop it there.
Just nudge it a little.
I don't know if that helped
or if the bookshop employee
reorganized it right away.
So, if you decided to write,
- - you must have first liked to read.
- Yes.
What's your favorite book?
- - My favorite book?
- Your favorite.
I have too many to choose from.
But I just happened to bring them today.
Wait a second.
- - This is what I'm picking up today.
- Yes?
You have a lot to say,
a lot of favorite books...
I have a lot of everything.
A lot of fat, problems, and things to say.
- - Hair, too.
- I have a lot of hair.
I'd show you if I could.
I will when we have a chance.
- - The book--
- What chance?
I'm not sure.
There might be a chance at some point.
- - You don't have to.
- Okay.
All right, then.
You don't have to show me.
Goodness. I didn't mean it, anyway.
Do you want to do ssireum,
traditional Korean wrestling, with me?
Oh, I wouldn't dare.
You don't want to kill anyone, do you?
That'd be brutal.
I'll do it with you some other time.
No, you don't have to.
No, thank you.
THEY'LL BE FINE WITHOUT IT
My middle school had a ssireum team.
- - I just remembered.
- Really?
Why didn't anyone ask you to join?
What made you think that?
Of course, they asked.
HA HA
Also, in college, the rugby team
really wanted me.
You'd be great on TV shows.
I told you, I was on five!
HA HA
HE KEEPS BEING RUDE TO HIS GUEST
I already told you about that.
Can I please take my book out?
You're so funny.
- - Here are my favorite books.
- So funny.
It was hard,
but I narrowed it down to these three.
First, Shin Kyung-sook's novel,
The Girl Who Wrote Loneliness.
- - Right.
- This book
is about a girl
who moves from Jeongeup to Seoul
in the '60s to '70s
and attends a work-study program.
She works in a factory during the day
and goes to night school to study.
- - That's what it's about.
- That sounds exhausting.
That's right.
She's so young.
She's only in middle school.
It explores the inner world
and the beauty of the teenage girl.
The next one is A Very Old Joke.
You know Park Wan-suh, right?
- Yes.
- Yes, who wouldn't?
This is by Park Wan-suh,
the author of our generation.
It's about a man who has an affair
with a rich former classmate.
What a bold theme.
Yes, I love this book.
- - I love these kinds of stories.
- I see.
So, I brought this.
And the last one
is by Agatha Christie.
She's a very well-known
English mystery novelist.
I read all 80 of Agatha Christie's books,
and this one's my favorite.
It's called Crooked House.
- I see.
- Yes.
People keep getting murdered
- in this family.
- Right.
So the girl, who's the main character
and the narrator,
tracks down who the murderer is.
Among all of Agatha Christie's books,
- - That's right.
- this one's your favorite.
I think it's the essence of her work.
I, Hocrates, the man who asks,
will start asking questions
about Park Sang-young's life.
The first chapter
of Park Sang-young's life.
Crooked House.
"I made that story up."
"I don't believe that."
"But it's true."
"I sometimes make up stories. It's fun."
FROM CROOKED HOUSE
Since you were a kid,
have you liked to come up with stories?
I loved it.
It was like this.
When my parents' friends would come over,
they'd always talk to me.
They liked the way I talked.
- - They did?
- They thought I was fun to listen to.
And I was also a good listener.
So they liked talking to me.
When I'd go to after-school classes,
the teachers said I talked like an adult.
- - I got that a lot.
- I see.
I think that shows
that I've had this talent or personality
ever since I was a kid.
So, this full-length novel
made young Sang-young
- - like books?
- Yes.
I first read Agatha Christie's books...
Do you remember
the Asian financial crisis?
- - Of course.
- Yes.
It's a big event that affected
- - most Korean citizens
- Yes.
around 1997 and 1998.
- - I was in elementary school at the time.
- Right.
You know those asset seizure stickers?
I was home alone one day
when I heard the doorbell
and opened the door.
Then, people in suits came in
without taking their shoes off.
More than a dozen of them came in
and put those stickers everywhere.
I was only a pre-teen.
Imagine how scary that was.
- - Were you alone?
- Yes.
So, I called my mom.
She came home from work
and started crying.
She said, "I'm sorry you had to see that."
That's when I felt how bad it was.
After that, they asked
my dad's friend's family to babysit me.
They lived in the same apartment complex
as we did.
- - I see.
- They had a lot of daughters.
There were three girls
who were in middle school and high school.
- - And the youngest had a bookshelf.
- I see.
The bookshelf had
the complete works of Agatha Christie.
I started reading them,
and they were so good.
My world before those books
was limited to world literature
adapted for kids and teens.
- - Books like that.
- Right.
It was a somewhat sanitized world.
But in Agatha Christie's world,
there was adultery, passionate affairs,
murder, crime, and violence all over.
They were so shocking
and stimulating to me.
Those books were so thrilling.
Reading books
became fun to me.
In just a few months, I read all 80 books.
You were only around ten.
- - It would depend on the child,
- Yes.
but it must've been lonely
to be by yourself.
Also, you must not have liked
being at someone else's place.
My mom was also worried,
and other adults
were concerned about that, too.
But to be honest,
my mom didn't let me watch TV,
but that place had everything I wanted.
- - I could watch you on TV.
- Right.
I could watch Lee So-ra's Propose.
They also had an audio player,
so I could listen to new songs by H.O.T.
and S.E.S., too.
That place was like
an amusement park to me.
Did you like K-pop idols?
I loved them. I still do.
I've liked K-pop idols
for almost 20 years now.
Who did you like first?
I'm sure everyone loved them.
It was S.E.S.
The first album I ever bought in my life
was the first album by S.E.S.
That's when it all started.
So, you've never stopped
being a fan since then?
Yes. I started liking
other groups as well,
but it has never stopped.
Who else do you like?
To list the ones
that I've been really into,
there was TWICE.
I absolutely loved them.
I voted during
their first reality survival show.
I picked those members myself.
FANS WOULD OFTEN SAY
"I RAISED THOSE MEMBERS"
And fast forward to now,
I've been into TWS.
You know, "Plot Twist."
SUDDENLY SHOWING THE MOVES
And "OVERDRIVE."
- - You also like boy groups?
- I do.
I like them equally.
IMAGES HE PROVIDED
Both girl and boy groups.
I love them.
My friends say
I like groups that end with an "S" sound.
S.E.S, TWICE, and TWS.
- - They end with an "S" sound.
- They do.
TWS is from PLEDIS Entertainment.
- - That's right. You know their company?
- PLEDIS.
That's four S's.
You're right!
PLEDIS: TWS'S AGENCY
I'm friends with the founder.
Oh, with Mr. Han Sung-soo?
HOCRATES KNOWS EVERYONE
Could you tell him that I love TWS?
I couldn't get tickets to their fan event.
- - Oh, no!
- I'm so sad about that.
You even know the founder's name.
Trust me, every fan does.
- - They do?
- I know all of them.
Lee Soo-man, Park Jin-young,
Han Sung-soo...
How could I not know them?
Of course, I know them.
Would you like to say something to him?
To Mr. Han Sung-soo?
- - Not to TWS, but to Mr. Han Sung-soo?
- Yes.
Mr. Han.
He's the one who made TWS
into the great group it is today.
That's right. Sir, you have a great eye.
Please, do your best.
Fans have a lot of complaints.
We hope you'll work harder.
WE HOPE THE MESSAGE REACHES HIM
All right.
Sure, you can like books.
You can like books,
but writing
is a different matter, isn't it?
When did you discover your talent?
I wasn't trying to,
but every time
there was a writing contest at school,
I'd win first prize without even trying.
Wasn't it like that for you?
Didn't you just somehow start ssireum?
- - All the chubby kids did it back then.
- I see.
But still,
you were widely recognized,
even if it was for your build.
- - Right.
- I was the same.
I didn't know I was a talented writer,
but I kept getting recognition.
Everyone told me I was a good writer
and that I was well-spoken.
In storytelling contests
or debate competitions,
I won all the prizes.
You weren't trying that hard,
but you won contests.
I never tried my very hardest.
I'd have to say
that was a matter of talent.
Was that too obnoxious?
That wasn't my intent.
No, it's okay.
You're just being honest.
I'm not good at anything but that.
Let's move on to the second chapter
of Park Sang-young's life.
- - The Girl Who Wrote Loneliness.
- Okay.
"Writing.
The reason why I'm so attached to writing
is probably that I think
this is the only way
I can get away from feeling
like I don't matter."
FROM THE GIRL WHO WROTE LONELINESS
Could you explain?
- - I think it's pretty straightforward.
- Right.
She's a teenage girl who suddenly ends up
in the unfamiliar city of Seoul.
- - The book is about her loneliness.
- Yes.
The thing that gave meaning
to her life was writing.
That's what the section is talking about.
Because I'm also an author,
that phrase really spoke to me.
How did this book
influence you as an author?
THE INFLUENCE OF
THE GIRL WHO WROTE LONELINESS
Because of the situations
that I mentioned before,
I lived in Daegu
until I graduated high school.
- - Yes.
- During that time,
I was very frustrated.
I wanted to be free.
I wanted to break free.
That's why,
when I was applying to college,
I applied to every single university
in the city of Seoul.
So, I had to go take the tests.
But there was a problem.
The train tickets
from Daegu to Seoul were expensive.
I had to get round-trip tickets.
I applied to ten universities,
which means the tickets
would cost a million won in total.
My mom thought it made no sense.
Trains, accommodation,
and application fees are no joke.
So she came up with the idea
of me staying in Seoul
and coming back
after I've taken all the tests.
So I stayed with my cousin
in his boarding house room.
I stayed in that room in Seoul
over the summer break.
I was there by myself,
taking essay tests and entry exams.
I couldn't talk to anyone,
so I was lonely.
I read this book in that situation,
and every phrase
describing the girl's loneliness
and sense of isolation
resonated with me.
It brought me great comfort.
It felt like someone else
was voicing for me
the loneliness
that I couldn't put into words.
It felt like someone
had entered my heart and then left.
So naturally, I started thinking,
"If an author is someone
who can affect other people's lives
so deeply,
it'd be meaningful
to devote my life to being one."
I thought it could be a noble thing
for the first time in my life.
After I read
The Girl Who Wrote Loneliness,
I genuinely started considering
becoming an author.
It motivated me.
I want to ask you something.
Listening to your family and colleagues
cheering you on during hard times...
You don't find comfort in it at the time.
But reading sad novels
gives you courage, comfort,
and the power to get back up.
Why do you think this happens?
- - Well...
- Isn't it a bit selfish?
It is,
but novels are a selfish genre.
And humans are naturally selfish,
if you think about it.
That's why I think
it's natural
that reading can do that for you.
That just means you read it right.
After enduring that period,
- - you finally went on to college.
- Yes.
Did you major in creative writing
or Korean language and literature?
- - I wanted to major in either of those.
- Yes.
But I ended up majoring
in French language and literature.
- - French?
- Yes.
I know a bit of French. Oh mon Dieu!
Bonjour! Avez-vous mangé?
What's that? Avez-vous mangé?
It's "Have you eaten?"
Avez-vous mangé?
How good is your French?
I can't even read store signs.
I gave up on the French language.
I focused on the literature part instead.
I kind of neglected my studies,
- - but I double-majored in journalism,
- I see.
and attended academies
because I really wanted to write.
I kept writing stories in secret
and submitted them
to different literary contests.
That's how I grew
my dream of becoming an author.
But actually, being a full-time author
comes with a lot of difficulties, right?
- - Yes, a lot of difficulties.
- Right.
Getting a book published
isn't as important
as getting people to read it.
I wanted to write for a living,
so I started working for a magazine.
- - You started working.
- Yes.
- - That's the reality.
- Of course.
As I mentioned before,
my family wasn't wealthy.
I had student loans.
It was an apprenticeship.
- - There was a mentor-mentee culture.
- I see.
The mentor trained interns on the job,
and I was an intern reporter.
I was bullied at work, so to speak.
Getting coffee for the seniors
was a given at the time.
But aside from that, there were also
personal attacks and insults.
I was born in 1988.
One of the interns was also born in 1988.
We must've been
around 25 or 26 at the time.
The seniors were
watching us work and said,
"Was there a nuclear accident in 1988?
These kids are the worst."
Something like that.
I thought that was harsh,
but I also found it funny.
It went like that every day.
I came to work at 9 a.m.
and left at 11 p.m.
I worked every weekend.
But I only earned
around 1.08 million won
per month after taxes.
After paying rent and so on,
I would be left with nothing.
So those were difficult times.
What was hardest for me
was that I started working there to write,
but I was only copying the press releases.
- - Right.
- That was my job.
I had stories inside of me
that I wanted to tell
using my own language.
But all I was doing
was writing for someone else.
That wasn't the direction I wanted to go.
It wasn't the life I wanted.
I had a strong feeling that it wasn't.
That's why I thought,
"Screw it, I'm still in my twenties.
I'm already in debt.
What's a little more?"
I went to creative writing grad school
to write whatever I wanted.
That's what I decided to do.
So you quit your job?
Yes, I just left,
went to grad school,
and started writing.
I wrote a twelve-page short story
every week.
In my first semester,
I submitted one to a writing contest
and made it to the finals.
I came in second.
You're often one of the finalists.
That's my specialty.
AUTHOR WHO ALWAYS GETS NOMINATED
"Your specialty."
It's quite a shame,
but do often end up
being one of the finalists.
Don't be like that.
Hold on. I'll tell you why it's true.
I made it to second place on my first try.
I thought if I tried a couple more times,
I would win first place.
So I made an ultimatum.
I thought, if I couldn't
become an author in two years,
I'd give up completely
and try to make a living
- - doing whatever I could.
- Right.
May I add something?
I was training as an athlete
at a similar point in time,
and I think
that's the period that drives you crazy,
- - when it's just out of reach.
- Exactly.
- - If there's no chance of winning, fine.
- Right.
But if you reach the finals and lose...
- - It's maddening.
- You can't even quit.
In those two years,
I kept submitting to contests
and counted the times.
It was 50 times.
Almost every time,
I lost in the final round.
In the final round?
Not every time,
but I made it to the finals so many times.
You really are a finalist,
through and through.
That's what I really was.
I still remember the names of the authors
who beat me and won.
Even after over a decade,
I can still give you ten names.
Park Seo-lyeon, Jung Young-su, Kim Mella,
Yang Seon-hyeong, and so on.
I heard this story from your perspective,
but I bet the judges
couldn't believe it either.
I'm sure of it.
"He was just eliminated.
Did he submit again?"
It was really like that.
"Did you submit the same story
in a different contest?"
AN URBAN LEGEND AMONG WRITING CONTESTS
Then, my two years were up.
After I graduated,
all I had was a debt of 20 million won
and the memory of failing 50 times.
That was all I was left with.
- - You probably wanted to give up.
- Yes.
I really did.
So I started working again.
- - Again?
- Yes, but this time,
I put on a suit
and went to an office.
- - It was just an ordinary company.
- I see.
- - So you gave up on writing.
- Yes.
But every night in bed,
I felt uncomfortable somewhere down there.
I tried to figure out why.
It turns out I couldn't give it up.
I wanted to write.
But I didn't have time because of work.
I thought about it.
If I went to bed
around midnight or 1 a.m.,
I always woke up around 5 a.m.
I'd keep my eyes closed and wait
until the morning before going to work.
I decided to use that.
- - So...
- How?
- - When I woke up at 5 a.m.,
- Yes.
I'd get up, take a shower,
go to the office,
and write at the coffee shop
on the first floor.
If work started at nine,
that means you had three hours.
Yes, I started at six
and wrote until 8:57 a.m.
before I ran up the stairs to work.
I wrote every morning like that
from January to June.
So I wrote for six months
and submitted
to the Munhakdongne contest in June.
On the day the winner would be announced,
I took a day off. I was at Seoul Station.
Okay, why?
My mom was coming to Seoul
- - for her physical examination.
- Okay.
So I was waiting for her
in the McDonald's at Seoul Station.
And I got a call
from a number starting with 031.
When I saw that, I got a feeling.
- - Right.
- I could feel it.
I felt chills on the back of my neck.
So I answered, "Hello?"
They said, "This is Munhakdongne,"
and I knew I got it.
I was so happy that tears came to my eyes.
So, I hung up in a rush,
and then I saw my mom.
She came up from the KTX platforms,
and I yelled,
"Mom, I won the Munhakdongne contest!"
She was freaking out and screaming.
Everyone was looking at us.
We were hugging each other.
We were freaking out together.
She wanted me to tell my dad,
so I called him.
I said, "Dad, I won Munhakdongne!
I'm a professional author now!"
He was screaming, too.
He said he was so happy
because he knew how hard I'd been trying.
Then, he asked me if winning
the Dongnebangne contest was a good thing.
I said, "Dad, Dongnebangne
is a free daily newspaper
you can use to buy secondhand goods.
Munhakdongne is a literary magazine
and publisher."
I had to correct him on that.
- - I heard there was a cash prize.
- Yes.
What did you do with the money?
As I mentioned before,
I had a lot of debt.
Munhakdongne's cash prize
was ten million won.
I wanted to pay off a big chunk of my debt
and eat somewhere nice.
That was the plan.
So, I received the cash prize.
And my mom came back
to hear the results of her physical.
- - Right.
- So,
we were eating beef short rib soup
at a restaurant in Seoul Station.
I was enjoying it,
but my mom kept giving me
all the ribs from her soup.
"That's strange. It's not like her."
That's what I thought.
So I asked, "Mom, why aren't you eating
any of the ribs in your soup?"
"I don't have any molars."
- - That's what she said.
- I see.
She needed dental implants,
so her molars and the bone
surrounding them were removed.
She told me she couldn't chew
- - or eat meat.
- Okay.
At first, I felt bad for her.
But then I thought,
"Then why did she order short rib soup?"
That occurred to me.
I started thinking,
"Why is she telling me this?"
I asked her,
"How much is it going to cost?"
She said, "Seven million won."
After paying the taxes on the cash prize,
the remaining amount
would be 7.5 million won.
So I asked for her bank info
and my cash prize paid for my mom's teeth.
- - For her dental implants.
- Yes.
It was exchanged for two of her molars.
My debt was still the same.
- - The prize paid for your mother's teeth.
- Yes.
She's still using those teeth.
What changed after debuting?
My attitude toward life
completely changed.
- - Did it?
- Yes.
Before that, anything painful or difficult
felt like a natural disaster.
It was something that just happened
without me knowing the reason behind it.
So I had a hard time dealing with it.
But ever since I became
a professional author,
everything that was painful and bad
had a reason.
They become writing materials.
I started thinking they'd help me
become a better author.
So nothing feels scary anymore.
- - It's the same stone,
- That's right.
but one can see it as an obstacle
while another sees it as a stepping stone,
- - That's right.
- even though it's the same stone.
Every stone in the world
became my stepping stone.
- - Your view changed.
- Yes.
My attitude toward the world
completely changed.
- - My life became something different.
- I see.
IN A WAY, I THINK I WAS
PROVING MY EXISTENCE BY WRITING
FREEING MYSELF FROM THINKING
ABOUT DOING OTHERS' WORK TO NO END
AND FEELING THE SENSE
OF USING MY VOICE TO TELL MY STORY
MADE ME ENDURE THE REALITY
OF HAVING TO MAKE MONEY WHILE LOSING SLEEP
FROM I BETTER NOT EAT BEFORE BED TONIGHT
We cannot discuss your life
without discussing Love in the Big City.
Why do you think so many readers
and viewers loved Love in the Big City?
Because it was well-written?
Is it because I wrote it too well?
"THE PROSE IS VIBRANT AND ADDICTIVE"
BOBBY FINGER, NEW YORK TIMES
"A STUNNING DEBUT" PUBLISHERS WEEKLY,
AN AMERICAN MAGAZINE FOR PUBLISHERS
ONE OF THE TOP 10 BESTSELLERS IN FOYLES,
THE UK'S BIGGEST BOOKSHOP CHAIN
LOVE IN THE BIG CITY CAPTURES THE WORLD
TRANSLATED AND PUBLISHED IN 15 COUNTRIES
GETTING CALLS FROM THE WORLD'S BIG CITIES
STOCKHOLM
NEW YORK
MANILA, AND MORE
SHARED WORLDWIDE THROUGH A WORLD TOUR
In my opinion,
I think
how good the work is and how loved it is
are completely different matters.
I think for this novel,
I got lucky in that matter.
If I may say so boldly,
I think our generation
has been waiting for a book like this.
I think our society and generation has.
This book has a very direct queer theme,
which is something that was not discussed
so much in Korean society.
At the time, there had not been
many works of literature
that portrayed love between queer people
in such a universal and ordinary way.
I myself, as a reader,
was unhappy about that
when I was writing this.
"Why are queer people in media
usually portrayed as
having pitiful or miserable lives?
I wanted to see queer people
live their ordinary, everyday lives
in any form of media.
I wanted to see that
in a work of literature.
That's how I first started
writing Love in the Big City.
I had a lot of fun writing it.
I had the confidence that I was
writing a story that the world needed.
Then something amazing happened.
It sold 40,000 copies in just one month.
I made more in a month
than I used to make in a year.
Not me, the publisher, or anyone was ready
- - for this to happen.
- I see.
Even my mom called me and said,
"I saw you on the news on TV Chosun!"
MY SON IS ON THE NEWS!
They offered overseas publication.
Yes, that's true.
Deborah Smith,
who translated Han Kang's book
- - and received the Booker Prize with her,
- Yes.
contacted me and said,
"I think Europeans would like your novel.
Could we sign a deal?
We'd like to do that
before it's published."
I said I'd love that, so it happened.
That's how you got nominated
- - Yes.
- for the Booker Prize.
I couldn't believe it.
- - "What's going on?"
- Yes.
Something I could never have imagined
just happened overnight.
And famous film companies contacted me.
It wasn't just one.
They all told me that they wanted to
make screen adaptations of my book.
This book opened up
a whole new life for me.
All those times
you lost in the final round
gave you the energy and material
for this book to bloom like this.
In the end, this book
also lost in the finals
of the Booker Prize.
But it's enough for me.
I was happy just to be
one of the finalists.
HE DIDN'T WIN BUT BECAME WIDELY KNOWN
You lost 50 times
in national literary contests.
You have to try 50 times
in international contests too.
- - Fifty times?
- Fifty times.
- - Then...
- You have 49 left.
I'll have to do it until I die.
I don't know if I can.
When Han Kang won
the Nobel Prize in Literature,
I was talking to an author I was close to.
We were chatting online.
A lot of people in literature watch the livestream
like it's the Olympic Games.
- - Really? - "Who'll win this year?"
- Really? - "Who'll win this year?"
My friend said, "Is Han Kang a nominee?"
And I said, "We're also nominees."
For the Nobel Prize in Literature,
every author with a publication around the world is eligible.
You're always a nominee.
I've been a nominee for ten years straight.
So I guess I could try 50 times.
No one can confirm it,
but you might've been a finalist for the Nobel Prize in Literature too.
LET'S SAY HE MADE IT TO THE FINALS
LET'S JUST SAY HE DID
Jeez, I was so close!
Those pesky finals!
When will your next book come out?
It's planned to be published in June this year.
The title is The Woman Who Wears the Straw Crown.
I've mainly been writing contemporary love stories until now.
I've been writing
- - about the love of young people. - Right.
- about the love of young people. - Right.
But what started it all for me
was passionate love affairs.
Like the book I mentioned,
I followed in the footsteps of Park Wan-suh
and wrote about a woman born in the '40s as the daughter of a wealthy family
and her revenge, love, death, and crime.
It's a mystery novel.
For the first time, I wrote about a person
unlike me in terms of generation and gender
in the form of a mystery novel.
A passionate and suspenseful mystery crime novel.
- - That's right. - Yes.
- That's right. - Yes.
I'm very nervous about it.
I put effort into it,
so I hope people will like it.
When it comes out, will you send some copies here?
- - Of course. - We'll display it.
- Of course. - We'll display it.
I'll save the best spot.
- - In the center, please. - Yes.
- In the center, please. - Yes.
That would be great.
If not, I might just nudge it a little.
I'll come by and nudge it with my shoulder.
So, tell me.
As a novelist,
why do you think people of our time have to read novels?
I can say it confidently.
You don't have to.
I'm sure your publisher would love to hear that.
This is what I meant.
Times have changed.
In the past, you could only acquire knowledge through text.
But now, there's a wide range of media
from which you can obtain knowledge easily.
Since ancient times, this is the era
where written language is consumed the most.
That's because we communicate through text.
We text each other on our smartphones,
use AI, and so on.
In those ways, we're already consuming texts.
So, it's not entirely necessary
to consume traditional books.
But despite all of that,
there are people who I really think should read books.
Just like how I found comfort in books,
for people who feel like
no one in the world really understands them,
books can be the most effective, easy, and fundamental solution
to that sense of loneliness in my opinion.
If you want to feel like you're not alone,
to know that there are people who perceive the world the same as you do,
to feel that sensation,
there's nothing in the world like novels.
I wrote a TV script, and I love films.
I love all of those,
but novels are the only form of media
that speak to you one-on-one.
So to those people,
the people who feel lonely,
I'd like to recommend novels.
You said it's not necessary,
but after talking to you,
who grew up reading novels,
I think peopler I was close to.
I think people should definitely read novels.
I'd like to say that.
You're too kind.
All right, then.
I said I'd recommend you
- a book today.
- Yes.
What book should I recommend?
Right!
How about this one?
The book I want to recommend to you
is Strange Planet by Nathan Pyle.
HOORAY!
We're so used to this Earth,
but it must be very unique to an alien.
- Yes.
- Sang-young.
You have the power
to view the familiar world
in a special way,
just like the alien from the book.
May you always see the world
from a unique perspective
like you're on a trip to Earth.
I, Hocrates, will be rooting for you.
Thank you.
I haven't read this yet.
It looks like a fun read.
Thank you for coming today.
Are you glad you came?
- Yes, I had so much fun.
- I'm glad.
It was really like
looking at my life story.
What are you going to tell
your fellow authors
about meeting Hocrates?
When you tell them
what I'm like.
"He's so big."
"He's so big.
You guys thought I was big?
Next to him, I'm nothing."
What's the cutest neighborhood
in the world?
- Kangho-dong?
- Yes, Kangho-dong.
This is Hodong's Bookshop.
We heard Park Sang-young's
life story today.
That was a great read!
At last
It's you.
- You do everything well.
- I'm Lee Ja-ram.
KOREA'S TOP PANSORI SINGER
LEE JA-RAM
FROM YE-SOL, THE NATIONAL STAR
Singing came before my first words.
TO BECOMING THE GRANDMASTER OF PANSORI
Can't I tell a more familiar tale?
I'm glad to meet you, you brat
FIRST CONCERT ON HODONG'S BOOKSHOP
WHO IS PARK SANG-YOUNG?
SOMEONE WHO WROTE LONELINESS
AND SET IT DOWN
TO GIVE A WARM EMBRACE
TO EVERY STRANGER IN THE BIG CITY
Subtitle translation by Cayle Kim