[Northeast Stories: The Rising Era]
[Episode 13]
Hongbing.
Someone's looking for you.
Take a seat.
What's up?
Brother.
I'm here to discuss something
with you.
I want to hire your guys.
For business.
Business?
My crew here,
they've all done some things.
No worries, I trust them.
How many people do you need?
How many do you have?
That's a big ask.
You're not just talking, right?
The contract.
[Staff Employment Contract]
Advance salary.
A real business.
That's all of us.
Brother.
Let's talk about something.
Give me some air.
It's way too strong.
Open the window a little bit.
What's the matter, bro?
Everyone's here.
The matter?
Living.
Back then, we just messed around.
But now,
we all need to settle down.
With families to take care of,
want some stability, right?
So now,
here's the thing,
that can settle everyone down.
I just want to know if you're on board.
Sure.
Of course.
You don't sound like an "of course".
Unwilling?
Dajun,
say something.
Bing trusts me,
so I won't waste your time.
I've started a company,
it's called Caiman Express.
We're hiring staff.
If you want the job,
just sign now,
and start tomorrow.
You get a month's pay in advance.
So, we're delivering packages?
Isn't that like pulling a rickshaw?
Bro,
I might lose my face.
You still care about saving face?
You don't even have food at home.
Face?
Here.
Come on.
It's all voluntary, really.
Even Bing said so,
I'll sign.
Right.
I'm signing too.
Alright.
It's all voluntary.
When can I get discharged?
I told you a couple times already.
We're just being responsible for you.
You need a couple more days
of observation.
Still need to observe?
I'm already fine now.
How much is your hospital stay per day?
Around a hundred or so.
What?
Around a hundred?
Can you keep your voice down?
Is this your place?
There are still patients here.
Don't disturb others' rest.
Hurry up and take this out for me.
I'll leave. Give my money back.
You paid for a week.
You can't get a refund if you leave now.
What's with your attitude?
I'm sure it's not as good as yours.
You sell clothes pretty well too.
Look at this quality.
The seams are all coming apart.
You know,
I recognized you
the moment you came in.
Who are you blaming for your weight?
When I bought clothes from you,
did I weigh only sixty?
I was just as chubby back then.
You totally talked me into this.
You said the quality was great.
That it was custom-made for me.
And super stretchy, too.
Now I wear it daily, looks like a Qipao.
Who are you blaming for this?
It's not the clothes, it's on you.
Yeah.
I'm bigger, but I'm healthy.
I'm strong, you know.
So what?
You took the tag off already.
That means I can't refund it.
I won't return it back.
So what?
Anything else you need?
Nope, I'm good.
Take a break.
Remember to get some rest.
This is bullying.
Why am I still so weak?
Don't mess with me.
What happened?
Did you finish up at the company?
We already had some new staff.
Don't worry about it.
Did you pay the hospitalization fee?
Couldn't you just keep the money?
I'm better now,
I'm leaving the hospital.
Go get back the rest of those money.
Oh.
Well.
Let me do the accounts for you.
About your illness,
if you're not fully healed,
won't it cost even more later?
Yeah.
So the hospitalization fee
is no big deal?
Yeah.
Exactly.
That's what I thought before.
But,
after hearing you, it makes sense now.
It's really not necessary.
Don't go.
You've paid anyway.
I can stay more days.
Stay more days?
Yeah.
Alright then.
Let's tuck you in now.
What snacks did you bring?
Sour noodles, good for appetite.
Jichun Trading, pay back the money.
[Pay us back]
Mr. Gao.
Our number of staff expanded sevenfold,
so vehicle costs went up too.
Plus, we added franchise bonuses.
Now the company's cash flow
is starting to have some problems.
We can't pay our suppliers anymore.
How's Caiman Express doing?
It's okay.
Okay.
If it's good, just say it's good.
If it's bad, just say it's bad.
What do you mean by okay?
You usually talk a lot,
why so quiet now?
Caiman Express uses low-cost transport,
and same-day delivery,
so it's got 80% of the market now.
The returns are way higher than before.
They've grown over ten times.
So you're saying I spent all that money,
set up that Feng Shui thing,
and Ma Rulong wasn't hurt,
but actually got stronger, right?
Get out.
[Youku Information Technology (Beijing) Co., Ltd.
holds the global exclusive online distribution and broadcast rights]