=The Long Season 2=
Wait, wait.
You just can't stop vomiting, huh?
You must be sick now.
Feeling any better?
Don't talk such rot.
Do I look like I'm any better?
At... At Sun Guilan's home,
what on earth did you see?
Don't be nosy.
It's an internal affair.
Internal?
Between you and the police?
The police and civilians are a family.
Haven't you heard of it?
Nonsense.
Bed No. 15.
Injection time.
Still in the buttock?
That's what scares me.
No cover?
Who would peep?
You, I'm afraid.
Cover me.
Fine, fine.
You turn around.
Come on.
Did I never see it?
Take off your pants.
Come off the bed, too.
Can't you give the injection like this?
I can't!
You have a muscle tension
and how can I give it?
But I would still be nervous.
Wait... Wait a second.
Let me prepare for it.
Turn around, please.
OK. Thanks.
You must be new.
Done.
What? Don't make such a noise.
Or the new nurse would be angry.
Young guys just suck.
What a manner!
Get me... Get me out of the hospital
so that I'll no longer suffer.
Come on. Be careful.
Raise your leg.
I can't.
My right buttock aches.
You... You do this.
Follow my move.
Take it slow.
Slow, slow.
I... I can't sit.
Wait.
Who gave me the flowers?
And they're white.
Why didn't he just give me a wreath?
Gong Biao.
Who?
The college student who sent you here.
When he came, you were asleep.
He put down the flowers and then left.
Oh, he's a college student.
Then I can understand.
He means I'm as pure as white flowers.
He's a nice young man.
Well-educated and affectionate.
Good.
He's up to something, too.
What are you looking at?
No... Nothing.
I... I came to check on Mr. Wang.
He's in the ward.
How can you find him here?
I came to see if his medicine is ready.
Don't stroll here unless you have to.
Or you would disturb our work.
I'm sorry.
It's also bad if others see you here.
I'm... I'm leaving immediately.
Idiot.
I should go.
Who pulled up my flowers?
(Office Building of Hualin
No. 1 General Steel Works)
Hualin Steel has
a glorious history of 50 years.
It can't be ended in our hands.
The shortage of raw material is temporary.
But if spreading rumors
(Song Yukun)
to disturb the production is a crime.
Yesterday, some workers caused trouble.
Find them.
Punish them accordingly!
I'm not afraid to offend!
I'm not afraid to crush
those troublemakers, you know?
Who are those troublemakers?
I won't mention their names now.
Lay off some workers and redirect some.
Make a list.
And why do we have to do this?
We're suggesting a piece of information
that we must abolish the
lifetime employment and accept change.
Right?
Accepting change is
the best solution for our factory.
We only do what we think is best for it!
As for recent problems,
do you have any thoughts?
Speak up!
Gong.
Mr. Song,
I have something to say.
Our factory has a problem now...
Get me some more water.
If you don't object,
all branches and departments
should submit the layoff list asap.
Mr. Song, as for what you just said,
I have some ideas.
When you have time, may I...?
Mr. Song,
some police officers have come.
Will you go? They're waiting.
Water, water.
Bring your water.
Go make some good tea in the VIP room.
Okay.
I'm Ma Desheng
with the Criminal Police Unit.
I know you.
Director Zhu often talks about you.
You've been keeping order in my factory
these days and I really appreciate it.
Be seated, please.
You know what?
The workers' riot has had
a terrible effect on my factory.
The leaders
has to receive severe penalties!
Even if you didn't come,
I would go talk to Director Zhu.
I didn't come for this.
I want to talk to you
about the dismemberment case.
I had too many meetings a day
that I muddled it.
How about we talk in the VIP room?
No need.
Just a few words.
The dismembered body
was found in your living quarter, right?
Hope you'll cooperate
with our investigation.
I will.
As much as I can.
I've quit.
Go.
He mentioned a driver.
Who's that?
I'll come to get it next week.
OK.
Don't forget to handle mine early.
Thank you.
Liru.
Wang Xiang?
What are you doing out here?
I have something to ask you.
Go ahead.
We're relatives.
I'll help as much as I can.
Something happened in the living quarter
and you must be aware.
I am, you know, a vigilante.
I offered a little bit help
but ended up in hospital.
Now, our factory doesn't have money
or other support.
Then, I don't want
to take advantage of the government.
What do you want exactly?
I want an early discharge.
Could you please check
how much the bill is.
However much it is,
the factory will pay.
I don't think so.
Your cousin has had her stents
for nearly three years
but we haven't got even a penny yet.
Tens of thousands.
With this much money,
we can even afford a Santana.
Right?
Wang Xiang.
Cousin.
Come back for the medicine.
Check the bill for me, please.
It was so rude of you.
She's your cousin.
She's dissolute
and that's not family stuff.
How could you say that
about your cousin?
What?
What's wrong?
Oh, no!
You should have added some cold water.
Don't bother. I swallowed it.
No, come on.
I just asked her to check the bill
so that I would be prepared.
The independent accounting is ongoing.
I don't want to be urged for the bill.
But they still owe me for my stents.
That's a different case.
Our bills can't be mixed.
I'm to blame.
My poor body has wasted all our money.
And Wang Yang can't work in our factory.
Stop, stop.
Don't. Don't.
Don't whine.
If you screw my expensive injection,
I would whine.
Look where we are.
He's up there.
Thanks for your hard work, nurse.
Come on.
Right there.
Hualin Steel's future.
Hope you'll recover soon.
Mr. Song has come.
What did he come for?
It can't be anything good.
This way, please.
Wait, wait.
Mr. Song, there he is.
Mr. Song.
You've gone too far.
This ward.
(Multi-share Ward)
Mr. Wang.
Where's Mr. Wang?
I remember this is his ward.
Mr... Mr. Wang.
Mr...
Here I am, Mr. Song.
My spittoon was full.
I was cleaning it.
Mr. Wang, you've set
a good example for our workers.
Mr. Song, what... what did I do?
The other day, a terrifying murder case
happened in the living quarter
of our factory.
At the crucial moment,
Mr. Wang Xiang rushed out to help.
Yes.
I mainly assisted the police...
Don't interrupt.
Please, Mr. Song.
This shows how responsible and active
our workers can be.
Because of that, he was injured
physically and mentally.
Now, he's still vomiting.
Nervous vomiting, actually.
But once he vomits,
he even spits his gall out.
Mr. Song,
can it be a work-related injury?
He didn't shrink back.
Nor did he regret it.
Here,
I'd like to declare something.
Workers of Hualin Steel are brave.
Don't believe rumors or spread them.
Remember.
Whatever happens,
our factory will be your support!
Mr. Song, my medical bill...
My wife means...
First, solidarity.
Second, stability.
Mr. Song.
He sounds quite reasonable.
The honor came so expectedly.
I wasn't prepared.
Even you weren't prepared...
There you are.
Let alone the scared murderer
who is hiding somewhere secret.
Right.
I didn't see you and I thought
you didn't work today.
I was on duty over there.
Why do you look so tall today?
Wedge-soled shoes, huh?
Mr. Wang Xiang, have a good rest.
Okay.
Hope you'll come back to work
as soon as possible.
Our leader has come here
to see Mr. Wang.
Take this.
I...
You take it. Come on.
My hands are dirty.
Nurse. Nurse.
Take this.
Give them a hand.
But I...
Hurry.
I can't.
Go ahead. Go.
Come on. Hurry.
Here. Take this.
I'm too shy.
Don't let Mr. Song hold it.
Sorry, sorry.
Here.
We're a family.
Sorry.
A nurse is a warrior, too.
Come on, Mr. Reporter.
Take a photo of us.
Move inside.
Stand close.
Okay.
Come on.
But...
Go away.
Look here.
One, two, three, cheese.
(Song Yukun, the factory manager,
paid a caring visit to vigilante Wang Xiang.)
Move over. I'm watching TV.
Come and check if it's straightened.
Just so-so.
Come on.
Walk aside and check it from afar.
OK. It's straightened.
What a huge honor!
In this photo,
Huang Liru's face is even
bigger than yours.
Only half of my face can be seen.
Don't care about such useless stuff.
Why did you compare the faces?
My name here is what really values.
Wang Xiang.
Honor is what we should compare.
Will the murderer see the photo,
and take revenge on you?
Why?
I just told the police
about our living quarter.
If I hadn't, others would have.
I can be recognized, huh?
Yes, almost.
It doesn't scare me, anyway.
Get Wang Yang here to learn his lesson.
He's asleep. Keep your voice down.
These days,
why does he go to bed so early?
Wang Yang.
Come down.
In a second.
(The police should serve the people.)
Some workers offered information.
Take a quick investigation.
Hualin Steel has thousands of workers.
If they make trouble, we can't handle that,
how many officers we have.
As for that information,
we made a preliminary check.
The businessman from Hong Kong
has been providing raw material
for Hualin Steel.
But he hasn't shown up this month.
Sintering and steel-making have stopped.
So, the workers are getting inflamed.
Is it possible
that he decamped with all the money
and is now eloping everywhere
with his mistress?
You know, it's quite common.
You think it's a novel?
Eloping?
Any evidence?
Just guess, huh?
Come on.
What do you say, Captain Ma?
Ma Desheng.
Go on with the meeting.
What's this?
The whole night,
you've been absentminded.
Did you hear what I just said?
I'm trying to think in some other way.
About the dismemberment case
in Hualin Steel.
Today, I checked the missing persons.
These girls
(Registration Form of Missing Persons, Shen Mo)
fit the profile of the dead woman.
Shen Mo isn't back yet?
No. We failed to contact her.
Tell me when she's back.
Your advisor has been worried sick.
Got it.
Can Shen Mo be in trouble?
That's scary.
I can't even fall asleep.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so quiet?
Nothing.
Did you see Shen Mo these days?
No.
We're looking for her.
We haven't seen her for days.
She isn't in her dorm, either.
Can she be in danger?
What are the police doing there?
How do I know?
Did they come for Shen Mo?
What are you talking about?
What do you mean?
I just asked. What's the problem?
(Victoria
International Entertainment Center)
Come.
Your job can be very easy.
Nothing complicated.
Every morning from half past seven
to nine in the morning,
you play the piano
for one and a half hours.
What songs?
It's up to you.
Foreign, elegant, and classy songs.
How can you play the piano?
Not bad.
I can play most songs.
Quite enough.
Do a good job and you'll get tips.
If a guest tips you, take it.
It's yours, then.
Let me show you around.
Within the one and a half hours,
you can't drink water,
go to the toilet, or stop playing.
As for the songs, repeat if necessary.
It doesn't matter,
because nobody really listens.
What we want is the feeling.
I mean, make it classy, you know?
Yes, Mr. Ge.
I get it.
For one night,
I'll try not to repeat the songs.
Think of me as your brother.
Ge.
What are you doing here?
Have you cleaned this room?
Hurry.
Why are you still on the phone?
You'll have to work soon.
Dress yourselves up.
What are you staring at?
Come on in.
Having a job through college
can be a good thing.
But...
Are you really a college student?
School just started.
This is my student ID.
I'm a freshman
at Hualin Health Vocational College.
Student ID isn't convincing.
I can tell it from your face.
Our place is quite upscale.
So, your look...
I mean, how you're dressed...
You...
You should accord with us.
Come over here.
Come on.
Your legs are straight.
Why do you wear pants?
I'm used to pants. Quite handy.
But they don't look pretty.
We offer uniforms.
See?
Continental dresses.
They're gorgeous.
If you wear that dress,
you'll look way better.
Let me take your size.
One hand span.
Two.
Three...
Ge,
I'll measure it myself.
You're too thin.
I'm afraid the dress is too big for you.
Let me take your chest measurement.
See how...
Don't.
Annoyed?
This is an entertainment place.
Without an entertainment spirit,
how could you work?
What...
What can I really do to you?
Sorry, Ge.
Then can I work here?
One pair of aces.
Four of a kind.
Sorry.
Shuffle the cards.
Haven't you been reading
the newspaper the whole morning,
Mr. Wang?
He finally managed
to be in the newspaper.
He has to read it many times.
Is the dead woman one of our workers?
Even the police don't know.
Who else knows?
Deal the cards.
Hello, Locomotive Dept.
Okay.
No raw material.
We can knock off.
Let's go home.
- Don't move.
- Wake up.
- Pay the bills first.
- Time to knock off.
Keep the accounts.
Don't do that.
For some money, people would even kill.
Pay me.
Let me go.
What are you doing?
Behave yourselves.
This is the workplace.
Mr. Wang, how about a rubdown?
No.
I didn't move at all.
Quanli, what did you do last night?
You look so sleepy.
Having a great time with your wife?
Your wife Li Qiaoyun
has gone to the Factory Affairs Office
with some other women.
Don't you get her back?
Stop the sarcasm.
Male workers in our factory can't even be
as brave as a wonderful woman.
I should go.
Why can he be so proud?
When the train doesn't work, he isn't
even as valuable as the coin in my hand.
Could you ever shut up?
Make way!
What's the fuss again?
Too crowded to move.
Stop quarreling.
What's the problem?
Come out. You.
Man, why do you keep yelling?
Put down the stick!
Making trouble, huh?
Beating someone
is a violation of laws, you know?
We don't beat anyone.
We want the list.
What list?
The layoff list.
We've been working for a lifetime.
Why can he fire us as he wishes?
Who would fire you?
All you can do is make trouble.
Didn't you hear?
Your director just explained this.
Your work is suspended
because of the businessman of Hong Kong.
What does it have to do
with the layoff thing?
Don't try to fool us.
We all know Mr. Song's relationship
with that businessman.
Four furnaces are stopped now!
Even the factory may close down!
All right. Stop arguing!
If everyone solved the problem
in his own way, there would be a total mess.
For this solution,
we have to take your leaders back
and get to know what exactly happened.
Go. Take him away.
Don't crowd here.
Clear away.
Stop the fight.
I even sprained my ankle.
Go.
You can't go!
You just can't!
Don't touch me!
- I know you guys.
- You can't leave!
Weight workers, huh?
If there's a layoff list,
you would be the first!
How dare you mess with me!
Let go of me!
Excuse me.
Why are you back?
I told you
that you couldn't get the medicine.
I had the operation two years ago
and I've been taking medicine
from this dispensary.
Why can't I take any today?
I warn you.
If you dare to cut my medicine,
I'm gonna kill myself.
Believe it or not.
Ms. Luo, scaring me won't help.
If you want some medicine,
you need Mr. Song's signature.
Without it, I couldn't give you any.
I don't mean to owe you the money.
But I haven't been paid
for my operation yet.
The factory owes me this.
I don't mean to owe you.
All right.
Understand?
Look.
Enough.
Don't bother to say this.
What?
Isn't this still the hospital
of Hualin Steel?
You know what?
I've devoted my youth to Hualin Steel!
But now,
I can't even afford the medicine!
How could you
(Dispensary)
bully me like this?
How unreasonable you are!
What's the problem, Cousin?
What happened?
Look.
I have the accountant's signature.
So far,
I haven't been paid for my operation yet.
He doesn't even give me the medicine now!
Then my stents wouldn't work!
Calm down.
Come on.
Why must you be so angry?
They're being such a bully, you know?
Your blood pressure may rise later.
Your heart beats so fast.
Wait here.
Just a second.
I feel dizzy.
Zhang, sorry for that.
That's my cousin.
It won't help.
Rules are rules.
I know.
Well, you...
Fine. Just this once.
Thank you.
It's OK.
- Thank you.
- Take it.
Keep it between us.
I know.
Cousin, come on.
Take the medicine.
Later,
let's figure out another solution.
Don't be angry anymore.
You paid for it?
I didn't.
I have a very low wage.
He didn't flirt with you, did he?
What are you talking about?
Don't imagine things.
He sold the medicine on credit.
Next time you come for the medicine,
you have to pay for it.
All right.
Calm down.
Listen, young man.
When you're still young, do good deeds.
Because you also get old someday!
Stop it.
Remember this!
This is the hospital.
Don't shout.
Be careful, Cousin.
Oh.
Still working,
Gong?
Director.
The attendance sheet is almost finished.
I'm going home after it's done.
Song didn't ask for me, huh?
I told him you went to the workshop.
Is everything OK, Director?
Yes.
The health needs a new stamp.
But Li Qiaoyun...
I'll give her a good lesson!
Good, Gong.
I observed it.
Our office has these young guys
and you're the most enterprising.
You'll have a great future.
This is my job.
Later, lock this in the cabinet.
The leader just signed it.
Keep it to yourself.
Don't worry.
I won't read anything
I'm not meant to see.
Never let anyone see it.
I should go.
Then, I'll sign the attendance sheet
on your behalf, OK?
OK.
(The First Layoff List
of Hualin Steel, 1998)
Eat.
Don't just sit there.
I just ate some.
Well, Gong,
you work in the Factory Affairs Office, huh?
That's right.
What's your job?
I usually help Mr. Song
with the management thing.
So, you're a leader, right?
Not really. Just a middle-level cadre.
You're so young and promising.
Gong, umm...
You know, three years ago,
I had a heart surgery
and it cost thousands of bucks.
But so far, it hasn't been claimed.
Tell me.
Who takes care
of this medical bill thing?
It's something about logistics
that I don't usually bother about.
I'll ask Mr. Song about it later.
Umm, well,
when does Mr. Song usually get off work?
If... If I want to stop him,
where should I go?
Mr. Wang called me, I guess.
He did? No.
Excuse me for a second.
Mr. Wang.
Get back to the sitting room.
The smoke is choking.
It's OK.
Let's chat.
Sure.
I love chatting.
Let's do it.
Gong, you're not native, right?
I'm from Shenyang.
See?
You're obviously from a big city.
Shenyang is the economic, cultural,
and political center
of the three provinces in the northeast.
Right.
Are you accustomed to life here?
Yes.
Just starting from the bottom.
That's right.
A real man is always ambitious.
Tonight, I'm gonna
make you some big dishes.
Mr. Wang.
One of the big dishes,
fried pork in scoop.
Go ask around.
Unless at a festival,
who would make such pork for a guest?
The first layoff list has come out.
You're on it.
What?
You're on the layoff list.
Just now, I saw the list in my office.
Me?
Layoff?
You must be joking.
The joke isn't funny.
But the way you say it is funny.
Why would I joke about this?
Mr. Song signed it.
At the workers' assembly next month,
it'll be announced.
Did you clearly see
my name on it, Wang Xiang?
Yes, Wang Xiang.
X-I-A-N-G.
I'm the engine driver
and model worker of 1990.
I'll be laid off?
The pork is burnt.
Mr. Wang.
What's wrong?
Think positively.
I'll go and ask Song Yukun.
Why? Don't go.
Or you would sell me out.
I risked quite a lot
to tell you about this.
Think about it.
The other day, he called on
other workers to learn from me.
But then he'll lay off me.
What can other workers learn?
The layoff thing?
Don't be angry.
In some cases, Mr. Song made sense.
I really admire him.
What did he say?
We should accept change.
Accept it if you wish!
I do a great job as the engine driver.
What change do I have to accept?
Tell me.
Why did you inform me so stealthily?
Did Song Yukun, that rotter,
sent you to tell me in advance?
Who do you think I am?
Can I be that evil?
Speaking of relationships,
you and I must be on the same side.
Who's on the same side?
Tell me the truth.
What are you up to?
Well, let me be frank.
I want you to do me a favor.
Be specific.
I want to get to know Liru.
Closer, I mean.
Closer?
Gong!
Mr. Wang?
What's up?
You want to get closer to Liru.
As her cousin-in-law,
I'm okay with it.
And...
When necessary,
I can bring your messages to her.
I really appreciate it, Mr. Wang.
I should go, then.
Gong, that...
That thing we just talked about.
If...
I mean if...
If I'm really on the list,
under what circumstances
can I be removed from it?
From what?
I mean, from layoff.
You work in the Factory Affairs Office
and you know the rules.
Is there any rescue plan or free pass?
There might be some.
A worker who has made
brilliant contributionsor had an award
from a unit of the city-level
or above the city-level
has to be given
adequate attention and protection.
What do you mean by contributions?
If I catch the murderer of the dismemberment
case, is that a contribution?
What murderer?
His face can't even be seen in the photo.
Did you recognize the right guy?
I can recognize him
even when he's skinned.
After he was hit,
why didn't he dare to call the police?
Have you thought about it?
What about we call the police?
That year, I told the police
all that I could say.
What else can I say now?
Let's catch them, then.
Didn't he kill Xiang's...?
Shut up.
Don't blab.
What is your problem?
I'll shut up, then.
Don't yell.
Xuelu, listen to me.
You text him,
saying the medicine is ready.
Ask him to come to get it.
I'll be waiting here.
Then I'll get him down.
Okay.
Can it really be such a coincidence?
The one who faked my license plate
just hit him?
Catch him and we'll know.
Scared?
Why would I?
I'm gonna skin him, without doubt.
He texted back.
He said he couldn't come now
and asked me to deliver the medicine.
Do it.
Ask him for the address.
OK.
Don't worry about me.
I won't be scared.
If he wants to hurt me,
I'll punch him and that's okay.
What are you doing?
Come on.
Drop this thought.
Why does my eyelid
keep twitching today?
Left or right?
The right one.
Is it an omen of misfortune?
Stick a slip of paper on it.
Which side?
The white side.
To stop it from twitching, huh?
We can't follow her anymore.
Or we would be exposed.
What would you like?
I'd like five skewers of potato.
Not afraid of high blood sugar now?
A little risk
can't stop me from living.
That's how you got diabetes.
Don't eat any, then.
I won't.
Just starch.
Why is she getting in there?
She asked us to get in, too.
Shall we?
Yes!
Heat it for me.
Where's she?
Let's search separately.
What, Biao?
Did she answer it?
She hung up.
Keep searching.
Biao!
Here's a door!
Did he see us?
Where shall we go?
We go separately.
Xuelu!
Hu Xuelu!
How can we find her?
We've got no clue.
Something happened.
Xuelu!
(Emergency Center
First Aid)
Remove it.
What?
The slip on your eyelid.
You asked me to use it.
What the heck!
It didn't work at all.
Did I use the wrong side?
Xuelu!
(Operation Room)
Keep your voice down.
This is the hospital.
Doctor, is that Hu Xuelu?
Yes.
Doctor, can she live now?
It's hard to tell.
Your wife is so badly wounded.
She's not my wife.
Then who's her family?
Come with me
and I have something to tell you.
Well, then...
I... I'll go.
Come on, then.
You wait here.
How did she hit
the high-voltage substation?
I didn't see that.
When I got there, she was wounded.
And who are you?
I'm her friend.
What about her family?
Her parents are exported workers,
in Korea now.
They can't get back very soon.
Be prepared.
For her death?
Who said that?
You need to repay for ICU deposit.
Get the money ready.
Pay it tomorrow.
How much is the deposit?
What did the doctor say?
Biao, don't be too worried.
We don't know if this is an accident.
But the police will figure it out.
Now, I understand.
Whenever you interfere,
everything goes wrong.
To catch the murderer, huh?
What murderer?
If you hadn't wanted this,
Xuelu wouldn't have been hurt.
Biao, you...
How can we explain this to her parents?
She is so young.
She isn't even married yet.
Who would take care of her all her life?
I would.
How could you?
What did the police tell you?
Does the man you described really exist?
No one believes you except me.
I'm such an idiot.
Where... Where are you going?
What else can I do?
Going home.
Let me drive you.
No need.
(Important place of guardianship
Non-staff members out of bounds)
Xuelu.
Xuelu!
What's wrong, Biao?
You don't have the key?
I do.
A little bit suffocating in the room.
I came out for some fresh air.
Fine.
Hello,
Dali.
What have you been up to lately?
Do you have spare money?
When did it happen?
But last year,
your father was still very well.
Hello, Xiaofei.
Where are you?
Are you flush with money lately?
I need some money.
You got divorced with no money?
When?
Then let's have dinner someday.
Hello, Shuang.
Do you...
Do you have Sheng's phone number?
Why can't I get through to him?
He's in prison?
Hello, Hao.
This is Biao.
Gong Biao.
A few days ago,
I bought some pigeons from you.
Can you buy them back?
What?
90% off the price?
You must be kidding!
I would rather boil the pigeons!
You guys keep cooing.
What's the point of that?
Other animals have babies.
But you can't even lay one single egg.
What? You all took contraceptives?
None of these friends
can be counted on.
Gong Biao.
You're home?
I thought you were out.
Where were you last night?
Driving the taxi.
And what about the money?
What money?
You tell me.
Money in the bankbook!
There was more than 100,000 yuan.
But now, only 3,000 yuan!
I didn't get a chance to tell you.
A couple of days ago,
I met a man who sold a taxi license.
The taxi and the license
cost 150,000 yuan in total.
That was quite cheap.
In this city,
no other license can be this cheap.
Some young guys wanted it, too.
I decided to buy it first.
So, I didn't discuss it with you.
What about my beauty salon?
I've paid the rent and deposit.
But I think you can offer
such beauty service at home, after all.
I'll drive the taxi
and save some money this year.
When the license is worth 200,000 yuan,
I'll sell it.
By then,
I can rent a bigger salon for you.
Once for all, isn't it?
Now that you have your own taxi,
whose night shift did you take?
Where's the taxi?
Don't mention it.
Shortly after I had it,
the traffic police detained it.
They said someone faked my license plate
and it's being investigated.
What bad luck!
Biao, you've got a talent.
Really.
You win.
I've been married to you for years,
but I didn't know you could do this.
Do what?
If a competition was held in Hualin
about making up stories,
you would be the champion, seriously.
Why don't you believe me?
It's true.
Ask Wang Xiang if you don't believe it.
Wang Xiang?
He's just like you, you know?
You both tell lies!
I'm done with this.
Liru.
What? Where are you going?
Live with any other woman you want!
What are you doing? Don't...
You're being a terrible bully!
Why are you even crying?
Seriously?
You're breaking my heart.
Do you even have a heart?
Yes, of course.
Listen.
It's beating fast.
Stop crying.
If your eyes are swollen,
the double eyelid operation would be wasted.
Fine.
You still have some money, right?
What?
The other day, you said
you wanted to buy some new machines.
Don't buy them for the moment.
I want the money for some emergency.
Not a chance!
I won't borrow the money.
I won't borrow it, OK?
Go find any other woman you want!
Come on. Don't go.
You sound like
you wouldn't come back anymore.
You're awake?
Would you like something to eat?
I had a nap.
Where are my socks?
I took them off and washed them.
They are as hard as rocks.
Why did you sweat so much?
Had a nightmare?
I didn't sleep very soundly.
Dad, I feel
you're not doing very well lately.
Is anything wrong?
Nonsense.
How can you tell
I'm not feeling very well?
We should go
buy some new clothes for you.
For the interview,
you have to look energetic.
OK.
Oh, this.
Dad,
I made a travel schedule.
When we arrive, we can first visit
the art gallery in the Art Academy.
It's near Huajiadi.
Then we'll visit the
National Art Museum of China on Wusi Street.
And another place...
Here.
But it's a little bit far.
We can take the subway.
Son, I rescheduled the tickets.
What... What tickets?
The train tickets.
I think
we can go there just before the exam.
What do you say?
Just before the exam?
I've got a lot of things to do lately.
Is it OK?
OK.
We can visit those places next time.
Dad, have some porridge.
♪What I'm free to choose every day♪
♪Can be just a little♪
♪When I can love you forever♪
♪Can be just one day♪
♪Then little by little♪
♪Then day by day♪
♪Then year by year♪
♪I've never changed♪
♪This is just an arrangement♪
♪An arrangement♪
(The intellectual property rights
(including copyright) of this production)
(are exclusively owned
by Tencent Penguin Pictures)