(Crushology 101)
(A Good Friend to Meet)
(All places, organizations, characters,)
(incidents, and backstories in this drama are fictitious.)
(Crushology 101)
Let's go hang out somewhere else.
Okay.
Wait for me.
When I was a kid,
I chose a fairy tale book based on...
its cover, whether it had a handsome man.
("The Crybaby Prince")
Getting the light and darkness right is important...
when drawing with a pencil.
Think of the lightest part as the origin.
Follow its path, and it gets darker. Easy, right?
That's when it hit me.
My heart pounds at handsome men,
making me a softie for good looks.
I sublimated this overwhelming sensation...
into art.
With that, I got into the Sculpture Department.
You're unbelievable, Bani.
Exactly.
You have such discerning taste in art.
Your boyfriend must be a looker.
Bani!
The first boyfriend I have chosen is...
(Ko Bong Soo, Yein University, Bani's first-ever boyfriend)
Bong Soo!
Say hi to him. He's my boyfriend.
My name is Ko Bong Soo.
Bani must not care about looks when dating guys.
Right? I guess she only looks at the inner beauty.
(Kwon Bo Bae, Nam Kot Nim)
Don't you go for looks?
Why are you dating him?
Bani!
I like you.
I'm serious.
(I like you.)
I like you!
Isn't it obvious?
He adores me tons.
(Officially started dating)
That's all I need.
Nothing is more important than feelings.
Even so, this doesn't feel all that right.
What can we do about it?
As long as Bani is happy, we should be too.
Hello.
(Episode 1: A Dynamic New Semester)
Fresh air with zero fine dust.
A bright sunny day.
And the refreshing breeze.
Everything is perfect.
But of course, the most perfect thing is...
Bani!
Bong Soo!
My undoubtedly happy love life.
Listen, Bani.
How about a trip this weekend? The weather will be great.
"A trip?" I love going on trips.
When should we go? Saturday or Sunday?
If you want, we can go on Saturday and return on Sunday.
You mean an overnight trip?
Yes. Is it a problem?
Oh, and this.
Ta-da.
What's this? Is it for me?
Yes.
I bought it, thinking it'd look good on you.
Pretty, right?
It's gorgeous!
Hold on. Let me put it on you.
I'm getting nervous.
I'll put it on you.
I'm sorry.
Is that it?
Do you think "I'm sorry" is enough?
- You bumped... - Sorry.
- How dare you... - Bong Soo.
- It still looks new. - But he...
I can tell the pearls are real.
Watch where you're going, okay?
Bong Soo. How do I look?
Pretty, isn't it? I love it.
Right?
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
- Hey. - Hi.
Kot Nim.
Here's your mocha latte.
- Enjoy. - Wait.
You're my ideal type.
For real. You're so pretty.
I see.
But I've got the nastiest personality.
What?
Enjoy your coffee.
Right. Keep up the great work.
Bo Bae. Isn't this really pretty?
Bong Soo has great taste.
It's all right, but not great.
"All right?"
How is this just "all right?"
Why are you so mean when it comes to my boyfriend?
Stop it, will you?
If we're asking questions, let me ask you one.
You have high standards for men.
But why did you ignore your boyfriend's looks?
Is there a need to ask?
- It's because... - Kwon Bo Bae.
What? Why are you here? Weren't you going straight home?
Didn't you say you needed this?
("Understanding Theatre")
Thanks.
- Was your name Ban... - It's Ban Hee Jin.
I remember telling you last time.
Did you?
I'm leaving first. Keep up the good work.
Bye.
Look at him.
Good-looking guys like him have no interest in me.
Are you saying...
that's why looks don't matter to you for your boyfriend?
Stop kidding me.
I know that a face like his isn't good enough for you.
That's ridiculous.
I wonder if you can say that even when you meet someone...
incredibly handsome.
My gosh.
Oh, no.
Oh, my gosh.
Where's the Sculpture Department's office?
(Cha Ji Won, Yein University Sculpture Major)
This is the Sculpture Department's office.
I see. Thank you.
I have my application to return to school.
When will it get processed?
Sorry?
Oh, right. Let's see.
Your application will be processed within the day.
You can enrol in classes after that through our website.
Got it. Thank you.
I should thank you.
Should I help you with enrolling in classes?
(Bang Ho Dong, Chun Choon Shik)
Hey. Did you see this year's freshmen?
The girls were all so pretty.
Of course. And I agree with you.
I especially found the bob hair pretty.
Oh, yes! She's a beauty.
- What about you? - Me? I can't say it.
I'll keep it a secret.
No, I can't say it.
Gosh.
Guys!
What?
Hi, boss.
Hello.
(Hwang Jae Yeol, Yein University 2nd-year Visual Design Major)
If you can't say it to their face,
don't say it behind their back.
(Lee Dong Ha, Yein University 2nd-year Visual Design Major)
- Understood. Sorry. - Sorry.
- Hi. - Hi.
How can he look so cool just standing there?
I know, right? He's my role model.
"If you can't say it to their face, don't say it..."
I can't do it. Let's go.
Gosh.
Yeol. That's no reason to kill their spirits on the day...
you've returned to school.
We need to nip it in the bud.
Keep being nice,
and they'll cause trouble later.
I see. As expected of the department rep.
Really. Why did I have to become the department rep?
It's such a hassle.
Hey, department rep. Wait for me.
You walk fast, department rep.
(Bani)
Gosh.
(Bong)
Is he busy?
(Jung Geun Cheol)
Oh, wait.
Hello?
Of course. What did I say? It won't be before long.
Who's that?
Go on the trip, and it's a done deal.
I already dropped a hint about being an overnight one.
You know, right?
How much effort I've put into sleeping with Bani.
- Is he crazy? - What in the world?
Yes. Bani, no matter what.
I've been looking for the chance to sleep with her...
since the day we started dating.
Gosh, but she was playing so hard to get.
I'm telling you, I couldn't even make any attempts.
I'm not sure if she's quick-witted...
- or really slow. - What?
Hey, Yeol.
- What's this broadcast? - I pulled cheap tricks,
- suggesting we rest somewhere, - What is he talking about?
but it didn't work.
That's why I'll make her drink...
the second we get to the destination.
He's talking about Bani, right?
I'm going to kill that punk today.
Since we'll be drunk,
she'll get the message if I humour her...
and get the mood going.
Hey. Did you seriously sweet-talk her into it?
My wish is her command.
For real?
Honestly, aren't I way out of her league?
I hit on her because she looked easy, okay?
Seriously?
I'll just keep hitting on her.
Why are you dating her?
Simply put, to sleep with her.
- Gosh. - I told you, didn't I?
That she was easy.
I'll make it happen for sure for all the time...
and effort I put into her.
What? That necklace?
I used it to soften her up to go on the trip.
It's fake anyway.
Looking for one that looked identical was tough.
Hey! What a wacko.
What?
The mic.
Oh, my.
Bani.
Bani! Oh, no!
I'm sorry.
We'd like to make an announcement.
We sincerely apologize for any inconvenience...
caused to the students of Yein University...
due to incorrect broadcast content.
- My gosh. - We'd like to apologize once again.
We sincerely apologize for any inconvenience...
caused to the students of Yein University...
due to incorrect broadcast content.
(Bong)
Oh, Hee Jin.
So it's...
It's...
It's all my fault.
But you're misunderstanding what I said.
I didn't mean it.
You're saying I'm misunderstanding after saying those things yourself?
I was just trying to show off to my friend...
and went overboard.
Do you think it makes sense?
It's true.
You know how much I like you.
Please believe me.
You jerk.
He's Ko Bong Soo who studies Philosophy.
Hey.
You're not even human.
It's humiliating.
It's Ban Hee Jin.
I can't do this anymore.
Hey.
You should also stop pretending.
Did you really not know my intention?
You wanted it too. Don't act like a victim only now.
What? Why?
You were all smiles when things were good.
But now you're embarrassed...
because your true colours might be exposed in front of everyone?
You're nothing special, but I've been putting up with you.
Hey.
I'm going to say this just once, so listen carefully.
I only dated you...
because you begged desperately.
Hey, I could meet a good-looking guy too!
Don't you dare show me that face from now on.
It's your lucky day.
You jerk!
Oh, my gosh. That was unbelievable.
The call cannot be connected.
She's not picking up.
Gosh. Seriously?
(Real-time Fiery Fist at Yein University)
(Gosh, Fiery Fist at Yein University is here.)
(- That guy is trash. - He should drop out of school.)
(But honestly, the girl has an issue too.)
Are they crazy?
"She brought it upon herself?"
Are they joking?
(- Fiery Fist at Yein University. - This is going to be so fun.)
(Ban Hee Jin, Sculpture Department, Yein University)
(- It's embarrassing. - I'm so glad she punched him.)
Bani.
It's all my fault.
What are you talking about? It's not your fault.
He's trash.
No.
Just because he said he liked me,
I let him have his way.
I like you.
I like you!
I'm just...
I'm just regretting everything.
What do you regret the most?
The fact that I thought it was all good...
as long as he liked me.
Actually, what was the most important...
was my feelings.
It's okay because you know now.
What's important is the future.
The future?
Yes.
I've made up my mind.
Listen carefully.
I'm going to start dating good-looking people too!
There you go!
That's what I wanted to hear for so long!
Yes. Go for it.
Please do that.
I dated someone who said he liked me,
but he turned out to be trash anyway.
I just want to have a crush...
on someone I like too.
She's sleeping so quietly.
Is she dead?
Fortunately, she's breathing.
(Kim Hyun Kyung, Bani's mother, Ban Yeong Min, Bani's father)
- Oh, my goodness. - Gosh.
If you're up, wash up quickly and eat.
I've made a refreshing hangover soup for you.
How about the other girls?
They had breakfast and left a long time ago.
Gosh, stop dawdling and get up quickly. You should go to school.
I should. I should go to school.
I should go and take a leave of absence.
- "A leave of absence?" - "A leave of absence?"
Honey.
Can you ask Bani...
if she really wants to take a leave of absence?
I will.
Oh, gosh.
What's the reason this time?
Why do you want to take time off...
as soon as the new semester starts again?
- "Again?" - "Again?"
Yes.
Don't you remember?
You said you wanted to move to another school...
as soon as the new semester began and made a fuss.
Oh, right.
I remember.
Let me go to another school!
Let me move!
Bani, no matter how much you want to do it,
you can't follow the student teacher to go to school in Gangwon Province!
What about it?
The water is clean, the air is nice, and it makes me happy.
What's wrong with that? Just let me go!
Coming.
Oh, gosh.
Hello.
We moved in next door today.
And my mother asked me to give you some rice cakes.
Oh, yes.
I heard someone was moving in. Was it today?
- You didn't have to do this. - Thank you.
He was her first love.
If it weren't for him,
she would've moved to Gangwon Province.
Oh, gosh.
No. He's not the reason I didn't go.
Anyway,
I've made up my mind for sure this time. So don't stop me.
- I'll get going. - All right.
If a strikingly handsome guy appears,
she'll never say she'll take a leave of absence again.
- A handsome guy like you. - What?
What is this? A signal?
Shall we go to the room?
I'm ready.
(Application for Leave of Absence)
- Excuse me. - Yes?
I'm kind of lost.
Do you know how to get to the library?
- Excuse me. - Yes?
I'm kind of lost.
Do you know how to get to the library?
What is this perfectly measured beauty?
Is this the Renaissance...
I've only heard about?
Or...
is it a golden ratio of a Greek sculpture?
He has charm.
He has great charm.
I feel like he would be choosing flowers...
with sad eyes somehow.
At that moment, the owner of the flower shop comes out and asks.
Is it for your girlfriend?
Then he smiles without a word.
I don't know why. He just has to.
Then...
he puts the flowers in a vase beautifully.
Let me tell you where he is.
It's his sick girlfriend's hospital room.
How are you feeling today?
Then his delicate and dainty girlfriend...
would answer.
"Same as always."
Oh, my gosh. Why does she have my face?
Get it together, Ban Hee Jin.
I'm sorry. I was thinking about something else for a moment.
Where do you want to go again?
Where is the library?
What?
Is this...
(Sculpting Technique)
Are you a freshman in the Sculpture Department?
No, I'm not.
Mom, Dad, I've made up my mind.
I'll never leave Yein University.
Let's go. I'll take you there.
Why were you by yourself?
Did you not make friends yet?
I'm a bit shy around new people.
I see.
It's okay. I understand it can be awkward.
You bumped into me thanks to that.
Actually, I'm the Sculpture Department's representative...
this semester.
If you don't know anything, feel free to ask me.
I'll tell you everything.
Sure.
How about your course registration? Did it go well?
It must've been hard as a freshman.
I was a bit late,
so I just registered for the remaining classes.
You did? You probably don't have a long break between classes then.
It's a bummer.
I would've scheduled all the classes for you...
if we had met just a week earlier.
Oh, have you tried the special meal at school?
You must try it.
Actually, it's a little expensive.
Let's eat together...
next time.
Yes. Let's do that.
(Main Library)
Thank you for taking me.
No need to thank me. I just did what I should do.
If there's something you don't know,
feel free to contact me at the number I gave you earlier.
I have a lot of past exam papers.
Okay.
I'll get going then.
Let's definitely meet up next time.
Okay.
Bye.
No way.
Who is that man possessing sublime beauty?
A sharp jawline, a cold gaze,
and chilly lips.
There's something to him.
There's definitely something to him.
Even the hottest summer weather would be blasted away.
He has that refreshing vibe to him.
Let's see. On the back of his bike...
would be his high school sweetheart.
That girlfriend of his...
must have dark hair with dark eyes...
Me?
Why did I add my face again?
Stop picturing you with them, Ban Hee Jin.
I'm glad I didn't take time off from school.
This is the Almighty telling me to stay.
("The Ultimate Male Divinity" by Ban Hee Jin aka Bani)
I see you have good taste.
It's by the top second-year student in our department.
With this piece, she received the highest score in history.
When it comes to artistic talent,
she'll be the most famous.
Hold on.
You kind of look like him.
Even more with that smile.
Enjoy.
What's his problem?
That was unbelievably annoying.
Excuse me.
I was just about to put my things in it.
So?
Shouldn't it go...
to whoever occupies it first?
I can finally function again.
Nothing cures a hangover like cream buns.
What you're saying...
is that you ran into not 1 but 2 handsome guys.
Back to back.
I had no idea our campus was this beautiful.
The campus...
is full of light.
Is it bright?
Lucky you.
I'd also like to encounter good looking guys like that.
Tell me about it.
We had better things to do then work on our art.
The new semester event is keeping us from having our eyes blessed.
Still, they look pretty when gathered like this.
They remind me of cherry blossoms.
I'd love to have...
cherry blossom petals flutter around me and my boo.
I doubt that's in my cards though.
It wouldn't be impossible if you put your mind to it.
You vowed to only date good-looking guys.
Enjoy cherry blossoms, lock eyes with love,
smack those lips together, and do it all.
You're taking it too far with the kissing.
(Student Council Room)
Creative Work of Art by Youth.
We need to get in.
Can we submit it by tomorrow?
- I'm almost done. - Okay.
Let's do this, Yeol. Let's get us a room.
I'm done on my end.
I hope they get us a room.
We'll have a studio free of charge.
I hear they have other benefits too.
We'll get in.
I stayed up countless nights trying to finish this.
Jae Yeol.
This is for you.
Sure. Thanks.
Jae Yeol, you're the best.
This is why you're my role model.
The one who stole women's hearts as soon as the semester began.
Who could he be?
He's my pride and joy as well as yours.
- Moreover, the whole department... - Hey. Shut it.
If you're going to be loud, take this and get lost.
Could us humble beings have something this precious?
- Are you sure? - Are you sure?
- We'll enjoy it. - Thank you.
That should do it.
(Yeinies)
Unbelievable.
Have you ever gotten anything like this before?
Of course I have.
Talk about a human air purifier.
How refreshing.
Yeol, have one.
- It's yours, so have one. - I'm good.
- He's right. - Thanks to you...
We got it thanks to you, so have one.
- At least have one. - Have this instead, then.
- Go on. - I'm good.
- Open wide. - I said I was good.
Watch out!
Are you all right?
I hope you weren't hurt.
What a relief.
That...
Oh, no.
My gosh.
Did it crack?
Check, will you? See if it's still working.
What about our work?
Did it crack?
Check, will you? See if it's still working.
What about our work?
(Yeinies)
What now?
Our blood, sweat, and tears were in that.
Well,
I only reacted thinking you were in danger.
This was never my intention.
I should've known better and I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
Whatever.
What will you do about my tablet?
Of course I should pay for a new one.
Do you even know how much it costs?
Well, I'll do what I can to...
(Tablet Pro 13 Gen 7 WiFi 256GB Gray, 2,000 dollars)
Is it 2,000 dollars?
Is that 2,000 dollars?
That costs 2,000 dollars?
That's expensive.
Would it be possible...
to pay you back monthly?
Does she think he's a department store?
Who pays back on an instalment basis?
We could at least give her three months.
I'll get you the money as soon as possible.
I'm...
I'm terribly sorry.
- Wait. - Hold on.
Your number.
Give me your number before you go.
Hi.
- Hey. - What took you so long?
Bani.
Hey, you're here. Have a seat.
(Grilled pork belly, Udon)
- Are you doing better? - What?
What? Why?
You were all smiles when things were good.
But now you're embarrassed...
because your true colours might be exposed in front of everyone?
You're nothing special, but I've been putting up with you.
Right, I forgot.
I'm the pushover girlfriend of Yein University.
Of course I'm all right.
I had been all right.
That's a relief.
I was seriously worried...
that you might take time off from school.
I know.
Maybe I should consider that.
Why should I...
when life is this beautiful?
You came.
- Have a seat here. - Sure.
He's so handsome!
No way.
Attention, please.
We'll start with Group A.
One by one,
you'll introduce yourselves.
Finally, a hottie joined our department.
Right? Isn't it a joy?
- By the way, how did you... - Hello.
get to know the grandson of Chaon Group's chairman?
- Freshman of 2025... - I was startled to say the least.
- I hope we get along. - You see, on my way to school...
- I'm next. - Hold on.
- Hello. - What was that?
Chaon Group.
He's the grandson of the group's chairman.
Didn't you know?
Hello.
I'm Cha Ji Won,
entering class of 2021, who just returned to school.
Entering class of 2021, who just returned to school...
(Freshmen Welcome Party)
(Sculpture Department Freshmen Welcome Party)
Everyone.
The one in front of you...
will be your partner for the year.
Greet one another.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hi. - Hello.
Should I pour you a drink since you're my senior?
What?
Gosh, why would you call me that?
Allow me to pour you a glass.
Don't be absurd. I should pour you one first...
since you're my senior partner.
Gosh, please.
I'm messing with you.
Besides, I can't handle any alcohol.
It was to get you to ease up.
Be comfortable around me.
How could I?
Not when I found out something huge.
You're the grandson of Chaon Group's chairman.
Am I even allowed...
to sit at the same table as you?
You're a funny one.
From here on out, just call me Bani.
Bani.
- Bani? - Yes.
("The Ultimate Male Divinity" by Ban Hee Jin aka Bani)
Junior partners,
were you able to get to know your seniors better?
- Yes! - Yes!
Since things have heated up,
we'll now...
begin the freshman initiation.
Go, Sculpture Department.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Cheers.
He said he couldn't handle alcohol.
Cha Ji Won.
- Cha Ji Won. - Cha Ji Won.
- Cha Ji Won! - Cha Ji Won.
- Cha Ji Won. - Cha Ji Won!
- Cha Ji Won. - Cha Ji Won.
- Cha Ji Won! - Cha Ji Won.
- Cha Ji Won. - Cha Ji Won!
- Hold on! - Cha...
I'll drink on his behalf.
(Sculpture Department Freshmen Welcome Party)
I'm...
his senior partner, after all.
I'll drink on his behalf.
That's so cool!
- Yes! - Nice!
- That's so cool! - Yes!
Go!
- Nicely done. - Nice, Bani!
- Ban Hee Jin! - Yes!
Are you okay?
Sure, so far so good.
Thanks. You're a lifesaver.
I'm glad I was able to make up for my error.
By any chance, do you have a wish?
That's part of the deal on my end.
Gosh, that isn't necessary.
I only helped you out to be rid of my own guilt.
Or do you have some time tomorrow?
You know the special meal you talked about? It's my treat.
What? I was going to treat you to the special meal.
I need to return the favour somehow.
Well,
if you insist, I won't say no to that.
I hope we can get along well,
my senior partner.
What?
I also hope we can get along well, my junior partner.
(Yein Village)
- Hey. - Hello.
(Welcome, Freshmen of 2025)
- Hello. - He's here.
Jae Yeol. What should we order?
If anyone crosses him tonight, they might see their end.
Right.
One of you might see your end.
Choon Shik. Ho Dong. Try your best.
All right. Attention, everyone.
This kind gentleman was largely responsible for providing us...
with an abundance of food and drinks tonight.
Why don't we all shout out his name?
- Hwang Jae Yeol! - Hwang Jae Yeol!
Come on. I barely heard you guys. Say it again, but loudly this time.
What's his name?
- Hwang Jae Yeol! - Hwang Jae Yeol!
Let's hear a toast from our department rep, Hwang Jae Yeol!
- Hwang Jae Yeol! - Hey, do it just this once.
- Hwang Jae Yeol! - Hwang Jae Yeol!
- Best. - Best!
- Department. - Department!
- Best Department Visual Design. - Best Department Visual Design.
Jae Yeol. By the way,
I guess the cash prize of the contest must be pretty big.
We just started our semester. But you're already treating us.
- Amazing. - Amazing.
Could we order anything we want to eat then?
Do whatever you want.
- Okay. Let's order meat first. - Nice.
- Yes. - Okay.
I can't get rid of this annoying feeling.
- Ho Dong. - Sirloin?
- Eat a lot. Let's have a feast. - Yes.
How about sirloin then?
What do you think? He seems to be in a better mood, right?
Is that how he looks to you?
- You're so good. - You're an expert.
- You're good. - You and your sense of humour.
Why don't we order four servings of sirloin?
- Game start - Game start
- Bani's favourite game - Bani.
- Bani. - Let's go.
- Bani. - No.
- A random game Bani likes - A random game Bani likes
- Let's go, game start - Let's go, game start
Yes! It's you!
- Drink it. - Okay.
- Drink it. - Come on.
She's having a blast...
when I'm feeling so miserable because of her.
Bani. Are you all right?
I think you're drunk.
My gosh. What are you talking about? I'm not drunk at all. I'm serious.
She's drunk.
What?
The tablet.
Is she pointing at me right now?
Darn it. I'm glad you're here.
Ban Hee Jin. Hey.
Come to your senses, Ban Hee Jin.
Hey. Stop right there.
I told you to stop.
- What are you doing? - Yes.
Your eyes.
The way you talk.
Gosh, I'm getting the chills.
Did you have to be so scary? Are you satisfied?
My goodness, you're so rude.
What? Rude?
I'm going to pay you back! Didn't I tell you that I would?
What are you doing? Hey.
Hey. Let go of me when I'm still being civil.
One, two,
three.
My gosh. How could a girl be this strong?
Hey, I told you to let go of me.
You. Come on.
This isn't fair.
I was just trying...
to protect...
this handsome face of yours from the fall.
What?
Darn it. Nothing is more precious...
- than this handsome face... - That hurts.
in this world.
Your face could easily be worth a million dollars.
You look...
even more handsome up close.
Hey.
That's really not cool.
Hey, don't open your mouth. Keep it shut.
If you open your mouth, I'm going to kill you. I swear.
Gosh, my head is pounding.
How much did I drink last night?
How did I get home?
And why do my hands feel so sore?
Did someone hit my hands?
What? The tablet.
Nothing is more precious...
- than this handsome face... - That hurts.
in this world.
Don't open your mouth. Keep it shut.
If you open your mouth, I'm going to kill you.
No way.
I must have gone mad.
(Exporting)
Ban Hee Jin.
I swear. You're going...
to pay for this.
Ban Hee Jin!
(Street Festival)
Darn it.
Maybe, I should have taken time off from school.
No. If he catches me, I'm done for.
You must run away now, Ban Hee Jin.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Ban Hee Jin.
(Face Painting)
(Campus Club Street Festival)
I'm sorry.
- Excuse me. - Oh, my. You're so handsome.
- Let's talk, Ban Hee Jin. - No way. He's so handsome.
- That little... Come on. - He's so hot.
- Seriously. So hot. - Oh, my.
(Campus Club Street Festival)
Darn it.
Come on.
Would you like to try flying the drone?
Hey, it's Yeol.
Where?
Can't you see him running?
I see. That is Yeol.
Why is he running like that?
(Yein Video Research Society)
(Corner Cafe)
(Star-ers)
Hey, Bani.
Ji Won. Let me hide behind your back for a second.
Ban Hee Jin.
Come on out.
They're not here.
Hey, that looks so unstable.
What are you doing? Hey.
Hey. What's wrong with this?
Hey, you could cause an accident if you keep that up.
I mean... Wait.
Hey, turn it off and restart it.
What's going on?
(Corner Cafe)
I doubt I'd get my happy ending...
under the cherry blossom petals.
You.
What are you?
(Crushology 101)
Well, hate turns into love.
Strangers become lovers. Am I wrong?
I really want us to be close friends.
Why is he being nice to me all of a sudden?
Get a grip, Ban Hee Jin.
- Excuse me. - What's happening?
How could an artwork speak?
Doesn't it sort of resemble me?
Was I really that harsh on Ban Hee Jin?
Bani?
No one knows from where and in what form destiny will come.
Will you be my destiny?
Hey, Ban Hee Jin.
No way. Can this be...
destiny?