My Girlfriend is an Alien
Episode 16
The Second Young Madam is going out.
You don't need to follow me.
Since the person behind you has been found,
then you should go down
and apologize to my parents and the innocent villagers
of Jiang Village.
Kill!
Help!
Stop!
What's going on?
The Second Young Master is going to kill me.
He has already cut many people with this sword.
His personal servant was badly injured last night
and died without eating.
Eat more if it's delicious.
Father, now I have a stable foot in Ning's Mansion.
Brother, I will be filial to you in the future.
It's the best you can think of.
I didn't hurt you for nothing.
You hurt me?
If I hadn't been lucky,
I would have been killed by you.
Nonsense!
This...this...this...
Tian Qi...
It's poisonous.
You are not a good son.
You don't deserve to be a father.
You should have died long ago.
It's poisonous.
Isn't this my jade pendant?
Prime Minister, please.
Prime Minister.
I'm sorry.
If I keep on chasing after him,
I will be dead.
Second Young Madam,
the Duke wants you to go to the front hall.
What is it?
It seems to be about the maid Jiang Le Yao.
Jiang Le Yao?
Yes.
He didn't take good care of Ni Tao.
What did Le Yao do wrong?
He did wrong.
But you are a criminal.
Prime Minister, please forgive me.
Second Young Master always took care of Le Yao.
Now he is...
You shouldn't have asked me.
What did I do wrong?
Isn't it about Ni Tao being poisoned to death?
You stole the jade pendant
and replaced it with the Duke's mansion.
You are now the second young master.
You stole the Duke's mansion
and replaced it with the Duke's mansion.
You deserve to die.
Why are you here?
Call me out.
This is mine.
You are lying.
This jade pendant is a pair.
It is a gift from my ancestor.
Back then, the old master
gave this to someone else
as a wedding gift.
How did it become yours?
Prime Minister, please forgive me.
This jade pendant
was polished by the old master
when he was in my house.
He gave one of them
to my grandfather.
As a wedding gift,
I was not a good daughter.
I was deceived by Rong'er
and gave him the jade pendant.
That's how he got
the wedding gift from the second young master.
I know it's too late to say anything now.
But this jade pendant
is a gift from my parents.
But my parents
have passed away in the fire.
It's all over.
This jade pendant
is the only thing
they left me.
I just want to take it back
as a souvenir.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
Sister Zhang,
I'm really sorry.
I really want to take back
the thing my mother left me.
Nonsense.
It was my grandfather
who saved the old master.
Before my father died,
he asked me to complete
the wishes of the ancestors
when he gave me the jade pendant.
Before your father died?
Yes.
No one can talk for you
if they know
that the person who did this is dead.
Is that
what you often say?
Impossible.
He...
He's dead.
I...
Sir, you can still be saved.
But you won't live long.
It's enough that you can point out the murderer.
Take him away.
That's how it went.
Because he's still alive,
how to deal with Chang Rong'er
is up to you, Duke Ningguo.
Chang Rong'er's death is not a big deal.
This marriage
was arranged by the old master.
Why don't you take this opportunity
to fight against the government?
That's not appropriate.
The second young master has been married.
How can he fight against the government?
If Duke Ningguo
wants to repay the old master,
why don't you
let Jiang Leyao be your adopted daughter?
Leyao, my respects to you.
Come in.
Thank you, Father.
Chang Rong'er,
you lied to the whole Ning family
without any reason.
You'll be punished for your death.
Come on.
Please forgive me, Duke.
Sister,
Sister was tricked by Zhuyong.
Please save her.
Father,
Rong'er grew up with me.
He also took care of me a lot.
Father,
can you forgive him
for the sake of Leyao?
I happen to
lack a servant.
How about
he go to my place
and be my maid?
All right.
Let him serve you.
Thank you, Father.
Yes.
You want to take away my identity, right?
You bitch!
How dare you hit me?
Now I'm the master,
and you're the servant.
You don't know
what to call me.
Lady Yuzhan,
I'll listen to you
in the future.
That's more like it.
But don't worry.
I won't make it hard for you.
Chang Rong'er,
you must
serve Young Master.
He knows.
He must have done it.
Go on.
I'll try to be romantic.
The most important thing now
is to deal with Jiang Leyao,
that bitch.
It's so weird.
She's always so gentle.
Why is she suddenly biting me?
Father,
Mother,
just wait.
I'll make Chang Rong
pay for it.
What does it mean?
He knows.
Did he also be reborn?
I'm here.