My Girlfriend is an Alien
Episode 2
Stop!
She is my girl.
Where are you taking her?
Get out!
You are not the one to be punished.
You are the one to be punished.
Second Young Madam,
it's your turn.
Why did you hit me?
I am the Second Young Madam.
Shen Er,
what are you going to do next?
You are a servant.
Why are you doing this to me?
I am going to teach her a lesson.
The lesson is decided by the Duke and Second Young Master.
But I will take care of it in the Second House.
Maids,
marry the Second Young Madam.
She will be punished for hitting the Third Young Madam.
When the masters return to the mansion,
she will be punished for her life.
My Lord,
the Ning family has committed suicide.
Even if we suspect that it is related to the Ning family,
we have lost the last clue.
Then go find a new clue.
Yes.
Thank you for saving my life, Lord Xiao.
This is not a problem.
You want to be my spy?
I can save you
with my ability.
You are indeed capable
of framing your master
and seducing the chief minister of the Xuan Yin Bureau.
What do you want to do?
The Ning family is strong and powerful.
It is a big and small family.
I want to come to Lord Xiao's house
to help the Ning family.
You are honest.
Then I will give you a chance.
In the study of Duke Ning,
there is a book called The Book of Ruyi.
Go and find it for me.
I will do my best.
Reply to me every two days.
Lord,
I am out of the way.
I will find you.
Then can you promise me
that if I am in danger,
you will appear in time?
You are my man
when you do things for me.
I will save your life.
Thank you, Lord.
We are in a cooperation relationship.
You help me find out the information.
Tell me.
What do you want me to do for you?
Next,
you just need to be a distant visitor
and watch a good show.
Give me back my sachet.
Help!
I want water.
Are they all dead?
Why are you back?
Isn't there a way out in Xuan Yin Temple?
Lord Xiao just wants to investigate
if the fire in the village is a man or not.
It's an accident.
That fire was an accident.
Yes.
Accident?
So I came back.
It's good that you came back.
I had no choice.
The situation was critical.
I have already thought of a plan.
You will be beaten.
You will not be in danger.
Do you believe me?
Of course I believe you.
You are my sister.
How can you harm me?
Of course.
I will not harm you.
Since you are lucky,
you should live well.
I will need your help in the future.
Lord Ning will take the second young master back home soon.
Qi Zhen will definitely report to the bad guys.
Do you have any way to deal with it?
The affairs of Ningguo Palace are busy.
I won't interfere with the second young master.
But Ning Tao is a fool.
He doesn't know what to say.
He listens to Qi Zhen.
With your beauty and wisdom,
it's easy to win the second young master's heart.
I don't want to serve that fool.
Now the situation is critical.
It's easier to serve the second young master
than to be kicked out of Ningfu.
I have prepared
the second young master's favorite jade cake.
And I added the lotus umbrella.
No.
I gave this fool the lotus umbrella.
You should enjoy it.
Help me to put on makeup.
Since you took my identity,
you should enjoy what I have experienced.
Okay.
Is it delicious?
It's hot.
You should sleep.
You won't sleep.
Sleep.
Don't bite me.
Shou has chosen the rich and the poor.
You asked for it.
I'm sorry.