My Girlfriend is an Alien
Episode 16
Jiang Le Yao
I'm Jiang Le Yao.
I'm here to ask for your hairpin.
You entered the Gui Gate Pass,
but you didn't enter the Xuan Yin Temple.
You broke such a broken hairpin.
Jiang Le Yao,
you don't even want your life back.
I want my life back.
I also want my hairpin.
I know you didn't want to kill me.
Otherwise, you can just do it
at the gate of Ning Manor.
You're wrong.
I just want to
torture you
here.
I also know
that the banknotes you're investigating
and the money in the back
are related to Ning Manor.
But Duke Ning is a man of power
and has a high position.
It's not convenient for you to do it.
As long as you're willing to return the hairpin
and let me live,
I'm willing to be your pawn
and take over Ning Manor.
As the maid of the Xiaos,
you still want to cooperate with me?
You're so ugly.
I heard that Xiao Jin
is not in her right mind.
Could it be...
As long as you're willing to return the hairpin,
I'm willing to be your pawn.
I'm willing to do
whatever you ask me to do.
You're as thin as a silk.
You're as tough as a tiger's paw.
You even want to hurt me.
They say that the Xuan Yin Bureau is a place of silence.
You're not a thing.
You're just...
emotional.
Nonsense.
I said something wrong.
Your Excellency,
I have an urgent report.
Hurry up and put on your clothes.
If you're really injured,
will others see that you're not well?
I'm also a big thing to you.
If you insist on doing this,
I can only accept it.
Your Excellency.
Get lost.
Okay.
Your Excellency, you're protecting me.
I'm very touched.
You...
You're good too.
Good things are disturbed.
You're right.
If you want to continue,
I'll come to Ning Mansion tonight.
I'll wait for you.
The scented sachet is broken, but it's written on the body.
It must be a very important person.
You must come.
I'll be waiting for you.
You're so brave.
Rong'er,
you're so brave.
You dare to steal Madam's gold hairpin?
I can't wait to see your dog bite the dog.
Nonsense.
What evidence do you have to prove that I stole the gold hairpin?
I said you stole it.
You're so stubborn.
I'll find out how to deal with you.
Search.
Lu Yao.
Yes.
Go to Madam Qi's room and search.
Good.
I'll wait here today.
Let's see whose room the gold hairpin is in.
Sister.
Mengmeng.
Madam Qi, the evidence is clear.
What else do you have to say?
Jiang Lu Yao, did you steal it?
Madam Qi,
did the maid steal it
or did Madam Qi steal it?
Chang Rong'er,
you're still cruel and ungrateful.
Since that,
I can only take the opportunity to save the chicken
and save the chicken from the chicken.
I didn't.
You'll know when you interrogate me.
Guards, serve her.
Xiao Jing Chu, aren't you coming?
Sir, the time has come.
Sir,
my family has an appointment.
Aren't you going?
No.
Sir,
the drug trafficker we've been watching
has entered Ning Mansion.
Come with me to arrest him.
Sir,
that's Ning Mansion.
It's not good to arrest him by force.
The Xuan Yin Bureau will arrest him.
Not only Ning Mansion,
but the palace will also be punished.
Yes.
My good sister,
if you don't want to suffer anymore,
just confess.
I'll plead for you.
You won't.
Guards,
report to Xichun.
Put her in the sack
and pull her out.
Then put the mouse and the cat in.
Even if you're in trouble, you can't say anything.
My good sister,
what are you screaming for?
My good sister.
Everyone,
close the case.
We won.
Sir,
my master is a priest.
You broke into Ning Mansion twice.
Aren't you afraid that my master will be punished?
If you find the criminal in Ning Mansion,
he should be the one who should be afraid.
Ning Mansion.
Search.
My lady,
please help me.
Please help me.
My lady.
Let me go.
Put her in the sack.
My lady.
Let me go.