Going Behind the Scenes
Episode 47
You're pregnant.
Me?
Your Royal Highness,
I saw this...
When?
This morning.
His mother died.
Thatב׳
No, I didn't.
Your Highness,
I did this alone.
Please don't involve Ning's family.
Now that it has come to this,
are you going to keep it from me?
Grandmother,
the child in Bingqing's belly
is mine.
You...
Do you have anything to say to me?
No matter who asks,
you have to make sure
that the child in your belly
is mine.
As for the Ningguo Palace,
I am the Crown Prince.
You will be the Crown Princess soon.
Even if she has other intentions,
I will not let her go.
Your Highness,
the birth medicine
is ready.
What did you do this time?
You must be joking.
After all, the one you are pregnant with
is the royal heir.
Yes.
Royal heir?
As long as the Crown Prince admits it,
then the bastard in my belly
must be the royal heir.
Do you know
what you are talking about?
Grandmother,
that day, I was
poisoned by a maid
who was about to climb the bed.
I did not want to let Bingqing down,
but I did not cure her.
Don't...
It's all my fault.
Please punish me.
Why did the Crown Prince
admit the child?
He really loves Bingqing.
All right.
Get up.
Thank you, Grandmother.
I will tell His Majesty
to let you get married as soon as possible.
Thank you, Grandmother.
The grass is
being stolen from the sky.
In the end,
it can only be a wishful thinking.
Do you think
the rules of the rich
will not allow you
to be a little bitch?
Sister,
this time,
I will not let you down.
Sister,
this time,
it's your turn to take the punishment.
The one who dies
will be punished.
With the testimony of this witness,
the charges against Zhao Momo
have been settled.
Qiao Bing,
you deserve to die.
Qiao Bing is not an ordinary guard.
Don't act rashly.
Trust me.
I will definitely give you justice.
The
Xiang Lang Yang.
The First Miss said her wedding dress was not enough.
Use your blood to dye it.
The silk soft armor.
The life of a killer
is what I will send you
to Zhao Momo today.
This silk soft armor
is better than the sword.
Put it on to be safe.
First Miss,
Jiang Liao will definitely die this time.
Die?
Isn't that too cheap?
The job is well done.
It's worth dying.
Good sister,
you killed someone.
You...
You deliberately let Qiao Bing die.
Yes.
I just want to see
how Xiao Jing Chu will help you this time.
Open the door.
Xiao Jing Chu.
Liao Yao, are you okay?
Where is the silver coin?
Let me see.
Leave me alone.
You go.
I don't want to get you involved.
We are already a team.
How can I be involved?
If I were to be in jail today,
would you leave me alone?
Don't worry.
I've been in the Xuan Yi Temple for so many years.
Leave the rest to me.
Sir.
The palace is rushing.
They said that Duke Ningguo
was covering up for you in front of His Majesty.
Your Grace,
you sent the Second Miss to the Xuan Yi Temple.
Aren't you afraid that Mr. Xiao will cover up?
I just want him to cover up.
A schemer
and a rich man.
Both of them deserve to die.
Has there been any news from the palace recently?
No.
Let Qiao Ping go and inquire.
Your Grace, Qiao Ping...
Your Grace, calm down.
Your Grace,
Ning Hua is pregnant.
Ning Hua is pregnant, Your Grace.
It's none of your business.
No.
Já SPEAKSRS
So live in the palace.
I'd have taken permit.
He is angled.
Ms. Jiang.
She didn't go out I guess.
He's out. It's fine.
But he's busy with work.
He can't be away.
So he asked me to send you a letter.
Tell me the truth.
My Lord.
My Lord is in a coma.
Drinking and drinking.
Walking on the mountain and flowing water.
A kind of memory is gone.
Drunk and drunk.
Afraid of dust and dust.
Drinking and drinking.
Walking on the mountain and flowing water.
A kind of memory is gone.
Drunk and drunk.
Afraid of dust and dust.