[English subtitles are available]
[Day Breaker]
[Episode 14]
So you are Song Cai.
Why do you want to cooperate with me?
Because you are so similar to Pala.
Am I?
No.
If Pala was like him,
he wouldn't have died on the boat.
Can we talk business now?
I don't work with people who take drugs.
I take drugs for inspecting the goods.
Don't look down on me.
Drug addicts are irrational
and lack judgment.
It will make things out of control.
You'll cooperate with me.
He's not responsible for you.
Based on my observation on you these days,
I have a deep impression of you.
You are indeed a capable person.
I hope I was right about you.
Few people can ask me out
in this way.
But I have a question.
Why do you think
you have right to cooperate with me?
I don't have any capital,
but the reason is that we have the same enemy.
The reason why you dare not show up
is not that you're afraid of the police,
but because of Cai Zhiming.
If this continues,
there will be a big war
between you and Cai Zhiming.
Besides, we've always been on bad terms
with the South Asian Gang.
You really need
people like us to help you.
80%.
The remaining 20% will be given to you as the profit.
I don't care how you sell it.
Pay by the end of the month.
Deal.
I've chosen the buyers for you.
Xian City.
Pala's previous transfer station.
Sanyuan Fast Food Restaurant.
I'll let you know the exact time.
Okay.
Where will we get the goods?
The goods?
Haven't you taken all the goods?
After finishing this transaction,
we can continue.
He's still very cautious.
We can only take one step at a time now.
What's the chance of
Liang Long and him
finishing Song Cai's test?
There's something I didn't tell you.
I'm under internal investigation.
In this operation,
he can only rely on himself.
It's okay. I trust him.
Did you hear that?
This is a gift for your promotion.
The platform
has been set up for you.
You have to seize the chance yourself.
Why are you doing this?
I told you.
I need help.
I know what to do.
If there's nothing else,
I have to go.
Officer Liao.
I've checked them.
Have you found anything?
Everyone's action report is fine.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am.
I have to go.
Your milk tea.
A cup of milk tea.
Sir, do you have a loyalty card?
You've had 9 cups on your card.
So this one is free.
[Bubble Tea, Loyalty Card]
Thank you.
Make me a big cup of milk tea.
Add a large portion of tapioca pearls to it.
Okay, wait a moment.
Here you are.
Though I look like this,
I wasn't this fat when I had just became a policeman.
I was just like you,
being both handsome and brave.
As for me,
since the first day when I became a policeman,
I've set a rule for myself.
Every time I catch a drug dealer,
I'll reward myself with a large cup of milk tea.
Are you sure you don't want a cup?
Hello, your milk tea.
The card of your shop.
The money.
Your loyalty card is full.
So this one is free.
Thank you.
Drug dealer.
[Bubble Tea, Loyalty Card]
[Police]
Chief.
I'm handing over the criminal.
A life for a life.
Take it to report on your mission.
Don't move.
Cai Zhiming!
Let go of him!
Cai Zhiming.
Cut the crap.
Get in the car! Get in!
[Police]
You only have this chance
to gain Cai Zhiming's trust.
Shoot.
What answer do you want?
Should I kill him?
If you really want to kill him,
you would have done it earlier.
Why do you wait till now?
Don't use Officer Liao as an excuse.
I'm not making excuses.
After this period of time,
I've found that Luo Xiang didn't come back
for taking revenge on me.
He must have another purpose.
Then you should help him.
He is the same as us.
He will understand you.
What about you?
Can you understand me?
I've never blamed you.
Actually, you know
I'm just another you in your mind.
I've already reported the situation
mentioned by you to the superior.
Ji suggested that
we should do it according to your plan.
The finishing work in Xian City
will be taken over by our people.
Don't worry about it.
Your priority now
is to gain Song Cai's trust,
and find the place where he hides the drugs
as well as other evidence of his crimes.
Don't let the drugs
come into the market again.
Got it.
Hao,
raise this car a bit more.
OK.
Chen Mo,
do you have any idea?
[Taxi]
[Port of Xian City]
[Police]
Tour guide.
Wait.
Your ID card.
Thank you.
I've passed the security check.
I'll wait for you at the destination.
By transporting the goods in this way,
I can avoid other people's surveillance.
If we do as you say, will it work?
No problem.
Divide it into three times.
Call Dai Wei
to confirm the receiving address.
Have you arrived?
I'll cast it over now.
Did you receive it?
Yes.
I'll continue to cast it.
No one answered.
What are you doing?
Come down.
Let me see.
Why did you climb so high
in broad daylight?
Officers,
I got lost.
So I climbed up to see
if there was any way out nearby.
It's isn't illegal to climb trees, is it?
Do you have your ID card with you?
I'm a tour guide.
I've just arrived today. I'm here to take a look.
OK. You got lost, right?
Alright. Come with us.
Okay, thank you.
Let's go.
Found the suspect.
Are you going in first?
Which of you is Xi's parent?
She is.
The competition between children
relates to the comprehensive quality of parents
and their dedication to the education.
Ma'am.
Are you listening to me?
I know, Ma'am.
A child of this age
needs parents' company very much.
Xi told me
her parents often stayed out for several says
because of work
without informing her first.
This will affect Xi's personality
and her life greatly.
She will become rebellious
and unsociable.
Officer Yu,
you're living a good life.
Uncle Cai asked me to remind you
not to forget your promise to him.
Mom.
Goodbye, Miss.
Xi.
Don't be sad.
Let's make up for the homework
after we go home, and it'll be fine.
What makes me sad is
that my dad is so calm.
You didn't do your homework because you wanted to see your dad.
He disappeared for two months.
As soon as he got home,
he went out again before he could give me a hug.
If you were me, could you stand it?
Officer Yu.
Notify the policemen in the nearby vital traffic lines
to stay more alert.
Report to me if anything happens.
Yes.
We lost one kilogram before the deal.
It's too difficult to do business.
It's Dai Wei.
Long.
Long! Long!
How did you get here?
I came from the forest.
It's not easy to be chased here,
but we can't avoid those roads
and checkpoints.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[Fast Food Restaurant]
[Hua City Police Department]
Let's talk.
I'm sorry, Xi.
What did you do wrong?
Everything I did is wrong.
Be more specific.
Think about it.
I think your attitude is the main problem.
Work is important,
but your life is also important.
Every time you focus on work,
I feel
I'm so far away from you.
Work is important,
but your life is also important.
Every time you focus on work,
I feel
I'm so far away from you.
Promise me
you won't disappear without a word again.
Actually, I just want you to see me.
You've always been in my heart.
I'll make it up to you, okay?
I don't need your compensation.
I just want you to promise me
you won't leave without a word again.
Got it.
But only in this way
can I guarantee your safety.
Only when I'm with you
can I feel safe.
Don't worry.
I won't abandon you.
Dad.
You've been away for two months.
Were you arrested by the police?
Are you a good person or a bad person?
Do you think I'm a good person or a bad person?
I don't care if you're good or bad.
I only know you're a good father.
It's been a long time since I took your shabby car.
Tomorrow is my birthday.
Take me out to go for a ride.
[Taxi]
It's a deal.
I've found a way to go to Xian City.
After getting the news about Song Cai,
we can take action.
That's good.
Officer Su told me everything.
Officer Liao, are you okay?
That's the case for time being.
Officer Yu will lead the team.
When you're on a mission,
I'll inform him.
He will assist you.
Whom are these flowers for?
I don't think I told you
about my family.
We always separate the personal matters from work.
That was when I first met you.
It's different now.
Now you are my friend.
Do you remember
when I first met you,
you were with your daughter in the hospital?
Actually, my wife had been in hospital for a long time, too.
But she's not as lucky as your daughter.
I don't even know
if I can see her get discharged from hospital.
In her mind,
I'm an excellent policeman
and a dutiful husband.
Maybe I don't want to let her down,
so I'll try my best
to make up for my faults.
This is for your daughter.
Today is her birthday, right?
How do you know?
It's written in your file.
It doesn't matter if I remember it or not.
It's important that you remember it.
Thank you.
Miss Zhang,
I'm not late this time.
Sit down. Let's order.
Waiter.
No need.
Miss Zhang,
I didn't mean this last time.
I just wanted to tell you...
Miss Zhang,
do you really not want to think about it again?
All the readers and I
are looking forward to your serialization very much.
Do you want to know
the follow-up of my stories?
Of course.
Next, we're going to collaborate with the radio station
to create a radio drama for this story.
Let me tell you.
If I go on serializing this story,
you'll appear in the story.
Goodbye.
Does the tea farmer in the story really exist?
Uncle Cai.
Let's start.
OK.
[Liang Long]
Happy birthday to Chen Xi.
I think Dad is back.
Officer Yu,
this is the report of previous activities.
Get familiar with it first.
Actually, I think
anyone can do this work.
I don't know why
Officer Liao asked you to do it.
I think it's a waste of talent.
You should go now.
Officer Yu.
We just received a report from a civilian.
It seems there's drug trafficking
around the junction between Hua City and Xian City.
Got it.
Get ready to go.
Okay.
Let's go.
[Police]
Mobile phone.
Song Cai only needs to deliver the goods
within the specified time.
Let's go.
Hello, are you Officer Yu?
Who are you?
I'm a chief of Xian City's police.
We came here as soon as we received the report.
We've deployed
people to all the main passageways
and checkpoints of Xian City.
No suspect vehicles have been found so far.
I heard that you are very familiar
about the situation here.
Please help to instruct the work at the scene, Officer Yu.
Get me a map.
Okay.
One bag is enough to support us for one year.
Two bags for two years.
Stop calculating it.
You'll have plenty of chances to calculate it.
Not just me, but all of us.
Go that way.
Wait. Wait.
Xiangxiang.
For safety,
let's split up.
Give it to me.
Each of us has half of it.
See you at the gate at 4.
Okay.
You go this way. We go that way.
Four o'clock.
No suspicious people were found nearby.
I asked the villagers around.
They didn't find anything unusual, either.
They must have gone into the mountain.
It's hard to find them if there's no direction.
Here.
You know the route of their drug trafficking?
I got the information yesterday.
I heard that someone would sell
drugs from Hua City to Xian City.
There are many vital traffic routes between Hua City and Xian City.
I deliberately drove out one of the drug dealers
and led him to find the secret passage in the mountain.
So,
this is not an arrest,
but an entrapment operation.
Xi.
Come and eat.
I made a lot of delicious food for you.
Just see which one you like.
Come on. Sit down.
Think about
which dish you want to eat first.
I'll get you a rib first, okay?
Try it.
It's okay, Xi.
Your dad said he would come back to see you.
He will definitely do so.
He'll buy you a gift then.
Are you happy?
Just eat.
Let me peel a shrimp for you, okay?
Officer Yu.
Please get ready for the ambush
at the trading location.
Roger.
Long.
Why did you choose this road?
It's a shortcut.
Xiang has to walk a long distance through that road.
So we can arrive earlier than him.
So you're the boss.
Attention, all units.
Three minutes are left before the transaction time.
Long.
Xiang is inside.
Why did Xiang arrive earlier than us?