Hey.
Searching for him a thousand times in the crowd,
Suddenly turning around,
He is right here.
Check.
Okay.
Feeling energized.
Captain Lu.
We found the person who stole Zhu Jin's wallet.
It's a habitual thief named Wang Qingchun.
I've already asked Xiaoyu to send the info.
We're also investigating here.
Someone has
Wang Qingchun's entire theft process
all recorded.
Posted it on Weibo.
Now they've even followed
Wang Qingchun all the way home.
That's great.
Send me Wang Qingchun's home address.
Mm-hmm.
Alright.
Well...
If you get there first, just keep watch.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Once we're inside,
you knock out Zhang Tao from behind.
I'll go restrain Wang Qingchun.
After we kill them,
just toss them into the river.
Tell everyone
they both went back to their hometown.
If we wait until tomorrow morning,
and he turns himself in,
we're both screwed.
I don't care about my own life.
But your mom
still counts on you, her son,
to take care of her.
Let's go.
Looks like they've got two new partners.
Wait a second.
Let me see if I can get something juicy.
You are...
Hello.
Excuse me, have you seen this person?
Hurry up.
She's inside.
Come in.
Maybe let the lady come out instead.
Just a few words.
Or maybe wait inside.
She's in the bathroom.
It's fine.
I'll just wait here for her.
Don't move.
Zhang Tao.
Are you okay, Zhang Tao?
Zhang Tao, are you alright?
Is Zhang Tao okay?
He's fine.
We'll leave first.
No rush.
He's alright.
We'll leave first.
Officer.
Thank you.
You saved my life.
Thank me?
We should be thanking you.
Your photos were a huge help.
And...
So that means
you solved the case using my photos?
Glad I could help.
That's really great.
The one you secretly photographed,
the girl whose wallet was stolen,
is dead.
Dead.
Just...
the girl I photographed.
She was raped and then killed.
If...
If only I had called the police back then...
Wrap it up.
Finished eating.
Pay the bill.
Come on, come on.
Here I am.
Two hundred sixty-eight.
Who's paying the bill?
Give it to me.
I'll do it.
I'll pay.
No need.
No, let me.
Captain Lu, it's always you.
Look at you all.
You're all grown-ups.
Why fight over two hundred yuan?
What do you mean?
You looking down on us?
No, just hurry, someone pay.
Hurry up and pay.
Sis still has a bit of cash.
It's fine.
Looking down on me.
No, you all...
What are you doing?
Let's hang out together.
I don't know you.
Let go.
Release me.
Don't bully the girl.
I'm not bullying her.
I'm bullying you.
Don't touch me.
Don't touch me!
Let go.
Police.
Sit down.
Call the police.
Hello, is this 110?
Someone's causing trouble.
Everyone, stand straight.
That's great.
Really.
Acting bravely.
Really, really good.
Very good.
So nice.
No.
Well...
My attitude just now...
I was a bit harsh to you.
It's fine, really.
Sorry.
You're from the northeast?
Yes, from the northeast.
We'll eat at your place next time.
Sure, just come.
Right.
One more thing.
Who's paying this bill?
Two hundred sixty-eight.
Well...
Can we get a group deal?
Make it two hundred sixty.
Two hundred sixty.
I'll scan.
Where do I scan?
Here.
Ah.
What's going on?
The body is badly decomposed.
Not much useful info.
Samples have been sent for testing.
Where are Li Ya and Chen Minmin?
They're here.
Sorry.
Captain Lu.
There was traffic.
Fill them in on the situation.
Got it.
The body.
Found by a sanitation worker.
Most body parts have been found.
After testing,
it's a female.
Oh my god.
Another dismemberment case.
Can we estimate time of death?
Based on decomposition,
death was about three days ago.
For details,
wait for the autopsy report.
I'll head over first.
More body parts found over there.
From the right hand.
Wait for fingerprint analysis.
Any surveillance nearby?
This is a
old river to be renovated next year.
It's remote.
No surveillance.
Alright.
Let Xiaoyu check.
See if there's
recently
any missing women cases.
See if any match.
Okay.
Xiaoyu.
Crime scene photos.
Back.
Alright.
Captain Lu.
We've checked.
Recent missing women cases,
there are ninety-six.
Most of these cases
are mostly
due to running away.
Exported the data.
Wait.
Enlarge this photo.
The victim.
Except for the thumb,
the other four fingers
were all bent backwards.
She was abused before death.
At the finger wounds,
no repeated cutting marks.
The killer is likely male.
Oh.
Veteran cop is a veteran cop.
Captain Ji.
You're impressive.
This killer,
I've seen him.
That's right.
Thirteen years ago,
back then,
all fingers on this right hand
were bent backwards.
The victim was likely abused before death.
Come.
Look.
Broken fingers.
They're different,
but broken in the same way.
The cutting method is also the same.
At the wound,
there's no
sign of repeated cutting.
And
such a cruel criminal—
all these years,
I've only seen one like this.
Old Ji,
you've kept this case file all along.
Don't tell me
after all these years,
you still want to investigate this case?
This matter—
Back then, we had already identified the suspect:
Jin Weihua.
When we tried to arrest him,
he managed to escape.
This incident
has become a weight on my mind.
Captain Lu,
can we request a consolidated investigation?