I have something to tell you.
Sister.
So,
you are my brother Daxi.
You are a child of Snow Leopard Group.
After the accident,
you were the one who lived with me.
Later,
it became Daxi.
And
I became you again.
I'm sorry.
I came here
to find out about my family.
But I didn't expect
you're much braver than I thought.
No wonder.
Not only do you know French, you also know everything.
Besides,
a series of
beyond description.
You're awake.
Daxi.
It's me, sister. Are you okay?
Where's Tong Sheng?
He left.
Gone?
Why did he leave?
He doesn't live here.
Why is he here?
Do you want him to take care of you?
No.
You miss him?
Why didn't you tell me directly?
Didn't I tell you yesterday?
I want you to talk to me alone.
You're still teasing me when I'm sick.
You don't look like me at all.
You knew
Daxi is not your brother.
Daxi
My mother brought it back
from the orphanage.
But I always treat him
as my brother.
But he is actually my brother.
I didn’t expect Daxi
is the lost child of the Tong family.
I only found out recently.
My father has been secretly looking for him.
He kept this from me and Dong'an.
Can you
stop
between Wanqi and Snow Leopard?
Don’t worry. I’ll take care of the rest.
Although my memory hasn't fully recovered,
I promise
I won't let what happened yesterday happen again.
or let anyone bully you again.
But you have to promise me
no matter what happens in the future,
don't rush out first.
Remember,
You still have me.
Bai Yuchen.
I've sent someone to handle it.
Handle it? How?
Don't worry. I'm just giving him a lesson.
and make it public.
He should be ruined by now.
Have a good rest.
Don't worry about the rest.
Daxi.
Child.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Have a good rest.
I'll be back soon.
Dad.
Why did you suspend the merger?
What happened at the press conference
at the press conference.
I need to think about it.
Also,
the new legal department you hired
made a mess.
It's such a shame
What is this?
I need to review it.
So the project is suspended.
Dad, it's not like that.
By the way,
how is Tong Sheng's recovery?
I plan to let him take over.
He's fine.
Is there any conflict between you two?
Of course not.
There are many things between brothers
we should care about each other.
You need to know that.
Of course.
Okay, that's it.
Dong Dong.
You forced me.
Are you back?
I bought some medicine.
I'm almost home.
I want canned fruit.
I'll go buy it now.
Forget it. I'll buy it next time.
Come back soon.
Tong Sheng, how are you?
Tong Sheng.
I think
remember everything.
Let's go home.
Everything is clear.
Dad came back from abroad.
Chang Ming.
Tell me.
Dad, I don't know what to say.
Brother.
Shall I start with you?
Let's start with how
in his car.
No, Dad.
My men did this.
I just found out.
He has fled abroad.
I plan to go abroad and catch him myself.
and face to face.
I really didn't know about this.
I really don't know.
You have to trust me.
Be quick.
I don't want to see Tong Sheng after tomorrow.
Understand?
Yes.
Keep an eye on Tong Sheng.
If he has any signs of regaining his memory,
let me know immediately.
Yes.
Brother.
Stop pretending.
Be more decent.
Chang Ming.
After Tong Sheng had a car accident,
I asked Dong’an to investigate the whole thing.
Then you met Kim Daxi in the company.
you controlled him
and signed a contract that affects the company's interests.
and asked me to fire him.
so that you can take over the company.
You colluded with Wanqi Group.
Did I miss anything?
Tong Sheng.
You have to understand me.
The moment Kim Dae-hee entered our house,
Dong’an found that
we got the wrong person.
But he advised me not to expose Kim Daxi.
and don’t rush to meet him.
We did this
to give you another chance.
I've been waiting for you to stop.
to admit your mistake.
Dong An.
You're hiding so well.
I still can't defeat the Tong family.
Chang Ming.
I treated you like my own brother.
Just like Dong'an.
We're family.
I didn't expect you to be so cruel.
[Wuxi Co., Ltd.]
Eagle Eating Fish Film (Wuxi) Co., Ltd.
Big Wing Film (Dongyang) Co., Ltd.
Production company.
Product
Qi Ning Tong Huaizhou
Feng Zhong, Zhang Zuxian.
The production team.
Chief Producer Qi Youning Xu Jiaman
Executive Producer Tian Longfei
Producer Commander Qi Xiaolin
Producer Wang Dongdong
The director team.
Director Li Yongqin.
The chief editor-in-chief judge, Xu Jia Man.
Executive Director Xiao Peng
Liu Lu.
The audition team.
Acting director Li Xiaochao.
Vice director Guo Qitao.
Actors team.
Tong, Sheng, Hu Bowen.
Tong, An, Tong Huaizhou.
Qi, Shao, Du Rong Yi.
Mr. Qi, Qi Ning.
Bai Yuchen, Yu Yifu.
Yan Shu Qi Zun.
The owner of the fish stall, Li Dongdong.
Jin Daxi, Zhang Shuhan,
Fella B Xiao
Qi Shao’s fiancée, Xu Jiaman.
Jin Daxi's substitute Yu Jiayi
Colleague A Yang Nuo
Colleague B, Yu Li.
Colleague D Wang Hongchen
Secretary Zhao Hongwei.
Ren Feng.
Fatty, Gao, Yu.
Sisters B Yu Huang
Yang Jun from the internet cafe.
Network cafe Gangster C Sun Liao
Waiter, Zhang Bai Liang.
Game player A, Yang Yongfei.
Doctor A, Li Yongqin.
Personal doctor, Pu Jian Ping.
Security B, Shi Yunyu.
Steward Qi, Su Ke.
Reporter B, Zhu Yu.
Journalist C Jacky.
Girl A, Yu Qu.
Girl B Lin Shuqing
Participants of Snow Leopard Group.
Participants.
Jiang Wenlong, Sun Huanan, Han Mengnan, Yu Jiafeng. Zhu Jincheng, Huang Wenjie, Hao Jialei,
Qi Junhong, Cao Xiaoli, Shi Feiyan Li Xin, Yang Shuai, handsome, Ma Su Tiao, Pan Zhonghang.
Photography team.
Photographer Zhang Dongdong.
Camera A, focus. Cai, cool.
Li Xinghan, focus on B.
Photographer assistant Lin Haozhe
With the pilot, Fu Zhengwei.
Assistant Zhang Wencai.
Assistant Guo Chentao Niu Zifei
Art team.
Art instructor Liu Dafei.
The prop for the play, Li Cong.
The main focus of the prop is Yong Long Long.
The styling team.
The team leader, Li Huifang.
Makeup assistant Cui Jintong Xu Yuzhen Bai Jinrong
Costume assistant Wang Lu, Hu Jiang Chuan, Xiang Yu Xin
The recording team.
Recorder, Hsu Hwi.
The venue team.
Manager Yang Yong-fei.
Lee Jun-seung.
Driver team.
Car management, Zhang Xiaolong.
Peng Wenyu.
Xiamen SuperYingying Film and Culture Media Co., Ltd.
PR Director, Li Jiatong.
Video Planning, Wu Yu Lin.
Late production.
[Wang Simeng]
The project manager, Wang Simeng.
Editing instructor Zheng Shifei
Video production.
Subtitles producer Li Ang
Personor, Jing Mingrui.
Special effects production Li Ang
Voice production.
Kou Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Voice Producer Li Ti Xi
Music, Li Ti Xi.
Human voice editor Liu, Feng, Zhang Haoyuan.
Mix, Zhang Haoyuan.
Original music, Kou Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Jin Dahuan, DDD.
Qi Shaoyan Peng.
Bai Yuchen's wife and Hu Xiaoxian.
On the Riverside River of Wuxi,
One, become famous.