‪ADAPTED FROM A SHUQI.COM NOVEL
‪ORIGINAL AUTHOR: SENLIN LU
I pick you.
Judging by the wounds, she was whipped.
No…
No!
All this crying is ruining the mood.
Let me keep you company, sir.
You're new here, right?
Aren't you scared?
What good would fear do?
Survival comes first.
Instead of making a scene,
I might as well find someone dependable.
Interesting.
Are you up for a little game?
Only if you play by my rules first.
What game would you like to play, sir?
Your toy is certainly special.
Not as special as you, pretty lady.
My turn.
Sure.
Do you remember Hanxiao?
No.
Is that your name?
Wrong answer.
You get a punishment.
No!
Go away!
Come on.
Get back here!
Where are you going?
Lu Zhenglian?
LU ZHENGLIAN, LEFT GRAND REMONSTRATOR
Don't be petty, sir.
You're quite something.
There she is.
Get her!
XIUHONG HOUSE
Something's wrong.
With this qilin badge
bestowed by His Majesty,
I act on his authority. Let us through.
I've never heard of it.
You've got some nerve.
Get her!
Go ahead. Run.
Why aren't you running now?
Does it hurt?
Take my eye if you want,
but your life is mine to take.
You're an Inner Guard.
What are you doing here?
Can't figure it out?
Come with me
to the Palace Investigation Bureau
and think it over.
Tie her up with a rock and sink her.
No one's ever seen this woman.
But she's from the palace. Are you sure?
If she lives,
we'll all die.
Do it right.
- Who's causing trouble here?
- Sir.
Sir, they're trespassing.
We're from
the Palace Investigation Bureau.
Oh my.
My apologies.
The Wannian County offices
will fully cooperate
with the Inner Guards.
May I see your warrant first?
We tracked them all the way here.
There was no time for a warrant.
Without a warrant, our hands are tied.
- This is a private residence after all.
- We have no warrant,
only this qilin badge.
Who knows if that's even real?
- You clueless fool!
- I…
We ask for His Majesty's forgiveness!
- Let's split up.
- All right.
Didn't Jiang Tingwei tell you?
I'm not just an Inner Guard.
I'm also His Majesty's niece,
Princess of Fuchang County, Li Peiyi.
Things went wrong. Get everyone out.
Come out.
There's been a situation.
Gentlemen, I'm afraid
we must call it a night.
- Hurry, sir.
- Be quick.
- Come with me.
- You can play next time.
Why not pick someone to push me in?
That way, when His Majesty investigates,
only one of you
will die with your whole clan.
You. Do it.
Me?
But she's a county princess.
If you won't do it, we'll kill you too!
Relax.
Just give me a gentle push.
Hurry up. Be quick.
Get all the girls out. Hurry!
- Come out here! Over there!
- Come out!
Hurry up. Stop dawdling!
Hurry up!
- Move it!
- Hurry.
- Take everyone and come with me!
- Come on!
Your Ladyship! Your Ladyship!
Relax.
Just give me a gentle push.
The rest of you, come a little closer,
so I can remember all your faces.
If I die here,
at Xiuhong House,
you'll be the scapegoat they chose.
But if you save me,
I'll be in your debt,
and I'll repay your kindness.
- Any sign of her?
- No.
The back courtyard!
Officers, what are you looking for?
Official investigation. Step aside!
How dare you!
How weak do you think
the Palace Investigation Bureau is?
Arrest them!
- Where's that crazy girl?
- The back courtyard.
Boss.
Who did it?
It was him. He pushed Her Ladyship.
- We didn't do anything.
- Let him go.
Bring the rest
to the Palace Investigation Bureau.
I'll question them myself.
Thank you, Your Ladyship!
Check for hidden passages
and secret doors.
No one gets out.
Understood.
- To the storeroom.
- Yes.
XIUHONG HOUSE
- Prosecutor Gu.
- Left Street Inspector,
- why are you here?
- There's been an incident.
Your Ladyship!
Taozhi's in the secret room
behind the south wall
of the easternmost room
on the second floor.
Your Ladyship,
what are we looking for?
It's become an embroidery room?
Taozhi!
This belongs to Taozhi.
Less than two ke has passed.
Where could they have gone?
LONGXIANG NOODLES
The carriage.
The ward gates are closed now.
They can't have left Daozheng Ward.
Those men aren't ordinary people.
With all the residences
and taverns in the ward,
they won't be easy to find.
Mr. Gu, where did you see
the carriage? Show me.
Come with me.
Your Ladyship, we've only caught
a few workers and guards.
No sign of the others.
Tell Zhang Boyan
to search with Prosecutor Gu.
Look for a man with an injured left eye
and a few young girls.
They should be easy to spot,
unless someone is helping them.
But come dawn when the ward gates
open, they can be gone.
- Hurry.
- Understood.
"Birds die for food and people for money."
Is this bit of money really worth
your life?
Take the money.
Just pretend you never saw me, all right?
What kind of business do you run?
It must've been quite profitable.
Please, have mercy and let me go.
All right.
I'll let you go.
Thank you, sir.
Sorry,
I forgot I had an assistant with me.
Is there anything else
valuable in that bundle?
I already gave you all my money.
Sorry, but you'll need to come with me.
Move.
- Hand it over.
- What?
Evidence.
Wait.
LONGXIANG NOODLES
This is where I saw that carriage.
It took everyone away?
It was a large carriage
drawn by two horses,
wider than most by at least two chi.
They were in a hurry.
They must've squeezed everyone in.
Makes sense.
Come on.
Where are they?
I'm new here.
I just do odd jobs.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Didn't Your Ladyship come by before?
No orders were placed these last two days.
Who exactly are you looking for?
Think carefully.
They tried to drown me.
I can have you executed at any time.
The workers didn't know who you were.
They thought you were a thief breaking in.
But they do deserve
punishment for lynching.
I failed in my supervision.
I'll accept any punishment.
You're quite the stewardess,
eloquent and quick-witted.
With just a few words,
you've made all your faults
sound like mere poor supervision.
No matter.
I've seen your tricks.
You'll see mine
when you get
to the Palace Investigation Bureau.
I truly don't know
what Your Ladyship is talking about.
Where is Jiang Tingwei?
He's Mr. Sun's bodyguard.
You should ask Mr. Sun.
Fine.
FENG'S GROCERY
From here,
the carriage tracks are shallower.
Someone got off.
There should be eight women
under their control.
No way they'd let them
be seen out on the street.
The ones who got off here
must be the men Her Ladyship saw.
Where would they take my sister?
Mr. Gu, don't let worry
cloud your judgment.
The ward gates are closed.
They must be hiding
somewhere in the ward
that draws no attention.
On the west side of Daozheng Ward
are mostly taverns and brothels.
Residences are mostly on the east.
Judging by the tracks, they went south.
What if they're just circling around?
That man's got an injured eye.
I doubt he's in the mood
for tricks. Go ahead.
Let's go.
XIUHONG HOUSE
Care for some wine to warm yourself up?
I can't hold my liquor.
I'd better not drink.
Reliable as ever.
I'm not familiar with officials
from the old dynasty.
What should we do next?
I've been told the female musician
Remonstrator Lu favors
is at Swallow House.
Mr. Xiao, let's pay it a visit.
All right.
These old bones need rest.
I'm heading back.
I'll take those people back to the bureau.
Let's go.
Mr. Xiao, did we ever meet before?
Has Your Ladyship forgotten?
As an Astronomical Bureau official,
I rarely enter the palace.
So, did you ever
meet me before?
I don't remember.
SWALLOW HOUSE
You…
Easy…
This is Master Lu's private room.
Have you come to the wrong place, sir?
The night is lovely.
Remonstrator Lu, you seem
to be enjoying it to the fullest.
Who are you?
Someone wishes to see you.
PALACE INVESTIGATION BUREAU
Who came up with this alibi
for you, Remonstrator Lu?
I'm afraid I don't follow, Your Ladyship.
I went to Swallow House
at half past the You hour
and stayed in my private room
the whole night.
That's odd.
At half past the You hour,
I saw you at Xiuhong House.
Impossible.
I was at Swallow House the entire time,
listening to music and admiring
the moon with Liu Ying'er.
If I'm not mistaken,
you entered through the back door.
Only Liu Ying'er saw you, right?
So what?
That means, apart from her,
no one else can vouch for your story.
Quite the opposite.
Everyone at Swallow House
can vouch for me.
Liu Ying'er played a lovely piece,
but I thought the ending was a bit trite
and made some harsh comments.
She got upset, stood up, and walked away.
When I chased after her, I lost my footing
and tumbled down the stairs.
It caused a commotion.
A lot of people at Swallow House saw it.
When did you fall?
If it was after
the fifth ke into the Xu hour,
even if the whole Western Capital
saw you at Swallow House,
it means nothing.
Feel free to check, Your Ladyship.
I'm getting old. I can't remember clearly.
Your Ladyship, Consort Shu has arrived.
I didn't tell her anything.
Why is Your Highness
here so late at night?
Still risking your life
for an investigation, I see.
Eat this chicken soup before it gets cold.
You need to warm up.
This time, His Majesty
must reward Mr. Xiao properly.
It's the second time he's saved you.
Remember when you first entered the palace
and accidentally fell into the water?
He was the one who saved you.
Xiao Wenyuan brought him to the palace
for an audience with His Majesty.
His first time in the palace,
he got curious
and wandered to the Moonlit Pond,
where he happened to see you fall in.
He saved you.
He saved me?
Why has no one ever mentioned it?
His Majesty wanted
to grant him a great reward,
but Grand Tutor Xiao said
that with Huaijin about to join
the Astronomical Bureau,
being away from court affairs,
a great reward
would only invite suspicion.
He begged His Majesty to keep it quiet.
Your Ladyship, I can't draw
with you staring at me like this.
I just heard
that when you were a boy,
you saved someone from the Moonlit Pond.
Now that you mention it, I suppose I did.
You never spoke of it.
It's nothing to brag about.
Yes, I saved someone,
but I also got caught
sneaking into a palace courtyard
without permission.
I got a severe scolding and was grounded.
Don't you want to know who you saved?
The person I saved
wasn't Your Ladyship, was it?
That's right.
You saved my life, Mr. Xiao.
Really?
You rescued me
right after I fell into the water.
Did you see anyone else
nearby at the time?
Wasn't it an accident that you fell in?
I'm just curious as to where
my maids were when I fell.
There couldn't have been
anyone else around,
or I wouldn't have needed to rescue you.
Why are you leaning
so close, Your Ladyship?
I'm thinking about
how to repay your kindness.
No need for that.
Your Ladyship,
Remonstrator Lu flat-out denies
going to Xiuhong House yesterday.
Zhenniang and the workers
aren't talking either.
I see. You may go.
Yes.
In less than two ke,
they turned the storeroom
back to the way it was
and got everyone out of Xiuhong House.
They really are well-trained.
It's actually not that hard.
There were lamp grooves
built into all four walls,
but only three walls had grooves
blackened from use.
The innermost grooves
showed no signs of ever being used.
They never lit the lamps on that wall.
And while the floor was spotless,
there was a patch of dust
about four cun square
at the very back.
They must've stacked the looms
and sundries against that wall,
used a screen to hide them,
and rearranged the rest
of the room as needed.
If something unexpected happened…
There seemed to be plenty of items,
but they were all light.
Even the banquet tables and stools
could be mixed in.
Just a few people could reset
the room very quickly.
Xiuhong House is well-located
and has plenty of side doors.
The people likely slipped away
while we were arguing with the guards.
Strange.
Lu Zhenglian really
did fall down the stairs
at the second ke of the Xu hour.
Many at Swallow House saw it.
But he was whipping me
at Xiuhong House at that same time.
Does he have a double or something?
The staff at Swallow House
might have covered for him,
but I questioned
all the guests individually.
They couldn't all be lying.
Is there anything special
- about the second ke of the Xu hour?
- No.
Then why do they all
remember that exact time?
I'll go ask again.
Wait.
The ward gates are open now. Post this up.
It'll help Mr. Gu find them faster.
- What's this?
- A sketch of Jiang Tingwei.
I'll get an artist to make more copies,
so we can post them around Daozheng Ward.
How many do you need? I can draw them.
I need you to come with me
to Swallow House.
Leave the sketches to the artist.
MAP OF DAOZHENG WARD
Prosecutor Gu, I found Zhenniang
at a villa in Daozheng Ward.
Let's go.
It's still warm.
They can't have gone far.
After them!
Your Ladyship, you should hurry
to the front hall. Something's happened.
Let the old man deal with it.
I'm heading to Swallow House.
Inspector Du can't handle it alone.
He came for you.
- Sir.
- Any sign of suspicious people?
Other than earlier this morning,
not many people came or went today.
We checked everyone,
but no one matched the sketch.
Sir.
Where did this come from?
An hour ago, a wedding carriage went out.
Their maid gave these to us.
Who else was in that group?
There was one coachman,
four or five maids,
and two or three dowry attendants.
The bride was in the carriage.
That's right. One of the ladies
gave us the pastries.
We're escorting a bride.
Escorting a bride?
Go ahead.
Set up checkpoints at all city gates.
Spread the sketch around.
- Yes, sir.
What brings you here, Eunuch Guo?
Greetings, Your Ladyship.
Forgive my bluntness.
Is Left Grand Remonstrator
Lu Zhenglian being held
at the Palace Investigation Bureau?
Lu Zhenglian must really carry weight
for you to come all this way in person
just to get him out.
I didn't come of my own accord,
Your Ladyship.
His Majesty sent me.
This morning, His Majesty
summoned Remonstrator Lu to court,
but he never showed up.
His Majesty was furious.
Only later did he learn
Remonstrator Lu was being detained
by Your Ladyship
with no charges filed.
His Majesty wants him released,
but the Palace Investigation Bureau
won't let him go.
So I had no choice but to come ask
for an explanation.
Xiuhong House was running
a brothel in secret,
imprisoning former palace maids
and forcing them to serve guests.
Remonstrator Lu was there last night.
I can't release him.
But has he been convicted?
Are you here to supervise
my investigation, Eunuch Guo?
No, I wouldn't dare.
It's just…
If someone wants to bring this matter
before His Majesty,
then I'll make a trip with you.
Greetings from Li Peiyi to Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, please hear me out.
Last night at Xiuhong House,
I saw with my own eyes a secret brothel
where former palace maids
were forced into prostitution.
Hanxiao, the victim
of the "Flower on the Wall" case,
was likely imprisoned there as well.
I saw and heard it clearly.
Remonstrator Lu was present.
But I just can't find evidence
to convict him.
Your Majesty, this is truly unfair!
How dare you even say that?
You disguised yourself as a courtesan
and went to such a filthy place.
Do you care nothing
for your own reputation
or for the royal family's dignity?
So, Your Majesty believes
I haven't wronged Lu Zhenglian?
If Xiuhong House
has truly imprisoned palace maids
and run a secret brothel
serving the powerful,
they will be severely punished.
But you can't detain
a fourth-rank minister on your word alone.
- I'm searching for evidence.
- Then he isn't guilty for now.
Is Your Majesty shielding him?
What is
the Palace Investigation Bureau for, then?
What use are laws and regulations?
Your Majesty's attitude
is what truly damages royal dignity.
How bold you are! And you tried to dodge?
See for yourself.
After the commotion you caused last night,
how many memorials
have landed on my desk this morning?
I'm investigating
in accordance with the law.
I'm not afraid of their petitions.
The petitions aren't about you.
They're about Lu Zhenglian,
accusing him of neglecting his duties.
They want Your Majesty to intervene,
to let you know
I'm holding Lu Zhenglian
at the Palace Investigation Bureau?
Do you know why they dared
to join forces and submit
all these memorials?
Don't you think they know I favor you?
Don't you think they expected
you'd come here to tell me all this?
They dare threaten even Your Majesty?
This isn't a threat.
If there had been evidence, it would be.
But without evidence,
they're simply making a plea,
asking for justice
for a fourth-rank minister
they believe
has been wrongfully imprisoned.
They really are cunning.
I was too careless.
For now, Lu Zhenglian's only wrongdoing
is drinking and staying at Swallow House
on a workday.
I'll release him right away.
You're still going to investigate?
Of course.
Only by finding evidence
and convicting Lu Zhenglian
can I make things right for Your Majesty.
What do you mean,
"make things right" for me?
I misspoke.
Only then can I bring justice
for the palace maids
and restore the royal family's honor.
Enough. Get out!
How did it go?
Release Lu Zhenglian.
I'm afraid someone's
already come to collect him.
It's getting late. We need
to head to Swallow House now.
Your Ladyship, your arm needs tending,
or the wound could get infected
and leave a scar.
That's what I want.
Does this remind you of Hanxiao's scars?
Was Hanxiao abused
by Lu Zhenglian before she died?
We'll know once it scars.
They want evidence,
so I'll find it for them.
Mr. Xiao, you were right.
She's a lot like me, only crazier.
She doesn't care about her own well-being
or life.
She'll risk anything to solve a case.
I've been watching over her
all these years.
She's gotten into plenty of minor trouble,
but at least
she's made it this far in one piece.
Mr. Xiao,
I'm getting old.
It's time I retired.
I've put in my request.
Once it's approved,
I'll be leaving the palace.
I used to worry about her
getting into trouble without me around.
But now,
I think she'll be fine.
- Thank you for everything.
- Inspector Du,
I don't quite follow.
No need to say more.
You're a smart man.
If I go on, it'll sound
like a deathbed entrustment.
I don't want to jinx myself.
Deathbed entrustment?
Shouldn't you go after her?
She's nearly out of the palace now.
SWALLOW HOUSE
ROUGE AND LAUGHTER - SILK AND SONG
Excuse me. Coming through.
Here's your tea.
There was quite
a commotion here last night.
First time for us, too.
The boss was furious.
The worker involved was fired before dawn.
Remonstrator Lu fell down the stairs.
Why fire a worker?
Enjoy your tea.
Wait.
- What is this?
- Money for your story.
Will you tell me?
Here we have a prize called
"Hundred Birds Return to Nest."
It's the most expensive in the house,
worth 50 liang of gold.
That much?
On the third day of the fifth month,
at the second ke of the Xu hour,
Mr. Lu presents Miss Miao
with Swallow House's top prize,
"Hundred Birds Return to Nest"!
- Nice!
- Wonderful!
Announce it to the whole house.
- Yes.
- Hurry, go.
- The boss had us
- On the third day of the fifth month,
- go around the whole house, calling out,
- at the second ke of the Xu hour…
"On the third day of the fifth month,
at the second ke of the Xu hour,
Mr. Lu presents Miss Miao
with Swallow House's top prize,
'Hundred Birds Return to Nest!'"
Please welcome Mr. Lu!
Where is he?
Where is Mr. Lu?
But Mr. Lu never showed up.
Instead, Remonstrator Lu did.
Ying'er! Ying'er!
Let me explain. Slow down!
Ying'er,
slow down.
Move aside! Ying'er!
Let me explain, Ying'er.
- Ying'er, hear me out.
- Leave me alone!
- Master Lu!
- Remonstrator Lu's tumble
made quite a scene,
and everyone soon forgot about Mr. Lu.
Master Lu,
are you all right?
Mr. Lu spent a fortune,
but Remonstrator Lu stole the spotlight,
showing up at Swallow House on a workday.
What was meant to be a joyful event
ended up as a laughingstock
across Daozheng Ward.
So our boss told us
never to mention it again.
Is Mr. Lu a regular here?
No, he was new.
It was his first time here,
and he spent lavishly.
But I doubt he'll ever be back.
He won't be coming back.
In fact, I doubt this Mr. Lu even exists.
Do you keep a water clock here?
Ordinary businesses
can't afford a water clock.
Then how did your boss know
the time so precisely?
One of the staff
probably asked the night watchman
and reported it to the boss.
Enjoy your tea.
SWALLOW HOUSE
I've told you everything.
Remonstrator Lu stayed in his private room
until he was taken away.
That's the truth.
Even before His Majesty,
I'd say the same thing.
That's not what we're here to ask.
Last night, you and Remonstrator Lu
played music, admired the moon,
and composed poems.
The moonlight must have been beautiful.
It was.
The crescent moon
hung above the willow branches.
Master Lu even wrote lyrics for a piece,
"Mist shrouds a silver boat.
The moonlight crowns the flowers.
The heart is drawn
to the beauty."
Did he write these lyrics before he fell?
Yes.
After his fall,
he stayed on the couch to rest
until you arrived.
Have you noticed something?
I need to return
to the Astronomical Bureau to confirm it.
Who's there?
Remonstrator Lu, I've found
the evidence as you demanded.
Come with me once more.