ADAPTED FROM A SHUQI.COM NOVEL
ORIGINAL AUTHOR: SENLIN LU
The murderer slaughtered him
and didn't take any money.
Do you have enemies here?
We don't have much contact
with the locals.
But doing business is dealing with people.
How is that possible?
We sell Ping'en specialty to the south
and mostly deal with rural farmers
and southern merchants.
We never had to know the locals.
You know your family business quite well.
Madam.
Well…
Just say it.
Someone opened the side door
to Young Master's courtyard.
Mr. Xiao, shall we?
This place is unattended?
Of course it is.
But the bamboos keep dropping leaves.
So it's hard to keep it clean.
That's the side door over there.
A tragedy happened at home.
Instead of checking on Young Master,
you came to check the door?
I sent someone
to check on him this morning.
He's just fine.
What's so special about this side door?
Why did you panic?
Master minded the manor layout.
This door is here to gather energy.
No one is ever allowed to pass through.
Master even added a lock
with a mechanism
that only he can open.
Let's check on Young Master.
He's too weak to see guests.
WU MUJIN, YOUNG MASTER OF WU'S MANOR
Mother.
Meet Fuchang County Princess
and Astronomer Xiao.
They are our guests.
Greetings, Your Ladyship, Mr. Xiao.
May you be well, Mother.
May you find peace and solace.
When did you sleep last night?
Father asked me to go to bed
at the Xu hour.
So early? Can you fall asleep?
No.
But lying in bed
and watching the bamboo shadows
eventually puts me to sleep.
Do you burn incense in your room?
Young Master.
Did you sleep well last night?
The wind and rain
along with the thunder scared me.
I didn't sleep well.
Did you hear anything else
apart from the thunder?
I was awakened by thunder
in the middle of the night
and saw a figure.
Right there.
A figure?
It may have been too dark,
but did you make out
that person's height and build?
Did that person speak?
Young Master.
Did that person look like this?
You have to be his friend.
Mujin. You are amazing.
Do you want to avenge your father?
If you can recall
what that person looks like,
I'll catch him right away.
It was so dark last night.
How did you see a figure?
Did the room suddenly brighten up?
A big lightning bolt
made my room brighter than in the day.
So you did see that person.
I… I was going to see who that person was.
But the thunder followed.
I… I was scared.
I covered my ears and counted to ten.
The thunder finally stopped.
Then, the room went dark.
I didn't dare to go out.
Good boy. Go play.
Can you tell who it is?
No.
Why don't we see
any servants in the vast courtyard?
This courtyard is quiet
and adopts a geomantic formation.
Master didn't allow us to enter at will.
Even I can't come at will.
Only Mr. Zhong
gets to come and go
because his Four Pillars of Destiny
are compatible with this place.
He takes care of Mujin here.
Does Mr. Zhong burn incense in his room?
I checked it for you.
It also contains
that… that flower…
Did my uncle have
a deep affection for you?
We were more like family members
rather than a loving couple.
This child is not your own, is he?
You figured it out?
Mr. Xiao can even read the stars.
He noticed at a glance.
That's right.
I can't have children.
Master brought him back.
It wasn't easy for my uncle
to have a child.
But he kept the child
in this damp courtyard
just because you didn't like him.
What is it if it's not love?
Seeing him
does make me grieve over my misfortune.
But I didn't ask for him
to live here.
Mr. Wu arranged for it?
Mujin has always been weak.
Years of medication had no effect.
Then Master invited Mr. Xu
to design this place based on Feng Shui.
It's said to save his life
and boost his energy.
Who is this Mr. Xu?
Xu Daoyin owns a manor
in Qingtan Town near here.
Many people worship him.
Master also set up a scripture hall
for Mr. Xu at home.
Scripture hall?
Let's take a look.
Alright.
You don't have to come.
Wang will lead the way.
Understood.
Your Ladyship. This way.
Please look.
This is Mr. Xu's statue.
What are these jade tablets for?
Please don't.
These jade tablets
are tokens obtained
from worshipping Mr. Xu.
How do you worship him?
With money, naturally. To seek protection.
These jade tablets
have all been blessed by Mr. Xu
and placed here
to protect the household's peace
and fulfill Master's wishes.
That's quite a lot.
My uncle must have spent
most of the money he made on Xu Daoyin.
Well, Your Ladyship.
Be careful with words.
Mr. Xu, we pay our respects.
Please offer Mr. Xu an incense
to seek forgiveness.
-He found a way to make money.
-Indecent.
Y-Your Ladyship. What are you doing?
You have to respect the statue.
There's blood.
Blood?
My master was so pious to Mr. Xu.
Why would he hurt him with this statue?
This wooden statue is heavy,
consistent with
the estimated murder weapon.
The murderer hit the victim repeatedly.
He must be quite strong.
What Young Master saw last night
was staged by the murderer
with the wooden statue.
The courtyard is not on the way
from the scripture hall to the bedroom.
He went by on purpose.
There are many potential
murder weapons in the bedroom.
But the murderer chose
Mr. Xu's wooden statue.
He even went to wash it
and put it back after the murder.
He left us so many clues.
It feels like failing him
if I don't look into them.
Are you unwell?
That child's courtyard is cold and wet.
With so many bamboos inside out,
it gets no sunlight at all.
Does a courtyard like this
really save his life and boost his energy?
Something is wrong with the layout.
If he keeps living there,
he may perish in three years.
It's so dangerous?
The same object,
placed in different positions,
makes a world of difference.
Peach wood stake in the Li position.
Fire clashes with wood,
draining all auspicious energy.
The stone blocks
resonate with the bamboo grove,
unable to gather energy.
Given Wu Mujin's age,
he can't withstand this layout.
Wait.
I remember the stone in the courtyard
wasn't in the grove
but beside the peach wood.
The formation has been moved.
But the one who set it
never intended to protect Wu Mujin's life.
Xu Daoyin deceived my uncle?
I'm not sure.
But someone
wants Wu Mujin dead, while someone else
is trying to keep him alive.
I don't believe
a single stake and a few stones
could hold such power.
While they can't alter one's fate,
they can benefit the occupant
by creating a nice environment.
This harmful layout blocks wind and light,
greatly limiting vision and movement.
Even a healthy person
can't live here, let alone a child.
I see.
Gloomy courtyard. Winding corridors.
No sunlight.
I was there for less than a ke
and already felt a headache.
No wonder the child is sickly
and no tonic ever improved his health.
Mr. Xiao, are you feeling sorry for him?
How do you deal
with the pity for the people
involved in the cases?
All cases derive from nothing but desire.
Desire for love or profit.
A single thought can destroy others
and harm oneself.
I am only human.
How can I remain indifferent?
But if you want to keep doing your job,
you must learn to treat yourself
as someone else.
Treat yourself as someone else?
This is the method I came up with
to not suffer from caring too much.
When a case ends,
let that version of yourself
stay behind in that case.
Grieve and feel pity as much as you need.
But the you right now is another self.
You can stride forward
and move on to the next case.
Then, when the next case ends,
leave another self behind.
You are really clever.
Do you ever meet the selves
you've left behind?
Why would I meet them to double the pain?
I'm not doing this to myself.
If all the pain can be isolated,
then I hope you can stay further away
from your former selves.
What?
I said I'll try it next time.
Your Ladyship, I found
the medicine dregs in the grass
outside the victim's bedroom.
Dang Gui, cinnamon,
Sichuan lovage,
Achyranthes root, plantain seed,
and safflower?
This recipe looks so familiar.
It's the Tuohua Decoction.
-To induce labor?
-That's right.
In this prescription,
Dang Gui and Sichuan lovage
are blood-activating.
The amounts of the herbs
in the medicine dregs
far exceed the normal dosage.
If the dosage of these two herbs
is not properly controlled,
it could cause fatal bleeding
during labor.
The Imperial Medical Office
has prohibited its use
for many years.
But the herbs in this prescription
are easy to find.
The authorities are far away.
The folk people
still induce labor with it.
Something happened at Wu's Manor.
Madam Wu claimed to suspect Wu Mujin
and moved him out of the courtyard
and had people search the courtyard.
Didn't I ask you to protect Wu Mujin?
-How did this happen?
-Where did he move to?
A guest room right next
to Madam Wu's bedroom.
She said she'd put him
right under her nose
so that he couldn't cause trouble.
Why did she suddenly
grow suspicious of him?
Because only Young Master's
incense doesn't contain
Datura flower.
Thus, Madam decided that he was involved.
He's such a feeble child.
How could he kill someone?
Isn't this ridiculous?
Let her be.
Magistrate Wen.
When will your messenger
come back from the Western Capital?
It will be tonight at the earliest.
Your Ladyship.
Our years of friendship
have gone to waste?
You went and found an outsider
for the investigation?
Your Ladyship. Wuren insists on coming.
What do you mean?
-That messenger won't be here until night.
-I…
Magistrate Wen.
Coming.
Your Ladyship.
-Get me a horse.
-Understood.
Your Ladyship. Where are we going?
To Qingtan Town.
Find Xu Daoyin.
SEE SIMPLICITY AND EMBRACE PLAINNESS
For the Heaven-Inquiry Ceremony,
line up at the gate.
We came on behalf
of Wu Siping from the Ping'en County.
Distinguished guests.
Forgive me. Please follow me.
This way, please.
Mr. Xu is preparing for the ceremony.
Everyone. Please rest
in Mr. Wu's courtyard.
Someone will lead you
to your seats for the grand event.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
He has a courtyard in this manor.
He's spent a fortune here.
But how did you figure out
where the door is?
Wu's Manor adopts a geomantic formation.
Mr. Xu's manor
must have followed the same design.
The manor leans against the mountain,
and the layout follows the concept
of the Big Dipper.
The whole manor is, in fact,
a massive geomantic formation.
What about the side gate?
The side gate we passed through
is the Gate of Life within this formation.
So there must be another exit
besides the main gate.
The mechanism wins your recognition.
Mr. Xu does have some skills.
How do you know I took a jade tablet?
I've been around you long enough to tell.
Reading the stars again?
I'm used to watching the stars
as soon as night falls.
Aren't you tired of it
after so many years?
Not at all.
They like my old friends.
We communicate without talking.
Is that so?
I want to talk to them, too.
What do you want to say to them?
I bet they know all the secrets.
They've seen all kinds of crimes and sins.
Culprits and thugs hit the road at night.
I thought you could be romantic.
In the end, it's still about cases.
I'm not in the mood for romance.
My mind won't be at ease
until I find an answer.
I wonder if my father
ever told the stars his worries.
Do you remember
that the stars have helped us many times?
Ask sincerely
and they'll offer you the answer
one day.
So I wasn't sincere enough?
It just takes time. They may
make mistakes in their busy days.
Why did you study astronomy
at the Astronomical Bureau?
I became an investigator
to figure out the truth.
Why did you become an astronomer?
For…
a promise.
To whom?
An old friend.
It seems that you are
also trapped in the past.
I hope the stars can solve all confusions
and help those trapped in the past
move forward.
Any progress?
Nothing.
The manor is full of twists and turns.
We almost got lost.
It seems that the whole manor
resembles Wu Siping's courtyard,
full of twists and turns.
Why is that?
Mr. Xu set up this layout.
More importantly,
they don't want outsiders to walk around.
This place hides a lot of secrets.
It should have an unobstructed view,
but except for Wu Siping's courtyard,
everything is covered by trees and bamboo.
We can't see anything.
That's right.
We made a big circle along the mountain
and found nothing.
The manor is so meticulously designed.
He also managed to earn
the deep trust of Wu Siping
and make a fortune.
It seems this Mr. Xu
is no ordinary charlatan.
We'll see him
at the Heaven-Inquiry Ceremony.
That is Xu Daoyin?
XU DAOYIN
Why is the ritual bell hanging in the air?
What's going on?
Mr. Xu is making inquiries.
‎What's happening?
-His head…
-It really works?
First attempt to ask about fortune.
Second attempt to ask about fortune.
-His head is gone!
-His head is gone.
Mr. Xu is quite something.
Where did he go to make inquiries?
He moved. He's still alive.
-Oh no.
-Something went wrong.
Don't panic, everyone.
Please.
Listen to me.
Mr. Xu
was summoned to Heaven.
He will be back.
Someone. Open the gate.
Everyone, please get some rest.
Once Mr. Xu is back,
we will inform you.
Be careful.
Dear guests. Please go back and rest.
Step aside.
Who dares to stop the investigation?
A mechanism.
Such a horrible death.
It was a murder.
The incision in the neck
is very flat.
Only an extremely sharp blade
can achieve that.
But the altar was in plain sight.
There was no blade.
Such a neat cut
is beyond human power.
Human head. Mr. Xiao, don't look.
Who is it?
This is Lady Yue.
Mr. Xu's immortal companion.
I only heard that Mr. Wu
invited distinguished guests.
I didn't expect it to be Your Ladyship.
Forgive me for the negligence.
Things went wrong at the ceremony
and frightened Your Ladyship.
I will handle this.
Please go back and inform Mr. Wu.
Mr. Wu is dead.
Has Mr. Xu ever offended anyone?
I don't understand your question.
The Heaven-Inquiry Ceremony
connects people with the gods.
If the gods are displeased,
they may punish
the mortals.
Save your story
for those followers
who spent a fortune here.
One more lie,
I'll send you and this dead man
to the afterworld.
Don't forget.
Mr. Xu could be dead by now.
Don't you care about him?
This person is named Liu San.
He is Mr. Xu's protector.
Protector?
He was merely a stand-in
for Xu Daoyin's "miracle" performance.
At the start of the act,
Xu Daoyin
stood in front of this curtain,
which had a hook on it.
He put the ritual bell on the hook.
The dark curtain
blended with the moonlight,
making it appear as if
the bell was floating mid-air.
Liu San, dressed in identical robes
and wearing a face cover
matching the curtain's color,
stood behind it.
During the spray of molten iron sparks,
the two swapped positions.
Xu Daoyin
stepped onto the platform behind,
revealing his face above the curtain,
while Liu San remained
on the altar as the "body."
With the play of light, shadow, and smoke,
to the audience down the hill,
it looked like Xu Daoyin's head
had separated from his body.
Xu Daoyin's head
disappeared during the spray
of molten iron sparks.
A moment later, blood spurted out
from Liu San on the stage.
Did Xu Daoyin kill Liu San?
No. Liu San was really decapitated.
It's more complicated
than changing positions.
This is the murder weapon.
Copper wire?
They didn't use a knife.
Instead…
Have you heard of people
getting hurt by a kite string?
Some things
are more dangerous than we imagine.
Both these pillars
show signs of rope wear.
Although all pillars are tied
with thin ropes
for gauze curtains as decoration,
these two have
the most prominent wear marks.
They were likely pulled by a heavy force.
When the mechanism was triggered,
the rope moved rapidly,
and the sharp copper wire hidden inside
was enough to sever a head.
Someone set up the copper wire
before the ceremony.
Let's check the back.
This is from Mr. Xu's clothes.
No blood here.
So he was likely just abducted.
There's more than one perpetrator.
Not necessarily.
The culprit could seize the moment
when the guests
were distracted by the iron sparks
to abduct Xu Daoyin
and pull the switch to activate
the mechanism on the altar
to kill Liu San.
Whoever designed
such an intricate mechanism could have
carried this out alone
if he timed it right.
Involving more people might bring trouble.
Who designed the mechanism on the altar?
Mr. Xu, of course.
But the mechanisms are heavily guarded.
Only Mr. Xu and Liu San had the key.
We've never been inside.
Your Ladyship.
Let's save him first.
He's still missing.
Once I find the killer, Mr. Xu is safe.
These four guard the entrance
from the manor to the altar.
Xiao is in charge of the mechanism tower.
Have you seen anything unusual?
-No.
-Are you sure?
Xiao. What about yesterday?
I…
I've been here watching.
I check it every day.
Last night, I checked one more time.
When Liu San went in with Mr. Xu today,
I was watching this door.
I didn't see anyone suspicious.
Xiao. Mr. Xu treated you well.
If you neglected your duty
and got Mr. Xu killed,
I wouldn't let you off.
I-I have a clear conscience.
Let's meet Her Ladyship.
Xiao.
It's hard to hide out there.
To enter the tower,
they have to pass by Xiao.
Unless…
The incense?
Yes. More Datura flowers.
Xiao. Did you burn this incense?
My daughter made me a repellent sachet.
I never use incense.
Think carefully.
Were you feeling sleepy, dizzy,
or a bit drowsy?
No.
He didn't enter the tower?
None of the servants
in the Wu's Manor admitted
that they fell asleep.
The person who killed
Wu Siping and Liu San
and abducted Xu Daoyin
is likely the same individual.
This person has free access
to the manor and the Wu's Manor
without drawing attention.
He's either from the manor
or a martial artist from outside.
It's easy to find a traitor.
But the outsider could be anyone.
Did Wu Siping and Xu Daoyin
have a common enemy?
They were all compassionate and kind.
Why would they have enemies?
Bad news.
Lady Yue, bad news.
-Someone broke into the Vitality Hall.
-Vitality Hall?
It's just a place in the manor.
Since someone broke in,
we have to take a look.
Well…
Let me take care of it.
It's just a trivial matter.
Nothing is trivial here.
The killer is still at large,
likely waiting to do more evil.
Keep looking for Xu Daoyin.
We'll go to the Vitality Hall.
VITALITY HALL
The Vitality Hall
mostly houses young women.
This may be inconvenient.
Please stay.
Won't you ask about it? Someone broke in.
Liu discovered it.
But that person has run away.
What about the baby?
It was a bit of a shock. Nothing serious.
Scared, huh?
Tell me everything. I'll do you justice.
Be quiet.
Don't shout.
‎-Be quiet.
‎-Okay.
Come with me. I won't hurt you.
Be quiet. Be quiet.
Help. Help.
What's wrong?
Get him.
So deep.
Trace the blood.
There's blood here.
Still wet.
Here too.
He ran that way.
Let's go.
You took medication?
To calm the nerves and protect the baby.
We have it all the time.
No.
What do you smell?
There are too many smells in this room.
Fine, rest first.
Why are there so many pregnant women here?
Mr. Xu took them in.
Some women come from poor families.
Some were unmarried but got pregnant.
For some reason,
they couldn't have the baby at home.
Mr. Xu took these poor women in
and found good people
to adopt their children.
Xu Daoyin was too kind
to just take in these few, right?
Orphans, the elderly, homeless people,
those with illnesses or disabilities.
They all need shelter.
Can this manor really house so many?
Mr. Xu also took care of those people.
He just didn't
accommodate them in the manor.
So he was kinder
to a certain group of people.
Have you mobilized everyone?
Be sure to find Mr. Xu
before Her Ladyship.
Everyone is out. Dead or alive.
Don't make any mistakes
about the delivery tonight.
We're all set. Nothing will go wrong.
Pack up everything.
If Mr. Xu really…
Rest assured.
I've contacted the boat
leaving Qingtan Town.
If Mr. Xu is dead,
we'll wrap up this deal tonight
and get out of this manor
within an hour.
He got away.
We deserve punishment.
It's understandable.
This manor seems to have
many secret passages.
Xu Daoyin is not the only one
who masters mechanical techniques.
Your Ladyship.
Lady Yue prepared a meal for you.
She's so thoughtful. Thank her for me.
She is grateful for your help
and told us to look after you.
The servants are at the door.
Tell us if you need anything.
It's wise to be cautious of people.
Xu Daoyin's immortal companion
can't be a simple woman.
It seems tonight
is destined to be restless.
How do you know?
Persimmon.
I don't know whether it's good or bad.
Anything bothering you?
No.
I'm waiting,
just as you said.
Look at the Alkaid.
It's too far away. I can't see clearly.
Do this.
See through this.
Now I see it.
If waiting doesn't work,
you can take some measures.
Any wise advice?
It's getting late.
Go to bed.
VITALITY HALL
I am Madam Wu's servant Wu Lie.
Greetings, Your Ladyship.
Please help her.
Wait outside. Play it by ear.
Harder.
-It comes out!
-Your Ladyship.
Almost there.
Harder.
The baby is coming out.
Get her up.
Why is Liu giving birth so much earlier?
-She was probably shocked.
-Harder.
It's bloody in here.
Please wait outside.
-Shocked? She should rest.
-Almost there.
-Why are you pushing her to give birth?
-Almost there!
Hold her now.
Have the medicine.
Stop it. Don't you hear me?
The baby is coming out. We can't stop.
Hurry up.
Hold her.
Beginning of the Hai hour.
He's born.
-He's born.
-Come with me.
He's born.
She's bleeding. Hurry.
Hurry.
Give me that.
What's going on?
Stop the bleeding.
Your Ladyship.
Let's leave it to the midwives.
-Why can't you stop the bleeding?
-Look!
Hurry.
It doesn't stop.
She's dead.
VITALITY HALL
Your Ladyship is kind.
Unfortunately,
Liu was too weak.
I don't think you care about her at all.
That's a serious accusation.
The Vitality Hall
was set up for the poor mothers.
Of course, we care about them.
Tuohua Decoction.
Strong medicine.
A slight mistake can make
a delivering mother bleed to death.
The Imperial Medical Office
has prohibited its use.
Did Liu go into early labor due to shock,
or did you induce her labor?
She was the one with the child.
We could only deliver the baby
when she was ready.
I know the Tuohua Decoction
can't be abused.
But once a woman is pregnant,
the child's life weighs more than her own.
She told us to prepare
the Tuohua Decoction
and asked us to save the child,
even at the cost of her life.
Since you're innocent,
then why did you poison our food?
No, I didn't.
All the ingredients I prepared
are top quality.
If you don't believe me,
take the dishes
to the yamen for inspection.
You're right again.
Lady Yue is really skilled and bold.
At this point,
she can still respond calmly as usual.
Roast mutton with veratrum
instead of scallion.
And ginseng-infused medicinal liquor.
You've mastered
the "Eighteen Incompatibilities."
What a pity.
I've learned from the best.
She knew the food incompatibilities
much better than you.
You intended to murder me
and used banned drugs
to kill the woman in labor.
What are you trying to do?