(Salt Gang's Headquarters)
On the eighth day,
the Chai family and Zijin Hall
will settle our feud
at Yunshui Manor in Jiangzhou.
Years of grievances
will lead to a battle.
Dan Xingbian
claims righteousness
in the martial world
but is a mere delusional fool.
Flaunting his imperial connections,
he's grown intolerably arrogant.
I've heard recently
he plans to quit martial arts
to focus solely on chess and painting.
His "five crafts and eight trades"
are street-level lackeys.
(Chai Yu, the Chai family's head)
They wallow in false peace
and complacency.
Lord Chai,
my porridge should be ready.
If we keep talking,
it will grow cold.
If I bring it in to eat,
that would be impolite.
You, Hu Qianshou,
fear impropriety?
I came to your private chambers,
yet couldn't even see your face.
This crippled form
requires a privacy screen.
First,
it shields me from drafts.
Second,
a maimed man prefers not to be seen.
Lord Chai, you descend
from imperial bloodlines
and are a leader of our era.
Don't stoop to my level.
Let me be blunt.
When my family clashes with Zijin Hall,
will your Salt Gang
side with anyone?
(The Legend of Heroes)
=Duel on Mount Hua=
(Adapted from Jin Yong's novel,
The Legend of the Condor Heroes)
=Eastern Heretic and Western Venom=
=Episode 3=
Lord Chai,
I'm no martial artist.
I possess no fighting skills.
My allegiance means nothing.
Your Salt Gang's wealth rivals kingdoms.
Don't speak of wealth—
you'll get me killed.
Why hoard such fortune then?
The Salt Gang deals
in contraband salt.
This illicit trade
breeds enemies.
The imperial court opposes us too.
The imperial court
is our mutual foe.
Why not form an alliance?
Our situations differ.
You antagonize the imperial court,
while the imperial court antagonizes me.
The Salt Gang must
navigate dangerous margins.
You must
excuse my candor.
Let me mention several incidents.
Ponder these carefully, Master Hu.
Last October,
the Grand Treasury's
Left Repository
saw seven officials die overnight.
All poisoned.
Two summers past,
Mingzhou's vice-prefect drowned himself.
Yet when retrieved,
his head and body were separated.
Five days ago,
Bazhou's new vice-prefect,
Feng Youlan, vanished.
Presumed dead.
Master Hu,
if you refuse aid,
the Chai family will war
with your Salt Gang.
Lord Chai.
Lord Chai!
Lord Chai, Master Hu is calling you.
Close the door.
(Hu Qianshou, Salt Gang Leader)
Stop hiding.
Face me directly.
Lord Chai, please go ahead.
My family and Zijin Hall
both harbor your spies. Correct?
Your profits
partly grease imperial palms,
while the rest
are spent on your family
and Zijin Hall.
Otherwise,
how could the Salt Gang survive
between court and martial factions?
(Qi Qing, the Chai family's warrior)
Among Qi Qing,
(Tie Lin, the Chai family's warrior)
Tie Lin,
(Tie Mu, the Chai family's warrior)
and Tie Mu
outside the door,
who's your man?
You came to visit me
and brought three of the Chai family's
six elite fighters with you.
Or are the three all your men?
True elite fighters
can't be bought with money.
Lord Chai,
you're overly suspicious.
I've made myself clear.
I won't leave without reason.
Your Primordial Celestial Qi Art
has reached the seventh layer.
(Shi Xing, Salt Gang Leader's Aide)
Here's my proposal.
If the Chai family
clashes with Zijin Hall,
I'll side
with the Chai family.
Among Zijin Hall's
five crafts and eight trades,
who's your mole?
Exposing them
would endanger their lives.
We all just want to earn some money.
Fine.
My people in both factions
will follow your commands.
Agreed?
On the eighth day,
I'll meet Dan Xingbian.
Before that date,
half of Zijin Hall's
five crafts and eight trades will die.
Lord Chai,
you overestimate me.
Two from the eight trades
died in Ba County.
Five remain in Jiangling City.
If I didn't value you,
why would I make this personal visit?
Then let one more die today
to prove my loyalty to you.
Deal.
Safe travels, Lord Chai.
I'm crippled
and can't see you out.
Farewell.
Go to Lin'an and inform Dan Xingbian
that Chai Yu has visited me.
The Chai family
will war with Zijin Hall.
And I'll support Zijin Hall.
Master, are you certain
about joining this conflict?
It's not direct involvement.
The elites I planted in both factions
exist for such occasions.
After the eighth day,
the Chai family will vanish
from the martial world
along with Zijin Hall.
Only our Salt Gang will remain.
Understood.
It's cold.
The message from Kuizhou.
(Letter)
Well?
You need to tell me anyway.
The Young Leader is dead.
Explain clearly.
Master,
your son,
Hu Baili, has died.
What else?
Seventeen is arriving shortly
with Young Leader's body.
Next time the porridge cools,
you'll die.
Understood.
(Jiangling)
Let's go.
Bravo!
Punch him!
Why staring at me?
Stop gawking! All of you!
It's nothing.
We've never seen you
look like this before.
Don't stare anyway.
You're dressed so beautifully
yet forbad anyone to look.
Why?
This isn't for your eyes.
Watch out.
My dress.
Pan.
It's our young lady. You've seen right.
My lady, two people are at Cuihua House
accompanied
by a scholar-looking stranger.
We never saw him in Kuizhou.
Were the Five Elders summoned?
Elder Fu of Hat-making is in Pengze.
He should arrive.
As usual, nobody follows me.
My lady!
Only two Westerners remain.
Even if Ouyang Feng is skilled,
if we attack together,
we could eliminate them.
Why must you...
Why must what?
Why bother inviting the Five Elders?
It's complicated.
Complicated? My lady, please do explain.
Does this outfit look bad on me?
You look beautiful no matter what.
My lady,
I think it's best if our group
stays by your side for now.
After all,
I killed one of the Westerners.
If Master Dan truly blames us,
Pan Jie can't bear it.
My lady,
how complicated is it really?
To put it simply,
I just want to mess with Ouyang Feng.
(Cuihua House)
Good!
- Small!
- Big! Big!
This is
way too lively.
Want to play?
Mr. Ouyang,
how about we find a quiet place to rest?
We're already here. Let's explore.
Only the South has such places
in all the realms.
Let's go.
Yaoshi.
Inside the carriage?
There's also a woman.
The 'undying body' Young Leader
brought back from Mount Ba.
A final act of his filial piety
to you before dying.
Open it.
My son died at the Kuizhou branch.
Why did you bother to return?
Master,
it's to let you
understand the full story
before I leave for good.
Go ahead.
Young Leader obeyed your order to ambush
and kill Bazhou's new vice-prefect,
Feng Youlan, at Mount Ba.
Feng Youlan was killed,
but his daughter jumped off a cliff.
Young Leader searched the cliff base
and found her miraculously alive.
Her body emitted a scent
that repelled insects.
She could even jump up and run.
Continue.
Young Leader was filial.
Understanding your health,
he brought this woman to the branch,
planning to send her to Jiangling
for your examination.
Following Young Leader's pigeon message,
I went to kill the Westerners.
I failed the task,
and the garrison arrested them.
So I brought their belongings
back to the branch.
At nightfall,
a sorcerer came to retrieve the luggage
and killed your son.
Sorcerer?
Master,
I have never seen anyone
with martial arts at such heights
or even heard of any.
No martial arts
could reach such heights.
He was with the Westerners?
Yes. We encountered them
at the post house.
Their leader is Ouyang Feng.
His martial arts are good too.
Anything else to add?
Leader, two more points.
That sorcerer and this woman
must be lovers.
At the post house,
the sorcerer fed her pills.
Her survival from the fall
must be connected to him.
Seventeen!
Deng Zhao!
Master,
Deng Zhao is our Kuizhou branch member.
I...
I ordered him to track the sorcerer
and Ouyang Feng.
Master.
Let him in.
Seventeen.
Master.
Go ahead.
The sorcerer and two Westerners
arrived in Jiangling's
Cuihua House.
Go to Cuihua House
and tell that sorcerer to come here.
To headquarters?
Didn't you claim
he's involved with that woman?
Don't disrupt business.
Just make him come alone.
Understood.
The tiles
must be revealed
from bottom to top bit by bit.
- This is the fun of Pai Gow.
- Right.
Revealing them all at once
ruins the suspense.
Exactly. You don't know how to play.
Did I win?
You get a pair of Red Heads.
Third smallest, reversed.
But it's fine.
Want to raise by ten coins?
- Yeah.
- Go ahead, raise it.
Gotta raise the stakes.
But mine is small.
Well. Mine might be even smaller.
Right. Exactly.
Deal. Ten more coins.
Such boldness.
Blow! Blow!
Call! Call!
Call!
Double celestial pair.
Second highest straight.
You tricked me?
Honor your losses.
Well? Enjoying this?
If you're good, beat me then.
Exactly.
Again.
Do you have someone you care about?
I do.
He died at Kuizhou Yamen.
Three of us came from the West.
Lie died. Only two remain.
With you, we become three again.
You are nothing.
But Young Master likes you.
You make him happy.
Entering South improved his mood.
Killing you might be better.
But I fear upsetting him.
Human hearts are too complex.
Too complicated.
From Kuizhou
to Jiangling, it's a three-day journey.
But my son's corpse shows no decay.
You caused this.
I'll untie you.
Can you move?
Can you speak?
In my youth, I visited Mount Ba.
There,
cliffs tower hundreds of feet.
How could anyone survive such a fall?
Sorcerers don't exist in this world.
The person
who gave you the pills—what's his name?
How did he save you?
Don't move. Stay still.
I know a bit
about alchemy poison.
To get the best alchemy poison,
there are two methods.
First,
you need vast wealth.
Second,
extensive time commitment.
Don't move. Stay still.
I beg one thing of you.
Go ahead.
Kill me.
All actions bear consequences.
Your father died by my son's hand,
and my son
was killed by the one
who gave you the pills.
He'll arrive shortly.
You'll meet him.
I'll make him
pay with his life for my son's.
Want to raise again?
Did you see the tiles?
No.
Even if you did, it's nothing.
I didn't see them.
I trust you.
How much?
Bring a gold ingot.
- Young Master...
- Bring it.
Youngster,
gambling shouldn't be about wealth.
I don't want wealth.
Then why?
I can't accept this.
You come from wealth.
You can't handle failure
and are too arrogant.
This ruins both wealth and health.
Gambling hates overcompetitiveness.
I won't play with you.
You Southerners have no backbone.
Then let's gamble.
Don't mention North or South.
One gold ingot.
You dare?
The stakes are too high. I'm panicking.
Forget about the gold.
Let's just add ten more coins.
How's that?
Scared, are we?
I've never feared anything in my life.
Reveal the tiles.
- Is it big?
- Ask him.
Is it big?
Double celestial.
Same as my previous hand.
Second highest straight.
Don't show off again.
Who showed off?
Show your tiles!
I'm about to lose my entire fortune.
Blow! Blow! Blow!
Call! Call! Call!
Youngster,
my apologies.
Ultimate Treasure.
You'd see this maybe twice
in a year of gambling.
You lost again.
You...
You just inhaled my secret concoction,
Three-Day Spiritbane.
I was pondering
whether to come in.
I'm Hu Qianshou.
And you?
Huang Yaoshi.
Yaoshi?
Yaoshi, do you wish to let her live?
I do.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't have saved her in Ba.
How did you save her?
I realigned
seventy-plus broken bones
in her body
and fed her two Ninefold Yin Pills.
Ninefold Yin Pills?
I accidentally concocted them years ago.
Only seven existed in this world.
Now only
five remain.
To save her,
would you die?
Why force this choice?
I bear her no enmity.
But you killed my son.
Since he's already dead,
don't dwell on it.
Dwelling changes nothing.
Letting go brings peace.
That makes sense.
Take me with you.
I told you at the post house.
I can't take you.
Forget it.
Then why did you return?
My sworn brother Ouyang Feng said
I should meet you.
Your earlier words made sense.
Since my son is already dead,
there's no need for dwelling.
Dwelling changes nothing.
If you truly believe that,
that's great.
I vowed long ago to stop killing.
Back then,
it was truly unavoidable.
Are you truly
not involved with her?
My men told me that.
We're mere strangers who crossed paths.
Including now,
this is only our third meeting.
Then I retract my earlier words.
Let me reframe this.
To let her live,
will you kill your sworn brother
Ouyang Feng?
Why insist on forcing choices?
Because no one here can stop you.
And you refuse to take her away.
Earlier,
I used my Three-Day Spiritbane on her.
By the Chou hour, she'll forget
everyone she ever knew.
Tomorrow, she'll forget who she is.
By this time the day after,
her soul will scatter.
Before Chou hour, bring me
Ouyang Feng's head.
I'll detoxify her and let her leave.
And then all debts are erased.
I, Hu Qianshou, keep my word.
Go.
Heavens!
I'm leaving.
Go then.
I won't be coming back.
Never return here.
It's best to forget those
I remember in this life.
Soul scattering is even better.
In this world,
is there anything
you need me to do for you?
Just one thing.
Don't listen to him
to kill your sworn brother.
Live well in this world
as long as you can.
Someone
once said the same words to me.
Word for word.
Go now.
This is farewell.
What's your name?
Feng Heng.
Go, go, go!
Step right up! Place your bets.
No changes after the final call!
Bet! Bet! Bet!
Big! Big! Big!
Big or small? Bets closed!
My luck is unstoppable today.
Let's all enjoy this.
You kid.
Thank you, Lord Chai.
This brat's generous.
Here, take it.
Young master, these Southerners
are shameless cheats.
Losers pay gracefully.
We're being honorable.
Youngster, you're decent.
I like you.
Let's burn this den of thieves,
slaughter these shameless rats,
take the gold back, and go.
Where's Yaoshi?
Why care about him?
Just burn it all and reclaim our gold.
Then I'd be no better
than the scoundrels.
Exactly.
Today's been fun.
I'm content.
Keep these two gold ingots.
Let's play again.
Off we go. No more games.
Mongrel, trying to flee?
What did you say?
Return the gold.
Another round.
Last two ingots. Three straight wins?
I refuse to believe it.
You little brat with a filthy mouth.
We'll settle this later.
Fine. Let's see you escape now.
Youngster, what's your name?
Ouyang Feng.
I'm Chai Qiong.
Today I'll satisfy you
and teach you a lesson.
Deal the tiles.
Stop laughing.
Is my hand big?
Sir,
you've got twin High Steps.
Only Zero Mist loses to this.
Heaven help me.
Help me.
Please don't let it be the smallest.
Blow! Blow! Blow!
No more blowing.
Ultimate Treasure!
Dominates all!
So ecstatic.
I'll slaughter you all...
Sit.
Want to bet three horses?
Purebred Ferghana steeds.
I live and eat at Cuihua House.
What use are horses?
Just say yes or no.
Fine horses!
Pity. No use for them.
Take them to market at dawn tomorrow.
Yes, Lord Chai.
The horses became his?
Come on, move.
Ouyang Feng,
losing everything's a blessing.
Let's find Yaoshi.
Leaving like this?
Don't go. You can't leave.
Apologize for your insult earlier.
Young Master, you heard it.
We gave him gold and horses.
Now he wants my apology?
How should I apologize?
You're admirable.
His apology is enough.
He's with me. His apology is my apology.
Then your apology will do.
Hand over the gold.
Zhao, no bloodshed.
Apologies won't do.
Kneel and kowtow three times to leave.
There is still time to kneel.
I'll make you kneel!
Two more to go.
Know martial arts?
Just a bit.
Care to test it?
I honor my bets.
He insulted you once.
And you slammed him down.
Let's go our separate ways.
No.
Two kowtows remain.
Don't want to hurt you.
Come on then.
I've won plenty of gold from you.
I'll fight one-handed.
You will?
Right. Only one hand against you.
You're asking for humiliation.
Your martial arts are passable.
But your acupoint strikes are good.
Youngster,
that's one kowtow just now.
One more left.
You've been restless
since the first hand,
enduring no hardship at all.
Poor gaming manners
and mediocre martial arts.
Well. I will handicap myself further
to teach you propriety.
What's this?
A mishmash of martial arts,
nothing remarkable.
It's been years
since I last fought anyone.
Today's game amuses me.
So I'll stretch my old bones.
Come on.
Let me show you
Mount Baituo's techniques.
Not entirely formless.
Not bad. Not bad.
Youngster, your skills impress.
Who are you in Southern martial arts?
Don't mention martial arts.
I'm just a gambler.
Don't mention South.
You Northerners
and Westerners should know
this is the Song.
Are you the South's top fighter?
Why keep saying "South"?
It's the Song.
Are you the best?
Losing to the best would be honorable?
At least second or third then?
Youngster,
fortune changes like dice rolls.
We win this hand and lose the next.
Don't lecture me.
Such a sore loser.
I'm the best fighter in Cuihua House.
First in Jiangling as well.
In the Song,
who dares claim supremacy?
Excuse me.
Where's Cuihua House's stable?
Left turn outside.
Thanks.
You're with Ouyang Feng, aren't you?
In a way.
Ease his worries.
Life has ups and downs.
Time for me to gamble more.
Lady Luck smiles today.
♪I dive into a terrific conflict♪
♪Forgetting all worldly things♪
♪I drink at the window♪
♪Everything is all sodden with dew♪
♪I'm an enlightened person♪
♪Yet I feel lost while traveling♪
♪In my whole life♪
♪It's hard to travel light♪
♪Traverse thousands of miles of land
with every step♪
♪Half a lifetime
witnessing the changes of the world♪
♪Unexpectedly,
love is like a sharp dagger♪
♪Hurting my heart♪
♪My azure robe withstands
a thousand crashing waves♪
♪Unaware of suffering so long♪
♪Yet this passion might shatter♪
♪Leaving me adrift♪
♪My heart is full of sadness♪
♪I'm determined to sever bonds♪
♪The world believes
true hearts can conquer all♪
♪However, it's a lie♪
♪The world is so big♪
♪Yet I have nowhere to go♪
♪The mortal world has become chaotic♪
♪Leaving me alone♪