I was already leaving.
I returned to tell you one thing.
Tomorrow,
Master Hu will pick you up.
He'll go to Jiangzhou.
I'll follow him
behind.
When it's convenient,
I'll talk to you.
At your convenience...
Got it.
The candle's lit.
I help you put it out?
Thank you.
Master Hu.
Have you decided?
Tomorrow,
I'll go with you.
Mr. Ouyang and I happen to
be heading to Lin'an too.
Three horses await outside
for you and your companion.
I don't know
how I can thank you.
If possible,
could you examine my crippled legs
and see if you can treat them?
Okay.
Where's your injury?
The spine in my back.
I had a fight in my youth.
It's an old injury.
It's been 18 years.
Too late.
(The Legend of Heroes)
=Duel on Mount Hua=
(Adapted from Jin Yong's novel,
The Legend of the Condor Heroes)
=Eastern Heretic and Western Venom=
=Episode 5=
You practiced martial arts,
unlike Feng Heng,
an ordinary person.
When she was injured,
she happened to meet me.
I'm also lucky
to meet you now.
However,
every three days,
bonesetting once.
After two bonesettings,
take one Ninefold Yin Pill.
Seven cycles.
After 21 days,
take another pill.
Then you will walk normally.
However,
you can't use martial arts.
Can I
have the Ninefold Yin Pill now?
This pill
regenerates bones and tissues,
but carries toxicity.
I'll risk anything
for normal legs.
I'm not refusing you.
You have to take it
after six days
and two treatments.
Give it to me now.
Thanks.
Baili.
I met Huang Yaoshi by lucky chance.
After my crippled legs are cured,
I will destroy him.
I saved your life.
You're welcome.
Why did you save me then?
Someone injured you
with the Primordial Celestial Qi Art
of the Chai family.
I'm making it up to you
on their behalf.
Not because you're virtuous.
You're not good.
Ouyang Feng is better than you.
Young Master.
He'll be fine.
He'll awaken in an hour.
Splash water on his face to wake him.
Then why not do it?
Asking me?
Why should I fetch water?
I'm staying here
for you two.
Your physique is good.
An average martial artist
needs two hours to clear the poison.
You woke up earlier
than I estimated.
Why are you here?
The gold.
Huang Yaoshi not only recovered the gold
but asked me to deliver it personally.
Though two ingots are mine.
I've had them.
When I arrived,
I saw Tie Mu trying to kill you.
I drove him away.
Tie Mu?
You should thank me.
Thank you.
Not sincere enough.
Thank you so much, Mr. Chai.
Don't I keep my word?
It's pretty fair.
I made you kowtow for a reason.
I made you thank me for a reason.
Your martial arts reign supreme.
You can act as you please.
I'm a top martial artist
only in Cuihua House,
Jiangling,
not in the whole world.
Your friend Huang Yaoshi
might be better than me.
Yaoshi?
Impossible.
A top-tier master
did a telekinetic trick and cheated.
But it's fine.
I'll wait here for him.
How many top masters like you
does the South have?
The Song.
Alright.
Few top masters exist.
But now, Huang Yaoshi joins the ranks.
How dare you remain here!
He killed Pan Jie.
Why bother?
The knife on Pan
is yours!
Never thought you'd deny even this.
You also killed Nianyu
and Bidao.
Slanderous lies!
Pan was a top martial artist.
Even Lie can't defeat him
on his own.
How could I kill him?
Since Lie died
by my Pan's hand,
you murdered him in revenge.
Shamelessly,
you call him Pan.
As a guy from Western Regions,
you're so unreasonable.
You murdered Pan.
But when confronted,
you wept?
It's time to kill you
and avenge Pan's death.
Prepare to die!
How stupid you are!
There's a traitor among you,
yet you help him?
He poisoned the food!
What a silver-tongued guy!
Shut your mouth!
Where's Dan Min?
The Chai family abducted her.
We couldn't catch up.
Then why return?
He murdered Pan!
You colluded with the Chai family
to poison the food
and incapacitate Dan Min,
so Tie Lin and Tie Mu
could abduct her.
I was poisoned too.
You're pretending.
Look at you now.
You look fine.
Nonsense!
You suggested poisoning the food.
You told Tie Mu
to silence my master and me.
Tie Mu is a top-grade expert.
If he wants you dead,
will you be standing here alive?
If I hadn't been poisoned,
Tie Mu couldn't have fought me.
Who poisons themselves
while waiting for killers?
You're in league with the Chai family!
Mr. Chai came to deliver the gold
and drove away Tie Mu.
Who?
The martial world
is quite lively, isn't it?
What are you?
You greasy runt!
Mind your tongue!
Asking for a beating.
Old man, I'll deal with you first.
Are you Mr. Chai?
Why?
I guess you're Chai Qiong.
I'm Tang Long.
12 years ago,
I once met you.
I spend every day at Cuihua House.
No need to talk about history.
Mr. Chai.
Tie Mu is from the Chai family.
When he tried to kill Ouyang Feng,
why did you save him?
Who said I saved him?
You're spouting nonsense!
I don't care about the Chai family.
I hate matters
of the martial world.
I'm here to repay gambling debts.
I just arrived.
How should I know what
you're talking about?
Did you hear that?
Clearly,
these two Westerners
just lied.
Kill them
to avenge Miss and Pan!
Given your rudeness,
I gave you three slaps.
Do two more yourself.
What insolence!
Attack them together!
Let us
kill the three of them.
I'm not afraid of fighting.
But let's make it clear first.
I have nothing to do
with the Chai family
or Zijin Hall.
I'm on my way
to Lin'an.
Stop pestering me.
Finding Dan Min should be your priority.
Fight!
Bring it on!
We'll follow your advice.
But if we
have questions again,
we'll come back to you.
Are you kidding?
Let's settle it...
Do you want to leave?
I've been trying to suppress my anger
all night long.
Whoever bears my anger
will be unlucky.
From now on,
we'll head straight to Lin'an.
Focus on traveling.
No provocations, no meddling.
Young Master.
We're never afraid.
Just kill those
who provoke us.
I'm not afraid.
But meeting Miss Liu Rusi in Lin'an
and returning home matter.
Lie died for nothing.
The killer died too.
And I'm not the killer.
I exerted all my strength
but didn't even touch his robe.
And he only used
one hand and one leg.
You saw it yourself.
What about Huang Yaoshi?
We're not traveling with him?
Yaoshi might be a master.
How strong is he?
I'd like to know too.
I'm waiting for you.
Mr. Chai.
Where's the gold?
Inside.
What about Mr. Ouyang?
Also inside.
Thanks.
Come down. Let's duel.
Why?
You cheated at gambling.
You lost two rounds and got angry.
Then you played a trick.
If I hadn't realized it,
how would I reclaim
Mr. Ouyang's gold?
Fine, I see.
It's fair.
Even so, come down and fight!
I haven't met a worthy opponent
in ten years.
So, I killed my time at Cuihua House.
If we don't compete,
I won't feel peaceful from now on.
Mr. Ouyang.
Should we find a place to rest first
or set out immediately?
Where did you get horses?
Master Hu gave them.
When traveling,
we can rotate
between six horses.
That's good.
We lost our horses.
Huang Yaoshi! Don't leave!
Mr. Chai, I'm leaving.
If you don't fight,
I'll make the first move.
You're a reasonable man
and won't force me,
right?
How could you come and go like this?
You're killing me.
Shouldn't you tell me
where you're taking me?
Lord Chai is waiting for you
at Yunshui Manor.
I'm hungry and thirsty.
Here you go.
I need to change clothes.
Can you see me
dressed like this?
What's wrong?
Everything's wrong.
To meet Chai Yu,
I should dress properly, right?
There's a tailor shop
in Pengze.
I need to wash my face too.
Fine.
We'll make a stop in Pengze.
Miss Feng.
It's a long journey.
Riding a horse isn't proper.
And in a carriage,
we should keep our distance.
I'm a disabled man.
Miss Feng.
Don't overthink.
About the Three-Day Spiritbane,
I'll neutralize it once tonight
and once more tomorrow night.
Then it'll be cleared.
Miss Feng, don't worry.
I'm not worried.
Really?
Because of him,
I'm not worried.
Do you like him?
Of course.
Does he like you?
He will.
It's rare in this world
to find someone as pure-hearted
as Huang Yaoshi.
And his martial arts are great,
right?
Sure.
He
isn't far behind us.
Seventeen will contact us midway
as agreed last night.
Your father is already dead.
Stop dwelling on it.
My son is dead too.
Let the past be.
I'll let you
and Huang Yaoshi be together.
Consider this
my good deed.
Though before
I never heard of you,
I know exactly
what you're like.
What am I like?
Evil people rarely change.
You're the type
of incorrigible villain.
Though I'm young,
I've traveled widely with my father
and seen many people.
In this world,
bad people outnumber the good.
Truly good souls like Huang Yaoshi
are even rarer.
Miss Feng has a calculating mind.
You're the schemer.
You
have ulterior motives.
Right.
You need me
to clear the Three-Day Spiritbane.
And I
need Huang Yaoshi
to treat my crippled legs.
After that,
what do you plan to do?
Miss Feng.
Overthinking is not good for you.
Huang Yaoshi
hasn't decided to take you away yet.
She's read countless books
with a good memory.
She is very knowledgeable.
Before leaving,
I put out the candle
in her room.
Then I stood in the corridor
to listen to her breathing.
Later,
her breathing grew
calmer and calmer.
Then she fell asleep.
She was in her room,
and you were in the hallway.
You could still
sense her breathing?
Exactly.
Mr. Ouyang,
did I make any mistakes?
You're experienced in this.
If I make a mistake,
you must tell me.
I'm experienced?
You told me to meet her.
Where did I go wrong?
You're only talking about yourself!
Do you know how
I spent last night?
- You...
- I lost all the gold.
- Well...
- Not exactly.
You won it back later.
Besides the gold,
I lost three horses too.
I got beaten in the stables.
After mastering Mount Baituo techniques,
I thought
few could rival me.
Yet in the stables,
Instantaneous Leap, Shentuo Palm,
bone-piercing
and pressure-point attacks,
even at full power,
I couldn't touch Chai Qiong.
He only used one hand and leg!
Understand?
Zhao even watched me
kowtow to him three times.
Did that happen
before you asked me to see Feng Heng?
When did I
ask you to see her?
When?
After you returned,
you hesitated to choose
between her and me.
Are we still friends?
I haven't had friends
for ages.
Now, I can do anything
for you.
Come on.
Sounds like you've lived for centuries.
Are you immortal?
Is your mind addled?
I...
After you left,
Dan Min came.
She talked nonsense too.
I met her once by chance.
She claimed to fall for me
and be with me forever,
traveling the world.
Good heavens!
Luckily, the food was poisoned.
Zhao fought Zijin Hall
outside,
while I fought inside.
Then another expert came,
spouting gibberish.
If Master Chai hadn't come
to deliver the gold,
I, Ouyang Feng,
would've died.
Do you know martial arts?
That's not important.
Dan Min...
That's crucial! Don't talk about her.
My fault.
I was too selfish,
only talking
about myself.
Now, it's your turn
to speak, alright?
No.
You're so slow.
Have you eaten too much?
Turn!
She already made you upset,
didn't she?
Sure, but not the kind
you're thinking of.
I saw her as a friend.
Yet she attacked me.
I refused her,
and she asked me to kill her.
How could I possibly kill her?
But she is pretty cold.
If I refuse her, she'll kill me.
What's going on?
In Kuizhou,
I asked you to travel with me
because I hoped you'd tell me
about the customs of the South.
It's your turn to talk.
About what?
Do you know martial arts?
Are you a master?
Where has
Dan Min gone?
She was captured by the Chai family.
The Chai family? Why?
How should I know?
The martial world is complex.
None of my concern.
If I were captured,
would that not concern you?
It's different.
You're male, and she's female.
I see.
Mr. Ouyang,
you should find her.
Why should I?
You must voice your feelings
and make her understand,
or you will keep being upset.
I swear
I won't fall for a woman
like her.
Then you must let her know.
I'll keep it to myself.
What if she dies?
Keeping it to yourself won't help.
You will remain upset.
Right.
Go.
Caught up with you again!
Get out of here.
He's here for you.
I know.
Come on.
I hate being bothered.
Quick! He's getting away!
He's escaping.
Ouyang Feng,
you look pale.
Feeling unwell?
(Pengze County)
Tie.
Tie!
Pengze was flooded
a month ago.
Only 16 soldiers remain here.
Tie!
Tie.
Salt Gang's people are here.
- Salt Gang?
- Yes.
Two large carriages.
Staying at an inn on the east.
27 people and 36 horses.
We came to the wrong place.
Let's leave.
Where can you change clothes?
Turn a corner ahead,
and there's a tailor shop.
I went there last year.
Pengze County is deserted.
No tailor shops remain.
Check it out. There might be one.
Who are you?
They're from the Chai family.
The Chai family?
What should we do?
Why are they here?
Are you scared?
What's there to fear?
Sure, nothing to fear.
I'm just a woman.
You have a dozen men.
Two masters are with you.
What's there to fear?
Withdraw!
Don't meddle in their affairs.
- Go!
- Come on!
Move!
(Tailor Shop)
Is anyone there?
Wait.
Pengze County is deserted.
What are you doing here?
What's your name?
Qi Qing.
What's your rank in the Chai family?
Dismount.
Answer my question.
How can you run a business
with no customers?
I have nowhere to keep the stuff
in my shop.
The floodwater receded.
I came back to clean and repair.
Customers
will come eventually.
(Fu Ruoqing, Clothing Rraft in Zijin Hall)
You've come after all.
Ms. Fu.
I need to change clothes
and wash my face.
Why are you dressed like this?
I...
I've fallen for a man.
Does your brother know?
He doesn't need to.
And the man?
Get changed inside.
Clean water's precious.
Use it sparingly.
Okay.
I need
to go inside.
Hold on.
Why are your hands tied?
Come here.
What's going on?
Tie underestimated her.
This woman is a master.
Which rank do you hold in Zijin Hall?
Third in the five crafts.
Clothing craft.
I'm Fu Ruoqing.
Have some tea?
This clean water was carried
from distant sources,
more precious than tea.
Fu Ruoqing.
I am
no match for you.
But Qi Qing and I can
defeat you together.
So, you're Tie Lin
and Qi Qing.
You'd better stay out of this,
or you'll lose your life.
Let me take Dan Min to Jiangzhou.
Alright.
After Dan Min changes clothes
and I talk to her,
you can leave.
What will you say?
She came specifically to see me
and said she liked a man.
As an elder of hers,
I ought to advise her.
Drink some tea.
Please wait patiently.
A young girl will
take a while to get changed
and wash her face.
For the record,
both of you also stand no chance
of defeating me together.
Since we can talk,
why resort to force?
You're right, madam.
I'm not that old.
Don't be so formal.
You have seniority over me.
I only have seniority in Zijin Hall.
You two
don't be so formal.
Huang Yaoshi.
My leader fears you might get lost.
He sent me specifically to tell you
that Miss Feng will rest
at Pengze County.
If you want to enter the county,
we'll get the meal ready.
If you proceed onward,
please inform us
of your next stop.
The leader will escort Miss Feng
to meet you.
Got it. Thanks.
Go!
You may go.
We part ways here.
Are you not entering the county?
I'm going to Lin'an,
not entering Pengze.
Then I'll be back soon.
Wait for me.
I won't wait.
We just came across each other.
Eventually, we'll part ways.
Why do you say that?
Since passing through Kuizhou
into Jiangling,
as you said,
I've been upset.
Zhao and I should head straight
to Lin'an.
You told me to find Miss Feng.
Then go ahead.
Don't split your focus.
I'm leaving.
Go and find Dan Min.
Where can I find her?
The martial world here is complex.
What can I do even if I find her?
Can't you wait for me?
Yaoshi.
Tell me the truth.
Who exactly are you?
I'm just a nobody.
Huang Yaoshi.
I knew you'd take this path.
Stop.
Mr. Chai.
What exactly do you want?
Tell me the truth.
Who exactly are you?
I'm just a nobody.
That makes it even stranger.
We must have a fight.
If you lose to me,
I'll return to Cuihua House
and gamble again.
Mr. Ouyang, help me persuade him.
I'll be right back.
Don't go.
Him?
He can't help.
He's no match for me.
I won't deal with him.
Go ahead, Yaoshi.
Stop avoiding me.
Let's fight.
Fight or not?
So infuriating.
Wait for me.
So infuriating!
Set off to Lin'an.
From now on,
don't meddle in anything.
Ms. Fu.
Where's the used water?
Inside.
Throw it away.
Give it to me.
Tea?
Yes.
Do not
enter.
Speak.
Drive them away first.
Can't they hear it?
I asked Pan Jie
and Yu Dian to invite Ouyang Feng
to dinner
in Jiangling.
The Chai family poisoned the food
and seized me.
I don't know
how Ouyang Feng is.
Let them tell you.
Who's Ouyang Feng?
The man I like.
From Western Regions.
Nobody knows him.
I've decided.
I'll spend my life with him.
Why?
No reasons.
Well, that's good then.
Is his family wealthy?
I guess so.
His martial arts are good.
Stop talking now.
We're taking her.
With Ms. Fu here,
you think you can leave?
Does Ouyang Feng like you?
Sure.
Otherwise, why did he drink with me?
They poisoned Ouyang Feng too.
Did you hurt Ouyang Feng?
Answer Miss Dan's question.
Make it clear before you leave.
You conspired with the Chai family
to poison Miss Dan Min.
Where have you taken her?
We didn't poison her.
Chai Qiong was with you.
Stop arguing!
Since he is not here,
it's time to make you pay.
No need to talk anymore.
Why must you keep harassing us?
I didn't even avenge Lie's death
in Kuizhou.
Even if my martial arts
may seem inadequate,
I can still
fight all of you.
Fine.
Now that this guy is injured,
you'll have to
fight the four of us.
You have
a short temper.
What a loser!
♪I dive into a terrific conflict♪
♪Forgetting all worldly things♪
♪I drink at the window♪
♪Everything is all sodden with dew♪
♪I'm an enlightened person♪
♪Yet I feel lost while traveling♪
♪In my whole life♪
♪It's hard to travel light♪
♪Traverse thousands of miles of land
with every step♪
♪Half a lifetime
witnessing the changes of the world♪
♪Unexpectedly,
love is like a sharp dagger♪
♪Hurting my heart♪
♪My azure robe withstands
a thousand crashing waves♪
♪Unaware of suffering so long♪
♪Yet this passion might shatter♪
♪Leaving me adrift♪
♪My heart is full of sadness♪
♪I'm determined to sever bonds♪
♪The world believes
true hearts can conquer all♪
♪However, it's a lie♪
♪The world is so big♪
♪Yet I have nowhere to go♪
♪The mortal world has become chaotic♪
♪Leaving me alone♪