[Warning]
[No dogs abused during production]
[All incidents in the drama are
fictitious, only for recreational purposes.]
[Beware when watching.]
[Previously]
Even dogs won't eat this.
It doesn't taste good at all.
♪ Knock, knock, knock on the door ♪
I won't let you eat it, Boredy.
Flint, you're so mean. How could you say
even dogs won't eat food made by Tul?
♪ Your world seems so lonely,
doesn't it? ♪
♪ Can you hear my loud heartbeat? ♪
Whether I let you stay or not
♪ Boom boom boom, when you get close ♪
has nothing to do
with whether you'll win or not.
I just don't want you to hurt yourself.
♪ From a world that once felt cold ♪
♪ Now that you're here,
every day gets brighter ♪
♪ Woo woo woo ♪
♪ Woof woof woof, my heart ♪
[Doctor prescribed you medicine.
There's food in the fridge.
Please groom Mr. Nirun.]
Doctor prescribed you medicine.
There's food in the fridge.
Please groom Mr. Nirun.
♪ Knock, knock, knock on the door ♪
♪ Your world seems so lonely,
doesn't it? ♪
♪ Can you hear my loud heartbeat? ♪
♪ Boom boom boom, when you get close ♪
♪ From a world that once felt cold ♪
♪ Now that you're here,
every day gets brighter ♪
♪ Woo woo woo ♪
♪ Woof woof woof, my heart ♪
♪ This little dog has melted my heart ♪
♪ Because you came, my frown disappeared ♪
♪ Because your dazzling smile ♪
♪ Makes my heart skip a beat ♪
♪ And I don't know how to stop it ♪
♪ You like dogs, right? ♪
♪ Then what about me? ♪
♪ Will you let me be the puppy in your heart? ♪
♪ Please, Bro ♪
[DogBro]
[The star in my eyes:
[Brother Tul, a soccer player
from engineering school]
[Comments before he entered the ward]
[This year's Moon of the Uni
will definitely be Tul.]
[Cmusohot]
[Share the story of soccer player Tul.]
[Dog Slave Story]
[A newly opened corgi cafe]
[A kind boy from the north]
[An engineering school's freshman Tul
has made his IG a public account.]
Thank you, Brother Meen.
[Tul: Thank you, Brother Meen.]
I'll finish them all, Doctor.
[I'll finish them all, Doctor.]
It'll be best if you take the medicine
right after a meal.
[Meen: It'll be best if you take
the medicine right after a meal.]
I'm going to take a shower.
You look so happy these days, Boredy.
The recommended content on your phone
should be all about Tul, right?
What are you talking about, Chatterbox?
My recommended content
is all about my research.
The AI is super smart now.
Do you know?
You take your phone with you at all time.
If you often mention something
or pay much attention to something,
it will appear
in your recommended content.
Try it if you don't believe me.
Samoyed, Samoyed, Samoyed.
Check yourself.
Will it really work?
[Deep Dee Y]
[Romance series
adapted from a popular novel]
[The Samoyed that heals your soul]
[Dowry: 99 baht]
Hey, it's really all about Samoyed.
[Love the dog if you hope to keep one.]
[My name is Sen Yai.]
My mom made me delicious snacks today.]
But just now your recommended content
was all about Tul.
[Congratulations to the freshmen
of the engineering school
on winning the second place of the freshmen's
soccer match for the fifth time.]
You're talking nonsense.
Because the freshmen's
sports meet just ended,
it's normal to get so much
recommended content about it.
Let's go.
[First-aid Teaching Day]
Meen and Kim will go to
the engineering school later.
Chatterbox and Flint, follow me.
-Okay.
Can I not go? I don't want to.
So you'd rather go hiking
with your juniors?
That'll be more tiring.
Flint, follow me.
Uh.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Here, I bought you a bottle water.
Thank you.
So do you want me to go to
the engineering school with you?
No, you go to the school of humanities.
I can really go with you.
Let's keep our distance.
Otherwise, people will think
you're clinging to me.
I am.
Fine.
You should come to class first.
You suddenly appear and disappear.
It looks cool.
But if you get an F,
I'll have no idea how to help you.
I know you have good grades,
but it's good to come to class more often.
Are you worried about me?
I'm not worried about you.
I'm reminding you to examine yourself.
I don't need to. I know I'm good.
Yes.
Hey, Meen.
Have you ever had a secret crush
on someone?
Why do you ask?
Well, are you having a secret crush
on someone?
You can tell me about it.
I, the "doctor" will keep
a secret for my "patient".
I want to ask you,
if we have a crush on someone,
do you think we should tell them?
Yes.
You're so handsome. Who will reject you?
I think
if someone rejects you,
they must be very stupid.
They must be very stupid to reject me?
It's so hot.
Drink something sweet, Boredy.
No, thanks. I already bought one.
You drink it.
I have class. I can't go.
Thank you so much.
They must be very stupid to reject me?
Yes, you're handsome, rich,
and has a good personality.
And you're very considerate.
Anyone who rejects you is a fool.
I think that person
should be really stupid.
Let's pack up.
Friends are waiting.
Okay.
[Seniority Order]
It's finally over. I'm hungry.
Do you want to have rice or rice noodles?
This looks delicious.
Parrot's food is so good.
-Hello.
-I'd like Tom Yum Goong
noodles without vegetables.
-Okay.
-Anything else to go with your noodles?
-Well...
Make it carefully, okay?
Okay.
-Don't make it too spicy.
-I want a strong flavor.
Well, I want a strong flavor.
And as the shop name says,
make it super delicious.
Sure.
The meatballs look delicious.
Can I have meatballs?
Okay. Put more spice.
Very good.
Meatballs.
Large portion, please.
Okay.
Brother Kim, are you here to eat?
Yes, Tul.
The dishes from the engineering school
are so beautiful.
I'd like a bowl of rice noodles
with non-spicy soup.
Okay.
Rice noodles with non-spicy soup.
-Miss.
-Yes?
I'll pay for Samoyed Bro's order later.
No, I can pay for it myself.
You know what?
With an engineering school student card,
I can get a 50% discount.
Hey, hey, hey.
Can I use this discount, Tul?
It can only be used by one person.
You two seem close.
We three are friends, Brother Meen.
Sun isn't usually with us.
He disappears after class.
Here.
This is my student card.
Swipe it here.
Okay.
Oh.
Oh, Meen!
What are you doing?
Turn around and look.
There!
As a BL fan, I'm going crazy.
[An engineering school student
let his boyfriend use a 50% discount.]
Gosh!
Junior!
Miss, how much money was the discount?
I'll pay it to you.
No need. Is there really nothing
between you and that guy?
You look like a couple.
No, I'll pay the full price.
No need.
I'm a BL fan. He has paid for your food.
Uh...
Sorry, I used the kitchen
without your permission.
You know how to cook?
I cook, I'm good at caring animals
and people love me.
If a busy person like you
adopts me,
I promise I'll take good care of you
for the rest of your life.
I refuse.
It's already tiring to keep Mr. Nirun.
I made yours too. Have a seat.
Well, I've had lots of assignments
to do recently.
Can I invite a friend here
to do assignments with me?
Yes.
I won't mind if you ask people
to do assignments here with you here.
Mr. Nirun, this is for humans.
You can't eat it.
I've prepared something you can eat.
Here.
It's made according to the same formula
as Mali's mother's.
Eat up, Mr. Nirun.
You know Mali?
The food its mother cooks for it is
better than that she cooks for people.
Cute, right?
Which Mali? Show it to me.
Of course, Kitty.
What did you cook?
Fried rice with sausage.
There's some left in the fridge.
I still remember
when I was a kid, we had it together.
My mom made it for us.
Tul.
I've eaten. I'll get back to work.
Hey. You won't eat
the fried rice with sausage I made?
I don't want to.
It's too salty.
♪ Knock, knock, knock on the door ♪
How is it? Is it good?
Just average.
♪ Your world seems so lonely,
doesn't it? ♪
Its taste is preferred by Bangkok people.
If you want to let people here like it,
you'll have to work harder.
♪ Can you hear my loud heartbeat? ♪
♪ Boom boom boom, when you get close ♪
♪ From a world that once felt cold ♪
What?
I'm just hungry. It's not that delicious.
♪ Now that you're here,
every day gets brighter ♪
If it's not good enough,
I can cook for you again at home.
♪ Woo woo woo ♪
♪ Woof woof woof, my heart ♪
♪ This little dog has melted my heart ♪
I'm going to
finish assignments with Phetai.
♪ Because you came, my frown disappeared ♪
♪ Because your dazzling smile ♪
♪ Makes my heart skip a beat ♪
What kind of dog it is?
Samoyed.
If I have a lover,
I also want to raise a dog with them.
You're so small just like a cat.
I think you'd better keep a Persian cat.
Don't say that. You may get scratched
by a cat.
A small cat's scratch
can get you really hurt.
You want me to teach you a lesson?
Come on!
Hey, I quit.
I'll get going then.
Okay, let me walk you out.
Okay.
Hey, your phone.
Bye.
Be careful on your way home.
Okay.
You're already missing me
after one minute?
I'll take a shower and get changed
so that my whole body will smell good.
Okay, bye.
You look like a Samoyed dog.
You're more adorable than scary.
Should I pretend to be so scared
that I need someone to do CPR for me?
Nonsense.
Have you called your mom lately?
You've been here for almost a month.
No, I haven't, Brother Meen.
I've been living alone
since my first year in high school.
You know my mom
doesn't care about me at all.
When my mom came to Chiang Mai for work,
she asked me to live with you.
You still need to call your mom
instead of not telling them anything.
Is that a rule for living here too?
Why are you making it a big deal
and writing it down?
I wrote down everything you said.
Let me see.
No, you can't.
-Let me see.
-No.
-Let me see. Let me see.
-No, you can't.
You're stingy.
I follow all the rules you said.
Brother Meen, you should
be nicer to me from now on.
Okay.
I bought you a layer cake.
Don't forget to eat it.
A layer cake? Will you eat it with me?
What an old-fashioned joke.
Where did you learn that?
Are you dating someone?
Brother Meen, you don't want me
to date anyone?
You look like a naive puppy.
I'm afraid someone will break your heart.
Love makes so many people heartbroken.
What are you doing?
I was hurting myself.
Only in this way can I get true love.
Nonsense.
I mean
come and break my heart when you're free.
I'm busy.
Hey, Brother Meen.
I'm going to Pokpong's bar today.
How will go there?
Don't drive if you get drunk.
Maybe someone will pick me up?
I don't have time.
Go yourself and come back yourself.
Then I'll ask Phetai to give me a ride.
Phetai?
Yes.
But they might drink until morning.
I think I'll spend the night at Phetai's.
Until morning?
Yes. Those engineering students
always drink all night.
I'll go get prepared now.
-Come here.
-Hey.
I quit.
Does Tul have
a secret crush
on Phetai?
[7th Alley, Nimmanhaemin Soi]
Come on, bro.
Wow.
What other team can be the runner-ups 5 times
in a row like the engineering school's?
Cheers.
We're really a top team.
Let's stay on the football team
at least until our senior year.
Hey, I have a question to ask you.
Do you find it weird
if a man likes another man?
What's weird about that?
I like men too.
Huh?
If it is a man like you,
I will like him too.
You're so serious about romantic love.
How can I not fall in love with you?
Well, how is he?
Did he start to open his heart to you?
I'm not sure.
But I did my best.
You're so handsome.
You'll get him eventually.
You're a sweet-talker.
Let's have another drink.
Cheers.
Aren't they the losers
from the engineering school?
And they look like they want to be beaten.
Hey, we're having fun.
Why are you picking a fight with us?
Let's drink our own drinks.
Go back to your table!
Let's avoid trouble. Otherwise,
other customers will be unhappy.
Please.
It's none of your business.
Stay out of it.
Hey, mind your language.
What?
Are you this sissy's boyfriend?
Oh.
This sissy
works here.
Can you earn 300 baht?
Looks like you don't
have money for drink.
I know. You must get your food and drink
by amusing your friends.
What's wrong with being a sissy?
You're so rude.
I'll show you what I've got!
Hey!
Wait, let me handle it.
Get out of my bar.
I'll tell your seniors
not to step into my bar again.
Don't ever talk rudely here again.
Get out of my bar now!
Go!
Are you okay?
Sorry, Sun. Sorry, Pokpong.
It's all my fault.
Tul.
You are my bro.
Your friend is also my bro.
I'm Pokpong.
Of course I have to protect you.
I'm sorry, Pokpong.
I almost caused trouble at your bar.
It's okay.
I would've done the same if I were you.
Have fun. Enjoy drinking.
Cheers. Cheers.
Come on, let's dance and relax.
Go on. Come on.
Let's dance.
Yes, like this.
[Men]
Today I must know
who Tul is dating secretly.
Meen.
Who's Meen?
I'm not Meen.
I'm a cat.
What are you doing here?
Kim said you weren't coming today.
Are you looking for Tul?
Hey.
I'm looking for something to eat.
In the restroom?
It's my business.
I'm exhausted.
Meen, what are you doing here?
Well.
I'm walking Mr. Nirun.
Where's Mr. Nirun?
Here, here.
Where is Mr. Nirun?
Oh, it broke free.
-It broke free.
-Yes, it broke free.
-Mr. Nirun broke free.
-Nirun.
Mr. Nirun.
Where are you, Mr. Nirun?
You can come out now.
-Mr. Nirun.
-Where are you, Mr. Nirun?
-Ouch.
-Mr. Nirun, come out. Please help find it.
-Where is Mr. Nirun?
Go to the men's room. Then you don't
have to wait in line for too long.
No, I'm shy.
If you hold your urine too often,
your boyfriend won't like it.
Stop complaining. You're a devil.
No, there're so many people.
I'll go to the ladies' room, but...
Meen, what are you doing here?
Didn't you say you weren't coming?
Come on.
It's as if you hadn't come together.
I'm leaving.
Hey, Meen.
I just saw your bro
being teased by your enemies.
-But I...
-Where is he now?
At the entrance.
-Hey.
What's going on?
Don't you think it's weird?
Do you have the same feeling?
How about we follow him?
-Do you want to go?
-No, no, no.
I think I smell love.
Did you smell it, Pokpong?
Love.
This is the men's room. Girls, get out.
I'm a man too.
Hey, Cutie.
So cute.
Can I take it home?
No. Put it down.
Put it down. Put it down. Give it to me.
Let it go.
Tul.
Tul, wake up.
Wake up!
Hey, what are you doing to my bro?
Hey, Brother Meen.
Don't worry, he's Sun.
We're on the same side.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I thought you were our rival.
No.
Did he drink?
He drank a lot.
Something happened.
So he kept drinking.
Tul is allergic to alcohol.
See? He's blushing.
I'm sorry. I didn't know that.
So I didn't stop him.
It's okay.
Sun.
Yes.
Phetai.
You go back first. I'll take care of him.
Then I'll go.
Be careful on the way, Tul.
Bye, Brother Meen.
I don't want to go back yet.
I'm not drunk yet.
Are you going home alone
or do you want me to drag you home?
Who is this Samoyed dog
ordering me to go home?
I'm not going home.
I'm a Samoyed dog?
Okay.
A disobedient dog should treated this way.
Hey.
Come on.
I'm not going back.
Then I have to do this to you.
You can't everything at will.
I'm not going back.
Yes, you are.
No.
Yes.
Go back!
♪ I don't want us just to be friends ♪
♪ I want to be ♪
Brother Meen?
♪ Someone important to you ♪
♪ Then why do you look at me sometimes? ♪
♪ When I look into your eyes ♪
I want to go home now.
♪ I wonder ♪
What did you say?
I want to go home now.
I want to see Brother Meen.
♪ if you'll let me stand beside you? ♪
♪ Will the place in your heart ♪
♪ Possibly be mine? ♪
♪ Even though I know it's a dream
beyond my reach ♪
♪ Just let me stand beside you ♪
♪ It feels good just to be your backup ♪
Why are you sitting here alone?
Aren't you going home?
I've been hailing a car online.
But no one takes my order yet.
Do you need a ride?
It's okay.
Hello, Mom.
I'm out for a part-time job.
I didn't fool around.
Well.
Do you want to talk to my friend at work?
My mom?
Mom, why did you turn on the camera?
He's shy.
Where is he, Sun? Turn on the camera.
I haven't seen him yet.
Hurry up.
Hello.
Hello, kid.
We're about to close the shop.
Don't worry. I'll give Sun a ride later.
You're so good-looking.
You look like Sun's...
Bye.
We're closing the shop.
It's not good to lie to the elders.
You naughty kid.
Who asked you to give me a ride?
Come on. It's late. There's no taxi.
I can walk you home.
You won't get bitten by dogs
if you walk behind an adult.
I'm afraid of being bitten by you.
You know what?
Every time I see you, I think of someone.
Who?
My mom.
She likes to help others.
She can't stand seeing
someone being bullied.
When you got angry with me
because of Hawaman,
my mom's image came to my mind.
About Hawaman...
Don't worry.
Let's go.
I'm sorry, Brother Meen.
Oh.
Someone from the bar
used my IG to follow many accounts.
Aren't you going to reply to him?
Hey. You just block him?
I don't care about him anymore.
[The stars in my heart:
the freshmen Tul and Phetai]
[Pretty cute.]
[The admin thinks they have chemistry.]
[Photo of Phetai and Jun]
[Phetai is very charismatic in the engineering school]
Brother Meen, I'll lean on your thighs
and get some rest.
[Phetai: Are you home?]
[Tul: Safe home. Good night.]
The AI is super smart now.
You know that?
You take your phone with you at all time.
If you often mention something
or pay much attention to something,
it will appear
in your recommended content.
Try it if you don't believe me.
You and Phetai
seem very close.
Yes, he's my best friend.
He's not my type.
I like animal lovers.
who look naive.
More importantly, I like
people older than me.
It's such a poor thing.
He raised it when it was young.
When it grew up,
he just threw it away.
Humans are so cruel.
Sun, don't worry about Hawaman.
I'll take care of it for you, at least...
I'll take care of it
until it finds a new home.
Someone really followed me home.
It's called walking you home.
Then...
That's enough. I've arrived at the dorm.
-Bye.
[Sun: Thank you for today.
I'm sorry for being mad at you.]
Brother Meen, I have something for you.
Here.
Here. Look.
I had the key made and...
Let the dolls watch the key in case
someone comes home late.
I can know Mr. Nirun
and this cute thing
are waiting for me at home.
Brother Meen, can you scratch my head?
Like this?
Your single brother
wants someone like you to belong with him.
♪ if you'll let me stand beside you? ♪
♪ Will the place in your heart ♪
♪ Possibly be mine? ♪
♪ Even though I know it's a dream
beyond my reach ♪
♪ Just let me stand beside you ♪
♪ It feels good just to be your backup ♪
[Directed by Thunwa Wongnarathiwat]
What's wrong, Mr. Nirun?
Do you want to play with a toy?
I'll go in and look for it.
Rules in the apartment.
Rule No. 10: Don't enter Meen's room
without his permission.
Rule No. 11: Don't forget to give Mr. Nirun
water regularly because Mr. Nirun has two layers of hair.
Rule No.12: No conflict with anyone.
But if someone tries to cause trouble first,
you have to fight back.
Number 13: Call Mom.
Rule: 14, No dating because Brother Meen
doesn't want me to date.
You entered my room without permission.
Hey, should I set some rules
some rules for you?
What the heck?
I just came in to get Mr. Nirun a toy.
Look!
Brother Meen.
Thank you
for letting me live here.
Okay.
Take a shower and let's eat.
Room No. 14.
If the date is Brother Meen,
I want to break that rule.
What Rule No. 14? I know nothing about it.
Hurry up.
[Next Episode]
Sun...
There's something on your lips.
Let me take it off for you.
♪ I know I'm not important ♪
♪ But I still like you stubbornly ♪
You know what?
♪ Every time in my dream,
you are the person I want to see ♪
I was so embarrassed
♪ It's obvious that you're the one ♪
when I knew you always knew it
♪ But many times I wasn't sure ♪
but I still treated you like that.
♪ Why you looked at me
that way sometimes? ♪
Hi, doctors.
♪ When I look at you ♪
As I expected, you must be here.
♪ But I want to know more about you ♪
Who has a dog? I'm allergic to dogs.
♪ if you'll let me stand beside you? ♪
♪ Will the place in your heart ♪
Don't treat others like this again.
What if someone falls in love with you?
♪ Possibly be mine? ♪
I can tell at a glance
♪ Even though I know it's a dream
beyond my reach ♪
you like Brother Meen.
He's also pursuing his love.
♪ Just let me stand beside you ♪
And the person he likes is you.
♪ It feels good just to be your backup ♪
♪ When it thunders on a rainy day,
I'll stay by your side ♪
[Watch “DogBro”only on iQIYI APP and iQ.com]
♪ I'm ready to be ♪
♪ The person you can see
when you turn around ♪
♪ I don't want us just to be friends ♪
♪ I want to be ♪
♪ Someone important to you ♪
♪ Why you look at me sometimes ♪
♪ When I look into your eyes ♪
♪ I wonder ♪
♪ if you'll let me stand beside you? ♪
♪ Will the place in your heart ♪
♪ Possibly be mine? ♪
♪ Even though I know it's a dream
beyond my reach ♪
♪ Just let me stand beside you ♪
♪ It feels good just to be your backup ♪