Diyun.
Why are you here?
Are these medicinal herbs dried?
I'll send them over by sunset.
Is your injury healed?
I'm okay.
If I didn't owe Yunyuan a favor,
I wouldn't stay here doing hard labor.
As for Yunyuan,
the rebuilding of Shishannan Village
is all being managed by him alone.
He lives up to his reputation as the revered King Kunmi.
On this point,
I, Diyun, admire him.
However,
I will absolutely not give you up to him.
Why are you dragging me into this again?
I thought you two had buried the hatchet.
I am a living person.
You keep fighting over me,
what do you take me for?
Say, Little Highness,
did you catch the snake demon?
That snake demon is very cunning.
It has many clones.
How could you fail to catch a mere snake demon?
I...
Qingluan.
Yueying.
Yueying, what's wrong?
Save him first.
Yueying.
Brother.
Yueying is critically injured.
Return immediately.
Sister Qingluan,
who on earth could injure Yueying so severely?
He's not a reckless fool.
Even if he couldn't win,
he could have outrun them.
I hope Yueying is okay.
Brother and Diyun are both inside.
He will definitely be fine.
Yunyuan.
Brother.
How is Yueying?
Lend me your Spirit Pearl.
How do you know I have a Spirit Pearl?
I've never shown it to anyone.
Does Yunyuan really know me from before?
Here.
Saving Yueying is what matters.
Wait for me.
Yunyuan.
Are you two okay?
Here.
Why are you all still here?
Waiting here won't help anything.
Go back and rest.
We'll talk tomorrow when Yueying wakes up.
I'll help you back.
Where is the guest room?
I'll take you to rest.
Thank you for today.
It was nothing.
Sister,
have something to eat first.
How is Brother doing?
He and Diyun are meditating in the room.
How is Yueying?
His primordial spirit is stable now.
We dragged him back from death's door.
Don't worry.
He'll wake up tomorrow.
If I find out who hurt you like this,
I will skin them alive
to avenge you.
Why do I feel so uneasy?
Yunyuan.
Yunyuan, what's wrong?
This isn't working.
By my soul,
enter your spirit.
Dragon God above,
protect your primordial spirit.
Ling'er.
What happened?
Who hurt you?
My cultivation is lacking.
That's why I fell into the Snake Demon's trap.
The Snake Demon?
You mean that Flood Dragon?
He held many civilians hostage.
He only uses dirty tricks.
I was careless for a moment,
and fell into his trap.
I barely escaped the barrier he set up.
That Snake Demon is cunning.
We only encountered his clones before.
I underestimated him this time,
and met his true form.
I was also played for a fool by that Snake Demon.
You mean,
there are still many survivors there?
Knowing it's a Snake Demon makes it easy.
Let me go.
I am his natural predator.
My bloodline alone can suppress him.
This time,
I'll skin him and make soup for Yueying.
Wait.
Qingluan.
We need to discuss this further.
Go to my room and check if Ling'er is awake first.
Okay.
Diyun.
Tell your father, the Heavenly Emperor,
to stop these indiscriminate divine punishments.
Stay out of this.
My clan receives mortal worship.
Naturally, we must slay demons
and uphold justice.
Justice?
You ignore whether people live or die,
as long as you hit the demon?
You call this kind of divine punishment
"justice"?
If the lightning harms civilians,
the Heavenly Laws will provide punishment.
I will report this matter.
I will ensure the innocent receive justice.
A thousand years ago,
when demonic energy ravaged Kunmi,
the Heaven Clan never cared about Kunmi.
Now,
there is no need for you to care either.
On this matter,
the Heaven Clan indeed acted improperly.
Tsk.
Dead fish eyes.
"Dead fish eyes"?
Was he talking about me just now?
I'm going to teach him a lesson.
Rest well.
I'm going out for a bit.
General, you mustn't.
The prophecy the Prophet sacrificed his life for
will surely come true.
Once my Lord returns,
he will unite the Three Realms.
Grand Protector,
when do we retrieve the Spirit Pearl?
And the Qiankun Cauldron?
Be patient.
We must plan carefully this time.
We cannot repeat our past mistakes.
If the Spirit Pearl is destroyed again,
we will never have another chance.
I need a plan.
Got it.
Help!
It's a human.
No.
It's a demon.
He's still breathing.
Hey.
Wake up.
Forget it.
Help!
Is anyone there?
Ling'er.
Be careful.
I'm exhausted.
Ling'er.
Who is this?
I found him by the road.
He's just a little demon.
Hasn't Yunyuan returned yet?
That snake demon is cunning.
It's hard to catch.
This little demon likely failed his tribulation.
His cultivation was scattered by heavenly thunder.
He can barely maintain his human form.
Where am I?
Young man.
What's your name?
Do you know that carrying you back
completely wore me out?
I'm Yinfeng.
Thank you, Sister.
I was just a small demon in the mountains.
But I had bad luck.
I got caught in a great demon's thunder tribulation.
Thank you for saving me, Sister.
I am forever grateful.
Haha.
Hey.
No need to thank me.
And don't think about offering yourself to me.
Just rest here and heal.
Go back to your cave and cultivate once you're better.
Yinfeng.
And I'm Nongyue.
You're just a little demon.
Why do you have such a fancy name?
Why are you looking at me like that?
As if I bullied you.
Oh, come on.
We know where he came from.
Don't be so mean.
You're scaring the kid.
Let's go.
Come to my room.
Okay.
Sister.
Stay close.
I still don't know your name.
Just call me Sister.
Ling'er.
Wait for me.
Luochen said...
...you can't just pick up men off the street.
Ling'er.
Yueying.
How is your recovery coming along?
I'm fine now.
Who is that demon boy with Ling'er?
He lost his cultivation in a thunder tribulation.
Fortunately, the Princess saved him.
Ling'er is kind-hearted.
Keep an eye on him.
Investigate his background.
Yes, General.
Diyun.
You're still here?
Ling'er.
You're helping Yunyuan with his work.
You know,
you're actually a pretty good guy.
When I first met you,
I thought you were totally unreliable.
But after spending time with you,
I see you're actually quite dependable.
So,
I used to be unreliable,
and undependable?
Just like an idle rich playboy.
An idle rich playboy?
Not bad.
Better than a landlord's foolish son.
Slow down.
Where's Yinfeng?
He took his medicine and went to sleep.
I went to investigate the place he mentioned.
There are indeed traces of a lightning tribulation nearby.
There was a small village there.
It got caught in the blast. No one survived.
Perhaps
the great demon undergoing the tribulation
and the snake demon that attacked the village
are the same one.
The same one?
I'm not sure yet.
I need to look into it more.
You didn't find out for sure?
When Yinfeng wakes up,
I need to ask him again.
I'm just a low-level demon.
You're up?
Why didn't you sleep a bit longer?
Ling'er.
I feel much better.
I made some snacks.
Diyun.
Just ask me.
I'll tell you everything I know.
I won't hold anything back.
Okay.
Tell me exactly what happened that day.
I was cultivating in the mountains that day,
when lightning suddenly struck.
I was on the edge of the impact zone,
but the lightning was so powerful
that I couldn't dodge in time and got hurt.
I passed out by the roadside.
Luckily, Ling'er saved me.
But I didn't even see the great demon.
So,
you don't know much either.
I need to go back there.
I'll go with you.
Evil demons like that
don't deserve to stay in Kunmi.
Yunyuan made Kunmi a place where all clans live in harmony.
We can't let these demons ruin it.
Ling'er.
You'd better stay at Yunshenbuzhichu.
But I want to help you.
Ling'er, this is serious.
That snake demon ran Yunyuan and me in circles.
If it really is that snake demon,
and we have to fight him,
I might not be able to protect you.
But what if it's not the snake demon?
Yinfeng said
he was absorbing the villagers' essence.
If we let this continue,
more innocent people will get hurt.
Ling'er.
Diyun is right.
Our powers are weak,
so we shouldn't get in the way.
So you're afraid I'll hold you back.
No.
Ling'er.
Diyun.
Why don't you go scout again?
I'll stay and look after Sister.
Yinfeng.
It's windy outside.
I'll walk you back to your room.
Okay.
Is this kid doing this on purpose?
It's like this every time.
He goes to hunt demons secretly by himself,
and lies to me that they ran away.
Sister.
Why don't we
sneak out and go ourselves?
That's not a good idea.
They're just worried about me.
If I sneak off,
they'll be worried sick.
How about we leave a letter before we go?
We're just going to check the situation anyway.
Just scouting.
It shouldn't be dangerous.
After we leave the letter,
by the time they see it, I'll already be there.
They won't be able to send me back.
That's a good idea.
Young man,
you look a bit dull,
but you're actually quite sharp.
It's decided then.
Okay.
I'll protect you, Sister.
The sooner, the better.
Go pack up.
Okay.
The sooner, the better.
What a naive little girl.
So easy to fool.
Why is it like this?
Are the demons still here?
I don't know either, Sister.
Maybe
we should wait for King Kunmi and Diyun.
If that great demon is still here,
I'm afraid the two of us won't stand a chance.
Who says I can't handle it?
Without them,
I can still teach these demons a lesson.
Hey, Sister.
What a strong stench.
It seems these demons
have harmed many lives.
Watch out, Sister.
Such fresh spiritual energy.
Yinfeng, watch out.
Summon the Spirit Pearl, quickly!
With my soul,
enter my spirit.
Dragon God above,
grant me success.
Something's wrong.
Why does this Spirit Pearl have no soul?
What's going on?
Let me check again.