Who exactly are you?
Aran.
I am Ayin.
What's wrong?
Speak.
Who are you really?
Why did you approach me?
What do you want?
I adore you.
I want to be with you forever.
You...
You are a Demon.
Aran.
Be my Queen.
You are the Demon Lord.
Aran.
Marry me.
In your dreams.
Immortals and Demons are on different paths.
We don't belong to the same world.
Don't be delusional.
Those villages...
Did you do that to those villages?
Did you kill those people?
No.
Aran.
You care about the common people.
How could I harm them?
Aran.
Marry me.
Let us protect the world together.
What do you say?
Where are those people?
They have been settled properly.
Don't worry, Aran.
On the day of our grand wedding,
I will make sure the whole world
comes to congratulate us.
Whatever you want then,
I will give it to you.
You've lost your mind.
Open it.
The barrier you set yourself,
even you can't open it.
How could I open it?
You...
Don't think this will hold me.
Let me go.
Are you all right?
Senior Brother.
I'm fine.
Why are you here?
To take you back, of course.
To be my Heavenly Queen.
I will settle today's score with you
another day.
Let's go.
Ayin.
Have you gone mad?
Aran.
I just want you to be my wife.
Lunatic.
Do you not know Immortals and Demons are on different paths?
Senior Brother will soon find out I'm missing.
He will definitely come for me.
And I will only marry Senior Brother.
I said I would marry you.
And I will.
Aran.
It's only been a few days.
and you're about to marry your Senior Brother?
Is it...
just because he is the Heavenly Emperor?
Don't touch me.
Since Aran
does not want to be the Queen of our Demon Tribe,
then I will kill the Heavenly Emperor,
unify the Three Realms,
and let you continue to be
the Heavenly Queen.
Lunatic.
Where am I?
Does it feel familiar?
Very familiar?
I built this especially for you in the Demon Realm.
It's a little different from our cottage in the Human Realm,
but don't worry, Aran.
I promise to turn the Demon Realm
into a colorful new world.
I won't allow
you to do anything to harm the innocent.
Okay.
Whatever you say, Aran.
Later,
I'll come back to keep you company.
My Lord.
Did you find it?
My Lord,
I found out that
the Spirit Pearl passed down by the Dragon Clan
is the key to obtaining the Seven-Colored Stone.
The Dragon Clan.
No wonder I traveled the Human Realm for so long
and never found it.
Speak your mind.
I'm in a good mood today.
I wanted to say that
the Dragon Clan and the Heavenly Clan have been allies for generations.
With the Heavenly Queen now in the Demon Realm,
if we try to take the Spirit Pearl now,
it might force the Dragon and Heavenly Clans to join forces
against us.
And your injuries haven't fully healed.
I am worried...
My injuries are fine.
Regarding my wedding tomorrow,
handle the arrangements yourself.
Yes, My Lord.
The Love-Locking Curse.
The so-called righteous Heavenly Clan.
Nothing but despicable hypocrites.
They actually cast a curse on Aran.
Who?
Who broke the Love-Locking Curse?
It was...
Don't even think about escaping the Demon Realm.
Why did you seal my powers?
To keep you from running away, of course.
You...
You're certainly direct.
Aran.
My feelings for you are real.
I've never lied to you.
Aran.
We spent so much time together in the Human Realm.
Didn't you feel anything for Ayin?
Not even a little bit?
Feelings?
Aran.
Turn around.
Don't look.
Oh.
I'll go get some food.
Earlier...
Oh.
The fruit I picked is really sweet.
Taste it.
How is it?
Is it sweet?
I think it's sweet, too.
Is this what love feels like?
No.
I've known for as long as I can remember
that Senior Brother is my destiny.
I must protect the world with him.
I couldn't possibly fall for another man.
No.
I don't believe you.
You can lie,
but your eyes and your heart
cannot.
I can only marry my Senior Brother.
From the moment I was born,
my destiny with him was sealed.
Aran,
no destiny is sealed at birth.
He is lying to you.
Don't try to drive a wedge between Senior Brother and me.
He would never lie to me.
It doesn't matter.
If you don't want to admit to the past,
that's fine.
But from now on,
you will remember your true feelings.
Without the Love-Locking Spell,
I'd like to see how that Heavenly Emperor controls you now.
I'm tired.
I need to rest.
Please leave.
All right.
Rest well.
After tomorrow,
we will never be apart again.
Goddess Xingran's Love-Locking Spell is broken.
What is destined to come
will come eventually.
A Love Tribulation.
How is she?
Why hasn't Aran woken up yet?
Goddess Xingran was struck by spiritual power from two realms.
Her internal organs are shattered,
and her spiritual roots are damaged.
She needs daily spiritual healing
to recover.
Okay.
Then I will transfer spiritual power to her every day
until she is fully healed.
Your Majesty,
there is something I don't know if I should mention.
It concerns Aran's injuries.
Speak freely.
Do not hide anything.
Her injuries are not critical.
They can be treated.
However,
just now,
I accidentally discovered an anomaly in her Love Vein.
What does that mean?
Soon,
Goddess Xingran will face a Love Tribulation.
And this tribulation may alter the fate of many,
including yours, Your Majesty.
I fear for your throne...
Are you saying
that Aran's husband will not be me,
but someone else?
The variables are too great.
I dare not make wild predictions.
The Love-Locking Spell.
Use the Love-Locking Spell.
Seal Aran's Love Vein
so she cannot fall in love with anyone else.
That is a forbidden technique.
The Ancestral Emperor long ago decreed
that no forbidden techniques are to be used.
Moreover,
given Goddess Xingran's current condition,
she cannot withstand the spell.
Such a forbidden technique...
What would you have me do?
Watch helplessly as she falls for another?
Watch her take
the Phoenix Tribe's hundred thousand elites,
marry someone else,
and become a threat to the Celestial Tribe?
Goddess Xingran was raised to be the Heavenly Empress.
She wouldn't do that.
I'm just being cautious.
After all, I...
...love her.
Welcome to my wedding.
Ye Yin.
Hand over the Heavenly Queen.
Here with me,
there is no Heavenly Queen.
There is only
the Queen.
Hand over Ah Ran.
Or I will bathe your Demon Realm in blood.
If you're here for the wedding,
I welcome you.
If you're here to cause trouble,
then let's see if you're capable.
What happened?
Ah Yin?
Let's go take a look.
It really opened.
Ah Ran.
The one who put the Love-Locking Curse on Ah Ran
doesn't deserve to speak her name.
So you broke the Love-Locking Curse.
If it weren't for me,
I wouldn't have guessed
that the Heavenly Emperor who preaches justice
could be so despicable.
Even without the Love-Locking Curse,
Ah Ran...
...she still belongs to me.
In your dreams.
I won't give you that chance.
Stop!
My Queen.
His Lordship gave orders.
This is between him and the Heavenly Emperor.
If you don't want to trigger a war between immortals and demons,
and see corpses everywhere,
please stay by my side.