♪Wander through the bustling world♪
♪How could we forget each other?♪
♪Indescribable contemplation♪
♪Under the bright moon,
I enter the realm of dreams♪
♪Could you be the one in my dreams?♪
♪Only then will I look back with joy♪
♪Do you understand? Are you flustered?♪
♪Are you weary? Just let it be a memory♪
♪Shall we forget or shall we anticipate?♪
♪Either way♪
♪My feelings are as tender as summer♪
♪Holding hands, I want to see
the four seasons flourish with you♪
♪Warming the ends of the earth♪
♪Finally, in this boundless world,
everything is under the embrace of longing♪
=Blooming Days=
=Episode 19=
Nice gun.
Lianchu.
There're many people.
We should put it back.
He Lianxin.
You should be named a wet blanket.
You're trying to mess with me, right?
I want to save your life.
I don't need you to save my life.
If you could save any life,
you
should've save your sons,
who died one after another.
Lianxin.
Isn't this gun
as good as Lianxiu's?
Greetings, Your Highness.
The prince wanted to see you.
Bring the gun along.
(He Yunshuo's Ninth Son, He Lianjian)
Nice gun.
It matches your honourable status.
Forgive me, father.
I was just foolish.
Foolish?
No.
You weren't foolish.
I am instead.
I remember
you asked
many times for the gun
and I didn't give it to you.
I gave it to Lianxiu as a reward today.
You're the heir.
You saw the gun
being taken by Lianxiu.
Of course you feel upset about it.
I wouldn't dare.
You wouldn't dare?
Speaking of this,
I was foolish in another way.
You're the heir since birth.
I wanted
to nurture the tolerance
that a prince should have
since you're little.
I found you the best teacher
and gave you the best.
You even enjoyed
the same treatment as I got.
I did it so that you wouldn't
say you wouldn't dare
in anything.
When you disappointed me,
I blamed Yuan Baili,
your study companions
and all servants around you,
but I forgot
I was the cause
of your arrogance.
I understand.
You're
indeed
very
disappointed in me.
Of course.
I was so pleased when you
advised me to cancel the hunt,
but you did this
today unexpectedly.
Other than
thinking about your petty matters
every day,
how many times
did you practise riding and shooting?
What could you hit if I give
this gun to you?
A bird?
A pig?
A mung bean?
Father.
Why do you want to humiliate me?
Have I wronged you?
Lianjian.
Yes.
Aren't you practising shooting?
Compete with Lianchu.
Really?
Father.
What do you want to shoot?
I...
The cup.
Do it.
Here you go.
Step aside.
Father.
Do you really want to humiliate me?
If you don't take over the gun,
it's self-humiliation.
Take it.
Shoot it.
Your turn.
Aim and pull the trigger.
It's simple.
Shoot with the gun.
It's really simple.
Take it.
Shoot there.
There.
Guards!
Physician!
Call the physician.
Call him!
Don't be angry with Lianchu.
Otherwise,
he won't
play with me anymore.
Guards!
Young Master Xin.
How is it?
Just as you expected,
The prince told outsiders
that Young Master Jian
only had an acute disease.
The physician was urgently
summoned to treat him.
Since father
still has the heart to defend Lianchu,
there is still a way out.
Yes.
Beiyi.
How certain are you
in treating a gunshot wound?
A gunshot wound is rare.
I can only try my best.
Go back to prepare the medicine.
Do it as fast as you can.
You must save Lianjian.
Noted.
It seems that we still have to
add fuel to the heir's fire.
We have to think of a way
to do it.
I've
got it ready for you.
Your Highness,
I've talked to the physician.
They're preparing
medicine for Young Master Jian.
Leave now.
Aren't you the heir's guard?
Your Highness.
I have to risk my life to report something.
Go ahead.
Would my father believe it?
He's in a high position.
Of course he's afraid of assassination,
especially by the heir
that he has appointed
for over 30 years.
The heir has reserved sufficient power.
The prince would believe it
even if he's reluctant.
Don't follow me.
I want to walk alone.
I served beside the heir just now.
He said
you must be bearing a grudge
against him because of Young Master Jian.
Rather than of being deposed by you,
it would be better...
It would be better...
What is it?
He'd rather strike first.
Make way.
Why should I?
Don't you see I'm working?
Take a detour.
Why don't you...
Mao Da.
Greetings, Your Highness.
I guessed
you could hold out.
Surprisingly, you're living well.
You're contented
with peace of mind.
Very well.
Not really.
I'm only able to endure loneliness.
It's not difficult to endure loneliness.
It's difficult
to endure injustice.
With your words,
I could endure any injustice
in the world.
I believe in you
but I can't save you.
Do you hate me?
You're the master of Quliang,
but there're still things you can't do.
No matter how great your power is,
they're your family after all.
Family?
Can't Quliang
tolerate my family?
The weather is getting cold.
This place is colder
than the southern outskirts.
I'll let Yu Dechang
send you some tailors
and...
No.
Maybe you could leave the courtyard soon.
I hope your words will come true.
I'm leaving. Go back.
Have a safe trip, Your Highness.
Luckily,
today,
you stopped me, Ms. Lian.
Otherwise,
I would've ended up scolding the prince.
Forget about staying in the courtyard.
(Look, Your Highness.)
The bird has fallen to death.
The birds
saw only food.
They fought one another.
Their hatred fed on envy.
In this case,
will the female bird feed
as kindly as usual?
I believe
the female bird has the nature
of feeding its children.
It's also the nature
that a bird is greedy about food.
It will be less greedy
when it grows up.
I'm afraid if it remains greedy,
it will cause a great calamity.
Mao Da, bring the horse.
Noted.
Ms. Lian, where do you want to go?
Deer Terrace.
Young Master Xin is in danger.
Oh no!
How is it no prescribed yet?
The gun's power was too strong.
I couldn't feel the pulse
of Young Master Jian in person.
So...
Stop.
Just tell me
how long Lianjian can stay alive.
Till daybreak.
Daybreak?
I can only
be the heir until then.
Are you still thinking about this
when we're losing Lianjian?
Stay calm.
The best physician is on his way.
I'll
meet father
with you.
You're guilty in this matter.
You must admit your mistake.
Do you hear me?
All right.
Good.
Later...
Later,
we'll meet
at father's tent later.
Your Highness.
Your cloak.
sincerely repent
As long as you could before the prince,
he wouldn't punish the heir heavily.
I'll go
to see my father first.
(The heir said)
(he must act
before Young Master Jian dies)
(We should lose no time. It'll be tonight.)
Where is Lianxin?
Who's there?
Why are you here?
Girl.
It's been two years.
I really...
Actually,
if I wasn't here,
you could've become
the fish in the net.
The prince
should've believed a slanderous charge
and thought you wanted to kill him.
How do you know?
I met the prince.
His eyes was full of tears
when he saw a bird dying
in the fight for food.
He said
endless greed would
cause a great calamity.
He must have thought of his children.
He also said I would leave
the southern courtyard.
I was banished by you.
I can't leave
without your pardon,
unless...
I can't leave unless
you lose your power
and it isn't up to you anymore.
The prince
should've plotted an ambush.
Leave now.
No, I can't leave the heir.
Are you still thinking about the heir?
The heir has made a mistake,
but I can't let him be framed by others.
He Lianxin.
The prince is already suspecting you.
Have you considered
how dangerous it is now?
He Lianxin.
When will you finally believe me?
Seize him!
How dare you!
I'm the heir!
What do you want to do?
You...
I'm the heir!
What do you want to do?
Why do so many of you
ambush at my father's tent?
What is your intention?
Let me go!
Father.
Father!
They all are my trusted aides.
They are loyal.
As for you,
I want to ask
about your intention
of breaking into my tent at night.
Forgive me.
What are you doing?
As long as Young Master Xin pled for you,
you  would get through this safely.
Father!
That...
That isn't my dagger!
Father.
(When He Yunshuo loses)
(the last vestige of his expectation)
(for his son whom he's loved for years,)
(he won't entrust Quliang)
(and his lifetime promise
made to the Emperor)
(to this son.)
Thank you.
Fine.
You still want to save me,
even after how I treated you.
Why?
You still want to save me after I caused
the death of our child.
Why?
I ruined your marriage
and banished you
to the southern courtyard.
You still saved me.
Why?
Do you really hate me
as much as you say you do
or are you lying to me?
♪Inner feelings like clouds♪
♪Would it be out of reach?♪
You're overthinking it.
I helped you
only because of the outcast status thing.
I can retreat
as soon as you're safe.
Once.
Even if it's just once,
♪It melts frost♪
♪Are you fed up? You must
be missing that person♪
♪Forget each other? Look at each other♪
have you
ever missed me?
♪Eventually, the entire world
is under longings♪
Young Master!
Young Master, where are you?
He Lianxin, I hate you!
Young Master!
Young Master.
You're here.
I'd been looking for you.
I heard something happened to the heir.
I'm very worried about you.
Are you all right?
(He Lianchu didn't abide
by the ancestor's conduct)
(and the prince's teaching.)
(He has lost ability
to handle political affairs.)
(He has lost conduct
that unites the officials.)
(The heir of Prince An)
(mustn't be him.)
(The Emperor grants He Yunshuo's appeal)
(to depose He Lianchu
from the position of the heir)
(and detains him in his mansion.)
Lianxin.
I've punished
everyone who came to plead for him.
Do you still want to plead for him?
Father.
Deposing the heir is an important matter.
Please think twice.
You're close to Lianchu.
I guessed
you would take part in it,
but you didn't.
So this is the only thing
I'm relieved about.
Lianxin.
Don't be another Yuan Baili.
What brings you here?
You told me
you're saved,
thanks to Lian'er.
I'm thankful.
So I came for a visit.
Yes.
It's thanks to her.
Unfortunately,
that's not for saving me.
I don't feel cold.
Lingwei refused to eat just now
and spilled the food.
I asked her whose fault it was.
She said it's Zhihui.
(Shen Jingrong's Daughter, Lingwei (Childhood))
Such a young child
has learnt to speak against her heart
and the heart of an adult
is much more complicated.
Who knows what is really
on an adult's mind?
Forgive me.
Young Master.
On the other day,
Zhiyue gave me something.
She said she found it
at Lianwei House.
It could make you sad.
So
I didn't dare to take it out.
Ms. Lian sewed this handkerchief
for you before she was banished.
(Xin)
(Once.)
(Even if it's just once,)
have you ever missed me?
I recall
the pain you give me
every day
so that I can remind myself
every time.
I'll never forget.
I hate you
every day.
(Girl.)
(Do you really speak
against your heart?)
Since you keep something in your heart,
rather than speculating alone over here,
why don't you go to that person
and ask her directly?
Go to sleep when you're tired.
Ms. Lian.
It's dark.
Rest early.
It's fine.
Just few more stitches to completion.
Who is it?
Mao Da and Mao Er.
It smells great. Is it ready?
It's just done.
It's freshly stewed to warm you up.
Thank you for thinking about me.
You've come at the right time.
These are for the two of you.
What are these?
The mansion received new wool.
The weather gets cold.
You often travel outside.
Wear it close to your body.
It can keep your knees warm.
I'll serve you with the soup.
We...
We lost our parents since we're little.
No one ever treats me
as good
as you.
You're nice to me.
I surely keep you in mind.
That is how people are.
One's family
may not be as close as friends.
Ms. Lian.
Drink it while it's warm.
It smells so great.
Hot.
Blow it before you drink.
Go back.
Go back to rest.
Try it.
Ms. Lian, it smells great.
Ms. Lian.
We're forced to poison you to death.
You mustn't
blame us after you go to hell.
My heart...
She's not dead?
No.
(It's hard not to get suspicious,)
(with your actions just now.)
Hot.
You're so cruel.
Ms. Lian treated you well
over the last two years.
She saved everything for you,
not to mention the monetary reward
during Spring Festival.
She even remembered
to give you auspicious tassels.
She didn't look at the things
sent over by Mr. Lv
and she sewed kneelets for you,
but what about you?
Ms. Lian
shouldn't have been kind to you.
Dongli!
Stop talking.
Ms. Lian.
We know
you're kind to us.
We swore before
that we wouldn't sell you out
no matter how much money was offered,
but this time, it's different.
It has nothing to do with money.
Our lives matter.
Who was it?
Who threatened you?
We swore
we wouldn't sell you out anymore.
Today,
I'll tell you who it is.
He is...
Ma Da!
Ms. Lian!
Ma Da, wake up!
Why?
Are you assaulting us
after you failed to poison me?
Mao Er!
Mr. Lv.
Mao Er.
Nan Ruzhen.
Thank you.
Thank you for reminding me.
Although you've escaped this time,
it won't lucky for you
to survive the crisis everytime.
If Nan Ruzhen knows
the assassination failed,
she'll go even further.
Dongli and Li Tang.
Yes.
It's time to go back.
Young Master!
Young Master.
We've received an urgent report.
The southern courtyard
was broken in last night.
What about her?
How is she doing?
The details are unclear.
I only heard...
Yes?
I only heard that the robbers
fought with the guards.
They all died.
Girl!
Madam, it's time for the meal.
Not now.
I want to wait for Lianxin.
I want him to see
my best look as soon as he comes back.
Where is my hairpin?
My jade hairpin.
Where is it?
You're wearing it.
My poor memory.
Do I look good?
Yes.
You're a great beauty.
Anything is nice on you.
You're clever.
Ms. Lian has been confused for some time.
She could recognise people at first,
but not anymore
after she was frightened last night.
Why did no one tell me
about what happened?
Ms. Lian was a servant-concubine
who is banished.
No one else
would dare to disturb you.
I'm, however,
thankful to those robbers.
Hadn't they killed anyone at the courtyard,
you wouldn't have appeared.
Ms. Lian.
- Don't catch me.
- Stop running. Be careful.
Su Nanchun?
Let me do it.
Su Nanchun knows how to comb one's hair?
Ms. Lian, it's Young Master Xin.
Leave us.
Not Young Master Xin.
He is Su Nanchun.
Young Master Xin doesn't want me anymore.
He doesn't want me and the child.
Young Master Xin...
Why wouldn't he want you?
He sent Su Nanchun
over to serve,
accompany you,
wash your face
and comb your hair.
Really?
He sent you over?
It's true.
Yes.
He sent me over.
♪They deepen the bind♪
He said
he was sorry
for not coming to see you.
Sometimes,
it's because of his pride.
Sometimes it was jealousy.
He also said
♪Deceitful afterglow♪
he felt as if his heart
was cut by a knife
when he saw you
in this situation.
♪See you through♪
♪Despite twists and turns♪
♪The scenery in my life
is plain yet beautiful♪
♪Under your propulsion♪
He said
he missed you very much.
How did you
get hurt here?
How did you hurt yourself?
How? Let me see.
It's this. Remove it.
No.
Girl.
It's easy to get hurt now.
Stop wearing jewellery, okay?
No.
Young Master gave this to me.
Please don't take it away,
okay?
Sorry.
Madam.
Young Master Xin has left.
He will come.
He still loves me.
He wouldn't
let me wait for nothing.
He also wouldn't
hurt my heart again and again.
Ruhua.
Do you remember
for whom he kept me waiting last time?
Young Master, everything has been loaded.
Set off!
(General Xin's Mansion)
(Baoji Clinic)
Ms. Lian.
Young Master Xin sent Su Nanchun
to pass a message.
He would leave Quliang
on a business trip for a few days.
He might not make it here.
Tell Su Nanchun
I've run out of medicine,
and Young Master may make another trip.
Ms. Lian.
Young Master
can't leave in this case.
I know.
He hasn't been working
for the prince
because of your illness.
I know.
Just do it.
Noted.
After the heir is deposed,
the young masters
are busy working
for the inheritance.
Lianxin and Lianxiu
had the highest hope at first,
but Lianxin has been holding back for you.
Sure. Let Young Master Xiu
have an advantage.
What else could he do?
Lianxiu has won the favour
of half the population in Quliang.
Even the prince and officials
compliment him.
You're wrong.
The prince and officials
won't compliment him simultaneously.
Yao, you...
Lianxin asked to resign again?
Yes.
He wanted to get medicine for Ms. Lian.
He refused to leave Quliang.
Good.
Very well.
I plan to appeal to my father.
Surprisingly,
Lianxin receives the job
coveted by many people
over half a year,
but he let go of it.
Luo Qinglian
got crazy at the right time.
Do you think
that's really great?
The death anniversary
of the late princess consort
is a few days away.
The prince wants
to pay his respects in person.
He'll be accompanied by Young Master Xin
if you aren't in Quliang.
Let it be.
The heir has been deposed anyway.
The late princess consort
isn't as important as before.
Luo Qinglian.
I thought she was
a stumbling block last time.
Surprisingly, she is a ladder to me.
Come on.
Get some fresh air
with me at the garden.
(You've made Young Master Xin stay again.)
Since someone else wants to do it,
I should let him.
Lian'er.
The heir was deposed too soon.
He Lianxin is still fledging.
The foundation he built in hardships
has left with almost nothing
over half the year.
Why do you want to do this?
You'll find out soon.
Success or failure
depends on this time.
(Lian'er.)
(What are you)
(plotting?)
(Secondary Courtyard)
Come down, Ms. Lian!
Ms. Lian!
It's no joke if you fall.
What is she doing?
Young Master.
You're here just in time.
Ms. Lian called herself a bird
since she got up in the morning.
She insisted that she should
fly up to the rooftop.
A bird?
She does have many ideas.
Hurry and think of a way.
Fine.
Girl.
You mustn't jump down.
We're birds,
but our wings
aren't as useful
as before.
You can't jump.
We?
Is Su Nanchun a bird too?
♪From the chaotic dust♪
♪Gracefully stepping out♪
♪Only then did I understand
the beauty of the world♪
♪Why, and for what♪
♪Holding pure intentions
in my heart♪
♪Clinging to black and white♪
♪Only then did I realize
that the path is simple♪
♪It is love♪
♪When fate♪
♪Surges like deep clouds♪
♪Regardless of♪
♪What experiences may come♪
♪Unable to linger♪
♪Mountains and waves
are insignificant♪
♪My promises to you remain♪
♪Unafraid of obstacles
along this worldly path♪
♪Worries are few♪
♪The moon sets, stars scatter,
and mournful sounds ring♪
♪My promises to you remain♪
♪Life after life♪
♪Will follow my heart's desires♪
♪Forever unchanged♪