♪Wander through the bustling world♪
♪How could we forget each other?♪
♪Indescribable contemplation♪
♪Under the bright moon,
I enter the realm of dreams♪
♪Could you be the one in my dreams?♪
♪Only then will I look back with joy♪
♪Do you understand? Are you flustered?♪
♪Are you weary? Just let it be a memory♪
♪Shall we forget or shall we anticipate?♪
♪Either way♪
♪My feelings are as tender as summer♪
♪Holding hands, I want to see
the four seasons flourish with you♪
♪Warming the ends of the earth♪
♪Finally, in this boundless world,
everything is under the embrace of longing♪
=Blooming Days=
=Episode 7=
In the world,
people will be nice to you
if you have value.
If not, you'll be abandoned.
Does that include
Madam De?
What?
You keep calling your mother
while you were dreaming.
It's not Madam De.
You'd better forget
everything that you heard.
I'm not interested in remembering it.
I just want to let you know
that there are many people
who take relationships seriously.
People are not as cold as you think.
Are you talking about Lv Beiyi?
Yes.
He may be willing to die for you,
but you may not be
the most important to him.
To Lv Beiyi,
his life is only the third
most important thing to him.
You're not the most important
to him either.
Fame and power is.
Girl,
I'll make a bet with you.
One day,
you'll know that I am right.
Don't let me see you the day you end up
crying alone.
Don't worry,
there won't be such a day.
Lv Village is right ahead.
This is where you
agreed to meet Ms. Lian.
My old house is in front.
I think my family is living here
after our place was seized.
I wonder if Ms. Lian
managed to escape.
I wonder if she'll get here
in time tomorrow.
Mr. Lv.
("The pain of being in the outcast status
is more important than life and death.)
(It's more important than relationships)
(with your family and loved ones.")
(Zhao's Ancestral Hall)
You two, search over there!
Come here! Over here!
Sir,
the soldiers tailing the leper were killed.
It must be them. Let's go.
Yes.
What's wrong?
I was told to pass on a message
from your brother.
that they've found traces of Young Master.
They should be able
to get hold of him soon.
At the same time,
he wants me
to ask you once again
whether you have changed your mind.
Should we go ahead as planned?
Tell him nothing has changed.
Go ahead.
Yes.
I
made a deal
to meet them here.
(Lv Village)
Then we shall part ways here.
When I go back,
I will tell them
you died saving me.
My father will be sad for a while,
but he won't ask questions.
Starting from today,
you two
should travel around the world together.
I'm thankful
that you're willing to change your mind
to fulfill our wishes.
However, you are badly injured.
Allow us to first
send you back to your mansion.
I'm not fulfilling your wishes.
I'm just repaying you
for saving my life.
I won't accept it
no matter what you do.
I'm even less interested
to watch the two of you
displaying your affection.
I'm leaving.
Ms. Lian!
Dongli.
Dongli, where is Yi?
Where's Yi?
Mr. Lv.
Ms. Lian, stop kneeling.
You've been here for a long time.
His whole family
died because of their status.
It's all my fault.
They died because of me.
All because of me.
Get up.
You won't be able to bring them back to life,
no matter how much you blame yourself.
Dongli.
Ms. Lian, stop doing it.
Your hands are bleeding.
My woman is not allowed
to do work like this.
I'm not your woman.
You still are for now.
No need to be upset.
Soon,
you will get what you wish.
Will Mr. Lv still come back?
Will he hate Ms. Lian?
If he returns,
I will be forever thankful
and repay him for the rest of my life.
If he doesn't,
I won't blame him either.
I will help him for the rest of my life.
How do you plan to do that?
I'll do anything,
as long as he wants it
and it's within my power.
Outcast status?
So what if he's in the outcast status?
If you...
If you are willing to come back with me
and I succeed one day,
his outcast status will be altered.
Please protect us, Buddha.
Be careful!
Ms. Lian!
Kill them!
Be careful!
Get them!
Kill them!
Go!
Lianxin!
Brat.
If you were any later,
you'd have been collecting my body.
You wouldn't allow anything
to happen to yourself
if you didn't see me.
Please forgive me
for coming late.
Young Master Xin!
Forgive me
for coming late.
Brothers-in-law,
please rise.
We're all family.
What's with the formalities?
Speak!
Who commanded you to do this?
If you tell, your families
will be spared.
Young Master Xin.
They've all taken poison
to commit suicide.
The heir would of course make sure
that none of this would trace back to him.
Lianxin,
Ms. Lian
must be
my famous sister-in-law.
Whether or not she's your sister-in-law
depends on the choice she makes.
Since you're all safe and sound,
I shall make a move first.
Let her go.
Lianxin!
Do you know what the heir
is saying about you in front of father?
He accused you of plotting to kill him
and harming the people in the process.
If she leaves,
no one can prove your innocence.
He Lianxin, are you
going back on your word?
How dare you!
You're not going anywhere.
You are coming back with us.
Once the matter is settled
and you prove Young Master Xin's innocence,
how hard can it be for us to let you go?
How hard can it be?
He is willing to let me go,
but will the prince let me go?
Long delays cause complications.
There can be more trouble.
Then it's meant to be.
It is kind
of Young Master Xin to fulfil your wishes.
Do you really think
that a servant-concubine like you
can make your own decisions?
Brother,
make a decision.
How long will you be in misery
if you don't marry Lv Beiyi?
For a lifetime.
Then, go.
Lianyi.
Lianxin!
What's wrong with you?
You life matters.
Young Master Yi,
you're exaggerating the thing.
Even a tiger would not eat its cubs.
No matter how mad the prince is,
at most, he'll just disqualify him
from succeeding him.
He wouldn't kill him.
How can a royal family be compared
to the families of ordinary people?
Losing father's trust would result
in not being able
to fulfil our lifelong goals.
How is that different from dying?
I've always been arrogant
and never begged anyone for anything,
but today...
Lianyi!
I beg you, Ms. Lian, to save my brother.
Ms. Lian, we beg you
to return with Young Master Xin.
What are you...
I dare not accept this.
It's getting dark.
I want to wait a while longer.
He will come.
Listen to me.
No one is allowed to hurt you,
including yourself, okay?
I will alter your outcast status.
Everyone has his or her own destiny.
I remember the first time
I saw Madam Yao.
She told me
that a woman did everything for men.
It was a woman's destiny.
I answered her
that I wanted to live my own life
and take control of my own life.
I couldn't do it before this.
Will I still have a chance?
Young Master Xin,
you once doubted the possibility
of true love
that required nothing in return.
I never do.
I'm willing to give up everything
just to have one person
to grow old together with.
I thought
that he would think the same.
♪Gentle breeze brushes across the face♪
♪Look up♪
♪Moonlight on a moonlit night♪
♪Memories buried, so many past moments♪
♪Love and hate, ups and downs♪
Young Master Xin,
I will go back with you
to aid you in your great plan.
I will never betray you or run away,
but remember what you said.
If you have a chance,
help Lv Beiyi alter his outcast status.
If I have the power,
I will alter Lv Beiyi's outcast status.
This is my promise to you.
Swear upon this comb.
♪A lifetime of entanglement♪
They say
that this represents two people
growing old together.
♪Fine rain, murmuring, people are waiting♪
♪Look back, like a dream, like a fantasy♪
♪Hidden in the dim lights♪
♪Holding hands, gazing at the vast stars♪
♪A tear stirs ripples♪
♪Just for your sweet smile♪
♪You remain on the opposite shore,
the river curves around♪
♪The music ends, people disperse,
the long night road is endless♪
♪Engraved in the stone tablet of three lifetimes♪
♪Regret is deep, fate is shallow♪
♪Waiting for flowers to fall and scatter♪
♪Pain flows into the heart♪
♪The night with a sail♪
♪This life, I'm with you♪
(Mansion of Prince An)
The Title Granding Ceremony begins.
In accordance to the heavens,
this is an order to you.
As a response
to the request of He Yunshuo,
Prince An of Quliang,
Prince An's sons will be
given the titles as followed.
His eldest son, He Lianbo,
(He Yunshuo's Eldest Son, He Lianbo)
will be given the title of a lord.
His fourth son, He Lianxiu,
will be given the title
of General of Valiant.
His fifth son, He Lianzuo,
will be given the title
of General of Protection.
Announce this to everyone
and let this be known to all.
We thank His Majesty for his grace.
You all may rise.
His Majesty's acceptance of my request
is his trust in me,
but there is one thing
that I am ashamed of.
I'm sure everyone
has heard of what happened.
A few days ago,
on the way to visit the ancestral tomb,
many big stones
fell off the mountain
and killed some of our people.
I am heartbroken.
They all say that Quliang
is peaceful and prosperous now.
Are those falling stones
a sign of peace?
Can we claim to have prosperity
when the people have died?
Some people say
that this is nature's will
and that I am not the one to blame.
According to this fortune teller,
if it is nature's will,
then I shall ask
for the heaven's protection.
I have prayed.
However, in the last few days,
I can't eat well nor sleep well.
No matter how I think of it,
it is not heaven's will.
It is a man-made disaster!
He Lianxin.
Yes.
Kneel.
You said those big stones
were intended for Lianxin?
Yes.
He escaped?
Yes, he did.
How did he get hurt then?
Is he faking it to deceive me?
It's true that he escaped,
but his injury is real as well.
He was injured while saving the people.
Are you saying that he risked his life
to save the people?
I saw it with my own eyes.
How were you able to see clearly
in the midst of the chaos?
I escaped quickly to a safe place.
So many men were unable to escape.
How did you, a weak woman,
manage that?
It's because I was prepared.
You're prepared?
What does that mean?
Were you already planning to escape?
Is Lianxin not good to you?
Young Master Xin is great to me.
It's exactly his kindness
that made my sins unforgivable.
Are you talking about Hui'er's death?
Your Highness.
My marriage was granted by you
and I am forever grateful to you.
However, my life
was also granted by you.
If my life was wasted away
in the Xin's Mansion,
wouldn't I let you down?
Do you know
that your words
are the exact opposite of the heir's?
Lianxin said he forgot everything.
You all have given me
a difficult problem.
I had no idea
what Young Master Xin said.
I also didn't know
what the heir said.
All I know is
what I'm telling you are all
I seen with my own eyes.
There is not a single lie.
You may not have seen
it with your own eyes,
but I believe
that you know what's going on.
Your Highness,
the people you sent
for investigation have returned.
(Secret Memorandum)
(Secret Memorandum
The Emperor's Letter)
He Lianxin
is benevolent and kind.
He loves the people as his own.
He shall be given the title
of General of Illustrious Virtue.
I thank His Majesty for his grace.
Thank you, father.
I'm not the one you need to thank.
Bring Luo Qinglian here.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Luo Qinglian's actions of protecting
Young Master Xin are meritorious.
Her righteousness, loyalty
and bravery are commendable.
You are gifted with
the late princess consort's jade flute.
It grants you death exemption for life.
Luo Qinglian,
from now on,
you shall stay
at Young Master Xin's mansion in peace.
Thank you, Your Highness,
for your kindness.
Rise.
Lianchu.
Father.
Do you know
why I asked for an imperial edict
to grant your brothers titles?
You wanted to inspire them
to make great achievements.
I wanted to inspire you!
Father,
I...
It seems I was wrong.
All right.
You don't have to greet me
in the next few days.
Take the time for self-reflection
in your mansion.
Why did you conceal the fact
that the heir wanted to kill me?
The heir was punished
exactly because I concealed that fact.
If I spoke the truth,
you'd have been the one punished.
Weren't you thinking of the same thing
when you said you forgot
about what happened?
Why would you question me,
your servant-concubine, about that?
Servant-concubine?
From now on,
I, Luo Qinglian,
am your servant-concubine.
I'm afraid that we'll have to
rely on each other in this lifetime.
Who did it?
What?
You're not the one who killed Hui'er.
Who did it?
I don't have evidence,
but I can swear upon my life
it was Mu Haiyao.
From now on,
you will say goodbye
to the past completely.
In addition to helping me to gain power,
you have one more important task
in your life starting from now.
Live well.
Welcome back, Young Master Xin.
Congratulations on receiving
the title of General of Illustrious Virtue.
You're well-informed.
You all may rise.
Thank you, Young Master Xin.
Paler.
Madam, Young Master Xin is back.
Why are you panicking?
Young Master Xin has a show to watch.
He won't return so quickly.
A show?
Yes.
The Madam Rui's show.
Huairui, what are you doing?
I ask for your forgiveness.
You've kept the house
in an orderly manner.
Why should you seek forgiveness?
Over the days,
you had been suffering
and almost lost your life.
As your wife,
I wasn't there by your side.
Please punish me for that.
How was that your fault?
Besides, didn't you send
Fang Erge?
I did,
but Erge didn't do anything
when he saw that you were in trouble.
Really?
Why didn't he act?
Was he scared
because there were too many people
or was the ground too wet
that the horses slipped?
Neither.
I told him to.
What a pity.
No matter how great and high
the position of the primary consort is,
it still doesn't come above
the honour of the Fang family.
I thought I was clever
for wanting to get evidence
of someone trying to harm you,
but I didn't expect
that you'd almost lose your life.
It was foolish of me.
I am ashamed
to be representing the household.
Please oust me
from my position as the primary consort.
Please reconsider it, Young Master Xin.
Everyone knows
that the first lady is virtuous.
Please show sympathy
for the loss of her son
and don't blame her.
Please show sympathy
for the loss of her son
and don't blame Madam Rui.
Enough.
Huairui,
the honour of the Fang family
is so important.
So I must return from the chaos.
I was able to rise from the ashes.
Otherwise, how could I be worthy
of being the Fang family's son-in-law?
Am I right, Huairui?
Thank you for your understanding.
Why would I blame you?
Stand up.
Everyone, get up.
I heard of Ms. Lian's contributions
to your safe return
and the title you received.
I'm flattered.
I just did what I was supposed to do.
Of course my woman
will go through life and death with me.
Su Nanchun.
Yes, Young Master Xin.
Order people to tidy up
Lianwei Mansion.
Starting from today,
Ms. Lian will no longer
live in Liuyun Cottage.
Yes, Young Master Xin.
Qinglian, just live there.
At least it won't
disappoint Yao.
Oh right, why don't I see Haiyao?
I've been trying to talk some
sense into her these days,
but I didn't know
she'd still be unwilling to see you.
What happened?
It's the heir.
I heard that Yao
heard something
from the heir
before this happened,
but I don't know why
this was concealed.
Madam, you were right.
Young Master Xin and Ms. Lian
are on their way here.
Also,
as expected, the first lady
was not punished.
To gain power,
he still has to rely
on the Fang family's support.
How could he punish her so easily?
Too bad I
thought I was being smart
and misjudged the person
who shared my bed
and Luo Qinglian.
Greetings, Young Master Xin.
Where is Madam Yao?
Madam is sick.
What's the illness?
Madam was worried
for your safety these days.
So she hadn't been
eating and sleeping well.
We did our best, but it was of no help.
When Madam heard that
you were returning today,
she was so excited
that she woke up early today.
Who knew
that she'd faint when she was
about to come out to greet you.
Have you asked for a physician?
Yes.
Physician Zhang from
Wang Mansion is inside.
We'd like to ask everyone
to please wait outside.
After the physician has checked on her,
I will...
No need for that.
Since Yao is not feeling well,
it's even more reason for us to see her.
Greetings, Young Master Xin.
Congratulations on receiving
the title of General of Illustrious Virtue.
All right. What's Madam Yao's sickness?
Another piece of great news.
Madam Yao is not sick.
She's three months pregnant.
Ruhua.
Greetings, Young Master Xin.
Get up.
What if
this affects the baby?
I'm not that precious.
Who says you're not?
How can my woman
and child
not be precious?
Go in and have a seat.
Don't stand around.
What if it affects the baby?
Come on, have a seat.
Ms. Lian,
Lianwei Mansion
is close to Weixi Pond.
The scenery is quite nice.
When Lady Mo
was pregnant
and wanted to move out
of Tinglan Pavilion,
Young Master Xin didn't pay her any attention.
He has given it to you.
It goes to show
his love for you.
Ms. Lian, this place is so pretty.
It's so much better than Liuyun Cabin.
(Lianwei House)
♪From the chaotic dust♪
♪Gracefully stepping out♪
♪Only then did I understand
the beauty of the world♪
♪Why, and for what♪
♪Holding pure intentions
in my heart♪
♪Clinging to black and white♪
♪Only then did I realize
that the path is simple♪
♪It is love♪
♪When fate♪
♪Surges like deep clouds♪
♪Regardless of♪
♪What experiences may come♪
♪Unable to linger♪
♪Mountains and waves
are insignificant♪
♪My promises to you remain♪
♪Unafraid of obstacles
along this worldly path♪
♪Worries are few♪
♪The moon sets, stars scatter,
and mournful sounds ring♪
♪My promises to you remain♪
♪Life after life♪
♪Will follow my heart's desires♪
♪Forever unchanged♪