♪Wander through the bustling world♪
♪How could we forget each other?♪
♪Indescribable contemplation♪
♪Under the bright moon,
I enter the realm of dreams♪
♪Could you be the one in my dreams?♪
♪Only then will I look back with joy♪
♪Do you understand? Are you flustered?♪
♪Are you weary? Just let it be a memory♪
♪Shall we forget or shall we anticipate?♪
♪Either way♪
♪My feelings are as tender as summer♪
♪Holding hands, I want to see
the four seasons flourish with you♪
♪Warming the ends of the earth♪
♪Finally, in this boundless world,
everything is under the embrace of longing♪
=Blooming Days=
=Episode 10=
Greetings, madams.
Ms. Lian.
Just now, Young Master Xin
sent someone to Lianwei House.
He said he wanted
to take you to Baizhen Lane.
I think there's good news for Ms. Lian.
Baizhen Lane,
as everyone knows,
is Lianxin's favourite place.
However, until now,
he's never let his wives
and concubines accompany him there,
myself included.
Madam,
Su Nanchun has arrived.
Let him in.
Madam Yao,
the prince just rewarded
a box of silk flowers to our mansion.
Young Master Xin knew you liked them.
He sent me
to deliver them promptly.
Are all in this box for me?
That's what Young Master Xin said.
Doesn't his wife even get any?
Young Master Xin said
that Official Mu had contributed a lot
and as long as you liked it,
everything would be yours.
He said it depended on you
whether others would have any.
I'm flattered.
Let Ms. Lian decide, shall we?
I dare not.
With all the love he has for you,
he could give you
the entire Langyue Hall,
not to mention a few fake flowers.
Su Nanchun.
Let Ms. Lian choose.
Madam Yao, you see
a few fake flowers,
but I see
the entire garden at our mansion.
I never realised
you could be a sweet talker.
Enough, choose a few.
Yes.
I know
my place.
I get to have a share
because
you have been gracious to me.
How could I overstep my boundaries?
All right, put the flower on you.
Thank you, Madam Yao.
Ms. Lian, this bracelet
seems quite precious.
It doesn't look like something
you would have.
It's from my ancestors.
I've always worn it.
Madams, please continue
your conversation.
I'll make a move first.
What are you doing?
Do you see
any inconsistency?
I don't,
but since when did it become
about trusting someone
based on whether they slip up or not?
It's not that.
I can't fathom
how someone who pretends to like us
would help
her enemy's family
and not give herself
any chance of making a comeback.
I'm tired. You should leave too.
Let's hope
this won't happen again.
Young Master Xin.
Why did you bring me here?
What else can you do here
but to spend money?
Young Master Xin,
welcome. Your presence is an honour.
Come on, have a seat.
Recently,
we've received a batch
of excellent items in our shop.
I'd like you to take a look.
Come on,
bring them over.
All right.
Have some tea.
Thank you.
Young Master Xin, look at this.
It's quite nice.
Many have tried on these earrings,
but none looks
as good as you do with them.
If I put the scallion
on this large pancake,
it is ready to be served.
You must be joking, Young Master Xin.
How can a face the size of a palm
look like a cake?
I have something even better.
Bring it over.
Yes.
Young Master Xin, take a look at this one.
The colour is good.
With a scale beam like this
and a weight,
it's the perfect match
for the large pancake.
Young Master Xin.
All these
are the treasures of our store.
If you don't fancy anything here,
we truly have nothing left.
You're being too humble, Mr. Zhang.
If even your shop has nothing to offer,
where else in Baizhen Lane
can one shop?
I'm not being humble.
You've almost browsed through
the entire Baizhen Lane.
If you found something you liked here,
we
would be honoured.
Unfortunately,
your standards are too high.
My shop has
truly run out of precious stuff.
Are you saying
that you've brought out everything?
We've brought out all of them.
Really?
Didn't you purchase
golden leaf filigree glass beads yesterday
from Lecture Bureau's Official Qi?
On the day before that,
you acquired the peony-patterned
porcelain vase from Official Feng
at the Magistrate's Office?
Also,
you even bought a silver platter
with scale-patterned enamel
from Mr. Zuo.
They were all purchased
at extremely low prices.
Where are these items? Show them to me.
Look.
I can't hide anything from you,
Young Master Xin.
I did buy those items,
but as you know, it's business
and it's all about buying and selling.
Those items
have been sold already.
- All of them?
- All of them.
- They're sold so quickly?
- Yes.
- All to one person?
- Right.
Who was so generous?
The buyer wishes to remain anonymous.
Young Master Xin,
you understand the rules.
Please don't make it difficult for me.
How long do you want to shop?
We'll shop until we
find something you like.
Do you mean shop
until I find something I like
or until you figure out
the secrets of Baizhen Lane?
Lately, Official Mu has worked hard.
If you want to reward anyone,
you should reward him.
I'm a bit tired.
Let me rest for a while.
Waiter, bring some tea.
Didn't you contribute too?
Haven't you been busy lately?
What could I be busy with?
I'm staying home all day.
How could I be busy?
Why
haven't I seen Li Tang?
He said he had some family matters
and applied leave.
He went home for a few days.
He'll be back today.
How come I heard
that someone saw him
outside the house of my fifth
sister-in-law's younger brother
who has stolen
money from the Treasury.
First, you provided a false testimony
to get Huairui punished.
Then, you provided information
to help Mu Tianshu to gain merit.
It seems like everything
is going according to Haiyao's plan.
What's your plan, girl?
I don't quite understand.
You know
that Madam Rui was wronged,
yet you're going with the flow.
Aren't we planning
for the same thing?
I don't have any plan.
I'm just the Idle Young Master,
who wants to spend my days
in this world of art and culture.
Are you?
However, I've heard recently
that Baizhen Lane
has been extremely merry.
All the high-ranking officials and nobles
are selling their treasures
to pay off their debts.
Who wants to pay back
and who doesn't?
It's all in this world of art and culture.
What else
do you know?
I do know something.
Whenever you feel awkward,
you'll speak in a prolonged manner.
You're so smumg.
Hey, let go.
Let go.
The one I think of year after year?
Only you and I know the feeling.
Shopkeeper,
please pack this ring.
It's quite unfortunate, Young Master Xin.
This ring has already been reserved.
Reserved again? Who reserved it?
This...
I see. The person
wants to remain anonymous.
I'm sorry, Young Master Xin.
Everything is fated.
It's fated to acquire something
or not.
Not getting it now
doesn't mean you won't
get it in the future.
Girl.
Fate is an effect, not a cause.
There's nothing of value here.
Who would buy them?
If I didn't keep some
of Official Li's belongings,
he wouldn't leave.
He said he's in a hurry
to repay the debt.
I only agreed to sell them for him.
Sell them for him?
That's if someone wants to buy them.
Go.
Throw them away.
Wait, these things...
Don't get the wrong idea,
Young Master Xin.
My shop never deals
with these low-quality items.
I was pestered and had no choice.
I'm taking these.
(Li's Residence)
Do you know whose house this is?
Don't take it.
Please come down.
Be careful.
(Li Qianmo's Father, Official Li)
Greetings, Young Master Xin.
Father-in-law, please get up.
Your Highness.
Young Master Xin has left Baizhen Lane.
Is everything done?
It's almost done.
First, he discovered the smuggling
in the Treasury
and pressured Young Master Zuo and others
to take the lead in repaying the money.
He's at Baizhen Lane now
to observe the situation
and control it.
The difficult task
of collecting the debts
is cleverly managed
by Young Master Xin.
I don't know
if Young Master Xin has passed your test.
Yu Dechang.
Yes.
Have you noticed anything
that doesn't seem right
about this situation?
It all appears
too calm
and too smooth, doesn't it?
Just wait and see.
The most heart-pounding
part of the story
has yet to happen.
(Li's Residence)
I never thought that Madam Mo would
be so lucky to have such kind father.
Other people borrow from the Treasury
for their own indulgences,
but Official Li
did it to help the poor.
I remember the first time
I met him a few years ago.
There was also a flood happend.
He sold his own fur coat
to buy grain for the disaster victims.
I asked him,
"How would you pass the winter?
Are you going
to sell all your silk clothes?"
Do you know what he said?
What did he say?
He said
that he had already
sold his silk clothes the previous year.
At that moment, I thought
that he was truly a good official.
No matter what,
I couldn't let him down.
Unfortunately,
aside from clearing his debt,
there's not much I can do for him.
I just hope
that Qianmo's child
can be born safely.
I'll take good care
of the child.
Aren't you afraid
that people will say you're unfair?
Unfair?
In this world,
there's good and bad, rich and poor,
and injustice everywhere.
I only believe
in one person's conscience.
What's the matter, girl?
Do you suddenly think I'm not so bad
after all?
Lv Beiyi
isn't the only good man
in the world.
Look at him being all stern and rigid.
What's good about him?
I'm much better than him
who's like a cold and hard stone, right?
Aren't you tired
of teasing me every day?
Why would I tease you?
You're the treasure I obtained
with a great horse.
I cherish you more than you can imagine.
Really?
Do you really like me that much?
If you like me so much,
you must be willing
to do whatever I want.
I think
there are too many women in your house.
I want you
to get rid
of all your women.
Since you
love the beauty more than power,
then the Fang and Mu families
are useless.
Even the title of your father
becomes meaningless.
Why don't we
elope and live happily together
under the moon and stars?
Wouldn't that be better?
If you're afraid,
please keep your distance
from me in the future.
I'm not a servant.
Where did this girl learn all this?
Miss, it's Young Master Xin.
I told you not to turn around.
What should we do now?
Follow me.
Quick.
Yuanxue.
Is that you, Yuanxue?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Maybe I was mistaken.
It's all right. Let's go.
My Lady, let's go back.
We'll go back when I've seen
whatever I want to see.
However, we...
What if your father finds out
we've gone out without his permission?
Forget about that.
(He Yunshuo's Daughter)
As long as we return before nightfall,
(He Yuanxue)
no one will know.
Who are you?
Stay away!
What are you doing?
Lady Xue.
Why did you try to kill me?
You got in the way of Young Master Xiu.
Enjoy your meal, sir.
Eat and drink well.
Sir, would you like anything to drink?
May I borrow this for a moment?
Hello, brother. Eight horses.
Help me.
Thank you, sir.
Have a pleasant journey.
Excuse me.
Here's your liquor.
Let me tell you,
This is the last of it.
Go somewhere else tomorrow.
It's okay if you come alone,
but you brought
a friend with you.
I'm talking to you. Do you hear me?
Also, you
seem feminine.
You don't look like a good person.
Keep your voice down.
Sorry!
- Why are you in such a hurry?
- Sorry!
What's the rush?
Can't you see where you're going?
What kind of person is this?
Help! Is anyone there?
Help...
Don't come any closer.
You...
Do you know who I am?
I...
Red beans on the dice.
Do you know how much I miss you?
In the future, when you drink,
you'll see how much I miss you.
Let's see if you would
still dare to do it.
Can you please take me somewhere?
Just tell me
whatever you want.
I will make sure...
I just want to peacefully
retrieve my jug
and find a place to drink quietly.
If you keep making noise,
I'll make sure you won't be able
to speak in the future.
Greetings, Madam Rou.
Why did you come unannounced?
(Xu Jirou's Maid, Huafu)
Huafu, bring some tea.
Yes.
It's been a while since I was released
from my confinement
and I hadn't come
to visit you, Madam Rou.
Please forgive me.
It's late and you've come to see me.
It's very kind of you.
Hui'er's bracelet isn't
suitable for you.
If you wear it for a long time,
it will hurt you.
I didn't expect
that you had such deep feelings
for Madam Yao.
I'm impressed.
I have
a message for you.
Insincerity begets insincerity,
while truthfulness
may not beget truthfulness.
When you sleep with the tiger,
watch out,
you might be hurt one day.
Dongli, let's go.
When Madam Rou returned,
did you notice her hands?
What happened to her hands?
They were very red.
I deliberately touched them
and they felt like ice,
like a pair of hands
exposed to the harsh winter.
What does that mean?
It's not winter now.
Where did she go
to have made her hands so cold?
The Ice Chamber.
It's not summer.
What would she be doing there
so late at night?
Ms. Lian, be careful.
Ms. Lian, take it slow.
It's so cold.
It's all ice here.
Is there really something there?
Ms. Lian, does that mean...
The children will be exchanged.
Have a rest.
He doesn't dare to come in.
He doesn't dare
because you're here.
However, you're going
to leave eventually.
He's waiting for you to leave.
You mentioned that you
wanted to go somewhere.
Where is it?
Kongxin Temple.
Is the life of
a wealthy young lady too leisurely,
that you want
to play the game of becoming a nun?
You wouldn't understand.
Since I was born,
this is my first time
seeing the moon outside.
The place I live
is like
a grave,
piled up with beautiful clothes
and jewellery.
The only way to leave
is to marry
a rich and powerful man
I've never met before.
Then I would move to another grave.
Since I have no way
of living an ordinary life.
I can at least seek refuge
in monastic life
and the tranquillity
of the ancient lamps and Buddhas.
An ordinary life?
Do you know
what an ordinary life is?
One rises at sunrise
and retires at sunset.
Simple meals
and mutual support
between family members.
You're so sheltered.
Let me tell you
about an ordinary life.
Have you ever tried
losing everything overnight
and watching your family, young and old,
hanging themselves in front of you?
Have you tried
being well-educated,
but discarded like worn-out shoes
and trampled like weeds?
Have you tried
being on the verge
of marrying your beloved,
only to have her
snatched away
by another man?
When you've experienced all this,
come and talk to me
about an ordinary life.
Lianxin,
please come back early tonight.
I'm about to give birth.
Without your company,
I'm worried.
I won't be back early today.
Although we have enough
money for the flood relief,
I still need to escort
the official funds from the Treasury.
You're delicate.
Am I not accompanying you
for meals early in the morning?
Isn't that enough?
I can't stay away
from you for even a day.
Look,
I even peeled the egg for you.
Stop bothering me.
I'm just teasing you.
Young Master Xin!
Official Mu is here,
waiting outside.
Just right.
Let him in.
You two
can have a good chat.
Official Mu said that many commoners
were protesting in front
of Testaments and Treasures Bureau.
He asked you to go and take a look.
They don't owe the treasury money.
Why are they causing trouble?
Official Li...
He took his own life.
(Loan Reminder
from Testaments and Treasures Bureau)
Su Nanchun,
look for Official Mu immediately
and have him appease
the protesting commoners.
Tell him
I've already
cleared Official Li's debt.
There's no reason for him
to commit suicide.
Also, I will also investigate the truth
and provide an explanation to everyone.
Go.
Lianxin.
What about Mo?
Don't tell her.
Her pregnancy is unstable.
She can't handle this.
She will have to
endure even more soon.
Madam. Madam Ye has arrived.
Why is she here?
Greetings, Madam Yao.
Please have a seat.
What a rare guest.
Have you
not been to Madam Rui's place recently?
I do have a desire
to be of service to her,
but when I told her frankly,
she didn't even
open the curtain.
She is meticulous.
Someone ordinary like me
can't get close to her.
So, today,
I came to seek a different master.
What kind of place
do you think this is?
I appreciate
your kind intentions.
Although I'm insignificant,
I don't need your service.
Please go. I shall not see you off.
You don't need my service,
but what about the secret
in the Ice Chamber?
What?
If this mansion
truly has no place for me,
it might not be a bad idea for me
to lie in the Ice Chamber
like your child.
You're talking nonsense
early in the morning.
How come I don't understand
a word you're saying?
You don't understand?
I wonder if Lianxin does.
Are you trying to threaten me?
(Testaments and Treasures Bureau)
Official Li was a good official!
He died under such pressure!
Exactly. If it weren't for Official Li,
our entire family would
have starved to death!
- We want to see Young Master Xin!
We want to see Young Master Xin!
Sir, the commoners
are causing a serious disturbance.
It might not be good for you.
Should I send the troops?
It's a big deal to deliver the money.
Just let them be.
Use the back door.
Yes.
Yuanxue?
Lianchu.
Stop, have a rest.
Madam, if you can't take it,
let's go back today
and walk tomorrow.
I'm enduring it
for a better future.
I hope I can
give birth to a son
without any complication.
It's almost time, Madam.
Just one more month.
Yes, only one more month.
Really?
Is there no doubt?
I heard it directly from Young Master Xin.
He also said
that Madam Mo must not know this.
So, what's the reason?
Isn't it clear?
Madam Mo's pregnancy
is already unstable.
If she finds out
that her father committed suicide...
What did you say?
I deserve to die.
Sorry, Madam.
What did you say?
Say it again.
I said...
I told you to say it again!
I said
Official Li committed suicide
because he couldn't repay his debt.
Madam.
Madam, please stay strong.
Madam!
Madam is bleeding!
Get a physician!
A flower parasol.
Take a look at this! A flower parasol.
Flower parasol.
(I laughed at your self-importance.)
You are the most cowardly of all.
Your suffering today
is not due to your circumstances,
but because you've lost your dignity.
(However, your chosen way of life)
(is to willingly discard)
(the last shred of your dignity.)
(Tinglan Pavilion)
Madam.
Please breathe.
Hold on, Madam.
Madam, Madam Ye is here.
She seems...
Madam.
Madam Ye, you...
I was ordered
to help Madam Mo with the childbirth,
as the situation is dire
and can't be delayed.
It won't take much of your time.
I have something to show you.
Mu Haiyao lost her child.
What?
Madam Yao.
Tell me.
What should we do next?
Can you spare my life?
I will do
whatever you ask me to do.
She...
She wants Li Qianmo's child.
Madam Ye.
Madam.
Madam. Madam Yao is in premature labour.
(Langyue Hall)
Madam.
Almost.
Push!
Madam.
Hold on.
Madam is too weak
from her premature birth.
She can't be exposed to the wind.
Close the door.
Yes.
Madam, please hold on.
Madam Rui.
Step aside.
I'm afraid it's not appropriate.
Madam Yao has given an order.
No one is allowed to enter.
Xu Liangchuan.
She is just a side consort.
Have you lost your senses?
You won't even make way for Madam Rui.
Get out!
Madam Rui.
All right,
I want to see Yao. Let me through.
Madam Rui.
Madam Yao is in labour.
Even you can't force your way in.
It is improper.
Since when is it your turn
to determine whether it's proper or not?
Jingshan!
Yes.
Madam Rui!
Madam, hold on.
Forgive me for offending me!
Xu Liangchuan!
What are you waiting for?
How dare you!
You're just servants.
How dare you disobey my orders.
Aren't you afraid of being fired?
Madam Rui, don't forget that.
Madam Yao
manages all the affairs
of the house now.
Do you still think you can boss us around?
Just do as you're told.
No matter what happens,
Young Master Xin will defend us.
Yes.
Madam, hold on.
We want to see Young Master Xin!
My dear villagers!
I know where Young Master Xin is!
Follow me!
All right!
Let's go!
♪From the chaotic dust♪
♪Gracefully stepping out♪
♪Only then did I understand
the beauty of the world♪
♪Why, and for what♪
♪Holding pure intentions
in my heart♪
♪Clinging to black and white♪
♪Only then did I realize
that the path is simple♪
♪It is love♪
♪When fate♪
♪Surges like deep clouds♪
♪Regardless of♪
♪What experiences may come♪
♪Unable to linger♪
♪Mountains and waves
are insignificant♪
♪My promises to you remain♪
♪Unafraid of obstacles
along this worldly path♪
♪Worries are few♪
♪The moon sets, stars scatter,
and mournful sounds ring♪
♪My promises to you remain♪
♪Life after life♪
♪Will follow my heart's desires♪
♪Forever unchanged♪