♪Wander through the bustling world♪
♪How could we forget each other?♪
♪Indescribable contemplation♪
♪Under the bright moon,
I enter the realm of dreams♪
♪Could you be the one in my dreams?♪
♪Only then will I look back with joy♪
♪Do you understand? Are you flustered?♪
♪Are you weary? Just let it be a memory♪
♪Shall we forget or shall we anticipate?♪
♪Either way♪
♪My feelings are as tender as summer♪
♪Holding hands, I want to see
the four seasons flourish with you♪
♪Warming the ends of the earth♪
♪Finally, in this boundless world,
everything is under the embrace of longing♪
=Blooming Days=
=Episode 33=
What do you want to say?
I want to say that
even if Madam Rong
blames you wrongfully,
it's just temporary.
Everything will be fine when it's over.
How will it be fine?
Lingwei may not be able
to meet Madam Rong
after she leaves this time.
Mother, what if...
What if my sister runs away?
If she does,
not only Madam Rong
will be executed,
the war will be rekindled
and there will never be peace.
However, Madam Rong said...
What did she say?
It's my fault.
Your Highness, Madam Lian is here.
- Greetings, Your Highness.
Where is she?
Your Highness.
The princess was ready,
but she suddenly
fell sick.
She fell sick? What kind of sickness?
Chest pain.
She's shivering all over
and unable to walk.
Do you remember what I've said?
Yes.
We mustn't let the princess
be found by the people of His Highness.
Kill her
if there is no choice.
Go.
- Noted.
To incite a war,
we won't even spare
our own niece.
Lianzuo.
She's our niece,
but she can't compare
to our future.
Future?
Future.
Madam Rong.
His Highness asked you...
Got it.
Let's go.
Xiangning!
Save Lingwei!
Zhao'er, travel out of the city.
You must find Lingwei.
Mother, I...
I know
you're close to Lingwei,
but we can't hesitate on this.
Lingwei's life is at stake
if she doesn't come back.
Lingwei, are you okay?
Zhao'er.
Go. Get inside.
Lingwei, why are you crying?
I'm crying in front of my brother.
I'm seriously a bad sister.
I'm a bad brother instead.
You do nothing wrong.
It's me.
It's my life.
I only hope
I wasn't born in a prince's family.
my father didn't inherit the title.
Zhao'er, what are you doing?
Leave. I won't stop you anymore.
I'll set you free.
- Come on.
- Silly Zhao'er.
What if I run away?
Will I be happy after that?
I'll part with my mother.
I'll get the family involved.
Leave.
Lingwei.
When I was little,
grandfather said this to me.
Quliang has many children.
He worked hard on political affairs
so that the children
could have enough food and clothing
and play happily.
He said
one who looked out for others
was great.
I get it now.
All right.
I promise.
If Celun bullies you,
I'll lead a troop to exterminate Cige'er
before bringing you back.
Leave now.
Lingwei, don't come out!
Go!
(Lianxin.)
(There is no way)
(to undo the mistakes of the past now.)
(This is)
(all I can do for you now.)
(I don't ask for your forgiveness.)
(I only ask you to stop the war)
(and restore peace in Quliang.)
Father!
Wait, father!
Please meet someone.
Greetings, Father.
Cease the war.
Benefit the people.
May you
bear the words in mind
and never fight against each other.
Respect and love each other.
Never abandon each other.
Stop!
(Three months later)
(Prince An's Mansion)
Your Highness!
Madam De...
What happened?
She may not live long.
Physician, Rong...
Madam Rong is weak
and she caught a cold.
I'm afraid...
What is it?
She may not hold it any longer.
Mother.
Madam, you haven't slept all night.
Why don't you go back
to get some rest?
Lian'er.
Rou.
You're here.
Rong.
Don't cry.
Everyone dies.
I've lived my life without
any injury or pain.
I'm content with having
you all by my side
in the end.
After all,
I failed to persuade His Highness.
I don't get to set Lingwei
free.
Rong.
I'm sorry to you.
Don't talk about this.
Come on.
Play chess with me.
No. You're tired.
I won't play.
I always listen to you.
Listen to me
for once,
okay?
Okay.
I'll play.
Let's play.
Do you remember us
playing together for the first time
during the first Chinese New Year's Eve
after you entered the mansion?
Of course.
We even made dumplings together
at Lianwei House.
Do you remember who won?
You, for sure.
You always
beat me over the years.
On that day,
we bet on the loser
making dumplings
and spent two hours in a game.
In the end,
I narrowly won by an exchange.
I was so thrilled.
I got a big smile.
Stop talking.
Well,
I appeared
to be a steady person.
Why was I so thrilled
over a petty thing?
You have no idea.
I was thrilled
not because I beat you.
It's because you're by my side.
That's great.
You thought I didn't know.
I was well aware.
I didn't play better than you.
You lost to me every time
to please me.
The exchange.
It's always that.
As long as you...
As long as you're happy,
winning or losing doesn't matter.
You've lost again.
Yes, I've lost again.
What do we bet on this time?
Whatever
you say.
I want you to promise me
that you'll assist His Highness
in securing the title
and making Quliang stronger and better.
A stronger and better Mu.
Only then,
My Lingweil
wouldn't be bullied by Cige'er.
I'm begging you.
I promise.
I promise you everything.
Rong.
Lian'er.
Remember what you've said.
Remember.
Rong.
Lian'er.
Remember what you've said.
Remember.
Why do you leave me behind?
Why?
Madam!
-  Madam.
- Rong.
Madam.
Don't you want me anymore?
You don't want me anymore.
Your Highness.
You think she died
because you didn't help her.
She hated you. She resented you.
She'll never forgive you.
My mother
said nothing to me.
She was already unconscious
when I arrived at Zhaohui Courtyard.
She actually fell sick
as soon as she knew
Lingwei was getting married.
I got angry.
Why wasn't I informed?
Qiushi said
mother allowed no one
to say a word.
Before she lost consciousness,
she allowed no one
to step out of the courtyard.
That's my mother.
She's ruthless.
She was dying.
She could either blame
or reprimand me.
She kept
her son from seeing her.
Your Highness.
Had I known
she was critically ill,
I would've served tea
and medicine to her
and cleaned her up in person
whether she accepted it or not.
Even if she chased me out
for a thousand times,
I would've held on until the end.
It's not
about forgiveness.
It's
about having no regrets in my life,
unlike now.
Qinglian.
There're always flaws in life.
If none of us can stop it,
let's fill it inch by inch
by doing our best
in our remaining lives.
Don't worry, Rong.
I'll make Quliang stronger
with His Highness.
I'll protect Lingwei.
(Wild pansy and stone)
Your Highness. Lv Beiyi is here.
Leave us.
Yes, Your Highness.
This
was written by my father in person.
Do you know
what it implies?
Wild pansy is a plant.
A stone that looks like jade is a stone.
- It implies that...
My father kept every plant and stone
of Quliang in his mind.
I thought so at first.
Only today
I truly understand
my father's intention.
You've worked hard this time.
I'll reward you handsomely.
I don't dare to take credit
after being defeated by Cige'er.
Defeated?
I'm not stupid.
Cige'er wouldn't have sought truce
if you didn't win
all three previous battles.
I've sent someone
to investigate the case of the bran.
I'll give you and Mu Tianshu
an explanation.
It seems
you have guessed
who the mastermind is.
I don't want guessing,
but evidence.
I won't be a worthy opponent
if I can't get the evidence!
Your Highness, you don't have to take
senior princess consort's words
of disappointment to heart.
She
was right.
I thought
Quliang had prosperous people
and strong soldiers.
The war against Cige'er
is a wake-up call.
From now on,
I'll take it as a warning.
A few years
to a decade.
I'll do my utmost.
I'll be a great master of Quliang.
Your Highness, you have to.
In addition to the aforementioned,
I'm afraid there is another reason.
Your Highness,
you're entrusted with a secret mission.
You said
(Wild pansy and stone)
wild pansy and the stone
aren't just plants and stone in Quliang.
I've finally
figured it out.
(Diligent)
The late prince spent 40 years
to establish Quliang
so that he could send troops to
rescue the Emperor one day.
Zhimei.
Why are you still up?
It's late.
You haven't gone to bed too.
I was waiting for you.
Why are you holding the poison?
Tomorrow is the coronation ceremony.
I would rather kill myself
than being killed by Lianxin.
It's you.
You tampered with the provision.
You hadn't stopped at all.
Why did you do that?
I told you
everything was well arranged.
Why did you act willfully
without my knowledge?
Surprisingly,
I've become an outsider
despite being your wife for years.
My wife?
Yes.
My father left me in the cold
11 years ago
due to the incident at the armoury.
When you abandoned me
as if I was a rag
and turned to support my eighth brother,
did you think of yourself as your wife?
For the past 20 years,
I love you
genuinely.
All you want is to become
the princess consort!
When you ignored
and trampled on me mercilessly,
did you think of me as your wife?
Young Master.
Are you talking to me?
Yes!
This is how I want to talk to you!
Don't forget
I'm the head
of this household!
You're
just a woman of mine!
Wife?
How are we husband and wife?
Husband and wife who soar together?
Husband and wife who exchange hearts?
Deeply connected husband and wife?
No.
We're husband and wife who fly away
separately when a disaster strikes.
(Quiet Thinking)
Madam.
Tomorrow is the coronation ceremony.
Rest early.
Yes.
I'll be the princess consort tomorrow.
I wonder if anyone will still come
to greet me after that.
You're confused.
The incident of the attire with
Luo Qinglian's has been settled.
No one is in a position to compete
with you anymore after
the bran incident.
You'll be the princess consort
tomorrow onwards.
Princess consort?
A pathetic princess consort.
What is the point?
An empty title.
I cannot compare to the one who lives in
His Highness' heart.
Even when
she was sent to Correctional Institution
and she disobeyed His Highness,
His Highness pampered her
and missed her
as usual.
Madam.
You have a guest.
Who would come so late?
(Qihe's 49th year
Coronation ceremony of Prince An of Quliang)
An edict to Prince An.
The Emperor decrees.
(Lord Rui's Mansion)
The late Prince An, He Yunshuo,
put in painstaking efforts
to have created
the prosperous Quliang.
Now that He Lianxin inherits
the title,
all officers in Quliang
should serve him faithfully
and play their parts
to be worthy of the Emperor's trust.
(Memorial tablets of He's ancestor)
The decree is announced to all.
The end.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
His Highness' order!
External management must
depend on internal function.
Both should be compatible.
It's better to be in the right position.
Greetings, Prince An.
- Congratulations, Your Highness.
- We'll play our parts
- and serve you fully.
Rise.
I'm conferred by the Emperor
and on my father's bequest
to take over Quliang.
I'll depend
on you all from now on.
He Lianxiu. He Lianyi.
- Yes.
(Royal edict)
I've asked for a royal edict
to appoint He Lianxiu
as Lord Li
to supervise administrative affairs.
He Lianyi will be appointed
as Lord Yi
to supervise military affairs.
- Thank you, His Majesty.
- Thank you, Your Highness.
- Your Highness, you're brilliant.
I'm brilliant?
I'm not even close!
Someone actually mixed bran
in the army provisions
during the war against Cige'er
under my nose
and nearly killed my army
and ruined Quliang.
There was an unfaithful
and unrighteous
officer under my rule.
How dare you say I'm brilliant!
I sent someone to investigate it
day and night.
The outcome
is in this letter.
I haven't opened the letter
so that I can find out
who the officer is
with all of you
today at the coronation ceremony.
Who is the sinner?
Primary Consort Fang has been
named the princess consort.
Side Consort Mu as
side princess consort.
(Side Consort Luo as
side princess consort.)
Side Consort Luo...
Hold on, Ms. Ma.
Ms. Ma.
What is going on?
The bran incident has been investigated.
The one who mixed bran
in the army provisions
was Madam Lian's father,
(The head is Luo Rongyu.)
Luo Rongyu.
It's simple if you don't want to be
a pathetic princess consort.
Just get rid
of the person loved, protected
and kept in His Highness' mind.
I heard that your younger brother,
Fang Erge,
investigated
the bran incident.
This can't be.
This can't be!
♪From the chaotic dust♪
♪Gracefully stepping out♪
♪Only then did I understand
the beauty of the world♪
♪Why, and for what♪
♪Holding pure intentions
in my heart♪
♪Clinging to black and white♪
♪Only then did I realize
that the path is simple♪
♪It is love♪
♪When fate♪
♪Surges like deep clouds♪
♪Regardless of♪
♪What experiences may come♪
♪Unable to linger♪
♪Mountains and waves
are insignificant♪
♪My promises to you remain♪
♪Unafraid of obstacles
along this worldly path♪
♪Worries are few♪
♪The moon sets, stars scatter,
and mournful sounds ring♪
♪My promises to you remain♪
♪Life after life♪
♪Will follow my heart's desires♪
♪Forever unchanged♪