♪Wander through the bustling world♪
♪How could we forget each other?♪
♪Indescribable contemplation♪
♪Under the bright moon,
I enter the realm of dreams♪
♪Could you be the one in my dreams?♪
♪Only then will I look back with joy♪
♪Do you understand? Are you flustered?♪
♪Are you weary? Just let it be a memory♪
♪Shall we forget or shall we anticipate?♪
♪Either way♪
♪My feelings are as tender as summer♪
♪Holding hands, I want to see
the four seasons flourish with you♪
♪Warming the ends of the earth♪
♪Finally, in this boundless world,
everything is under the embrace of longing♪
=Blooming Days=
=Episode 13=
Do you want to find out with me?
You're also aware
I'm known as the Idle Young Master
where all I think of
are the matters
of Baizhen Lane.
Lianxiu, my brother.
Do you enjoy chatting with me?
Look at you,
happy to the point of tears.
Oh, Lianxin.
Have some tea.
That was a clever way
to achieve one's goal.
The heir's problem is solved.
The silver owed
can finally be paid off.
These things aren't the most important.
From now on,
Young Master Xiu
no longer
has the means to go against you.
If I may be bold to ask,
have I passed the test?
You're knowledgeable,
excel in military strategies,
and exceptional in medical skills.
If I refused you,
wouldn't that make me
the biggest fool in the world?
Please take a seat.
But
I want to be that fool.
Because of her?
How unexpected of you.
Between a woman and ambition,
you actually chose a woman.
How would you choose?
I would choose
to have control over my life.
Only when I live without being controlled
can I have both women and ambitions.
That
was the last chance I gave you.
The first time
was when you stood her up in the forest.
That's how she became my woman.
The second time was when you met again
under the moonlight.
You rejected her and pushed her away.
Lv Beiyi,
I gave you three chances
to get the woman you want.
But you chose to give up every time.
So, from now on,
you and Luo Qinglian
have no connection.
Is this the condition to become your aide?
No.
I don't need to choose
between ambitions and women
because I'll have both.
So, this isn't the condition for you
to be my aide.
Remember this.
I'll win her
not because you gave up.
Don't you think you're too confident?
Lv Beiyi,
do you know
my favorite phrase
in this world?
"There's a whole lifetime ahead."
There are many things in this world
that are worth waiting for.
Be it women or Quliang.
And what I have is patience.
Let's go, Master Lv.
Young Master.
Young Master,
we have collected many antiques
at low prices today.
Do you want me to show them to you?
Sell them.
Sell them all!
Yes, Young Master.
Madam, aren't you going in?
I heard even Madam Yao
suffered a downfall too.
Yes.
Madam Yao sure was unlucky.
This is just when she thought
she was doing well.
Do you really think it was bad luck?
Luo Qinglian,
it seems my concern about you was right.
Have you found the one I asked for?
I've found that person.
She's just waiting for you
to personally instruct her.
Well done.
The day we'll need her
won't be too far away.
(Your Highness,)
(I have done as you have instructed)
(and returned the silver owed
by Young Master Xin)
(to the Testaments and Treasures Bureau.)
(Official Zheng from the bureau said)
(the treasury in Quliang is full.)
(We won't have to worry
about it for years.)
(The growth of Quliang)
(is Mu's hope.)
(General Xin's Mansion)
Back then,
I used to bask in glory.
Today, I've came down.
I never expected you
would be the only one to see me off.
People's hearts are fickle.
Why take all those pretense
during good times seriously?
I never expected
the only one who truly cared for me
would be you.
It's a pity that my plans
had led to this outcome.
How dare you.
How dense can you be?
Is this plain carriage suitable
for Madam Yao to ride in?
Don't you know the usual carriage
that Madam Yao rides in?
I ordered them to do so.
Things are different now.
We're just following the rules.
I hope you won't mind, Haiyao.
Cut the pretentious act here.
I'll make this clear to you.
As long as I'm alive,
you're my enemy.
Well, I never intend
to be your friend anyway.
Since I can be
the person you hate the most,
why not?
The person I hate the most?
You're still not worthy.
Mu Haiyao,
you're now a commoner.
Madam Rui speaking to you
is giving you face.
Watch your manners.
Have you all had enough
of this commotion?
If there's nothing else,
just get back to your place.
I want to wait for Young Master here.
Young Master is not here.
What?
He went out early in the morning.
Why?
You never expect
Young Master wouldn't even see you
one last time?
That's impossible.
Young Master will come back.
You're someone
whom His Highness can't tolerate.
Do you think Young Master
will treat you the same as before?
Haiyao.
Young Master.
Since you're leaving,
have you packed enough food
and everything you need?
Is there anything you still need?
Young Master,
I won't be able
to serve you by your side after this.
I hope
you'll take good care of yourself
and be safe.
Get up.
Haiyao.
Thank you for your concern.
Don't worry.
I'll take extra precautions.
Moreover,
Master Lv has excellent medical skills.
With him by my side,
I don't have to worry anymore.
Lv Beiyi?
Listen up, everyone.
From today on,
Master Lv will be my aide.
I don't want to hear anything
about what happened in the past.
- Yes.
Haiyao,
it's getting late.
Do you have any requests?
Young Master,
can I really speak of it?
Of course.
Apart from you,
I'm most concerned
about my newborn child.
It's a pity that he'll be separated
from his birth mother
at such a young age.
So, I earnestly request,
if there's a chance,
I hope I can come back
to visit my child more.
You can rest assured.
This child
will have a new mother to care for him.
He won't suffer.
What?
Haiyao, you said
the child can't be without a mother.
I've decided
to let
Qianmo raise and care for the child.
Young Master.
Young Master, no.
You must let me raise this child.
He can't live without me, Young Master.
Haiyao.
Young Master.
Don't worry.
We will take good care of him.
Raise him well.
I hope he'll be as outstanding
as your father in the future.
Thank you very much, Young Master.
Young Master.
Young Master,
I have a request.
Speak.
The journey to the southern outskirts
is lonely.
I hope
someone can accompany me.
What is she up to?
Mu Haiyao doesn't make decisions
without a purpose.
Luo Qinglian,
congratulations.
Lv Beiyi
is his aide now.
As long as he serves diligently,
Young Master will put his trust in him.
But do you think
Young Master
will elevate Lv Beiyi's status?
Your past with Lv Beiyi
is his lifelong shame.
Lv Beiyi is useful to him for now.
So he'll naturally treat him well.
But if he ever inherits
the title and becomes a prince,
the first person he'll kill
is Lv Beiyi.
Impossible.
Do you think Young Master
is a kind and honorable person?
Look at everyone
at the Young Master's Mansion.
They're all his pawns.
Once they're no longer useful,
they're cast aside like old shoes.
I'm the best living proof.
He has no genuine feelings for me.
Let alone for you.
Madam Yao, stop wasting your effort.
I won't fall for your instigation.
Luo Qinglian,
you set up such a plot
just to put me in a dire situation.
But you had unwittingly
accomplished one thing.
As long my brother is alive,
Young Master won't take my life
no matter what I do wrong.
What are you trying to do?
Girl.
Bring the physician.
Let me examine her.
Young Master,
should I fetch the physician?
No need.
Take some hot water.
Young Master,
should I get some hot water?
Young Master.
Young Master, your arm is injured too.
Why don't we tend to your wound first?
No matter.
Ms. Lian is not seriously injured.
She passed out from shock, that's all.
Yi...
I knew...
I knew
you would come and save me.
Yi...
Did you think I wanted to kill her?
Weren't you?
Of course not.
The greatest pain
is not death.
But heartbreak.
Yi...
Girl, take your medicine.
Open up.
Here.
Young Master?
Why are you here?
I...
You're seriously injured.
But why do you keep fidgeting?
Yi...
Where's Master Lv?
All you need is me.
I could take this chance
to return your favor from last time.
Then is he hurt?
He's perfectly fine.
I'm glad he's not hurt.
Why aren't you concerned about me?
I can't continue to be indebted to him.
I owe him too much.
I can't be indebted to him again.
Why?
Must it be him who saved you?
If it wasn't him,
don't tell me it was you.
Why can't it be me?
You only care about important matters.
Why would you risk your life
for a servant-concubine?
I'm ruthless and only care about profit.
Fine.
Then
what's on Lv Beiyi's mind?
Is it you?
Young Master, I'm tired.
Girl.
Girl,
how well do you know me?
And how well do you know him?
I only need
to know His Highness.
Girl,
is it all just business between us to you?
Does everything that I do
can't even be compared
to one strand of hair
on Lv Beiyi's head?
(Your past with Lv Beiyi)
(is his lifelong shame.)
(But if he ever inherits
the title and becomes a prince,)
(the first person he'll kill)
(is Lv Beiyi.)
What about you?
You saw Mu Haiyao
push me off the carriage.
Will you punish her
to seek justice for me?
You knew I had
to endure for now.
Mu Haiyao truly knows you well.
Didn't you promise to protect me?
Is this the promise you made to me?
Girl,
there are many solutions
to solve one problem in this world.
The promise I made
may be fulfilled a little later.
But it will not be broken.
About low status,
have you truly considered
elevating Lv Beiyi's status?
(Young Master,)
(I thought)
(no woman)
(in this world)
(could win even a trace
of your affection.)
(I never expected)
(you would even risk your life for her.)
Girl!
(But so what?)
(No matter who saved her,)
(only one person will get hurt
in the end.)
So you think I'm deceiving you?
I only want
to hear the answer from you.
Since you think
I'm such a scoundrel,
why did you make a deal with me?
Why did you ask me to let Lv Beiyi stay?
I only want to hear the answer
from you.
(I want you)
(to remember this moment forever.)
(Let this pain create)
(a constant thorn in your heart)
(that won't go away,)
(even after ten, twenty years,
or a lifetime!)
Never.
Where are you going?
Leave a despicable scoundrel like you.
I admit I'm despicable.
I was never a person of good character.
You were the one who misjudged,
misguided and led astray.
Now, you are my servant-concubine.
You belong to me.
This is a fact
that you can never change.
Su Nanchun!
Yes, Young Master.
Tonight, the servant-concubine
of the Luo clan
shall share my bed!
Madam,
there you are.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Zuiliu,
have you noticed any changes here?
Of course.
Mu Haiyao has been sent away
to the secondary courtyard.
With so many people changing sides,
I'm afraid the number of positions
would be limited.
I don't mean them.
Luo Qinglian is sharing
Young Master's bed.
Starting today,
she truly becomes a part
of the Young Master's Mansion.
In the future,
which position she'll occupy
is something we can't predict.
(General Xin's Mansion)
(Qiege Hall)
Miss!
Ms. Lian!
Ms. Lian,
this cloak is a gift bestowed
by Young Master.
He specifically said
that this cloak isn't ordinary.
So please cherish it.
What are you doing?
Move aside.
But Young Master.
Move aside!
Young Master...
Lv Beiyi.
If you pierce me with this sword,
I will let you go far away.
If you can't do it,
you have no right to criticize anything
about me and Luo Qinglian from now on.
Princess?
(Qiege Hall)
Young Master, you scared me to death.
But you are very bold.
You were sure enough
that he wouldn't dare thrust you.
But
I was hoping that he would.
Huairui.
May I be bold to say this?
Please do not take
such a risk in the future.
Get up.
Thank you, Young Master.
Why are your hands so cold?
I'm fine.
Is she not feeling well?
Young Master,
Madam Rui didn't sleep at all night.
She was sitting in Little Master's room
until morning.
No matter how I persuade her,
she wouldn't listen.
Zuiliu.
Huairui,
I've never been able to give you
a proper closure about Hui'er.
Whatever Young Master wishes to do,
I will stand on your side.
Huairui, you didn't sleep well, right?
Why did you come here so early?
I came for two reasons.
First,
I want to congratulate you
for favoring Ms. Lian.
And the second one?
The second reason is,
that I humbly request
that Madam Yao's expenses
in the secondary courtyard
be the same as those
in the our mansion.
What did you say?
You want to reward her?
Yes.
Huairui,
she pushed Qinglian off the carriage
just yesterday.
And about Hui'er...
Hui'er...
Hui'er was my flesh and blood.
After he died,
I wept every day,
wishing to make the person who killed him
pay a thousandfold.
But...
But now,
you still need her.
You must avoid having
Mu Haiyao
and the Mu family
hold any grudges against you.
Avenging Hui'er
is important.
But what matters most now
is the one alive,
and that's you, Young Master.
Mu Haiyao killed Little Master.
I wish
I could tear her to pieces.
Or at least make her suffer
in the secondary courtyard.
I can't believe
you actually asked for a reward
on her behalf.
Can her suffering
in the secondary courtyard take her life?
Of course not.
But my life
is far from safe here.
How come?
You're the primary consort here.
Primary consort?
A primary consort without a son
doesn't seem to be justified.
When one Mu Haiyao leaves,
another will take her place.
The only thing
that can secure my position
as primary consort
is Young Master's guilt.
You mean...
The more I compromise,
the deeper Young Master's guilt
is to me,
and the more secure my position becomes.
I suppose
Hui'er in the afterlife
will forgive me, right?
Madam, please don't be sad.
Little Master was a sensible boy.
He'll surely forgive you
and watch over you to discipline those
who misbehave.
I just hope
the next one
won't be Luo Qinglian.
Miss, you've been sharpening it
for almost an hour.
This hairpin is sharp enough
to pierce through stones.
- Miss!
Miss, are you planning to...
Stay out of this.
Miss, don't do anything foolish.
- Miss.
- Miss, are you...
Stop following me!
Just stay out of this!
Young Master Yi,
you may have stopped me once.
But not the next one.
You're indeed different
from other women.
No wonder Lianxin favors you.
Young Master Yi, don't flatter me.
I can't afford
to enjoy his affection.
Of course, you can.
Just look at this cloak you're wearing.
You probably don't even know
the story behind this cloak, do you?
Does this belong to Madam De?
You only know
that Madam De is Lianxin's birth mother.
Yet you don't know
it was also Madam De
who made him suffer.
Since Lianxin was born,
he was raised by Madam Yi.
(It was only when he turned nine)
(that he returned to Madam De's side.)
Mother, I want that cloak.
I want that cloak, Mother.
(At that time,)
My dear son.
(Madam De just given birth)
(He Yunshuo's Eighth Son)
(to Eighth Brother, He Lianhua.)
(He Yunshuo's Eighth Son, He Lianhua, childhood)
(He Yunshuo's Eighth Son)
(She wasn't concerned about Lianxin,)
(He Lianhua, childhood)
(who was away from her for many years.)
(She only gave her attention
to Lianhua.)
(Once,)
(Father rewarded Lianxin with a cloak)
(because he excelled in his studies.)
Show it to me.
(Lianxin likes it very much.)
Hua, do you like it?
- Do it again.
- Turn around.
Watch this.
Hua.
How nice.
(This is the cloak
that Madam Yi personally sewn.)
(Lianxin has been keeping
and cherishing it all this while.)
(He would get angry
if anyone else touched it.)
(But now,)
(it's on you.)
People always say
Lianxin may appear suave.
But he's actually unemotional.
Do you know why?
It's nothing but a facade
for his scheming.
It's because he's afraid.
I was sent to Madam De
when I was young.
It was the nine-year-old Lianxin
who raised me.
Nobody understands his fears
better than I do.
He never received love from his parents.
To him,
doing well would earn him rewards.
And doing poorly would result
in abandonment.
He may say he doesn't care
about anything.
But deep down,
he's terrified of losing
more than anyone.
It has been over twenty years.
There isn't a single moment
he doesn't wear a mask.
He's never had a moment of relaxation.
Why are you telling me this?
Because you can save him.
Don't forget
you were the one
who stopped me from killing him
fifteen minutes ago.
If I hadn't stopped you,
would you have killed him?
Ms. Lian,
I, He Lianyi,
swear on my life.
(Lianxin can lie to the world.)
(But he won't lie to you.)
(He never received love
from his parents.)
(To him,)
(doing well would earn him rewards.)
(And doing poorly would result
in abandonment.)
Mother, I miss you very much.
I miss you very much.
(In this world,)
(there's no genuine affection
without reason.)
Does that include Madam De?
What?
You were calling out to your mother
in your dream.
That wasn't Madam De.
No matter what you heard just now,
(it's best for you to forget it.)
(You were obviously carrying
so much pain.)
(Why can't you be honest with me)
(and clear up my misunderstanding
of you?)
(He Lianxin,)
(if you treat me sincerely,)
(how can I be indifferent to it?)
(But do you think Young Master)
(will elevate Lv Beiyi's status?)
As long my brother is alive,
Young Master won't take my life
no matter what I do wrong.
What are you trying to do?
Mu Haiyao,
I calculated every possibility
but couldn't prevent your final move.
Ms. Lian, Su Nanchun is here.
Young Master.
Please sit down.
Join me for a drink.
I can't afford
to enjoy the drink you offer.
Aren't you here to kill me?
Getting me drunk
will make it easier for you.
Do you know
what is the easiest thing
to do in this world?
Tricking women to drink.
But do you know
what's the hardest?
I'm not interested in knowing.
It's deceiving you.
The environment here
forced me to learn how to lie
from a young age.
Be it to women, my brothers,
and even my father.
Out of every ten words I say,
nine are lies.
I never worry about remembering them
or my conscience bothering me.
But why is it
so hard to deceive you?
Is it difficult?
You deceived me for six whole months.
Would you believe me
if I said I didn't?
All right.
I'm afraid it's too late for everything
after last night.
Girl,
do you hate me?
I hate you to the core.
It's very late.
Princess,
you should leave.
When I refuse to leave,
not even you
can drive me away.
Princess,
with your status and riches,
why waste your time
on a weak person
like me?
It must be very tough
to carry so much pain alone,
isn't it?
♪From the chaotic dust♪
♪Gracefully stepping out♪
♪Only then did I understand
the beauty of the world♪
♪Why, and for what♪
♪Holding pure intentions
in my heart♪
♪Clinging to black and white♪
♪Only then did I realize
that the path is simple♪
♪It is love♪
♪When fate♪
♪Surges like deep clouds♪
♪Regardless of♪
♪What experiences may come♪
♪Unable to linger♪
♪Mountains and waves
are insignificant♪
♪My promises to you remain♪
♪Unafraid of obstacles
along this worldly path♪
♪Worries are few♪
♪The moon sets, stars scatter,
and mournful sounds ring♪
♪My promises to you remain♪
♪Life after life♪
♪Will follow my heart's desires♪
♪Forever unchanged♪