[My Summer Sweetheart]
[EP12]
Ma'am, it's about the Aman Island.
That's
what Zhu Jinhao's been delaying for?
Find some competent people
to stir things up.
You mean...
What's the worst thing
that can happen in the service industry?
Safety hazards.
I'll send someone to handle it now.
And contact the media partners,
invite them for a vacation.
Alright, I'll arrange it now.
Zhu Jinhao,
I can make things happen
with your soft approach.
[Look!]
Isn't this the little coffee shop girl?
Running into me today, bad luck for you.
My boyfriend is waiting for me.
Your boyfriend?
That little coffee shop boss, right?
I was about to settle things with him.
Come on, you're coming with me today.
[Stop!]
That's my boyfriend!
I'm leaving!
Help me,
those two guys are thugs!
Your boyfriend?
Girl,
you sure change boyfriends fast.
Dude,
lend me your girlfriend.
How about it?
Sure.
Come on,
get up and continue!
No... no, we wouldn't dare.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
If they had dared to really touch me,
I'd have taken them down with me.
Impressive.
You too,
I didn't know you could fight.
Well, now you can know more about me.
Hi, I'm Shen Jinchuan.
Hi, I'm Summer.
Let's go.
Lately, there's been a lot of incidents,
happening all of a sudden.
Why do you say that?
I haven't been here long,
but everyone here is warm and friendly.
Those two seemed like
they came just to cause trouble.
You like it here?
Yes.
Summer,
when I said I wanted to pursue you,
it wasn't just on a whim.
Remember the birthday party?
I said you reminded me of someone.
The first time I met her
was also at a party,
in a similar situation.
Was it just as embarrassing?
She was the one
who stood up for justice.
You're not using me
as a stand-in because your confession
didn't work out, are you?
Anyway, to show my gratitude,
I'll treat you to coffee. Come.
If it's not made by you,
I won't drink it.
Don't worry, to show my sincerity,
I'll secretly make it for you.
Let's go.
Hey everyone,
I drank coffee from this shop
and look,
I'm showing signs of poisoning.
Let this video be proof
in case something happens to me.
Be my witness...
Jia?
Sir!
Boss!
Help me out!
Wake up!
What did you give me?
I'm telling you,
I'm going to post this online!
You'll pay for this!
We'll take responsibility,
but let's get you to the hospital first.
Jia, what's going on?
I don't know! What should we do, Summer?
Smell this.
Let's go check it out.
Let's go. Hurry.
Selling baskets,
picking up coal cinders,
carrying water, chopping wood.
You're here.
Mixing liquor and coffee is dangerous.
This is common knowledge.
[But since it happened in our shop,]
we'll cover your hospital fees.
How about that?
What do you mean?
I drank your coffee and ended up here.
What now,
trying to shirk responsibility?
You've made a fake food poisoning.
Do you wanna discuss about
responsibility at the police?
Oh,
trying to threaten me?
[I'm just a tourist]
and you did this to me!
None of you
[are getting away]
with this!
I'll report all of you!
You drank white liquor
and then had coffee at our shop.
- The liquor...
- Bad news!
We have bad news about the coffee shop!
How could?
Let's talk outside.
Serves them right!