THE LATE SEO JUN-SEOK
MARCH 2, 1992, TESTIMONY OF SEO JUN-SEOK
-I've brought the tape.
-Really?
We will record your testimony now.
March 2, 1992.
Name, Seo Jun-seok.
I listened to your dad's statement.
What did he say?
Your father, Jun-seok,
wasn't a murder suspect to begin with.
Your dad went to the police
to report a murder.
He said those guys
killed his friend, Oh Gil-han.
He went to the police
and even brought pictures as proof.
His testimony was of a witness
and not a suspect.
He talked about
how those goons killed Gil-han,
and what they were doing at the scene.
Jeong-hu, this is plenty.
Come back, okay?
This is enough for the broadcast.
What do you think?
What do I think about the bastards
who killed my dad,
framed yours for murder,
and screwed up our lives?
Let's proceed as planned.
Let's see this through.
There was another lonely death.
Park Dong-cheol was kicked out
for blowing the whistle on the matter.
But he kept an audio tape
for the past 22 years.
It was of Seo Jun-seok's statement.
Yeong-sin, throw it!
I suspect Park Dong-cheol
was killed by the people
trying to destroy that tape.
Because the 22-year-old tape
that he gave us just before he died
had some incredible stories about them.
Wait, wait!
Let me meet Boss.
What a nice house.
Who are these people he referred to?
A reporter at Someday
went somewhere to ask just who they are.
This person is only referred to as Boss.
Hello.
The man you're hiding
is Boss, isn't it?
Hello, I'm with Someday News.
May I ask you a question?
Is that a no?
These people must be working for Boss!
I will ask these men instead.
Would Boss let you hurt a reporter
on a live feed
or let him get beaten up?
Careful.
I'll get in trouble if that breaks.
His name is Park Bong-su.
He has a business card from Someday News.
Didn't you say you were Healer?
I heard you'd meet me if I said that.
If you are Healer,
I will make time to talk to you.
If not--
Will you kill me?
I really don't want to die.
So, tell me.
Are you really Boss?
Do you control men like Oh Tae-won
who goes around killing people?
If you were curious,
all you needed to do was ask.
You didn't have to take my picture.
Well, you see...
I had no choice.
If someone bothers you
or if you don't like them,
you kill them.
Meanwhile, we can't.
It's so unfair.
That's why I need
to get your face out there
and put a warning under it.
"Beware of the beast."
Do people thank you for that?
I don't know
because I haven't done this before.
Kid.
Who are you really?
Among the people
that someone like you killed
was a man named Seo Jun-seok.
I'm his son,
Seo Jeong-hu.
Mister.
When you kill people from now on,
think about their sons and daughters.
You never did until now, did you?
Look.
The video ended mid-interview here.
This is the house.
Please wait.
We need orders to take action.
By the time you do, it'll be--
We can't barge into any house
just because we're police officers.
Are you kidding me?
We can't reach our reporter
in Boss' house.
YEONG-SIN IS FILMING AT BOSS' HOUSE
We just received a new video.
A reporter at Someday news
is filming the front of the house.
The police seem to have arrived.
It's been a very long time since we had
such a young person in this house.
Come, have a seat.
Have a drink.
I don't drink with thugs
who killed my father.
You're mistaken.
We don't kill people.
You order others to do your dirty work.
We work to save everyone.
How do I explain this?
You keep saying "we"
which is pissing me off.
How many bastards like you are there?
There is us, who look after people,
and then those who have us
look after them.
Young man,
which do you want to be?
You talk too much.
I thought you were some formidable figure,
but you're just an old man
who just wants to talk.
I'm telling you that
I've grown fond of you.
Think about it, but I won't wait long.
We will record your testimony now.
March 2, 1992.
Name, Seo Jun-seok.
Those people
call themselves "farmers,"
which is insulting to real farmers.
Hi.
Oh Gil-han, Choi Myeong-hui, and I
had chased these farmers
for over a year now.
We got a tip that they were
secretly moving a truck.
We figured it was a slush fund.
That's what
these so-called farmers do.
They think our nation
is their vegetable garden.
They play with politics
by funding politicians
to fit their taste buds.
They make laws that they want
and profit from them.
Hey, miss.
You can't go in there!
Jeong-hu, what's wrong?
I keep wanting to sleep.
Why are you always sleeping
whenever I see you?
You're always waking me up.
Did they drug you?
Should we go to the hospital?
I'll sleep it off.
Is that him? Is he okay?
He's sleepy.
We found him.
-Yeong-sin.
-Yes? Do you need something?
Our dads were very close, right?
Yes.
Yes, they were thick as thieves.
I wish you could've seen the broadcast.
Tell me about it.
You know,
you're a reporter too.
Watch the news a little.
Please.
That day in 1992,
our dads went out to investigate a story.
-Take good pictures.
-Don't worry.
-Make sure they're in focus.
-When were they not?
I just never told you, but you...
-Wait, what's that?
-Isn't it awesome?
-It's a recent model.
-It's expensive.
-Let me try it on.
-Hey!
-Stay still.
-What?
-Hey.
-Have you lost your mind?
-Hey!
-You'll break it.
-I'm trying it on.
-No!
Just once.
At first, they thought they'd get
pictures of the money exchange.
In their minds,
it was a quick and easy job.
What's that?
As you can see...
It's 200 million won per box.
I saw at least ten boxes.
That's 2 billion won
per truckload of paint.
I want that paint container.
What are you thinking?
They wouldn't kill me.
I'm a reporter after all.
What if they kill you?
That'll never happen.
What was that?
I'll lure them.
You get the paint container.
Hey!
Who the fuck are you?
Get him!
Stop right there!
Wait. Hold on.
-Hello.
-Who are you?
-What are you doing?
-You can't take that!
Stop!
-What's wrong?
-Gil-han's in danger.
So...
Wait here. I'll get Gil-han.
Keep the car running.
Let go! Hey!
Gil-han...
-Gil-han is--
-Jun-seok!
-Hurry.
-But Gil-han...
Gil-han... Gil-han!
Write down the license plate number.
Yes, sir.
I ran and hid for days
and found out what that paint was.
COMPONENT ANALYSIS
This is fake minium.
When poured over steel frames,
it will speed up the corrosion.
It's usually applied to prevent rust,
but it does the exact opposite!
Hey!
That's where the recording ends.
Our old men
led such tiring lives.
I know.
It's over.
-What is?
-My homework.
My master, my dad,
and you.
Good job.
-Yeong-sin.
-What?
I thought about this while I was sleeping.
As if that's possible.
Is it hard to just live
like ordinary people?
Is that how you want to live?
Will it be hard for me?
Let's give that "ordinary life" a try.
Will you be by my side?
Of course.
Good.
I thought you were preparing
Ji-an's birthday dinner.
I did a simple one at lunch.
I thought you had an episode.
Yes, but it was brief.
Please don't be sick.
I'm going to try not to be.
I watched Mun-ho's broadcast.
I hoped you wouldn't have.
Were you okay
after seeing that?
How much did you know?
What haven't you told me?
There is nothing that I haven't told you.
I was waiting in the car that day.
Jun-seok ran in
and said we had to take off.
I did what I was asked.
I never told you,
but I always suspected Jun-seok.
I'm glad I was proven wrong.
This soup is good.
Is it a consommé?
I tried a new recipe. Do you like it?
Close your eyes just once.
Then open them again.
You'll see things you didn't see before.
That is called "maturing".
I...
saw everything.
Jun-seok...
killed Gil-han.
We were
following the truck
supposedly transporting a slush fund.
When we arrived at the scene,
the truck driver saw us and ran off.
Inside the truck
were boxes filled with cash.
They started fighting over the money.
Jun Seok wanted to keep it,
but Gil-han said he shouldn't.
That's when Jun-seok killed him,
his own friend.
I couldn't stop him.
That's how money is.
Or maybe that's how people are.
Sorry?
Oh, the money?
It was revealed to be
the Democratic Party's funds.
Isn't it scary?
That money made my friends
kill and be killed.
It broke. That's sad.
I tried to be careful
even though I was running around all day.
Well,
your mom must be a very good cook.
Dad, if you go to her house,
the kitchen counters and sink
are down here.
They must have built it
to accommodate her wheelchair.
If she cares for the kitchen that much,
there is no question
that she's a great cook.
-Dad, have some.
-No, have some first.
But I brought it for you to try. Here.
-It's good. It's not too sweet either.
-Right?
So when is that punk coming?
Which punk? You know I have so many.
Drag him here.
Will you beat him up?
Why must it be someone so frail?
You're vulnerable to violence
which is why I hoped you'd find a big guy
into whose arms you can hop in and hide.
Why does it have to be
a scaredy-cat and crybaby?
Why are you laughing?
Was that funny?
Hey.
-Why are you laughing?
-A scaredy-cat and a crybaby?
Is that funny?
-How did you get in?
-Through the window.
-Step back one meter.
-Why?
Back off a bit more.
You said you want to live
like ordinary people.
Let's talk on the bed.
Then first,
use the door when you come
to your girlfriend's house.
Fine.
Second,
if you want to date your girlfriend,
meet her father and ask for his approval.
That's a bit...
Third,
give your girlfriend a gift
on her birthday.
Today is my real birthday.
Right.
Ta-da.
Gifts should be new and wrapped.
The tracker on your phone was disabled.
This is can be a GPS tracker.
Unbelievable.
Are you saying that you'd stalk me?
No, you can turn it on when you want.
You can turn it off too.
When you feel like you're in danger,
turn it on.
Otherwise, keep it turned off.
Okay.
-Thanks.
-May I hug you now?
-Do I frustrate you?
-No.
Then why are you pushing me away?
You said you want to love
like ordinary people.
Love?
Yes, love.
Then what's this?
This is
something that's not quite ordinary.
Got it.
I'll take all the necessary steps,
so just wait.
Don't take too long.
Meet your dad and get a regular paycheck.
And use this thing called a door...
I can't do this.
I think
I should come back some other time.
Chi-su, I forgot the...
Hello, sir.
I came today to introduce myself properly.
I need to get your approval too.
Well, I'm sorry.
Why are you in there?
-Don't come in.
-Dad.
You come in, and he's dead.
Go easy on him, okay?
Look.
I will ask you a few questions.
Sure.
That day before, at the cafe...
You and my daughter...
Well...
I was standing right there!
Chi-su, please.
Let's find out more before we kill him.
Chi-su, no!
Calm down
and have a seat.
Please sit.
I'll ask him instead.
-So, first...
-Yes, sir.
How far did you two go...
What the hell?
How was the pollack soup?
I really enjoyed it.
See? It was him.
He's the one she nursed all night long!
Chi-su!
You! How dare you kiss her in front of me!
No, Chi-su! You can't kill him!
Stop.
Do you think a lawyer can't throw a punch?
-Get over here.
-I'm sorry, sir.
Sorry? You're not even married.
You should wait
until you're married.
I didn't do anything wrong.
-What?
-Chi-su, stop!
-Chi-su!
-Hey!
-You. Get over here!
-Chi-su!
I'm sorry!
-What are you sorry for?
I really didn't do anything to her.
We just got a tip
that I'm not quite sure of.
What was the tip?
Someone said he met Boss.
Did you get his information?
Well, not exactly.
Take a look at Someday's website.
Things keep popping up.
I THINK I'VE SEEN THE OLD MAN SOMEWHERE
IS HE A KILLER?
We'll create a program for gathering tips.
We'll collect anything about Boss
and the minium incident in 1992.
Find the useful ones
and double check them.
Interview tipsters in person if possible.
If we're going to do
Kim Mun-sik's counter-broadcast,
we'll need more manpower.
Here comes reinforcement.
Hello. It's me, Park Bong-su.
You idiot.
How dare a rookie go undercover?
You did great. Good job.
You did a great job!
We missed you!
He said he wants to live
like ordinary people.
Let's go out tonight.
It's not easy to live
like ordinary people.
I don't think he knows what that means.
What's so great about it anyway?
But I think that's what he truly wants
seeing how he came back as Park Bong-su.
Good job.
He quit being Healer too,
but I think he was laid off.
He got fired.
Myeong-hui talked about you a lot
on the phone.
Really? What did she say?
She wants to see you again
and asked me to set it up.
She wants a Choi Myeong-hui special.
She does?
-Excuse me.
-Sure.
Let's do that special!
I know someone who seems to live
in a different world.
It's true.
He did live in a different world.
I worked on Seodo Bridge in 1992.
You know what happened, right?
It collapsed before it opened.
We talked about it a lot back then.
They suddenly asked us
to switch the coating.
What happened to the company
that built the bridge?
Isn't it obvious?
It was acquired just before it went under.
-May I go now?
-Yes. Thank you for your help.
Are you sleepy?
But now, he wants to join our world
and live like ordinary people.
It's kind of funny and sad to see.
Okay.
-Let's go to Yeongdeungpo.
-Wait, Yeongdeungpo...
That's so far.
It will take us forever to get there.
I saw Boss with my own eyes.
I was an assemblyman's aide
seven years ago.
He wanted a legislature passed,
and our assemblyman...
You know how felines are.
They sleep unless they're hunting.
He's just like them.
His paycheck is such a waste.
Park Bong-su.
Yes?
Your paycheck was deposited. Please check.
Okay.
My salary...
Ms. Jo, how much was my pay?
After deductions here and there,
it's a little over 900,000 won.
Wait.
After a full month's work?
You took a bunch of days off too.
So 900,000 won for a month's work.
Should I take on some part-time jobs?
-If they're simple enough--
-By the way, return that earpiece.
-Why?
-You quit, remember?
You shouldn't hold onto company property.
Come on. How can you say that?
Are you kidding me?
Darn.
-Get your act together!
-Her and her temper.
Black box!
Don't you see those things
in all those cars?
What can I do?
Every street has parked cars.
That's why your predecessor
stayed on rooftops!
Isn't it a simple dream?
He just wants to live like everyone else.
Still, that's what he wants,
so I'm letting him be.
He's a bit older than I am,
but he acts like a 13-year-old.
That's why I have to look out for him.
Is that friend a guy?
Yes.
-A guy you like?
-No.
Yes.
You said you have another interview.
Yes, but I have time.
The meeting is nearby.
Let's see.
Look at me, please.
Would you mind speaking casually to me?
Shall I?
Close your eyes.
All done.
Right, the interview.
You're going to watch
Kim Mun-sik's interview, right?
I don't think that's related to the man
that we know of.
Excuse me, sir.
We can't do a broadcast
on your wife who ran away.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Bong-su.
Park Bong-su!
-Yes?
-Answer the phone.
Sorry, wrong number.
Bong-su!
Will you move?
-We can do it like that.
-Sure.
Sir, I think we're doomed.
-Why?
-Mr. Kim's interview will be off script.
-What? Why?
-I just found out myself.
Mr. Kim told them
as soon as he got to the studio
that he's doing the interview
without a script.
Chief Kang is so stressed out right now.
Things are really tense.
INTERVIEW WITH KIM MUN-SIK,
NEW REPRESENTATIVE OF JEONGMIN PARTY
Sir, this is a live broadcast.
-If you say anything wrong--
-Don't worry and just relax.
Chief Kang,
ask me anything you want.
I know that people are talking about
the conflict between me
and my brother, Kim Mun-ho.
Yes, some question
your ability to manage Seoul
since you can't even
manage your own family.
My brother and I are both reporters.
I first became a reporter in 1980.
My brother is popular
because of this series,
but I was a member of that
pirate radio broadcast he mentioned.
I even brought a picture. May I show it?
-Yes, I'd like to see it.
-Okay.
Let's see.
Of the five friends, this is me.
This is my wife.
I fought for freedom of press
during those harsh times.
So even if my brother is wrong,
I must let him be
to protect the freedom of speech
that I fought for.
Pirate radio broadcasts
are a bit foreign to me.
What do we do about our broadcast
now that he's off script?
It was like that back then.
It's canceled.
-We weren't allowed to report much.
-All right.
So, we had to do pirate radio broadcasts.
Honestly, the press
has too much freedom these days.
I hope you know that
past generations sacrificed a great deal
so that you can enjoy this freedom.
I'm surprised to know
that the president of Jeil News
was part of a pirate radio broadcast.
I have something to show you.
What could it be?
Hold on a second. Aren't those yours?
These are the tapes
of our pirate radio broadcasts.
I've cherished them for the past 20 years.
Do you see the dates?
This one is from 1980.
Do you see this magazine?
It must seem weird to young people,
but this is how
simple and innocent we were.
Did that pirate radio show create it?
Yes.
Well, we only published one issue.
The magazine is called Healer.
What does it mean?
Do you see this?
"The media is what diagnoses
and treats the illness of the society."
With that conviction,
I've protected the media.
I now want to devote myself
to the city of Seoul
for this nation's freedom,
democracy, and order
that we protected with our lives.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
What for?
Please don't cry.
You'll have another episode.
Is something wrong?
Those tapes...
Do you want me to get them back for you?
It won't be very hard.
You don't do that anymore.
You want an ordinary life.
So Yeong-sin told you.
Yes.
I wish you could live like that too.
That's for me to work on, but...
Are you okay?
You scared me.
I thought you were going to cry.
I almost did.
Because they stole your tapes?
Come over with some beer again.
I have so much to tell you.
With Yeong-sin too?
Yes.
My people are the best in the world.
I'll use this office for the time being.
Put in another desk here.
I'm sure you have another office to use.
What, me?
Instead of here?
Set up the room once the desks come in.
Yes, sir.
You must not know who I am.
Look here. I'm Bae Sang-su, the president.
It's called Double S Guard
after my initials.
And this is the president's office.
Yes?
People are walking out of Double S Guard.
They destroyed
all the security cameras nearby.
Take pictures and send them to me.
Don't forget the license plates.
-Should I follow them?
-No. Stand by.
But what are we doing here?
We're giving Healer
his retirement pension.
He sent pictures of the guys
who followed him
from Park Dong-cheol's place.
That means Park Dong-cheol's real killer
must be among them.
Why are they hanging out
with Sang-su's gang?
Where have I seen him before?
I know I have.
This is Someday News.
We're taking tips about Boss.
A take-out joint?
No, I don't know their number.
Seventy percent of the posts are fake,
and 20 percent of the posts are nonsense.
But we got more than expected.
We got a few on Seodo Bridge.
It touched a nerve
among its blue-collar employees.
Think about it.
A bridge they worked on collapsed.
What if it collapsed after it opened?
Sleep a little.
You look like you haven't slept.
It's about to begin.
I don't know how or from where.
Right.
But they only know how to do one thing.
They'll probably start by cutting us off.
It's a dirty move
that I hate responding to,
but it's very effective.
Damn.
This is bold of you two.
She can't sleep
if other people are around.
What about you?
I'm not "other people."
Look over here.
I hate leaving pictures of me behind.
I've liked taking pictures
ever since I could walk.
-But...
-Yes?
You want to take on that Boss guy, right?
That's right.
Will Yeong-sin be in danger again?
I'm not sure.
Do you want to take her far away?
If you do, it'll be easier
to live like ordinary people.
I'm hesitant.
Why?
I've been wondering why,
and I think it's because of you.
We can't leave you alone and go far away.
I'm touched.
But...
What?
I can't live without her anymore.
So if it's for her, I can abandon you.
That's fine.
Sorry, wrong number.
This is Someday News. Do you have a tip?
We need to record the call. Is that okay?
Sure.
Hold on.
Yes, go on.
Here's your mail.
SUBPOENA
Sir.
You have something
from the Prosecutor's Office.
PROSECUTOR'S OFFICE
SUBPOENA
This informant can introduce you
to the employees from back then.
Begin with making them feel safe.
Sure thing.
Wait. Who are you people?
Why are you here?
We're from the National Tax Service.
The National Tax Service?
What is it?
We received a tip that Someday News has
been funded through suspicious channels.
Who's Kim Mun-ho?
That's me.
If you agree, we'll begin our search.
If you refuse, we'll make it compulsory.
What? No, not that!
Wait!
I bought that with my own money!
These are our company documents.
I said these are ours!
Come on!
Seriously?
Damn.
-Sir...
-Yes?
-Is there something...
-No, it's nothing.
-Hey, Bong-su.
-Yes?
My wife runs a chicken place
and the city suddenly did
a sanitation check.
They found bacteria in the water filter
and shut down the place.
The fine is over 10 million won.
That couldn't be related
to what happened today, could it?
Never mind. Get back to work.
It couldn't be.
Shit.
What?
That car. It seems odd.
What is it?
Ms. Jo, can you track Kim Mun-ho's phone?
Shut up about me retiring!
I think he's been kidnapped.
What do you want to do?
Do you want to go with me
or wait at Mun-ho's place?
You'll probably get in a fight, right?
Probably.
Go and bring him back.
-Let's go.
-Hurry off already.
Okay. You know the combination, right?
-Make sure to lock up--
-Don't worry. Just go.
All right.
Make a right at the intersection.