=A Taste of First Love=
=Episode 4=
Weiyi, didn't your boyfriend
keep you company
when you watched "Carmen",
your favorite opera performance?
He was busy with work.
There are only
two possibilities if a man
has no time
for the woman he loves.
First, he doesn't actually love you.
Second, he's too incompetent for you.
In my eyes,
my boyfriend is the best.
Weiyi, you said the same thing
about me back then.
Let me send you home.
You can stop here.
There's still some distance
before we reach your place, you know?
My boyfriend might be home.
I don't want him to misunderstand us.
You're finally back.
I was worried about you.
Q asked me out tonight.
Mingyuan,
I'm so tired.
Dear,
I suddenly remembered
that I haven't returned
the shared bike yet.
Just forget about it.
That won't do!
Hello?
I can see that your boyfriend
is locking his yellow bike.
Were you following me?
I was just curious.
Weiyi, I think you walked home
because you missed the last bus
after finishing
the opera performance, right?
That's none of your business.
Your boyfriend didn't even pick you up
at this late hour.
Does he really love you?
Our relationship has
nothing to do with you.
Weiyi,
are you truly happy right now?
Sir,
how did it go?
It was hard for me
to get my hands on the tickets.
("Carmen" Opera Performance VIP Ticket)
Weiyi,
did you watch the opera performance?
Yeah.
I thought we promised
not to exceed our monthly budget?
We still have to pay the deposit
of our first apartment together,
am I right?
I didn't spend a single cent on it.
Q's friend
gave us the tickets for free.
Q?
She's just a clerk.
Where did she get herself
such a generous friend?
Could it be that someone
is trying to court you two?
That's impossible.
Q and I have nothing.
Why would they try to court us?
People's hearts are unpredictable.
Anyway, we shouldn't owe them any favor.
You'll have to repay them eventually.
Don't you think you're overthinking it?
You're not relaxed when you should be.
But haven't we always been
living like this?
Yes.
But sometimes,
I do think that it's exhausting.
I think you must have been
too busy with work lately.
You need to calm down.
(Weiyi, are you)
(truly happy right now?)