And you must divorce her now!
No, I won’t!
Mookmanee and I love each other.
How well do you know her?
Why did you sign the marriage certificate with her?
Can you stop getting in my way—like Mum does?
love and what I need in life are two different things.
My Lady, Miss Prangdao is here.
Good morning, Step-Mother
Sit
I have something for you to do.
When are you going back to England?
Next week
No. Move it.
You’re staying here to help me
—and help your brother.
Songprod is blinded by his love for that girl.
Tomorrow, I’ll have you move into their house.
You’ll be my eyes and ears.
What are you scared of Prangdao,
Songprod won't be mad at you.
Listen to me
—no one can help Songprod but you.
I want them divorced as soon as possible.
Thank you, Songprod,
for helping me with all the expenses.
You’ve been a big help.
It’s all good, Mook.
Don’t worry about money.
If you need anything else, just let me know
—no need to be shy.
Thank you again, Songprod.
Alright then, I’ll get going.
What’s taking you so long? Do you need my help?
No need, I’ve already done it.
Hey, what’s with that smile?
So, when are you going to tell me
what you’re up to?
Now you’re bringing groceries into the house.
Isn’t that a little odd?
Odd? How?
I’m his sister—buying groceries for my brother.
What’s wrong with that? You’re just picking on me.
You!
Yes, I am picking on you.
And frankly,
I think you’re trading yourself for your brother just for me to mess with.
I am not! Let me go!
No.
I know you’re here to spy on me.
Well, good!
Then you can see for yourself
how lovely Songprod and I are together.
Feel free to come live with us
—you won’t have to keep coming and going.
You’ll see everything clearly. That way, you won’t miss any of the ‘important’ events.
Do you dare?
You said it
I'll be waiting.
Well, I have to go to work now.
See you around... sister-in-law.
Hello, Aunty Den?
Prangdao! I’ve just landed at the airport.
Come pick me up right now—it’s soooo hot here!
Okay
Beautiful! Beautiful!
Okay, change.
Perfect. Very pretty, Mook.
Alright, we’re done. You can rest now.
Thank you
Bravo!
Hello,
Mookmanee is currently doing a photoshoot for your product promotion Nita.
Good. I’ll head in now.
You go watch Songprod at the hospital.
I want to know his every move.
If there’s anything, I’ll call and update you.
Social media trends are really big right now.
I’ll make it even bigger. Just you wait.
Ok, bye
Okay, cut! That’s a wrap. Thank you, everyone.
Thank you
Mook, I think you need to stop engaging on social media for now.
I don’t want you fighting with people online.
This time... it’s different.
Anti-fans again?
What are they saying this time?
They’re boycotting all the products
and reality shows you’re endorsing as a brand ambassador.
They claim what you did was ‘immoral’
and shouldn’t be supported.
It’s getting big,
Mook. You should be prepared.
I don’t care, Peem.
It’s not far off from what I expected.
Oh, Peem! This sunscreen is amazing.
I was under the spotlight just now,
but my skin doesn’t feel irritated at all.
Is it really that good?
Here, give me your arm.
Even guys need to take care of themselves.
I can’t be the only one!
No way! It’ll be sticky.
It’s not! Let me tell you
—this is the new innovation, Aqua Tech. It’s lightweight,
non-sticky,
I confirmed
Look! It’s already gone.
Plus, it smells really nice.
Try it!
Oh... it does smell good.
See? Fast absorbing, right?
It’s good.
Who’s that?
Oh, that’s Miss Nita—
the owner of the food supplement product.
She’s also the heir to the pharmaceutical empire
... and and Songprod’s fiancée.
Mooknanee is the current brand ambassador,
but she’s done for.
Miss Nita.
I need to talk to you.
Privately.
Follow me.
Hello, Songprod? Nita’s here.
I’m here to talk about the contract agreement.
At first, I considered contacting your agency,
but since I had business nearby,
I decided to handle this personally.
You’ve damaged my brand’s reputation, Mooknanee.
I have more than enough reason to terminate our contract.
Get to the point. What do you want?
I want you to divorce Songprod.
He’s my fiancé.
And let me warn you—
I will do whatever
it takes to get him back.
My advice?
Back off now,
and I’ll pretend none of this ever happened.
Are you threatening me?
There’s no point, Nita.
Songprod and I love each other. You can’t force me out of his life.
Love?
Someone like you?
To be frank, I’m not surprised.
If I came from a background like yours,
I’d probably do the same.
With a rich man in front of me
—who wouldn’t want him?
You’re right.
You want him too, don’t you? But he didn’t choose you
—he chose me.
So, don’t bother me, Nita.
Do whatever you want. I don’t care.
You!
Are you done talking?
Please excuse me.
you two signing marriage certificates
—this is all just a cover for something,
Answer!!
Was it worth it, Mook? Giving up this much?
More than enough. For her, I can do anythingplease,
wake up soon.
What? You’re getting married next month?!
And you’re just going to let it happen, Songprod?