No, no, wait.
Where are we going?
I have plans later.
I promised my girlfriend.
You guys go ahead.
Call me if you need anything.
Put your girlfriend on hold.
Right now,
there's something more important waiting for you.
Let's go.
Move out.
Wait,
where are you taking me?
Turn around.
Let me go first.
Student Lin.
We've finally found you.
I'm not a leader.
I always follow the rules.
I've been an excellent student since childhood.
I haven't done anything wrong.
Have you got the wrong person?
Student Lin.
Don't be nervous.
We're not here to arrest you.
We just want to
learn from you.
We've been looking forward to meeting a talent like you
for a long time.
Let's go.
[Salute]
Everyone, please be seated.
Academician Li Fenghua from the Academy of Sciences.
The top expert in nuclear electronics in the country.
Hello.
Academician from the Engineering Academy.
The legendary Professor Kang in atomic materials.
When I was studying the textbooks,
I always wondered
if your beard was real or fake.
Finally meeting you in person today.
Professor Xue, the high-energy physics expert,
your books are way too expensive.
My heart was bleeding when I bought it.
I'll get you a copy another day.
Professor Wang.
Is there anything
on my face?
What are you doing?
Professor Wang.
My classmates and I were wondering
if you were balding.
I wear a hat
mainly for sun protection.
So you actually have hair.
Lin,
we've met now.
Please take a seat.
Since everyone is here,
I hereby announce
the Chase the Sun Project research team's
first meeting.
Now in session.
Chase the Sun Project?
What's that?
Mr. Gu,
you're determined to win this time.
The competition is just too weak.
Mr. Zhang,
can we start the exam a bit later?
Mr. Gu.
I can stall until the chairman arrives.
Once the chairman gets here,
we must start immediately.
Got it.
Go get all our available cars
and bring them all.
Block the road from the chairman's house
to the company completely.
All the cars?
Your fleet of cars -
the chairman knows them all.
If we get caught...
We can't worry about that now.
Every minute we can delay counts.
Gu Shaocheng has put a lot of effort into this.
If Lin Dongfeng doesn't come,
we stand no chance of winning.
Alright.
I'll give the orders right away.
Is this Lin Dongfeng
really that impressive?
This is how
everything happened.
Lin,
do you have any questions
about what happened today?
No.
Everyone has already
seen the comments.
Now,
[Japanese characters]
[Japanese character]
you experts
should discuss this with him.
Let's discuss possible approaches to controlled nuclear fusion.
Feel free to speak your mind.
Director Yang.
I think we should first verify
if he's really the author of that commentary.
In my opinion,
he's too flamboyant
and impulsive.
No matter how I look at it,
he doesn't seem capable of writing such a groundbreaking thesis.
Mr. Kang.
I've already explained everything.
Academician Kang,
how would you like to verify this?
You're a master in materials science.
Should we start with rare-earth barium copper oxide's
extraction and synthesis,
or with the principles of room-temperature superconductors?
Rare-earth barium copper oxide is a layered crystal.
Barium ions and rare-earth ions
form one layer in a square close-packed arrangement.
Copper ions and oxygen ions
form another layer in a square close-packed arrangement.
The two layers are nested together through oxygen ions.
It can be prepared using solid-state reaction,
vapor deposition,
or liquid-phase deposition methods.
Room temperature superconductors
can be prepared using
yttrium barium copper oxide with infrared pulses
to cause atomic oscillation and displacement,
making the copper oxide bilayers thicker and the interlayers narrower,
thus increasing the coupling degree.
All of this
was mentioned in my message.
Academician Kang can take a look at it.
So what do you think
is the key to making controlled nuclear fusion
available for civilian use?
The prerequisite for civilian use
is miniaturization.
We could try
a multi-module structure with detachable high-temperature superconducting coils.
Has the data you mentioned earlier
been verified?
Most of it comes from my calculations.
Some parts
due to limited school resources and equipment
haven't been experimentally verified yet.
Moving forward,
we can combine numerical simulation with experiments.
Then using your proposed
superconducting material preparation process and optimization plan.
If successful,
it will dramatically improve radiation effects and control capabilities.
This would allow controlled nuclear fusion
to achieve breakthroughs not seen in decades.
Do you all believe
his reasoning is feasible?
Huangri Juice Bar.
Huyue Juice Bar.
Approved.
Hengri Juice Bar.
I hereby announce.
Student Lin Dongfeng's
political review has been approved.
After consideration by higher authorities,
national level.
The Controlled Nuclear Fusion Research Team
has been officially established
in Jiangbei City.
The team's code name
is Zhuri (Chasing the Sun).
Security classification
is top secret.
Resource priority
is highest priority.
Security level
is maximum.
All domestic resources.
Yang Zhengdao will be responsible for coordination,
all units must fully cooperate.
The research team members are:
Li Fenghua,
Kang Tianfeng,
Xue Tai,
Wang Fei,
Deputy Leader Wu Wenyong,
and the Leader is
Lin Dongfeng.
I...
Leader Lin.
The weight of history
now rests on your shoulders.
Director Yang,
may I ask something?
Being the leader,
is there a salary for this?
Let's follow
Professor Wu's standards.
What do you think?
Professor Wu.
They say university teachers don't make much money.
May I ask about your salary?
Teaching and nurturing people
is indeed modest pay,
but my professor title
is still quite valuable.
You can put your mind at ease.
You old men all have children and grandchildren.
You have no idea how demanding mothers-in-law are nowadays.
Am I being demanding?
Tell me, am I asking for too much?
I never said he needs to be like Shaocheng
who's a company CEO
with a fortune worth billions.
But he should at least be comparable.
He should at least be able to afford a car and a house.
Do you think he can get into Huasheng Group?
I gave you both a chance.
And then what?
The interview starts in three minutes
and he's nowhere to be seen.
Let's go home.
Just wait a little longer.
If you want to wait, wait by yourself.
I won't stay here and be embarrassed with you.
Let me tell you.
If he can't get into Huasheng Group,
you and him...
There's absolutely no chance.
Lin Dongfeng, what are you doing?
Wanzhi.
Where's your mother?
My mom
said she wasn't feeling well
and went home first.
Wanzhi.
Don't wait here anymore.
Go rest in my office.
When Lin Dongfeng arrives,
I'll let you know.
No need.
Take Miss Zheng to rest.
Miss Zheng,
this way, please.
Do you know what time it is?
Why haven't we started yet?
Are you planning to keep everyone here for a midnight snack?
The chairman hasn't arrived yet.
How can we start?
Don't think I don't know your little trick.
Blocking all the roads
so my grandfather can't get here.
I've already sent a helicopter to pick up my grandfather.
Judging by the time,
he should be here any minute.
Grandpa.
Chairman.
Hello, Chairman.
Huasheng Group's
annual
talent selection meeting
is now officially beginning.
Is that the college student you found?
Did they lose their nerve?
Or are you hiding them as your secret weapon?
Gu Shaocheng,
why so anxious?
The game isn't over yet.
Nothing is certain.
Well...
Massachusetts,
this,
New Jersey,
and that
Imperial Tech.
By the way, sis.
Do you know who's setting the exam questions this year?
Professor Wu from Qingbei University.
He's an internationally renowned authority.
If you're not acquainted with him,
I can introduce you later.
The outcome is decided.
It's no fun anymore.
Sister.
You can stay here by yourself.
I'm going to rest.
When I receive the award after the competition,
I'll even have to thank them.