Wanzhi.
The property of the Zheng family
I don't want it.
That's right.
We are good friends.
But according to our previous bet,
you lost.
Lin Dongfeng, you're the one who lost. You're the one who lost.
It’s yours. It’s yours.
East Wind.
Where did you get so much money?
I've been working on projects
for some technology companies.
I didn't expect these companies to be so generous.
What bet?
What are you talking about?
East Wind.
Sorry.
Sister Gu and I like you very much.
So we made a bet before.
Who can make more money in a month?
Those who earn less
quit the competition.
Obviously,
Gu, you win.
Lin Dong Feng.
I give it to you.
As long as you can return the Zheng family's property to us,
On behalf of my mother,
and my late father.
Thank you forever.
Okay.
Deal.
Wanzhi,
What you said just now
really mean it?
We can't go back anymore.
I wish you and Sister Gu happiness.
Wish you happiness too.
Bingqing.
Let’s go.
East Wind.
We are finally together.
I'm sorry.
This is the latest watch.
It's 10,000 yuan, right?
I know you always want it.
Since you did well today, I’ll reward you.
I love you so much, Wanwan.
It's done. Let's continue.
I won't lose!
What?
Let me dance.
I'm an intellectual broadcaster, okay?
This is the second stage of experiment.
that needs to be reviewed again.
You didn't sleep well last night?
You look pale.
I didn't get any rest. I'm fine. I'm fine.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Come on.
You broke up again?
What are you talking about?
No way.
I'm not in the mood to date now.
We have
a national mission.
How can I be distracted?
I just
I didn't sleep well last night
Roommate keeps snoring It's too noisy
In that case
let's take a day off.
I'll show you around.
Let's hurry up and calculate the data.
Wu is waiting for me.
No.
As your research assistant,
I want to ensure your work efficiency.
With your current state,
I can't guarantee the accuracy of these data.
You need to change your brain.
Okay.
Where are we going?
Are you okay?
Let me take a photo for you.
It looks delicious.
Look inside
Come on.
Come here
Here.
I quit.
I'm so tired.
Look at you.
You should exercise more.
I can't even play.
It's so boring.
Oh no.
I was just playing.
I forgot about my business.
Hey, Editor Yang.
Yes.
Okay, we'll be right back.
Right away.
What?
How many people are waiting for your key data?
but you went to the amusement park all day.
That's ridiculous.
And you.
I asked you to be Lin Dong Feng's assistant,
not to play with him.
Write 3,000 words of self-criticism for me.
and send it to my office tomorrow.
No, sir.
I'm not feeling well today.
Let Mr. Yang take a walk with me.
and change my mind.
I'm just afraid that my condition
and affect the experimental data.
Shut up!
Who told you to be a hero?
I took him out.
It has nothing to do with Lin Dong Feng.
We have to go back to school.
We still have a lot of data to calculate.
Stop!
What else?
Mr. Yang.
Go back
go back to see your mom.
You haven't been home for weeks.
Your mom missed you.
Yes, Editor Yang.
Don't call me that.
There's no outsider here.
You know,
I don't like
call me that.
Okay.
He's your dad. He's your dad. He's your dad. He's your dad. He's your dad.
He's your dad.
He's a father
who has never been to an amusement park with his daughter.
He has never
who has never celebrated a birthday with his daughter.
He has never fulfilled
as a father.
So what if I go to the amusement park?
I only know Lin Dongfeng for two months.
can go with me.
And you
You've been my father for 22 years,
but you never kept your promise.
I had fun at the amusement park.
Because since I grew up,
This is the first time I've ever had someone go to an amusement park with me.
I'll give you the self-criticism tomorrow.
Let's go.
So Editor Yang is your father.
No wonder you know the research center so well.
They all envy me.
I had a father who was a high-ranking official.
But only I know
he is not a good father.
Since I can remember,
I only see him a few times a year.
and get sick once.
once during Chinese New Year.
When he quarreled with my mom,
it was once.
He's always arbitrary.
I like physics,
but he insisted that I study medicine.
He said it was for my own good.
He never thought about my feelings.
Every time
I want to communicate with him,
he seems to be busy.
I know.
I know he's busy.
But how could he be so busy
He doesn't even remember his daughter's birthday.
You can't say that.
I think Editor Yang loves you.
But his identity
is not
you didn't really know everything.
As the saying goes,
he lost his family because of everyone.
I think he must have his reasons.
Actually, over the past few years,
I don't hate him anymore.
I just feel wronged.
Sometimes, I'd rather he's just an ordinary person.
In this way,
he might be a good father.
Thank you.
for listening to me today.
It's nothing.
You were the one who comforted me last time.
We're even now.
And you're my only scientific research assistant.
What if your condition
and affect my work?
I forgot if you didn't tell me.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
To the canteen again.
Go back to the lab.
I urge you
to calculate the data of the second stage as soon as possible.
Mr Wu is still waiting.
No.
I'm tired today.
Shall we take a day off?
I can't.
Let's go.