Director Yang,
it's me,
Lin Dongfeng.
I suspect
there are issues with Huasheng Group's chip technology,
involving serious intellectual property infringement.
I request
to immediately terminate the approval process.
I've sent the evidence to your email.
I've received it.
The documents look fine.
You'll have a decision
within 5 minutes.
Okay.
Thank you, Director Yang.
You just contacted Director Yang from the Science and Technology Department.
You'll have results in five minutes.
Kid,
if you're going to pretend, at least make it believable.
Calling Director Yang?
And getting results in five minutes?
Do you know how high-ranking Director Yang is?
You can only see him on TV.
You'd never meet him in person.
Exactly.
Even Mr. Gu senior
would find it difficult to meet Director Yang.
If you can call Director Yang,
then I must be
the Jade Emperor himself.
Hey, you there,
on the big screen,
give me a five-minute countdown.
Go ahead and laugh.
I hope later
you'll still be laughing this happily.
Since you're being so stubborn,
I'll give you five minutes.
In five minutes,
I will take the stage with both chairmen
to announce the new technology to the world.
At that time,
I will definitely have my lawyers sue you for defamation.
Let everyone see
just how ridiculous and laughable you are.
Hello.
This is
Yang Zhengdao from the Technology Department.
Listen carefully.
I don't care what instructions Chairman Tang gave you.
If you dare to give Huasheng Group
a green light for their allegedly plagiarized technology,
you will bring everyone on your team tomorrow
with resignation letters to see me.
Only one minute left.
If you kneel down and beg for mercy now,
for Wanzhi's sake,
I might still spare you.
I was enjoying the mountain view from the tower,
when I heard commotion outside the city.
Time's up.
Chairmen,
let's go on stage.
Alright.
Did I trust him wrongly?
What?
Fine.
Yes.
What's wrong?
The approval was rejected.
The new technology launch has been suspended.
Chairman Tang,
we're about to go on stage.
Please don't joke around.
It's true.
That's impossible.
You both told me...
Today's plan will go without a hitch.
Mr. Gu.
This is what the higher-ups want.
We have no choice.
We hope you
can understand our situation.
When you made your promises,
you all beat your chests saying nothing would go wrong.
Now that there's trouble, you want to abandon ship
and ask me to understand?
No way.
This stage today,
you're going up whether you like it or not.
You have no choice.
No, no, no.
How dare you!
Gu Shaocheng,
I've been too lenient with you.
If it weren't for your grandfather's sake,
who do you think you are
to negotiate terms with us?
You really think you're something special.
You're just a board director.
Who do you think you are?
You're a dime a dozen.
Let me tell you something.
If you dare to be disrespectful again,
I'll make sure your Huasheng company never has a good day again.
Mr. Nie!
What are you talking about?
That's going too far.
Young Gu,
today's approval process
did encounter some issues.
However,
that doesn't mean
it won't pass in the future.
After all,
Mr. Nie and I are both here to help.
Right?
Besides,
we've had a friendship with your father for so many years.
That's right.
How could we possibly ignore his own child?
Mr. Tang, I...
Don't worry.
We'll continue to follow up
on everything here.
We won't be staying today.
Mr. Tang.
Dongfeng.
I thought you were just a genius student,
but I never expected
your background would be so impressive.
Not really.
Director Yang,
thank you.
I should be thanking you.
Thank you for discovering this issue in time.
Otherwise, if that patent infringement had gone to market domestically,
we would have become an international laughingstock.
It's my duty.
Director Yang,
there's one more thing.
There's a Chairman Tang
and a Chairman Nie.
They seem to be deeply involved with Huasheng Group.
I've already spoken with the relevant departments.
We'll take action once the evidence is confirmed.
You're so wise, sir.
You know,
less flattery
and more experiments.
The weight of history still rests on your shoulders.
Yes, understood.
Let's go.
He just left.
What's going on?
The number you have dialed is temporarily unavailable.
What's happening?
Mr. Gu.
Is the press conference still happening or not?
Exactly.
Is it still on?
Mr. Gu.
Why did the two chairmen leave?
There's not a problem, is there?
No, no, no.
I've already transferred all the money to you.
Can this new technology still be launched today?
We all came here because of your promising news.
Heavily invested in Huasheng stocks, huh?
That's right.
Put everything into it.
What should we do?
Exactly.
Is it happening or not?
Well, it's like this.
The two chairmen said
the new technology documents are still being processed.
Today's release is postponed.
Postponed?
What?
The release is postponed.
Please stay calm.
Huasheng stocks hit the limit down!
Give us our money back!
No, no.
Please, please.
Everyone, don't worry.
Pay us back!
Everyone, please calm down.
Give us our money!
Everyone, please.
There's no problem.
Stop right there!
I won't.
Stop!
You won't lose your money.
Do you know who I am?
We see you clearly.
You're Director Gu!
If you hadn't promised the stock would rise today,
we brothers wouldn't have mortgaged our houses.
That's right! Beat him up!
Beat him! Beat him!
No, no, no!
Stop hitting him!
Hit him!
Stop it!
Beat him!
Stop!
Wanzhi,
are you okay?
Stop fighting!
It's too chaotic here.
Let's go outside to talk.
Let's go.
Hey, Miranda,
bring some people over
to take the young master home.
As soon as possible.
Wanzhi.
I want to explain my relationship with Miss Gu.
We really don't have...
Shut up.
Let me explain.
Miss Zheng, it's like this.
Lin Dongfeng and I are just business partners.
Hmm.
You had too much to drink at the selection meeting.
I was the one who brought you back.
To repay me, Lin Dongfeng
rushed to participate in
Huasheng Group's competition before the selection ended.
The next day, I had some data that needed processing.
I paid Lin Dongfeng to help me.
What you saw in the dormitory
was absolutely not what you imagined.
I accidentally spilled water on my clothes.
I had no choice but
to change into his clothes.
I don't know if what I'm saying
makes sense to you.
What about these?
It's not Wanzhi.
I and her...
Shut up.
Miss Zheng,
a few staged photos,
what are you trying to prove?
I don't deny the scenes in these photos.
Lin Dongfeng did go to the mall with me,
but that was to make you happy,
to buy you a gift.
I can retrieve the security footage from that day
and show you
what really happened at the mall.
I think the reason you broke up with Lin Dongfeng...
It's not just these few photos, is it?
Your relationship
doesn't seem that cheap.
I was too selfish before.
About the marriage with the Gu family,
I'll think it over carefully.
Perhaps
Dongfeng and I
are truly not meant to be together.
It's related to the Zheng Group's debt, isn't it?
How did you know?
When I heard Gu Shaocheng introducing you on stage,
I figured it out.
Years ago, your father borrowed a lot of money
from the business world to prevent Zheng Group from being acquired.
Perhaps Gu Shaocheng
is using this to threaten you.
He didn't threaten me.
It was my own choice.
Besides marrying him,
I can't think of any other way to save our family.
Wanzhi, trust me.
I have the ability now.
What I'll create in the future
will be worth more than 10 billion.
I can definitely help you clear all the debts.
Dongfeng.
When will you ever be more down-to-earth?
Let me prove it.
This guy might be exaggerating about the billions in value.
But with his talent,
he should be able to pay off your family's debts.
Besides,
he knows such influential people.
If the creditors are pressing,
I can lend him the money first,
as long as he's willing to give Huasheng a chance.
I'm willing.
As long as it helps Wanzi,
I'll do anything.
So.
Actually that day,
you attended Huasheng's selection,
and you got a perfect score.
Your mother would definitely approve of us if she knew.
As for what really happened that day,
I'll tell you everything later.
Mm.
Alright.
Mission accomplished.
You must be hungry.
I'll treat you all to a feast.
Miss,
the master wants you to return immediately.
Please come with us.