[A Beautiful Lie]
Xing Zhizhi, why did you do that?
[Five years ago]
Although I knew you got
a degree in rehabilitation medicine,
[Five years ago]
I never thought you'd actually switch to it.
[Xing Zhizhi; Attending Physician; Thoracic Surgery]
Do you know how much Professor Ge expects from you?
Can you live up to his expectations?
Can you do justice to these skilled hands of yours?
Come on, let's sit down and talk.
Sit down and talk.
Isn't there still you in the thoracic surgery department?
[Xing Zhizhi; Attending Physician; Rehabilitation Department]
I know my own limits.
Why did you really stop performing surgeries?
Isn't helping patients recover
after surgery
and return to their normal lives
a meaningful thing?
That's not what I meant.
Tell me honestly,
did you run into something at Suman?
No.
[Episode 20]
[You mean, even if you're lying]
[I still have to pretend to believe you. Whatever you say is right]
Xing Zhizhi.
I believed it.
What you said before about that quantum entanglement
and destiny,
I believed it all.
Because I remember now.
How are you holding up?
Hang in there. I'll save you.
What's your name?
Qin Xiaofei.
When I was in France,
you saved me.
When you rushed to save me that day,
it was just like that time.
I remembered everything.
You saved me once again.
Maybe you're right;
fate has a way
of bringing us together again and again.
It must be because we're destined to be together.
I want to believe again—
believe that you'll stay with me,
that you're the one heaven meant for me.
It took away my father
and my home,
so it should compensate me for something, right?
Go to sleep.
Qin Xiaofei.
You finally remembered.
I didn't believe in fate before either,
but again and again,
it has brought you back to me.
Fortunately,
everything is over now.
I hope it's all over now.
I'll be with you.
I won't leave you.
You're a doctor.
I beg you, please save my baby.
It's sweet.
[Wang De Wang Xylitol]
Xing Zhizhi?
Xing Zhizhi!
Something has come up at the hospital, so I have to go.
I made you some porridge. Remember to have it in the morning.
Don't forget to take your cold medicine as well.
I left the xylitol on your bedside table.
Eat more fruits to get your vitamins.
I'll call you when I get there.
Do well in your filming.
I'll be waiting for you to come home.
As your boyfriend, I'm exercising my rights.
Tell Hao Jun to stay away from you.
[Rehabilitation Clinic 3]
You're a doctor.
I beg you, please save my baby.
[Qin Xiaofei]
[Decline] [Answer]
Morning, Xiaofei.
[Mic on] [Speaker on] [Camera on]
Xing Zhizhi,
I voice-called you
[Mic on] [Speaker on] [Camera on]
twice last night,
but you didn't answer either of them.
[Mic on] [Speaker on] [Camera on]
You just woke up now, didn't you?
I had three meetings yesterday,
ten new cases, and eight follow-ups...
Stop, stop, stop.
Tell me what's really going on with you.
Nothing, just sleep-deprived.
You're still lying to me, aren't you?
Xing Zhizhi,
you're not regretting being with me, are you?
We've just started dating,
and you're already lying to me.
It's clear you have something on your mind.
You're the one who told me
that in a relationship, we should treat each other honestly.
But now, look at you...
I didn't expect I'd be the only one fully committed to this.
What time did you finish shooting yesterday?
[Xing Zhizhi] [Qin Fei]
Xing Zhizhi.
Are you trying to change the subject?
[Xing Zhizhi] [Qin Fei]
Tell me.
What's going on with you?
Is something bothering you?
No.
It's just
that I've been having the same dream lately.
I keep dreaming
that I'm lying in ruins,
and then
you're telling me to pull myself together.
That was quite an ominous dream you had.
Other couples get to be all lovey-dovey
when they're dating.
But only you
had that kind of dream.
You did insist that I tell you.
True.
You have such a beautiful girlfriend,
but you can only see her through a screen.
You can't kiss or hug her.
And I have to film romantic scenes with another actor.
Oh, right. I have a kissing scene later.
[Mic on] [Speaker on] [Camera on]
Dr. Xing,
when you dream tonight,
remember to give me a kiss.
Qin Xiaofei, wait until you come back,
and you'll see how I'll deal with you.
Don't say it if you won't follow through.
I'm heading to the set now.
Bye-bye.
Hurry up, hang up the phone.
Hello, Mr. Xing! Hello, Mr. Xing!
Hello, everyone. Hello, everyone.
Slow down.
Your head is hurting again.
When are you going to
tell Qin Fei about me?
We'll see.
Qin Fei still doesn't know about what happened to you abroad, right?
What if she can't accept me?
She won't.
But what if she can't?
Aren't you worried at all?
Your headaches are getting worse.
Go see a doctor about it.
Xing,
from what I see in this scan,
there doesn't seem to be any problem.
Then why
do I keep having headaches
and trouble sleeping?
Well, regarding your symptoms,
you're a doctor too,
so you know
the human brain is a very complex thing.
This may be
the post-concussion syndrome,
but it may also be...
I mean, it may be
caused by psychological issues.
If not, come to our hospital's
psychiatry department and have them take a look.
Du, you...
You...
We all work in the same hospital.
What are you afraid of? Just have them check on you.
[WeChat]
Today's girlfriend update,
please check.
I had oatmeal with milk for breakfast.
As per your medical advice, I didn't go hungry.
The soup at lunch wasn't good at all.
I really miss your homemade pork rib soup...
There's no signal at the outdoor set today,
so I don't know
when these WeChat messages will go through...
Here is a wildflower for you...
Mainly to remind you...
that you're taken now.
Don't pick up on other girls!
Xiaoxiao says
communication is key in relationships.
So I'm sending you whatever comes to mind.
You must do the same—
report your whereabouts to me anytime, anywhere.
You're not replying at all...
Looks like there's really no signal.
Xing Zhizhi, I miss you so much.
I'll be back soon!
[Qin Xiaofei]
I've been really busy with work today
and just now got to have lunch.
I miss you too.
[Qin Xiaofei]
[Decline] [Answer]
Xiaofei.
You're taking a break? Let me tell you,
the director praised me today.
It's the first time
a director has told me
that my acting was decent.
And Xiaoxiao also said I was really into the role
and that my acting had improved.
Are you happy?
Of course, I'm happy.
You know very well
that I did go through some hardships for this show.
What's wrong?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Do you think I'm being too talkative and clingy?
How could I be, Xiaofei?
I love it when you're clingy.
And I love
how you share everything with me, whether it's big or small.
However, Ms. Qin,
you mentioned getting deeply into the role.
Are you talking about the romantic scenes with Hao Jun?
What if you can't get out of character?
I...
Xing Zhizhi,
why have you suddenly
become so insecure?
That's not like you.
This is my first relationship, and I'm often alone,
so it's understandable
that I don't have much confidence, right?
Then I'll tell you some news.
What is it?
Because my acting skills have improved rapidly,
[Mic on] [Speaker on] [Camera on]
I can wrap up early.
Really?
[Mic on] [Speaker on] [Camera on]
I'd like a bag.
Okay.
Sir, this item
is half price for the second one today.
Would you like a second one?
No, I don't need it.
Just one is enough; just one.
[Spicy tofu] [Braised eggplant with potatoes]
Three, two, one,
action.
Okay, cut!
That was the final scene of Qin Fei!
Good! Good!
Come on.
Qin Fei, congratulations on wrapping up.
Thank you.
Good job, well done.
During this time,
I've had high expectations for you.
You've also made great progress.
Good, very good indeed.
I'm reserving you for my next show,
so don't raise your price.
Thank you, Director.
Come on, Director, let's take a photo together.
-Okay, come on.
-Okay.
Come on.
Okay, everyone, let's take a group photo together.
Anyone else here want to join us for a photo?
It's okay. Come on.
Ms. Qin, may I have your autograph?
Ms. Qin, I'm such a big fan!
I love you so much. Can we take a photo together?
Ms. Qin. Ms. Qin.
Could you sign an autograph for me, please?
Ms. Qin, let's take a photo, Ms. Qin.
Thank you; you're so beautiful.
Ms. Qin, Ms. Qin!
Thank you, Ms. Qin! Thank you, Ms. Qin!
-Ms. Qin, you're so beautiful! -Come on.
-Okay, thank you.
-So beautiful!
Alright, good job.
Ms. Qin, could you sign an autograph for me, please?
Ms. Qin, you're so gorgeous, Ms. Qin!
Ms. Qin, Ms. Qin!
Could you sign an autograph for me, Ms. Qin?
One at a time, please. One at a time.
Excuse me, make way, please.
Make way, please. Let me through.
Hello, thank you. Thank you all.
We'll sign for you next time; next time.
Goodbye everyone, goodbye, goodbye.
Goodbye, Ms. Qin!
Alright, attention, all departments!
Let's head over there.
We're about to change sets.
Hold this for me.
Okay.
Wait for me in the car.
Congrats on finishing filming.
All packed up?
It's so nice to have someone waiting for you at home.
What's this for?
Thank you for helping me get this role.
What are you thanking me for?
You earned it yourself
through your own efforts.
Do you know
why I like Wang Hui?
Because she's brave.
She knows
to move on with her head held high.
Xiaoxiao,
I'm really grateful to you.
Thank you for encouraging me
to embrace a new love.
Now, I'm going to embrace love.
What about you? What are you planning to do?
Chen Shen does seem quite unreliable,
but I have to admit
that he really likes you.
When did he buy you off too?
I can't help it.
He offered too much.
He said if you agree,
he'll give me his entire fortune.
How about this?
You pretend to agree first,
and then we can split his money.
You sold me out, and I have to give you half of the money?
Be happy,
leading lady.
Xiaoxiao.
Xiaoxiao, I'll head back first.
Okay.
Didn't I tell you to come later?
You must have been waiting for a while.
I didn't have anything else to do,
so I came early.
Rose.
It's quite beautiful.
Who gave it to you?
Qin Fei. She wrapped up filming today.
Oh, right, right.
Well,
I've brought you some snacks.
They are all fruits that you like,
and this soy milk.
Didn't you say you really loved it last time?
I'm now the distributor of this soy milk.
You can have as much as you want from now on.
Well,
do you want to go see a movie together later?
I heard there's a good one out.
It's okay. If you don't want to watch,
then we won't. I can just take you home.
Let's watch.
What movie?
Let me check what movies there are.
I bought tickets for two movies.
One is a romance,
while the other is a sci-fi.
If you don't want to watch the romance,
we can watch the sci-fi movie.
This sci-fi movie
also has a love plot in it.
Cheers.
What did you think of the movie today?
What do you think?
I think it's just okay.
Really?
You spent half the movie looking at me
instead of watching,
and you still think it's just okay?
Elaborate on that.
Well, if you put it that way,
it also proves that you spent half the time looking at me.
If you weren't looking at me, how would you know that I was looking at you?
How long have you been interested in me?
Why did you suddenly ask that?
I don't think that is a good movie.
A one-sided love,
where only one person waits alone,
is too cruel for anyone
and unfair.
Am I right?
It is unfair.
But love
is never about fairness.
Even if only one person is waiting,
as long as they're willing
to wait,
I think that's okay.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Okay.
We still have time.
Whose movie do you want to watch next?
I'll go with you.
Really?
Really.
Okay.
Opportunity knocks, but once.
Better tell me quick before I change my mind.
I want to watch "Summer Girls."
Can you watch it with me?
Then, let's watch it.
Really?
Really.
Okay.
But I'll just give it a try.
I can't guarantee that this movie will be good.
If it's not good
and you want to leave halfway,
you have to tell me.
Don't worry.
Even if this movie isn't good,
I will definitely
leave in the middle.
I'm just joking.
I definitely won't leave.
Don't worry.
I was joking.
I was only joking earlier.
Whoever leaves first is a dog.
Rest assured.
I definitely won't leave.
Hurry up and eat; the steak is getting cold.
You're so handsome.
Dr. Xing, what's the occasion?
Handing out sweets so early in the morning?
So sweet.
What are you talking about?
Isn't it Nurses' Day today?
I thought I'd hand out some chocolates to you.
The drinks will be here soon.
You all have one. You all have one.
Thank you, Dr. Xing.
No problem, no problem.
You seem to be in high spirits.
Did something good happen to you?
Is your girlfriend back?
What are you talking about?
Everyone's been working really hard lately,
so I thought I'd bring some chocolates
to reward you for all your hard work.
Well, that girl, you know?
No, no. Forget it. Forget it.
Take the chocolates. Just take the chocolates.
Well, well, Xing Zhizhi.
You're already taken, yet you're still flirting around here.
Yes, each one has different flavors, and then...
No wonder you didn't reply to my WeChat messages.
Flirting with girls here, huh?
And you said
that you thought of me on the day and dreamed of me at night.
-It was all just an act.
-The drinks will be here soon.
Alright, I'm going back to work now. Goodbye.
Thank you, Dr. Xing!
-It's okay.
-Thank you, Dr. Xing!
I was standing right in front of you for so long,
yet your eyes were glued to those young nurses.
You didn't even spare me a glance.
You really are a piece of work.
Where are you?
When did you get here?
Didn't you say
you'd be back tomorrow?
Coffee booked the flight ticket too early.
Alright, then, I'll take you out for something good.
I'm not going.
All the chocolates are gone.
What's left for me to eat?
Tell me the truth.
Why did you buy chocolates for them?
I can explain.
Isn't it Nurses' Day today?
So I gave them chocolates.
It's just an employee benefit.
We have to give them something on Nurses' Day,
right?
Don't be jealous, okay?
Don't be jealous.
I am jealous. Why shouldn't I be?
Are you still jealous?
You're still jealous, aren't you?
Alright, alright.
What are you doing? There are so many people around.
Alright, don't be jealous, okay?
Okay?
You must be tired after such a long day.
Go home and get some rest.
Tomorrow at ten in the morning,
let's meet at the bottom of the mall by your place.
What are we going to the mall for?
To go on a date.
Why isn't he here yet?
I'm all covered up like this.
What if Xing Zhizhi doesn't recognize me?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Qin Xiaofei.
I... I got stuck in traffic on my way here.
Good thing you recognized me.
I was worried you wouldn't find me among all these people.
How could I not recognize you?
Look at this entire floor;
you're the one dressed the most strangely.
How am I dressed strangely?
If it weren't for you
insisting on meeting in such a public place...
I'm a public figure after all.
I'm all wrapped up like this
just because I'm afraid it'd affect your life.
Alright. How could I be afraid of that?
I'm only afraid you don't want to affect my life
and might run away without taking responsibility for me.
Zhizhi,
would you feel
that dating me is particularly a hassle?
We're going out on a date,
yet it's like we're sneaking around.
And we can't even take a nice couple photo.
How could I be?
Since it's a date,
let's do something exciting.
Are you up for it?
What exciting?
We are in public.
What are you planning to do?
Are you scared?
Xing Zhizhi, Xing Zhizhi.
Alright, I'm just teasing you.
Come with me.
You...
No. 108.
-No. 108.
-This way.
[Hi BBQ; BBQ Hotpot; Self-Buffet]
-No. 108.
-This way.
[Hi BBQ; BBQ Hotpot; Self-Buffet]
Come on, come on.
Have a seat. Be careful.
[Hi BBQ; BBQ Hotpot; Self-Buffet]
-No. 109.
-Come on.
I want to take a photo there.
Let's go.
Slow down.
There's no one here. I want to take a photo here.
Come on, we've already taken dozens of photos.
Please, let me take one more photo.
Just one more.
Alright, one last photo then.
-What's wrong?
-Why is she
dressed so strangely?
Wait, doesn't she look familiar?
Doesn't she look a bit like Qin Fei?
Qin Fei?
Isn't she with Hao Jun?
No way.
Our Hao Jun wouldn't be interested in her.
Let's gesture a heart.
Look.
-It's Qin Fei.
-Qin Fei!
-It's really Qin Fei!
It really is Qin Fei!
-Qin Fei.
-Qin Fei!
I know you didn't really want others to notice.
[Mic on] [Speaker on] [Camera on]
But do you really think
wrapping yourself up like a zongzi
could fool anyone?
Do you know of
a clumsy denial resulting in self-exposure?
[Ren Siqi] [Qin Fei]
Alright, I've taken care of
those two high school girls.
Please, just be good, okay?
Stay at home
and don't go out anymore.
I know.
You won.
My turn now.
Boring, boring, boring!
Come on, focus on the game.
I heard there's going to be a lunar eclipse in two days,
which only happens once every three years.
Ren Siqi said
that you should stay at home.
Isn't it nice to have a date at home?
We have food, beverages, and movies.
And you have me.
Xing Zhizhi.
Is it really Ren Siqi who wants me to stay at home,
or is it you
who has bad ideas, Dr. Xing?
What bad ideas could I possibly have?
Xing Zhizhi, stop smiling.
Ren Siqi is already
discussing a new show with me.
I might start filming next month.
I'm really tired of staying at home.
I just want to have a normal date.
You're clever, aren't you?
Can't you think of something?
Please.
If you
make my wish come true,
I'll make some of your grown-up wishes
come true in return.
Then,
can you fulfill my wish first?
Let's go.
[Huhai Hexi Hospital]
So, after Qin Fei came back,
you two haven't had a proper date?
Yeah.
Every time we go out,
it's like, "It's Qin Fei and I'm invisible, or you're so hot, and she is invisible."
So you two have just cooped up at home?
Get your mind out of the gutter.
You wouldn't know what I was thinking
unless you were thinking the same thing!
You're pretending!
Actually,
Qin Fei just wants a simple, ordinary date.
Why is it so difficult?
I really wouldn't know about that.
I've never dated a female celebrity.
I can't relate.
What did you say?
I said I've never dated a female celebrity.
What?
Liu Yanze, I need your help urgently.
Why are you coming to me
for dating advice?
You're clueless; Qin Fei doesn't have much experience on it either?
Stop talking nonsense.
Qin Fei finally has some time off,
and she just wants to go out and have fun,
but we can't go anywhere without being spotted.
You... you help me think of a solution.
Listen carefully.
If you guys choose to drive somewhere,
first make sure no one is following you.
Of course,
you could also take a couple of laps on the overpass
to play it safe.
However, a lot of people already know
my car and license plate,
so for important dates
or short trips,
we usually have a backup car in advance,
just in case.
Actually, if you don't want to get spotted,
the most important thing is to blend in.
[Travel]
The key to blending in isn't about wearing hats or masks,
but rather a completely different style
and a relaxed state.
Even if people see you,
they'll only think you're
an ordinary person who looks like a celebrity.
The more you're afraid of being noticed,
hiding, and sneaking around,
the more likely you are to attract attention from passersby.
One last point:
if you want a long, uninterrupted date,
it's best to choose a night.
It's dark.
As for the location,
try to pick somewhere with fewer people
and, preferably, private spaces.
Of course, if money isn't an issue,
you could always book the entire venue.
I'm having dinner with Chen Shen.
I've got to go now.
Who is it?
Guess.
How am I supposed to guess that?
Qin Fei.
She's planning to go on a date with Xing Zhizhi.
Why haven't you started eating yet?
Come on, try this meat.
It just arrived today.
It's especially tender. Here.
We've been eating like this every day, and I've gained weight.
Eat... eating these won't make you gain weight.
And shrimp too won't make you gain weight.
All of this is based on my personal experiences.
As for everything else,
you'll have to figure it out yourselves.
Xiaofei,
I'm off work.
[Use this elevator for outpatient check-ups]
Where are you? I'm in the parking garage.
What?
Your girlfriend's here to pick you up after work,
and you're still dragging your feet.
[Use this elevator for outpatient check-ups]
My legs are sore from standing.
You just came like this?
No one noticed?
No one noticed. Pretty impressive, huh?
Very impressive.
Dr. Xing, off work?
Yes, I'm off work.
And who is this?
Hello, sisters.
Oh, right, she's my cousin from a distant relative's side.
She's on break from school,
so I'm showing her around.
Alright, have a good time then.
[Use this elevator for outpatient check-ups]
We'll be going now, Dr. Xing.
-Bye.
-Bye. Take care.
[Use this elevator for outpatient check-ups]
-Bye.
-Bye. Take care.
How was that? I pulled it off, right?
You're good.
So, cousin, where shall we go tonight?
Here.
Thank you, thank you. I'll return them to you tomorrow.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Come on, give it to me.
Hey, what are you doing?
Stop it; people can see us.
I'm hungry.
Alright, alright.
Then, you
put the batteries in the flashlight.
I'll go make some noodles for you.
What are you afraid of?
Are you afraid that someone might see us?
I'm not; why would I be afraid?
How could I be afraid?
I...
I'm not afraid.
If you're not afraid, come on, come on.
Give me a kiss.
Fine, I'll kiss you. Sure, who's afraid?
I told you that you were afraid, yet you still wouldn't admit it.
-I'm not.
-Then why are you avoiding?
-He coughed, and I…
-Come here. Come on.
Look how nervous you are.
Well... they're all watching.
Who's watching you?
If you're like this, let me tell you.
If you don't care, then I won't care either.
I'm really going to kiss you. I'm really going to kiss you.
[Alarm: 10 minutes later]
Wake up.
It's time to watch the lunar eclipse.
Come on, get up.
Ten more minutes.
Hurry up, or we'll miss it.
You go. I'm not going.
If you don't get up,
I'll tickle you.
Get up; get up.
-Don't tickle me.
-Get up.
Get up, get up, get up, up!
Are you a dog? You bit me.
You're really angry now.
Then, then...
bite me again, then.
Alright, don't be mad.
Hurry up; we're going to be late.
We're going to miss it.
-I haven't put on my wig yet. -It's fine.
The eclipse will be over soon.
I want to ask you a question.
After seeing me in Paris,
did you try to find me?
No. Why do you ask?
I just wanted to know.
But now I regret having asked.
Next question.
Have you ever watched a lunar eclipse with someone else?
Think carefully before you answer.
If you answer incorrectly,
you'll be in serious trouble.
I haven't.
You're the first and only one.
I'll barely consider that a correct answer.
Look, the lunar eclipse is starting!
Look.
The ancients' words weren't very reliable.
Didn't they refer to the lunar eclipse as "the Heavenly Dog devouring the moon"?
It doesn't look like a dog at all.
But...
the lies from the ancients sound more poetic.
So people just pretended to believe them.
When many people believed them,
those lies turned into beautiful legends.
Do you get what I'm saying?
Yeah.
You mean
that even if you're lying,
I still have to pretend to believe you.
Whatever you say is right.
Clever.
What about me?
Would you believe everything I tell you?
Xing Zhizhi,
I'm asking you questions now.
Who said you could ask a question back?
You're so bossy.
I am particularly bossy.
And I have plenty of flaws too.
I'm unreasonable and willful.
And you bite.
Alright, alright.
I like you just the way you are,
okay?
Does your hand hurt?
It's this hand.
Then does this hand hurt?
It hurts. Of course, it hurts.
It doesn't hurt. Not at all.
I would.
I'd believe everything you say.
♫The silence of night, the breath of rain♫
So don't lie to me, okay?
♫They became pleasant because of you♫
♫I never told you how much I missed you♫
Xiaofei,
I will never hurt you.
♫I never told you how much I missed you♫
Never.
♫When I opened my mouth, I couldn't say anything♫
Come on.
♫You, jade-hued and radiant bright♫
♫You, ashen-gray with gaze downcast♫
♫Amid all the shadows, you're the only one I see♫
♫I never told you♫
♫I've never been so firm♫
♫You're the one♫
♫Longing for you to become the air I breathe♫