[A Beautiful Lie]
[Eighteen years ago]
It seems the boss has changed the oil today.
It doesn't taste as good as the old oil did.
[Eighteen years ago]
Why aren't you eating?
I didn't do well on the exam, so I'm not in the mood.
Look over there!
What a big teddy bear!
Do adults also like plush toys?
I learned from a book
that many plush toys
feel almost like human skin.
When you're feeling down,
hugging one can cheer you up.
I really want one too.
Here, give it to me.
-Come on.
-What are you doing?
Do you feel better now?
[Episode 32]
[Qin Xiaofei, I miss you so much]
Qin Xiaofei,
today is the 25th day of treatment.
I slept 9 hours yesterday.
It's very quiet here,
and the air is particularly good.
In the morning, I can even hear the birds singing.
I feel like I've gotten a little better.
Today's breakfast
is milk, black pepper beef sandwich,
along with strawberries and bananas.
I heard that they produce white tea here.
I had some yesterday.
It has a very light and fragrant taste.
What are you doing now?
Qin Xiaofei,
I miss you so much.
[October 23, 2023]
Who is it? Who is it?
Wait, wait. What are you doing?
Fei, it's me, it's me.
You scared me to death.
Where did that person go?
-I've been looking for him for a long time.
-Fei,
I've figured it all out.
This rehabilitation center
is divided into two parts.
The front is for accommodations,
and we also perform here.
Further inside,
it's more high-end and private,
specializing in rehabilitation vacations,
with a medical team on site.
You said Xing Zhizhi is inside there, right?
I think so.
I'm leaving.
Fei,
don't forget the small cake you made.
Here.
-You mustn't let Xing Zhizhi see you.
Why is this place so big?
Where exactly is he?
Brother, slow down!
-Sister,
-Wait for me!
The black bear is over there!
Big black bear!
Who are you calling a big black bear?
How do I look like a big black bear?
Do I look like a black bear to you two?
Brother, let's go.
The big black bear looks fierce.
I'm clearly a beautiful princess bear.
Black bear? Poor eyesight.
Are you alright?
Did you get hurt?
May I...
Get up first. Come on.
Do you want to take off this head
to get some fresh air?
You can't take it off?
Well, why can't you speak?
Dolls can't talk.
Alright, very professional.
This is your cake.
It's a bit damaged. Here you go.
Eat?
You want me to eat it and be happy?
Thank you.
Indeed, very few people come to this place.
I'm very happy to see you.
♫You occupy my sight♫
♫Light up every moment♫
♫When I keep thinking about you♫
♫The whole world has fallen♫
♫My heart♫
♫I just want to stay by your side♫
♫My love♫
♫I will do anything for you♫
♫One more time♫
Thank you.
♫Till forever♫
Goodbye.
♫We're meant to be together♫
Bye.
Be careful.
♫We're meant to be together♫
♫You occupy my sight♫
♫Light up every moment♫
[Happy and safe]
Is the treatment not progressing well?
What did Director Li say?
He thinks my medication dosage is too low
and suggested I increase it.
[Self-Rating Anxiety Scale]
But that might carry risks
and could have varying degrees of side effects,
like slowed reactions or emotional flatness.
Yes.
So you accepted this treatment plan?
I promised Qin Fei
that I would return to her side as soon as possible.
You're a doctor yourself.
You know what risks mean.
Are you really not going to reconsider?
I want to get better quickly.
Since you've already decided,
I'll do my best to assist you. Just keep a calm mindset
and don't worry too much about the side effects.
Don't worry, I'm feeling pretty good right now.
You seem to be in a good mood today.
Did something good happen?
Not really.
I just bumped into a teddy bear.
It must be part of some activity at the rehabilitation center.
It even gave me a cake.
At that moment, it felt quite healing.
Sister, we're leaving now.
Goodbye, beautiful princess bear.
-Bye.
I didn't expect these few jumps to be so tiring.
Qin Fei?
Hello.
Who are you looking for?
I'm looking for your boss, Ren Siqi!
How did Qin Fei know Xing Zhizhi was there?
Ren Siqi, don't play dumb with me.
You're the only one who's been to my office.
Was it you who turned off the office surveillance?
Yes.
You're quite honest.
You've left me at a loss.
Ren Siqi, how could you do this?
You even learned to steal, huh?
How could you say that? What are you talking about?
Don't interrupt me.
I'm not finished yet.
I'm telling you,
Xing Zhizhi is my patient.
Don't let your personal matters
interfere with my patient's treatment.
This is
Dr. Xing's therapist?
You know her?
Oh, I know her really well.
Please don't get angry, okay?
If there are any issues,
we can solve them step by step, right?
Ren Siqi, I'm telling you,
your actions aren't hurting me;
they're hurting Qin Fei and Xing Zhizhi.
Was Qin Fei discovered?
No, she wasn't.
Then it's no big deal.
What do you mean by "no big deal"?
Just because nothing has happened doesn't mean it's fine.
I really can't stand you anymore, Ren Siqi.
You have no sense of boundaries at all.
You have no bottom line.
You were like this when we were dating,
like this in our marriage,
and now that we're about to get divorced,
you still haven't changed!
Right, we're about to get divorced.
What is there for me to change?
Fine.
I had the lawyer revise the divorce agreement.
Just wait for the email.
I won't receive it.
I forgot the password.
Let me tell you,
if you dare to give Anji spicy ribs again,
I'll make sure you never see it again in your life.
I'm taking it for a check-up next month.
If there's anything wrong,
just you wait.
Anji loves spicy ribs.
I boiled them seven times.
I tasted them, and they weren't salty at all.
I don't believe your nonsense!
Still working, huh?
So this is the one you've been telling us about,
your childhood sweetheart
and later the supporting,
gentle, virtuous wife,
Mrs. Ren?
Alright, don't tell anyone.
Get off work early. Goodbye.
I'm leaving.
I talked to Ge Wu again today.
The treatment is already halfway through.
Starting tomorrow,
the medication dosage will be increased again.
It will be another adjustment process.
But as long as I have something to look forward to,
the days won't be too hard to endure.
I really want to eat the sweet and sour pork from Yang's Restaurant.
I also miss my family and friends,
and Qin Fei.
She's waiting for you.
Qin Xiaofei seems cold and fickle,
but she is actually very soft-hearted and values relationships deeply.
She likes to lie.
She said she loves money a lot,
but actually, she can abandon everything she has
to start over to pursue her dream.
-Big liar.
-Take a breath.
Look, I've only made these few major categories.
[Stage Design Plan for Zhongkun Dance Troupe Tour]
And what do you think of this stage?
I think this part
can be bigger.
[Must-Review Short Questions for College Entrance Exam]
[Hope]
Come on, get someone to take them.
These are the drinks and snacks I bought for everyone.
[Hope]
Pass them around, pass them around.
-Thank you, Boss.
Hello.
I need a car for five o'clock tomorrow morning.
There are 12 of us.
To Chailiang Grand Theater.
Okay, thank you. See you tomorrow then.
-300.
-100.
-250.
-150.
-250, 250.
-Only 150. I...
-250.
Are you guys playing drinking games or discussing the budget?
Qin Fei, 150 thousand is really enough.
Let's not spend
unnecessary money, okay?
Real flower petals for the fairy flower scattering?
Let's switch to paper ones.
Real flower petals look beautiful; we can't save money on that.
Okay. So this one.
Each point here is a drone?
Count how many there are.
This won't work; it's too expensive.
The designer has already been hired. It's a must.
Qin Fei.
Ren Siqi.
This is the last performance.
We must leave a deep impression
so that the audience can feel the lingering effect
even after they get home.
And the promotion. The promotion!
Can we not cut back on that?
Sure. Then why don't you just sell?
Who would buy you?
Qin Fei, I can agree,
but the money really won't allow it.
If that's the case, I'll have to call for backup.
Dr. Ge Wu should help me, right?
I told her.
We insiders should know that.
Add another 50,000. 200,000 at most.
Deal.
Thank you.
The original plan was 200,000.
How about we negotiate a bit more?
-How about 180 thousand?
-No.
No, we've already made a deal.
Anji,
has Mommy been late again?
Mommy is never on time, right?
Do you think Mommy is bad?
Is she doing it on purpose?
Who are you calling bad?
Anji, come here.
Come here.
Oh, right. Well...
I've given you the divorce agreement for a long time.
It's not that simple.
The company is currently under a betting agreement.
As the boss, I have to
carefully review every contract.
Carefully review?
I'm not asking for shares of Xingyi.
You're unkind to me, but I can't be unkind to you.
Who are you calling unkind?
I'm unkind, I'm unkind.
We're about to get divorced.
I'm not the type to take advantage.
I will give you what you're entitled to.
When?
Are you that eager?
I'm dead eager.
Alright, I'll push the legal team, okay?
Ren Siqi...
Don't you want to get divorced?
I think you're the one who doesn't want to get divorced.
I'll give you everything you're entitled to.
But I found Anji.
You can't take it away.
That's final.
Anji, let's go!
[Hamilton Anxiety Scale]
This is the treatment situation over the past month
based on the plan
[Hamilton Anxiety Scale]
that Director Li adjusted from last time.
After increasing the medication dosage for half a month,
your condition has shown significant improvement.
In the last two weeks,
your condition has become increasingly stable.
Xiaojia hasn't appeared again, right?
Not even once.
Do you still think about things from the past?
Occasionally.
But I feel my emotions have settled down a lot,
and I feel much more relaxed.
All your indicators are normal.
Your overall condition
is in line with expectations.
Your recent condition
looks quite stable.
I think you can return to a normal life now.
Is that so? That's good.
What's wrong, Xing Zhizhi?
It seems that
you are not happy.
No, not at all.
My emotions and condition
are much better than before.
And I haven't seen Xiaojia again.
But I still feel like
something is a bit different.
Tell me more specifically.
I don't know, I don't know.
Xing Zhizhi,
I think you can try to relax a bit first,
return to your previous life,
and interact with people you're familiar with and close to,
like Qin Fei,
your family,
and friends.
As for the follow-up medication dosage,
we will adjust it
based on Director Li's examination.
Regarding the issue you mentioned,
give yourself some time.
Let's observe together slowly.
[Huhai Hexi Hospital]
Meilan,
how long has it been?
Only 30 seconds,
and there are already ten pieces.
Isn't our best record in thoracic surgery
30 pieces in one and a half minutes?
That was set
back when Xing was at his peak.
Look at Dr. Xing.
It seems like he's going to break the record.
Should we
increase the difficulty a bit?
Let me tell you something really funny.
Once, I was arranging a surgery,
and a patient's family member
came to me
and said, "Doctor, do you have any antibiotics
that don't kill bacteria?"
What does that mean?
Right? I was really puzzled at the time too.
So I said,
"What do you mean by that?"
He replied,
"Doctor, I know this request
might be a bit difficult,
but my mom
believes in Buddhism,
and she doesn't want to kill."
Not bad, Xing!
So steady!
You're not even laughing at something this funny.
You are amazing!
The last two pieces.
81 seconds.
Done.
How long did it take?
86 seconds.
Dr. Xing broke his own record.
That's incredible!
Well done, Xing! That's impressive.
Dr. Xing,
let's take a picture together.
Dr. Xing.
[Qin Xiaofei]
Xing!
You truly haven't lost your touch!
Are you preparing to spread your wings
and return to thoracic surgery?
My vacation isn't over yet.
I'm just back to help Ms. Ge
organize some surgical materials.
Your vacation isn't over,
and you have broken the record.
Even with us telling such a funny joke,
it didn't affect you at all.
Have you turned into a robot?
I seriously doubt
whether you've been getting treatment these past few months
or if you've been on a training program.
Jealous?
You can also go on the "training program".
What a cold joke.
But anyway,
you've made progress,
and I have too.
See?
The youngest associate chief physician.
Have you made a breakthrough on your project?
Come on, take a look.
[China Foreign Medical Treatment]
How is it?
[5. Prognosis of Ground-Glass Nodule Type Lung Cancer]
[6. Management of Multiple Pulmonary Ground-Glass Nodules]
How is it?
[5. Prognosis of Ground-Glass Nodule Type Lung Cancer]
The data looks good.
The experimental setup is also quite inspiring.
It's indeed impressive.
Who asked you about this?
Look here.
[Finally, I would like to thank my girlfriend, Coffee, for her enduring support]
How about I propose to Coffee with this?
You're going to propose to Coffee?
If I keep delaying getting married,
my parents will come over from my hometown.
So,
for the lifelong happiness of your brother,
you need to do me a favor.
[0° Bar]
Are you going to propose to Coffee here?
Yes, you have no idea
how envious Coffee was
when you confessed to Qin Fei.
She even complained that I wasn't romantic enough.
But you know,
proposing is something
you do only once in a lifetime.
The key is to cater to her tastes.
Coffee likes it,
so I'll recreate the scenario for her.
How does it look?
Do you feel a sense of déjà vu?
♫Amid all the shadows, you're the only one I see♫
♫I never told you♫
♫I've never been so firm♫
♫You're the one♫
♫Longing for you to become the air I breathe♫
♫Thinking of you might give me the courage♫
♫To softly say that I miss you♫
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
Oh ,right.
How about you
teach me this song? You sing it well.
I'd like to learn it.
♫The silence of night, the breath of rain♫
♫They became pleasant because of you♫
[0° Bar]
♫I couldn't say anything♫
What's wrong?
Your expression isn't right.
Do you know what's on your face right now?
It's a big, bold indifference.
Do you understand?
Although indifference is also a kind of feeling,
it's definitely not the kind of feeling I have for Coffee.
Can you show more feelings, please?
[0° Bar]
My emotions and condition
are much better than before.
And I haven't seen Xiaojia again.
But I still feel like
something is a bit different.
What did Director Li say?
He suggested I increase the medication dosage.
But that could have side effects,
like slowed reactions
or emotional flatness.
You're a doctor yourself.
You know what risks mean.
I promised Qin Fei
that I would return to her side as soon as possible.
[0° Bar]
[Qin Xiaofei]
[Decline] [Answer]
[0° Bar]
[Qin Xiaofei]
[Decline] [Answer]
[0° Bar]
The number you've dialed is currently unavailable.
What's going on?
He just told me it was today.
Why isn't he answering the phone?
Fei, are you done?
There's a bunch of things that need your confirmation.
I'll be right there.
Fei, this is the visual effect of the laser show
added for tonight's closing performance.
Take a look.
If there aren't any issues,
I'll arrange it now.
Coffee.
If Xing Zhizhi has already
left the rehabilitation center,
why hasn't he contacted me?
Dr. Xing has been discharged?
Hasn't Yu Zhecheng told you?
No, he hasn't.
Fei, do I look like someone
who has time to date right now?
Also, ever since I got promoted,
Yu Zhecheng and I went from meeting every week
to basically dating online.
However, he seems to be
acting a bit mysterious lately.
When I just video-called him,
he seemed to be at the bar where Xing Zhizhi
confessed to you.
He didn't admit it.
I saw through it right away.
Plus,
there was music playing at that time.
I got it.
Dr. Xing isn't contacting you
because he wants to give you a surprise.
A surprise?
Building anticipation.
It must be that way.
I was wondering why that music sounds so familiar.
It's the song Dr. Xing sang
when he confessed to you.
He's still so romantic.
It must be that way.
And I'm pretty sure
it'll be after tonight's closing performance.
[Qin Xiaofei]
[Decline] [Answer]
I've been reading a lot of love stories lately.
There was a man
who planted trees for a girl for 20 years.
He also saved all the letters they wrote to each other
when they were kids.
When they got married,
he brought them all out. It was so romantic.
If my illness can't be cured,
♫Star in your eyes♫
will you...
♫And I feel so blue♫
No.
♫The wind of missing is blowing towards me♫
But that doesn't mean I won't be angry with you.
You told me before
that if something goes wrong,
♫Suddenly going up, suddenly going down♫
we should solve it together
and trust each other.
♫Suddenly going up, suddenly going down♫
And now?
♫Suddenly at the end of my sight♫
When you had a problem,
you ran away
♫Suddenly at the end of my sight♫
and left me alone.
♫Light is glimmering♫
And what about you?
What would your role be
♫Light is glimmering♫
in a family drama?
♫Into my dream, my love♫
Anyway, I will protect you.
I'd believe everything you say.
♫Stay with me, my love♫
So please don't lie to me, okay?
I will never hurt you.
♫Stay with me, my love♫
♫For one more time, one more second♫
I will never hurt you.
Never.
♫For one more time, one more second♫
♫Stay in your eyes♫
[Qin Xiaofei]
[Decline] [Answer]
♫Stay in your eyes♫
[Qin Xiaofei]
♫Till the last day of my life♫
[Decline] [Answer]
[Qin Xiaofei]
♫Till the last day of my life♫
♫Stay with me one more♫
Propose already! You're killing me!
♫Every moment to eternity, I keep it for you♫
Even Luo Xiaoxiao has surpassed me.
When will I finally get my proposal?
♫Every moment to eternity, I keep it for you♫
Just wait a bit longer.
Wait until I'm fully recovered.
♫Every moment to eternity, I keep it for you♫
Pinky swear.
Propose when you're recovered.
A stamp.
♫Into my dream, my love♫
♫Stay with me, my love♫
♫For one more time, one more second♫
♫Stay in your eyes♫
♫Till the last day of my life♫
♫Stay with me one more♫
♫Every moment to eternity, I keep it for you♫
[Qin Xiaofei]
♫Make my heart beat faster♫
[The other party has cancelled]
Xing Zhizhi,
today is our dance troupe's closing performance.
Why haven't you arrived yet?
Next, let's welcome
the much-anticipated Zhongkun Dance Troupe
[Hope]
to present their new dance, "Hope".
A round of applause, please!
[Hope]
He's still not here yet?
Who said I'm waiting for someone?
Keep being stubborn.
Don't worry.
His not contacting you must be because
he's preparing a big surprise for you.
Take a look at me first.
How do I look in this outfit?
You look nice, very beautiful.
When I'm on the stage as a guest later,
are you sure you don't want me to mention your contributions?
No need to mention me.
Just mention the girls for me.
Are you preparing to be a behind-the-scenes hero?
Isn't it good to be a behind-the-scenes hero?
I really enjoy my current life.
I also really like my job.
Enjoying your current life?
That means you really like someone, doesn't it?
[Hope]
Thank you. A big thank you to the dancers
of Zhongkun Dance Troupe
for their wonderful performance.
[Hope]
As this is the closing night,
let's welcome
[Hope]
tonight's mystery guest!
Hello, Ms. Luo Xiaoxiao.
[Hope]
Welcome!
You're really dressed up today.
[Hope]
[Danger! electric shock]
You're really dressed up today.
You look stunning.
[Danger! electric shock]
First, please say hello
to all our friends here with us.
[Danger! electric shock]
Thank you.
Hello everyone, I'm actress Luo Xiaoxiao.
I'm very happy to have received the invitation
from Zhongkun Dance Troupe today.
Xiaofei, congratulations.
You're not going to blame me for coming too late, are you?
How could I not blame you?
You finally came back.
You didn't answer your phone after the treatment ended
and didn't even let me know.
Say something.
[Hope]
You arrived early?
Congratulations.
Congratulations on your dance troupe's successful performance.
Tacky! So tacky.
Zhecheng said that a sense of ceremony doesn't need to be innovative;
it just needs to cater to preferences.
I think you'll like it.
What else?
Xiaoxiao and Coffee said you would give me a surprise.
Is there more?
Qin Fei,
go home with me.
I want to take you to meet my parents.
Are you serious?
[Moga Hair Salon]
Fei,
I rarely get a day off.
You really don't know how lucky you are.
Didn't I bring you here to enjoy yourself?
Fine.
I'll cover the cost of the hairstyle you get today.
Okay!
Help me choose a style.
I haven't done my hair in over a month.
What style should I go for?
I think highlights would be nice.
And didn't you always want
to try a reddish-brown color before?
But I'm going to meet my boyfriend's parents. Highlights won't be appropriate.
Really?
You're finally going to meet your in-laws-to-be?
Congratulations!
Well...
what about long, straight black hair?
I think elders prefer that style.
But I feel like long, straight black hair
doesn't really suit my style.
I want something
that makes me look elegant
but still keeps my personality,
and that also shows
I have an artistic vibe—
a style that reflects both
my gentleness and my elegance.
No problem, ma'am.
Look,
our salon currently offers styling services
specifically designed for meeting parents, interviews,
matchmaking, and other occasions.
For only 3,888,
we guarantee you'll look brand new.
Why don't we give it a try?
Let's try it.
Then I want one too.
I want a look that can help me
dominate negotiations—a powerful woman's style.
It has to be powerful.
-Of course.
-Sir.
I'll take one of those
-3,888 services.
-Okay.
Tomorrow my son is bringing his girlfriend home.
I want a hairstyle that is serious
yet gentle and can help me
bond with younger people.
Is that possible?
No problem.
Let me go and get prepared.
[Moga Hair Salon]
Doesn't it look brand new?
I'll go get the bill ready.
Fei!
[Crispier than chips]
Here.
Congratulations to your triumphant return.
[Crispier than chips]
Thank you.
What's next?
Are you going back to the hospital?
After the vacation ends.
So,
what about you and Qin Fei?
Fill me in so I can help you out.
I plan to take Qin Fei home
to meet my parents this weekend.
Good for you.
That's pretty efficient.
Does that mean
we'll be drinking at your wedding soon?
We will definitely be very happy.
You...
Wait, wait.
We will definitely be very happy?
You're so programmed,
like a robot.
Are you putting on an act in front of me?
How am I putting on an act?
What do you mean?
Did you and Qin Fei
have a fight?
No, we didn't.
Why do you ask?
I just feel like something's off with you. It's...
[Qin Xiaofei]
[Decline] [Answer]
I just feel like something's off with you. It's...
[Qin Xiaofei]
Hello?
Xing Zhizhi, I'm doomed!
I can't go meet your parents.
What happened?
Xing Zhizhi...
I have to call the police.
That stylist must have a grudge against me.
I spent 3,888
and got this look!
This is simply fraud!
Look at me.
I look terrible, don't I?
Not at all.
I don't think you look terrible.
It's just...
a bit special.
You think I look especially terrible!
What should I do now?
My image is ruined.
How can I meet your parents like this?
How about we postpone it
for a few days? Is that okay?
Don't be angry.
I think it's quite cute.
Besides, my parents are meeting you as a person,
not your hairstyle.
But my hairstyle
is also a part of who I am,
and it's very important.
Their first impression of me
can't be of my hair
looking like a Lhasa Apso, can it?
Trust me,
it really doesn't matter.
Let's go tomorrow, okay?
But...
Xiaofei,
listen to me.
This is the first time I'm bringing a girlfriend home for a meal.
It's because
I'm sure that you are the one.
It has nothing to do with your hairstyle.
But this hairstyle really is ugly.
I'll help you figure something out.
Is this the solution you came up with?
Wearing a hat when I meet your parents
for the first time feels too informal, doesn't it?
I think it's fine.
Don't overthink it.
They won't care about that.
It's my first time meeting them.
What if they don't like me?
How come you're not nervous at all?
Is there a need to be nervous?
Why...
It's you!
It's you?