[A Beautiful Lie]
[17 years ago]
Dear friends and family,
thank you so much
for attending the wedding of Lu Dawei and me.
Dawei and I
each had our own journeys
in the first half of our lives.
Because of fate,
we are united as a family
for the rest of our lives.
I am deeply grateful to my husband,
Lu Dawei,
for giving me
and my daughter, Xiaofei,
a complete family.
From today onward,
you
are Xiaofei's father,
and Xiaofei is your daughter.
Thank you.
Xiaofei. Xiaofei?
She was just sitting there a moment ago.
Xiaofei?
[Episode 8]
[Some relationships, if left to go with the flow, may gradually fade away over time]
Can you do it or not?
Does it still hurt?
It's alright.
It doesn't look serious to me.
Do you still need to go to the hospital?
No need.
This little injury is nothing.
I'll just keep applying the ice. That's all.
Alright, alright.
You do it yourself.
By the way, let's talk about your thing.
Why do you insist on seeing Qin Fei?
No particular reason.
I just find her interesting.
Mei said
you two are old acquaintances.
How about helping me set up a dinner with her?
I'm afraid that if I just reach out to her
out of the blue,
it'll scare her.
Scare her?
It'd be lucky if she doesn't scare you.
She's like a hedgehog—
crazy and unpredictable.
If you say something wrong and make her angry,
all her spikes will stand up
and hurt everyone in her way.
What do you mean?
Do you have some kind of issue with her?
There was a small misunderstanding before,
but it's all in the past now.
If there's any issue,
it's more that she thinks I'm the problem.
Anyway, getting involved with her won't do you any good.
Why do you insist on getting to know her?
There's no reason.
I'd rather you two didn't know each other.
Alright. I'll think of another way.
Well, um...
Where are you going?
I'm leaving.
Where to?
Home.
Well...
Aren't we taking a vacation in a few days?
Do you want to go out and have some fun?
We can go abroad for a few months.
Go by yourself.
I want to do something I want during the vacation.
How about this?
Take me to the hospital now,
okay?
Wait, where are you going?
I'm not leaving.
I'm getting you a new ice pack.
That one isn't cold anymore.
[A Happy Family]
Hey.
Drinking when you're unhappy
will only make you feel worse.
Xing Zhizhi,
just because I'm talking to you now
doesn't mean I've forgiven you
for taking advantage of the situation this morning to ask for my WeChat.
Understand?
If you don't mind, I'll sit here.
Dr. Xing.
Are you drinking this beer because you're happy or unhappy?
The older you get,
the fewer happy moments there are.
Alright.
Just for that,
let's have a toast.
When did you start growing up?
Me?
It was around elementary school, I guess.
At that time,
I met a really good friend
who I really liked and trusted.
But she didn't keep the promise between us
and left without saying goodbye.
What a coincidence.
That friend of yours who didn't keep her promise
also grew up around that time.
Her father passed away.
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't know.
There's nothing to be sorry about.
It's been so long already.
It doesn't matter anymore.
By the way, Xing Zhizhi.
There's something I want to talk to you about.
Can we postpone Xixi's counseling
for a bit?
Why?
Didn't Xixi say she didn't want to go?
I've grown up and I'm not happy.
But if there's a chance,
I want Xixi to be a child a little longer.
Even if it's just for one day,
I'd like her to be willful and happy.
I happen to be going to the mall tomorrow.
I want to take Xixi with me
to buy her some things she likes,
like pretty clothes
or drawing supplies.
I want to do everything
that can make her happy.
Sounds good.
I'm off tomorrow,
so I'll go with you.
Are you serious, Xing Zhizhi?
I should warn you, I tend to attract trouble.
If you go out with me
and anything happens,
I won't take responsibility.
It's fine. I'm happy to.
Whatever.
Oh, Chubby,
don't wait for me for dinner tomorrow night.
I need to go back to my place.
Alright.
That man is so handsome.
So handsome.
Which color do you like?
That pink one.
The pink one?
Pink really suits you.
Let me put it on you.
It looks great.
Let me try this one.
It looks good on you too.
Xixi,
can you check for me
if those two people behind me are looking at me?
Slowly, Xixi. Slowly.
Ms. Qin Fei, I think you're overthinking it.
They don't seem...
to be looking at you.
Then what are they looking at?
He's really handsome.
[ZIHAN]
He looks so tall.
Check out, please.
Okay, ma'am.
Ma'am,
these three hats cost a total of 360 yuan.
Here.
Alright, I got it.
He's really handsome.
Hello, sir,
may I help you?
No.
Are we done now?
Yes.
Thank you.
Hold this for me.
Put this in the bag, okay?
Excuse me, please.
Thank you.
Let me do it.
Let me. Let me.
I just saw you bought three hats.
Is one of them for me?
Stop being so narcissistic.
I like both of them.
I want to wear them interchangeably.
Alright.
Whatever you say.
It's your money anyway.
Let me see.
This one seems to suit you pretty well.
It's yours now.
It does suit me.
Xixi,
do you like these sneakers?
No, I don't. Let's go.
Xiaofei's mom, the ribs are ready.
The ribs are ready?
They are ready.
Alright, ribs.
Be careful not to burn yourself.
Okay, okay. I got it.
The ribs are pretty good today.
How many dishes have you prepared?
Take a guess.
Just tell me.
Eight.
That many?
Good.
Let me take the ribs out,
and I'll marinate them later.
What are you steaming?
I'll pour out this soup.
No!
I need to thicken the sauce.
Put it back.
It's in the way over there.
I'll put it somewhere else.
So annoying.
There are hairy crabs too?
Of course.
Go and season the salad.
Are you ordering me around now?
Gosh.
Fine.
Why are you looking at me? Mind your own business.
Gosh.
If you're happy, just be happy.
No need to pretend you are not.
It's none of your business!
Let me tell you.
Later, clean up the kitchen.
Alright.
Mr. Xing, I want that unicorn.
Okay, I'll get it for you.
here.
This one looks like a pig.
No, it doesn't! Look how pretty it is!
Take a look yourself!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ms. Qin, why did you buy so many things?
I finally got everything I needed.
I haven't been shopping in a long time.
There is stuff for all ages—it's pretty comprehensive.
You're quite curious.
Xixi, are you happy today?
Yes, I am.
I ordered this for you.
I don't usually drink milk tea.
It's zero sugar, zero fat, and zero calories;
it's their specialty.
You can only drink this.
[Cinema]
I'm sorry.
I had an unexpected surgery this afternoon.
Something came up at the hospital.
I might not be able to make it.
Sorry, Coffee.
[I won't be able to go out for dinner tonight. A patient came in unexpectedly]
[Sorry, Coffee. A patient came to me, so I'll be late]
Sorry, Coffee.
[I won't be able to go out for dinner tonight. A patient came in unexpectedly]
Yu Zhecheng, you big flake!
You deserve to be single.
Why?
Coffee?
You... you didn't go in?
Answer me first.
Why do you deserve to be single?
I'm too busy with work.
I don't have time for a girlfriend.
I'll keep canceling our dates.
Again
and again.
If I keep being this busy as a doctor,
she'll eventually dump me.
Well, your girlfriend is different from me.
I want to find a boyfriend who's a doctor.
Even though he's busy,
just thinking about
how doctors are busy saving lives
makes me feel it's pretty noble.
Coffee, do you...
really think so?
Yes.
Yu Zhecheng,
before you resign,
could you introduce me to a responsible
and energetic doctor at your hospital
who is dedicated to saving lives?
I've bought tickets for five movies.
I've bought double tickets
for the next three movies today.
I can go
and see any of them with him.
Here, take this.
No, no, no. I grabbed the wrong one. It's not for today.
This one.
What are you waiting for?
I won't accept anyone who's not a doctor.
Then you might as well stop looking.
Isn't there one right in front of you?
Your boyfriend
will cover the cost.
Let's go, my boyfriend.
The next movie is about to start.
[Preparation Room of Rescue Operation]
Director Xiao,
the artist from our company
[Preparation Room of Rescue Operation]
that I previously mentioned,
Qin Fei,
[Preparation Room of Rescue Operation]
has a great sense of variety shows.
She is also athletic
and has even volunteered.
I think she's very suitable for our show,
"Rescue Operation."
She's a great fit.
So you still want her on our show?
Yes.
As you know,
our show is a very positive program,
so we have high standards for the image of our guests.
I think I've made myself very clear.
Once the final list is confirmed by the station,
I'll let you know.
Okay.
[Rescue Operation: Let's Take on the Challenge]
[Rescue Operation: In Preparation]
What's wrong with us?
Aren't we quite positive?
[Rescue Operation: In Preparation]
Mr. Ren, there's new public sentiment.
There's a guest list for "Rescue Operation"
[Rescue Operation: In Preparation]
released on Trending Search,
and Fei's name is not on it.
[Rescue Operation: In Preparation]
Is... is this real?
[Let's See If Your Favorite Star Is on It]
[The Guest List of the Popular Variety Show, Rescue Operation, Has Been Revealed]
Is... is this real?
[Let's See If Your Favorite Star Is on It]
[Actress Jin Na, A Former Athlete And Now An Actress Who's Professional In Inspirational Roles]
[The Girl Next Door, Actress Jin Weiwei, Who Can Be Both Cool and Sweet]
It's about what I heard.
Alright. We came for nothing. The guests were decided long ago.
Let me see the comments.
[Comments]
Okay, turn it off.
[Xingyi Work-related]
Isn't this the positive energy we're looking for?
Let's go.
Watch the movie now.
You can take your time watching me later.
Three tickets are quite expensive.
Is it the hospital?
You should answer it.
[Advertisement]
[Decline] [Answer]
[Demon Lord Mr. Ren]
Hello, Mr. Ren, I'm watching a movie.
Alright, stop watching.
Something's happened with Fei.
Come back now.
Okay, I'll head back right away.
What happened?
Something happened with Fei.
I need to get back quickly.
I'll give you a ride.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Silly.
You really like this doll?
Well, it's yours now.
Mine?
Why?
Don't tell me, let me guess.
It must be because
I'm Xixi's idea of a unicorn—
pure and dreamy.
Most importantly,
I look just as good as it does.
Ms. Qin, you're not a white horse.
You're a hedgehog princess.
Mr. Xing is the real Prince Charming.
Him?
Prince Charming?
Wait a minute.
If he's Prince Charming,
why did you give this to me?
A prince should be with a princess.
Come on, Ms. Qin.
Why haven't you confessed to him yet?
Little rascal, you're making less and less sense.
Don't ask just any questions.
So do you love him or not?
How old are you?
Do you even know what love is?
Love is liking someone
and wanting to see him every day.
So do you like this?
Yes.
Do you love it?
But toys aren't people.
It's the same.
Liking isn't loving, and loving isn't just liking.
Overall, both of them are quite complicated
and require a lot of time and energy.
Even if I had the intention,
I don't have the energy to think about these things right now.
So do you not love me anymore?
I love you.
I will always love you.
But this love isn't the same
as what you just mentioned.
Oh, right.
You're just a child.
Don't spend your days pondering these things.
I need to talk to you about something serious.
We didn't go to
Dr. Ge Wu's today, so tomorrow…
I'm not listening!
You get angry too easily, Xixi.
Alright.
I'll head out then.
I'll come back later to keep you company, okay?
Silly Xixi.
I'm leaving.
[Now Mr. Ren is planning to use this photo for your publicity]
[Fei, you guys were photographed]
Xing Zhizhi!
Can I borrow your car?
Where's the key?
It's... in my pocket.
Sorry about that.
I'll take the car now. Thanks.
Is everything alright?
Steamed mandarin fish.
We'll start eating once Xiaofei gets back.
Is it 7 o'clock?
Let me check.
It's 7:02.
There might be a bit of traffic.
[1 message from 1 contact]
[WeChat]
Stop playing with your phone and get ready to eat.
Something urgent happened, so I won't be coming.
Let's eat.
We are not waiting for my sister anymore?
No, we're not! Eat up!
But... my sister...
Eat!
[Princess Qin]
[Decline] [Answer]
It's not right, you know.
You know Fei's temper.
If she sees it later...
We'll deal with that when the time comes.
First, let's make the photo...
Don't look at me. Look here.
Photoshop Fei's face and make it clear.
With sunglasses on her face, it's hard to tell that's her.
[Fei]
[Decline] [Answer]
Alright. Focus on your work.
Maybe I should just forget about it.
If Fei finds out I'm being a traitor,
she'll kill me.
You're usually so close with Fei
that it feels like you're one person,
but you're afraid she'll kill you.
Don't you feel wronged on her behalf?
I'm not...
Not what? Hurry up.
Once it's photoshopped,
we'll send it out
with the press release together.
We need everyone to know that our Qin Fei
isn't the type to use charity for show.
Thanks, but I don't need it.
She said thanks, but she doesn't need it.
Just say what you want to say.
Don't hold it in and make yourself sick.
Qin Fei,
can you tell me
what you're thinking?
I just don't understand.
A photo taken casually by a passerby
was discovered by the company,
and we bought it for your promotion,
but you refused and aren't happy about it.
You even directly closed our laptop.
What were you thinking?
Is this what you like?
When others criticize you,
you feel happy and excited, right?
You told me to speak my mind.
I did tell you to speak your mind,
but I didn't tell you to insult me indirectly, did I?
Ren Siqi,
I know you want me to turn things around. I get it.
But shouldn't we think about others too?
We can't just push Xing Zhizhi into a trap ahead
when we know it's there.
And there's Xixi.
She's there for rehabilitation.
If you expose her in the press,
won't that be inappropriate?
Think rationally and answer calmly.
You and I
can't take this responsibility.
But Qin Fei,
you are an artist,
not a volunteer.
You're concerned about Dr. Xing
and Xixi,
but what about yourself?
What about your career and work?
Do you still want them?
Yes.
But not through this.
You don't have to step back.
I just want to apologize to you.
I really should apologize to you.
Regarding this matter, I've caused you
a lot of trouble from the beginning.
We've known each other for quite a few years now.
Besides our colleague relationship,
we could say that we're each other's friends, right?
So now,
as a friend, I want to ask you
to help me.
You've put it that way,
so what else can I say?
Thanks.
I'll pay for the photo from my account.
Bye.
Wait a minute.
Let me say one more thing.
You and this Dr. Xing...
what's your
relationship?
Just friends.
It doesn't seem like that to me.
This Dr. Xing... Well,
I think he's quite handsome.
You've been protecting him all along.
Do you maybe have a bit of a crush on him?
Come on, Ren Siqi,
can you not think about this so superficially?
What do you mean by that? How old are we?
The reason I'm acting like this
is that he's a doctor.
I believe he has value and contributes to our society.
If I get him involved in this,
I'd be worried that heaven might punish me by shortening my life.
[WeChat]
[Mom]
[Something urgent happened, so I won't be coming]
[I'm sorry]
You're back.
How was it? Is everything okay?
Everything is fine.
You haven't eaten yet, have you?
Let me heat up the dinner for you.
Eat up.
What about Xixi? How is she doing?
She's asleep.
During dinner,
I tried to test the waters.
She still doesn't want to go.
But Xixi's counseling
can't be delayed for too long, right?
Right, theoretically.
But I actually think
your approach
is worth keeping on trying.
Really?
Slow and steady wins the race.
Did Gu Wu say not to rush it
and put too much pressure on her?
Let her do things that make her happy.
That's what I'm good at.
With your approval,
I'll take Xixi, ignoring everything else,
and just focus on having fun.
Eat up.
Did your mom come to Huhai?
You were planning to go home tonight, weren't you?
How did you know?
Don't tell me you can read fortunes.
I guessed it based on the things you bought.
Did something hold you up?
Kinda.
No, I'm just going with the flow.
Going with the flow.
Some relationships, if left to go with the flow,
may gradually fade away over time.
Dr. Xing,
I'm a pretty clueless person.
Can you just say what's on your mind?
Why so serious?
I just feel that
wanting to go with the flow
means you have expectations
but are afraid your efforts will be in vain,
so you said you're just going with the flow.
In fact,
it's a form of escapism.
Are you trying to persuade me?
No, I'm just concerned about you.
I didn't expect our Dr. Xing to have the potential
to be the main character in a romantic drama.
Should I introduce you to acting?
If I weren't acting,
would you dare to respond to me?
I don't have the luck to be the main character,
nor am I interested.
[Pain Caused by Psychological Factors]
Organic injury?
electromagnetic wave therapy?
[Can psychological factors really cause pain?]
System desensitization?
What do all these mean?
There isn't a single one I can understand.
What exactly is wrong with Xixi?
Xixi said she really likes marathons.
Before, she even made a pact with her dad
to participate
in the city's marathon together when she grows up.
But now...
So it's because she loves it too much
that she's afraid?
This is also a form of allergy?
[Mr. Ge]
Hello, Mr. Ge,
this is Qin Fei.
I'm sorry to bother you so late.
I'd like to ask you some things about Xixi.
What is psychological allergy?
And what is systematic desensitization?
I think it might be very helpful for Xixi.
The fried eggs are ready.
Xixi.
You should eat it fully cooked.
Qin Fei,
do you prefer your fried eggs
fully cooked or runny?
Me? I don't mind.
You're all about "I don't mind," or "going with the flow."
Come on.
What are you mumbling about?
Nothing.
About what I said last night,
I was just kidding.
Don't take it to heart.
What?
Nothing. Let's eat.
If anyone can book the venue
at Huhai Dance Center,
please contact me ASAP.
Thank you.
I forwarded this right away.
It's really hard to book the venue there.
Ms. Qin,
are we going to the park for a picnic today?
Yes, the picnic.
I remember.
Hello, Qin Fei,
this is Liu Yanze.
I checked for you,
and there's a day available.
You can go check it out anytime.
That's great, Captain Liu.
I'm available anytime.
Where are you? Where are we meeting?
Liu Yanze?
When did you add Liu Yanze on WeChat?
I added him when we were in Linkang County.
Xixi, I'm sorry.
I have something come up today,
so I can't go camping with you.
Ask Mr. Xing to go with you.
I'm sorry.
I'll make it up to you later.
It's okay, I'll go with you.
This way, Ms. Qin.
This is our theater,
which can accommodate four hundred audience members.
The rental fee is this amount.
So expensive?
Fei, are you spending so much money
to rent this venue to make a comeback?
Keep your voice down.
You have no idea how hard it is to book this venue.
It's already good enough that we can sort it out with money.
Ms. Qin, you know the business.
You're a friend of Captain Liu,
so that makes you my friend too.
I've known Captain Liu for many years.
When there was a fire here before,
Captain Liu saved many people.
So for that reason,
we'll rent this venue to you today, no matter what.
Really?
However, regarding the rental fee for this venue,
our company needs to...
That's fine.
Okay.
Then take a look around, and I'll prepare the contract.
Okay. Thank you.
Where are we going to get so much money?
You've already lost so much money.
With no job and no income,
how are you going to get so much money?
Do you have to be so specific?
Xixi.
How's your painting? Let me take a look.
Here.
Here, have some water first.
Xixi,
isn't this lying?
Ms. Qin Fei is clearly not here.
Why is she in the painting?
Just this once, please.
Ms. Qin used to be around every time.
Is everything in your painting real?
If you don't believe me, look.
Let me see.
This is Ms. Qin buying food for us in the county town.
[Mid-Autumn Festival Gala]
This is Ms. Qin singing for us
at the Mid-Autumn Festival Gala.
This is when I met Ms. Qin at the hospital
when I first came to Huhai.
And this is Ms. Qin taking me to the supermarket.
Do you like them, Mr. Xing?
I do.
Do you like the paintings or Ms. Qin?
Xixi, I think
you really paint well.
And you have a gift for that.
But I have a question.
Look. You painted this Miss Hedgehog
so beautifully,
but this Prince Charming...
How is this anything like a prince?
You didn't even bother to give him clothes.
It's just too ugly.
Maybe it's because I, like you,
really like Ms. Qin.
That's true.
Xixi,
since you like Miss Hedgehog so much,
why do you refuse to listen to her
and go for rehabilitation?
Because she is too nice.
She surely doesn't understand that some things,
no matter how hard you try, you just can't do well.
Are you talking about rehabilitation?
Xixi,
but I feel like
what you said isn't entirely correct.
Everyone has things they can't achieve,
but we can still try our best.
Ms. Qin Fei also has her difficulties.
She doesn't want everyone to see them,
so she's always smiling.
Why doesn't she want us to see?
Because she's afraid we won't understand.
Alright.
Let's not talk about this anymore.
Xixi,
let's go over there and take a look.
Okay.
Captain Liu,
thank you.
It's nothing.
I'll be going then.
Bye.
Fei, are you still thinking about the venue rental fee?
You spent so much money for a dance.
Who are you going to dance for?
For you.
Come on. Can you stop asking?
Why are you so curious?
Actually, as long as you ask,
Mr. Ren will surely agree.
And this money is yours.
It's just temporarily in the studio account.
How could he possibly refuse to sign?
Ke Feifei,
I found you can be quite persuasive behind the scenes.
Is this your first day knowing Ren Siqi?
He holds grudges.
The photo incident just happened.
Asking him for money right now
won't end well.
It would be tricky.
I just wanted to comfort you.
Here.
It's so beautiful.
I really like it here.
Mr. Xing, thank you for bringing me here.
Next time,
I'll make sure to paint Prince Charming super handsome,
and I'll make Miss Hedgehog just a tiny bit ugly
to make Prince Charming look even better.
How about that?
Xixi,
you should make Miss Hedgehog look good too
so that they'll match, you know?
You admitted it, didn't you?
You also want to be a good match for Ms. Qin.
No, no. That's not what I meant.
I mean
that Miss Hedgehog and Prince Charming should match,
not that I want to match...
I...
This kid...
What's wrong?
Your Qin Fei is in trouble.
What's going on?