You have one new voice message.
First message.
Oh, hi there.
Uh, sorry,
but something… something came up,
and I have to go into the office now.
Uh, I'll have to cancel Reina's sleepover.
I already let your mother know.
Daddy, I don't wanna go home!
I wanna stay with you!
Sorry, sweetheart.
We'll see each other again soon, okay?
So I should be able to reschedule
for next weekend. I can make it then.
Oh, by the way,
someone told me that Kazuko Hosoki
used to have a yakuza boss
for a boyfriend.
Is that true?
I also heard that she spends
a lot of money at host clubs every night
and surrounds herself with young guys
like she's some kind of empress.
Don't talk about things like that
in front of our kid.
Daddy, I don't wanna go home!
Look, Reina, why don't I buy you
that stuffed animal we saw, okay?
Yay! Stuffed animal!
Sorry. I'll be in touch.
I got married
right after my novel came out.
After that, years went by,
and I struggled to release a second one.
Then, when we decided to have a kid,
he started forcing me into taking on
the role of a wife and mother.
One day, while he was drunk,
he said to me, "No one is waiting
for your next novel anymore, you know?"
It basically crushed me.
But then Reina…
That's my daughter.
She'd already learned to read quite a bit.
And I walked in on her
trying to read my book.
She couldn't possibly have understood it
because it's full of kanji,
but she kept going and going,
just reading the hiragana parts
she could catch.
When I saw that,
I told myself to release a second book.
Even if nobody else is,
at least my daughter
will be waiting for it.
That's how I feel.
Minori…
I'm also waiting for it.
I want to read your novel.
Mm. So how did things end up
with Hotta-san?
That man…
He never tried to control me.
He let me do my own thing.
Our relationship was based on respect
for the other person's life.
So you two never fought?
Oh, of course we did.
At one point,
things turned sour between us.
Although… it wasn't a good time
for the country either.
What do you mean?
It was the oil crisis.
Prices skyrocketed,
and our lives changed completely.
The government had to step in.
They ordered businesses
to reduce hours to save electricity,
so the streets ended up empty,
and so did my club.
We were driven to the brink
in a very short time.
I'm so sorry
things have ended up like this.
Here. I know it's not much,
but you can take everyone out
for a nice meal.
Please call us
if you ever need a band again.
Thank you so much. I appreciate you all.
All right. Let's go.
Another slow day today.
Maybe we should close early.
Oh boy.
If things keep going like this,
we'll go out of business.
Whose idea was it
to reduce business hours anyway?
I wonder how long they'll keep this up.
Who knows?
Oh. Hi, Noboru.
What are you doing here alone?
Did he send you here?
Madam,
can I talk to you?
Go ahead and place your bets.
Go ahead. Place your bets.
Go on. Go on. Place your bets, gentlemen.
Place your bets. Place your bets.
Are you ready? Are you ready?
Go ahead and place your bets.
- Place your bets.
- Okay. Done.
All set.
Showdown.
Middle card, three.
Anyone with three, open it.
Open it if you have three.
I'm gonna have to call it.
Today just ain't my day.
Isn't it a bit soon to give up?
If you'd like, I could always spot you.
Not in this economy.
I'll come back soon.
- I also better go.
- Yep.
Yeah, same for me.
- Thank you for the game.
- Yes, thank you.
You know it's bad for business
when the yakuza can't afford to gamble.
My club's doing badly enough.
Are you managing your family all right?
You don't need to worry about it.
I know you're trying to save face,
but if you need it,
I can get you some money.
Living off the money a woman gives you
is exactly how you lose face.
Hey. What if I sell the rights to my club?
Business isn't doing well anyway,
but it should be enough
to get you through for now.
You're the one who got it back for me,
you know.
- If it can be of help to you--
- That's enough.
Hmm.
My business is none of your concern.
Yes, but…
I know you need money
to keep the newer members afloat though.
Let me at least
take care of their allowances.
I'm very sorry.
Thanks.
Call me up anytime.
I hope you know what you've just done.
You little shit.
Now you're gonna find out
what happens when you play with meth.
Please! Have mercy!
My dad's factory went under,
and I needed money!
I'm the only one making money at home.
I had no choice!
You're a disgrace
to the Edogawa-ikka family!
Hey.
Yes, boss.
How'd you get the meth, huh?
Where'd you even get the money for that?
Answer.
Who was it, Noboru?
Who gave you the money?
Thank you for coming.
Mm.
It must be hard to do business
when the streets are empty like this.
Yes, it truly is.
What are you doing here? You didn't call.
I'm closing up.
Do you wanna go grab a drink somewhere?
Noboru has been expelled.
What? Why?
He used the money that you gave him
to start dealing meth.
Oh no.
He told you the young members
were struggling to get by
and asked you for money behind my back,
didn't he?
Yakuza are the kind of people
who'd rather deceive everyone else
before we get deceived.
If someone shows us sympathy,
we take advantage and bleed them dry.
That's just how we are.
That's why I told you
not to get involved in what we do.
I just wanted to help you. That's all.
Because I'm the only person
who can do that.
I never asked for your help.
Don't come around for a while.
FORTUNE-TELLING
MASAYA HOTTA
KAZUKO HOSOKI
Would you like to hear the results?
Yes, please.
You and this man
share excellent compatibility.
You sure about that?
Yes. It's very rare to see.
But having too much compatibility
isn't good either.
When you're in a lucky phase,
you amplify each other,
but the same thing happens
when you're in a bad place.
For you, especially.
You're the type of person
who drags everyone along with you
when you hit a streak of bad luck.
About ten years ago…
you lost someone close to you, didn't you?
Yes, my mother passed away.
I imagine
that since you were little,
you've never been able to sit still.
That's true.
You have more energy inside of you
than most people
ever experience in their lives.
An abundance of energy
that you simply cannot contain.
This is why you've been working so hard
without a break for so long.
You're a single-minded person,
and you stick to your own ideas.
But people have taken advantage of you
when you least expected it,
and you've gone through
many hardships because of that.
Despite that,
you've fallen and gotten back up.
Over and over again.
You've worked hard to get
where you are now, and it's paid off.
How do you…
Uh, how is it
that… that you know so much about me?
My fortune-telling is based on statistics.
Things become clear
through deciphering the records
that have been accumulated over millennia
by my predecessors.
Incredible.
Is there anything else
that you want to ask me?
Yes.
Uh, when will my luck get better?
Right now.
What do you mean?
Your luck will improve
from this moment forward.
The very fact that you passed by me once
but returned again,
well, that proves it.
Right now?
My findings suggest that you might
want to start a new business.
I should start a new business?
You were in what is known
as a "Void Period," a period of bad luck.
You're coming out of it now,
and you have a chance to change
your line of work and try something new.
It's time to make a change around here.
I'm turning this place into a disco.
That's exciting.
We're gonna make it
the number one disco in Tokyo.
- Yes, ma'am.
- All right!
All right, everyone.
We need to replace the flooring first,
so let's start with the tables and chairs.
Let's get everything outside.
- Yes, sir.
- I need everyone to work hard.
Yes, sir.
We'll be very generous with your bonuses.
- Take this.
- I got it.
Hi, we're Disco Manhattan. Here you go.
Please take one.
Hi, we're Disco Manhattan.
Disco Manhattan opening soon!
Here you go. Please take one!
All the equipment
should be set up onstage, please.
Hey, sis!
I got the new flyers ready.
So which one do you think is better?
Disco Manhattan. Here you go.
We're Disco Manhattan.
Please take one. Please?
Disco Manhattan, opening soon!
Please take one.
Hello, ma'am.
Teppei.
Nobody's gonna take a flyer from you
if you keep being polite like that.
We'll show you how it's done.
Oh, wait, but aren't you gonna
get into trouble with him?
He's the one who told us to come.
He wanted to help you out.
- Disco Manhattan is opening soon!
- Hey, guys. Here you go.
- A new disco's opening.
- Opening soon!
Thank you so much! Please, have one.
Disco Manhattan is opening soon!
Here, take a flyer.
Ladies, ladies, ladies, ladies!
Please, at least take one of these!
You can throw it away later!
Ah, wonderful! Thank you!
Cards are bound to break me
But I ain't busted yet
'Cause I've been called a natural lover
By that lady over there
Honey, I'm just a natural gambler
But I try to do my share
Go down gamblin'
Say it when you're runnin' low
You may never have to go, no, no, no…
- Thank you.
- Here you go. 500 yen.
My new business is a huge success.
Just like your prediction said.
You told me my luck would improve,
and you were completely right.
The success of your disco club
is simply the result of your determination
and your hard work.
The only thing I did
was to give you advice
based on ancient divination techniques.
I would love you
to continue giving me advice.
Oh, I brought you a small token of thanks.
I appreciate the offer,
but you've already paid me
for my readings.
Oh, please, take it anyway.
I don't accept anyone's gifts
because that might disrupt
the flow of my divinations.
Oh.
I had no idea
fortune tellers were so ascetic.
You know, I don't think
that I could ever live like that.
You may never have to go, no
Looks like business is good.
It's thanks to Teppei
and the others helping us.
Yes, well,
they just wanted extra pocket money.
Don't be too grateful to them.
Oh! You know what?
A fortune teller told me
that you and I were made for each other,
and that our luck
will keep getting better from now on.
Oh really?
Didn't you say
you didn't believe in all that stuff?
Really? Did I?
So, do you wanna
go for a drink somewhere?
Mm-hmm.
Hotta!
What the hell do you want?
Looks like
you're a real big shot now, huh?
Takiguchi-san,
I wish that… I could say the same for you.
That's 'cause somebody set me up!
Get out of here now!
I don't have anywhere to go.
Hotta!
No!
Help! Somebody help!
No, my love! Hang on! Hang on!
Please don't leave me!
Hotta! My love!
Please stay with me!
Please!
SURGERY IN SESSION
You'll be glad to know
the surgery was a success.
He's going to be okay.
Thank you so much, Doctor.
Well…
looks like
that fortune teller was wrong, huh?
I dunno. You took four bullets,
and you're still alive.
I would say that's pretty lucky.
Oh. Are you all right?
Uh, goddammit.
Being with you
is always exciting.
So I've made a decision.
I'm gonna stick with you forever.
When you're an outlaw,
you never know when you're gonna die.
So…
I won't be able to marry you.
Are you okay with that?
You know
I don't care about things like that.
I would even follow you to hell.
Isn't that kid adorable?
No. Kids are only adorable
when they're in pictures.
What is it?
Wait a second,
you're not blushing, are you?
Thank you both for waiting.
Of course. Shall we go in?
Uh, I dunno.
- I'm not really a picture kind of guy.
- Come on now.
- All right, ma'am. Please sit here.
- Okay.
Sir, if you would. A little closer.
Next time we come here,
we might have a baby with us.
Hmm. I can't hear you.
All right, here we go.
You know,
the two of you would have a cute child.
But there was no next time.
This was the only photo
I ever took with Hotta.
Do you mean that you broke up?
Why?
Didn't you wanna be with him forever?
It's never that simple
between a man and a woman.
I got most of the things I wanted,
except for a child.
Lately, I've been looking forward
to our conversations.
It sort of feels like I'm telling
my daughter about my younger days.
Me? Your daughter?
What? Is that strange for you?
Oh, not at all! Please go on.
You'd better go home for today.
Your daughter must be waiting.
This should be enough.
I've made a lot. Huh?
- Yeah.
- The origami, right?
- Good.
- I'm home.
Welcome home.
I'm sorry, Reina.
Should I make deep-fried prawns
for dinner?
- Yeah.
- Hear that? Deep-fried prawns.
What's that?
This is Shiro.
Daddy bought it for me.
- Yes, he bought it for you. It's Shiro.
- Mm-hmm.
Yay! Yummy big prawns!
You can do it, Mommy!
Careful now, honey. It's dangerous.
- Why are you using chopsticks?
- What? Who cares?
- Use your hand. It's dangerous, okay?
- That's way too scary.
You can do it, Mommy!
The Fire Bamboo Star is coming up next,
which is the "Star of Change."
It says
it's "perfect for starting something new."
Well, then, maybe I should take up
ballroom dancing or something, hmm?
- Sure, why not? Mm-hmm.
- Think I should? Huh?
- Mmm.
Don't forget your veggies.
Mmm!
Here, Shiro.
He can't eat that.
- Eat it, Shiro.
- Shouldn't you eat that?
Okay, I'll eat it.
- Hey!
- That's a good girl! Way to go!
Down came the sun
And dried up all the rain
And the itsy-bitsy spider…
Oh, that's good. Hold on.
- Here. We'll start again, okay?
- Okay.
You should look at the audience.
Okay, let's go.
Itsy-bitsy spider
Went up the water spout
Yeah!
Down came the rain
And washed the spider out
HERE ARE SOME REFERENCE MATERIALS
ON CHIYOKO SHIMAKURA. -KAWATANI
CHIYOKO SHIMAKURA TRICKED INTO
400-MILLION-YEN DEBT BY BOYFRIEND
Chiyoko Shimakura.
One of Japan's most beloved singers.
Her name shines brightly
in the history of Japanese entertainment.
Her voice,
beautiful and crystal-clear
as a bell ringing out,
she captivated the hearts
of her fans throughout the country.
Thank you all very much.
Wonderful job, everyone.
Excuse me.
Shimakura-san!
Excuse me! Excuse me, sorry.
Huh? Sawamura-san, what is it?
You look panicked.
It's the debt collectors!
What?
You'll never get away with this!
If your boyfriend tricked you,
you're still to blame for being gullible!
That's right! Now that he's disappeared,
you're the one to pay!
In 1977, when Chiyoko Shimakura
was at the height of her fame,
she was hit with an unexpected scandal.
Almost there, Shimakura-san!
Oh no!
They're in front of the apartment too!
- Guys, she's coming!
- Duck your head, hurry!
Her boyfriend had tricked her
into endorsing multiple promissory notes.
Pay what you owe!
And then one day, he disappeared,
and she found herself saddled
with a debt of 430 million yen.
One night,
just as Chioyoko Shimakura
was in the throes of hell,
she had a fateful encounter
with Kazuko Hosoki.
Hey.
Hey there.
Are you okay?
Don't do it.
Aren't you…
Chiyoko Shimakura?
I can't believe a star as great as you
could get tricked by a man.
How much longer is your run
at the Koma Theater going for?
Two… two more weeks.
Oh God. Two weeks?
You'll just have to do your best
to try and get through it.
How do you expect me to do that?
I can hardly even sing anymore,
the way things are.
And if I can't sing,
then I don't deserve to live.
I should
just get it over with.
Stop that!
You shouldn't talk about dying
so casually!
Have you got any idea
how many people need you?
Your music keeps them going!
I'm gonna help you with this.
Let me handle it.
What?
I'll help you
so that you can keep performing
and complete your contract.
There's no reason for you
to do that for me.
I mean, we're… we're strangers.
We've only just met.
I don't know about that.
I was in the same position as you
a long time ago.
You and I didn't meet here
just by chance, you know.
This must have been fate.
Please stay back!
I'm Hotta, from Shinjuku.
Starting today,
Chiyoko Shimakura will be under my care.
- What?
- What's going on?
If anyone has anything to say about it,
say it here. Right now.
Well, if that's true…
- Hotta-san.
- Come on, you can't do that to us.
She can't get away with this.
Out of the way, please.
Chiyoko Shimakura will continue her run
of performances here at the Koma Theater,
as she has many fans
who wanna hear her sing.
After the final show,
I'll set up a meeting with you all
to discuss everything.
Excuse us.
You look completely different.
Except that I… I don't feel
confident enough to sing through the show.
What do you mean, Ochiyo?
You know
we're at the point of no return now.
Mm. Yes, but…
Shimakura-san.
Places, please.
This is it. Time for you to shine.
Let's go.
Listen, Ochiyo.
You don't have to worry
about the debt collectors anymore.
Right now, all you have to do
is focus on your singing.
Uh, hey. What about the… the scary dream
I had last night, remember?
Yeah, of course I do. What about it?
It was my voice.
My voice wouldn't come out.
I'm onstage, and the curtains open,
and I open my mouth,
but right when I try to sing,
nothing comes out.
Don't worry about dreams like that.
Just focus on singing
with all of your strength,
and don't think about
that terrible man anymore.
You'll be okay.
You were prepared to die once already.
Now you can do anything.
Oh God! Please! Tell me what to do!
I'm so scared
that my voice won't come out!
You'll make it come out no matter what.
Never forget who you are.
You're amazing.
You are Chiyoko Shimakura!
All I have to offer you
Is my love alone
Yet you are always
Yes, that's right, you're a cruel one
With the tip of your little finger
You reach out to my heart
Yet today, once again
You only give it a touch
Even after the flowers fall
These feelings of mine
Of our heartrending love
Will stay in my embrace
They'll stay in my embrace
This secret
Will belong only to me
This love that I offer you
Is the kind that never fades away
From that point on,
Kazuko Hosoki and Chiyoko Shimakura
started a new journey together
and crawled out
of the depths of hell yet again.
It's practically a done deal.
Now the issues that should be discussed
are social security, tax reform,
foreign policy, and national security.
Mm.
A lot of issues should be discussed,
but instead,
they're trying to distract the public and…
I'm listening.
I wanted to give you an update
on the case concerning the article.
It certainly is taking a very long time.
You know that I only want
to hear good news, right?
- I've told you that before.
- Yes, I completely understand.
I'm very sorry to have to tell you this,
but they've taken a firm stance
and are determined to fight back
until the end.
There's not much we can do at this point,
I'm afraid.
The situation is extremely tricky,
and we'll…