♪A little bit sorry for my love for you♪
♪Sorry, I was a little late♪
♪I really want the unconscious longing
to appear faster♪
♪Can I get closer
and hear you say "I do" once more♪
♪Holding hands, the scenery
in midsummer is a new journey♪
♪The chapters of a fairy tale
are performed one after another♪
♪The promised moment
will definitely not be forgotten♪
♪Can I get closer and listen to
the frequency of your heartbeat♪
♪Start the countdown 4321,
a new scenery♪
♪I want to see all the scenes about you♪
♪No need to miss you anymore♪
♪Right by your side♪
=Jin Secretary=
=Episode 2=
(I won the world championship abroad
in mixed martial arts.)
(Due to an ankle injury,
I had to leave the ring)
(and came back home
to look for opportunities.)
(When I got home,
I found out my twin sister)
(was treated unfairly in her company.)
(She got slapped
and suffered a mild concussion.)
(So, my sister developed hypersomnia.
The company paid compensation.)
(She got 40 days of paid leave.)
(She's gradually getting better.)
(However, she's suffering mentally.)
(Her vacation is going to end.
I persuaded her to change jobs,)
(but she refused,)
(because joining WE Group is her dream.)
(So, I made a bold decision.)
(I dressed as my sister
and went to work.)
(I'll make those
who bullied my sister pay a price.)
Miss Jin!
(My neck...)
(It doesn't hurt now.)
The meeting for the new product
is about to start. The executives are here.
Alright.
Go to the meeting.
Miss Jin, hurry up. They're all here.
All of them?
I'll fight them all at once.
Who will present the new proposal later?
Anyway, it's not me.
I'm always nervous in front of Lan Chen.
He was voted the Top One
for Hubus Under 30 at such a young age.
Lan Chen is picky.
Let's see what will happen.
Hello, Mr. Lan.
Sit down.
Everyone, our new product
uses unique Tyroca seeds
from the Tianshan Mountains
at 37 degrees north latitude.
The extracted antioxidant matter
is as high as 78 percent...
63.4 percent.
Well, why did I say 78 percent?
After Tyroca seeds are dried,
washed, and purified,
0.25 grams of the antioxidant factor
attached to the surface will be lost,
which is a decrease of 14.6 percent,
so only 63.4 percent is left.
Mr. Lan is right,
but as the creative director,
I have an idea. Our product has passion.
It does not represent merely data.
It's just business.
There is no need
for passion in business.
All we do is to make the market
need our products.
I see, Mr. Lan.
Accelerate research progress.
We need money from Lihuai International.
Do it quickly.
Yes, Mr. Lan.
What happened?
I was accidentally hit
by a car this morning.
I hit him.
I was in his car.
Alright.
You guys can receive ten times of
medical expenses and consolation money.
Let's get this over.
You guys can leave, except Miss Jin.
Miss Jin.
Do you want to continue this job?
If you still want to be my secretary,
please don't be impulsive again.
I...
You know how you got this job.
I went against their advice
to make you my secretary.
Since you chose this job,
you have to be responsible.
Send me today's schedule. Buy me
macarons. Don't get the flavor wrong.
Put them on my desk in 15 minutes.
Humph.
Miss, please line up over there.
(Ten minutes later)
Here you are.
Thank you.
Hey.
Why didn't you queue?
He has reserved them in advance.
And this is the last box.
You can try a new flavor.
The last box?
I'll give it to you in this case.
I think you need it more than I do.
Thanks. How much do I owe you?
No problem. You can pay me next time.
Thank you.
Can I order that flavor?
Sure, Mr. Zeng.
We will make it for you right away.
Hey, Miss Jin.
Do you think
you can do whatever you want
because Mr. Lan backs you up?
You didn't learn a thing from that slap?
Are you a fool?
Be smart.
It was you?
She became a moron.
Show some respect, you two.
Don't upset Miss Jin anymore.
You better learn a lesson.
The man who hits a woman is the worst.
Find Ling Feng from the Muay Thai gym
to teach her a harsh lesson.
Who is Ling Feng?
Treat your colleagues well,
and don't underestimate women.
Or else I can do it again.
My appetite is gone. You eat them.
What's wrong with you?
Don't waste my time again.
Well,
you've been away for a month.
Let's review the work.
First, the development of new product.
This is the best way
to be invested by Lihuai International.
Second...
Miss Jin.
Did you notice anything?
What?
My tie is crooked.
So what?
Help me fix it.
What's wrong with you?
Can't you do it yourself?
It's what you should do as a secretary.
Since you chose this job...
Fine, I will help you.
♪Stars fall into my eyes,
and you fall into my heart♪
♪I make a wish foolishly,
but actually, you are the shooting star♪
♪Two lonely islands meet,
and it's the gift of fate♪
Ahem.
Mom.
Miss Jin, you may leave.
Okay.
Stop.
Do you remember me?
♪I pass through the crowd with you♪
♪As if we have a tacit understanding,
attracting each other♪
♪When the loneliness cracks,
warmth seeps in♪
♪You come with light,
shining into my heart♪
♪Stars fall into my eyes,
and you fall into my heart♪
♪I make a wish foolishly,
but actually, you are the shooting star♪
♪Open my secret♪
♪I hope you find
all the tenderness hidden for you♪
♪Sinking into your love,
I want to sink deeper♪
♪With each breath,
I can feel the sweetness♪
♪Two lonely islands meet,
and it's the gift of fate♪