♪A little bit sorry for my love for you♪
♪Sorry, I was a little late♪
♪I really want the unconscious longing
to appear faster♪
♪Can I get closer
and hear you say "I do" once more♪
♪Holding hands, the scenery
in midsummer is a new journey♪
♪The chapters of a fairy tale
are performed one after another♪
♪The promised moment
will definitely not be forgotten♪
♪Can I get closer and listen to
the frequency of your heartbeat♪
♪Start the countdown 4321,
a new scenery♪
♪I want to see all the scenes about you♪
♪No need to miss you anymore♪
♪Right by your side♪
=Jin Secretary=
=Episode 27=
It's not my fault.
You forced me into this.
(Lan Rensha)
You can't blame me.
Indeed, we've worked very hard.
We conducted massive market research.
Finally, we released
this successful product.
You still look energetic at this age.
I am really impressed.
Mr. Zeng, I think we can collaborate.
We should be qualified now, right?
Your company has long been qualified.
However...
What is it, Mr. Zeng?
Your new product is fairly successful.
But I always think
a product
without a soul is not sustainable.
Stop beating around the bush.
If you don't want to cooperate,
just say it. Don't waste time.
Please calm down. Take care.
Yes, grandfather, calm down.
I think Mr. Zeng must have his reasons.
Yes, your company is still
on our final evaluation list.
Please refine your financing plan
and bid then. Thank you.
I've told you to marry Gu Qianqian.
With the influence of the Gu family,
we wouldn't have been humiliated
by him.
Alright. Everyone's worked hard.
Let's go out for lunch.
Miss Jin, you go eat outside
with Lan Chen.
The two of us?
You two should go out
and relax while eating.
I have a meeting with Mr. Li.
- Yes.
- You two go.
Boss, you can talk to me
if you have any worries.
Well...
Can you be my girlfriend?
We haven't known each other for long.
Let's get to know each other better.
We haven't spent enough time together?
I think it's enough.
I think you like Zeng...
It's okay. Let's eat.
I'll go to the restroom.
Xi'en, why are you here?
I'm having lunch with Lan Chen.
Okay.
Thank you for giving me the chance
to be confessed.
What are you talking about?
I rejected Lan Chen.
Why?
He confessed to me,
but he actually talked to you.
You must get him wrong.
No, I've decided to start over
and compete fairly with you.
By the way, I heard
your new product has been launched.
Mr. Zeng said at the meeting today
that it's still not good enough.
What? With such good sales,
everyone would want to invest.
No, Mr. Zeng said
the product lacks a soul.
He also mentioned the financing plan.
Impossible. Mr. Lan
and I both think the plan is good.
If you think so,
I'll have nothing to say.
Alright.
There must be some misunderstanding.
I'll go ask Mr. Zeng.
- Alright.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
I'm afraid that you fell asleep.
You got changed?
Yes.
Is it because you got something on them?
Alright, well,
go back and eat.
After lunch, I'll take you home.
Have a good rest.
Okay.
I'll do as you say.
What do you think is the soul
of the product?
It means the inner essence.
How can a product last without love?
I mean, it's the same
with clothing design.
I think good clothing design needs love,
and accumulation.
Why are you talking
about clothing design?
You are bringing up another topic.
What do you mean by that?
Isn't this just a metaphor?
Besides, today's the weekend.
I'm not your employee. Speak properly.
I suspect you have schizophrenia.
You're always changing.
Miss Jin.
You are really special.
Haven't you been eating well lately?
We're together every day.
Don't you know about that?
Come on. Just tell me directly.
Alright, enough.
I mean...
You need to take good care of yourself.
Anyway, don't push yourself so hard.
♪I pass through the crowd with you♪
♪As if we have a tacit understanding,
attracting each other♪
♪When the loneliness cracks,
warmth seeps in♪
♪You come with light,
shining into my heart♪
♪Stars fall into my eyes,
and you fall into my heart♪
♪I make a wish foolishly,
but actually, you are the shooting star♪
♪Open my secret♪
♪I hope you find
all the tenderness hidden for you♪
♪Sinking into your love,
I want to sink deeper♪
♪With each breath,
I can feel the sweetness♪
♪Two lonely islands meet,
and it's the gift of fate♪