"Episode 4."
You think you can redeem
all with this small change?
Keep dreaming!
Won-jun.
Actually, I saw what happened.
You saw it?
If I were him,
I don't think I could have
forgiven you right away.
But that's just the start, right?
Thirty-one people.
These are the people I
have to ask for forgiveness.
"Notebook."
But do you know what hurts the most?
Among them...
There are people whose
faces I can't remember.
I guess you really are a bad person.
You just have to keep
sincerely apologising.
Besides, they are the
ones who will forgive you.
Don't they need time too?
Thank you, U-sol.
Thanks to you, I gained a lot of courage.
Did you just say that? I got goosebumps.
But I feel like my
courage is still lacking.
I have something I
want to tell you as well.
I'll finish my homework first,
then I'll tell you.
-Homework?
-I am very hungry.
Let's just eat there at Han Sung-yong's.
Don't beat around the bush. What is it?
Hey, there is something like that.
Only a true man can do this.
Then you can never do it.
Where else can you
find a true man like me?
So tell me quickly.
As I always say, a man
must know how to wait.
"Do your best, and let Heaven's
will take care of the rest."
A human should finish all his work
-and wait for the will of heaven...
-Won-jun!
This is a public place.
Pardon me.
-Won-jun!
-Fight me if you can.
Are you on Han
Sung-yong's side or my side?
-On Sung-yong's side.
-You punk!
"Shark: The Storm."
You're Cha U-sol, right?
"1 hour earlier."
"Notebook."
You're here?
"Dangjin Funeral Home."
You're Cha U-sol, right?
What were you doing?
Why are you still alive?
What did you do when Lee Won-jun died?
What were you doing?
I'm sorry.
Darn it!
Stop! What's wrong?
Say!
Why did Lee Won-jun die?
What were you all doing when he was dying?
Why?
Let go! Let go!
Please forgive me.
Forgive me...
If you're sorry, save Lee Won-jun.
-Save him!
-Stop, Yeon-jin!
-Why are you still alive?
-I'm sorry...
Please forgive me!
Calm down.
-Let go of me.
-Take U-sol out first.
Calm down.
Why? Why are you still alive?
U-sol, go out quickly!
You should save him!
"The deceased: Lee
Won-jun, Family: Lee Yeon-jin."
Crazy jerk.
Yeon-jin.
Don't hate your brother so much.
It's because of me.
Won-jun became like that because of me.
I shouldn't have said no
when he first came to me.
I should just work with him.
Sung-yong.
I shouldn't have learned
how to fight in the first place.
That way, he wouldn't have
been close to people like me.
That way, this will not happen.
-That's enough.
-I killed him!
I killed Won-jun.
It would be better if I died!
You jerk, stop it!
Do you still remember
what Won-jun said in the car?
Knowing you might be like
this, he still said it's not your fault!
That fool would always
brag that he's going to college.
He kept apologising even though
he knew he would not be forgiven.
For the first time, he felt like a human.
His life was like trash.
But thanks to you, U-sol,
he feels like a human for the first time.
But if you keep acting like this,
do you think he will like it?
Don't burden the person who has left.
I have received the
treatment. I can go again later.
Yun Ji-hee!
-Mum.
-Come home quickly!
Everything turned out
like this because of me.
How could I do that?
Ji-hee.
Ji-hee, what's wrong?
Hello?
Ji-hee!
-Mum, I'll call you back later.
-Ji-hee!
Darn it. Why did you come here?
Can't you see I'm working?
Let me eat and live too. Gosh!
So, what?
What are you going to do?
"Managing Director Cha Dae-po."
Please answer it.
This case is a stabbing incident,
so I can't just leave it like that.
I will take care of it as a solo crime.
Just come up with a scapegoat.
Why did that Hyun Woo-yong
always causing trouble?
I can't always keep
cleaning up after his messes.
Hey. This time...
makse sure the compensation is as good.
This is a murder case.
I get it.
-Make sure everything is well-prepared.
-I will.
Hey.
You jerk. Do you think
the police are pushovers?
-Grandma, I heard it well.
-Yes.
If you need any help,
"Inspector Kim Hyeong-kwon"
don't hesitate to contact me anytime.
Thank you.
I know you're very sad, but stay strong.
Everything will be all right.
-Thank you for your help.
-Sure, grandma.
So, you mean the police are
now on Hyun Woo-yong's side?
This is absolutely absurd!
What should we do now?
I'm leaving this here.
What's that?
"Let's finish what we were talking
about. From: Hyun Woo-yong."
It has been sent.
Hey.
Don't you want something fresh and raw?
-Let's go to a Japanese restaurant instead.
-Good.
Change the menu.
"Let's finish what we were talking about."
Darn it!
Police or whatever! We will do it!
Stop it.
If we go, what can we do?
Catch him, kill him or
drag him to the police!
What a jerk! How dare he
send flowers to the one he killed?
Do you want to go and get killed?
Do you think that's what Won-jun wants?
That's exactly what he wants!
-Sung-yong!
-As of now, you have to calm down!
Go away if you're afraid.
If you don't go, I will go alone.
Scared? Do I look scared now?
That jerk Hyun
Woo-yong, I want to kill him!
But now is not the time for that.
-We have to be patient now!
-Are you guys insane?
Are you guys gangsters?
Go out! The funeral isn't over yet!
Fight outside!
"Let's finish what we were talking about."
"Lee Dong-min (haven't apologised).
I broke his bone during exercise."
"Shin Min-sung (haven't apologised)"
"We are good friends and he was
seriously injured when we fought."
"Cha U-sol. I often hit him in
prison because he looked weak."
"A strong and good child."
"I will be a good brother
and be friends with him."
But I feel like my
courage is still lacking.
I have something I
want to tell you as well.
I'll finish my homework first,
then I'll tell you.
Homework? What is it? Tell me.
Hey, there is something like that.
Only a true man can do this.
"I will be a good brother
and be friends with him."
"Cha U-sol."
"Notebook."
What Sung-yong said is true.
Won-jun wanted us
to stay strong until the very end.
"Lee Won-jun."
I'll be back, Won-jun.
Let's go.
Let's make them pay for
what they did to Won-jun.
But let's make the right plan this time.
I'll go too.
This is my brother's
business. I'll go too.
Hey, that is a dangerous
place. We can't just go like that.
I don't think that's right.
Take this.
Let's go together.
If you truly believe that
the path you chose is right,
you must follow it, no
matter how difficult it is.
"Late, Lee Won-jun" -Won-jun
took my words and lived by them.
The path we take is certainly risky
but if we give up, nothing will change.
That's why we have to go.
I will be back.
Even if a big storm comes...
"Shark: The Storm."
Gosh.
Something odd keeps popping up.
It's odd.
There must be a reason why it's cheap.
Move aside.
It seems like you take photos a lot.
-Isn't this a bit odd?
-What?
Who takes an exam ID
photo in a sticker booth?
This thing gave me two
photos for 4,000 won.
Where else would you
find a good deal like that?
From the size alone, does it look right?
Which ID photo is wider than it is tall?
-Oh, really?
-Is that all you can say?
-Come on out.
-Wait!
Then, you can take photos like this.
Let me help you. I'll take a
shot of you with my elbow.
Is it really that strange?
That's odd, you fool.
It's embarrassing for others to see.
Guys, get inside! Look, I brought this.
This is for you because you like meat.
Meat. Okay, okay.
I like it.
Sang-hyup, let's go out
with the normal people.
Okay, go!
One moment! Ta-da!
You can't ignore this.
Because this is really funny.
-Why are you like that, too?
-Two photos for 4,000 won.
Where else can you get
such a good opportunity?
See? Everyone was tempted by the words.
This idiot came here to
take photos for the exam.
That...
Wait a minute.
Listen here. Wouldn't it be okay
if you tilt your head like
this and take the photo?
Look. He said the same thing.
You know how well U-sol studied, right?
-First place overall in the school.
-That's correct.
I'm going crazy.
This is too embarassing, even for me.
Don't!
My heart feels like
it's going to fall out!
I almost fell!
It is prohibited to say
fall here at this time.
If Won-jun fails the high
school equivalency exam
after saying fall, will
you be responsible?
If he ever gets into trouble
because of your mouth...
It fell down.
Fall.
U-sol, I'm going to fall because of you.
Forgive me.
Forget it. Let's take one photo and go.
Boss Han.
Am I your ATM?
Why are you like this, Boss Han?
-I have money.
-Do you have money?
I also have emergency cash.
-That's enough.
-Good grief.
-Is there a place to insert coins here?
-Well...
-No.
-Is this a thousand won?
Move.
That's a big boss!
The mode from earlier...
-Do you want to try this?
-Press it.
This or this?
-No, something still feels off.
-Move! Seriously!
-Where should I look, here?
-Look into the lens.
-Make a pose.
-Okay.
Get ready.
Hey, are you guys at a funeral?
Everyone, try to smile
a little sweeter like this.
-Shouldn't we strike a pose now?
-Let's do a heart.
Heart.
-I want to throw up.
-Throw up?
Sung-yong, are you really this tall?
It's been a while since
my feet touched the ground.
I'm levitating among the piglets.
-Then, I will go forward.
-Hey...
Hey! If the building is in
front, is the villa visible?
-Taking photo in three.
-It's not a villa but a single-family home.
-Do you want to be hit?
-It is capturing time!
-In the middle...
-Stay still, you rock!
-I'll go back!
-Move!
Like this?
Do a cute pose. Like this.
Your head is so huge!
Get out. Won-jun has to take an ID photo!