(Sorry Not Sorry)
(The characters, locations,
organizations, businesses, events, groups)
(settings, and procedures are all
unrelated to actual persons or events)
(Filming with child actors took place
under the supervision of
guardians and in a safe environment)
I want to...
kill him
He ruined my life
What could possibly stop me?
Well, there are many options
I want it to be as painful as possible
But you seem to be mistaken
Pardon?
Are you aware of what we do here?
You're an errand service center, right?
Well...
We're a start-up that just started
our business
(Errand Service Center)
(Based on trust and faith)
We named ourselves "Errand Service"
to be witty
but we're in charge of
arranging housekeepers,
cleaning, and childcare services
Wait, then by "errand," you mean...
But listening to your story...
Wow, that wretched bastard
I fully understand why you want to kill him
But then...
That request will cost
several Crores of won
Several Crore?
I'm flat broke after my divorce
With the loans I've taken out because
of him and our house, I'm already...
So, let's live in goodwill
If that's the case
we're looking for housekeepers
and cleaning staff
How much is the hourly wage?
(Sorry Not Sorry)
(Are you back on the market? Who cares?)
(I'm getting remarried!)
Yes, let's admit it
I'm a divorcée
An ambiguous divorcée, that is
I'm legally single but not socially
My life has always been like this
I can't believe it
It's not your fault
Be confident
That's not even a flaw these days
I know
But honestly, they can only say such
things because it's none of their business
Where did it all go wrong?
Marriage is reality
But I was too innocent
And only thought of love...
This was once my newlywed house
I currently live here alone
You startled me!
What the...
What's going on?
You startled me!
Why is it so hard to reach you?
Huh?
(Ji Eun-gyu: Are you
coming home late today?)
Hey, this is a question you'd ask a
family member who lives with you
You can't send me this message when we're
seeing each other in three or four years!
I was in a bit of a hurry
Wait, but why are you here in Korea
instead of America right now?
What about work?
And what's all this luggage?
I'll explain inside
Let's go home, Jay
This is my younger sister Eun-gyu
She's a single mother
We're not both divorcées
Because Eun-gyu was never married
(5 years ago)
That's how it turned out
It's a son
I named him Jay
Sperm...
Wait, do you want to hear about
the dad's profile?
- Why, you! Hey!
- The one I chose from the cryobank...
Hey, you crazy girl!
What? Son?
Return to Korea immediately!
- Calm down! Calm down, dad
- Did you know about it?
Mom, I had no idea!
No, I'll go there, Song-yi!
Ji Eun-gyu, stay right there!
I'm coming!
Hey, you crazy girl!
Honey!
Unlike me, who is ambiguous, my sister
is a wacko, without a doubt
And she made me a nephew via a cryobank
Hi
You should say hello to your aunt
Please let us stay with you for a while
Shoes over here
This is nice
It's a lovely house
The two of you can use the main room
It's over there
All right, then
Thank you
Mommy!
You must be nuts
Why do you still have this?
Do you regret it?
Why aren't you discarding this?
You've yet to learn about
the recycling culture in Korea
Just imagine placing that box in a plaza
where all of your neighbors walk past
People even glimpse at fliers piled up
at a supermarket
And this is clearly a wedding invitation
with a fancy ribbon
and it even has mom and dad's names
and my name on it!
At least, like...
Give the envelopes out for free
I mean...
That frame?
Large-size waste needs to be placed
outside with a sticker on it
That means it has to sit outside
for a few days
That's pretty much like announcing
to the neighborhood that I'm divorced
Who cares?
What?
Right, I get it
Let's get him to bed first
Come on Time for bed, Jay
Okay
Well done
Is Jay sleeping?
Yes
Wait, so what happened to you?
There was a bit of an accident
I won't be here for too long
I'll also pay for the living expenses
But it's a secret from mom and dad for now
You crazy, crazy girl
What have you done again?
Mom will go ballistic if she finds out
And I'm working from tomorrow
Huh?
Shush!
You'll wake Jay up
Have you returned to Korea for good?
Who knows?
Anyway, I've got everything sorted
so can you just take Jay
to kindergarten tomorrow?
You're driving me nuts
This is so frustrating
Until when?
New York?
Yes
As in the actual "New York"?
Not the bakery?
Yes, that's what I heard
You know it yourself
It isn't easy to join Noble Kindergarten
between semesters
But then, he's from New York,
so he's totally... How should I put it?
Yeah, he's an original
An American-born who was raised in America
That's why the principal accepted him
- Oh my goodness
- Huh?
"Native"
Your kid attends an English kindergarten,
so you should know some English, too
Is it not "Original?"
Negative, negative
The bus is here
Good morning How are you?
Have a good day
All right, let's get on the bus
- Bye
I love you, Shannon
Have a good day
Shannon!
I love you
Mom will be cheering for you
See you later
Yes, goodbye
Shannon!
I'm craving beer
Oh my, hello! Jay's mother
I'm Jay's aunt
I see
Okay, then, please come this way
You couldn't attend the orientation
so let me give you a brief guide
The children must arrive by 9 o'clock
and activities start at half past nine
After morning snacks, reading, and
writing classes will begin at 10 o'clock
We also have physical education sessions
starting at 11 o'clock
to stimulate children's growth
Kids' English Yoga has a significant impact
on improving concentration
and stimulating the growth plates
Do you want to see?
(Noble Kids Cheonpo Admission Guide)
Just how much do these people make monthly
to pay for this?
Competent much, Ji Eun-gyu?
Amazing, absolutely amazing
Just when did these people
give birth to children like this
And where do they make all this money...
Even if I get pregnant tomorrow
I'd be 40 by the time I
send my child to kindergarten
And I'll be 60 by the time
my child goes to college
No
It's okay
(A song to raise self-esteem)
Here's your coffee
What do you think, Ji-song?
Rabbit
I must not fall for this beauty
The boss is a villain
Huh?
Rabbit!
First of all, my name isn't Ji-song
My last name is Ji, and my name is Song-yi
Oh, that's right!
I'm sorry
Huh? Sorry?
Ji-song
Excuse me
Did you even process my order?
Huh?
I'm sorry, we'll prepare it for you
right away
If you wait a little, I'll bring it to you
So, please...
I'm a little...
No. 57, here's your latte, sir
I hope you enjoy it
What?
Song-yi, you're really fast
It's thanks to you
You've got slow hands
and feet and have no wit
But it's okay
Because you're beautiful
You, be my boyfriend
Huh?
Now, everyone, go home
Come this way
We're going home!
Why aren't you going home?
My mom can't come because
she has to work
so I have to stay here a bit longer
Jay, too Let's go home now
Bye, Jay
(Ms. Ji Song)
(HanM Card Installment Carryover Contract)
(Revolving, Current Sum: $290.70)
(Interest Payment Guide)
(The interest for the JH mortgage loan,
$644.90, is due tomorrow)
(Seoro Bank Sweet Home Loan)
(Payment Notice: $2100.39)
I've never seen anyone pour their soul
into buying a house
Your loan is bigger than your
salary from the cafe
That's not it, my mortgage loan...
Wait, but why are you peeking
at my text message?
Ji-song, it was unintentional
Song-yi, I said it's Song-yi
Uh...
The "Ji-song" I said earlier was an apology
Then, I'll wrap up for today
I have something to do afterward
Okay
Thank you for your work today
Take care
See you tomorrow
All right, slowly
Let's get on the bus
- She must be the mother of the new kid
- Jay, how was your first day?
I've never seen her before
It was all right
His pronunciation is spot-on
Hey, go and ask for her number
Let's invite her to our group chat
- Me?
- Yes
But then, what should I say?
Just ask for her messenger ID
You're good at asking for such things
Oh, Shannon!
Oh, you're here, Shannon
Huh?
When did they vanish?
What does she do?
Well, I'm not too sure
According to the principal, uh...
Where was it?
Wall, Wall Street?
Apparently, she worked at
a financial company there
- Wall Street?
- Yes
Isn't that the place that comes out
in movies?
Where people drive super expensive cars
that start with R or P?
Jay, let's ride that after Taekwondo
No way
It's probably her husband
It isn't easy for a woman to work on
hedge funds in the U.S.
I know because I've lived in the States
See you
(Pick-up: Popo Chicken, Distance: 13km)
(Delivery: Cheonpo S-Class 102-301)
(Slide to accept delivery)
(Start delivery)
(Bangs Card)
(The payment due is $301.29)
(New delivery request)
(Delivery Fee: $3.70)
(The interest for the JH mortgage loan,
$644.90, is due today)
(Emergency Loan Interest Withdrawal)
(Expected payment sum: $137.40)
(New delivery request)
(Expected Delivery Fee: $3.80)
(Please pay the overdue fee
of $560.39 as of today)
(Quick Sale: Cheonpo Central
River Forét the Hill 808-1604)
($6.2 million)
It already dropped $1.8 million?
Who are you?
Ma'am!
What?
Why are you so startled?
Who would see this
if it's down here so low?
This was why no one came to see the house
I was wondering who you were
You must be the newlywed couple
in building 808
Newlywed...
Please take good care of this
Write the "Quick Sale" nice and big in red!
Okay, okay
The real estate market is in recession
these days
So, people are reluctant
to look into "CenForét"
I told your husband this last time
I don't have a husband...
I told him to buy the leading apartment
Because leading apartments
are constantly traded, even in a recession
- The leading apartment?
- Yes
And where is that?
- Where...
- Over there!
Lake the Village Park View
(Lake the Village Park View 115-1405)
$1.3 million?
It's not that expensive
(Pick-up: Joy Pizza, distance: 21m)
(Delivery: Lake the Village Park View
Building 1002 #503)
It sure is a leading apartment
Do they spray perfume in the hallway?
Hana?
Did you just take a picture of me?
Pardon?
Please erase that photo
That rude attitude
and voice
That's Choi Hana, without a doubt
Hey, Choi Hana
Choi Hana was once my one-and-only
best friend
- You crazy wench
- Choi Hana!
An ex-best friend whom
I cut ties with, to be exact
I can't believe I came across her here
Excuse me
What's the matter?
I said I'd go outside
Oh?
Oh my!
Are you okay?
What's wrong with her?
Seriously, what's wrong with her?
I didn't know Choi Hana got married
She met a competent man just like herself
and was living here
(Warning! Do not park your
baby's car in the common area)
- You're here
- Yes
You!
What happened? Did you work out?
I came back from my part-time job
Part-time job?
What part-time job?
Uh... Well...
Because of my loan interest...
Oh my...
Wait, what's wrong with your arm?
I'm okay
No, what's the matter? Let me see it
- It's okay, it's nothing
- You're driving me crazy
Where did you get injured?
Jay
Are you comforting me?
Thank you
How did you get injured? Huh?
You're old enough to know better!
Get inside
Let's go inside and get ointment on that
It hurts
Go inside
You'll get injured if you're clumsy
Do you understand, Jay?
Ugh, you idiot, moron, fool
Are you nuts?
I know
What's the point of receiving this house
as alimony?
With all that mortgage loan...
Didn't you do the calculations?
Even from a mathematical approach...
I know!
But once this house is sold,
I'll repay the loan
move out, and then...
Hey, go and sleep
Seoul is pretty far, isn't it?
You should live in Seoul
if you're that competent...
That's enough
So, how much did you earn today?
Forget it! I'll deal with it
Song-yi
Living expenses plus half of the
monthly loan interest
I'll pay you that
Huh?
What do you say? Are you in?
No
It's too big a sum
Who said I'll give it to you for free?
In return, reduce your part-time job
and look after Jay
Just say the word, boss
Shall I organize the bedding for you?
You need to go to work tomorrow
Hey, get ready for work
Okay
Like so, I started living
like a Cheonpo Mom
That I had never lived before,
thanks to Eun-gyu and Jay
Jay, tidy up your toys
Jay, let's eat
Okay
Although, it was never peaceful
Oh my!
What the
Does this even make sense?
Darn it, it was like this last time as well
Which house is doing this?
Jay, that's dirty!
It's toilet water, it's dirty
Hey, prevent Jay from going inside
I'll call the management office
This is driving me nuts! Song-yi!
Our toilet is foaming, and it's going wild
- We need to wash up
- Do you know how much this is...
- We can't do anything or go to work
- Get out! Song-yi!
Because the toilet is foaming
- The toilet is a downright mess
- This is crazy, Song-yi!
- We can't tidy this up ourselves, sir
- No, no
Look at this
Can you please check which house
is responsible for this?
(NOBLE KIDS)
I'm here at last
The most flustering moment these days
is when I must meet new people
Excuse me...
And introduce myself
I have no plans to
get to know that person
and I don't even know if I'll
see them frequently or not
Hello
I'm Jay's aunt
I'm just here to pick him up
I see!
(End of conversation)
(This would be perfect)
But unlike myself, conversations
with mothers must go as follows
You must be Jay's aunt!
You're so sweet
Which class is he in?
Oh, really?
But then, are you married?
Just because I can't be bothered
(Q. Are you married?)
Yes!
- If I answer so
- Then, you must be similar to us
- I'm likely to see her frequently
- We should get along
Then, from my husband to childcare, etc.
I don't want to go that far lying
(Q. Are you married?)
No
But this, too, is a lie
I was married
(Divorce)
but I got divorced
But to say this
Do I have to?
How would I deal with this?
It's okay
Was it too much information?
I need to consider Jay's position
Excuse me...
You're the newcomer, Jay's mother, right?
Hello
Hello, Seung-hee's mother
Yeah, let's not over
think it and be honest
Actually, I'm...
Song-yi?
You're Song-yi, right?
Oh my!
It's me, Hana, Choi Hana!
Yeah...
Does your child also attend here?
Okay, let's say it with confidence!
No! I'm here to pick up
my nephew, and I'm...
Am I a divorcée or single?
Mommy!
You must be Song-yi's son
You're so good-looking
- How fascinating!
- Wait, that's...
Mommy!
Sia, Teo!
Goodness me, how beautiful
Goodness me
Wait, were they in the same class?
What a coincidence!
Goodness me
Did you have fun today?
Are you happy mommy is here?
- Yeah!
Are the two of you acquainted
with each other?
Sia's mom and Jay's mom?
Yes, we're from the same
middle and high schools
Alums!
What? Alums?
Oh my! I see!
What's the point of being an alumnus?
Not all alums are close
We were super close
We were best friends
Right, Jay's mom?
Me...
Jay's mom?
Confident? As if
Living in the leading apartment with
children in an expensive kindergarten
And she even has three children
She must be so happy
And to spill my current
situation before her...
I couldn't possibly say it
If I come across her
I wanted to show her I was doing well
Just like running into an ex-boyfriend
Dressed up nicely
And holding hands with a fine man
(Choi Hana)
"Best friends?" That rolled off her tongue
when we'd ghosted each other for ten years
Choi Hana, you just amaze me
But then, what should I do?
What if everyone thinks I'm a mother?
What's the matter?
Jay, let's go home now
No
Let's go Let's go home!
No! I want to go
Okay
But we're going after two rounds, okay?
Jay
But why did you say such a thing earlier?
What do you mean?
Why did you call me "Mommy" earlier?
I don't know
Do you think I'll cut you slack
if you're that adorable?
Your lie put me in a sticky situation
You shouldn't lie
Why?
Because it might hurt others later
Did it hurt?
Excuse me...
I'm sorry but by any chance...
Aren't I right?
What do you mean?
Kindergarten!
Noble Kids!
- Yes
- Oh my goodness! Oh my!
I also wanted to send my child there
but couldn't make it
Seung-jun, look Isn't he cool?
Hi, I'm Jay
Oh my! Why is he so fluent?
Hey, Jay How old are you?
I'm older!
My goodness
Does he get private lessons?
Why is he so good at English?
I heard kids take after their mothers
so you must be intelligent
That's not it
He doesn't take classes...
Jay grew up in New York
New York?
As in, "New York, dduru dduru..."
That New York?
Oh my goodness! That's incredible!
That's insane! Oh my!
That's...
I startled you, didn't I?
I only just moved here
so I needed someone to talk to
Goodness me
Wait, how old are you?
9...
Oh, my!
I was born in the 80s!
Oh my goodness!
That's seriously amazing!
Jay must be good-looking
because he takes after your looks
She isn't my...
We have something to do, so we'll get going
Jay's mom, wait...
Let's exchange numbers while we're at it
Tell me your number
- I'll see you next time
- Wait, your number...
I was almost there
It's so hard to make friends
What?
Why did you lie?
When did I? That's not true
I didn't lie
I just didn't clarify myself
I should know better
what to teach a child
No
Don't remember what I said just now
Forget it all
You said it'll hurt others
No, she smiled
No
You shouldn't lie
Okay, I won't
Promise
Let's never lie again, promise
Okay
Jay, what do you want for dinner tonight?
Fried chicken?
Then, I'll treat you to fried chicken today
Okay
Sia
Do you remember saying you wanted
to marry daddy as a baby?
No
Huh?
Are you not going to marry daddy?
Oh, I don't know!
Bae Sia
Sia, what about daddy?
Honey
I went to pick up the kids
and ran into an old friend today
She'll grow up and bring her boyfriend
at this rate, right?
We used to be really close
I think it's been around ten years
- Are you listening to me?
- Huh?
Did you have a friend here?
You always said you hated
the other mothers...
I mean, last time, Ethan's mom pitied you
for being a working mother
and whatever, so I...
She's such a joke!
There's a friend whom I was
really close to since middle school
but we suddenly drifted apart
Do you remember?
Yeah
I remember hearing about her
But then, it's a little iffy
I swear it's unlikely
Why? What is it?
The other mothers are frantically trying
to befriend her
I mean, her child is fluent in English
Apparently, they lived in New York
or something...
Why did she come to Cheonpo
instead of Seoul?
But then...
Song-yi is terrible at English!
She must've found herself a great husband
just like you
A husband!
What is going on?
She met a great husband...
But would I look too shallow if I suddenly
start contacting her?
Hey...
Ji Song-yi...
Do you not hear me?
Sia
Seriously, I'm so lonely
What kind of game is this?
This is...
"Close your eyes and stay still" game
Liar! This isn't a game!
Wait, just a little bit...
Try staying in bed for a bit more
Okay, let's sleep...
This is boring!
I'm so bored!
(Song-yi, do you still use
the same number?)
(It's been ages)
(It's good to see you again, it was so
hectic earlier, so I couldn't say hello...)
Okay
What do you want to play?
But who is that man?
What's wrong with him?
Everyone said
It was a good marriage
(Song-yi's Wedding D-58)
Congratulations, Song-yi
Wow, you look so beautiful
Song-yi is getting married to a nice guy
We'd never find a man like this
Why? What's wrong with us?
Exactly, what's wrong with me?
I mean, it's not like you're a competent
woman with professional expertise
working for a conglomerate
You're working for chicken feed anyway
and you've found someone to rely on
Look at her She's resigning
Excuse me
I'm sorry, but I'm offended
I'm going to work again once I move
I'm resigning because our house is in
Cheonpo because of my husband's work
Of course, you should be the one to move
Because your conglomerate-working husband
will make 100 times more than you
Wait, but then...
Your husband is so handsome
Look
Yeah, Song-yi is getting married
to a nice guy
And they even bought their newlywed house
- Not on rent?
- Not on rent! Yes!
I heard you're already living with him
They're all loans
My boyfriend has moved in already,
and I'll move in after the wedding
What gave you the certainty
to get married, Song-yi?
I felt I'd be happy living
a trivial everyday life
if I were with him
You'd look gorgeous in your wedding dress
Although I was never better
than anyone in my life
I believed I'd be happy like
everyone else if we were together
Do you want to receive it?
Okay, okay!
I should receive it
I miss you
How's the wedding invitation
gathering going?
I'm getting off work soon
It must be tough since he's been
working overtime lately
He'd be surprised to see me here
Why is he living like this?
Goodness me
Song-yi!
Well, that's...
Song, Song-yi
Yeah, so we're...
Song-yi, I can explain
This, this is...
You crazy bastard!
I can tell even if you don't explain
She's your ex-girlfriend!
That's true, but...
You crazy bastard!
- Wait, that's not it!
- How can you do this to me?
Hey!
- Hey!
- I swear that's not it
No, no
What do you think you're doing?
Song-yi, that's not it
I... I swear that's not it
How dare you!
Hey, that's not it
I mean, tell me what's going on
Why are you suddenly getting a divorce?
Do you think marriage is a joke?
You said you'd get married,
and now you want a divorce!
I mean...
I wasn't trying to get married as a joke
Hey, Song-yi
That's how it is
Everyone lives like that
You had an argument, didn't you?
But if he isn't a bastard
who cheated on you, live with him
But mom, he cheated on me
And I witnessed it
Strangely enough,
I couldn't spill the beans
I'd choose to look crazy to mom and dad
Than look pitiful
No, we didn't argue
I just wanted to start over
before it's too late
Then, you should've decided
before I handed out the wedding invitations
to my friends!
What's wrong with you all of a sudden?
You must've lost it!
You even registered your marriage
to get a mortgage loan!
If you call off the wedding now,
that's a divorce!
Wake up!
No! I looked into it
We've yet to get married
and haven't even lived with each other
We just registered our marriage
to get a house, so it can be annulled!
I told everyone about your wedding
What are you going to do about this?
- If you call off the wedding now...
- Let go, let go of me
Ugh! Wake up, girl!
Have you also gone insane like Eun-gyu?
The decision I made as an
adult wasn't easy to change
Pardon?
Am I still a married woman, then?
Yes, regardless of the situation,
you are married
You registered for your marriage because
you had such intentions
You also got a low-interest loan
for newlywed couples
We didn't even have our wedding
We only registered our marriage!
And I wasn't the one who suggested it
It was to buy the house, so that bastard...
I mean, that person...
Yes, but at that point,
you intended to marry him
Yes
But he cheated on me!
And that will be very advantageous
to you in the lawsuit
Because he's significantly liable
Okay, so you have clear evidence
that the two were having an affair, right?
You know, like a video or a photo
Or a voice recording with the consent
of the other party
No
Pardon?
I couldn't...
When I unprecedentedly witnessed
them before my eyes
I couldn't believe it
And at first, I hid like a fool
when I saw them
Evidence or whatever!
None of that came to mind
But then, miss?
You can't approach the law
emotionally like that...
I know, but what I'm saying is...
Wait, but then
Regardless of everything
you could at least give a word of comfort,
"It must've been tough," no?
The thing is, I'm someone who gives
realistic help
rather than useless emotional consolation
For example, swift and neat divorce
But then...
A reasonable alimony
equivalent to the client's pain
You're right, but!
Okay, then, let me summarize for you
The annulment of marriage...
Mr. Cha
You've never been betrayed by someone
you love, have you?
Have you ever been hurt?
I don't know
See?
You don't understand me
so how can I talk about myself?
Wait, there's no logical connection
between this and that
How do you plan to take my side
when you don't even understand me?
Come on, filing for a divorce
isn't some kid's joke!
There's no such thing as your side
or my side in this
There are sides to it!
No?
Goodness me
F... Forget it
You're not the only law firm available
I quit
I'm not entrusting this case to you
Gosh, this tastes disgusting!
Okay, I understand
I'm so sorry to hear that
I really want to help you
but I guess there's nothing
I can do about it!
If you don't mean it, don't say it
That, that...
What a temper
So I'm
Guilty of registering my marriage
58 days ahead of my wedding
And therefore, legally divorced
And socially ambiguously back
on the market as a single woman
(Interest Payment Guide)
(KG Savings Bank interest
loans due for payment: $2,580)
(Ms. Ji, your interest on $5,000,000
in financial loans is 4.28%...)
What a relief the screen is intact
I don't even have money
But if I must find one
good thing about this
I've grown up a little
No one can substitute for me
I must be responsible
For what I've done
He's a nasty person,
so I'll teach him a lesson
How amazing
It's you, isn't it?
Jay, auntie needs to poo-poo
Can you play alone for a minute?
Goodness me
It's not me
What is this sound?
Have they seriously gone nuts?
Just who on earth is doing this
at this hour...
No, no, no, no!
Oh, wait, wait
When am I going to clean this up?
Oh, no, no, no! Oh, no!
No, no!
Yeah, you're busted today
Where are you going?
To the nuisance upstairs!
We've had enough in the morning!
They're really asking for it!
Excuse me!
I'm from unit 1604 downstairs
Can you come out for a second?
Excuse me?
I mean, our toilet right now...
It's you, right?
Song-yi!
- It's me
- Tell me I'm dreaming
It's Jin-ho, the rock
The person I shared
my dark history with at 21
My ex-boyfriend
Song-yi
From an ex-best friend
to an ex-boyfriend
(Why are they all in Cheonpo?)
(Sorry Not Sorry)
Wait, how did Seok-jun marry
such a beautiful woman?
This is my mommy
Just why on earth is he doing that?
Please!
I said stop parking your
baby car in the public space
Even his handwriting is edgy
I ought to move out quickly or something
Hey, but why are you avoiding me?
Why do you always talk like that?
Why do you always pretend you care
and make me unfortunate?
Last time, she didn't talk about herself
at all
Is she hiding something?
Hello
I was wondering if we could
meet up separately