This show is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to actual persons,
living or dead, or real events
is purely coincidental and
not intended to offend any person,
profession, or organization.
I surrender.
With that evidence, you will go
straight to
the execution ground tomorrow.
The world turns blind
to slaves like us.
Our master, like Lady Nuanlaor,
might see.
Short and sweet version.
I'm carrying Khun Phra's child.
Get rid of it.
Don't let it be born.
I can't believe...
your tongue is steeped in sin.
Are you telling me
that you shot Khun Phra?
Sir, I didn't kill Khun Phra.
Please believe me.
- Shut up.
- Believe me.
Get down.
Ungrateful slave.
He gave you food
and a place to live,
but you repaid him with murder.
Mark my words.
Before noon tomorrow,
your head will roll.
I didn't kill Khun Phra.
I didn't kill him.
What's wrong with you?
You turned yourself in,
and now you're spouting nonsense.
I'm telling the truth.
Lady Jolie killed Khun Phra.
Come again?
Listen to me, sir.
I've investigated,
and I know that she killed him
because he dishonored and hurt her.
Is that true?
Yes, sir.
The gun.
The gun I was holding was hers.
She hid it at the mission station.
Oh, my.
So, you believe me now?
Go arrest her.
Thongbai.
Muahaha.
I don't believe you.
Hey.
Death's terror drove you mad.
And now, you're accusing her.
Hrr. Pathetic.
But fine.
Since your life is hanging
by a thread,
I'll let your ramblings slide.
Make every last moment count.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Make every breath count.
Bye, bye, bye.
Sir, wait.
- What?
- Please believe me.
I didn't kill Khun Phra.
She did it.
- Wait.
- Tch.
That should knock
some sense into you.
Ugh. Hack.
Muen! You rotten police.
If I ever get out,
you'll pay with your blood.
Oh, so you're
threatening me now?
You think you can take me on?
You're the one who's going
to lose your head.
Anything else?
You...corrupt police.
This country is in such disarray
because of scum like you.
Barking dog.
Your words can't save you.
You rotten filth. Bastard.
- Keep barking.
- Wait till I get out.
Sangthong.
Maiphlong.
I'm going to die.
Phi Thongbai.
Phi Sangthong will come to save you.
I promise.
♪ My player's soul
cannot resist love's spell, ♪
♪ My beating heart
submits to you, my belle. ♪
♪ In faith, I now
surrender all to thee, ♪
♪ This wild nature
that you clearly see. ♪
♪ Enchained by love,
these bonds I dare not break, ♪
♪ Though in your hands
my heart you twist and take. ♪
♪ Each day I bow to you,
my heart's reward ♪
♪ Dominate my heart ♪
♪ No one but you shall reign
and be adored ♪
♪ Dominate my heart ♪
"Mystery of the Deadly Sins"
Kratai.
Do you have
some kind of magic
to make me invisible or something?
Seriously, did you ever see me
do anything like that?
Tch.
Seriously,
why do I keep you around?
Can't help me none.
I always warn you
of things to come,
but you don't heed my warnings.
Tch.
- The coast is clear. I must go.
- Hold on.
If you go in now,
you'll get stabbed for sure.
Men aren't allowed in there.
Tell you what.
Hide in that cart over there.
Good thinking.
The sweets I gave you
weren't wasted after all.
Good luck, Phi Sangthong.
"See you later"
See ya.
Hmm?
What's it doing there?
It must've slid out.
Dangers can't touch me
because I'm always a do-gooder.
Hmph.
Stop the cart.
Uh-oh.
Now, I know the truth, Sangthong.
Thongbai...I'll save you.
What do you have in the back?
Rice, as usual.
What's the tarp for?
Smuggling opium?
No way. I wouldn't risk my life.
- I'll have to inspect it.
- Of course.
This is a disaster.
Hmph.
Pretty close.
Got lucky.
Still lucky.
Go away. That almost got my nose.
Anyway, I'll check the top as well.
Oh, heavens, help me.
Hey...Oof.
Phi Khiew.
Oh, Nong Champi.
Hoo.
Inspecting the cart?
You're so diligent.
It's only my duty, beautiful.
By the way, why are you out so late?
Watch out for the vermin.
Champi?
Is that her?
Well, uhm.
I just came to check on
the supplies
for tomorrow's menu.
Maybe I'll make
some chili paste for you.
Sure thing, Champi.
Heh.
What are in those other carts?
Lady Nuanlaor.
May we have a look?
Of course, Nong Champi.
Lady Nuanlaor.
Hold on. Hold, please.
Please hear me out. I mean no harm.
I just want your help with Thongbai.
He's in prison now.
He'll be executed tomorrow.
But I know
he didn't kill Khun Phra.
I know who did it.
Huh?
You know, really?
Lady Jolie killed him.
We found the gun
that she shot him with.
Would you help us save Thongbai?
You see?
My words as a slave mean nothing,
but yours as a noble
and Khun Phra's wife...
will carry weight with the police.
Please save Thongbai.
He's innocent.
Please.
I implore you, Lady Nuanlaor.
Please save Thongbai.
He didn't kill anybody.
Sangthong?
Why are you bothering Lady Nuanlaor?
Go away this instant.
I was pleading with her
to save Thongbai.
Don't bother my master.
If you don't leave now,
I'll call for help.
- Champi.
- Help...
Help. A slave deceives my mistress.
- Help.
- Champi? Do you need help?
You're heartless.
Oh, uhm.
False alarm, Phi Khiew.
Miss Nuanlaor. Excuse me.
Champi.
Thongbai is going to be executed.
You can't save him, my lady.
It's breaking dawn.
We have our priorities.
Maiphlong, what's taking you
so long?
I know the truth now.
Sangthong.
You're back alone?
Did you not find Lady Jolie?
I did, but...
She must've killed
Lady Rampueng, right?
- No, but...
- With her gone...
Who's going to save Thongbai?
Come on.
Stop guessing.
And listen, will ya?
I was talking,
but you kept interrupting.
Okay...I'll listen.
- Shut up and listen, okay?
- Uh-huh.
Here's what happened.
- Where're you going?
- Oh?
You killed Khun Phra.
Now, you're kidnapping
Lady Nuanlaor's sister.
- Hey, hey. Wait.
- Oh, no.
Are you pregnant, Lady Rampueng?
Short and sweet version.
I'm carrying Khun Phra's child.
She is pregnant with
Khun Phra's child.
So, the person with a strong
motive to kill Khun Phra
could be Lady Rampueng,
not Lady Jolie.
Oh, my goodness.
Why is this story...
so full of twists?
That's the same expression I made
when she told me,
but, in the end, she got me
totally flipped.
More twist?
Wait.
If she killed Khun Phra,
why was the gun with Lady Jolie?
That's the key to this whole mess.
The gun ended up with Ma'am
because of Lady Rampueng.
After Khun Phra was shot,
a commotion erupted, right?
Mm-hmm.
Thongbai.
Those three slaves broke
from detention and killed him.
- Oh, my.
- Hey.
This is not my gun.
I didn't do it.
You must believe me.
Believe me, I didn't.
Execute him.
Oh, no. No, no.
Thongbai.
What about these two?
Run. Fast.
Hey. Halt.
Lady Rampueng decided
to pick up the gun
when Thongbai caught
everyone's attention.
There she goes.
Did you catch them?
They ran faster than The Flash.
Who could catch them?
Then I'll take my leave.
I won't disturb the police.
Wait, nobody leaves.
All day, I've been with the dead.
What now?
Since the gun is missing,
we must search everyone here.
I say we start with you, Khun.
I am a Khun.
You're just a Muen.
Lower rank than me.
What authority do you have
to frisk me?
No one is immune to wrongdoing.
If you are deemed suspicious,
you must cooperate.
Don't think I'm unaware
that you also had
quarrels with him.
Shall I speak of them?
Try that after I pry
your mouth open?
And you'll see I'm
no stranger to a fight.
Afraid of being searched,
so she faked fainting.
What's wrong? Phi Rampueng.
Phi Rampueng.
Rampueng.
Pulse is normal. Nothing serious.
She probably fainted from a panic.
Lady Nuanlaor summoned a doctor,
who confirmed
Lady Rampueng was fine.
I have something else to tell you.
What is it?
She's awake.
Phi Rampueng.
How are you feeling?
What happened?
You fainted from a panic.
The doctor said you're fine.
What were you about to say, doctor?
- Well, um...
- Nuanlaor.
Let me speak with him alone.
But Phi Rampueng.
Please do as she asks.
Do you want to talk to me?
Were you going to tell them
about my pregnancy?
Mm-hmm.
I already know.
That's good.
I'll prepare some medicine
to nourish both you
and the baby.
- Hmm?
- It's all right.
That's not necessary.
Thank you, doctor,
but I'd like to rest now.
Alright.
- Please, see yourself out.
- Mm-hmm.
Guess what she planned
to do with that gun.
"Viewer Discretion Advised"
Hmph.
Stop that.
"Viewer Discretion Advised"
What are you doing?
Step back.
- Let me do it.
- No way.
You will not do it.
Give it to me.
Hrr. Huh.
I have nothing left.
Why can't you understand?
You still have your child.
If you kill yourself,
you're not just ending your life.
You're ending
your child's life, too.
The child has done nothing wrong.
Don't you want to see their face,
watch them grow,
or hear them call you "Mother"?
You're about to become a mother.
Your child will love and
be loved by you unconditionally.
It's okay.
With love and the name of the Lord,
I will help you.
Then, Ma'am hid the gun from her
to prevent another suicide attempt.
- It's that gun we found.
- Hold on.
I'm processing.
Lady Rampueng is pregnant
with Khun Phra's child.
Right.
But she didn't shoot him.
Affirmative.
After Khun Phra's death,
she wanted to die.
Betcha.
- Lady Jolie saved her just in time.
- Astounding, huh?
Then who shot Khun Phra?
"I don't know."
Dunno.
Hrr...stop playing for a second.
Every lead we follow
hits a dead end.
How will we save Thongbai?
What about Lady Nuanlaor?
Any luck?
Nothing?
She refused to help?
Even if she wanted to,
it's pointless.
Since Lady Jolie is cleared,
Lady Nuanlaor has nothing to stop
Thongbai's execution.
Are we forgetting
anybody, Phi Sangthong?
Who else? Just say it already.
Sangthong.
I don't hear
what you and Kratai talk about.
But keep your cool.
Everyone is frustrated.
We'll figure it out.
The moon is setting.
Not much time left.
Ma'am, let me wait
until the first light
appears on the horizon.
Okay?
This might be the last time
I see my sister's face.
You understand, don't you?
I believe Nuanlaor will
make it in time.
She has to.
Here she comes.
Nuanlaor.
Thank you for all your sacrifice.
Phatcharaburi is a remote town,
but you and your child
can start anew there.
And you won't have to
endure anyone's judgment.
Come along with me.
Leave everything behind.
I have some unfinished business.
When it's all over,
I'll come to you.
Promise me.
It's almost dawn.
You should go now
before anyone sees you.
Remember to always
put your child first.
Then take care of yourself.
Understand?
You must take care of yourself.
I'm so worried about you.
You, too.
Miss Nuanlaor.
You go ahead. She'll be fine.
Hey.
Any special request for this meal?
I'll take care of it.
It's your last meal.
Hey.
Eat some.
Can't you hear me?
Hey, are you deaf?
I said eat.
Eat.
Hey, can't you hear me?
Ah. Ugh.
- I didn't kill Khun Phra.
- Let go.
Hands off.
- I didn't kill Khun Phra.
- Hands off.
- Let go.
I didn't kill Khun Phra.
"Violence should never be imitated."
- Let go. / - Argh.
You killed Khun Phra,
and you're gonna kill me?
Beat me to death,
and I still won't admit it.
I didn't kill Khun Phra.
"Violence should never be imitated."
Enough.
If he dies here,
it's trouble for us.
Fine, let him starve.
Hrr.
Sangthong, figured anything yet?
I was up all night thinking.
Nothing yet.
- Sangthong.
- Hmm?
I just thought of something.
What is it?
If we can't get them
to release Thongbai,
we take him out.
Like how you just took my dipper.
What?
Busting a prisoner out
is a serious crime.
Ow. What am I supposed to do?
Hmm?
Sit on my thumb
while watching him be executed?
I can't do that.
He is my friend. I'll do anything...
to save him.
- Going somewhere?
- Gotta do something.
Good. Let's split up.
Two heads are better than one.
Pick a target.
Nice silk.
Watch out, kid.
Sorry, sir.
"Viewer Discretion Advised"
Ring. My ring.
Got a ring, got the money.
- Thirsty. One shot of liquor.
- Coming right up.
How much?
Hey?
Beans?
Who did this?
My ring. Where is it?
Wow.
Gold belt.
Ooh.
Yes.
Wow.
Thongbai, you're safe.
With all this stuff, I can save you.
Money talks.
Are you playing? Can I join you?
He was cutting up cake
with Lady Nuanlaor here.
Oh. Mapping out the crime scene.
Looks serious.
I won't bother you then.
Lady Rampueng stood to the side.
Here.
Muen Int was across from him.
Thongphiphop.
Sangthong.
Maiphlong.
Thongbai.
Where's the blind spot?
Oh, no.
Kratai, be careful.
Sorry. I didn't mean to.
Did it hit you?
Lucky I dodged it.
Don't make me yell at you.
Kratai, thanks a bunch.
Really.
Clear this up.
"Thank you."
Thank you.
- Hiya.
- Oh?
Wait, wait.
I'm not here to mess with you.
- Just a talk.
- Thief talk?
No, sir.
Hey, hey, hey. Slow down.
Weapon?
"I love you."
An I-love-you gesture.
Think I'm your friend?
Just teasing ya.
Here, here.
- Everything.
- Hey.
I want you to have these.
Once you take them, you just...
accidentally drop the prison keys
and take a walk somewhere.
So long as it's far from the cells.
Jewelry on the desk
and in my bag...
- yours.
- All?
Of course.
Like them?
Real things.
Hmm...wait.
Did you steal them?
Uh...of course not.
I earned money from trades
and bought these.
- Not stolen?
- No, sir. Positive.
So, is this a bribe
to release a prisoner?
I didn't say that.
- Oh...hmm.
- So, how about that?
Well, you came...
just in time, buddy.
- Thank you, sir.
- Okay, okay.
- Put all these back.
- Yeah.
Don't worry.
If you want more, just say so.
No problem.
Khun.
Sir.
Whatchu doing here? Out.
I have to talk to him.
Please let me talk to him.
I need his help.
He has no time for reckless slaves.
And you are aiding a murderer.
- Thongbai is not a murderer.
- Shut up.
Or you want to be thrown out?
Oh, no. No, Phi Jom.
Let go.
There you are, Khun.
I know the truth, sir.
- Sir, Thongbai is not...
- Jom.
Let go of him.
Yes, sir.
Sir.
I can prove Thongbai's innocence.
- Get in.
- Whoa.
Hey.
Bribing an officer
lands you in jail.
Come on. You all do it all the time.
Drop the act.
Hey. Not all the police.
Some are fed up
with the rotten system.
But it starts with you
looking to bend the rules
by bribing officials.
Enough bends and the whole
justice system snaps.
So, who's at fault?
You say I'm the crook.
But you took the jewels
with a smile.
Both you and me, of course.
But today, you are guilty.
Stay in there and cool off.
Hey, you took the bribe.
At least, let me out.
- Where's your evidence?
- What?
- Maiphlong.
- Hey, you're here.
How did you end up here?
My plan failed.
I wanted to bring you out.
Silly me.
Your coming here means
you found Lady Jolie?
Did she confess?
Thongbai. Listen carefully.
She didn't shoot Khun Phra.
Thongbai.
So, this is it.
I will be executed.
Hey, don't give up just yet.
Sangthong is still out there.
He's trying.
Don't give up.
Trust me. He'll save you.
Show me your proof.
Here it is, sir.
I mapped out the crime scene.
Here's where everyone was.
I was here.
Maiphlong.
Muen Int.
Ma'am Jolie.
You.
Miss Rampueng.
Pikun.
Miss Nuanlaor.
Khun Phra lying lifeless here.
Thongbai. He was here.
Sir.
Had he shot Khun Phra,
the bullet would've hit
the cake first.
But you were there.
You knew the cake was intact.
So, the bullet couldn't have been
fired from his direction.
Can you see that, sir?
Thongbai is innocent.
He couldn't have shot Khun Phra.
Will you acquit him, sir?
He's about to be
wrongly executed today.
Will you speak out for him?
This is not proof,
but your recollection.
Not enough to exonerate Thongbai.
Based on what you said,
I could just as easily claim
that he could've shot him
from there
and walked to admire his glory
right here.
But...
he didn't kill
Khun Phra for sure, sir.
If not him, then who?
My investigation
has failed to build
an airtight case, sir.
So, that's why
Thongbai is the murderer.
Dear Khun, please listen to me.
Throughout my investigation,
I've discovered several suspects
with motives.
Thongphiphop, crippled by Khun Phra.
Muen Int, obstructed
in his duties by Khun Phra.
Miss Rampueng, impregnated
with his child.
Ma'am Jolie, dishonored by him.
And even you, sir.
You were demoted
because of Khun Phra.
Hey!
It's the truth, sir.
And the truth is
Thongbai is innocent.
Khun.
I beg you, sir.
Thongbai is innocent.
He swore to me himself.
I swear.
Don't you swear in front of me.
I did you a favor
by listening to you.
No matter what,
Thongbai is executed today.
Jom.
- Yes, sir.
- Take him away.
Yes, sir.
Sir, please.
Whatever you came up with
is nonsense.
No one would believe
the words of a slave.
Sir. Thongbai is truly innocent.
He didn't do it.
- Go.
- Khun.
My friend is innocent.
- Go.
- Khun.
Please help my friend.
I would never harm my friend.
Thongphiphop, wake up.
Son, wake up.
Uh...what's the matter?
Today is the day.
Go watch the man
who killed your father face justice.
Then forgive him,
and ask for forgiveness
for your father, too.
Let it all end.
Forgive him
so your next life won't be bound
by this hatred.
Nothing will go wrong.
Your murderer
will face execution.
Justice will be served.
Don them neatly,
and in order.
How about it, you two?
Do I look the part
for today's promotion?
No matter how you stand, sir,
just impeccable.
You've captured the criminal
in a high-profile case
that has gripped
everyone's attention.
You'll surely be praised
and promoted, sir.
Heh. Very well.
After the execution,
you two will address me as
Khun Int.
Our Father,
who art in heaven,
hallowed be Thy name.
Deliver us from evil.
And if Thongbai is truly innocent,
let the truth be revealed.
Amen.
Thongbai.
Hey, Thongbai.
Eat this. You need your strength.
I snatched this from the guards.
Eat.
No, thanks.
Ow.
You'll die if you don't eat.
Eat, eat.
I'm going to die anyway.
People eat
to survive.
But I'm about to die.
I don't see the point.
You eat it.
Thongbai, you have to eat.
Don't give up yet.
There has to be a way out.
I'm sure help is coming.
Eat.
There is no way out.
No one's coming to save me.
Everyone must strive
for their own justice.
I am but a slave.
My words carry no weight
for anyone to hear.
Born a slave,
destined to die a slave.
I get that.
Guilty or not, it doesn't matter.
They treat us the same.
The harder we struggle,
the harder they stomp us.
Only power rewrites the rules,
wrong to right,
and no one dares to object.
Because we're just slaves,
we don't get the chance
to prove our innocence like they do.
Thanks, buddy.
All my life, I'm grateful
to have you and Sangthong
as friends.
Lady Nuanlaor.
Would you like breakfast?
No.
I'm not hungry.
If you don't eat anything,
you'll be weak.
Help me get dressed today, Champi.
Make me look beautiful.
Are you going out?
Mm-hmm.
May I ask where?
Where I should be.
There has to be a way.
We'll get out of this. Trust me.
Where there's a will,
Thongbai,
there's a way.
Okay?
We'll get out and have a big meal.
Hey.
Whatchu doing?
- Hey.
- Come on.
Let him go.
Whatchu doing?
Stay out of this.
Thongbai...Thongbai.
- Back off.
- You back off.
Where are you taking him?
Thongbai.
It's not the time.
Where're you taking him?
Stop yelling.
Soon, you'll be out to witness
your friend's execution.
Don't worry, I'll let you out.
You can't execute him.
He did nothing wrong.
Your friend is as good as dead.
If you're letting me out,
where's my bag?
And all my belongings?
That's evidence of bribery.
All confiscated. Forget about it.
The truth is, you pocket it
and still preach virtue.
- Pfft. Police scum.
- Ugh.
Hey, you.
Ugh.
Aye...you deserve this.
Whatchu staring at?
Nothing.
Uh.
If you're letting me out,
could you remove these chains?
Oh, yeah.
Sorry about that.
Oh, nothing.
- Stiff.
- Oh, stiff. Okay, okay.
- Huh?
- Nothing.
- Despicable slave.
- You deserve to die.
Scum. You deserve this.
You monster.
- Do it.
- Execute him.
Execute him.
Vile scum.
Only death.
Curse this slave.
Better off dead.
He deserves to die.
Behead the murderer.
Listen up.
Settle down, folks.
That's enough. Step back.
The end is near.
Poor slave about to die.
Meanwhile, I'll soon be
promoted to Khun.
I almost feel sorry for him.
I forgive you, Khun Phra.
- Thongbai. Thongbai.
- Thongbai.
- We're here.
- I'm here.
You're gonna be all right.
After two practice swings,
the third one will be real.
Stop the execution.
Lady Nuanlaor, you're supposed
to be in the palace.
Step back.
Don't interfere,
or you will be punished.
Punished, I will be, anyhow.
Because I'm the one
who killed Khun Phra.
- What?
- Huh?
Mom.
What's going on?
Who knows?
Khun Phra Bamroekrung
came to express the desire
to take your hand in marriage.
Best we're strangers.
Playing hard to get?
One day, she'll be at my feet.
May my exalted wife enter.
But first,
prostrate yourself at my feet.
- Let me have one.
- No. Step off.
I am not yet married to you.
You do not lay your hands on me.
I don't want you
to suffer, Nuanlaor.
It'll all be over soon.
Oh, dear.