This show is a work of fiction.
Any resemblance to actual persons,
living or dead, or real events
is purely coincidental and
not intended to offend any person,
profession, or organization.
I've made you fugitives like me.
Three of us have always been
solid since whenever.
We shared laughter.
How could we leave you in disaster?
Don't think I'm unaware
that you also had
quarrels with him.
Is it the person
you're thinking of?
Yes.
I believe Khun (Nobility title)
Bamrungnakon is the murderer.
Oh, this is a rickshaw.
Whose might this be?
My, it's like a supercar.
"Touch"
Please let me touch.
Wanna touch? Wanna feel?
Don't be so brazen.
This is a gift from the noble Lord
to my master.
"Touch"
Your unworthy hands shall not touch.
And who might he be?
I am.
The Lord honored my rank
elevation with this gift
from Khun to Khun Phra Bamroekrung.
This is one of the five
in existence.
"Number"
There, the serial number.
"003"
Every part...
"Limited edition"
is limited edition.
I admire the brilliance
of a man of status.
Not too close,
lest you mar my rickshaw.
I shall polish it
to a gleam for you.
Goodness, another supercar.
Well, well.
Thought you own
the only rickshaw in town?
The Lord granted me one as well.
But should you notice,
"Number"
mine has a serial number...
002.
Yours are all original parts,
unlike mine.
Your cheap gold ring isn't worth
one of the swag parts
Custom parts, huh?
Too many of those, the rickshaw
could fall apart at your feet.
Are you taunting my rickshaw's
speed and muscle?
It's on.
Me, sir?
Not you, then who?
Me, pulling, and you up there?
- Nonsense.
- Yes, sir.
- Quick.
- Okay.
Take us around, Jom.
The fast needn't overtake.
The furious needn't boast.
But I say...
Easy with the stacks of swags,
Fast it flies, the haters lag.
Go, Jom.
Yes, sir.
Go, Sangthong.
Quickly.
Go.
Yes, sir.
Why does misfortune
always find me?
Go quickly, Jom.
Sangthong, speed up.
Are you trying?
I'm flooring like Vin Diesel, sir.
Speed up at the curve.
Go.
Almost there.
♪ My player's soul
cannot resist love's spell, ♪
♪ My beating heart
submits to you, my belle; ♪
♪ In faith, I now
surrender all to thee, ♪
♪ This wild nature
that you clearly see. ♪
♪ Enchained by love,
these bonds I dare not break, ♪
♪ Though in your hands
my heart you twist and take. ♪
♪ Each day I bow to you,
my heart's reward ♪
♪ Dominate my heart ♪
♪ No one but you shall reign
and be adored ♪
♪ Dominate my heart ♪
"Mystery of the Deadly Sins"
I am not surprised
if Khun Phra Bamroekrung
died at the hands
of Khun Bamrungnakon.
Since I became Khun Phra's entourage,
I'd seen the two locked in fierce competition.
Be it about...
food.
This is mala soup.
A gift from a Chinese tycoon.
Afraid of the spice?
I get it. A mild gent like you
can't handle the burn.
Bland broth.
Brisk, smooth going down.
Ah-hmph.
"Flavorful"
It's full of flavor.
Good for you.
But my tongue...is numb.
Music.
And even...women.
From Khun Bamrungnakon, my lady.
Ahem...
A token of affection from
Khun Phra Bamroekrung.
No matter what,
they'd always been rivals.
Over trivial pursuits?
They can't be a murder motive.
Don't jump to
conclusions just yet.
There's more to it than you think.
What I told you
"Intro"
was just the intro.
And another thing.
They didn't start as rivals
but as...the best of friends.
A friendship turned sour.
Can that even be?
Now, poor Thongbai has to
bear the brunt of it.
Where should I begin?
Ah, listen up.
It began when Khun Bamrungnakon
first met Khun Phra.
"Wild Boar Gang"
Who is the Tua Hia (leader) of
the Wild Boar Gang?
I am the leader.
You barged in, shouting
and annoying me. Who are you?
I am Khun Bamrungnakon,
from the City Department.
I owe no courtesy
to a law-breaking Ang Yi
(Chinese secret society) like you.
What law have I broken?
Selling opium and running
an unregulated opium den.
The law states it's illegal.
Anyone smoking or trading opium
must face three rounds of flogging,
forfeit all property,
bereave of wife and children,
and feed grass to
official elephants.
Citing the law to the letter.
Your demeanor tells me you're
a new official in town.
And so, you don't know
this joint does nothing
against the law.
They buy opium because
smoking it eases their pain.
The pain vanishes after smoking it.
It's no cure.
It only numbs the pain.
Once it wears off, the pain returns.
Heavy dose gets them hooked
and unable to work.
In the end, they'll commit a crime
to afford it.
It disrupts the peace.
How could that be good?
Hey, the fault lies with those
who misuse it, not me.
Don't stand in my way of business.
The world has evolved.
Coarse ruffians like you
won't budge until knocked down.
You are under arrest.
Here, arrest me. Come on.
Oh, sir. There you are.
You suddenly disappeared.
Say, do you know this
Khun blockhead?
Of course, I do.
Why, he's my dearest friend.
Right, buddy?
-Hmm?
- No, I don't know.
What is it?
What's the matter?
See?
Don't say you're sulking
about last night.
Ah, I knew it.
Last night ticked you off.
Come on, buddy.
Well, last night,
we fought over a woman.
I won. He went mad.
Same old habits, old routines.
He just moved to Suwanthani
and must wise up of going-on here.
I hope you won't
hold it against him.
Now, let me take him away
and set him straight.
Big training day, yeah?
Alright, let's go. Walk.
"See you soon"
See you soon.
What did you do?
If I hadn't stepped in,
your guts would've been
all over the floor by now.
If I must die, then so be it.
As a royal official,
I serve the people.
Look.
I commend your courage.
Truly admirable.
Judging by your demeanor,
you must be new here.
Let me tell you in good faith.
Don't throw your life away.
Use prudence. Don't act so bold.
Learn to discern
the situations first.
That way, you won't
die in vain. Okay?
Who are you to lecture me like this?
I'm a Khun, just like you.
Khun Bamroekrung,
under the City Department.
You still have a lot to learn.
If you don't mind,
why not join me at my residence?
Here I am, sir.
High carbs or low, sir?
Whatever.
Come, please.
Let's enjoy this meal.
See if it's to your palate.
If anything, let me know, sir.
It tastes excellent, sir.
What a grand, spacious
residence you own.
And such flavorful food you enjoy.
I assume your fine wife
manages it all.
No, I don't have a wife.
Are you an ascetic type, then?
Not quite.
I've had 99 wives.
Ninety-nine wives?
Mm-hmm.
Figures.
Ahem.
Indeed.
Jealous, are you?
Not at all.
But I've often wondered.
When a man takes many wives,
it's seen as enviable,
as you suggested.
But when a woman takes many husbands,
it's considered disgraceful.
Well, men like us have
wealth and power.
We ensure our women
are well provided for
and lack nothing.
It's only natural.
So a wealthy woman could
have 99 husbands, too?
Well...she could, so long as
her men agree to that.
Certainly not me.
And there it is.
So, is the fault in
being born a woman?
Or is it in men, narrow-minded
and self-centered?
Let's just agree to disagree.
I say we...don't delve into trifle.
No need to quarrel.
Let's eat instead.
So, you're new in town, all alone,
and attempted a head-on arrest
at the Ang Yi den.
You like playing with fire?
Sir, we're serving
as royal officials.
We must be loyal to the kingdom
to ensure the nation's progress.
All for it.
I see.
But you shouldn't have
recklessly stormed in like that.
I'm all ears.
There's a way they,
the Ang Yi, can't anticipate.
"Wild Boar Gang"
My friend's new in town,
so he didn't know who's who.
But I've explained
everything to him.
Last time, I didn't
understand the system here.
My apologies, Tua Hia.
As a token of my heartfelt apology,
a basket of auspicious oranges.
Hey.
We play it cool to build trust
so they'll lower their guard.
Something auspicious.
Eat it, and you'll be prosperous.
If you're ready to befriend me,
I'll gladly overlook
your rookie mistakes.
I've got something
good for you, too.
What's that?
Trusting us, they'll want
to show off their opium.
That's the evidence
to arrest them on the spot.
What's the matter?
I'm in a good mood.
Shall I compose a verse
for the leader?
- Sure.
- Okay?
Go ahead.
So begins the tale of
the opium laced with gold.
A smoke that brings cheer
with no ill will to hold.
A generous Tua Hia, keeping me lit.
A pile of evidence
that proves our wits.
Buy-bust operation is a success.
Evidence, you say?
Uh...huh.
Are you baiting me
with a sting operation?
That's right, Di (little brother).
Sting, ain't it?
Is that so?
Then, here it comes.
Halt.
You're under arrest for trading opium,
a dangerous narcotic.
Get him.
Go.
Hey, hey.
Walk.
Are you alright, sir?
Wake up, wake up.
Enough. It hurts.
I'm fine.
It got the opium bundle.
What a relief.
I thought you were done for.
Why did you have
an opium bundle on you?
Well...it's evidence, you know?
Since we both came,
we get it done like a pro.
- I'm so grateful to you.
- Easy with the hand.
I shouldn't have been
impatient, as you said.
You've gotten hurt because of me.
Hey, don't mention it.
Anyone would've done the same.
Finally, the Wild Boar Gang
was dismantled.
The opium trade was
completely eradicated.
Painter, take this pose.
After that, they were promoted
from Khun to Khun Phra.
And personal rickshaws
as rewards from their superiors.
Take this pose. Ready?
Three, two, one.
- Best friends.
I am Khun Phra Bamroekrung.
I am Khun Phra Bamrungnakon.
- I swear.
- We'll be lifelong friends.
I prepared a fine liquor
for the occasion.
I am deeply moved.
Wait, what are you doing?
For a blood oath.
Hey, do we have to?
Don't we have to?
No need to go that far.
The liquor is enough.
- No? Really?
- Uh-uh.
And so, they became sworn brothers.
From your story, Sangthong,
I fail to see Khun's motivation
to kill Khun Phra.
Exactly, from what you've told me,
these two would've died
for each other.
As the plot thickens,
a turning point is revealed.
Oh...
Ah? Ah?
Know what that means?
- No
- Ow.
What does "turning point" mean?
A turning point means
an irreversible moment of change.
- Care for a visit?
- Stop by, my dear.
- We're here, sir.
- Thanks.
- Dokrak, he's here.
- Oh, Khun Phra.
Hello. Hello.
Suwanthani's staple.
Everyone visits this place.
"Relax"
Relax.
I'm fine.
Yeah. Don't get nervous.
- Inside, sirs.
Boss gets all the fun,
and again leaves me none.
Go easy on him. He's still shy.
Ahem.
- Evening.
- Evening, Phraya Mahapradit.
No need for formalities.
I'm here for the same
pleasures as you all.
Did you receive a reward from the Lord?
Is that the occasion here?
Well, I'm sure you've heard
about dazzling ladies here.
A little.
Khun Bamrungnakon,
you just posted here recently,
yet have taken down
a large opium gang.
You know? Everyone in town is
talking about your arrest.
Team effort, sir.
Khun Phra Bamroekrung helped me.
Hmm.
You two get along very well.
Well, how about this?
Soon, my term will be over.
Would you two run for
city governor in my place?
Uh.
Is that a good idea, sir?
We've just been promoted
not long ago.
Of course, it's a good idea.
If you help govern
the city in my place,
I wouldn't mind.
Okay, sir.
- Nong (Endearment term) Chaba.
- Yes?
Let's go.
Hurry.
I miss you.
Please, have a seat.
Thank you.
Hey.
When his term ends,
you should run for city governor.
It'd suit you.
Someone like me? No way.
You're more suited for it.
Come on. You're bold and reliable.
When the villagers have problems,
you solve them quickly.
They like that.
They need a fast-acting governor.
Nah. You're more suitable.
You tackle problems head-on.
You call out things others avoid.
I think, nowadays, the villagers
would want a governor who's
bold and righteous like you.
Nonsense.
You should run.
You'd definitely win.
- You do it. Don't encourage me.
- You do it.
- You.
My Lord!
Phraya Mahapradit's death
started the chain of events.
His vacant position
needed a new man to rise
and take control.
Such power had broken apart
the two friends.
How did they break?
How did the jar break?
It must be...Kratai.
No throwing shards.
It wasn't me.
Many people are out there.
People are coming?
Quit eating, will you?
Check it out. Get out there.
- Wait for me.
- Hurry up.
The slave from the wanted poster
and his friends came here.
Are you sure they're in here?
You'll be punished otherwise.
I'm sure, sir.
Officers, find them.
- Yes, sir.
We're doomed.
How did they find us?
I'm doomed.
They'll get me for sure.
Thongbai, we'll buy you some time.
You find a hiding spot. Go, go.
Wait, wait. Get our things.
They'll know someone's here.
You go that way, I'll go this way.
Clear?
Wait, Thongbai went that way.
We must hurry.
Oh, where are my glasses?
Sangthong, he's in trouble.
What do we do?
Ouch. Sangthong.
We're here.
Hey, Sangthong.
There you are.
Arrest them.
We've done wrong, sir.
Don't arrest us.
Who are you to give me orders?
We're sorry, sir.
We wouldn't dare give you orders.
We had nowhere to go
but this abandoned temple.
If we return to Khun Phra's estate,
we'll surely be punished.
Please have mercy on us, sir.
You...look up.
Sangthong.
Maiphlong.
Answer me.
where is your friend?
Thongbai disappeared
since the ceremony, sir.
We fled for fear of being captured
by the authorities.
We found this hideout.
Just us, sir.
Sir, we really have nowhere to go.
Please have mercy.
Don't stand there like a dolt.
Arrest them.
Stop.
Don't arrest them.
Why, sir?
I'll take them in at my estate.
But...that is against the law.
They belong to Khun Phra's
descendants, should they not?
You dare defy my order?
I said I would take them.
Any protest?
It is my greatest honor, sir.
I shall follow you
for the rest of my days.
Glory to you, sir.
Now and forever, sir.
- Uh...glory to you, sir.
- Glory...
- Now and forever, sir.
- Now and forever.
- Glory to you, sir.
- Glory...
Why become his slave?
We'd get closer to him
and gather more evidence.
If anything incriminating,
Thongbai might be
cleared of the charges.
Hey, that's clever.
Of course, it is.
What?
We've reached my house.
Thanks, officers, for escorting us.
You're dismissed.
- Yes, sir.
- My Lord.
Bye.
This is my estate.
I allow the two of you to enter.
- Yes, sir.
Wow, this house is huge.
Hey, you heard what he said.
He didn't invite you,
so you're not allowed in.
Then who will I play with?
I'll be so lonely.
Stay with Thongbai for a while.
If anything happens, let me know.
Go on.
Fine,...geez.
What's the hold-up?
Come in.
Yes, sir. Right away.
Jom. Hey, Jom.
Welcome back, sir.
These fools.
I've taken them
from Khun Phra's estate.
Task them.
- Feed and shelter them.
- Yes, sir.
Thank you, sir.
The name's Sangthong.
And this...Maiphlong.
Yeah, I remember your face.
The rickshaw-pulling lad.
After me.
Go ahead.
Wow...roomy.
Look, a queen-sized bed.
Bed? It's a canopy.
You two stay here.
Work begins at dawn.
- Yes.
- Sure.
Be diligent.
Come running to master's call.
He's kind and merciful.
But if you don't behave,
punishment is severe.
Understood?
- Understood.
- Yes.
So fierce.
We survive another day.
But now...
I'm famished.
I haven't eaten all day.
Hungry?
Come here.
Here,...I snatched these
along the way earlier.
Wow, when did you do that?
Just now. Want it or not?
Yes, yes.
Hey, Sangthong.
Does this place feel eerie,
unlike Khun Phra's house?
At first, I thought
there'd be many slaves.
Turns out, there are
only three or four.
Ever since the election for
the new governor began,
this estate has been like this.
Please welcome Khun Phra Bamroekrung,
the first candidate for
the position of governor,
to present his policies.
Louder, louder!
A good man with clean hands
and fine manners.
Number 1,
Khun Phra Bamroekrung.
Thank you.
What are you waiting for?
Cheer, cheer!
Brothers and sisters.
I, Khun Phra Bamroekrung,
grew up here.
I know your joy and grief.
I know what we've all been through.
Hardship and poverty are things
we never wish to face.
I want all of you to be
happier than this.
Happier than this.
The time has come for you
to find happiness.
I, Khun Phra Bamroekrung,
promise here and now
that the livelihood for common folks
and slaves will improve.
Improve our lives.
Slaves will toil for fewer hours
and find more joy in restful hours.
Most importantly, I will
support local industries,
such as...local liquor makers.
- Local liquor.
- Yeah, local liquor.
Please keep Khun Phra Bamroekrung
in your hearts.
- Number 1.
- Yeah. What a sport.
- Khun Phra Bamroekrung.
Here, take one. Take on.
Everyone, come get one.
Spread the word.
Khun Phra, sir.
Thank you so much for
your policies for
local liquor makers.
- Thank you, sir.
- It's nothing.
- Glad to be of help.
- Yes, yes.
Khun Phra, sir.
If you become the city governor,
will you abolish the law
forcing hundreds of workers
into liquor factories?
If so, a small maker
like me can thrive.
Uh...yes, yes.
Promise me, sir.
Promise, sir.
Yes, I promise.
Once I'm elected, yeah?
I must go to see my friends.
Vote for me.
Khun Phra Bamroekrung, number 1.
Number 1, okay?
- Yes, sir.
- Help me out.
- Good.
Sangthong.
Tell your brothers, relatives,
slaves, and master,
Khun Phra Bamroekrung, number 1.
Only number 1.
Thought you'd run away.
You know if you compete with me,
you'll end up
losing to me, like always.
Because I knew you'd come
spouting nonsense like this,
I didn't want to waste my time.
But after some thought,
when a dog barks,
if you don't stare it down,
it won't know who's in charge.
Told you many times not to.
Hey, you're next on stage.
Any interesting policies to win votes?
Or is it just empty,
like your hollow head?
Even before you're in power,
you already look down on everyone.
I don't see the man to lead society
coming from you.
Hey...
The kind of man I am is irrelevant.
I hold up the front of
a good person.
The image of the man
they want to see.
That's enough for me to win.
Remember this.
The people don't want
to hear the truth.
They want to hear lies
that give them hope.
But today, you will lose.
Your old tricks can't fool
anyone anymore.
Today...
it's about ideas,
hope,
and a shared vision for the future.
I'll make them see their better lives
so clearly they'll forget
your good-man masquerade.
They'll focus on
the better future ahead.
Dream on.
Hey...
Only fools believe
in your empty hopes.
Just wait and see.
The power doesn't lie in
you or me to decide.
But the people
through their votes.
Let's meet the second candidate
for city governor,
Khun Phra Bamrungnakon, number 2.
With that attitude,
you set out to lose.
Everyone here is of low status,
not by choice,
but by force,
even though we're
all born as equals.
Why must there be masters,
those who place themselves
above us,
and press us into
a lower class for life?
I, too, was of the lower class.
Through hard work,
I rose to become Khun Phra.
Seared in my heart is
that same pain you endure.
My candidate make empty promises.
Higher wages.
Thriving market.
But has anyone recognized the truth
that the core problem is inequality.
Slaves carry out hard labor
for absurdly poor livelihoods
because the masters
take cuts from their wages.
They abuse them
and unjustly exploit them.
Their income through
trade are seized.
All because they're slaves.
But today...
everyone deserves a better life.
Choose me as the city governor
and I'll ensure Suwanthani
has no slaves.
Suwanthani has controlled slaves
for generations.
The royal laws are written as such.
Do not speak of what is impossible.
Everyone will live as free individuals
no longer bound by class divisions.
I promise
no one will have to be
a slave ever again.
Slavery ends now.
Free the slaves.
No more slaves.
No slaves. No slaves.
No slaves!
to drugs.
His policy is a disaster, sir.
I take pride in being a slave.
Slave no more.
No more slaves.
I'll tell you.
Today is one of the proudest days
of my life.
I revealed my heart to the people.
It is important.
- At first,...
- Yes, sir.
No one applauded for me.
But after my speech,
the applause was thunderous.
Truly, sir.
This old woman, at first,
glared at me
as if she wanted to kill me.
But in the end, she brought me
a cart full of fruits and produce.
Down there.
Make sure everyone gets some.
Really, sir?
You will for sure become
the governor, sir.
What's going on outside?
Check it out.
Yes, sir.
- What is it, sir?
- Is Khun Phra Bamrungnakon here?
- He is, sir.
- There is a royal decree.
Alright.
Soldiers are here, sir.
- Who's here, Jom?
- Soldiers, sir.
Why are they here?
I don't know, sir.
Was he arrested? On what charge?
For earning public favor
through speech?
Khun Phra Bamroekrung
relayed to the palace,
stating Khun Phra Bamrungnakon
plotted treason,
seeking to change the royal law
and abolish
the abiding system of slavery.
Khun Phra Bamrungnakon
was to be executed.
But due to his past merits,
the death penalty was commuted.
Instead, his property was seized,
his rank stripped,
and he was demoted from
Khun Phra to merely Khun
from then on.
Why is he like this?
- Vile scoundrel.
- Horrible man.
- A wretch.
- He's a hopeless trash.
Wicked man.
"Disloyal"
Banish him. Get him out.
- Drive him out.
- Get out.
A wretch.
You ungrateful, arrogant fool.
Banish him.
Do not follow his example.
- Get out.
After that,
the governor's election was canceled.
Khun Phra Bamroekrung was
appointed as the new governor.
Close friends became bitter enemies.
All for power.
If it were me, I wouldn't
have let it slide.
I would've shot him that very day.
Hmm?
What did you say?
I said I would have shot him
that very day.
Ah, I agree with you.
Khun Bamrungnakon had the chance
to shoot Khun Phra that day,
and many other chances.
Why wait until the wedding day?
Yeah.
Hey, perhaps...
Khun Bamrungnakon didn't shot him?
What you said gave me
a second thought.
Well, if you're unsure,
I'll force a confession out of him.
That'll settle it.
What?
You're always so quick
to use force.
If you do that, you'll be punished
and thrown in jail.
Who will uncover the truth?
All this mystery
makes my head hurt.
I'm in no mood to eat.
Let's hit the sack.
But in Khun Bamrungnakon's house,
we could investigate further
and find something crucial.
Alright then.
Let's go to sleep.
You guys should sleep now.
Uh,...thank you.
Goodnight, Phi Jom.
What's with his yelling?
- Here, put it away.
- Okay.
Hey, pretty good pillow.
Wake up, wake up.
Don't make me mad.
Get up already.
- I'm getting up.
- I'm up.
Get off me so I can get up.
No more sleeping.
Get up.
Fill the buckets with water.
Sangthong, follow me upstairs
to clean Khun's room later.
- You...
- Yes.
water the plants.
- Got it.
He's riding on us.
I couldn't sleep at all.
First day, I get to clean
Khun Bamrungnakon's room.
Hey, Sangthong.
Khun may be testing your loyalty.
Don't worry. I'll be careful.
Don't forget why we're here.
Why are we here?
Wait...why are we here?
Water the plants well.
You're so slow.
Here...Khun Bamrungnakon's room.
Make it sparkly clean.
Come on.
Do a good job.
I must go for something.
I'll come back to check.
Yes, sir, Phi Jom.
Ugh,...there's nothing.
Nothing but this box is locked.
Whatcha doing here?
Eavesdropping.
I wanted to know what you found.
They could've seen you
and we'd be in trouble.
Come in.
Did you open the door
because you found something?
I was right to follow you.
Do you know this is a special lock?
Imported from the West.
Made of steel, with brass
and bronze mechanisms.
Guaranteed, unpickable.
Gosh.
I hate to say it,
but I can pick it.
Do it.
Et voilà.
That easy?
It's just a regular lock, isn't it?
You don't believe me?
It's a special lock.
Don't believe me?
Here, I wasn't bragging.
Try it yourself.
Why lock it again?
I want to see inside.
Because you think you can
pick it yourself. Go ahead.
- Maiphlong.
- What?
Why did I befriend you?
Oh, Maiphlong, help me.
Help Thongbai, please.
The most majestic lock-picker
in the world.
Yeah? Yeah?
- Most supreme in the universe.
- Quit your flattery.
Okay, I'll do it again.
Done. Easy as pie.
Open it.
This is the gun.
The same one used to
shoot Khun Phra.
So Khun Bamrungnakon
did shoot Khun Phra.
Abused power makes
people bow in fear,
not respect.
I'll find a way to get close
to Khun Bamrungnakon
and extract a confession from him.
Before I came to you,
Sangthong and I found a gun
in Khun Bamrungnakon's room.
This means he killed Khun Phra.
I am free of the crime. I'm free.
Who do we have here?
Khun Bamrungnakon himself.
An honor for you to visit
my humble little distillery.