[English subtitles are available]
Yun, read this one.
[Darn Tainan First Senior High School]
[I'd like to know who is the boss of your school, the principal or the chair of the parent association.]
[Let me be clear,]
[I just wonder if the school can stop the teacher from being bullied.]
[Do you mean Ms. Xie?]
[Not surprisingly, the rich are the worst.]
[Don't you know the principal is the chairwoman's watchdog?]
[Rumor is, slapping is the chair's best.]
[Watch out for being sued. Hehe.]
Between you and me,
[Xinyi]
did you post it?
Am I so bored?
And how could things between me and her
be resolved so easily?
That's right.
[Lesson in Love Episode 6]
[Ms. Chen]
I won't hand in this phone.
So I can contact you at any time.
Stop! Why running?
[Private Tainan First Senior High School]
Collect yourself first.
Before you get in.
Oh, my!
You're so heavy.
Come down!
What's your problem?
What brought you and Shuqi together?
I told her I like her.
Where was I then?
I stood you up.
Hey, what do you want to say?
Why are you shushing?
Not yet.
What do you mean?
What were you doing that day?
Tell me.
Let's go.
OK.
[Zhang Yixiang: I won't hand in this phone. So I can contact you at any time.]
I didn't expect the way you look
in casual clothes.
Don't be embarrassed to praise me.
Miss Chen, let's go.
What?
The meeting is about to begin.
Isn't it about enrollment of Grade 13?
Didn't you receive the notice?
The theme was changed.
Students and teachers of Grades 11 and 12 are required to be present.
Let's go. Hurry up.
[Lecture on power oppression in unequal romantic relationships]
Fellow students.
An equal relationship
includes power, identity and status.
More than these, of course.
The love affair
in a special relationship
is our focus today.
For example,
the most common office romance.
And
teacher-student love.
Fellow students,
do you secretly fall in love with your teacher?
Just kidding. I don't think you do.
You may say that
teacher-student love is romantic.
What's wrong with it?
How can teacher-student love
be unequal?
Everyone, please think it over.
Is your score determined by your teacher?
Yes. Right?
In this case,
you two won't
be equal.
This relationship
can even constitute
sexual harassment.
Not only girls
but also boys will be molested.
Everyone,
male teachers may harass female students.
Female teachers may also harass male students.
Right.
So, remember to protect yourself.
Thank you.
Thank Ms. Lyu for her wonderful speech.
Dear students, is there anything you'd like to share?
No.
What about our teachers?
Any personal experience is welcome.
No.
Miss Chen Mengyun.
Aren't you also a tutor?
Among all of your students,
is there anyone
who has the experience
of being molested by the teacher?
Would you like to share it with us?
Come on.
OK. Everyone, let's welcome Miss Chen.
Miss Chen, does any of your students
have such a problem?
I'm just a part-time tutor.
I have no story
to share with everyone.
Thank you.
Well,
let me share a case
from the Internet with you.
A student
said his teacher often asked him out alone
after class.
They met
in the activity room
or tutoring room.
The teacher told him to
help him with his study
or have a pep talk with him.
After a simulated exam, the teacher even
asked him to meet outside school.
They went cycling in the park,
went rock climbing,
and grabbed plush toys.
The student started to feel a little confused.
He thought he was not treated
as a student.
The teacher seemed to think of him
as her boyfriend.
Your mom means
you and Miss Chen, right?
Fellow students,
do you think
this is a normal relationship between lovers?
Or as Ms. Lyu just said,
the teacher forced
the student to date him.
Miss Chen Mengyun,
what do you think?
As a teacher,
do you approve of the teacher's behaviors?
She seduced the student.
Do you think
she is qualified to be a teacher?
[Someone took dating photos of a teacher and a student of our school]
Last time you said I framed her.
Now, with so much evidence,
what do you say?
How dare we said that?
Well...
this time, we will
handle it properly.
Everyone,
you probably already knew what happened.
In my opinion,
these photos
can only show
Miss Chen and Zhang Yixiang
met in private.
If we just conclude
they're in love only based on these photos,
it will be...
a little far-fetched.
And as we can see,
due to the shooting angle
of these photos,
they seem...
to be
very close.
A teacher and a student
met outside in private.
Don't you think it's inappropriate?
It's unavoidable.
In the same school district,
maybe they'll meet
after school.
If this had happened to me,
instead of a young female teacher,
I would've been sued by the girl student.
I saw them alone in the Western Pastry Room
once.
Zhang Yixiang is a member of the club
and Miss Chen is the adviser.
It's normal for her to be there.
Remember,
they kissed in school
at the beginning of the semester.
We have
talked about this, haven't we?
Zhang Yixiang
was messing with Miss Chen.
So I think
Miss Chen is very kind.
Despite being tricked repeatedly,
she is still nice to him.
If it were me, I wouldn't care about him.
Unlike me,
Miss Chen tutored him and even went sightseeing with him
when he got first place in the exam.
Miss Chen is indeed
our role model.
Everyone,
we should learn from Miss Chen.
Mr. Yan,
we're colleagues,
don't be so mean.
I was praising Miss Chen,
wasn't I?
Well, let's do it this way.
Everyone,
shall we listen to
Miss Chen first?
OK. I agree.
We should give Miss Chen
a chance to explain herself.
Miss Chen.
Defend yourself.
[C'MON PLAY UF]
Isn't the chairwoman awesome?
She knows everything.
What are you doing?
Are you sure
your mom didn't put a monitor on you?
The monitor should be on you.
Not on me. I'm not a snitch.
Not on me.
I got it. You idiot.
Your mom may have someone watching you.
Or how could she know everything?
Xia Yuxin,
am I right?
Hand in your mobile phone.
Yuxin, please.
Yuxin, your mobile phone.
Please hand in your mobile phone.
OK.
Your mobile phone.
Thank you.
Hand in your mobile phone, everyone.
Your mobile phone, please.
Great.
See, our accounts.
We all block your mom.
But she knows
what we do every time.
Hey.
Why are you here?
Ah?
It's a self-study class,
so it's not a big deal we skipped the class.
What about you?
Language and Literature.
Language and Literature class.
Then why are you here?
Did his mom send you here?
No.
-Where is the monitor?
-No monitor on me.
-It's not me.
-Take it out. Hurry up.
It was changed to the self-study class.
You just said it's a Language and Literature class.
Listen to me.
Miss Chen went to the Education Conference,
so it was changed.
It's true.
Stop. What do you want to do?
What do they want to do with Miss Chen?
Will she be fired?
Why?
Just because of what my mom said.
You're back early today. No night self-study?
Wow.
Surprised? Xie Shufen.
You already knew.
Haven't your spy told you
everything about me in school?
Change your shoes.
I just mopped the floor today.
Who is he?
Wash your hands and get ready for dinner.
I'm asking you who he is.
What did you do to our son?
And what did you do?
I did nothing.
Right, because you did nothing,
I have to be the bad cop.
Look at them for yourself.
Where did you get the photos?
You followed him.
No.
You sent someone to follow him.
That's right.
I did send someone. So what?
Darling, you've gone too far.
What do you mean by that?
You can...
Make it clear before you say something.
Do you know...
Your son and his teacher...
Try to talk nicely to him.
But you made someone follow him.
He didn't tell me...
[I won't hand in this phone. So I can contact you at any time.]
Anyhow, you shouldn't
send someone to follow him.
[Zhang Yixiang]
Are you all right?
I didn't know that my mom would ask someone to follow us
or that she would say those words during the meeting.
I have no idea about the photos.
I'm sorry.
May I give you a call?
It's so late. Where have you been?
Have you eaten?
If not,
let me cook something for you.
What do you want to eat?
Let me get you something to eat.
I know what you're going through.
I've been there.
I know the feeling of love.
I'm not trying to stop you
from getting a girlfriend.
But there are so many girls.
Can't you date one of your age?
Do you have to date
a woman so much older than you?
I'm not asking for your love advice.
If I told you
I liked my teacher too,
do you still not listen to my advice?
I used to have a crush on
one of my teachers.
It happened when I was in college.
Unlike other guys,
he seemed to be elegant and chivalrous.
But actually,
he was defiant.
Anyway,
I really liked him.
Many of my girl classmates also adore him.
But he treated me differently.
In his eyes, I was different.
At least, I thought so.
You and he...
Did you go out on a date?
But later I knew
he had already married
and had a kid.
So you didn't know.
If I had known,
I wouldn't have been with him.
I really liked him.
I longed for
the happy days to come.
I dreamed
we would get married
and live happily
together forever.
We would…
For him, I even…
Mom,
Miss Chen
is different.
She has never…
I mean
it's me
who ran after her.
You're still young.
She's an adult
and a teacher.
Her responsibility is
to lead you on the right path
and teach you to distinguish right from wrong,
instead of dating you.
Zhang Yixiang,
you're my son.
Protecting you
is my duty.
I won't let you get hurt
as I did.
Miss Chen is different.
She is not that type.
She will never cheat me
or hurt me.
I will never cheat you
or hurt you.
That's what my teacher told me,
but he still hurt me.
Yixiang, breakfast is ready.
I'll pass.
He doesn't want to eat. Don't force him.
Do you want me to wrap it up for you? You can eat it on your way.
Yes.
OK.
I'll eat it on my way.
Take it.
Go.
Did you poison our son?
What? I'm not finished yet.
Wanna continue?
Aren't you afraid of being poisoned?
What's new about yesterday's Education Conference?
If they ask you to quit,
don't listen to them.
What the chairwoman did is really despicable.
She washed your face in public.
I believe she was afraid
that firing you would irritate the board.
She didn't want her father-in-law to know
what Zhang Yixiang did,
so she just started by forcing you to quit.
What kind of person
would hire a private detective to tail her son?
Do you think it's a private detective?
What else could it be?
Some teachers of our school
do like flatter parents and the chairwoman, and snitch on others.
But I don't think they would sneak photos.
As for students,
their phones are taken away after the morning self-learning.
It can't be them.
Hey.
What are you looking for? Can I help you?
I thought you wouldn't come today.
I'm here to tell you
that I will never come again.
You've improved a lot in the recent mock exam of Language and Literature..
I don't need to teach you anymore.
Did the school's Education Conference punish you yesterday?
It's none of your business.
I'll tell the principal that you were forced by me.
If you really want to help me,
just don't do anything.
Otherwise, things will get worse.
Then… What about the phone for kids?
Can I still message you with it?
Teacher, my stomach is aching. I need to relieve myself.
All right. Hurry back!
Thanks.
Hey.
When is Xia Yuxin's birthday?
What's up?
Is today her birthday?
If today is her birthday, why would I ask you?
Do you know?
Well, what do you want to do?
None of your business. Just tell me if you know.
What are you talking?
Would you like to speak up and chat with others?
Xu Shuqi, what did you just hide?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Hasn't the school talked about it many times?
During the night self-study,
you can't use your phone.
Come on. Give it to me.
Give your phone to me.
I'll keep it for you.
When the night self-study is over, I'll return it to you.
The night self-study is coming to an end. Hang in there.
Carry on.
OK.
It's all your fault.
Sorry.
Mr. Li, my phone.
Next time…
Xu Shuqi!
Give it back to me!
No!
Are you a spy?
Give it back to me.
I saw you sneak photos of Miss Chen and Zhang Yixiang
outside the classroom for baking many times.
Hey. Did Zhang Yixiang's mom ask you to sneak photos?
Or it upset you that he was in love with Miss Chen
so you snitched on them?
I said give it back to me! Don't you understand?
No! I won't give it back to you unless you tell me.
No!
Did you take those photos?
Did Yixiang attend today's night self-study?
[Did Yixiang attend today's night self-study?]
[Zhang Yixiang]
Your call will be forwarded to voice mail.
Please leave a message after the beep.
I went to pick you up from school before.
I saw you getting on a bus,
but the bus was not going in the direction of our house.
I was curious, so I followed you.
Sorry.
Can I have a word with Miss Chen?
Since Yixiang attended high school,
he has never finished top in the school's mock exams.
He always comes second.
This time, with your guidance,
he finished top.
I haven't expressed my gratitude to you yet.
Sorry, it's my bad.
Chairwoman, don't mention it.
Zhang Yixiang worked hard.
It has nothing to do with me.
Miss Chen, you're too modest.
All right. Mom, I'll go back with you.
No rush. I'm not finished yet.
What on earth do you want to do?
I just want to express my gratitude to Miss Chen.
Miss Chen.
Are you free this weekend?
Come to our house. Let's have a meal together.
My teacher is busy.
OK.
Do you still feel sick?
Do you feel dizzy?
All right.
Yun.
You felt sick just now, didn't you?
Why did you begin to play with toys as soon as you arrived home?
Go wash your hands now!
OK.
After dinner, do your homework first.
I thought Yun had classes all day today.
She felt sick in the middle of the P.E. class.
The teacher called me,
so I took her home.
She felt sick?
Yeah.
Then what about your piano class?
I'll just take a leave this afternoon.
Don't you have class this afternoon?
You usually have lunch at the school canteen.
Why did you suddenly come home?
I suddenly had a headache,
so I wanted to take a rest at home.
I felt sick as our daughter did.
There's a special bond between father and child.
All right. Do you feel better now?
Are you going back to school this afternoon?
Yeah.
I took a snap. Now I feel better.
I'll go back to school soon.
Yun and me haven't eaten anything yet.
I want to cook noodles. Let's eat together.
It's OK. I'll pass. I'm not hungry.
OK.
Yun.
What's up?
Put your schoolbag in your room before having lunch.
OK.
Hurry up.
Mom!
What's going on?
Madam.
Excuse me. I'm here to hand in my report to my teacher.
Is he here?
How did you come in just now?
It seems that I haven't heard the doorbell.
I knocked on the door just now.
Yun opened the door for me.
Shize, is this your student?
Mr. Chen.
Didn't I tell you to put it in the department office?
I couldn't find the teaching assistant, and I thought
I don't have a class this afternoon.
Maybe I could give it to you by myself.
Thanks.
I gotta go.
OK.
Bye, Mr. Chen.
Bye, madam.
Bye.
What?
It was weird that my mom invited you.
But it was weirder that you came here.
The chairwoman invited me in person.
How could I refuse to come?
I cooked a few simple dishes.
Hope you don't mind, Miss Chen.
They're not simple.
The food I eat alone is really simple.
Alone?
Miss Chen, you're not married?
I believe you already know.
There's no need to ask.
How could I know Miss Chen's personal affairs?
Come on. Try the soup.
You even know how many times the principal fart
a day,
so you don't need to ask her about that.
His father and I have spoiled him,
so he's rude while speaking.
Mr. Zhang is not here?
Yes, he went to play basketball. Don't wait for him.
Let's eat.
Miss Chen, your parents don't live in Taipei?
My parents are gone.
I've got no family besides my grandma.
She's not used to Taipei, so she lives in the countryside.
But you told me you've got an aunt, right?
The chairwoman was asking about my family.
She's just a relative.
You're so clear about
her relatives.
Miss Chen, do you always treat students
in this way?
Which way?
In my spare time, I chat with students
to learn more about them.
Probably, my father has influenced me.
He's a teacher, too.
After classes,
his students often come to our house.
Your father is also a teacher?
He's a professor. He teaches art.
My mom majored in art, too.
Chairwoman, where did you graduate from?
Huaqing, right?
Is it your dad's school?
Yes, they're schoolmates.
They were from different departments.
What a coincidence!
Maybe the chairwoman really knows my father.
My father is a teacher there.
Really?
What's the name of your father, Miss Chen?
Chen Shize.
I can't remember.
I don't remember this teacher of our department.
I wish I could say I don't remember, either.
He's not my father anymore.
He had an affair with his student. They murdered my mom.
But you told me they had a car accident.
Yixiang, don't be so rude.
You brought up Miss Chen's painful memory.
Sorry, Miss Chen.
So did you see
your father's student later?
Yes.
But she said she couldn't remember.
She even forgot his name.
A woman doesn't even remember the man she loved.
She probably strung my father along.
Then she forgot everything.
However, she doesn't know
that she has ruined my family and my life.
When a teacher falls in love with a student,
the one who forgets after the relationship is over
is usually not the student.
I thought the soup would taste good.
However, it's bland.
Yixiang, there's no salt left.
Go downstairs to buy a bottle of salt.
Miss Chen is talking about her family.
Yeah.
It's a little bland.
It would be better if you added some salt.
OK.
I'll be right back.
Miss Chen.
Ssh.
Hi, madame.
I'm here to hand in my report to my teacher.
Is he here?
Bye, Mr. Chen.
Bye, madam.
When did you find out?
Chairwoman, now you remember who my father is.
I'm so sorry. I misunderstood you just now.
Many years have passed,
but you never forget about him.
As his daughter, I should feel delighted.
This is a warning for you. Stay away from Zhang Yixiang.
So you're worried that Zhang Yixiang
and the whole school will know
that you were a home-wrecker.
Is that the reason why you always single me out
and try your best to kick me out?
Seriously?
I wondered
what kind of teacher would be so warm-hearted
that she only picked some thankless jobs to do
and she even taught her student in spare time.
So before you started to work at the school,
you made a plan.
You deliberately seduced Zhang Yixiang
to retaliate against me.
Don't think that everyone is as shameless
as you.
No one is more shameless
than your family.
As a teacher, you seduced your student.
No wonder you're his daughter.
You killed my parents!
You knew he had got a family and a kid.
Why did you try to get close to him?
Wait a minute.
Here's a correction.
You're more like your mother.
When she saw your father bring me home,
she looked exactly
like you.
There are many kinds of salt.
I don't know which one I should buy.
Miss Chen, are you leaving?
What did you say to Miss Chen?
Zhang Yixiang!
Don't go, Zhang Yixiang!
What did my mom say to you?
Did she tell you what happened between her and her teacher?
Listen. Don't be mad.
Her teacher lied to her.
Her teacher said he didn't have a girlfriend.
However, she was already married.
My mom fell into his trap.
Do you believe everything your mom says?
Then can you tell me
what's going on?
You deliberately seduced Zhang Yixiang
to retaliate against me.
As a teacher, you seduced your student.
No wonder you're his daughter.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
My home
or a motel.