♫  I wonder what is love  ♫
♫  I want to know what is love  ♫
Cheers to the first night in the house.
It's good.
What? What? What?
Door's open.
Door's closed.
What are you doing here?
And you?
I was just... stopping by.
I just... stopped by, too.
How did you get in?
I got the password earlier.
Oh, the password.
You could've just passed by. Why come in?
I was passing by and...
passing by...
and they had this.
I wanted to eat it.
Have you had dinner?
Aren't you hungry?
You just stopped by as well.
How about some soju?
Do you want a shot?
Do you want some snacks?
Nope.
Have some soju at least.
What brings you here at this hour?
Do I have to tell you?
No.
This is so unfair.
I have to tell you, but you don't?
By the way...
What's up with the luggage?
What?
You traveled to get tteokbokki?
Excuse me.
Get out if you're not going to talk.
All right.
I happened to have been here for a while.
And it's been less than an hour.
I wasn't planning on this.
It just happened.
No one lives here anyways.
It should stay like that.
I have my reasons.
I know you don't know how to listen.
You're saying you're staying here or something?
I never said that.
I'm only staying here for a bit.
And you played a part in me having no place to stay...
Not a part.
You are the whole reason.
- So?
- So.
So... you can't stop me.
This is the least you can do.
Excuse me.
This isn't how you ask for favors.
It's not your house. Don't be so picky about it.
Anyways, it's a no.
I said no!
And this is my house.
I know it isn't.
What happened last night?
What the heck!
Calm down.
Hey.
Hey, wake up!
What?
You scared me.
You slept here?
Why would you sleep here?
Huh?
You told me to.
When did I tell you that?
You don't remember?
Okay, I'm leaving.
You think I don't have a place to go?
So many people want me.
Just...
Just stay.
You told me to just stay.
Wait a second.
How much did you make me drink?
Who does that nowadays?
Are you pretending that you don't remember?
You told me to stay.
I happen to have no place to go.
I'm staying here for a while.
So please don't just stop by.
You can leave now.
Let me sleep more.
Hey.
Hey, wake up.
What now?
Okay now. I get everything.
Don't let anyone know you're staying here.
Do you think I want to?
You really... messed up the place.
Why did this happen to me?
My star. How was the workout?
You look too comfortable.
Should I wear a suit?
Looks like something's happening.
Hold on.
Hello.
The first solution of "Get It Diet" is boxing.
It's an informative show.
She introduces boxing as a way to lose weight.
Take some rest before we resume.
Okay.
Joon,
let's not run into her.
Let's go.
Joon.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Where's Oh Inhyung?
We're on break. I think she's in the restroom.
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting for the shoot to restart.
You're here alone?
It's important for the company.
The staff—
But you didn't split the staff?
Into who's important and who's not?
It's none of your business.
We don't need to care about each other.
Just because no one's here, doesn't mean you're no one.
Hello.
These are solutions recommended by "Get It Diet." We strive to keep you healthy.
Our first solution is boxing.
Boxing is a workout that burns the most calories in a short amount of time.
Shall we meet the professional who will teach us simple boxing moves you can do at home?
Let's stop here.
Good job, everyone!
JJ, when did you come?
You're here alone?
Without any staff?
Yes.
This was scheduled last minute.
My manager's coming to pick me up later.
Is an unexpected shoot not a shoot?
Huh?
Who made the decision without me?
See you in the next meeting.
You're doing that on purpose.
I'm fine. Let's go.
Get dressed.
Let's go.
What are they saying?
Can you guys handle his true self?
A crazy cat?
An evil duck?
Me? That's me?
That's so mean.
I never thought people would call me a crazy cat and an evil duck.
Yes, Mr. Han.
Geunyoung.
We're drinking before the shoot begins.
How about dinner tomorrow?
Who's buying?
I thought you were parking.
Where have you been?
I bought this.
Is it for me?
Today's not even our anniversary. What the heck!
The hoodie was too big on you earlier.
Artists in my company should wear clothes that suit them.
When did you buy it?
I don't even remember.
You don't even remember?
No.
It's been so long.
Just because no one's here, doesn't mean you're no one.
Let's throw it away then.
Where is it?
I'll throw it away on the way out.
What is it?
Why?
My father told me this.
You have to know what to get rid of if you want to be successful.
I thought you wanted success.
Then you have to get rid of...
clothes that don't suit you.
Okay?
Don't be sarcastic.
What's bothering you now?
If you didn't lie to me in the first place, I'd never do this.
Okay?
Got it?
Joon.
Get some rest.
I'm fine.
Bye.
I meant to throw it away.
You don't have a trash can?
You came all the way here?
You know.
Some rude bastard threw this cheap thing away at someone else's house.
And it was yours?
I didn't need it.
Why don't you take it if you need it?
No, thanks.
You take care of it.
You would feel bad if your old clothes can't be recycled and become trash.
You know I get over those things quickly.
And you're quite good at picking up after my trash.
You've grown a lot.
You shouldn't care about what I picked up.
Don't act like you still own it.
I also picked up a doll on the street.
I wanted to give it back if the owner came around.
But he didn't. So what do I do?
I just have to play with it.
Hit me.
Take care of your trash.
After you left, Jaejoon came.
I never should've shown myself yesterday.
Why?
Did he see something?
And he went crazy over it?
I'm not too sure.
I think Inhyung... is in trouble.
Just keep walking next time.
Joon,
it can never be undone.
Okay?
Geunyoung.
I'll have a beer.
Okay, a beer.
Look around.
The place is called Dowon.
Like the place where Liu Bei, Guan Yu, and Zhang Fei swore their brotherhood.  (T/N: Romance of the Three Kingdomes, the three friends took an oath to become sworn brothers)
Let's do something similar.
Say "one" when I say "we are."
We are.
Do it for him.
- One!
- One.
One.
We're in the same boat now.
Let's drink.
Again?
Sure.
Cheers.
My goodness.  Here it comes.
Take a shot?
Of course.
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
♫  Which star are you from? Did you open my heart?  ♫
♫  How did you get in my heart?  ♫
♫  Shall I take a step closer? Shall I be brave?  ♫
♫  I'm around you again today  ♫
♫  Which star are you from? Did you open my heart?  ♫
Should we open one more bottle?
Okay!
You don't have ask.
Let's go to another spot.
♪ Say that you suck ♪
♪ You're rude! ♪
♪  Lee Geunyoung is... ♪
♪  ...very confident! ♪
♪  Keep looking at me ♪
♪  I'm shy ♪
♪ Shut up baby, Shut up baby  ♪
♪ Cheer up a bit more ♪
We're done!
It's finally over.
I told you earlier. I'm not good at variety shows.
So I'm worried a bit.
There's no such thing nowadays.
You just have to be yourself.
Of course.
I like you when you're drunk.
You're just saying that, huh?
No.
What about you? You can't lie.
Me?
I... hate sucking up to people.
And I really mean what I said.
Come on.
I know you guys will be great.
You can show me the show before it airs, right?
Sure.
Let's take another.
Cheers!
Nobody would notice if I walked out right now.
I'm not a big star like Hoo Joon.
And I don't have a huge role.
I'm just his anti-fan.
Can I sing another?
The mic is yours today.
♪  Fill me up with love ♪
♪  I think my battery is out ♪
♪  I can't live without you ♪
♪  I really can't ♪
♪  You're my battery ♪
♪  I think I'm running low on love dosage ♪
♪  I'm low ♪
♪  How lonely was I in those days ♪
♪ One day, two days... ♪
♪  When I faced the truth ♪
♪  With all my love... ♪
♪  I only take... ♪
♪  You're not the sun... ♪
♪  Don't think you're the center... ♪
- ♪  You can't do whatever you like ♪
- Don't do it.
Sing it together!
♪  I-I-I-I-I always do ♪
♪ Damn... ♪
I'm sorry.
Geunyoung.
You're here.
Here.
I heard Hoo Joon's here.
You're with him?
Yes.
Together.
You're doing the show.
I read the news.
Yes.
I wanted to fight him head on but...
He must've done something.
You're wearing heels.
Hit him again with them.
Maybe I should.
I told you.
Some people in this world cheer for you.
And I'm probably the most famous out of them.
By the way...
that really cheers me up.
I guess fans do help celebs when they're sad.
You can't be like this.
You already understand how celebs feel?
No way.
I told you not to worry.
I did drink a lot but I'm fine.
I'm not a kid.
Yes.
This is my number.
I got a celeb's number.
Save it.
All right.
Go home if you're drunk.
What are you doing here?
Who told you I'm drunk?
You're not in a real relationship to worry about her.
Only we decide... what relationship we have.
Geunyoung,
the top star is being mean again.
That's because he's an attention seeker.
He thinks he's the main character of everyone's life.
A total jerk.
What?
Want to join?
Or... are you worried about her or something?
That I might pick up what you throw away again?
Watch your mouth, Jaejoon.
Then don't look at me like that.
Geunyoung.
See you later.
Thanks for this.
You need to pay me back.
Take care.
Bye.
He's such a nice person.
How do you know him?
I won't tell you.
I should see you off but our taxi's here so we're leaving.
Goodbye.
So.
Goodbye, top star of the universe.
Where do you think you're going?
You're drunk. Let me get a cab.
I'm not drunk.
I don't want any more news about us.
I can just take the subway.
Don't joke with me.
I'm not even drunk!
Please just listen to me.
I got it.
Stay still, please.
I'm sorry. Just a second.
I've worked out so hard at the gym.
Is she heavy or am I weak?
Ouch.
Come on.
Okay, we're here.
We're here.
Please don't throw up.
Please don't throw up, okay?
She's for real.
Come on.
Wow, she's walking.
She wasn't sleeping.
Wow.
My back.
Lee Geunyoung.
Wow.
I'd better not have problems when I dance.
Let me ask you a question.
How...
do you know Jaejoon?
Huh?
You keep ignoring me.
Come on.
Don't take this the wrong way.
I'm trying to make it hot for you.
So that you sweat while you sleep.
♪ Fill me up with your love ♪
♪ My battery is out ♪
Thank you.
She's fast asleep.
It's so messy.
Then don't...
look at me like that.
Come on.
Please just don't throw up.
I hope I didn't throw up.
Did I?
Hello?
Geunyoung.
Who's this?
It's me, JJ.
Did you get home all right?
Oh.
The coffee?
Thanks for the coffee.
Do you want to pay me back for the coffee?
Sure. I will.
But...
does it have to be coffee?
Hello.
Did you wait long?
Not at all.
Can a celeb walk around like this?
Oh.
I run a company now.
You like hangover soup?
Of course, I do.
I wouldn't be here today if it weren't for this place.
I came here all the time when I was a journalist.
The soup here does it all.
It's not that you don't eat it, right?
No, I like it.
I also have a hangover.
Why? Something wrong?
Someone is giving me a hard time.
I want to hit him with a heel.
You should've told me.
I should have.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
Do this.
Your recipe?
Yes.
Enjoy!
Did you save my number?
Of course.
I'm not saved as "nobody," right?
Of course not.
It's Jaejoon.
Choi Jaejoon.
Just call me by my name.
Don't call me JJ.
That's funny.
Right.
I'll just call you by your name then.
Mr. Jaejoon.
Much better.
Hey!
You got yourself mixed up with Jaejoon?
What are you talking about?
He called me.
And told me to take good care of you.
Your career is over if you're caught drooling over someone else's girl.
And he said I'd lose money if that happens to you.
So?
You've really changed.
(Literally says: he's lost a lot of teeth.)
You're overly excited over what he said.
Why didn't you put effort into other stars?
So that you'll be well off without me.
I can't sleep because I worry about what the company will do without me.
You're not the only one who cares.
I can't even sit on the toilet because I constantly worry about your image, you brat!
Sir, he has a schedule.
Let's go.
Hey.
You...
Bye, bro.
Sir.
Are you constipated?
You just said you can't sit on...
No, I'm fine.
Yes.
The shoot is tomorrow and I don't know a thing.
Let's party after your shoot.
Okay.
I'll call you after I'm done.
Ma'am? Geunyoung is here.
You're here early.
As if you were waiting nearby.
I was nearby.
But...
you really dressed comfortably, huh?
Come in.
The staff will be here soon so we have to get you ready.
What the...
Wow, baby.
You look so pretty with makeup.
As if!
Who's this?
Isn't she too pretty?
Amazing.
You two look good together now.
It's a virtual marriage.
So we'll go with the wedding shoot.
Okay.
Let's do something more with the set, Geunyoung.
More than this?
Let's go. Geunyoung's set.
What are you doing?
Any problems?
You have to...
Bride.
- Bridegroom. You ready?
- Yes.
Yes.
- You too?
- Yes.
Yeah, camera!
I'm going.
Okay, good.
It hurts so little this way.
Okay.
Oh, yeah!  I like that.
That's what I'm talking about.
Bullets with love. Let's go.
Bullet of love fired!
That's good. Don't hold it.
Hold your hands.
Okay.
Let's do this.
Ah, it's okay.
Good! Now the other way.
Ouch.
Okay, good.
Okay.
You thought it was easy, huh?
Like this?
- Perfect.
- I like it so much.
You're so good at it.
As if you're killing each other.
That hurts.
That's it.
Look. You're going for a drive this time.
But...
Geunyoung is driving.
Huh?
She'll be okay with it?
You have a license, right?
I do have one.
Okay!
Then let's go right away.
Let's go with the next action scene.
It's only 100 meters so don't worry.
Geunyoung... Geunyoung?
- Huh?
- Are you okay?
Tell him you can't do it.
I'm fine.
It's just a little bit, right?
Everyone will have to work more if I don't.
I can do it.
You're a professional already.
Way to go.
A famous racer said,
"Driving is about pure instincts."
Are you done? Get in.
You can do it!
I guess you don't want to get hurt.
Of course, that's how you would be.
That's the most human thing you've done so far.
Shut your mouth.
What about the seatbelt?
Let's take it off since it's a simple shoot.
Okay?
Cameras are rolling.
Shall we?
Shoot.
Let's go!
One, two, three.
Shall we...
start the car, Geunyoung?
He's trying to put on a show.
I'll drive safely.
Okay. Let's go.
That was more dynamic than we thought.
We like it like that.
Geunyoung, hold on.  You're going a bit fast.
Stop!
Wait a minute.
Slower!
Wait!
Stop it!
Hurry up and stop!
Stop! Brake!
That's the gas!
Stop now!
We're going to crash!
Wait!
- What do I do?
- Hit the brake!
Stop now!
Stop!
Wait!
BRAKE!
♫  Which star are you from?   ♫
♫  Did you open my heart?  ♫
♫  How did you get in my heart?  ♫
♫  Shall I take a step closer?  ♫
♫  Shall I be brave?  ♫
♫  I'm around you again today  ♫
Cut!
Are you guys okay? You're not hurt?
I got confused between the brake and gas.
Shut up.
I'm...
sorry but I...
I said shut up.
Are you okay?
Geunyoung, are you okay?
At least she put on the brake.
You must be startled.
Don't let her drive ever again.
I said I'll put on the seatbelt.
It's my lifeline. Don't you know that?
To be honest,
I never driven a car before.
I tried to tell you earlier...
You did a good job!
Right.
After 13 years of not cooking a pigeon, I almost cooked two people.
They're fine.
Geunyoung, get out.
We'll take a break.
Let's clean this up.
Oh my god!
She has a thing for shocking people.
Make sure his face is okay.
What?
You're not hurt.
Joon, have some water.
I'm sorry, could you give us some time?
Let's go.
You must be startled.
You didn't see, right?
What?
Never mind.
There were three.
Joon.
What?
You okay?
No.
I'm not okay.
Number one and three.
It's 100 percent.
He must be really startled.
It was an accident.
A car accident.
A minor collision.
Why him?
Geunyoung, are you okay?
Yes.
Is something on your lips?
Are you just washing your face?
Man, that feels good.
Weird way of washing her face.
Here, Geunyoung.
Come sit over here for a second.
Um...
There was...
a small accident.
I think we got good footage.
Let's call it a day.
Just one interview for you, Geunyoung.
Okay.
Good job, everyone.
Thank you.
Good job.
Sorry about earlier.
Why did you hide your closet license?
Were you trying to kill me?
I would have died, too. You saw how scared I was. I was surprised, too.
You're one to talk.
You think I wasn't surprised? I didn't think they'd touch.
Shut up.
Don't act all selfless in front of me.
Huh?
Anyway, you've been revealed.
What will I do about him?
Are you nervous?
Huh?
Don't be nervous.
Be yourself in interviews.
Okay.
How did you feel when you first got the offer?
You didn't like it, right?
Of course, I didn't.
To be honest,
Hoo Joon and I...
did have issues.
So why did you decide to do it?
How should I put it...
It was like homework that I never finished.
It didn't sit right.
That's why.
Then how was the first shoot today?
Uncomfortable.
Will the accident air, too?
I don't think it should.
Will it?
What is this?
They said only the smell of feet remains.
What's happening?
It's surely nice to be
in a sauna.
I love it.
It's so cold.
Let's see.
Nobody texted me.
I know I made a mistake but...
how can he say that?
Other motives?
Revealed?
I wouldn't want a truck full of you.
You look like a wildcat.
Why do people say he's nice?
Right.
I'll get down to your duplicity.
You'll be amazed.
Hoo Joon's duplicity.
There's a lot.
Number one.
He says "Shut up" when he's angry.
You don't know how it feels unless he does it to you.
Hey!
You're hurt. What happened?
Who's the producer?
We rented a house to shoot.
Why go somewhere and get hurt?
Why do this in the first place?
It'll all benefit us in the end.
Of course, it will.
Not sure about who though.
Joon, by the way...
I bought the house.
It's your house after the shoot.
Why are you doing this?
Are you worried I might get in trouble?
It's for real this time.
I should change the producer.
That's fine.
It was just a small collision.
Oh yeah?
Then let's sign the paper after the meeting.
Okay? Okay?
He's so rude.
(Lit: I'm dirty, not sure if I should be a singer or not)
You're here.
- Hello.
- Hello, Hoo Joon.
This is Choi Hwajin, the director.
Nice to meet you.
Have a seat.
Director, you look so nice.
It's only for the show.
He never smiles.
Number three.
What?
Don't you know the password?
What the?
It's for security.
I told you to check it.
Let's go in.
Let's see.
We can set the camera...
in the living room and the kitchen.
I'm sorry.
It's nice to work more.
I'll get to it.
Mr. Choi?
How about one on the veranda?
That's nice.
Okay.
On the veranda...
I told them to keep the doors closed.
Mr. Jong!
Yes.
You didn't lock up.
We'll get in trouble for this.
You locked it?
Yes.
There you go.
Let's go now.
How about you treat us.
- Me?
- How about...
...beef?
Thank you for the food.
Did they really lock it?
It's locked?
Who'd come here to the 15th floor?
There's no neighbor.
Who should I call?
911?
Don't let anyone know you live here.
How about Mijeong?
You sure you're at a friend's place?
He's not stopping by today?
I need to use the bathroom.
Okay.
The manager said to call if I need something.
I need something more than ever.
Don't think about me and just do what you...
He's been gone a while.
It must be important.
Excuse me,
can I take this?
Of course.
Thank you.
Please, save me.
♫   I'm your Pop Star  ♫
♫  Oh yeah, eh  ♫
♫  Remember, I'm always your one and only one  ♫
♫  So that you can hear me all night long  ♫
♫  Oh, every day, every time, if you can hear me  ♫
♫  I'll sing  ♫
You'd better not do anything weird to our Joon.
Everyone's on Hoo Joon's side.
You trust his staff?
Call emergency...
I made you lonely.
I know.
Did Hoo Joon always keep so many secrets?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Roy.
It's my first time sitting in for someone.
Do you two knew each other?
♫   Where the light shines when I open my eyes   ♫
♫   I'll be standing right there   ♫