♪Yes, I see the sunshine everywhere♪
♪Happiness floats above the city♪
♪The new century comes like a dream♪
♪Making me feel warm♪
♪Is your old pocket watch still ticking♪
♪Can your old leather shoes still be worn♪
♪Here's a Future brand cigarette♪
♪Don't you want to try it♪
♪Oh, this is so good♪
♪Come on, Pentium computers♪
♪Let them do the thinking for me♪
♪Wear new clothes, get a new haircut♪
♪Relax a bit with Windows 98♪
♪Dress up pretty♪
♪The age of 18 is paradise♪
♪Our life is as sweet as sugar♪
♪Wear new clothes, get a new haircut♪
♪Relax a bit with Windows 98♪
♪On the journey ahead♪
♪There will be no more pain♪
♪Our future will be so cool♪
=Reopen My Journals=
=Episode 1=
Congratulations to our champion!
Dahua has defended his title
for three weeks.
(Digital Challenge Arena)
The big prize is waiting for you.
Looking forward
to your performance next week.
Thank you so much.
Alright, see you next week.
Join Digital Challenge Arena,
be the winner of life.
At the end of today's show,
we'll draw a lucky viewer.
Who could it be?
Let's find out together.
This lucky person is from Putuo District.
- Putuo! Our Putuo.
- Putuo District.
Putuo District, huh?
Puyang New Village.
That's us!
That's our New Village!
Could it be us?
Wang Shuocun!
Congratulations!
The lucky prize…
It's Section Chief Wang's son.
He seems so plain
and can't speak clearly,
always whispering.
Section Chief Wang's son.
How is he so lucky?
Sometimes,
luck can be hereditary.
Everyone in the factory knows
Chief Wang is lucky.
Why didn't your luck
as a union leader
pass to me?
Jiayue,
here's your letter.
Okay.
Do you know
what I, Liao Dongmei
have relied on
in my whole life?
Luck?
Please.
It's all about my strength!
Well, I'm lucky
to have a capable mom
like you.
What's happening?
Stop overreacting, girl.
Puyang No. 2 Middle School!
I have to call your dad.
I'll get Brother Xiao Han.
Ask him to come eat.
Okay.
Brother Xiao Han.
- Brother Xiao Han
- Jiayue, Jiayue.
Granny Zhao.
Hello.
Looking for your Brother Xiao Han?
Brother Xiao Han,
are you home?
Brother Xiao Han?
Xiaoying, hanging laundry?
Hello, Director Zhao.
Hello, hello.
Don't forget to pick up your oil
from the community center later.
Okay, sure.
(Mao Tou's Home - Idle People Keep Away)
Brother Xiao Han.
Mao Tou.
(Puyang New Village)
(Puyang Road)
Great shot!
Beautiful!
Nice shot!
Brother Xiao Han.
- Jiayue.
- Sister Jiayue.
Congrats on getting in!
Yes, congrats, Jiayue!
How did you all know?
Your mom told everyone.
She was louder than the speaker.
Not just Workers' New Village,
I think the whole universe knows.
Director Zhao, Director Jia,
see you.
- Alright, alright.
- I'll inform you
when the date is set.
Do you all know?
My daughter, Qian Jiayue,
got into No. 2 Middle School.
Congrats!
Your daughter got
into No. 2.
How did you know?
We heard it
from a great distance.
Join us for our celebration.
Love to.
- Everyone knows, right?
- Of course.
- Sure.
- Well done, Qian Jiayue.
Amazing, Qian Jiayue!
Jiayue, congrats.
Good job, Jiayue.
Mao Tou, are you still playing?
- Come on.
- Quick!
Qian Jiayue,
you did great!
Congratulations!
I'm heading back.
Brother Xiao Han,
Granny said tonight…
I know.
Dinner at your's tonight.
Your mom told me.
Hurry, Xiao Han.
She already told you.
Nice shot!
One more, one more!
Ka Men.
You startled me!
You walk like a cat!
Where are those two?
Still playing.
Mao Tou asked me
to bring his backpack back.
What's wrong with you?
You look upset.
Didn't you already
get the admission letter?
It's because of my mom.
Jiayue,
congratulations!
Thanks, Auntie.
Come in.
See?
Don't you think
my mom's annoying?
She's been hollering around.
Now the whole world knows
I got into No. 2 Middle School.
On the street,
everyone was smiling at me.
You're upset
because she told Xiao Han first.
Does it matter who told him?
It matters.
Four years ago,
I was two points short
of getting into the No. 2 Middle School.
I worked so hard for four years
just to be at the same school as him.
Now that I've finally made it,
I should be the one to tell him.
Boss Lady, forty wontons, please.
Xiu'e, you startled me.
Forty, huh?
Let me finish tallying this first.
What's up?
Why are you so close?
Just wanted to take a good look
at your expression,
and see if you're happy
or not today.
Are you crazy?
Stop doing that.
Wait here.
I'll get your wontons.
You look unhappy.
Aiping.
Sit here, Aiping.
What's going on?
Aiping, listen to me.
My daughter Qian Jiayue
got her admission letter
to No. 2 Middle School.
Jiayue got in?
Congratulations!
Keep it low-key.
Looking at Pei's face,
her daughter Ka Men
didn't get into No. 2, right?
We've been friends for years.
Should I just lay low?
Xiu'e.
- Actually…
- Aiping.
One mung bean soup.
Okay, have a seat.
Okay.
Sister Huang,
a bowl of mung bean soup!
Got it.
Xiu'e.
- Actually, Pei…
- Yes, yes.
Actually, her Ka Men really
can't compare
to my Jiayue, right?
My baby aimed for No. 2,
and Ka Men aimed for it too.
But it isn't just for anyone.
It's No. 2 Middle School,
a model school,
and a key school.
Not everyone can get in.
Aiping,
do you think
I should invite Pei
to the celebration?
If I do,
it'll just remind her
of her disappointment.
That's not good either.
You startled me.
You're upset.
I'm just speaking the truth.
Come on.
Actually, Ka Men is also excellent.
Ka Men. Ka Men.
A terrible name!
It's a nickname from kids.
Why are you calling it too?
Is it that hard to get in?
Is it really that special?
Xiao Han got a direct admission,
and I didn't hear
Aiping bragging
like you.
She's upset
because Ka Men didn't get in.
See?
What's this?
I can't see it.
Can you read it for me?
No. 2 Middle School admission letter.
Whose is it?
(Admission Letter of
Shanghai Puyang No. 2 Middle School)
Liu Wanqing,
you've been admitted…
Wang Shuangpei!
- Are you teasing me?
- She got in.
Why didn't you tell me?
You said Qing wouldn't make it.
- She did!
- You should tell me.
Why didn't you tell me?
All three of them got in.
Don't crumple it.
(Admission Letter)
I'll tell Baby the news.
You and Brother Xiao Han also got
into No. 2.
Your mom and Xiao Han's mom
(Qian Jiayue)
didn't brag about it.
Only she did.
This is so embarrassing.
Relax.
After the summer break,
you'll go to school
and come home every day
with your Brother Xiao Han.
I have a feeling
that for the next three years,
I'll be abandoned by you
and be all alone.
Only Jeff Chang will stay with me.
What nonsense are you saying?
I'm not talking nonsense.
I feel like
this secret base of yours
won't even have space
for Mao Tou soon.
Brother Xiao Han.
Jiayue.
Go inside.
Mao Tou,
what did you do this time?
Nothing.
Are you sure?
You said you'd do homework
after basketball
but went to the arcade instead,
playing Street Fighter
and even gambling.
What did you promise last time?
No more gambling or no allowance.
Give me the money.
Don't, please.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Hurry, let go.
- I won't.
- Let go.
Jiayue, don't do this!
- You can't do this, Jiayue.
- It's my lunch money.
Lunch money?
Granny said
your dad's on a business trip
this week.
You have all meals at my house.
(Ten yuan)
Tenner for you.
I'll hold the rest
until Uncle gets back.
It is too little!
Shut it.
I'm heading out now.
You're leaving?
Wait for me.
We're leaving now.
Give me my money back.
No way.
Why are you walking so fast?
I'm tactful.
I'm not as clueless
as Mao Tou.
By the way,
you said your mom would
buy you a computer
if you got into No. 2 Middle School?
Once you get it,
Xiao Han doesn't need to go
to Mao Tou's new house
at Jinxiu Garden.
He can use yours instead.
Let's go for a stroll at Xidian Mall
to celebrate the acceptance
of both of us.
It's to celebrate
you getting a computer.
Same thing.
It's a celebration.
(Yingmo Community)
(Puyang New Village)
Granny,
I'm back!
You're back.
Granny,
I bought some Butterfly crisps for you
at the entrance.
Butterfly crisp?
Let me see!
Here.
You bought a lot!
I'll try one.
How is it? Does it taste like before?
Delicious. Thank you so much,
my good girl.
What are you two eating?
Butterfly crisp.
Baby, give me one.
I want to try it too.
Mom,
why did you tell everyone
about my entering No. 2?
It's good news.
Of course, I want to share it
and make everyone happy!
Coming!
- Godmother.
- Mao Tou.
- Auntie.
- Xiao Han.
Hurry, wash up and get ready to eat.
Why are you wearing my shoes?
They're all the same.
Mao Tou!
Did you wash your hands?
You scared me.
Baby, don't scare him.
Youngsters are growing.
They get hungry easily.
Granny,
you don't know.
He played games and gambled today.
Playing games and gambling?
Mao Tou, I warn you
so you can't do that.
Relax, Jiayue.
I've already told Mao Tou off.
If he stops gambling,
we might consider
giving his money back.
I didn't say yes.
By the way, Mao Tou,
I need to use your computer
in the morning.
I need to type up a document.
No problem.
Brother Xiao Han,
actually, I'll soon
have a computer too.
You can use mine
in the future.
It'll be closer
than going to Mao Tou's house
at Jinxiu Garden.
That's great. Thanks in advance.
Brother Xiao Han,
I've finished
the Writing Collection.
I'll go get it for you,
I might forget later.
Okay.
I saved a lot of time,
since you got a computer.
Jiayue,
come here.
Granny,
I bought some Butterfly crisps for you
at the entrance.
- Here.
- You bought a lot!
I'll try one.
Mom! Mom!
What's wrong, Baby?
You read my diary again, right?
I didn't!
You definitely did.
The hair I placed inside is gone.
Hair? Oh dear,
hair is so light.
It might've
floated away
or fallen somewhere.
The key is not in the right place.
Baby, why are you guarding against me
like I'm a thief?
Uncle Qian.
- Your dad's back.
- I'm back.
Let's eat first.
Xiao Han, you're here.
Godfather.
Mao Tou.
Such a feast today.
What's the occasion?
I'll be right back.
I forgot to tell him.
Honey,
Baby got into No. 2 Middle School.
Her admission letter arrived today.
Really?
That's amazing.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Come on, mom.
Didn't you say you've called dad?
Everyone else knows
except him!
This is fantastic!
Your mom
gets carried away
no matter what she does.
I did it on purpose.
I meant to do it.
I wanted to surprise Qian Kang.
Are you surprised, honey?
So surprised.
Jiayue,
I'm thinking…
Baby,
Director Dong watched you grow up,
and I haven't told him
the good news yet.
I'll give him a call.
Finish eating first!
Let's talk after dinner.
Come on.
Let's congratulate Jiayue
on getting into No. 2 Middle School.
And congrats to Xiao Han too.
- Yes, yes.
- Come on, come on.
You're so amazing, Baby!
- Cheers.
Baby,
you and Xiao Han got
into No. 2 Middle School.
We're really so happy!
What do you wish for?
Granny will grant it.
I have three wishes.
The first one is
that I hope once I start high school,
no one will read my diary anymore.
Godmother,
what did Sister Jiayue write this time?
Me? Read her diary?
I didn't.
- No, no.
- Baby,
don't worry.
Granny will keep an eye on it for you.
Thank you, Granny.
Jiayue, what's your second wish?
The second one is
that I hope no one in our family
tries to take advantage of others
and gets looked down upon.
I'm heading out!
Chen Xiu'e,
you haven't been paid
for the forty wontons yet.
Wang Shuangpei,
I'll treat you the lobster
and big crabs
at Fuguilou Restaurant.
And you still want money
for those wontons?
So stingy. I'm leaving.
Why are you looking at me?
I swear
I'm generous.
Baby got into No. 2 Middle School.
I promised the neighbors
I'd treat them
at Fuguilou Restaurant.
I'm the most generous person.
- Why would they look down on me?
- Alright.
I just said what I want to say.
What's your third wish?
My third wish.
You all know it.
Mom,
you promised me.
Promised what?
It was during the New Year,
you promised me.
You said
if I got into No. 2 Middle School,
you'd buy me
a computer like Mao Tou's.
Xiu'e, you promised Jiayue a computer.
Baby,
I really don't
remember that.
I do.
Godmother said that.
You were sitting exactly
where Godfather's now,
and said if Sister Jiayue gets
into No. 2 Middle School,
let alone a computer,
you'd even pluck the moon
from the sky for her.
That does sound like her.
I think I remember too.
A computer is expensive.
You can't just decide to buy it
like this.
Then you shouldn't
make a promise so easily.
Stop causing a scene.
Baby,
let's hold off on the computer.
Make another wish.
Whatever you say,
I will make it happen, okay?
How about a trip to Yangzhou?
Didn't you want to visit Yangzhou?
Yangzhou?
When did I ever say that?
That was something I wrote
in my diary last year.
You again.
Sister Jiayue, seems like you'll still
need to use my computer.
Yes, use his.
We're all family.
No need to be shy.
Am I right, Mao Tou?
What was my second wish again?
Don't take advantage of others.
Who wants rice?
A bowl for Mao Tou.
One bowl is enough.
God-grandma, Godfather,
Godmother, we are leaving.
Alright, Mao Tou,
remember your homework.
Thank you, Auntie.
I'm heading back now.
Okay, come here
for dinner tomorrow.
Sure.
Brother Xiao Han,
the chicken soup.
Oh, right.
Thanks.
I'm off.
- Bye.
Goodbye.
(Jiale Wontons)
Unbelievable.
Why was business so good today?
All the pork wontons sold out.
Should we
buy more pork tomorrow?
Qing, you should go to bed.
Did you finish all the vegetables today?
Yes, all gone.
What about the meat?
That's gone too.
Liu Songming.
I think we mustn't buy
too much pork tomorrow.
- What if it doesn't sell out?
- Sure.
If we run out,
just ask Gu to deliver some.
Alright.
Mom,
look at Jiayue's mom.
She's so happy that Jiayue got
into No. 2.
I also got into No. 2,
but you and dad didn't
even say anything.
What do you expect us to say?
Remember,
you're studying for yourself,
not for me or dad.
If you study well,
the one who benefits is you.
Understand?
Who's calling?
Jiayue.
Qing is here.
I'll answer it upstairs.
She's going upstairs.
Wait a moment.
Mom, I've picked it up.
You can hang up.
Hello, Jiayue.
My mom won't buy me a computer.
Really? But wasn't it agreed?
You know how she is.
She never
keeps her word.
It's not the first time.
Forget it.
The computer's quite pricey.
It's understandable.
But it's not like I even asked for it!
She promised it herself.
At least your parents
hold a celebration for you.
Mine didn't even say anything.
She holds that
for her own face.
I don't want to go.
Alright.
Xiao Han is going, and you are not?
Honestly,
when do you plan on telling him?
I…
Baby,
I peeled an apple for you.
Want a bite?
No.
I'm already going to bed.
I clearly heard you on the phone.
What are you doing?
It's a bit dusty.
I'm cleaning it.
Don't eavesdrop on my calls.
Your mom did it again?
It's her again.
Baby,
don't worry.
Bad people are already
taken care of by me.
Mom, you're back.
Did you have dinner?
Yes, I did.
Why does it smell like glue here?
This afternoon,
I helped a friend with a model.
There's some chicken soup
from Jiayue's Granny.
I'll go heat it up.
Han, don't bother.
I'll heat it myself.
Go do your homework.
Okay, I will.
Come out.
It's in the pot.
Alright.
Han, I just bought celery and pork.
Later, I'll make some dumplings
and freeze them for you.
Eat them if you're hungry.
Okay.
What's wrong?
The pen leaked on my clothes.
Leave it in the bathroom.
I'll wash it.
It's alright, I'll do it myself.
Han,
does your pen always leak?
Wasn't the prize
for your first place
a pen?
Why aren't you using it?
It's okay.
This one still works.
(Speech Contest First Prize)
What would you wish for?
Granny will grant your wish.
A computer is expensive.
You can't just decide to buy it
like this.
Want some?
If not, forget it.
Humph.
All of you
act like spoiled kids.
Xiu'e,
how about we buy Jiayue
a computer?
That's easy for you to say.
I've already checked.
Do you know how much a computer costs?
I'd have to work for a year
without spending a dime,
and still need to
add money to buy it.
Maybe borrow a bit from mom?
We can pay her back later.
Worst case,
I'll drive a few more trips,
and we will manage.
Anyone,
but her,
I need my dignity.
You know
how she treated me before.
Forget about her.
Come on,
eat up.
Really?
I promised to reward you.
Hurry, change clothes.
(Keji Yuelian Computer Store)
Baby, let's go.
Qiu, heading to work?
Is this your daughter?
She's changed so much.
- Auntie.
- She's got in No. 2.
Do you know that school?
It's a model school.
Sister, you're really lucky.
Oh, your good fortune is ahead!
You go ahead.
- I'm seeing a friend.
- See you.
Mom,
why did you bring me to the mall?
Weren't we going to buy a computer?
Baby, I'll get you some clothes first.
The sales reps here
are all friends of mine.
We'll just say hi.
Sis!
- Mom.
- This one…
Baby, come, come.
This one is nice.
It looks good on you.
Look in the mirror.
Such a graceful young lady.
Everything looks good on her.
My daughter isn't just graceful
and pretty.
She's smart too.
Just entered No. 2 as well.
You know that?
The model school
and key school.
That's so impressive.
Clearly, you raise her so well.
You're a good mom.
So, Madam,
since she got into No. 2,
this outfit is perfect
for registration day.
(220 yuan)
Sixty yuan.
Madam,
it's priced at 220 yuan.
This is a mall,
not the Qipu Road.
You drive a hard bargain.
I also work at this mall.
I know
the rules.
Don't you recognize me?
I know Manager Cai.
Call him out.
I'll talk to him.
You work here?
Where do you work?
I sell thermal underwear
on the third floor.
So, I know
how the discounts work here.
You come to me next time.
I'll give you a discount.
Since you know Manager Cai,
I'll give you the employee price.
70 percent off,
just pay me 140 yuan.
You are not sincere.
140? Are you serious?
Fine, let's compromise.
I'll add ten more.
70, okay?
- Mom.
- Madam, it's…
I don't want this dress.
I'll go change it.
Baby.
Take another look.
Does this one look good?
This dress is nice.
That's
how you bargain.
You stay quiet, okay?
So, what do you think?
Here's the deal, Madam.
I'll give you a final price,
120 yuan.
No, no, 120 is too expensive.
- Madam.
- There are so many cheap dresses,
but I want this one.
Okay then, Madam.
- How about this one?
- I'm really satisfied
(Yami)
with these two clothes.
They're so pretty.
When you wear this
in registration day,
everyone will see
you're beautiful like a princess.
Then why would you bargain with her
for so long.
It was so embarrassing.
How so?
My money doesn't fall
from the sky.
I work 12 hours a day as a sales rep.
This is how I make my living.
Baby, dig in.
We'll head home when you're done,
and show your dad the new dress.
We're going home after this?
You've had the burger
and new clothes,
of course we're going home.
But didn't you say
we were gonna buy a computer?
Baby,
I said
I'd reward you.
This is the reward,
and this too.
Baby, I've asked your dad
to take time off.
Then we'll go to Yangzhou.
How about it?
Baby, as for the computer,
once you get into college,
I'll buy it for you.
I'm a woman of my word.
If you don't believe me,
let's make a pinky promise.
Come on, pinky promise.
Let's do it.
Fine. Eat more.
Granny, I'm home.
Welcome back.
Baby, don't be upset, okay?
No computer?
You lied to her again.
I didn't lie to her.
I gave her rewards.
What kind of reward is that?
What's wrong with them?
They're really nice.
Baby.
Baby,
don't get upset.
If your mom won't buy you a computer,
I knew a way.
I'll call your uncles
and tell them to get it for you.
Mom, stop messing around.
I don't want their money.
Baby, don't worry.
I'm not like your mom,
who breaks promises.
Always stir things up.
Baby,
your mom's gone to her room.
I'm coming in.
Granny,
I'm fine.
Let me ask you.
What are you doing later?
Any plans?
What about Mao Tou
and Xiao Han?
Qian Jiayue.
What?
When we head back,
you can go to the secret base.
Why?
Treasure hunt.
What treasure?
You'll know when you get there.
Here, have a popsicle each.
Thank you, Granny.
Thanks, Granny.
Here.
Thanks, God-grandma.
(Wonton shop payday)
Hope we didn't lose money
this month.
What's wrong?
What happened?
It's about the computer, right?
Computers are really expensive.
How did you know
it's because of the computer?
Qing said it yesterday.
She tells everyone but not me.
What's the point in telling you?
You never keep your word.
I never keep my word?
I told her I'd reward her.
I bought her two new dresses.
Both look so nice.
Dresses? Come on.
Can dresses compare to a computer?
A computer
costs thousands, really pricey.
Do you know how much
we're spending now?
For our family of three,
I only give my mom 500 for meals.
I already feel guilty.
We needed to pay
for Baby's extra classes before.
Now she got
into No. 2 Middle School.
I have to treat the neighbors to a meal,
you know, just to be polite.
Nothing comes free,
truly.
Slow down.
Alright, alright.
Let's not dwell on unhappy things.
Jiayue getting into
No. 2 is a good thing.
Don't worry.
Yeah.
I won't chat with you now.
I have to go to work.
Go ahead.
Have you eaten?
Yes, I have.
Don't worry, cheer up.
Slow down.
Aiping is really busy.
Working around the clock.
Look at Aiping,
working so hard,
but never complaining.
You should be content.
I'd rather have
Baby close to me.
Would you trade places
with Aiping?
Her husband
died,
and she lost her job.
The whole family depends on her.
She works for me during the day,
then at night,
she works as a nanny.
Would you do it?
Mrs. Guan, take one meatball.
That's enough for me.
Enjoy your meal.
Alright.
Aiping.
It's me.
Coming.
Pei.
Isn't Han home?
He's not home.
He's out for computer.
Kids nowadays love computers.
I can't see what's so fun about it.
Here, take this.
It's extra from the shop tonight.
It won't sell tomorrow.
Cook it for Han.
Thank you so much.
Don't say that.
You didn't come
just to deliver wontons, did you?
- Come in.
- No, no.
Speaking of, I'm so angry.
That Chen Xiu'e
who came to the shop and spoke nonsense.
I totally forgot
today's the 15th,
the payday.
Well, today's double happiness
for me then.
If you say it like that,
it might be triple happiness.
This is from Chen Xiu'e for Han.
Take it.
Xiu'e buys shoes for Han every year.
But now,
they've got other needs to fill.
I can't accept this.
No need to feel awkward.
This is stuff for disposal.
And the quality
is quite poor,
right?
Alright.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
I'll call Xiu'e later.
Just accept it.
Don't forget the wontons.
Pei.
You paid me extra.
My shop is doing well this month.
It's a bonus.
Mom, I'm back.
You're back.
I'll heat up some milk for you.
It's from Jiayue's mom again?
Yes, take a look.
Treasure hunt.
Use it to write your diary.
The old one
can be used as a decoy
for Godmother.
Jiayue.
Brother Xiao Han.
Here.
This is your reward
for getting into No. 2.
This is your prize.
From the speech contest.
It's called a treasure hunt,
but it's not really a treasure.
You can open it.
You don't like the reward
from your mom,
so Mao Tou and I get you one.
So you planned this.
I hope this pen helps you
write the articles you like
in high school.
It's gold!
No, no, this is too expensive.
Accept it.
As long as it is useful,
and of your liking,
it's worth it.
Take it.
(Speech Contest First Prize)
Brother,
did you watch Flower Fairy yesterday?
Jiayue,
don't leave keys outside.
My mom told me
that keys should be kept inside.
Don't let bad guys see them.
I got it, Brother Xiao Han.
See you at the secret base tonight.
I'm off to school.
See you tonight.
(Puyang New Village)
Brother Xiao Han,
do you know why I work so hard
to get into
No. 2 Middle School?
I know.
(End of Episode 1)
I heard those shoes I bought last year
were broken in just a few days.
That's really bad.
It was so embarrassing.
This year's shoes
are of good quality,
I promise.
They're not expensive.
They're stuff for disposal,
just knock-offs.
Thank you.
Are you canceling
the meal in Fuguilou Restaurant.
Cancel?
Why would I cancel?
Jiayue said she won't go.
The main character won't go,
and why are you holding it?
My Baby is sensible.
She might just be saying that.
She won't skip it.
How do you know
she refused to go?
Ka Men told you?
Thanks, Pei. No need to pay me extra.
She actually returned it!
♪Little girl♪
♪You've let your hair grow long♪
♪You've loosened the hand
that tightly held mine♪
♪No longer do you♪
♪Whisper in my ear♪
♪Day by day, you're growing up♪
♪Spring buds sprout♪
♪Summer trees bloom♪
♪Time stops for no one♪
♪Fairy tales fade♪
♪And scars remain♪
♪That♪
♪Is the cost of growing up♪
♪Learn to let go♪
♪Learn to play dumb♪
♪Please♪
♪Learn to answer like a grown-up♪
♪If you have an ordinary life♪
♪Then choose to be open-minded♪
♪Love♪
♪May be the key♪
♪My girl♪
♪You've cut your long hair♪
♪Tears drop from the corner of your eyes♪
♪One day, all alone♪
♪You climbed a high tower♪
♪And saw yourself growing up♪
♪Little girl♪
♪Don't♪
♪Be afraid♪