♪Yes, I see the sunshine everywhere♪
♪Happiness floats above the city♪
♪The new century comes like a dream♪
♪Making me feel warm♪
♪Is your old pocket watch still ticking♪
♪Can your old leather shoes still be worn♪
♪Here's a Future brand cigarette♪
♪Don't you want to try it♪
♪Oh, this is so good♪
♪Come on, Pentium computers♪
♪Let them do the thinking for me♪
♪Wear new clothes, get a new haircut♪
♪Relax a bit with Windows 98♪
♪Dress up pretty♪
♪The age of 18 is paradise♪
♪Our life is as sweet as sugar♪
♪Wear new clothes, get a new haircut♪
♪Relax a bit with Windows 98♪
♪On the journey ahead♪
♪There will be no more pain♪
♪Our future will be so cool♪
=Reopen My Journals=
=Episode 14=
Xiu'e, come on. Have a seat.
Let me give you a massage.
I heard Yang Min
came back.
Zhang Qiming
is pretending to be sick.
Do you think
Yang Min will fall for it?
What's the matter?
Xiu'e,
are you feeling unwell?
I feel a little upset.
It's the 21st century now,
why are they still so backward
and so male-dominated?
I know
you've endured so much these days.
But don't use "backward"
so lightly.
It's not gender bias,
just division of labor.
Women handle housework,
and men work the fields.
It's just how things are.
In the village,
we fought for water and land,
men had to risk their lives.
So, it's fair
to let them rest at home.
In rural areas,
men are the muscle.
Having a man
means more help.
We can't apply city standards
to rural life.
But how come
boys can attend school
and not to work,
while girls must drop out
and work?
Explain it to me.
Who will drop out?
Just now Baby said
your family won't let Jiali
continue her studies.
Your siblings
only let Qian Weihao
to go to college.
For Lin's family,
to pay for both kids to go to college
is too big a burden.
You know, Qian Kang,
I resent how my mom said
it was for my brother,
and forced me
to go to the countryside.
I'll never forgive her in my life.
Xiu'e,
why bring this up again?
If you hadn't come,
you would work at the No. 9 Factory,
you'd be laid off anyway,
right?
You wouldn't have met me.
If you didn't meet me,
how could we have Baby?
What nonsense!
That's just twisted logic.
It's not twisted logic.
I just want you to know
that people have their fate.
Don't overthink it.
What do you mean by fate?
So my mom treats me like that
is what I deserve
and is my fate?
Jiali can't go to school
is good for her
and is her fate,
right?
Let me massage your back.
Don't touch me. So annoying.
Honey,
let's head back early.
Out of sight, out of mind.
Besides, Baby said
she finds it quite boring here.
She wants to celebrate Xiao Han's birthday.
Let's leave on the fifth day.
How can we leave that early?
We agreed on the seventh day!
I say in the fifth day!
I'll get some water,
and give you a foot massage.
(Puyang New Village)
Watch out.
(Jiale Wontons)
I'm sorry
to keep you waiting.
It's alright. Get in.
Okay, okay.
I'm all sweaty from running.
With your condition,
how are you running?
I'm recovering…
recovering well.
The doctor says it's going well.
You can visit the Cancer Support Club.
I read in the newspaper
that many people with cancer
run marathons.
Sir, let's go.
You said you have
stomach cancer?
Which stage is it?
Early stage.
Different places have different terms.
Last time you mentioned
a life-saving medicine,
but it's hard to find,
only available abroad.
What's it called again?
I can buy some and
send it to you.
I don't understand English.
I don't even know my ABC.
I only know pinyin.
You...
Maybe it's Leike or something.
The foreign names are too complex.
I'll check it out later.
So hard to get.
Let me know once you find out.
Alright.
Sir, this isn't the way
to the Civil Affairs Bureau.
Come on, bro.
You're taking me in circles.
I'm gonna file a complaint!
Well...
You guys decide.
The lady told me this way.
Stop yelling.
He's not wrong.
I'm taking you to the hospital.
I have a friend
whose elder brother
is a tumor expert.
I'll take you to see him.
I don't wanna see a doctor.
My doctor
is good.
I trust him greatly.
You're ridiculous.
Come on, Doctor Liu
is truly amazing.
He's the best for stomach cancer
in Shanghai.
His specialist appointment
is impossible to get.
He agreed to see you
for my sake.
It's too sudden!
I didn't bring anything.
My medical records, my CT scans.
What should I say to him?
Prices for spinach?
You are truly ridiculous.
It's okay, just see him,
so he can check your condition.
That's all.
I'm fine!
I'm feel great.
You have cancer.
Cancer is not small stuff.
If the cancer spreads,
you could lose your life.
You're still young.
I won't go.
How about this?
If you don't want
to talk about your condition,
you can talk about other topics.
For example,
the Marriage Law,
how to divide property
after divorce,
anything you like.
When did you figure it out?
Before you got my letter,
I'm already back.
I went back home
to visit my mother,
then went to find you.
At the New Village gate,
I saw you
laughing
with Aiping.
That's when I knew
you weren't sick,
you just want a divorce.
This woman is
quite something.
You set a trap for me
and played me like a fool.
Acting with me yesterday.
I'm cooperating.
You don't need to do that.
You just wanted a divorce.
So did I.
Why pretend to be sick?
I've thought it through.
I'll compensate you.
Take a look at this.
If there's anything to add or change,
just let me know.
Party A: Yang Min.
Party B: Zhang Qiming.
Both Parties reached an agreement
and amicably decided on a divorce.
Party A agrees to give Party B
100,000 yuan in cash as compensation.
As for the 100,000 yuan,
I'll give to you,
sick or not.
I know I owe you and our son too much.
The custody of Child Zhang Yang
(Child issue)
goes to Yang Min.
That's my only request.
Come on, sir,
please pull the car over.
If you are dissatisfied,
feel free to voice them.
Pull over.
Zhang Qiming, stop right there!
What's wrong with you,
huh?
Do you have any shame?
You're fighting me for custody?
I've done everything
to raise him,
being both Mom and Dad.
Now you want to take him?
In your dream.
I'm thinking about our son.
Now you care about him?
Impressive, truly impressive of you.
Impressive indeed!
Sir,
everyone, come and see.
Be our judge.
When our son's five, you went to Japan,
and danced
in a nightclub,
kissing
and hugging.
You forget you had a son then?
When he's seven, he got appendicitis,
writhing in pain,
and crying,
"Where's my mom?"
"Where did she go?"
Where are you then?
Grade 3,
a fatty said he's motherless.
He beat the kid up.
That kid just stands there
while our son crying his heart out.
Where were you then?
Now you want him?
Is there any justice here?
Is it fair?
I came back to see him,
- but you didn't let me.
- Yes.
I didn't let you him,
because you are not worthy.
I know you hate me,
but you can't let that
ruin our son's future.
I'll take him to Japan
and find him a better school,
give him the best education.
I can give him a better life.
The best school, the best education,
a better life.
Now you're talking about money?
Let me tell you.
I've got money too.
I'm wealthy now.
Money's just paper.
I'm going all out today.
Divorce splits the property in half.
Fine, split it.
Everyone fights for pride.
Now, I've got money.
I'm a big boss now.
My son lives well with me.
Go to Japan with you?
You think you're so great?
If he wants to go abroad,
whether it's the USA, Australia, or the UK,
he makes the decision.
I can hang a world map on the wall,
wherever the dart lands,
I'll send him there.
With you in Japan?
Keep dreaming!
Why are you laughing?
I'm not bragging.
Everything I said is true.
The Montagut suits,
two thousand each, I have two.
I usually drive a Benz.
Portman on Nanjing Road?
I talk business there.
Alright, little brother,
enough already.
Go home and talk it out.
This is embarrassing.
What's embarrassing?
Do you know Mr. Bao of Shanghai?
Boss Bao on Huanghe Road.
I do business with him.
I won't talk to you.
I'll call your brother
and give him my address.
Come over tonight and see
our life now.
I don't care what life you're living.
I only want my son.
Goodbye to you.
You're taking him?
Let's go. Let's go.
Hey, sir.
You can take the wallet,
but give me my ID and bank cards.
How much is in here?
Give me two yuan.
I'll take the bus.
Come on.
He only has forty-something yuan.
Don't pretend you're rich.
Flaunting wealth.
Come on.
Blind to the big spender in front of you.
What a fool.
She's trying to fight me for custody.
Let her dream on.
A pipe dream!
Even Buddha values glory.
Every man has his pride.
Aiping, I have decided.
I'll be frank with her.
I'll show her
how well we are living now.
I'll call her in a bit
let her meet at Portman tomorrow.
You all have to help me.
Qiming.
Qiming, calm down.
Sit down first.
Calm yourself.
I...
I am very calm.
Aiping, Han,
you both go tomorrow.
The four of us
will go
all together.
Well,
I have computer training tomorrow.
I can't make it.
Qiming,
I shouldn't go either.
You should talk it out
with Yang Min
calmly and reasonably.
How can I talk to her calmly?
You didn't see her attitude.
"I'm taking my son."
What a joke?
She thinks I will trade my son for money?
Mao Tou, listen.
Don't be fooled by her sweet words
or her sugar-coated promises.
Whatever you want,
just tell me.
Don't miss this opportunity.
I'll fulfill your wishes.
I'm good either way.
You guys decide.
Little imp, you…
Mao Tou.
Be clear with your attitude.
Look at you.
You overreacting.
Am I?
I'm just stating the facts.
(First Canteen)
Mao Tou.
Brother Xiao Han.
Was it Thunderbird
that you were playing?
Show me.
I want to have a go.
This game is
pretty simple.
Just avoid bullets.
This is directions,
and this is attack.
You try.
Let me see.
Well…
so how do I make my plane stronger?
You just
eat the equipment
and it makes you stronger.
You're cutting cucumbers.
The wild ones smell so good,
I can smell them from afar.
You don't get them in Shanghai.
Xiu'e,
let me do it.
Be careful not to cut yourself.
I'll handle it.
Give it to me.
Kang, you're here too.
Such fresh vegetables.
- They're homegrown.
- Later,
stir-fry cucumber with eggs.
I'll make it later.
Alright, you go ahead.
Jiali,
I heard from your aunt…
Jiali.
- Kang.
- Sister.
Jiali,
your brother only has
one white school uniform.
Look, it's all stained!
Now I have to buy him a new one.
Such a troublemaker.
Jiali is quite good.
It's New Year's,
don't scold her.
Kang,
she's grown up now,
and can't even wash
her brother's clothes properly.
Wash it again.
No need to put on it.
Just drape it like this.
More impressive this way.
Look,
we can be on TV.
♪Waves surge and flow♪
♪The vast river never rests♪
Right?
You don't know how foolish
I looked before.
I thought Yang Min felt sorry for us
and gave 100,000 without hesitation.
Now I get it.
In her heart, only worth 100,000.
I gathered a bunch of documents.
I'll take them to Portman later
and show her everything.
Who's there?
Coming!
Aiping.
Great to see you!
I knew you'd come.
Listen,
I bought perfume.
Let's spray some on
before we go to Portman.
It'll cloud her senses.
Let me spray some on you.
Qiming, hold on.
I'm not here to go with you.
I've been thinking.
You'd better
not take Mao Tou there.
What if you both get emotional
and argue in front of him?
That won't be good for him.
Mao Tou,
do you want to go or not?
Why are you here?
Didn't we agree
to meet at Portman?
I think these things,
we better discuss at home.
Hello, Aiping.
Hi, Yang Min.
Well, then,
I'll leave you to it.
Founder
of Qimingxing Global Trading Co., Ltd.
Me, Zhang Qiming.
This property is under my name and his name.
Our company's business license.
In Xujiahui, Shanghai.
That photo is too small?
Here's a bigger one.
(Founder: Zhang Qiming)
Look.
The founder is Zhang Qiming.
Our business is now
covering all of China.
We've even expanded abroad.
This year, we entered the French market.
Have you been to France?
Have you seen the Eiffel Tower?
Why are you so worked up?
When you get anxious,
you just ramble on and on.
I know.
I understand everything.
Your business is doing well.
You didn't lie to me.
The house, car, factory,
and the company are all yours.
As you should.
Aiping, who just left,
back then, when our factory
selected the Factory Belle,
she ranked first, and you ranked fifth.
Out of jealousy,
you hid her thermos.
After we divorce,
I'll marry her immediately if she will.
Well, that's great then!
Congratulations then!
Thanks a bunch!
So, you see?
Am I living a good life?
Is my son
having a good time with me?
We are living very well.
Qiming,
since you're starting
a new happy life,
maybe you could consider
giving me custody of our son?
Out of question.
Don't even think about it.
Why are you so worked up?
Can't you let me finish?
He's your son, and my son too,
my biological son.
Could you give me a chance
to make it up to him?
I'll take him to Japan,
and give him good education
and a good life.
Isn't that great?
Besides, I know
Aiping also has a son.
After I take my son away,
they should be the happiest.
Do you think everyone's like you?
You keep saying it's for Mao Tou's sake,
but have you ever asked him
if he agrees?
He doesn't want to see you.
He slammed the door.
Mao Tou,
I know I've been wrong.
But I hope you can understand.
I went to Japan
only to improve
our living condition,
so you could live better.
Now that I'm capable…
Stop acting like a loving mother.
You say it's for Mao Tou,
but ask yourself,
did you go to Japan for Mao Tou?
Can you stop driving a wedge
between us?
Drive a wedge how?
What did I do?
He didn't want to see you,
I tried to persuade him
that you are his mom.
- Ask him out then.
- I tried to help.
Are you kidding me?
Why should I listen to you?
- Who do you think you are?
- Enough!
What's it all for?
You're fighting,
and you're fighting too.
Am I an object?
Have you considered my feelings?
Have you?
Little imp, no crying!
Zhang Qiming, don't yell at my son.
You are not worthy to be his mother.
Hey.
Is Qian Jiayue there?
Mao Tou?
It's me.
What's up?
No...
nothing.
Where are you?
I'm…
I'm outside.
So…
did you see your mom?
Mao Tou?
Lately,
I've been thinking.
What if
we could go back to
when we were kids?
When we were kids?
I remember back then,
every morning when I woke up,
I could hear you
calling me for breakfast.
You'd say,
"Mao Tou, Mao Tou,
Granny bought sticky rice cakes,
and fried dough sticks."
Then I'd quickly get up.
Also,
you and Brother Xiao Han
we'd go to school together.
Then after school,
we'd go to our secret base,
where
we'd play games,
play military chess,
and just have so much fun.
And in the summer,
I remember
that fan on the ceiling
spinning round and round,
while we ate popsicles
underneath.
And in winter,
during our winter break,
Granny would always buy
roasted sweet potatoes,
and bring them to us.
Then we'd eat them
while watching cartoons
under the wool blanket.
Yes.
Those were
the good times.
Why do we have to grow up?
When we grow up,
everything changes.
Nothing's the same.
Mao Tou.
Today…
Today, it's the first time
I saw her face properly.
When she left home,
you were still young,
so you probably
don't remember much.
No.
Actually…
actually I
secretly kept a photo of her.
The rest was burned
by my dad.
Well,
I found that one
in Grandma's belongings
after she passed.
I don't even know
why I kept it a secret.
When I learned
she was coming back,
I was quite scared.
Because
they always told me
that she was
a bad woman.
I was afraid
she'd be
just like they said.
But I'm also afraid she wasn't.
If she wasn't as bad as they said,
I'm afraid I'd miss her.
And if I miss her,
it would be like betraying my dad.
You don't need to overthink it.
Sometimes,
from different angles,
our standards for good and bad
are not the same.
As for
whether she is good or bad,
you don't have to listen to others.
You can try to understand her yourself.
I believe
your mom must love you dearly.
And,
most importantly,
both your dad and mom,
their love for you
is the same.
Didn't expect it to be so fast.
It barely took five minutes.
(Divorce Certificate)
Keep it separately.
Live your own life.
Take care of yourself.
Drop me off at the intersection
of Jiaozhou Road and Changshou Road.
I'll walk back.
No problem.
Free for a farewell meal?
Farewell meal?
Sure.
To celebrate
both of us regaining freedom.
Okay.
Japanese or Shanghai cuisine?
Japanese cuisine.
Alright, as you wish.
Then let's go for Shanghai cuisine.
Come on.
Let's celebrate!
I don't drink alcohol.
Just tea.
You quit?
I got the good stuff for you.
Your loss.
Weren't you a big drinker?
On my wedding day,
I was drunk as a skunk,
but you
didn't even blink.
Back then…
That was because I was young.
Such exciting things,
I really could drink a lot,
and didn't even blink.
But now, I can't.
I actually had a stomach issue,
gastric perforation.
I almost
didn't make it out of the hospital.
The doctor told me to quit.
I thought you went to Japan
and turned into a wine goddess.
Turns out you're still a mortal.
Is that old man good to you?
Which one?
Insane.
Marinated tofu with greens.
You still remember my favorite dish!
I'll tell you my story
to make you happy.
What's there to be me happy about?
Actually,
when I first went to Japan,
my life was nothing like
what you imagined.
I had no legal status then.
I was there illegally.
Every day, I was hiding
and scared they'd catch me
and send me back.
To survive, you know,
I really
did all kinds of odd jobs.
Every day before dawn,
I went out to work
and returned only at midnight
to my tiny apartment,
sitting on the little toilet,
eating cold rice balls.
Now that you know I've had it rough,
does it make you feel better?
These last few years,
things have been better.
I saved up a bit,
bought a house, and a car,
and even opened a shop,
became a boss.
But suddenly,
it all felt meaningless.
Always alone,
so lonely.
Why not come back?
It's been developing well these past years.
The overpasses are built
and the subways are open.
Isn't it nice to come back?
You really want me to come back?
If you do,
I'll stay.
When are you leaving?
Lose your cool?
Is your back sweating?
Why would I sweat?
Tomorrow.
I've already booked the ticket.
Everything's settled.
It's time to leave.
Yesterday,
Aiping helped organize it.
She told me to give it to you.
She said,
you're still his mom,
and Mao Tou is still your son.
When you have time,
come visit him.
Also,
Mao Tou wears size 43 shoes.
That's from me.
There's a photo
placed there by Mao Tou.
He said it's for you.
That little imp
hid that photo
and made it so wrinkled.
He said
he wants to go to Jinjiang Action Park.
If you're free tomorrow,
you can go with him.
You're leaving for Japan tomorrow.
I'll reschedule.
Kang, take a look.
Hao, let's go play outside.
A bit higher. Is this okay?
You go play yourself.
I stuck it on.
Eat this.
Hao, here.
Mom.
Weihao,
can I watch a program for a while?
- My classmate's in it.
- Firecrackers.
Wait a moment.
I'm still watching.
Weihao, let me watch for a bit.
- You can first…
- Wait a moment.
I'm not done yet.
- Slow down.
- Okay.
Alright, now
to our final question
for this round.
Will Chang Wuji
defend his title
(Round Two: Chang Wuji, high school student)
or will the challenger
(Yu Yao, college student)
come out on top?
Ten numbers.
Get ready.
Here it is.
Stop.
Write down your answer.
Show your answer.
Let's see the answers.
One is
7965498135,
and the other is
7965418935.
Let's see,
the correct answer is…
Congrats, Chang Wuji got it right again.
- Chang Wuji defended the title again!
- So impressive!
Congrats!
Now,
let's welcome Chang Wuji…
Qian Jiayue, did you watch
Chang Wuji's game?
Don't even.
I didn't get to watch it.
Why didn't you watch it?
But don't worry.
We all watched it for you.
He's so good.
He'll definitely win all the way
and take the championship.
Too bad I didn't bring my phone book.
Remember to congratulate him for me.
No way.
I'll go get his number for you.
Chen Mo,
forget it.
I need your help with something else.
What's up?
I might not make it back on the sixth.
Before celebrating
Brother Xiao Han's birthday,
can you go to my place first?
I had Granny make his favorite dish.
Can you take it over for me
and wish him
a happy birthday?
Sure, no problem.
Is it time for New Year's Eve dinner?
Don't eat too much,
or you'll come back twice your size.
We'll see who gets bigger.
Thank you, aunt.
- Good fortune and prosperity.
- Jiali.
What's wrong? You're not happy?
Happy New Year.
Jiali,
where are you going?
I'm done eating.
I'll go study.
It's New Year, we're all together.
Why study now?
Sit down.
Jiali.
Come sit.
Enjoy the food.
Cheer up, okay?
It's New Year, after all.
Look at her.
This is really good.
No idea what she wants to do.
She can't even help with chores.
I heard
Jiali is going to Dongguan
after the New Year.
Anyways,
girls don't need to study, right?
Exactly, what's the point of studying?
They'll get married.
- Aunt.
- Indeed.
Jiali's grades are so good,
why won't you let her study?
Jiayue,
your uncle doesn't make much
all year round.
But when Jiali graduates,
she can go out and make money.
You should think long-term.
Indeed a city child,
so different,
speaking so eloquently.
Is this the well-rounded education?
Is this how you talk to the elders?
Watch your attitude.
But
what Jiayue said isn't wrong.
Jiali's doing so well in school,
why not let her study?
Instead…
Sister.
Anyway, I think
it doesn't quite add up, Mom.
Then tell me,
what's right?
(End of Episode 14)
♪Little girl♪
♪You've let your hair grow long♪
♪You've loosened the hand
that tightly held mine♪
♪No longer do you♪
♪Whisper in my ear♪
♪Day by day, you're growing up♪
♪Spring buds sprout♪
♪Summer trees bloom♪
♪Time stops for no one♪
♪Fairy tales fade♪
♪And scars remain♪
♪That♪
♪Is the cost of growing up♪
♪Learn to let go♪
♪Learn to play dumb♪
♪Please♪
♪Learn to answer like a grown-up♪
♪If you have an ordinary life♪
♪Then choose to be open-minded♪
♪Love♪
♪May be the key♪
♪My girl♪
♪You've cut your long hair♪
♪Tears drop from the corner of your eyes♪
♪One day, all alone♪
♪You climbed a high tower♪
♪And saw yourself growing up♪
♪Little girl♪
♪Don't♪
♪Be afraid♪