Autumn osmanthus
and miles of lotus flowers.
The first part of the password is
'Autumn osmanthus and miles of lotus flowers,'
and the second part is
'Raise a million troops, stand at Mount Wu.'
Raise a million troops.
Stand at Mount Wu.
Jin Wutu
pays respects to the Twin Heroes.
I've caused both of you to be exposed,
and deserve
a thousand deaths for my fault.
It's alright,
but
there are Dacheng soldiers everywhere outside.
Why did you summon us?
What's the matter?
Get to the point.
Your superior,
Lord Helawo,
was executed due to clan disputes
within the royal family.
But before his death,
he didn't reveal how to contact you.
His Majesty has been planning a southern campaign recently.
But all the agents sent
have vanished without a trace.
The higher-ups had no choice but to wake me up,
and then gave me all the previous correspondence
between you two and Master Helawa,
so I could search for clues
to reestablish contact with both of you.
So where are those letters now?
Did you keep them safe?
Don't worry.
The moment we made contact,
I burned them all.
Good thinking.
Safe,
completely safe now.
Is there any possibility
that you might have missed some clues?
I almost forgot,
I still have the note you sent with your messenger the other day.
This thing
must not fall into Hou Wei's hands.
Burn it,
and there will be no trace left to prove your identities.
Everyone,
surround this place,
don't let anyone escape.
Don't be afraid,
I've long expected this day would come.
Both of you, follow me.
Take this.
What are you doing?
Sprinkle more over there.
Don't be afraid.
Those guards who were watching me
have been dealt with,
had nowhere to put them,
so I made them keep me company in bed.
Being watched all these days, this is our only hope.
Aren't you coming?
Someone needs to cover for you.
If the three of us leave together now,
we can all escape together.
You're safe now.
Use this to contact Dayan.
The great cause of Dayun now depends on you.
Go now!
Keep running. Don't look back.
White mountains.
Black soil.
I, Jin Wutu,
have returned today.
Come on.
White mountains.
Black soil.
I, Jin Wutu,
have returned today.
Attack!
Don't just stand there! Put out the fire!
Get water!
Chen Yiqu,
tell me honestly,
how did you know that was a secret order from Yun Kingdom?
I don't know.
I...
I really don't know.
When he said the password just now,
some memories seemed to flash through my mind.
In these memories,
someone told me about this password.
My dear.
What if I really am one of the Jiandié Twin Heroes?
What should I do?
Then we'll keep investigating
until you prove your innocence.
If I discover you're truly a spy,
I'll be the first to execute you.
What's wrong?
Are you afraid?
No.
I'm just thinking about how we're taking such big risks,
running here and there,
without finding a single clue.
What's going on?
Guards!
Surround this place!
Don't be afraid.
Both of you, follow me.
Are you crazy?
Look at this.
See if there are any other clues.
Four characters.
Meet at Hele Tower.
Just four characters?
There are no other clues.
How's your hand?
You got burned grabbing that note, didn't you?
It doesn't hurt.
I practice martial arts and have iron palm skills,
you wouldn't understand.
Would it kill you to admit it hurts?
You're always like this, that's why I...
Why you what?
Why you wanted a divorce?
No.
Let me tell you,
don't ever mention divorce again.
Who am I?
Who am I really?
Do you still recognize me?
I made you some ginseng soup. Drink it while it's hot.
You stayed up all night again?
I have a lot of medicine to prepare.
Drink up.
In a government office like this,
there aren't that many vacancies.
Take these pastries back.
Help me figure something out,
or just squeeze him in somewhere.
This much money?
That's almost a month's salary wasted.
Cut the nonsense.
Just tell me if you'll help or not.
That husband of yours
can't lift a finger to help himself.
Then find him something easier to do.
I don't care,
but if you don't help me,
next time you and your buddies need medical help, I'll...
Listen to yourself.
How about this,
I'll take the pastries, but you keep your money.
Next month, Old Yang is going home for mourning.
Have your husband come then.
Thanks, Xing.
How did it go?
It's done. Let's go home for dinner.
You didn't spend a penny!
Of course not.
That's impressive!
You have a strong personality
and want to heal the world.
I'm physically weak,
can't fight,
and have no memory.
I shouldn't be holding you back.
What do you mean?
Didn't you ask why I want a divorce?
Actually,
it's not your fault.
It's my problem.
Didn't you say...
Are we not allowed to mention divorce?
Is someone helping us?
Anyway,
we shouldn't stay here. Let's go.
Sir.
The beams have all burned down,
there's nothing left to investigate.
You're the one who's worthless,
Xing Dezheng.
Do all you government officials
slack off like you do,
going through the motions and waiting to die?
No, sir.
The men are still working inside.
Sir.
Chief,
we found three bodies. Get them ready quickly.
Heaven is just!
I've finally caught these inseparable heroes in one swoop.
Take the bodies back to the magistrate's office.
Quickly, this way.
This way.
Hurry!
Where is Magistrate Chang?
He went back to the magistrate's office.
What's the matter?
I found this
in the ruins.
Keep this matter quiet.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Chen Yiqu.
Where have you been?
I thought you were arrested by the soldiers.
You went to gather herbs.
This is Bai Lian,
you told me about it before,
it can treat burns.
Is it really Bai Lian?
Yes, it's Bai Lian.
You told me that
Bai Lian isn't white but green,
shaped like a palm,
and its leaves are very thin,
like thin paper
in texture.
Chen Yiqu,
I've told you not to eat these things carelessly.
Even though they look similar,
some might be dangerous,
and could make you go mad if eaten.
Although I don't know who sent this note,
take a closer look
at the difference between these two papers.
I can't tell.
This one
has a rough texture,
it's horsehair paper used by ordinary households,
but this one is different,
with a fine texture,
not easily torn and insect-resistant.
Say something I can understand.
This
is Yuan Book paper made by the Cai paper mill in the east district,
a special type of paper
that's very hard to get.
You have to buy at least 500 sheets
and place orders in advance.
Then the Cai paper mill
must have a purchase list.