The Inseparable Heroes
bid you farewell.
Spare me, great hero!
I know the rules.
I didn't see anything,
nothing at all,
I didn't see a thing.
But you just did, didn't you?
I didn't see anything.
Shut up.
From now on, answer whatever you're asked.
Who booked
the private room last night?
I don't know.
We're not the Inseparable Duo.
Aren't you two the Inseparable Duo?
Your wanted posters are all over the city.
Where's the
reservation list?
Hand it over.
Hou Wei took it.
You must at least know what the person who made the reservation looks like, right?
Actually,
nobody showed up that day.
Keep your hands where we can see them.
Where's the note?
I gave it to the officers.
Keep lying.
I forgot. It's right here.
Why did you hide it?
I only gave the innkeeper ten coins.
I was afraid he'd find out, so I hid it.
What are you sniffing at, dog?
Look here,
this handwriting,
professional constables like us can tell.
I can tell from the powerful strokes
so
I'm certain
this was written by someone with exceptional martial arts skills.
Smell this.
The scent of mutton.
I can't smell it.
Is it from a Western Regions shop
or a shepherd?
It can't be Old Zhang, can it?
He spends all day with sheep
and reeks of that gamey smell.
Who is this Mr. Zhang?
He delivers mutton to our shop,
from the west side
of town. He's Zhang the butcher.
Take care, sir.
Goodbye.
Safe travels, sir.
Who told you to use the front door?
Use the back door next time.
What could have made
this butcher Zhang
forget his place?
Something big.
And it must be
something urgent enough to activate these dormant agents,
for him to not use the back door.
So do you think this butcher Zhang
is a handler
or just a messenger?
If he's a handler, that's way too risky.
What kind of big situation is this?
None of your business.
Brother,
where does this
butcher Zhang live?
I only know he's from Taiping Village,
but I don't know his exact address.
Taiping Village.
Thank you, brother.
This is for me.
What are you doing?
I already paid him.
He's helped us so much, and you still hit him.
What if he could still get some useful information?
This guy won't spill anything even if you beat him with a stick,
just like you.
Let's go.
Come on, let's hurry.
Fresh black tea here!
Boss!
One bowl of tea,
steeped only three times,
no fragrance added.
Ah, coming right up!
This tea came in early this year.
I've prepared in advance.
Fresh tea here!
Get your black tea,
cools you down in the heat!
Here, black tea!
Fresh black tea!
Black tea for sale!
Come have some tea!
Who goes there?
Whoa!
I am Princess Yuean Li of Qinye,
heading to Lin'an on urgent business.
Who dares stop me?
Please be careful, Princess.
There are spies escaping from Lin'an.
That's exactly why I'm here.
Which way is Butcher Zhang's house?
What's wrong?
That fat guy drinking tea up ahead
is Hou Wei's lookout.
Look casual when you glance over.
How do you know?
We officials have our own
methods and protocols.
If I were watching this place,
I'd choose that spot too.
Good visibility, open position.
But...
The downside is he's easily spotted.
I think...
The direction he's watching
must be where Butcher Zhang lives.
There should be
other lookouts nearby.
What do we do now?
They're all watching.
If we go looking for him,
we'll be walking right into their trap.
Plus, the city is full of
wanted posters with our faces on them.
Moving forward recklessly
would be suicide.
Push to the extreme
to find a way out.
Let's go.
How exactly?
Can you handle it?
You can't even drink
this little bit?
Can you drink anymore?
If you can't drink, go sit at the kids' table.
Sit down and take a break.
Oh my, it's so heavy.
Sit properly.
Goodness, this is killing me.
It's crushing me.
Hou Weiqiang.
Waiter!
Bring me some sobering tea.
Right away, coming up!
Hou Weiqiang.
We're ignoring you now.
Don't mind him,
let's go buy some lamb.
Sir,
your sobering tea.
Lamb.
Butcher Zhang's lamb.
How do we deal with Butcher Zhang?
The Twin Heroes have been hiding for a long time.
This Butcher Zhang only arrived a few months ago.
I'm afraid they've only just made contact.
Let's try to trick him first.
It's been a while since I've had your lamb, Brother Zhang.
What took you so long?
I've been waiting for ages.
Come in, come in.
Hurry up.
My village isn't easy to find.
You two came all the way from the city,
must have been a tough journey.
Let me get you something to eat.
Do you know him?
I don't,
I thought you did.
I don't know him either.
Then why is he acting like he knows us?
How would I know?
Sir.
Should we make the arrest?
The men are all in position.
What's the rush?
You government officials
are always so eager for quick results, aren't you?
The lamb from our village
is very popular with city folks.
Even the wild dogs outside
are constantly craving it.
Have some water first.
Thank you.
Everyone stay calm.
What are you doing?
Do you have a death wish?
Who are you people?
Since you asked who we are.
This flatbread
is still warm.
The notice board at the flatbread stall
has sketches of wanted criminals all over the city.
Didn't you see that?
I can't read,
why would I look at that stuff?
We're here to rescue you.
The chubby guy who sat at the tea stall all day
with just one pot of tea,
the worker across from your place who's been kneading dough all day,
and that man
who's been trying to make sugar figurines but can't even make a decent one.
Don't tell me
you didn't notice anything suspicious.
I'm just an ordinary citizen,
why should I fear the guards outside?
Did I mention any guards?
No, you didn't.
We, the Inseparable Heroes, came to meet you,
and you're worried we might be impostors.
Autumn osmanthus,
lotus flowers for miles.
What era do you think this is?
Using those old phrases.
You've been exposed already.
Do you really think these outdated passwords
aren't known to them?
Raise a million troops,
stand ready at Wu Mountain.