You're quite amusing, young master.
You don't have any martial skills
yet you still try to show off.
Is there something wrong with your head?
I
truly do suffer from a brain ailment.
But as men of Dacheng,
whether we have brain problems or not,
when we encounter such despicable matters,
we cannot simply stand by and do nothing.
I am Chen Yiqu.
Thank you for your help earlier.
You were the one who acted bravely first,
and even got hurt because of me.
Let me take a look at your wound.
Time flies,
it's been three years already.
I once aspired to be a wandering doctor, free from all constraints,
never imagining I'd settle down with my own shop.
I originally just wanted to find a way to recover my memories,
to remember who I really am.
But before I knew it,
I had started a family.
Do you regret it?
I have at times.
But...
Surveillance Bureau! Official business!
Inseparable Heroes,
surrender immediately!
Don't move!
Put your hands on the table!
Fine.
Officers,
I work for the government too.
I can't believe spies like you
managed to infiltrate official positions.
What spies?
Wait, what are you doing?
This is evidence of your treason.
Chen Yiqu,
what have you done?
I haven't done anything,
don't make false accusations!
Treason is punishable by death,
don't frame innocent people!
In your Cloud Nation, it might just be beheading,
but in our Great Cheng,
treason is usually punished by dismemberment,
which means being cut into pieces while still alive.
Inseparable Heroes.
Misunderstanding.
They think we're the Inseparable Heroes, but
we're not.
Behave yourselves,
you spies.
How come you both say the same thing?
You two have hidden yourselves well,
our Surveillance Bureau has been watching for years
just to discover the codename 'Inseparable Heroes.'
If we hadn't accidentally found your handler moved to Lin'an,
we wouldn't have caught you red-handed.
We really aren't the Inseparable Heroes.
Then let's see
what this letter
actually says.
There's no need to look at it,
right?
No,
that's not it.
You can't read it.
Stay still.
Resolve grudges, let go of attachments.
Let's not discuss this further.
These thieves have become quite sophisticated.
They even managed to hide treasonous correspondence in divorce papers.
Must be using some kind of code.
When we get back to the office,
we'll let those old experts decode it.
Chen Yiqu.
You actually want a divorce from me?
I told you it wasn't me. Don't you believe me?
Love letter.
Look.
See for yourself,
what else could this be but divorce papers?
What are you doing?
Sit back down!
So what if it's divorce papers?
Let me tell you, Yang Tao,
I, Chen Yiqu,
am going to be a dignified man today,
and I absolutely won't let you, you tigress,
Go on.
bully me anymore.
Chen Yiqu, are you trying to rebel?
Both of you.
Sit back down, now!
Trying to rebel?
Is that what you want?
Just kill me then!
You have a death wish?
Both of you behave yourselves!
Or I'll execute you right here and now!
What are you waiting for? Run!
Xiaowei!
Don't worry about me!
Who are you?
Yang Tao, wait.
Wait for what?
Yang Tao is coming back.
Don't run!
What are you doing?
If you don't run, are you waiting to be caught?
If both of us believe we're innocent,
we should go back now.
If before I lost my memory,
I was truly a spy,
then I deserve to be arrested.
But I believe they will give us justice.
Come back!
Don't you understand Hou Wei's methods?
They'll only force confessions through torture.
By then, not only will you lose your innocence,
everyone connected to you will be implicated.
Since you saw that divorce letter earlier,
we are no longer husband and wife.
From now on,
we have no relationship whatsoever.
From now on, I, Chen Yiqu,
will take responsibility for everything I do
by myself,
so don't interfere.
Chen Yiqu!
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
The person is already dead.
What are you looking for?
Are you crazy?
Why did you come back?
The blade was swift,
killing with a single strike.
The imperial guards are skilled fighters,
but this killer
is far more formidable than them.
Is this really the time to discuss this?
You were never here today.
I've never seen you,
now go quickly.
Divorce papers.
It must be officially registered with the authorities
Verbal agreements mean nothing
and neither does your word.
I just don't want to be dragged down with you.
Autopsy.
Disgusting.
This wound
is about 20 inches long.
It was made by a blade
that's thin at the edge but thick at the spine
which pierced straight through the body.
But such weapons are common
unless we can find an exact match.
This wound pattern seems rather unusual.
That's right.
The wound runs diagonally from the lower left to the upper right.
This indicates
that the killer was holding the knife with their left hand.
Yes.
The killer
is left-handed.
Sir.
Everyone,
guard the front and back doors.
Lao Li, Shaobing,
come upstairs with me.
Yes,
sir.
What should we do?
Chief,
where are you going?
Let's go.
Chen Yiqu, don't make me hit you.
Hurry up.
It's quite high.
Surveillance Bureau.
Now we're in big trouble.
Boss.
What kind of person
would dare kill an imperial guard?
Li,
go get the coroner.
Shaobing,
bring the innkeeper and the waiter here.
Hurry up,
gather all the valuables.
Someone's trying to frame us.
This way.
Boss.
This place is so small,
looks like they've already fled.
Search again
for any clues.
Yes, sir.