The second date is about to start.
I think they might be super sweet together.
My hand is already tired.
I'll help you relax.
Such a natural interaction.
Physical contact.
Oh no, I'm shipping this couple too.
Oh my gosh.
Control yourself.
I think we can form a group.
For middle-aged and elderly hobbies.
We are the middle-aged and elderly group.
After watching their date,
I started shipping them.
Shipping Ryan.
Yes.
How about I introduce you to
our specialty dishes here?
These are our recommended dishes.
Yu Yue has a very high emotional intelligence.
It never gets awkward.
At my heaviest two years ago,
I reached 180 pounds.
But if it's always just one person
constantly trying to find topics to keep the atmosphere lively,
I think it would be tiring.
I didn't get excited.
They both have concerns now.
There's a sense of distance.
This
isn't very good, right?
I'm so messy
After coming back, I heard from Shunshun
that Lola might not be feeling well
It seems that Lola is a bit unwell
She is indeed a bit unwell
She felt much better after lying down for a while
When she was with me just now
she was feeling very down
It might be because of my profession.
I think buying some of these warmers might be useful.
That's not very good.
Not good, so messy
It's okay
No need to knock.
Thank you
Where did you get this from?
I heard you weren't feeling well
Because of a stomachache
Thank you, impressive
It's nothing, get some rest early
You too, bye
Bye
Cow
This part contains some very complex information.
We need to sort and handle it.
For example, Yu Yue.
After he came back from his date,
he heard about Lola's situation.
He seemed to have some emotional changes.
There were some changes.
Yes, and actually on the first day,
after he rejected Lola,
he has been
unable to recover, right?
Yes.
Maybe he hasn't fully decided
who he really likes.
I don't think so.
I think he did it out of politeness.
Out of politeness.
Because in his state,
I didn't see any sign
of him liking Lola.
Agree
I think Laura in this matter
She is a bit insecure now.
So she made this call
Ask her about that friend.
But what I want to say is about these four men
Not enough to prove anything
Yes
It's these four men
No need to think so much
I think her first girlfriend
That's right.
Just be yourself.
Why do you need to adjust with others?
I think you're great just the way you are now.
Very good
Just be yourself.
Because the one he likes is you
Otherwise, he doesn't like you.
What's the point of making him like you?
So that's why we often
We will discuss that topic.
It's when you're in the early stages of a relationship
What you want to show to others
is your true self
or your best self
I think the true self
is the best self
It depends on how long you plan to interact
If you plan for a short-term relationship
of course, showing a better side is better
to leave a good impression
If you plan for a long-term relationship
then the sooner you show
your true side, the better
others will accept you more easily
and there won't be a reversal
saying "Oh, so this is what you're really like"
I actually think
rather than showing the best self
showing the true self
is more important to show
different aspects of yourself
for example, Laura's cheerfulness
and her boyishness
sometimes she uses it as a
"mask"
Yes
including when Yu Yue gave her
that hand warmer
she also said
Cool, very good
with her kind of voice
Where did you get this from?
I heard you weren't feeling well.
Stomach ache, so
Thank you, impressive
You're welcome
I think she is doing it for herself
Create a protective mechanism
Yes
So she can let go of that defense mechanism
Show your vulnerable side
I think it's a very good progress
Yes, being genuine is the best.
Yes
That's why I really like her
Her male best friend gave it to her.
Opinion
It is very useful to her.
It was exactly what she thought before
The reason for feeling a bit frustrated
She feels a bit frustrated
It's because she thinks the first day
She should have responsibility
Make everyone happy
So she is quite tired from doing it.
In the end, no one chose her.
Her male best friend just told
The problem with her
Actually, there are some so-called
Some actions intended to deliberately please others
It will gradually become quite tiring.
For example, if there is an apple in front of you
Maybe I usually eat apples by myself
I don't even peel it. I just wash it.
At most, cut it in half and I'll eat it.
To please, for example
I want to give this apple to Wang Yanlin
I still insist on peeling it perfectly.
You never used to
How well can you even do this?
Or maybe it's not necessary to do it this way.
Totally unnecessary
Yes, and I think
You can't start like this.
Has Laura ever had
Some previous emotional experiences
Received some
I wonder what kind of person would suit her.
She is suited for someone who completely trusts her.
Only then will she believe in herself.
She now belongs to
Make others feel comfortable.
I'm not feeling well.
I started to doubt myself
What part is wrong?
And she said before that she wanted to
Here to date
And now we've all become buddies and friends.
She probably had a premonition.
I think it's better not to make any assumptions.
The one who understands you is the right one.
There must be many people who like it.
A girl like her
I think Wang Yanlin saw it.
What does Laura need the most?
It just needs something that is completely unnecessary
The person who pretends to be strong in front of her
was already very confident in knowing
This person likes me
Yes
She can already bring sunshine to many people
She needs someone who can shine on her
Maybe this person
is not someone who can give a lot of sunshine
but can give sunshine to Laura
She will feel
That's right
It's possible
Well said
Yes, I think it was well said
Applause
There should be applause here
Laura needs to have confidence, Laura
This is just the first time
It's just a first meeting date, no rush
There is more time
for everyone to get to know Laura
and for everyone to get to know each other
So our eight guests
will also welcome
their first day off in the semi-mature apartment
their first day off
They will have more interactions
Let's go take a look together
Can I hitch a ride in your car?
Sure
Where did you go to school before?
In the United States. How about you?
I was in Chicago.
Did you study dentistry?
No, I was in Chicago.
I studied finance.
I guess I'm half a colleague with you all.
So how did you end up becoming a dentist?
After I came back, I worked in finance first.
Then later I felt that this
might not be suitable.
So did you go back to get another degree?
Yes, I went back to take the college entrance exam again.
Then your age
Age
I am the youngest among the guys.
I am younger than all of them.
And much younger.
They are all much older than me.
That's impressive.
I also wanted to say "ah".
All three of them were born before '85.
What do you mean by "ah"?
Three before eighty-five
You can't tell, right?
How do you maintain it?
I think that person
I forgot the name again
This is called
Is it Yu Yue?
I am Yu Yue
Sorry
It's okay
Yu Yue is you
Who did you originally think Yu Yue was?
I thought it was that Europa
Europa is actually Zhou Jinshun
Shun Shun
And then there's Huang Ruen
Yes, Huang Ruen is just Huang Ruen
Huang Ruen is the oldest among us
Oh no
You can't tell
Such good skin
Yes
Oh no
This "oh no" is really
Morning
Has Luo Ying gotten up?
I
It's nothing, I was just asking casually.
First thing after waking up, look for Luo Ying.
Just focusing on her, that's good.
I like this straightforward approach.
Very clear.
Liking someone means liking that person.
Where is everyone now?
These people have gone to work.
Do they have to work today, on Saturday?
It seems they don't rest.
Your dentist deserves praise.
Ours.
Did Luo Ying go out?
She
They probably left together, right?
Didn't they say yesterday they would take her to the city?
Actually, the two of them went out secretly to have fun.
We're having a barbecue tonight.
We'll go buy some things this afternoon.
Let's go together, it's perfect timing.
Is there anything you want to eat?
I'm the best at barbecuing.
Now all the words
can't reach his ears anymore.
What? Who's good at barbecuing?
This has nothing to do with him.
Look
at your expression
You look so capable
Expression, mouth
Wiping sweat, sweating
Your eyebrow is wiped off
Eyebrows can't be wiped off
Tattooed, waterproof
Another one is coming, who is it?
Huang Ruien
No water to drink
Big brother, I'll do it
Help
Come
A little girl doing this kind of thing
What are you doing
Thank you
In the future, let the boys carry these things
Just call the boys
I saw you guys working out
And I also thought that by doing this
I could also get some exercise
Do you want to eat
Can I eat it
You can eat it
Lola, you've worked hard
Let's go to the supermarket
Let's go
Let's try Chef Laura's cooking today
Everyone, take a look at what you want to eat.
You can also buy a little.
First, buy the necessary things you remember.
Lola, you lead the way.
This way.
I can't choose, you do it.
Just pick a fresher one.
How about grilled eggplant?
This is also very tasty.
Zucchini.
Get a green onion.
Enoki mushrooms.
Should we buy some squid rings?
Bought it.
Got it.
No chili powder, buy chili sauce
There's that
Can you eat it?
It mainly depends on you
No, this is what Luo Ying said she wanted yesterday
She said she wanted it
This looks so delicious
This is delicious
Oh no, I'm going to get fat
You won't get fat
Help
Wow
We both have all snacks
That's about it, let's go
Let's go
Let's buy some props
Halloween
Here's one for you
This one
Try it
I'll take a picture of you
Okay, start, go
Expression
These two people have already
Gotten closer
Have a barrier with others
So serious
Sweet moments
Shipping couples online
Today I already shipped a couple in person
Shipped them so quickly
Although it was unexpected
But shipping in person is quite sweet
Let's go
Go
Let's go straight to the kitchen.
Okay.
Have you already started?
Who prepared so much of this?
Ingredients?
No, I just cleared out the fridge.
Thoughtful.
What's wrong?
Nothing, great job.
You look really tired.
This Huang Rui'en has a feeling
The old man seems to have been unlocked
We need to keep a close watch
Sorry
I'll thread it.
Do you want to thread this?
I'll give it a try.
You thread one first as an example.
It's about alternating sides.
For example, one side bends this way.
Then the other side bends the other way.
Is our charcoal fire still burning?
It's still burning. I just checked.
I'll go take a look.
The charcoal should be almost ready.
But it seems that Laura hasn't
shown any special reaction to Yu Yue's concern.
She doesn't even look at him.
Yes, she is deliberately avoiding him.
Is it deliberate?
She should be able to feel it.
Of course.
Be careful, I'll handle it, really.
Move aside.
Over there
Alright
Yu Yue is definitely going to change
Be careful, don't burn yourself.
It's okay, really, it's okay.
Alright.
Hello
My name is Lola
Impossible
I discovered
he has been following me
I was quite touched
I thought this guy was pretty good
This is a bit hot, be careful
Don't burn yourself
Cheers
Happy New Year
Is anyone's birthday coming up?
It should be soon.
His birthday is on
October
1st or 10th of October
Double Ten
How should I say it?
It's October 10th, right?
The ten, then the month below
Ten comes first
It's two "tens"
One with a grass radical, one with sun and moon, right
Cute Festival
Cute Festival, let's have a drink
Happy birthday, "Mengmeng"
I feel like that horse
It turned into "Wang Mengmeng"
Mengmeng, get up
Mengmeng
Yes, I thought of that too
How about we play a game of visiting three parks?
For example, what's in the zoo?
These games are really for my age
Yeah
Okay
I used to play this
Playing a game that kids play now
Kids born after 2000 play now
Catching fingers
It's like catching ducks, catching a few
Look
Post-2000s, you guys aren't post-2000s
I don't get it
Try it once, slower
Slower, try it once
Five, six, seven, eight
Catching ducks, catching a few
Catching a few
Just say a number
For example, you say catch eight hundred
Then we start quacking eight hundred
Quack until tomorrow morning
Let's have a limit, okay?
Ten is the limit. Ten it is.
Alright, it's official. It's official now.
It's official now.
I think Huang Ruien will lose.
I think so too.
There is a punishment for this, right?
Truth or Dare
How about letting Huang Ruien start first?
Come on, catch the duck, quickly.
Catch some ducks. How many?
Catch six.
Got them.
Catching ducks
It's your turn
Wait, you were too slow
That's right
So strict, oh my gosh
Is it really that strict?
Then just keep asking Huang Ruien tonight
Alright, I lose
Yes, just ask her
I'll ask her
So, truth or dare?
Can we ask quietly?
No, you can't
Aren't we supposed to get to know each other?
They know each other
Yes
Don't get involved in this, okay?
I guess I don't understand the mood
Alright, just the age of first love
The age of first love
Freshman year
I don't remember how old I was
Alright, it's in the past, and then
Catching ducks, how many?
Catch three
What's wrong?
Did you catch them or not?
It's a bit difficult for Huang Ruien
We didn't get to know each other today
We just know Huang Ruien
We know him
Eating quietly
What was your first love like
That's not very specific
When was your first love
What happened
That's not a question, right
Not a question
When did it end
Fifteen or sixteen, I guess
Sixteen, I don't want to know the age
I don't want to know the age
I just want to know what happened
What kind of person was the other
The other was the school beauty
The school hunk with the school beauty
Incredible
Said it calmly and confidently
She was the school beauty
Satisfied now
Satisfied
He just spoke like Jerry Yan
Yeah
So F4 is complete, right
All complete
So fast? Are you sure you can do it?
Yes
No, try again
Follow my rhythm, okay?
Follow my rhythm
One, two, three
Does it have to be this fast?
Can you do it?
He's still okay at the front
Catch the ducks, how many?
Got them
Really?
How many?
Lost
Do you want to ask privately? We allow it.
Sure, go ahead.
Huang Ruien, ask boldly.
Ask what? There's nothing to ask.
Yeah.
We've asked everything that needed to be asked.
We don't know.
Aren't we supposed to get to know each other?
Are you happy today?
Happy, thank you, good.
So official.
He let her go.
So boring.
Everyone is a little expert at shipping couples.
Feels like the scene.
They ship even more enthusiastically in person.
Catch ducks, how many?
Catch ten.
Got them.
Wait a minute.
You're wrong.
Ducks quack.
Not croak.
Isn't an accent okay?
How many relationships have you had?
Seven or eight times, right.
Seven times or eight times, seven or eight times.
I don't know if one time counts.
Seven times, eight times.
Seven or eight times should be seventy-eight times.
Really, do you have to ask so clearly?
It really is.
Catching ducks, how many?
Catch five.
You didn't finish, did you?
Finished.
Then it's you.
Big brother was counting ducks all night.
I don't know if it's time or what.
Huang Ruien lost.
Huang Ruien, today should be his...
...most mentioned day by everyone.
Six, right?
Six ducks.
Six ducks, just right.
Game black hole.
Why are there more again?
Go to bed early
Amazing, you're so good at this
You're really good at this
I don't quite understand, uncle
Uncle, what are you thinking about
If someone likes him
they would find this quite cute
a silly side
So, what do you want to ask?
What have you done before
that was the most romantic?
This is good
The most romantic thing I've done
is to participate in "Half-Mature Lovers"
That's lame, go home
No way
Check, please
Did you get paid?
Give him a dare
Don't let him tell the truth
That's not the answer we expected
I have to give the answer you expect, right?
Give the answer we expect
So frustrating
Next time, no choice
Next time, he only gets a dare
What is a dare? How do you play?
A dare means you have to do whatever you're told
Yes, do an action
Like drinking while doing a handstand
Yes
Can you demonstrate?
Crying while doing a handstand
Zai Zai (Vic Chou) does this too
Right?
What was that phrase again?
When you're sad, stand on your head
and the tears won't fall.
So cheesy.
Haven't you all seen
"Meteor Garden"?
Don't you know
the "Meteor Garden" reference?
Can't get over it, huh?
If apologies worked, why would we need the police?
Let's not do that "quack quack" thing anymore, okay?
Can we change it?
I think catching ducks is fun.
Even if we change it, it'll be the same.
Then let's play Truth or Dare.
Truth or Dare.
Let's play a numbers Truth or Dare.
Thirty-two.
One to thirty-two.
Nineteen.
Good choice.
One to nineteen.
Ten.
You can do it.
Ten to nineteen.
Eleven.
Got it.
Even this got it.
Alright, you know how to play now.
Alright, beautiful.
Our Huang Rui'en has grown up.
Great job.
Grown up.
Very good.
And then?
Then you think of a big dare.
What is that?
Why are you looking at me? Look at him.
Just suggest anything you want.
I did a daring action.
The suggestion just given by Laura is
For example, to touch
the hair of someone you like.
Let's do it this way.
How to do it.
Go touch the head of someone you like.
Head.
Should we set some limits?
Same sex, opposite sex, etc.
Really?
Right, what if he touches me?
For example, to touch
the head of someone of the opposite sex you like.
Shut up, you
Then go and touch it
the head of the person you like
leave some room for them
the head of the person you currently like
for now, you can change it later, right?
who knows
playing this big on the third day
how to get through the next few days
That's what he said
What does it have to do with me
Sovereignty, you don't have to listen to him
The sovereignty is in your hands
Okay
Don't let him influence you
Okay, then next time I won't listen to him
Let's get going.
Actually, he knows very well.
Playing dumb.
Start, quickly.
Change it.
I think maybe for him,
it's a bit too difficult.
Yes, don't make it hard.
I feel like he really wants to go on an adventure.
But I think chandlee is holding back.
That awkwardness.
Makes Yang Mengjing a bit uncomfortable too.
Actually, I can see that girl
is disappointed while laughing.
Oh darn.
If it were me, I wouldn't be happy, right.
So let's do it this way,
I'll help you think of one.
Just take off your own shoe,
and use it as a phone.
Then say a sentence
that you want to say to someone you like.
So this is the big adventure?
Are you satisfied or not?
Yes
So this week
I was really happy to be with
her
Not her, it's you
Yes, really
I was really happy to spend some time with you
a very good time
Yes, thank you
Yes, you reminded me of
End of speech
You reminded me of Zai Zai (Vic Chou)
Thank you, my childhood
It was terrible
So much dust
Are you really pointing the sole of your shoe at yourself?
Yes
Isn't it supposed to be the inside of the shoe?
The inside towards yourself
Hitting yourself with the sole
It's okay, the inside might have a bit of a smell
Alright, let him go, let's do another one
You go ahead
Come on, next one
Next one
Salute
Yurik (Yu Yue), don't let me draw you
I'm telling you
Have you noticed
that guys seem to be asking questions
and stuff like that more often
while girls don't
Yes
They haven't asked us any questions
It's either me or Huang Ruien
Yes, hurting each other
The girls haven't
Yes, I don't even know what you're thinking
Okay, I wrote it down.
Nan Nan guesses.
Nan Nan starts.
Nan Nan guesses fifty-five.
Fifty-five to one hundred.
Sixty-six.
Sixty-six to one hundred.
Seventy-seven.
Seventy-seven to one hundred.
Ninety-nine.
Seventy-seven to ninety-nine.
Ninety-eight.
Seventy-seven to ninety-eight.
Eighty-eight.
Seventy-seven to eighty-eight.
Eighty-seven.
Seventy-seven to eighty-seven.
Eighty-two
Eighty-two to eighty-seven
Eighty-three
Eighty-three to eighty-seven
Back again
Only four, five, and six left
This time we are finally going to turn the tables
Right on the mark, okay?
Handle it yourself
Eighty-six
Hit
Right on the mark, I'm talking about you
I'll tell you what to ask
Then you ask him if it's okay
Alright, you say it
After these three days of interaction
Is there someone of the opposite sex you like on site
Over here, very seriously
Quietly eavesdropping over there
What? After three days of interaction,
is this your ideal type?
Is it Laura who wants to know?
Yes, it's definitely Laura who wants to know.
It's obvious.
On the spot.
Yes.
She didn't specify gender.
So annoying.
Don't give them an excuse.
You thought for so long.
I think with the current understanding,
it might not be enough.
If we look at the current situation,
no.
Got the answer.
No, right?
It hasn't reached your ideal standard yet.
With the current understanding, I think not.
Okay, let's move on.
Alright, stop asking.
Alright.
Actually, I think it's quite normal.
Because even if there is,
it might not be me.
People really need to get along.
What conclusion can you draw in one or two days?
You really need to continue to understand more.
Because of the previous sentence
the situation has become complicated.
Let's analyze the previous statement
that Yuyue said.
Based on the current understanding,
what did he really mean?
He wants to tell Zhou Nan that they are not suitable for each other.
Yes, I feel the same way.
It seems that Yu Yue has feelings for Zhou Nan.
It feels like the two of them
Not that suitable
If there's another chance,
I think he might lean towards Lola.
I think Lola has feelings for Yu Yue.
She has always liked him.
Yu Yue has clearly distanced himself
from his relationship with Zhou Nan.
I think Yu Yue has always been the kind of person
who considers the bigger picture.
He takes care of everyone.
And Lola, a girl by herself,
is still cooking for everyone.
So he goes to help her.
It makes others look like they're leaving her to work alone.
I think he's that kind of person.
Do you think it has to do with
him rejecting Lola before?
I think he feels a bit guilty.
A bit apologetic.
Let's discuss a question.
Is it necessary to feel guilty for rejecting someone?
Is it necessary?
In relationships,
I think as the one who rejects,
you definitely feel
sorry and guilty.
A little bit, yes.
Do you think the rejected person
doesn't really need to
have your sympathy?
That's right, but
The interesting part is here
It's when we know
how to reject others' rejections
there will always be a bit of guilt
we have another insight
when you want to confess
don't be afraid of being rejected
you always feel that if you are rejected
you will lose something
but actually, you gain a bit of credit
so even if they reject you
in their mind
you still leave a good impression
because they are forever stuck at that moment
always thinking you like them
give them a good feeling, right?
expressing affection is beautiful
yes, expressing affection is a very good
contribution to society
yes
of course
then chandlerpan also refuses to admit
his feelings for Yang Mengjing
seem to be
then just go and touch
the head of the person you like
I don't think it's reached the point of rejection.
He didn't admit it.
No announcement. He didn't announce it.
He refused to announce it.
It's not particularly certain.
He might still like her.
But he didn't take this opportunity.
Announce it.
There won't be a big plot twist in the end.
Chandlerpan went to find Lola, right?
Can he?
Look at this idea.
I think there's a pattern here.
It's those who can control the situation
seem quite at ease
What are they actually looking for
I really don't know
Those who are quieter
like Huang Ruien
They, towards people like Huang Ruien
who are relatively underestimated
are relatively underestimated
They know what they want
quite clearly
Anyway, the boss is really into Luo Ying
As soon as he hears Luo Ying
It's too obvious
He immediately asks if Luo Ying is up
Where did Luo Ying go
Then he hears that Luo Ying left with someone
Immediately
I put myself in Luo Ying's shoes
Alright, next up is
our heartfelt moment segment.
The rules this time are as follows:
Everyone in the apartment is required
to post a moment on social media.
The recipient of this moment
is someone you want to express your feelings to today.
It doesn't have to be love.
It's about expressing your feelings to a member of the opposite sex.
After all eight people have posted their moments,
each person has one chance
to check the moment of
the person they like the most.
Next, we will predict
who will check whose moment.
Everyone will decide individually,
then reveal their answers one by one.
Explain who you think
will have a successful emotional connection.
You peeked at my answers.
Your eyes are too big.
You peeked too obviously.
Obviously, right?
I saw it, your big eyes were looking over here.
Let's first listen to Wang Yanlin.
I think Huang Ruien.
He probably wanted to see Luo Ying's.
Wang Nengneng was looking at Yang Mengjing's.
Basically, everyone thinks
Luo Ying and Huang Ruien
and Wang Nengneng and Yang Mengjing
are both mutual.
Zhou Nan looks at Zhou Jinshun
Why does Zhou Nan look at Zhou Jinshun
Because she can clearly feel
that Yu Yue doesn't like her very much
She can give herself a way out
So she looks at Zhou Jinshun
I think although Zhou Nan said
it's not particularly ideal
but I think Zhou Nan still wants to know
what he thinks
She won't give up on him because of one sentence or one day
She won't completely give up on this person
Who will Zhou Jinshun look at?
Luo Ying, right?
I wrote it like that too.
Yes, look.
I said two people would look at Luo Ying.
Yes.
I don't think Zhou Jinshun would.
He wouldn't put himself in a bad situation.
It's already obvious.
Two couples appeared at the scene.
I even checked other people's social media.
Then he should be able to hear that.
Yu Yue already expressed.
Their date wasn't that successful.
So I think Zhou Jinshun would look at Zhou Nan.
I think we should look at Laura.
Because I really can't guess him.
I think you posted it correctly.
Zhou Jinshun and he cooked together.
Most likely, beef rice.
Lola, I think it might be
Yu Yue, right?
Yes, I feel the same way.
I originally thought Yu Yue
wanted to see Lola
but I always felt
he didn't have that kind of feeling for Lola
it was more like friendship
like a feeling of friendship
I eventually let him choose Zhou Nan
I think he just wanted to confirm through his circle of friends
to make sure about this matter
it's really hard to judge now
whether he is acting out of sympathy
or out of a transferred affection
my choice is Yu Yue
will go see Lola
he wants to see
if she received the signals he sent her
I feel that just now Yu Yue
was quite clear about the signals from Zhou Nan
I feel he might
still want to check again
if Lola still likes me now
because she was chosen before
how she feels about it
to see if she changed her mind
Alright, thank you all for your analysis.
Everyone, next up is our
second moment of truth.
Who will predict the most accurately?
Let's find out right away.
Huang Ruien is now
experiencing the feeling of liking someone
and is completely infatuated
Here he comes.
This darn love
Hello
Just sit here, right?
Yes
Yes, just sit here and wait
She sat a little apart
and left an empty seat
not sitting very close to them
Why are you sighing
A bit tired
Hello
It's me
Where should I sit, big brother?
So I can look at four different people of the opposite sex
You can choose one out of four
Huang Ruien, why don't you sit over there
They've saved a spot for you
It's so cold
I'll just cover up a bit
It is a bit cold
Everyone has come down
Yes
It was only cold a couple of days ago
Sorry, am I really the last one
Chuyi (Zhou Nan), did you
write a short essay
or did some evening exercises or something
No
Thank you
Can we go up now
Who goes up to choose first
Whatever
You're closer, you go first
The pressure is overwhelming.
Adding drama for himself
I really want to kick him
Going up to see, right?
Yes, but only he can see it
Others can't see whose it is that he's looking at
After three days of interaction
is there your ideal type here?
I think the current understanding
may not be enough
based on the current situation
no
actually, I think it's quite normal
people really need to get along
what conclusion can be made in one or two days?
we really need to continue to understand more
If he says no,
I think he might be
in the same mindset as me,
which is to be more cautious,
and not so brave.
So I sent this message to him,
and also to myself.
Both of them were sent to Yu Yue.
Who is it?
Lola
Her social media posts actually make me
feel quite sad
and then with what happened today
is there any connection or relation
You really need to be careful with your leg
because it might hit the doorknob
because I wrote it for him
so I want to see if he wrote back to me
She is going to see him, Zhou Nan
Zhou Nan is going to see Yu Yue
Thank you for your hard work.
He said to Laura, "Thank you for your hard work."
The one who cooked.
It's so bittersweet.
But would she think
it was also written for her?
Because it was a tiring day of dating.
I think she can understand it wasn't written for her.
Watch closely
Then it's my turn.
Go for it!
Hurry up, brother, make it quick.
This man is full of mystery.
She said that math needs to be learned well.
It's about Huang Ruien.
I think it was meant for him to hear.
A slightly disappointed expression
You observe their micro-expressions
Next
Lola will definitely look at Yu Yue
Don't click randomly, Lola
Be good, don't reverse it, Lola
Yu Yue's
Thank you for your hard work
Alright
I'm alive again
You're better now
Feeling better
This meaning is clear
I'm sorry
I think that message was meant for me
A little bit of happiness
Just a little bit
I'm quite happy too
Being seen, that's it
Let's go to Disney to watch the fireworks. Come on.
I haven't been to Disney yet.
I'll go with you next time.
Disney
What day are the fireworks?
On the weekend, only on the weekend.
We can go see the fireworks.
Quite happy
It belongs to the two of them
Actually, I can see where he points
I can guess who he's looking at
So smart at this moment
Can't see it
I also wanted to send it to the "Big Bad Wolf"
to say a few words
It's kind of encouragement
and also appreciation
being your true self
He said she has a cool vibe
a girl's coolness
These two pairs
Big brother must have written it very straightforwardly
"Shall We Talk" is the song she released
Such great details!
If she was looking at me
She should understand what I mean, right?
What
They both posted the same thing
Oh my gosh
Actually, I've always been familiar with this song
She knows what I want to say, right?
Next one
Why are you sighing?
What does it mean after watching?
Came over with a small pout.
Hiding the inner joy.
Isn't it?
What should we do, you tell me.
So annoying.
Don't be arrogant, look
Big brother
Just for that smile of yours
I'd be willing to choose wrong
Big brother is getting a bit full of himself
That smile of his
Do you want to switch back?
Did you return it?
Did you return to that?
Don't look.
Don't scare him, okay?
Don't scare him.
Zhou Jinshun understood.
Zhou Jinshun suddenly understood everything.
We can go sing now.
I won't go. You guys have fun.
Go up and take a look.
Do you have an early class tomorrow?
Yes, a morning class.
Good night.
Because I can feel
the person he wants to pay special attention to
I feel that this time
I can learn cooking well from Lola
Who, you?
Everyone should be able to
pick one for Lola
Hello, my name is Lola
Impossible
The two of us
For now, we might still be friends
I think
Whose camera is this?
This is Lili's (Luo Ying's).
You can give her the camera.
And have a chat with her.
Of course.
I feel like I'm not my usual self.
I don't know, maybe it's this house.
It's making my adrenaline levels
a bit different, I think.
This thing of yours,
I searched for it for a long time.
Thank you.
Don't throw it away, put it aside.
Good night.
I have never achieved what I wanted
Tomorrow night
Can I invite you to dinner
But someone has already asked me out
I seem to have disliked expressing myself since I was a child.
I might be the same way with emotions.
Actually, I rarely say "I love you."
Or "I like you."
So annoying.
What should I do?
I don't know either.
When will you send the key to the confessional room?
I might.
I might try to use it.
Using the confessional room can initiate
an opportunity to be alone with this person.
To make up for what he missed.
That date opportunity.
Okay, this Yu Yue
finally chose to see Lola
The professor thinks it's
because of why he ultimately chose
I said whether it's out of sympathy
or genuine affection
he would be interested in seeing her
because over the past day
he has done a lot for her
It's just that he and Lola
Yu Yue and Lola in the future
still have the potential to develop
Yes, because this time they both looked at each other
the signals between them are very clear
I think there might be some
stories between them in the future
But actually today
in the previous scene
one was Zhou Nan
and the other was Zhou Jinshun
they actually encountered a
similar situation
when the person you signal to
does not give you a particularly positive response
or even a rather obvious
negative response
if it were you
would you continue to take the initiative
or would you back off
I think adults generally
would gracefully withdraw
The more mature a person is, I think the more they will
Really?
Not necessarily
No, they won't
Mr. Xue
Are you the type to take the initiative?
If it's good enough, then take the initiative and keep going
Who do you mean by "good enough"?
The other person is good enough
Even if she rejects you many times
Still
No, once or twice
I think it's acceptable
So brave, Mr. Xue
This is a logical reasoning
If it's something good, of course people will compete for it
Do you agree?
I think young people
shouldn't be afraid of rejection
But if they are rejected
they should also understand clearly
what the exact reason is
What reason is there for not liking you?
Then we can only be a bit more dignified.
Would you choose to leave with dignity?
Yes, a bit more dignified.
Can't you hold on a bit longer?
No, if they...
Mr. Xue, they said they don't like you anymore.
Do you still need to sharpen your mind?
Don't be too straightforward.
I think it can be felt
We can both feel it
Should we keep pursuing it, is there still a chance?
I think it can definitely be felt
Tiantian lets out a long sigh
Do you have something to say?
No, actually, for example,
I might have a small experience myself
Maybe it's just that I think
my so-called retreat
hasn't really had any situation
to retreat from
this retreat might cause misunderstandings
you need to think if it's me
who didn't do well enough somewhere
should I also have more courage
to ask or discuss it
anyway, dating is quite complicated
I didn't understand what you were saying.
That's why you're still searching.
She looks at it from both the male and female perspectives.
From the perspectives of both the rejector and the rejected.
Trying to empathize and understand each other.
Isn't it?
Don't reflect on yourself.
You didn't do anything wrong, Tiantian.
It's not your fault that you're single.
It's my fault, I do have issues.
Mr. Xue, whose fault is it?
It's no one's fault.
I think many of us now
The biggest problem is
We don't know what we really want.
We can't find ourselves.
The person who can make our hearts flutter.
That's the biggest problem.
I think once you find it,
You need to create that opportunity for yourself.
Alright, next in this round
I will announce the results of the researchers
our prediction scores, okay?
Wang Yanlin
guessed seven relationship lines correctly
Da Tiantian guessed seven relationship lines correctly
I also got seven
You also got seven
Ziwen, like me, got six relationship lines
Yixin also got seven relationship lines
The professor also got seven relationship lines
Not bad
Next, we will present to this round's
love researchers
engraved love locks. Tiantian's
Thank you
Tiantian's love lock
Here, professor
Thank you
The first love lock
Yixin
Thank you
Alright
Here, Wang Yanlin
Thank you
Alright, now please hang your love locks
on our love sapling
Another one
Now I'm the only one who got "shaved bald"
Right?
Alright, everyone
Next, we will have
the second date after moving in
This time, the date is arranged by the female guests
Arranged by the girls
The way of dating is by fate
We invite four female guests
After returning to the room, each person will draw a picture
symbolizing their idea of
perfect love
The boys, without knowing anything
will make a blind choice
Whichever girl's picture you choose
you will go on a date with her
for the second date
Blind choice
But actually, it is based on
understanding the girl
He can guess
who would draw what kind of picture
I quite like this game rule
The six of us will also draw on the spot
our idea of
the most perfect love
So difficult
What should love look like
Can it even have a form
This is going to reveal my drawing skills.
Really
It's hard
How much time do we have to draw?
Simple drawings
Everyone, don't create any masterpieces
You are also thinking
I drew it too ugly
This is too scary
I don't even want to show it
It's all over
Wang Yanlin, please explain
The perfect love in my mind
There is a small cottage or something
Then the smoke forms clouds
At home, there are two parents
With a child
Pushing a newborn in hand
And holding a dog
There are mountains and water
This is a dog
There is the sun
Yes, a dog
There is the sun, there are children
A beach is enough, right
Comfortable
Teacher Xue, are you playing mahjong?
No, it's all food
Everything on the table is food
There is food and drink, chatting and talking
Then the characters are a family of four
A family of four
We are all responding to the two-child policy
Mine is very similar to Wang Yanlin's
It has the sun and then clouds
The weather is very nice
Why are there two little pigs?
A couple, this is their second child
Why is one red and the other green?
Is it red for boys and green for girls?
Yes
A lightning boy
A lightning girl
And here is their food
There is meat and vegetables
Life is good enough
Pretty good
I want to draw two spoons
Embracing each other
Two people entwined together
That feeling
But I can't draw it
I want to draw two lying together
Two carrots
Spoon
It's your big spoon and small spoon
That nickname
Yes
Yixin
I think it's just
First, the middle was originally a circle.
But it's missing a piece.
I just think that love is never perfect.
And then a circle outside
It's just two people holding hands
Yes, I just think that beautiful love
It definitely requires two people.
Manage together
Then embrace and create
To understand is
So they came holding hands
To make up for this
gap
For this gap
There is no perfect love
Very profound
I also painted love
Yes
There is no one
It's because once I went with Brother Jing
to record a reality show
Many years ago
At that time, one of the observers was Teacher Feng Tang
Then he saw
our interaction
and said that we were like
"Grass grows, warblers fly, mixed flowers bloom on trees"
I remembered this sentence
Later, I checked
Actually, he adapted it from ancient literature
It actually describes a
vibrant spring scene
I really liked this sentence
I think that when two people are together
it should always be vibrant
like the feeling of spring
Understood
Okay, this is just to get things started
Let's take a look at the female guests
and see what their ideal
perfect love looks like, come on
The things I drew are very simple
It's the image of my ideal life
A family of four
And a dog
I just hope
The other person also hopes
To live a simple
But loving life together
Even if it's plain, we won't feel
That life is predictable
I drew a poker card in the top right corner
Who else plays poker besides me
Among the girls
And there's also red wine
So it's pretty obvious
You should be able to guess it's mine
I want to say that in a relationship
you should feel comfortable
both of us should feel at ease
and happily swim in the water
I drew a fish
I suddenly remembered his name is Yuyue
Is this not a good idea?
It's a bit obvious
Yuyue
Oh my
I unconsciously drew the person I like
There is a popular saying now
about mutual effort
This saying really resonates with me
Feelings are not a one-sided matter
The person I like
should also have me in their heart
And in each other's eyes
the other person should shine
Leave the opportunity to fate
because I also need to understand everyone
I drew Disneyland with fireworks
because I have never been to Disneyland
Then on the first day
I talked about this with Wang Nengneng
What I drew definitely represents anticipation
The corresponding person, right
You drew very well
Yes, you drew so well
I'm afraid the guys might guess wrong
There are two who probably won't guess wrong
I think Yu Yue
and Wang Nengneng probably won't guess wrong
It took a long time to draw
It was drawn very carefully
Mickey, roller skates
You guys are so fast
Take a look
I don't understand
I don't understand what this painting means
This is very abstract
This is among the vast sea of people
The feeling of spotting you at a glance
I think that's what it means
Is that what it means?
This playing card
Just likes drinking and traveling
This
It's obvious
But I can't figure out who this is
I can't figure out who it is either
Not sure about the others
But one might be
I'm sure it's "Big Bad Wolf"
I want to mention
Go ahead
I was left out yesterday
Can I choose first?
No problem
Go ahead, choose
I'm aiming for Luo Ying
I think that one is Luo Ying
I'll choose this one
Then I'll take this one
I don't know
They all say it's destined
I hope it will be the person I have in mind
So it's a cliffhanger, right?
We'll find out next episode.
Yes, everyone.
Did it capture your hearts?
Is it
I thought there was already an answer.
Yes
So, this date of destiny
is full of anticipation
We are also looking forward to
seeing new pairings
new choices
and new sparks flying
But we must remind everyone
that as we watch this
these eight guests
have only been in our semi-mature apartment
for just three days
which means that what we see
whether it's the probing
the choices, or the changes
it's all part of the process
everything is just beginning
so let's generously
give them the time and space
to wait for them to
write their own stories
I believe this is also
what makes "Semi-Mature Lovers"
the most exciting
Alright, thank you everyone
We'll leave the suspense for the next episode
See you next time
Bye-bye
This episode is called "Destined Date"
We let the female guests
each draw a picture
and the men choose their dates based on the paintings
to decide who they will date
They also bring flowers
for extra points
I'm not sure who it is either
Since we're here, let's make the best of it
Hello
After today's date
at least in my heart, I feel
we have gotten much closer
This kind of man is good
At our age, we don't act so impulsively
What about love at first sight?
I still hope to get to know different people
Who is it?
Lola
Dressed up meticulously
So beautiful
Because last time she was with Yu Yue
It was mutual
Even the cameraman was moved
His expression
The young girl thinks you're not good enough
I hope it will be the person I have in mind.
But even if it's not, I can accept it.
I am here for Luo Ying.
I have been happy all day today.
I am so sad.
It's just the beginning, don't worry.
Because they haven't confirmed their relationship yet.
You see, relationships are just that difficult.
The past two days were too exciting.
Today is a boring day.